[Applause]
no no no no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
I feel like I'm not no
I feel like today
I will be super frustrated again thank
you for the red super chattel wow
a visitor from a far off land
where
thank you
where is that
I will read that properly during a
proper superchat reading but if you're
only visiting then you might not hear it
when I read it properly
which means you should not be visiting
you should be living here you should be
uh always here
you're from Ohio for sure
is it like from a different different
whole life fandom or like completely
outside of youtubing
now you make me feel me curious
from
Chicago
I mean it's far from me that is far from
me indeed not far from from some of you
especially if you're in Chicago whatever
let me pour some water
oh wait
[Music]
ah you're looking forward to Friday
what did I press
did I press the right oh
you need to Sandy land So within the
tubing fandom that's not that far away
thank you
that makes more sense now to me
[Music]
yes I'm playing Uno I'm playing Uno with
me and Nina on Friday on I think Nina's
Channel
it's like Germany and Austria no I
wouldn't say so no
me now
Vitamin Water
felt like taking in some vitamins today
and it's orange so let's go
Oh I thought it says garlic
[Laughter]
the product was garlic
but it's his organic for organic
unfortunately it's not garlic water
pretty good though
does garlic have vitamins
garlic foam yummy no garlic what
what the hell garlic yum
at first stream I'm catching
[Music]
ever or
in a what what we did watch we actually
watched the tears of the Kingdom
gameplay video yesterday the moment it
went live we watched it during my stream
yeah
[Music]
you
mean
wait
up
Sam you guys all make me question
everything
oh
[Music]
oh my God thank you
garlic does have vitamin C
and on others I can't remember
[Music]
incredible
wow wow wow garlic
amazing garlic good for you Garlic's
good for all of us I would say unless
you're a vampire
vitamin Chihuahua vitamin K
pretty moms just like how it relatively
Horizon free
what what that makes absolutely no sense
motion you are crazy you're out of your
mind
you are out of your minds you're just
stretching everything now for your own
convenience wow good
yeah
OMC is in a lot of different things
well here's you don't have to sign up
you're right here at the source now as I
said so I haven't played in like a
couple days like a week or so right so
this is going to be a [\h__\h] show
hahaha
I have this feeling something's gonna
make me absolutely morb and molds today
as if last time wasn't already enough
okay it says 26 what the [\h__\h]
20 Sports Place completion 26 out of the
the 100 that we're not aiming for right
so in reality we're more like at 50
percent
okay
it works really well by the way I stole
that title idea somebody said Chihuahua
is the chozo and one
okay well let's continue
[Music]
first live stream of yours oh nice to
Lucky since you don't have to work today
oh welcome please enjoy it's gonna be a
long one so you better watch all of it
all of it
[Applause]
make more Caverns look at
look at the orange big suit
it's me this game it's just me where the
[\h__\h] are we how do I play this game
what
no
game was not safe
we're stepping back on that okay first
of all shoot okay wait was that a
missile
this is normal Shield right
[\h__\h] okay I shot a missile and then this
is locked on
foreign
what's is X something is X nothing
why is panic ball mode which will ensue
a lot today I'm sure mold more cabins
yes
this is Jump okay X's jump Shoot
Bubble Ball
where are we where are we going
I guess we're gonna are we gonna go for
the purple door
where are where are we where am I
did I lose progress I better not have
lost any progress
okay uh oh this is also jump oh and yeah
we have double jump now
okay ah
good
okay
oh fire
oh ah [\h__\h]
horrible this is gonna be horrible
I I
where am I where am I where am I
where am I
just blast them away with oh God okay
keep on jumping you know that's good
oh God why doesn't okay there we go
gonna ask why does it take so much Miss
us love [\h__\h]
what what I already don't know what I'm
doing
uh they think they're dead or one more
ah
I I I I don't go oh dead
okay I guess that was warm up
there's an e-tank in this room
can I reach it
[Music]
'd be cool it will come back to you I
hope so I really hope so what is this
elevator oh but there's a tank
[Music]
so that's not really this room though
isn't it like uh I mean how do you get
there for the lava do I get like a an
upgrade for my ball where I can
gopher lava starts at Aya scanning how a
scanning helmet
oh geez North Channel door sealed
great
it's really helpful
this machine is functional but it's not
receiving power do you want Power oh
wait what free
do you want Power free nearby power
conduits must be energized for it to
open less of electrical energy will
energize the conduits condo is ready yet
some heat that is invisible in the
normal Spectrum
you mean I need to look at the Spectrum
what
what am I gonna shoot at
am I gonna shoot at this
or
are these monster sounds
good
because I was like listening trying to
find out where the step sounds are
coming from and
and my hands scared jump scared me
what are these stamp stuff and they're
like up there maybe
[Music]
system next to the doors look with visor
next to the door
through the door door door door I mean
there's a door here
murlocs
is that activated I think it is like
connected to another one
oh wait oh yeah this one's
connected to
both connected Maybe
there's the third one oh there's another
one
[Music]
nice
so they're functional now oh
ah that's what's happening
um
can I zoom out why is it so close you
little [\h__\h] again now we meet again
uh wait wait wait where's the entrance
I hear look I'm too close
oh well
so
uh which one is the one I want to go to
I'm gonna go here first
we will
that was not it
but is it something else that's
interesting I guess just uh this screen
access to each Channel go granted level
11 channel has been cooled oh
he's Channel The Witch door
ice gonna show me
ah okay okay okay first another hotel
[Music]
panic panic panic panic
I don't know uh uh is me on it this way
maybe please wait I don't know where is
this
[Music]
I think I think I got it okay okay uh
what uh
[Music]
okay when I'm coming back that means I
have to go right because first it was
left so now yeah now it's on my right
and so far the Beatles haven't gotten me
okay okay
yay
okay why am I so zoned in guys can I
undo that
was close yeah not at all I feel so
zoomed in maximum energy increased and
the timer is off so it stays like this
the whole time
build a view option
pretty sure it's normal okay
I have to feel so close okay now we go
back up uh this is here
can't catch me I'm pink now
are you winning 10 so I don't know I
just started but I don't feel like I'll
be winning today
I have a bad feeling I don't know
oh so
bye brother
[Music]
hub
hmm
he did it
[\h__\h] dude
yes
really happy for him because yeah he
applied at many jobs I mean
kind of late but he did he did it and
then he had a lot of
um a lot of job interviews yesterday and
the day before yesterday
and there were a couple that he
liked especially
and one of those
did actually reply to him and say you're
in
mom
yay
no longer in need well I mean he's
apparently still he's not starting uh so
soon he's got like another month
before he starts
yeah but it's nice because
um
uh yeah he'll be closer to me
where am I going
should I have no elevator the wrong way
[\h__\h]
is there a safe behind it or what
let me go back in down please
you can use them to build your furniture
and stuff yeah I mean in the future yeah
I might ask him if I need something
um because I feel
like an annoying person
if I always ask
the same friends because I don't have
many friends
I'll I'll
is that where it came from
[\h__\h] I don't want to fight these
bastards again
that's where I came from
okay
confusing I thought I had to go for the
purple door again
ah
wait have you switch oh
I remember she remember I say fun okay
now we go up
I assume is
where I started what
what
eh
oh
[Music]
well saving was fine too
um
[Music]
you don't have to switch beams
does that mean I have to
does that mean I have to fight those
bastards again
all right
I'm out
you can run past them towards where
there's two blue doors
but I feel like the one up high on the
right side I wouldn't know how to reach
right away
the other one made me neither
so I'll I think I might have to fight
them again
Myself by accident
don't jump into the lava
I have dark beans I forgot about those
[Music]
so much fun don't jump into the lava at
least I didn't become Panic ball
okay did they maybe drop some
missiles for me no nothing
well useless okay
no time to see the lava I try
I
I would [\h__\h]
I should be able to jump up there and I
think that's you know how to get up
there to the blue door
uh platforming
[Music]
guys
what easy
what's with this can I make this
no
don't think I can go here now
um
unstables blocking path maybe with the
big big boom
the big the Ultra Mega super ultra boom
what was it like charging and then
firing a missile
can't break it yet okay does not waste
the last missile I have
I'll get something later to blow it up
okay well the other Blue Door
[Music]
oh my gosh
please do not spawn the others
up here
now okay
oh my God what the [\h__\h]
what is that
[Music]
can I find it
is that something to find or I just make
it turn around so I can jump on it
no no no no oh I got one I got one
I got poop hey okay
missiles
I hate those the bottom the ground ones
I hate those two I always step on them
oh there's more of this one
I think it needs to charge no now it
doesn't want to turn around at all
I thought that's what you do
this room
very tall room
with a white door and the blue door
and some platforms up there
hold on I need to be closer
whoa
how long do they stay like that
oh
nice too
I'm just gonna go to the next room
already
white means ice cream ah which I don't
have yet
that was pretty clutch really we made my
jump yeah I jumped pretty early
I mean come here
okay wait how do I get over there
[Music]
I guess I have to scan
uh this hanging rockstarship appears to
have a weak spot near its face some
stalactites can be dislodged from
ceilings along uh-huh
I think I understand
no
I did not understand
uh missile
oh people people Oh I thought I had to
look at the
the heaty part
for the hity mask
visor
[Music]
so far we're making
progress but we just started
grapple hook later
oh [\h__\h]
oh it's not a normal I thought I wasted
the missile again
do they come over here from this
distance
no
I wish I did wait please come over here
please come over here
what about you
I'm so far
[Music]
Nani
Auntie chamber climate and normally
detected
I don't really know what that means to
me
but wait there's another one of those
wait quick quick ah now it's gone [\h__\h]
[Music]
shoot the lava dragon yes nice too
if you drop something no really oh wait
there's something there again ah from
the dragons
down it doesn't only work with the other
guns
wait
[Music]
hi
hi both work await
huh
I'm good was that an intended way of
doing it I mean we're about falling down
I suppose
still manageable Panic did I come from
there yeah
okay please stop
ah maybe ball
hi
it was controlled Panic yeah an
improvement
goodbye why why why I miss
what the [\h__\h] what
does my charge be not hit
that's weird
why don't we like
trying to find right now anyway
where are we going yeah bye
[Music]
powerbeat doesn't hit as well as a way
these lab worms are really reminiscent
of spiral
um
T chamber yeah I know I know
what is this
ah wait how do I do this
um I remember
oh boy deny wouldn't I
how
oh oh
where should I
should I drop myself somewhere or just
go and tell them
whoa
did I go in the circle
[Music]
did I go in a circle
no no I just went for the room right
yeah
why waste
elevator broom but is there
and look at those girls
been here before
I can go up here okay
[Music]
I'm going to the toes over
foreign
okay
oh oh
music
what
elevator is Spanish for the evader don't
you mean it's the other way around
elevator is English
come on
come on elevator
and what does evader mean what
what
is it a joke
I can't see
I haven't been here before
once again backtracking I guess
I can't see ya
[Music]
my game's so dark shouldn't that make my
monitor brighter
uh
that one there's a red door too
what
someone who Evans
okay
uh oh
give me
which visors
I don't wanna hate this visor
ah it doesn't make it better anyway
it doesn't make it better
thank you remember
[Music]
yeah it makes it worse
so you guys not telling me I assume I
have to go to the red door but I don't
know how to reach it
but I've been here before you
going
where is Dad's chamber
no way I have to go through here again
right I don't
I hate backtracking
I really do
foreign
okay now we have four doors to choose
from
I mean do we have to go to the elevator
to the elevator
I know I know that's how Metro games I
am I don't like it though
[Music]
foreign
no that's where I am
I going
where am I going
here
oh that's where I am
I'm still gonna get it white
well I mean that's all the way over
there I don't see how
that really helps me I'm guessing
elevator
Michael
I don't know
yeah the map is hard to read
not the one guy
what's that white yellow what
there's no white door
the elevator I'm sure
wait elevator elevator
to my left
is that not where it came from no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
it can't be
I love right now or recharge your chip
nothing good
[Music]
to choose a runes I have no idea
are
no but now I'm here
do you think I remember where that is
do not I don't remember anything I have
short time memory or I have no memory at
all actually I don't remember things
that have happened recently and I don't
remember things that have happened a
long time ago
I don't know remember things that
happened a decent time ago either
I don't remember anything
I wish I had better memory
I don't want to use my myself for that
oh
I got it finally
mosquitoes are back oh no those are not
the mosquitoes that I was talking about
last time what
keep up
who will win
a overpowered bird in a summer suit or a
little beetle
maybe the Beatles but I feel like it's
weak point would be the back
uh yeah is this not something where I
have to like get around it
[Music]
seems equal it's not equal stop why is
it so good at turning itself towards me
no okay this is not it
I'm ball
yeah what you don't have to fight it but
I wanna
look at that finally I get behind it how
did I do that
come here nope
did it recharge when it went on the
ground under the ground
oh this one's really smart though like
it moves so quickly
Make It Count Make It Count Make It
Count
well this is stupid when I was on fire
hey Beetlejuice Beetlejuice Beetlejuice
I finally did it
[Laughter]
okay oh hi where to next oh the white
worms Maybe
that we haven't visited yet maybe now
they're accessible
possibly this one
I think I'll I would perf I would
probably go through that one first the
last one
that was the beetle
an actual start what do you mean start
like a star in the sky did someone name
a star in the sky Beetle just because
honestly there's so many stars in the
sky that you could probably name them
anything or you mean like a star like a
celebrity called Beetlejuice
[Music]
yes
wait
you mean yes two there's a star in the
sky
missile on the half pipe half pipe
oh okay
it's a red giant star why did they call
it Beetlejuice
yeah I didn't see blind Walmart
okay uh
how do we how do we do the charging
thing again
I'm not like that
[Music]
and I just
but I'm not uh
okay does it charge my missiles though
is it
I'm not sure I'm 28 now
okay
uh what I was going to go
this way so this is behind me
okay
it gives me five Ah that's very nice of
them
owl
you juicy
why don't they like is that just how
they are they walk a little bit in a
group and then they just stand there
so weird what a weird enemy
yeah
oh so there was a purple door here
it's just some enemies
it was a purple door here apparently I
was here before uh-huh I assume
I assume
I assume this is it
this is how I get there
off oh this is not how I get there all
right
it's still pretty far
double jump
do a flip
there's something here
oh
I mean
does that activate anything wait this
wait isn't that a foreign
okay
yeah easy easy
I don't know why but when I panic let's
do it my my thumb just goes to why
no why
a ball
that I know I see the trash clearly well
it's obviously there
do I just make it wait scan
and thank you multiple blah blue
[Music]
blah blah blah
it looks like I can make it explode
do I waste a missile on this become Bell
s
here afraid to take as well oh more
missiles more missiles I was hoping for
the track though oh it's not here
okay
track was up on the other side oh really
yeah
you know
[\h__\h] what am I doing I don't know how to
do this I keep on forgetting
I need a call ah here
oh
this is crazy it makes me feel dizzy
hi progress babies
all right
not me
Korea
what is this room this is just very sass
like if I take one or two more steps
enemies are gonna show up and I'm gonna
panic
Bring It On
they're not bringing it on
sus
this room is safe
how can it be safe
what's that ah little bug
I'm putting panic
okay
I feel like they're immune
middle
ah blancho but it's not too high
it looks too high
no wrong visor uh
[Music]
Oculus oh is that where Oculus Rift got
its name from did they take it from this
thing
the Oculus exposed a single eye when
active
the electrical field that covers it is
enough to deter most Predators if the
I guess it's his own word huh uh if the
Oculus attacks anything capable of
presenting a real threat it retracts
into its per impermeable shell
oh
it doesn't really give a [\h__\h] about me
I bought a ball honey
I was wondering about those they look so
cracky
[Music]
that stress really blah blah
oh there's another there's more up there
hmm
wait
no
um
do I break them
oh
free missiles
but it's still
now it's done what did that do
maybe if I break all of them the whole
structure will be too weak
and then fall apart yeah
um
will not be able to support it anymore
look well even the cutscene for that
yeah and it will all just go back down
by one yeah yeah because it was
a little bit too high up
oh and now there's more
whoa
what the [\h__\h]
yeah
what
why did they not take my normal hits did
I really need to use missiles for them
[Music]
what is this place oh for later maybe
that looks like too much too high
well
and never completely different area down
there all right
wait
scan skin
that looks just like a virus
play the purple mutated puff over from
first epidermis
and class of weapons can still do the
job however the gas within the
concussive weapons
it's my normal weapons
didn't feel like it was doing the trick
s it has to be okay they're really
making me use all my missiles here
[Music]
oh
yeah okay you need to come here
with many weapons with many missiles
there's more and more coming
can you guys like not
are they gonna endlessly spawn
yes this
is uh
I went
I jumped out of panic because it was so
stinky and like draining my my health
oh should I just
jump up
little bastards
uh so middle and then up there okay but
I'll get rid of like oh
[Music]
okay
oh I'll think about this one later
good you gem that was more dangerous
than standing in love with somebody yeah
it drains HP like really fast what about
these little fast turkeys
foreign
[Music]
what do you want
I don't know is that what it wants he's
invincible
shoot where he isn't okay
tricky
right
[Music]
okay okay
breaking
thank you
thank you one again no what was that
no stinky ones this time
but more of these oh oh this is a really
interesting
power
seeing you're doing well nah
doing normal but thank you
I should Miss no
no I came in with a lot of missiles
though
y'all babe if they don't give me
something to charge my missile soon
I have to make everyone count
uh yeah but I'm gonna be lacking exactly
one
no I did them all I did them all
right
party time
so close
a new me fresh out of the oven weight
Buster what
that's so unlike me I'm the one who
creates the waves at the concert venues
mmm
what do you mean first try
why wouldn't it be first try it wasn't
even a boss monster involved
I have this powerful attack uses
missiles while active
using the wave beam press and hold that
are a to charge
then press R to fire
and then iPhone could it uses missiles
because I didn't have to go back for my
missiles more missiles yeah I only went
back because I was being stinky bombed
[Music]
a super missile okay so normally I
wouldn't be using this right only for
like maybe some special things to
destroy
wait where where what how oh I found it
I thought it was gonna get its own
little thing on the bottom right
you guys will have to tell me again how
to activate that because I don't
remember
okay
[Music]
should I try to go to this
place oh yeah because down there wasn't
there something to blow up
no I didn't miss it yet
no ah
is it the one on the water
no
that's just a normal purple door though
okay
this one I really can't get yet okay I
need a gravity suit
[Music]
okay then we go back and we'll go to the
other
let's realize this kind of has hands
or like a little burp burp feed
is holding it
you need an upgrade up to upgrade I'm
too heavy okay okay
[\h__\h] why did I use a missile again
I don't understand which one is the wave
theme what
oh no
no not this time no no no
all the locks on
[Music]
them we'll just test it out whenever it
happens whenever I need it
when I'm holding now oh okay
no
maybe I should
have
why are you all gotta be like that
[Music]
where is that one
it's hard to speak ah whatever
oh hey missiles
okay
so we got charged back up a little bit
okay now
hi
now the other room
well let me just
think how to get there
there is
something there
oh a little small
let's see
a little small little tract
or pulling through here go for safe safe
oh okay okay yo yo yo I can try
where am I there
save this
a little bit far but okay
should be this way
your little suckers again you know when
I saw someone sent it to me thank you
for letting me know
Lord of the Rings Musical
is happening this summer in the UK it's
not in London though
oh
it's kind of
that makes it kind of difficult
out
nice
nice yeah they're like licensed so
cool and and and yeah
you're gonna use the Lord of the Rings
characters
and I don't know I just thought okay I
want to go there so you know Iron tea
has been saying that she wants to meet
me right like she researched me
and I mean I still want to go to the
beach vacation with her a little small
one but she also you know she loves Lord
of the Rings more than me probably
because she can say
say the lines
by heart she knows them by heart
so but she will not know the lines of
the Musical Boy heart probably I'm I'm
guessing they come up with their own can
I reach that
guessing they come up with their own
stuff
at least partially
I wonder
okay why did I never notice that
and she speaks Elvis so she doesn't
speak English
for real for real
but
I felt like I wanted to go so we
immediately books
trip flights flights are booked really
expensive though what the hell more
expensive than usual
uh I didn't buy this one
I'll tell you about this one
break bottom
how do I have to go out
ah I guess I can
what am I doing
okay
okay and now we have to go back
yeah flight tickets booked and uh
tickets for the musical also already
booked it's done in London but you gotta
like take a train
and the bus and stuff was like
I forgot what it's called
what near to London
um
that'll be the first time that I ever
travel outside London in the UK but also
I just have never
I only been to London once and I've
never been like anywhere else
in the UK before so exciting but I think
like
um it'll be a little bit of a waste to
just be there for one day
so rmt and me we're gonna check out
a little bit more after that
because
last time we were also together in
London that the one time I've been there
before was with her and it was ice cold
because it was in the winter
um
it was ice cold so this time I wanna
um maybe enjoy it in the summer because
it's in the summer
and the place where they do the musical
it's not like a typical you know theater
Hall whatever no no it's like it's like
really nice like a A fitting venue I
would say maybe look it up then you'll
know is it telling me again to go to the
anti-chamber thank you I'm trying to
find a safe Point
wait I already saved didn't I whoopsie
foreign
okay anyway I saved a second time
watermel theater yeah
that's right what a Mill theater hey do
they all just fall down once you hit one
of them is that how they work
why are they so annoying
also now they only dropped one Health
thingy what the hell
what they're like lice is disgusting
make sure you get some fish and chips
whilst you're here hey I've had fish and
chips before in that one trip that ice
cold trip and it was it was all all
right it was like way too big the
portion was way too big
I want to try it again though
maybe at a better place I felt like that
was not not as good as it gets
next what
foreign
are we going here
game wants me to go elsewhere but
but I also want to see if I can reach
this place
anyway that means
oh I went a different way
I went a different way
I can't go there yet okay but then how
do I go are they
well how about what
what I'm so confused
I'm so confused
there were upgrades in the room you can
get
where's the Anderson but that's what I'm
thinking this whole time like I don't
know how to get there see it's already
frustrating me
that's not the anti-chamber it says no
it was kind of like alone
anyway how the [\h__\h] did I get back to
where I came from
I came from there but I feel like
oh
sorry guys sorry guys
I'm so sorry
you wow I'm really confused
oh God just go through it
[\h__\h]
a book
ew ew ew ew
ew
but a good source of HP and stuff
okay I'm here
oh there's two
there's friends all right these are the
normal ones
let's go
hmm
so we don't have to go to that blue room
yet so maybe
maybe I have to go there at some point
and then I'll just keep it for that
moment because you know you guys don't
seem to be
saying that I really have to go there
yeah this one I look stupid don't they
this is the beehive
oh it's right in my face
and there's more okay no [\h__\h] them I
don't wanna
breaking my my focus
wait is this
[Music]
they really do break my focus
please stop please please just stop okay
the big tree is hiding a missile you
mean the one that I've also noticed
I don't know
[Music]
um
there's too many ways please tell me
I'll keep the map like this
oh wait it's like like something which
which way
where the bees were
where is that
this one
off the left this one uh
yeah yeah
left twice so here and then and then
here
[Music]
isn't here
more left
okay like all the way here
oh wait there's a stick there's a
there's a question mark here
go all the way left
ah wait uh and then in the furnace room
furnace room okay furnace room
I wish I could make a mark on the map
keep on going
how do I go there
ah wait is it this one
okay uh yeah okay
uh ball
no yes
oh more more more more
this is like the most unnecessary mob in
the game I must say
they're way too easy to kill they're
kind of so unnecessary because they load
up bat as much health as they take
they're so unnecessary oh they are
literally for refilling okay okay well
then
I will say nothing no more
I left again I suppose okay
here
oh
missile power-up missile in that room
where I just came from
for real for real
do I really need all the missile
upgrades so like I feel like I got
plenty maybe don't maybe not
in the fountain
I jump in when it's
not fountaining
what
ah maybe as ball it can throw me up
there
all right
I'm coming to get my missiles
[Music]
if you use the wave Buster you'll be
yeah Okay I uh because I was thinking
doesn't that like use up all your
freaking missiles
I mean it totally does
okay
I do not have plenty what
I feel like I have plenty
uh
oh I would have been really close to the
other room too oh well another time
where am I looking at
okay
uh basically
straight ahead
at least all these rooms are easy to
pass
nice for ones
I know a safe room here maybe I are safe
here too
we don't want any more disasters like
last time where I could really really
angry
do we do we
good idea hmm
always take the safe I have learned from
my mistakes
you know I woke up today with um
some happy messages some happy
invitations
some happy messages from jenma
um
it's quite nice quite a difference quite
a contrast to waking up to
negative messages I like it
please keep them coming
[Music]
am I going the right way
yeah we're going the wrong way
fascinating
what am I
oh yes okay back
I'm going towards the missile don't I
already have it though
is there another missile I don't have in
here yet
I feel like I possibly have gotten this
one already
[Music]
there's two destroy wall in the middle
we're in the middle
stand
[Music]
would be nice
I have another Korean lesson tomorrow
ah this one maybe
and good news no no not related to my
birthday
no no no no no
how's it going the last it's pretty good
so far as I feel very confident in my
reading so I feel like next step is I'm
gonna start learning some words words
and how to build sentences
got your homework done there was no
homework except like practicing a little
bit and no I did not do that yet I mean
um something in streams you know like I
guess that's kind of like practicing so
is it here or what
foreign
[Music]
it's really annoying
you barely got time
oh this is the truth I can't break this
one I don't know
I don't know which role I have to bring
it's just the shoulder inscription I
don't have to break that one the one
tries to kill
uh-huh
yeah okay but all that information
doesn't help me because I was I was
asking about which one to break
a wall in the living room
middle I don't understand I don't
understand none of this is
that because you know
there's many rooms there's these places
are big I don't understand if you say
middle then I don't know what middle
means
that alone does not convey
yeah break that one points exactly
I do not understand though
yeah yeah when was I going
and we don't think it was going this way
so
oh it's right there Chihuahua it's right
there it's above you
wait which one's from this one
why does it always turn itself around
again every time just stay where you are
for [\h__\h] sake
okay that one up there
to go there
oh
remember kiwawa the platforming here
okay
don't need a little [\h__\h]
eh
yeah I never understood until this point
that you can kill them completely ah
[\h__\h] hell
I don't like how it looks like that yeah
you have to use like both control sticks
which is in theory that is fine
but
[Music]
no no this is like not even close to the
molding levels of last time yet
not even close
I can just probably jump directly
I'm gonna break this game now
[\h__\h]
ah
and now ah this way
don't fall down anymore kiwawa please oh
[Music]
right
that's why right
Yahoo
thank you
I got it I got it I can't even shoot
this weapon that fast
it's literally impossible
okay fully charged here we go
[\h__\h] you
wait
the other videos faster I don't know but
I don't want to keep on Switching in
between
wow
for the first time she did see
Unthinkable the incredible the
absolutely convenient thing to do
can you believe that she did it
she learned
furnace room it's right there
over there
hello Bounty Hunter hello I still don't
really think or feel like a bounty
hunter though
it doesn't feel like I'm doing much
bounty hunting
the only feel the thing I've I feel like
I'm hunting is booties
all righty what is this trap for
none
is there something to get you
what
oh
is this the pap I have to take anyway
ah I'm in the furnace and there's a
white door
this is the white door for the the new
beam I have
to be
what are these little [\h__\h] doing here
how do I find these again
but I have to go here does that mean
there's an ice ice cream in this room
there must be
a nice beam
there's another path oh it's the mate
it's long time baby
so what is this otherworldly pestilence
that infests the land seeking out life
when it's blind need for corruption and
where did the meteor that brought it
originate was it crafted by alien hands
or is it a roving chunk of a planet that
suffered a violent end our minds quail
in horror at the thought that long ago
in some corner of the universe as yet
unseen by our eyes an entire planet was
perhaps once coated with this great
poison whatever cataclysm may have
ruptured that doomed Place must have
been mighty indeed and if other meteors
from its spread through space bearing
this evil to the Far Corners of the
universe we hold fast to the hope that
this is not so that the only surviving
remnants of this evil are here on Talon
4 then at least there is hope for
eradication
foreshadowing
is it
wait so when you guys say there's
another path you mean within this room
or within the room that I just came from
where I was balling through
this one
oh yeah
let's see I mean there's many tracks
there's something up there
[Music]
understand it
I was in front of it
[Music]
but this is where I would where I bald
out of right
right why is it not
thank you
no that's the path oh
she ain't falling oh
where am I now
[Music]
oh that little room
s
oh lots of lore
[Music]
that's not the proper lyrics
please don't get the wrong idea
who is there three different pieces of
lore here
let's read
to the interested one you mean me if you
read his words then Our Hope has not
been in vain your path is fried with
danger monstrosity is beyond the
description lurk in the shadows starving
hunting for prey searching for ways to
quench the poisonous urges that bloom in
their brains some of these are shrewd
but they are blinded by their evil
designs believing in the black thanks
for Super Chat
oh
and probably stick to harness it for
their own ends it is these last that are
the greatest danger when you read the
universe of these creatures you will be
doing true and trusted one
no no if our Temple the cradle will
prove powerful enough to contain this
evil forever for now it wraps around the
abdominal Abomination cutting it off
from the world above however we believe
the power of Cipher which has been
produced by linking the 12 artifacts
should be strong enough the fate of this
world is now left to the one who will
collect all the artifacts in the future
time when the entrusted one knows is
approaching
no no what
many shows are gifted with a distant
sight and even more begin to learn it as
our harmonization with the universe
becomes more and more complete WE peer
forward
I read nipples
seeing Prophecy in the ripples of water
hearing rumors of coming days on the
breath of the wind though we celebrate
the distant sight many of these Visions
are dark the voice of the prophecies and
the most common tales of the coming of
the worm born from parasites nurtured in
a poisoned womb the worm grows devouring
from within until the world begins to
rot not all prophecies come to pass of
course but we cannot help but fear the
Stark important
oopsie
there's a missile up there
[Music]
but I want to see can I go here
Miss outdoor
finally a new room
thanks guys I really don't need to load
up though because I'm yeah and that's
why they uh sometimes spawn more of the
health balls and sometimes less now it's
not spawning anything because I'm doing
pretty fine for myself
is that why or does it not is it
actually not connected and I was just
completely unlucky just now no no it is
for that
I was wondering why sometimes they spawn
more HP and sometimes less
yeah what do you mean my obsession with
nipples must be stuck I don't have an
obsession with nipples and even if I had
one then why would we stop it and also
what the [\h__\h]
I'm gonna Panic I'm gonna Panic what
what
what what
what's that
okay switch to powerbeam what's the
power beam is this the power beam
no no I don't really care about that
scan that one
tells them goes
the other one okay
try not to die since it's been a while
since your last name
[Music]
statue of a chosen Elder according to
his chosen Lord these statues served as
the watchful guardians of tomes and
shrines
my stretch hands are empty as if
awaiting and offering may I offer myself
and this is trying times
just don't die
I have a lot of e-tanks you'll be fine
if
check out check the new weapons
do I have to use chargeable busy okay
okay
don't go
we're at it I don't see them where are
they why am I finding
okay I'm good I'm gonna go this is Jesus
it's gonna be easy
where is it
what's hiding just hiding
I keeps on trying to track something and
I keep on interrupting it
dead
more
that's it
that's it I should have scanned it well
it died too fast it's not my fault
this is
way better than I did yeah
yeah
it didn't even get to attack me
is 69 HP nice
oh
I remember to bring more there will be
more
uh-huh
well his pants are glowing Now give me
that
hear me
give me this
I think combo
don't don't crush me like an apple or
don't rip me apart like an apple
what
I didn't expect
okay okay
one more please
how cute how it holds me
big burp holds
holds ball ball
right here we go
yay
ah
okay
what does that do
brakes one two three
uh-huh uh-huh
those are holding my room
service is quite common early
game of bowling so there's like three
colors there now
one's purple
one's red one's white
see
I can't open these doors yet but I can
open
the one up there apparently what is this
safety Shield online Windows secure
[Music]
scan them
ah erratic energy wavelength uh-huh
uh energy signal that appears to be
affected by the pot yeah
Heat
well I know I have the the purple one
is the red one
um my normal my basic one is I doubt it
I doubt it
I just did I just see
it's a hole here
point
that means if you knew this you could
save here wait
no wait it's not it's not a safe point
it's a missile replenisher oh
that was a safe point right at the bus
that would have been a typical
uncharacteristic of this
sassy game
okay but now what now what
I meant like try to jump up there
[Music]
could be manageable oh yeah oh
shoot the purple ah okay okay
I thought I had to become I had to
become ball
okay I shot it
[Music]
effect
you have to do this again
ah
there's Lord behind him ah this is on
purpose I fell down on purpose to read
this
things bound to Earthly shapes are
temporal and frail existing in a single
Dimension they are fragile vulnerable
and ultimately mortal however not all
things obey this law shapeless they wait
beyond the realm of perception emerging
only when one arrives who can feel their
presence
such as the will of the chosen our will
to defeat the evil seeping into this
planet remains we desire only to see the
darkness meet Ascend the will of the
chosen has no mind or reasoning of its
own though this will be the address and
trusted one's trial
brain empty moment kiwawa
girlfriend jump in football okay okay
it's not not purple anymore though but
okay
I understand
people beep
oh it turned the other ones off
oh
A New Path is open yeah thank you I saw
that I mean I'm I'm very stupid but I am
not that stupid
not quite
do I have to fall into that cute one
oh will she shoot me into that again
no
do I have to press L again
phew
oh
now it turns back
different kind of smart thank you
hi hi hi
yeah
yeah we are at the new door
yay oh
what is that
what is this ramen's book
spooky
training shot off is holding maintaining
the water level of reflecting pool at 95
percent
strain it
drain it down
scary
turn back trust us
turn back
I need a large straw
I have to do it myself I have to drink
it
I got one guy
said that who said that
who was that little [\h__\h] that said that
no I can't find it anymore ah Naveen
Naveed why are you one guying me
why would you do that
scare me I don't want to go on the water
start
oh
could I
named
there is a
a cable
oh there's something here
thank you oh my smart face
activate I don't know do something
ball
oh
fishies did not like that
oh no
I hope the fishes went to a better place
oh wait this is a huge pipe now is it
I think someone else
ah
ew [\h__\h] you why would you do that
I thought they were not alive
they're trying again
do they want me
to explode inside
or or should I try to avoid them
[Music]
try to avoid them
ah okay well
it's good to get them out of the way
once
now that we have some space here
left to right
and left can we get much higher yeah
thank you for the super Shadows
where am I
ah perfect Blue Door
save point
that's a safe point
I did get much higher but not much
higher a little bit higher
[Music]
there's another ball thingy oh what is
that
just decoration
I like being a ball because when I'm a
ball I'm small
and I'm round
what is this room
oh it's an elevator
very cautious now always I'm very
suspicious like stuff is gonna attack me
immediately
check the other rooms first
um
oh wait but like why would the game let
you go there without the item that you
need
oh there's another one there
oh wait
it's not how you do the thing
I'm getting the feeling for it now
though don't worry don't worry
for real it was right there why does it
let me go somewhere else first just
missing it
[Music]
baby
oh
can I freeze things with that
Oh we must test it but way before that
no I wanna go there
your little [\h__\h]
okay
didn't even get caught
and it's another elevated room
now I found two elevator rooms well
which ones go first
ice cream does a lot of damage and if
something gets frozen solid typically
for a charge shot it can be shattered
with a missile oh thank you
two paths but one Chihuahua
pick one evil one okay
he's stepping through the Hologram ah
South
the southern lands I want a chocolate I
want to eat the chocolate
foreign
[Music]
new place
no
it's so far
music was kind of late but new music is
here
oh
I didn't even charge that one though
okay
[\h__\h] up again
nice has high damage for slow fire Rage
when
oh yeah yeah it's pretty slow
um
but it freezes a lot of things so that's
cool
all right
let's go first
oh there's nothing here
oh there's a track oh this one looks fun
let's do it
please please let me hop on
okay ah [\h__\h]
there we go
it's like twisted like a cracker
and now
let me fall
[Music]
I'm like a pretzel twist me like a
pretzel baby
so I've heard Little Caesars corn cob
Pizza is not real but now I've heard
they have a pretzel crust pizza
and I was really curious about that I
wish we had Little Caesars here even
though you guys told me it's not that
good but they make they make interesting
things
um
not that bad actually
I've been told that it makes you like
salty
but I showed it to my brother and I said
isn't this amazing because
pretzel
you know pretzel is kind of our thing
Austria and Germany is kind of our thing
severe water situation
ah
don't know what to do with this
it's mid but it's not completely bad
you can't tell me what the tier list is
can I break this wave beam
all right I guess it's time to test test
that out
do I have to do the big thing
oh that um okay okay
um
hmm
it doesn't go anywhere
it's a really good chocolate
it's so good
head back to show the wrong way I need
to go to ice place
Jojo
what
I am Jojo
I mean I should take the other elevator
Maybe
or what
we'll just go here
okay
well speaking of pizzas
so
you remember do you remember my pizza my
mid-life crisis Pizza friend
he's an old
friend no known him for a while now
uh for like
anime convention stuff
and yeah he started like getting really
into pizza or like last year maybe
and
has served our friend Circle Pizza
already
several times and yo I have to say like
for real it seems like it's art the
pizza making pizza making seems like
it's art
wait this way right
because like really
important which ingredients you use and
depending on the combinations of these
ingredients and you have to get like
everything perfect and then then you
will be able to eventually reach the
Perfection of pizza
and he's kind of got it all figured out
now
um
[Music]
so
he found the tweets that I made about
the pizza the corn cob Pizza I know he
found the Twitter list that made about
buying a pizza oven he was like hey yo
and I'm like yeah I was actually
thinking about asking you for like
advice anyway like how to
how to make
the pizza I mean I don't
I don't need it to be like perfect you
know
that's not my expectations I just wanted
to make a joke Pizza
but then he offered his help said he
would help me make the dough and we make
a test pizza with this pizza oven
because it will be the first time I'll
be using it
and because he offered his help I was
like all right all right all right
all right now I'm kind of like really
into it because then I thought like oh I
want to put this on the pizza and then
and this I'll make my dream Pizza yeah
yeah that would be great
and by the way for the for the
parasocial ones Among Us AKA also me so
you know it's it's we're the same
uh he's got a girlfriend you know so for
a long time so they're happy okay it's
just about making pizza okay it's just
my friend's Circle okay Mamma Mia
why am I just walking through this was
there another way can you kill these oh
oh yeah all right they just go away when
you scare them
some
some male people like oh my God
boyfriend no not my boyfriend someone
else's boyfriend but um I told you guys
many times as you know I am always the
Third Wheel always
while I always fart Wheels
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
fun easy kill
it's a pizza oven single
yes it will be a singular pizza oven I'm
not getting two
cool place interesting place
is this
what there's a white door down there
okay
[Music]
yeah so he's gonna bring his own flower
I already bought like flour additionally
to it that sounded good in terms of
reviews but apparently like
this guy oh he
what's oh oh they're like oh
they're like half dead already
he went to like the best pizza place
in town apparently and found out what a
flower they use
and then it's kind of like an industrial
like one that you don't get that easy
apparently
oh he's got like the secret the secret
Pizza flower
will be it would be so good
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
why did they go up there
they ran away from me
you're busy where are they going
what
was that like a programming mistake
because
normally what what
I scared them
I'm not that scary
what is that
[Music]
anyway so yeah it will be really good
ingredients but my plan is since I'll be
eating it alone
um because like he'll be there to like
prepare it
only the doll like I'll shape it myself
and I'll decorate it myself
so you know we'll have fun with it but
I'm wondering maybe I'll make two pizzas
because I don't have to eat it right
away last time when I had a pizza
um don't go this way wrong way
last time when I had a pizza
um like that from like a pizza oven like
a good one
from the pizza party that we had in our
friend circle before
um it was still very good on the next
day so I think I'll just make two pizzas
so I'll make them half half though
um
I do I'll do
where do I go
if I if I wasn't supposed to go there
where do I go on it was I here before
was I even here before where am I what I
wasn't here before where am I I'm
confused what the [\h__\h] where's this
place
who am I
what
don't go down
you can have explorers but it's better
later okay do I go back into the big
area
there's uh I guess there's like a I
can't turn this
let go
[Music]
oh technically I was here before
back to big one back two okay
uh how
back up here
[Music]
no I wrote it on Twitter my plan is
my plan is
and so one half
with tuna and corn
yeah and you know the only ones I said
this on Twitter but the only ones were
always like rid of that by me mentioning
a tuna Pizza are literally only
Americans like it's normal it's even
normal and all missiles
don't go don't go in the water right
even though I'm in the water
I'm in the water maybe it's okay maybe
it meant a different water but it's
normal it's even normal in Italy and
yeah tuna on Pizza is really good I can
really recommend it and normally what I
see is like tuna with onions
which is really good but I also like to
combine tuna with maybe onions yes but
also with corn additionally corn really
good I recommend it fits it matches it
works
that one is fun okay
I want to go to the missile I know I'm
confused
can I go back up
it's a one half of tuna and I'll make
one half
I'll make one half I found a special
spot one half with uh
[Music]
also genius I know you guys some of you
are gonna be like what the [\h__\h] but I
say this is good trust me trust me
I will not take any of the pineapple
slander from the pineapple haters
foreign
[Music]
pineapple and then okay so that will be
one pizza
get the best of both worlds and then I
make another Pizza which I will make
with I got this idea suddenly because I
haven't had this pizza in a while
chicken barbecue with corn because
actually if you Google chicken barbecue
Pizza I don't know but when I Googled it
I got many samples that also had it with
corn I've had it before
it fits well too
yeah
that way we have some more interesting
ones there too and then the other one oh
yeah for the pineapple one I'm thinking
to add either ham or bacon as well like
little little drips not like all over
and then the fourth one was gonna be
salami in cold which I think fits really
well too and in theory if you wanted to
go crazy I guess you could do salami
with a pepper pepperoni not the
pepperoni no the Peppa pepperoni what do
you call them in English
but I think I'll just keep it with
salami and and corn kind of simple
the pepperoni no not bell peppers
um not bell peppers it's just pepperoni
pepperonis right what why didn't um
pepperoni become another word for salami
when Babylon needs for me something
completely different
no I will not be blending it
no I will not put a lot of work into
this pizza then just blend it
oh perfect except for the corn well
that's a problem because this will be
all about corn you know that
Okay so
this is something to read
ah same type of container found on the
space pirates research really got the
material seeping out from the ruptured
metal is highly toxic oopsie I touched
it several times
this all sound so good right I think
they're really good and they're all like
you know actually normal common pizzas
here in Austria at least
analysis indicates that this may be the
phasin compound the space pirates were
using in the biological biology
biological experience
foreign
sorry I was having fun talking about my
pizza because I'm really excited about
the pizza now because I think it will
turn out really great I'm in the oven
the oven has decent reviews it's not as
good as the the oven that my friend has
I would say I assume but still a decent
uh like oven you know you know why I'm
not using my oven that I already had
well because you can't make the really
good pizza with it
and
that the reason is that even if you turn
your oven to the highest
High test highest heat it will still not
be enough to do the pizza like it should
be done yes but these off and I know it
looks like a waffle maker to some of you
guys crazy crazy guys uncultured somehow
shake my head
um but yeah it's more than that it's a
pizza oven
yeah and normally
it will finish the pizza in the two
minutes yes
what is it honey
she's gonna show me the same place again
aren't you
I don't know gravity gravity chamber
I bet it can make a mean waffle no
but you can you can no it
we can't
no
don't misuse my pizza chamber I will
call a pizza chamber now
hmm
that's where I have to go now but what
about the other place am I in the
anti-chamber now
am I in the anti-chamber yet
where's Santa chamber
why is it telling me to go there now
because I haven't even gone to the
anti-chamber yet I don't think so oh the
artifact Temple wait wait
what's up am I where I think I am
oh
I circled back
so many corn type food yeah yeah yeah
yeah Korea gets it you know I feel like
most countries understand how beautiful
corn is
except apparently America although I
don't think you guys dislike corn it's
just you guys uh don't put it on pizza
or you don't even think about putting it
on pizza but you really should consider
it
um
okay so but the funny thing I'm being
serious about the pizza inside but Pizza
surroundings will be corn cob and I have
come to the conclusion that the smartest
idea without losing the joke would be to
use one or two probably two because I'm
making two pizzas two big corn cobs and
then try to cut them into like eight
pieces like each corn cob into eight
pieces like uh length lengthy pieces
and um and then just lay them lay them
on the just for the photo up just lay
them down on the edges because I don't
think I will
um I will cook the corn cobs beforehand
maybe Grill them even but I don't think
I'll be putting them inside the pizza
chamber
because I am I'm worried about the heat
Maybe
yeah I might test it out but I don't
know I'll ask my my pizza friends about
it
um
yeah I think they would fit if I cut
them if I just put eight eight biggest
corn cobs in there it won't fit but if I
uh take apart one corn cob
it would in theory maybe uh fit I think
so but you know anyway
so the pizza chain but you go
you're friends with pizza no it's Pizza
friend it's the friend that makes good
pizza
yes okay now where do we go now what um
what
damn I can't believe I got like this
huge room connected here now
where the [\h__\h] do I go now
for real
do I
what do you hear when I say corn cob
gravity well well well well well
wow wow what
do I go to the Talon Canyon
to the root cave
and then to The Mug more Kevin sees you
can go to magma get to ice world okay
so this way I think
sorry no time for you
no time for you
uh what
please no surprise oh
[Music]
even now I can't kill you with your
spikes out
glad I did use a funny subscribe thank
you well done I have to ask you
questions because you say you don't know
how you stumbled onto my channel do you
watch YouTubers at all
or do you mean like you're for real just
like randomly out of nowhere am I your
first exposure to YouTubers
I'm very curious Hollow talk with you
Lennox
am I going
come on newbies we need more newbies
more more mom where was I going what the
[\h__\h] I lost track already
lost track
no not here let's say here okay
did I miss the answer
ah your challenge popped up on my feet
you didn't ask my question am I your
first exposure to be true boost
am I your thirsty
I'm gonna scare him away
yeah well you have to you have to be
able to get through questioning like
this because if you can't then you're
just not just not made for this life
as a kfp chicken
oh yeah by the way you're a chicken now
now that you subscribed to your chicken
just so you know
I said I am I am oh why
what oh Nathan good membership gift
though maybe it will reach uh our
newcomer
thank you
where did it go where did it go yeah
yeah you're my first and nothing scares
me haha that's why you're so funny let's
go we have a chicken that is scared of
nothing
chickens are my mascot by the way not my
mascots my fans but also my mascot
yeah because I I run a fast food place
okay this is where everything starts
getting confusing but please don't be
please don't be
scared off
there's much lower but it doesn't have
to scare you up are you guys gonna try
to get him a membership now
thank you
just take it step by step okay take it
step by step
where are we going
on track we're going down down down down
down
okay okay
down down don't go too down
maybe I do go very down
more memberships
we'll get him eventually
yeah bgm is pretty good
pretty chill right now sometimes it gets
very intense but this one's really chill
so
why you know you just randomly stumble
into here but you know where I have to
go
wait do you even know about the pizza
chamber how do you know about the pizza
chamber I'm just kidding you we're
probably here for a couple more minutes
no but the pizza chamber
why do you have to opt into being gifted
membership that's weird yeah is that
what you have to opt in no way really
is that a thing are you like
automatically opted out first
where am I
oh I didn't know that
Twin Fires
magmore workstation okay do I go left or
do I go right Lava Lake
Charles a ruins North
I have to opt in
[Music]
I'm gonna ask my YouTube
fendrana elevator uh
pandrana drift South this one
okay so left again
what
no no now it's right
this way
I think
I think I got it now
is this an easy way for me to get there
yes more memberships
but who knows guys if he even opted in
for that
how do you opt in
now they're curious now there are their
ears perked up
is that why I haven't been getting
memberships so far
what the [\h__\h] is that why I also haven't
been getting memberships when I've been
randomly randomly listening to other
streams
finally it makes sense
this room again
is it in your YouTube
settings
yeah am I a brand account oh what the
[\h__\h]
but that's unfair friends wants to get
membership too oh
boom
you can click on chat and hit all you
can do it while you're in the chat
uh-huh
there you go guys
kfp is so good at explaining everything
[Music]
just jump over there and accept some of
the pain from the lava
or should I go the long way
I feel like I wanna just go for it
worth it that wasn't even that much
damage
[Music]
am I still going in the right way yep
okay straight
to Hell let's go ah what was it with
this one how do you just normal hits
okay
come on come on
[Music]
today memberships are on the rise again
what the [\h__\h] is happening what what do
you mean
shut up I have to do another membership
stream next weekend wait
I will never find these bats is
different ever again you do remember how
much [\h__\h] I was struggling with them
them mosquitoes fighting them again I
mean I didn't say I was struggling like
I knew how to fight them
totally knew how to fight them but it
just took a long time when they were
spamming them at me thanks for the
memberships
[Music]
there's a made to be annoying
they're literally mosquitoes okay so now
we go
up here to the right
up here okay okay
you have to continuously check my map so
that I don't go the wrong way
this is the problem with backtracking if
you're new to the place then you can't
you just go to the door that you haven't
opened yet but
it's not so difficult but here I have to
be I have to make sure
I'm going the right way
so many generous people today yeah
[Music]
yeah got it
this is by the way also in some way a
pizza chamber
you could totally use that as a pizza
chamber I think
let's go
so many memberships
didn't
should I say was there a safe point
there
more workers I mean members
isn't the chamber just an oven yeah
that's what I'm saying but I figured
chamber is a cute word because the game
keeps on throwing it at me
Auntie chamber
and then we went to another chamber I
had a safe point right there all right
all right all right oh rattle rattle
rattle rattle
ride
what's cool what a big cool ice cold
[Music]
awesome
there's a there's door that I can now
open
Hallelujah
today I think we're really making good
progress
been
two and a half hours now and I feel like
I've been making good progress okay
these ones do not like that one
oh Funky Music here
I don't know what a coincidence
balls
but it's also keeping its own though
oh no no I could always break them maybe
I just didn't try hard enough
banana room
okay yeah it really does look like a
banana
open up
green doors
don't know which one to aim for first
but
I'll go by instinct
I hear enemies and I don't see them
[Music]
oh
ah these ones
all right
I hope this is a good place to proceed
to
I'm scared
the museum is kind of ominous now or
minions um I don't know what
oh don't tell me this is what I need
[Music]
no not that way oh Hallelujah I don't
like the heat version thing at all
oh lights I love it
I'm not a huge fan of it either
[Music]
way different way different way
s
you can't even they're so fast you can't
even focus on them
can't lock them on
[Music]
stupid birds
ah
how many times we're gonna repeat that
[Music]
is this the whole silly original song
hey
no no no no no
it's a super old Pink song though
kind of funny one day
that really look at them
cute
this way I like them way more than when
they're like going in a circle in the
tunnels
yeah pink yeah
huh
what is that a camera again
what the [\h__\h]
man
[Music]
much better
people
maybe scan oh
I mean if you are in a situation like
this where it's between surviving and
dying huh
you will think Chihuahua the Panic Ball
Lady can think of scanning something in
that kind of moment
was this missile only
no
[Music]
I did
what's not that youthful
it looks like it's being controlled by
um
you know those like
those little cards that you get a
controller to ride to like move them
around with
okay this one we can scan
glider docile Airborne creatures with
unusual magnetic properties gliders live
a relatively peaceful existence they
have a magnetic signature attuned to
Common grapple beam grapple beam
do I get the grapple back soon
sport of glider riding involves using a
grapple beam to attach to a glider then
staying on it as long as possible
there's a door there
you can't race that one anymore because
maybe that one yeah
[Music]
ah I can't log on to them
I was trying to blow them up and now I
can walk on
people people what about this one
no
huh wonderful
that's exactly what I needed all right
all right
which one first I'm gonna check somebody
said maybe there's a safe room is this
the safe room it is the safe room
I feel so safe and warm here like in the
uterus
is that where the babies are staying
is that where they stay
I need to learn women biology again
cool right
yes yes okay wonderful
one
day
am I shy Lily now
that's it
was really funny watching a little bit
of some clips from Kobo shy Lily collab
and also recently couple apparently got
a boyfriend her new song is so nice did
you guys listen to it she's so sweet in
her songs and then she's such a Savage
sogucky in her streams
a little [\h__\h] stay here oh they learned
how to dodge
I got him I got him
we got him
come here
ah
welcome
yeah you sound very cute but apparently
our fans called kobukers they are
panicking now because
she claims to have found
a boyfriend
of course it's only a joke
she even told me
so happy for you Kobo
does this mean we might have to do the
you know the talk now with you
but it's okay I don't I don't
I'm not even mad
all the family are yeah yeah it's pretty
funny
[Music]
I'm having a family themed panel with
her at Anime Boston soon
ironically
the
um panel theme should I really go this
way
panel theme is actually like it was an
idea from
management they were like how about you
do this
uh
yeah I don't know I don't know why
people go that well because I don't
think we have many things in common at
all
uh yeah we're supposed to prove our
family bonds by showing how much we have
in familiar I guess
I don't think we really have anything
unfamiliar
in common in common
but we'll see we'll soon
yeah we'll we'll probably fail at that
mission proving
How We Are Family
gotta line up early for good season
I think we'll both be singing too so
we'll hear some Kobo last singing and
some Wawa live singing isn't that great
exciting
what is that
I didn't want to
see
[Music]
a little [\h__\h] again
it's reflex
what
[Music]
adding our toes can fish [\h__\h]
yeah
what are you
Joseph aquatic Predator made of
electrically bound skeletal halves brain
is located in the upper half of its body
while the heart and digestive tract
occupy the lower half linked only by
electrical impulses to have somehow
functioned effectively enough to launch
the gels up to the top of the Talon for
Aquatics food chain
oh
wait I'm from this side it doesn't look
like a fish at all or does it turn
towards me
how do I kill
how do I kill it I have to get I have to
get it to open its mouth so I have to
get closer huh
yeah
now I would like to get out of this
water and figure out how to proceed in
this room
uh
uh Watts
I fell down from the top and I kind of
need to go to the top again oh wait
there's more
[Music]
there was one more
ah okay
I thought I would shut down everything
that's
I'm looking yeah yeah yeah I was looking
at the top
more water they're really um emphasizing
the water right now
foreign
the gravity chamber so I assume
I think I know what's gonna happen what
the [\h__\h]
do I have to take care of that thing
first
I don't know if I want to fall down it
doesn't look like there's actual grounds
there
right
tentacles go bye-bye do they come back
though
okay we're good we're good we're good
come on open your mouth
Sarah is here oh yeah yeah I recently
I've heard from her yes she's doing
really well and um
yeah she greets all the cave people
and thanks you for her for your sweet
comments
it's very flattered
she's a bit shy actually so I was
actually surprisingly I suppose
how do I
do the kiwama go back up outside the
water
um
ignore the tentacles
for a moment
there is a door and while the map tells
me the same
job
[Music]
um
here here here
more tentacles
oh
I didn't is this the same place no it's
the that monster spawned
so it's not the same
imagine you're at the dentist just
saying I want to look at your teeth
thank you
it's free free service free dentist
appointment
didn't go very well but why can I not do
a double jump
don't
you look at that
what is that I wanna have
what what isn't the bubbles well
something's holding me back the whole
time
or is that the gravity suit
[Music]
Sailor Moon moment
no
I don't want to be blue I want to stay
Orange
what
was it purple
purple it looks blue movement in liquid
environments is no longer hindered
what
oh my God look at that movement
incredible let's go
yay okay okay next next door I want to
go
up here up here
[Music]
and then oh what
huh
sorry sometimes this game I don't see
where where I need to go it's confusing
that's definitely got this oh again
time to backtrack everywhere no
what the [\h__\h]
look at you you look like you're from
the new Zelda game that thing what the
hell
come on blow up what was that
the [\h__\h]
love a bit of backtracking a little bit
is fine but it's not just a little bit
so I have to go back
why no teleportation
you hadn't seen that one yet I feel like
I haven't
thank you
this part is backtrack heavy
yup hi
hello
it's me stop dodging me
no no no no no no no no no
they make it more difficult for me than
it should be
okay so I feel like one of the few
things or maybe the only thing we're
missing now is a grapple hook
which way is home straight
oh unbelievable
door behind me
huh
what
there's a door he said I didn't really
come through that door
I said the next upgrade gotta be the
grappling hook like five times in this
game
power bombs last being two Bean combos
new suit one with all one more advisor
this advisor
the other side that one
I don't think I can make the jump back
like I did it through here
foreign
no wait for real like why did somebody
say I have to go this way is that a
shortcut to my
um
to my thingy
shortcut out and now it's not a shortcut
anymore because I'm
I missed it
yeah
I can go over here the other way too it
still is okay uh
well this is impossible at first
[Music]
let me up please let me um
no
this is like kind of similar to that one
time where
last time I just
jumped down instead of to the safe and
then I had to backtrack to
yeah live out the consequences of my own
actions
but at least this time it's not as
dramatic
f you
okay
I don't know the right way
there's two doors again are there two
doors no way one of them I came out of
probably the one down there
look like it's right there but it's not
um this one yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
shooters
and now it goes boom
what an interesting enemy
okay now kiwabo not repeat mistake again
ah
[Music]
la la
wow
oh no there's so many of them
this thing is so weird
what the hell did you guys see the
meatballs I made yesterday
[Music]
it's actually kind of funny to me like
I'm proud of what I cook but the way
everyone Praises me like I just made
some freaking Masterpiece on Twitter
looks like it's served in the restaurant
I would legit buy this I want to eat
this I'm so hungry oh my God face feed
me hey you guys you're really pushing my
ego
right by your wrong way
right away okay
actually so yesterday it felt so smooth
that's what I was saying oh I feel like
I leveled up in cooking I felt like I
was
having such an easy time I was watching
uh Netflix on my tablet I was watching
the office so yeah watching the office
while cooking comfortably
and then I don't know everything went so
well normally I didn't like making
meatballs and stuff like that that much
because
like and then like
getting into the meat dough like that
and
mixing in I don't know I didn't like it
so much before but this time it kind of
was pretty easy and fast
foreign
no I wasn't re-watching the whole thing
I was just watching like Random episodes
recently every now and then because what
I'm actually watching isn't on Netflix
but on my iPad I don't have what I'm
actually watching so yeah
a remote controlled car this Black
Knight that comment came in like
30 minutes late because I think you're
reacting to something I asked 30 minutes
before
that's weird
you get used to it yeah maybe I did get
used to it which way
where are we go what I completely lost
track
where is
here maybe
gravity no that's why I came from
Gravity Chambers where it came from
where's home
control tower
Observatory research and ruined
courtyards
go to nearest in
this one thank you mug more thank you so
much
oh thank you soon guys okay so our
banana broom or sausage room yeah
wait wait wait
whoa whoa whoa
whoa
hey I like how they die
so dramatic and one more
hey my HP I need to load up my ass
please don't
don't explode on me buddy don't
get a bus thank you okay
um
that one that one that one it's all the
way up it's at the highest point of this
room
[Music]
up the funky looking tentacle tree
um
jump here maybe
jump here
don't go here
[Music]
was that jump possible I'm not sure
do you remember how the super missile
yeah charge it and then miss out yeah
yeah
I just I mean I know how to do it but I
don't remember it anymore in the moment
where maybe it would be helpful to do it
because there's other ways to do it and
I guess I didn't feel like
remembering it in that moment
specifically thank you for reminding me
of its existence though I do know how to
do it I just don't
I didn't remember the existence
[Music]
also
yeah
almost almost sausage room
it will be helpful against some enemies
in next area okay
foreign
[Music]
oh look oh
South now you actually can stare a
little bit I guess I looked more purple
now indeed
don't fall down
oh
Nani ah and we're here again
elevating myself yes
well I don't have so many emotions yeah
[Music]
hmm
purple looks good on you well it does
but I want to be I guess it looks nice
I'm still mostly yellow
and it's kind of one of my colors so
y milk for sub channel oh what what
what's up Channel what I don't know what
you're talking about what's up Channel
you might want to say yeah yeah I mean
where where though
maybe this room
should I go ah wait that was behind
whoa
gutenberg's Channel
I don't have any control over that
channel
oh
rip German Channel
wow
let's just not talk about that okay
everyone who talks about it will be
banned for life
[Music]
censorship being implemented in kiwawa
Channel
hahaha
I don't want some music at some point
sometimes
what
I am so sad there is no typical physics
on her chest such a missed opportunity
you mean Samus
she's in full armor
you horny little [\h__\h] why would why
would she have jiggle physics
please no no no no no I'm glad she
doesn't have zerophysics people put way
too much jiggle physics on everything
that doesn't need that much single
physics it just looks on unrealistic
yeah metal is kind of known for lack of
jiggling
really sad you left John for that no
no no the sun is so dead completely it's
uh
and we'll be back
wait
guys am I going the wrong way
just let me know
if I am
[Music]
when
just know it's my membership yeah good
for you
why are we with you again dude oh
and it actually makes me bounce that
like towards him he wants to play oh
hey Kawaii where are you charging
something right now I don't want to get
down there when you're charging
something Buddy
wait a second
chance beam was with the normal one
right oh my God it's so he's still the
charging
oh
that was weird
how do I fight this one again did I do
it before
didn't I fight him as a ball oh no
we're telling you wrong way okay
I don't think you were really telling me
not enough people were telling me and
I've been told to not get one guide
again
foreign
[Music]
but then I got I got confused because of
the
safe point
okay go into hot place
sorry working the fryer
that's all right thank you
did I save
D did I end up saving
I think I did but for good measure
here
let's do it again
no don't let
don't let me no no no
no no no no no no
right after having saved
Michael made me wait so long
[Music]
next time
what's this chef
killing them so easily now
makes me so happy and we going to is
this my
what
I will never
be able to remember
what all these places are
and what place leads to what place I
don't even know how you guys do it am I
oh
yeah yeah yeah I'm guessing uh this way
the long way because there's nothing
there I guess over there
is it like a white door
there's a white door do I go to the
white door
long way can't gold area okay
[Music]
long way
that way
yeah I can imagine if you play this game
for the first time when it originally
came out like what
who are you supposed to know where to go
I would not know
[\h__\h] you
I think I had a lock for when I played
yeah but if you played it like really
really like at release then damn
sounds like a lot of suffering and
struggling
foreign
I am in very deep [\h__\h]
like really deep it's really deep
what what's going on I don't
what
it wasn't even that much use that much
HP that I love love I can't talk sorry I
was in a really hot situation right now
it was not comfortable which way did I
come from where am I going this one okay
let's not do that anymore let's not be
so [\h__\h] impatient okay
oh
really does gravity should really reduce
the damage does it make me stronger
against oh time to test it out I guess
it does feel like I took less damage
than usual hmm
well then isn't that basically an
invitation for me to just
jump in again and again
that's what it feels like certainly
no HP
at least sometimes
[Music]
a door is there
hi hi
nice
oh I got trekking all day every day baby
didn't know you could freeze so I also
didn't know until Chad told me so don't
feel bad about it
submerge in lava
in Super Metroid wow wait did I just go
back again
elevator
I love it all right
without taking damage damn well that was
that was being incredibly strong suit
then I I think there should be a lava
suit I think for Gravity suit it doesn't
make sense it makes you resistant
against lava there should just be an
extra suit for that
but what do I know I am just
a random player of this game and I don't
know [\h__\h]
don't be surprised this time there we go
I saw it coming
hi beautiful
I would have skipped them if my HP
wasn't so low I kind of want that HP
this place is always like what
[Laughter]
literally don't know where I'm going
what I'm doing
what do they expect from me
right
am I going to Red what am I going
am I going to
oh the door where I am right now
red for later
supposed to switch the switch no no no
many times already today I've been told
oh switch visors and it didn't help me
that room is nothing different it's just
like
that is badly designed that's it I'll
stay by my opinion
here right
I'm almost there
who's there again it's like oh
just want to sit down for a minute crack
a beer can open and watch some goddamn
TV is that too much
sorry that difference
personality came out of me for some
reason I don't drink beer yeah
oh my God my God Karthik stuff
oh my God
look can I make my ship purple too I
feel like it should be matching with me
[Laughter]
Albuquerque Wawa
no no Alto kiwawa is also not an
alcoholic no no no no no no
there's literally no timeline
[Music]
where Chihuahua drinks
alcohol this is just the base stats that
she has
a beer chill will never happen that's
right not even non-alcoholic because I
think it's disgusting
Head East
where is East you mean East from this
view right now or
is there an actual East like when I
point it like this is this North and
then
right is this is East
the other big room okay
that way
[Music]
yeah yeah I just realized there was a
compass I didn't notice until now
that's right that's how it should be
so why are we going to the other big
room now again eh where are we going
this time Kane didn't even tell me to go
anywhere specifically
how am I supposed to know like am I
reading this game's mind what
how do I know that I want to go there
now what the hell
[Music]
what the hell I went into the wrong room
give it a moment okay okay if I just
stand around does the game recognize
that I don't know what to do
help
help I mean I have cats but still
eventually it will take pretty that's
what I've been noticing but even at
times where I was actually purposefully
doing something else
game I really don't know what I'm doing
help me please
boy
things it's still things that know what
I'm doing I am I am successfully making
a sink that I am a good Metroid player
that's what I call you
maybe now this mosquitoes will show me
where they're going all the time where
they're running off to
[Music]
so
water
I've got the water suit I've got the Ice
Beam it's time to open all the doors
missile
I will come and get you I will I'll get
you I will get you
[Applause]
[Music]
increased by five
that's right but what isn't there like a
door here I guess it is not in the water
oh hi
oh
[Music]
Nanny what is this room this is nothing
this is nothing
huh
okay was that very mummy is I was
thinking that too while I was saying it
huh
I don't know what I'm doing
ball in that room
[Music]
thank you I forgot about that
foreign
this is where I will need my heat visor
soon
set is that it
was that I checked this place out right
yeah I'll fix you
why does that not do anything
it's for ambience
it's nice Ambience I'll give you that
what the [\h__\h] is that
no no no that scares me no no no no
[Music]
now the worst part comes a bit later
okay
it got a lot of rooms really dark yeah
I'm scared
okay I'm fine thank you
[Music]
what
foreign
[Music]
oh it's already opening oh
is it
oh no it doesn't
and that's how it is oh look at that oh
okay thank God when I asked you guys oh
do I need it again
I didn't I didn't mean like you know you
guys said yes but I thought when you
said yes you meant there's gonna be like
big ass rooms continuously like that
what the [\h__\h] what's up
turns out that wasn't the case
you only really needed to see when you
first get it
I am now because that was like my least
favorite section of the whole game
hey you make me so happy
oh
wow
[Music]
nice
and the water isn't so bad either
anymore now
because now we can move freely although
I didn't even think it was that bad even
when our movement was restricted I
thought it was okay
obviously now we can do more
[Music]
okay let's go to that blue dog
Water World version of Samsung
that's why you need to grab this with
aha
[Music]
it makes a lot of sense
here
so even though my movement is normal now
uh
the sounds are dampened
the music is not dampened though
yeah I wonder you say you used to hear
about the gravity so it takes ages but I
wonder so that means you can skip it
not really no can you can you skip for
Speed running purposes can you skip
getting the gravity suit and just move
on without it
[Music]
okay one could say everything there is
damp you mean because it's wet
you can skip all this area
[Music]
for real why am I here done
if you want to walk here yes with
glitches oh
[Music]
what am I doing where am I going
where's Blue Door
over here
what
blend and blend this shoot might be
normal
[Music]
this door has some power four nearby
power conduits must be energized okay
four nearby
and there's one there
[Music]
yeah
one is there
when I see below
and
last one
oh wait isn't that wrong there why did I
not say that before because I I did turn
on the heat vision
foreign
last one is here
[Music]
okay
nice
open
hands open I'm scared I'm
oh it's really dark
oh no no it gets
it gets darker and brighter oh I like
this green light
all right there's another one of those
I was just I don't even need to read I
was just guessing
how many do you need two
hours enough well
no open oh do I go this way first
there's two paths
better to not run away immediately
[Music]
we're playing more uh mentored Prime
tomorrow aren't we
well you guys probably don't think I
will
finish it tomorrow do you
know
depends on how I play
how does that work there's a there's a
thingy down there
bye
tank
it's like a
I already activated okay
[Music]
Let's scan missile
thank you
guys always say scam but that one guy
basically just
gave me shortcut
saved me precious time
so if you guys
play
possible
ow
[Music]
I didn't waste it
what what ah this is really confusing I
don't see
[Music]
it's possible if you don't get too
tilted
unicorns need every tank you have for
the section after this oh my okay but
like how do I get this one
sorry
[Laughter]
nanny
oh I can't believe I made that jump
[Music]
oh I feel like I can jump more in the
water
[Music]
beautiful
can I make that jump
yeah
time for heat vision just to check
what
he did
I think he did
[Music]
why did he just fall
dead into the water
what's happening up there
jump scare
ah
Everything feels so tilted it's
confusing
there's not even a hole here how did it
get how did they get there
oh my God I made it
all right
it's good that I activated the bottom
one at the beginning
because there's two no is there more
than two
is there more than two
oh
let's reach
[Music]
I thought I was being
exceptionally smart
is it this one
it's not moving so I think it is
me ah
okay okay okay
almost my job yeah a good attempt I
needed three
I thought that was like I was gonna be
at the top and then I just had to
activate one more thing and we're gonna
be like oh my God so smart key Marvel
for seeing ahead into the future must be
fortune teller oh my God can I hire you
to tell my fortune please
tell me what's up in my life kiwawa I
need to know
[Music]
and then I'll be like yes I'll tell you
if you're fortunate but you must promise
that you will not attempt to interfere
with it
oily
[Music]
oh my God
hell oh my got another one
oh I found this
one
ah now I understand I wanted to do the
yellow super beam oh [\h__\h] I don't wanna
how much did I lose
my God
okay at least I tried it once
it sucks the missiles not that much
I hope so
what
yeah this place is where the tutorial
happened right
but it's changed a lot since I was here
I think this was like
[Music]
wasn't this kind of different
how did it change so fast
and now what the Wawa do blew up and
crashed crash in the cloud is crazy but
it looks like like I don't know 200
years passed
what
sorry I'm blind I don't see anything
right now I saw that one thing but ah
into the water oh
this thing where I say yai don't die
[Music]
oh
it's me
why why
take care of the damage
reminds me of Amy
oh the elephant I remember elevator
can I scan again does it not work
anymore
doesn't work anymore but
would you look at that
made one more
or is that where I came from
why is this confusing me
one here ah
there's one there
damn it
can reach from here
come on
how
climbed back up
Chihuahua
okay kiwawa I will do that
how did I not see that before
[Music]
are you guys falling asleep yet
don't
[Music]
no wow
wait but isn't the door up there how do
I go up
[Music]
what no I came from the big door up
there after I left to go to the smoker
so anyway I started blasting
alien tentacles
ice them
I keep on switching back to the purple
one because I I get this feeling that I
need to activate those doors with it I
don't even know if I really have to
oh yeah
hi hi hi hi hi
come on come on
beautiful
I'm switching around much pressure
I got uh kind of used to that too
oh there's more
one how many do you need there's another
one
oh jump from here
thank you
and then one more
is
and don't stream what do you mean it's
only been three and a half hours no I'm
not planning to do during stream today
but maybe tomorrow nah
not really in the plan
oh wait that's it
how did I not see that before
I mean if I need to play like
two more hours to finish it then I'll
I'll do it if that's like if that's how
it is tomorrow
if I'm like really close to the end
then I'll try my best
[Music]
to get there because I don't really like
doing streams that are like so short
[Music]
for several reasons
hmm
which door
which door is the new one the one I just
looked at right
[Music]
what
that pipe was in the way no that's where
I came from
what
or is it wait it connects possibly
no I just okay I didn't come from there
it just is exactly the same system
what are you locking on to
oh my God
another one what's happening
how did that happen
[Music]
do I want to go down there I don't think
so
what the hell
you good buddy
oh yeah
what is that
what did I just do
I
[Music]
I go down there where they come out of
exploding and dying what a
suicidal thing to do
what is this blue bloops for
wow Sam is for Real
for real
about time
[Music]
for the Bounty for County we shall
suffer oh that's
oh that's underwater ball
he's like Spaceballs
[Music]
wow
wow big jump no come on
Echo ball go
Overworld
but underwater again
fascinating
foreign
look how fast I'm taking care of them
whoa who's the boss now
shut tomato this world
I've been here before it seems
great Tree Hole do I go up to the
elevator
I love the scenery in this game so far
yeah it's quite pretty like I said this
is the first stream already I think but
it doesn't it wasn't e-tank it doesn't
feel like it's a GameCube game but I
don't remember the original Graphics I
just feels like they must have upgraded
it a lot
a tank
you tanked okay
in the tunnel
[Music]
in this one
oh
is it
[Music]
do I have to do one of those fancy
double jumps
okay okay
um
[Music]
oh oh no
wait
go
all right so you don't throw the bomb at
the very end you throw it a little bit
before so that once you fall down you
reach that point just in time oh my God
[Music]
it's really hectic
really difficult you see that was too
low
[Music]
pass too low too
[\h__\h] that's Mis timing
that's
oh God that's too hot uh high in here
[\h__\h]
ah
I said it would have just been able to
go left immediately
no need for more bombs right
although
[Music]
yes
skills guys I've got the skills I've got
the power
yo
Pro Gamer kiwawa
I am so proud of myself
I drink a little bit
[Music]
skills to pay the bills we have
that's kind of true
kind of my motto All right where are we
going next
um there was an elevator right
I'm assuming I have to take the elevator
or the blue door
oh they're probably the blue though
because I don't know what's behind it
yet
the white door huh
oh
that one
I am right there ah
[Music]
I'm heading for the scariest part of the
game
intense radiation detected
perfect timing
I'm scared
this part is the hardest
[Music]
no no what no I don't want to play
anymore no
no
I'm scared
who's scared of me
why you tell me
this is safe just ahead can I go back
is it too late
no elevator rooms always have to be safe
elevator rooms always have to be safe
a head not behind me
ah okay
I thought I missed a save
no I'm scared no no no no no no no
not the absolute worst but it's pretty
unforgiving it tests you
at least at least
like you know when I stream for the
first time in a while
I'm like completely lost
at least I worry I'm like pretty warmed
up today so
where's the safe point Mommy
Mommy
okay
what if I died before
oh
and that's me
that's me
they showed me some I saw some enemies
ourselves somewhere
longest stretch about the safe I think
and not just this game but the Prime
series as a whole
no [\h__\h] way
safe system to the left
the purple door
can I go down
you guys scared of me
am I hitting
oh probably not why am I
now I'm hitting
laughs
look at those incredible tactics
am I hitting though
oh yeah I did I shouldn't have looked
Peak shooting like an FPS Pro hey
that was that was good that was good
Oh I thought I was on the ice cream
ah
take this for [\h__\h] sake
Champion what the [\h__\h]
out
oh
what why did that take so much more time
turrets get stronger oh man well
okay
purple door
oh my God I can't sound scared
it's purple door here
yes
ah what is this voice
it's a part of the bgm
thank you please grant me access thank
you
what voice don't say then
oh is that those Pass power rats spicy
Pirates Spice Girls
um
[Music]
stop talking please it scares me
because you guys said it's scary now I'm
even more scared
no no kiwama don't be scared no no no
don't let them
have that kind of control over you
how to go down
and I'll find a way or there's a will
there's a way he's just as scared ah
they say that like
Mommy
parents would say that when you're
scared of like a spider so I'm not a
spider
oh
Nice Shot [\h__\h] you space pirates
[Applause]
not giving them any time
full health
yo reflexes Panic reflex this is what I
call this
anymore anymore okay
anymore
wherever next one next I'm on the bridge
sorry I have no overview of this place
ah over there
all right that seems kind of hard to
reach
all the cure to let you know they're
there enemies cannot go through doors
but can shoot through yeah I have
noticed yeah
I can platform oh wait ah
can I go up there
I don't know
brain horde moment
there's a platform on the other side
past the pillows other side okay
[Music]
line show strikes again
no it's not really Blanchard I was just
on the wrong side oh this is dark again
indicates recent news device is
currently inactive should be activated
[Music]
any more like secret things for me to
get here
missiles
nice
I'm at Max anyway
oh
oh just needed one yeah bye yeah bye
yeah bye
[Music]
feels yeah bye
oh but look at that was that there
before
am I the crane
what what is this
can I get picked up
what did I do
yeah
I control
key why am I in control
I'm guessing I have to read oh yeah
crane control is no active now active
what a convenient coincidence
coincidence that the crane is lined with
those
hit
wait but if it moved away did it move to
me
oh my God yeah
oh missiles
it's like when they built the crane they
knew that Samus was gonna come in her
ball form and make use of it
they wanted me to do it they're just
playing with me in the end I'm just a
character in their world
I'm just a video character
you guys also just video character you
guys are also the NPCs were all just
NPCs ever thought about it that way
it's just like they're playing Lego and
I'm just a Lego piece
yeah yeah
we're all in this big simulation
um
sorry to break everybody's Minds with
that
I cannot unball myself here
for real I feel like there's space for
it though
okay and now
it's still doing the wee-wee
maybe if I turn it again this time it
will lead us over there
I wonder
no
oh well at least I put things back where
they were
or should I not wait but that acts as a
platform
that kind of acts as a platform
for grapple hook maybe even but uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah when do I get my
grapple beam eh
but somebody said go down
Andrew this is not Stanley's power I
wish it was need more Stanley games
soon TM
um
Maybe
what about this place
dual control force field is online the
activation controls are likely nearby
the activation controls will go
hmm
nearby
what are those
I passed it
wait what's this
oh it's just a box ow
explosive bobs not just the Box
past it
foreign
disabled
force field disabled but not this one
I was here
[Music]
disabled two of them
okay
thank you
should I like
safe before I move on because I already
feel like I spent some time here and I
don't wanna
you know what I will
yeah
yeah yeah
it never hurts it will hurt if we don't
yes yes
the last time you'll save in a while
I've read that
long last passage without saving
in a Metroid gameway that's an elevator
sorry
got confused again
I see Shiny door I want to go
back
all of them are back
[\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] why don't you why does it
not see me
okay
there's one more I think but oh well
we'll deal with him in a second when I
find ah there it is
[Music]
every time you move two doors Ah that's
how that looks ah ah two doors until
they respond
[Music]
are you doing the Kobo wave was no no no
no no no no no no
because I am scared and panicking
ah you little [\h__\h]
now hopefully that was it already we're
going down
wait I don't need to do that right
this one is just as well
all right
[Music]
so so much
why are these still my biggest enemies
guys did I'm super Miss silent no no
come on you know how to do this
but there's two so that they're like
not going to the one that I want is to
go to but no no I did the trick
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
that's what I want to thank you
all the turret malfunction
what
I'm scared
why am I so why am I so extra careful
now if you scan that this Amazon oh
oh
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait do I have to um
use my heat visor for this one
ah okay
oh [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
oh he already did
more more more more more more more
[Laughter]
another beautiful example of Penny ball
the freezing doesn't freeze them though
unfortunately but and it's kind of hard
to see but when you have the thermal
Visa visor on you don't really see it
well
in my opinion if you're actively hitting
them or not or if you missed so it makes
me question my ways
if I charge it it always does
okay okay
some enemies it does for some it doesn't
you know
it was scary
huh
is it okay to move on here
spam wave beam that I want to lose all
my missiles
I don't want to be that wasteful
oh no
wait
don't please don't come please don't
come I'm not here I'm not here
Scandal purple beam only purple beam
only thank you that's what they would
tell me if I would scan them
they've been
they're immune to anything else we do so
wait I have purple and then uh how does
it work I charge it and then I
push the missile button
is that how that works again no way
faster oh just normal wave beam normal
okay
it's kind of like you know
well done I I should not
are they immune to myself I guess so
let's go let's go somewhere else guys
stunlock
oh oh you're dead Okay crazy hi I'm fine
well they were trapped with me
that was a little better panic situation
because we were introduced into new
enemies but it's all good it's all good
we're okay we're fine
we're gonna be fine
what is this
security buyers can lock someplace locks
keyed to space pirate life sends only
x29
I may not be a space pirate but I am a
bounty hunter I feel like that's kind of
you know since I am in space I feel like
that's kind of the same thing
but okay
you be like that
hi
we are not the same
hello I'm scared that's why I'm moving
really slowly right now
in case you haven't noticed yet
missed the first encounters I chose with
us ghost yeah you have to watch that I
got them oh
purple purple
that thing but in purple
it seems so because it kind of was
purple
and even when I couldn't see it oh my
God Panic or maybe not maybe it was just
a normal one okay
I don't know
oh hey I even like I'm doing it without
the heat Vines right now
no no nothing here really really
oh sorry cilantro
I'm scared
this is what I'm like always so careful
about like sometimes you jump into a
room and then the enemy's already right
there
no Boston just remember this room uh-huh
okay
mikochi pirate wins eh
they have a meeting should I not disturb
them
foreign
did not notice
I like this like stun locking tactic
right now very much
or rat all right all right all right
would be nice to have some something to
load up my HP but okay I guess not
um recommended battle systems for elite
Pirates are as follows shoulder bounded
plasma bleep
space pirate encrypted data decoded
initial project Helix experiments with
spice pirate embryos were disastrous
about babies bye bass
wait a stop moving what the hell
koala
let me try something
the face and infusion process the
generated brain tissue even as it
augmented muscle mass what are we saying
none of what we have termed Elite
Pirates lived to maturity what
the few what are these words it's like
they just stick to random words next to
each other and hoped it would sound like
a sentence
uh at least to me
I got scared to be yeah Frozen the few
that survived their infant Hood suffered
severe psychotic breakdowns as juveniles
killing anything within their zone of
procession okay that sentence I
understood research teams Clara made a
recent breakthrough in which parasite
studies with a phase and strain code
named vertigo were highly successful
since then we have successfully fused
vertical phase and with space pirate DNA
with great success the latest batch of
elite Pirates have reached maturity
successfully and are ready for field
testing and training
thank you
oh what did I do what did I do okay I
just turned the platforms on okay okay
why are you guys saying Miko Pirates
because baby
oh I hear more of them
they're not the purple ones I might want
to use the ice beam oh there are the
purple ones
oh
are they playing hide and seek
come down little sucker
they weren't like kind of smart they
were not like
straight coming at me they were first
like hiding
come on
I was like I think
going
been thinking
for me because they're so open
I'm stuck
well
[\h__\h] hell I can't platform when I'm
loading this up
that little [\h__\h] come down
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you
yeah that's right
oh my HP
no wait something I've been shooting
with um what's that all right I got used
to it in the beginning of the game I was
always shooting with a but then I
realized
well it may show that I'm a pro gamer if
I do that and then combine it with like
jumping around
but it's also making a lot of things
more difficult so I stopped doing it and
then got used to that r
m
wow
security alert all stations
has made plant fall on town for the
hunters among us all units are here by
order to attack iron on site terminal
forces authorized report all sidings of
iron oh
shits
platform systems
no
um
man please
you got it all wrong I'm just here
trying to talk you know totally
wait that's a that's a that's like uh
the other one
[Music]
oh my God my HP oh my God my HP I really
need something
[Music]
really really really
game sometimes very nice when give those
lies for life
but sometimes sometimes other enemies
they don't spawn anything at all what
the [\h__\h]
oh
pause beam online all the firing mode
what are you
oh
did that just open up A New Path
attention only is reported to your
Battle Stations uh failure
to comply with this orders and active
phrase and treason's punishable by
termination
geez Jesus
please do not shoot again
wait shoot again actually
because
I feel like supposedly it opened up a
path but not really
no you can scan the beam Cannon hi
um
so what now
oh wait there's like several packs
that I could open up
I feel like I hear like a really numb
sound of an alarm
that just might be part of the PGM
oh yes platforms yes yes I love it so
much it's my favorite pastime
how do I move it how do I move this
thing
how do I move it because I wanted to
look over here for example
10 44
[Music]
um
13 percent
oh
yeah don't you dare fall down
oh bye
I think this is hard to see how to tell
where it actually currently is
what's going on I'm just gonna start
blasting
which one is it the red one
oh nice
okay
two spins per section okay
are there enemies coming out of it no
okay
is that oh
all I wonder
yeah we probably should blow up this one
too
can I go the other way around or do I
have to go in circles
one has a missile blast them all
are there ones on this side too
that's where I am
hopefully not
okay that's
straight
I think
I missed the missile
don't worry I'll get back to it
this one and this one okay everything
but this one oh there's also one there
okay
okay okay okay
thank you
and uh
one and two one and two and then one and
two
should give us
another one where there might not be
anything interesting in it but I'm gonna
blast it anyway
and then
one and two and one and two
okay
one and two that's the last one
yay ah would you look at that oopsie
my ball looks different now too wait it
looks so
wow
oh my God
that's kind of fancy purple bone very
fancy
and the other ones are useless wow
can I make that jump
yeah easy
four myself
we go for the door in a moment please
wait please hold hold the line
um
I'm scared I feel like
I should
go back to safe at this point already
but then I go for so many doors that the
enemies will be back so but look at my
health
that's why you guys said I will need all
my health tanks
[Music]
and they'll just all respawn and I'll be
in trouble again so even though I will
know them better and I will know the
paths better
still
what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah
do I ignore this laser stuff
do I land on the platform
I just no it's fine
okay the laser didn't hurt me at all wow
I guess only if I were just falling down
as a Sam normal Samus then maybe it
would hurt
surely some enemies in here
I'm probably gonna die eventually
I'm scared
oh
um
yo
that was necessary just to save some HP
you know
wrecked
represents the central pillar in this
room the pillar contains several
rotating sections oh they can be moved
to gain access to different areas
rotation of the pillow will alter the
path of its magnetic Railway ah
so okay how do I move it
oh
oh my God I can't believe he dropped
something
well let's see
I'm coming scan data power surge is
detected oh thank you
honey
oh it's pretty close this time Central
Dynamo
that's where the game wants me to go
currently as if I wasn't already on the
right track
BF
what
next oh
at this one
what
are some space pirates
[Music]
should we keep it like this for once for
one for for now
oh
I don't want like a frustrating moment
where I'm gonna
die again
goodbye
and then I have to backtrack everything
where I do everything
oh there's another one
just don't panic are you do you know
what streamer you're watching right now
it's my thing it's like my trademark
Panic is my trademark
line up Brad path
like so
uh wait how do I get back
do I have to go to the bottom again
and line up right down jump
okay
I'm scared
the bottom again okay
now to fix it down here again too
which one am I lining up
how do I know when it's lined up
it's from this angle I can't say
oh because it's a hologram only
and maybe I got it right
spiders
all right all right all right
foreign
now it's lined up
why are they so loud
they're at the top they're gonna unlock
bamboozle me aren't they
[Music]
he's moving it's not about
the move which color is Eagle
because I guess yellow oh are they
lasers are they ever lasers the same
color no
nope they're not
and why
I only took one one hit from him though
so
that's pretty pretty good
I would say oh there I can't to jump
over there
but
not really reachable
uh but dancing well I feel like we broke
something like this before
but with
what
the warning Trooper oh
not yet oh am I gonna get the red
last laser thingy
oh
thank you
oh they get some HP
yo precious yummy yummy yummy Red Bulls
thank you
four
more and more no
honey I can't
oh that didn't hurt me because I kind of
fell through that one
the last one didn't even have to use the
track
there are crates near wow you know the
game too well are you playing like
besides me
is that an elevator room
foreign
okay okay but it's not a safe
unfortunately
of course not because you guys said it
will be a long time I expect so much
[Music]
great oh missiles
dangerous
stay away from those
uh missiles 69 missiles let's go
this place looks okay so far
oh I see you there's a shadow of a
I think it's a space pirate
probably
nice explore the crate
you guys you guys
who's gonna attack me
oh
get all the HP I possibly can
give me that why can I not reach give me
come on you can do that jump you wow
put that fingers in the way
try jumping I'm jumping
maybe from here is it even fun
[Music]
so close
jump slower delay the second jump
[Music]
oh first try
give
you agree right that was first try
guys that had like so much slower now I
just really don't want to die
I probably will end up dying anyway
what is this
foreign
the activation
maybe they will activate it once they
see me
oh
wait it's not deactivated
oh scam optical illusion no wow just
stupid I thought
I thought mine had the same sh like
shield in front of it as those over
there
[Music]
remember the Superman style you mean
this one
[Music]
your staff notice something coming
I was charging it I was charging it but
then cutscene I don't know if that
counts
oh
[\h__\h] wait I forgot uh wait wait uh
missile
um not only are but also what x sorry
currently brain somewhere else went out
to buy milk
again
Elite pirate face and enhanced space
pirate incredibly strong armored and
well-armed
uh-huh
Elite Pirates are pro tent foes okay
Energy Siphon system absorbs beam weapon
shots
so anything that's not a what
wait so my um
only missiles work so but if it's a beam
with a missile so super beam
that works right
Miss salsa
when his hand is up don't shoot
oh
and then I'm gonna miss that when his
hand is up I can use a missile
if he holds up a shield
he will absorb it otherwise he's sweet
okay
only absorption was a panda Shield
so wait wait if hand is up no if hand is
not up anything works
and if hand is up only super beam works
or only missile Works a phantism
no nothing works nothing at all not even
missile
normal missile only
to concussive face weapons will arms the
Ali pirate is effective in close combat
and that distance their massive sides
can be a weakness and their Slugger
speed allows for evasional you know
okay when hand is up just don't shoot
just try to stay away maybe
it's not that is it
[Laughter]
[Music]
just getting started
ah
I was so worried he didn't even put his
hand up you guys were at me so much it
wasn't the boss huh
um
my God
oh
there's no space fires though
uh wait does this one not drop like
anything nice like um HP
please stop please stop making space
pirates sounds
on the other hand we'll put them to very
good use very soon
space pirate potato called
normally these are just big mini bosses
practice for the bus oh okay
did I have like a similar system
what sorry crater continued to meet with
failure The Shield of strange energy
that protects it is it is impermeable
and all attempts to Tunnel past and have
proven fruitless our continued fertility
in this matter has made all the more
significant in light of the recent Live
Form readings we've discovered emanating
from people within the crater analysis
of them indicates that a massive
creature is what
G State G stating what
G stating what does that mean
gestate gestating what is that
they're absorbing enormous amounts of
face and from the face and
it means it's growing oh
we're at the heart of the impact crater
this discovery makes accessing to create
a doubly important not only will it open
the door of the vast that pause that's
off face and move in but it will also
lead us to this creature whatever it may
be
I want to say you guys at head office
have surprisingly Liberal sonicals
Liberal does that mean because it's um
because it's like separate
it's not always separate though you mean
because it's separate
also I left my ski club somewhere so how
do I get a company you're not getting
that
you can just get yourself new ones but
thanks for coming to Austin uh a towel
optional
oh yeah he was surprised because it was
not separate oh yeah yeah we have places
that are not separate no I guess most no
actually most places are not separate
liberal means loose oh yeah yeah lose
yeah that's why I don't really like
sauna here much
but I feel like Sonic culture and mostly
in other places as well is just mixed
saunas and
just have fun and be naked I guess
that's what I thought it was in most
places
because that's just sauna that's just
what sauna is
hmm
I've only been to McDonald's before yeah
I think me too
ah
won an ostrich that I went to with my
best friend I think that one was
possibly
women only because I only saw women but
who knows maybe maybe it was still mixed
probably still mixed most of them were
mixed that's for sure
new pirate data
security command issued an all points
alert after the fall
of the best the alert concerns kiwawa
also known as the hunter subject is
heavily armed and extremely dangerous
subject uses a powered armor suit of
unknown design and battle along with a
number of potent beam and concussive
weapons all combat units are instructed
to terminate kiwawa on site preferably
the fashion that will allow Salvage of
her powered armor suit and weapons a
considerable Bounty will go to the unit
who delivers koala to command Dead or
Alive with man is not oh [\h__\h] they're
serious
ah
[Music]
this is why I am legitimately scared
which color was that it looked White
[Music]
it was one huh
[\h__\h] now I have to change weapons
[Music]
okay I did Panic ball once again oh my
HP
phone
[Laughter]
open
oh
please why you give me so many missiles
when all I need is help
oh man
[Music]
there's still one more I think
yeah or more than one
[Music]
no more maybe maybe no more
oh
that's not fair is it
is he gonna come
[Music]
heart's over what's up
is he called a cup
[Music]
craters
think there's any
so this is so so evil
right door should I go for the right
there in the bottom
there's some crates upstairs eh
how much is he doing now there's no safe
points
and there's they barely drop the healing
stuff and there's no craters barely
Burly is this a crater
what is that
let's go see
I don't think greatest oh there
oh
come on missiles I don't need so many
missiles no
okay
[Music]
next room is infinite health safe one is
much further really
okay which door up or down
I love your panic attacks thank you
glad you're enjoying them it hurts my
throat but I'm also having fun I guess
it's funny
up okay
I got one guide almost somebody said
down before
man they just show up out of nowhere oh
there's more craters
I didn't drop anything
okay now why so stingy
yeah
once I learned a new word I use it all
the time now I say it all the time one
God
save Point close they say so I I should
be fine
about this week
oh that's where I need to go for
um
results are informed field studies on
the bathroom group JoJo ask me
please are extinct when
we believe that Talon 4 was once the
stronghold in a great chosen Empire
brought Low by the meteor strike
planetary Devastation brought an end to
the chosen yet remnants of their society
remain we are studying these relics in
an attempt to harness their power what
is of no use to us we destroy in time we
shall have all we need from this dead
race and shall wipe this planet clean up
their ugly ruins wow damn sheesh
the dead should serve the living not
hinder wow wow man chill the [\h__\h] out
man
[Music]
be terrifying
although we are still no closer to
finding the artifacts of the chosu just
like me I also feel like I'm not closer
at all
that's one thing you have in common we
have at least produced a viable
hypothesis uh for their function it
appears that each of the artifacts
corresponds to one of the statues on the
temple platform and that each one acts
as a small key to a huge lock judging by
the number of statues we assume there
must be 12 artifacts thanks for
repeating that information to me because
you think I forgot that
remember that part once you find the
resting spots of all 12 we can bring
them here unite them with their statues
and open the gate system at long last
once we do the impact crater and
whatever creature it shelters
will be hours from taking for the ticket
homo homo
fourth grade level
granted thanks I guess
yeah the artifacts why have I still not
found them
only one right we have come to another
dead end it is clearing out that we will
never discover the locations of the
chosen artifacts
until we can decipher the messages
carved into the statues in this
abdominal Temple abominable
our language databases are woefully
inadequate and our linguistic and
analysts can come up with little more
than vague theories
there's your hint
oh
the best hypothesis that we can offer is
that finding artifacts will require
items spiritually linked to The Chosen
civilization however without these items
we're lost in common command grows more
impatient by the day
then they should they shouldn't try to
get my dead body then they should try to
get my Alive's body and then take it as
a hostage and then use me to find the
artifacts and all that eh
wouldn't that be smarter of them to do
if they're if they want the results
did I not get it
that is even more difficult for them
[Music]
Hearts aren't smart
put the older things are running down
they're using words that I don't even
know so they're definitely smarter than
me
they're outsmarting me
they don't know you know but I'm a
chosen
should know
anyway
what
I'm gonna get like suddenly blasted
again
please don't
oh
[Music]
this is a farming room
farming run
what the [\h__\h]
it's fun rolling here oh
wait
um
but it also hurts me it hurts me quite a
lot though
oh no
[Music]
[\h__\h] help
I have footsteps again why do I
sometimes
happy
[Music]
your space pirate
go back and Farm
what
climb for the other side
go back into room
hot
I just have to do it like from a safe
angle
okay
oh thank God
thank God
oh
it's like a
um
what's it called again
steam sauna healing me
and there's a lot of steam
the ones in the back I can't get but oh
well gotta kill them when they're closer
did you know that like in Finland
at least I found this out because of all
all the times I've been on the Finland
airport now at this point
um
most people even when you're like not
super rich
apparently have
uh saunas in their homes like small
saunas it's like pretty standard I mean
if there's any Finnish people in the
shed and they say it's wrong please
correct me but this is like the comment
there um
quite nice
I think if I get a house
maybe I'll also built myself a little or
have myself built a little sauna
because you can just get like a really
small one you don't even need a big room
for that just get yourself a tiny one
person two people
sauna
because that's really healthy saunas are
really healthy and you could you can go
like daily
why did they stop coming out of the ride
home
yeah it seems to be true
come on no more this takes so much time
now
a good step towards my dream house
[Music]
yeah I'll I'll go until full health no
less than that
power beam faster
but they don't necessarily spawn faster
though
almost though
hmm
not even like using the auto aim oh my
God
sheesh
a
fun camping
I wonder if the developers like made
this on purpose this room knowingly
like the one Mercy they shall give me is
this
but only if you think
Sports
to use this room like this
100 dated
well if you know I would have kind of
kind of preferred the save point though
but I guess I'm I'm
not to be rewarded like this
okay we got it
pretty much there now
oh yeah baby
show our spa vacation is almost over and
we will go back to the horror of
everyday life now
how realistic
two singles hits
oh my God
she keep on hitting
she keeps on hitting oh I'm full I'm
falling I can't stop okay let's go
let's make this worthwhile please please
please
can someone give me give me nickel an
estimate of like you know how much
longer until safe point and what's
what's uh coming up because I'm like
freaking the [\h__\h] out every every room
one fight and then save
three rooms okay
free worms one remote free worms one or
two okay well in any case it's close
okay a couple more ones in the invisible
boss
I strippers okay the the invisible ones
okay
he also welcome to spoiler me the color
if you know
before
eyes
sounds so close but
okay
that one was not ice
foreign
I feel like not even worth to go back
healing now that's okay oh because even
we're even getting a freebie
there must still be more because the
music is still playing
[Music]
please stop walking around fine
oh I see one there that sounds yellow
foreign
ly come from behind is he please not
some of them are really smart and they
just show up out of nowhere
there's one more and the one though
I just
oh my friend
around all right
yes
yes and almost back to full health again
it's not that scary Chihuahua it's not
that scary
[Music]
not that scary no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
no no no no
no no no
I'm love still breathing in you realize
that to survive
I need to save at every place
unit identical Blue Elite pirate oh no
Elite pirate obsoons propensity for face
and hands they don't wake up yet thing I
think okay enabled our research team to
infuse it far beyond our safety research
and Center results have been extremely
encouraging it's constant it's constant
phase and diet has increased and
increased its mass exponentially but it
has retained all mental faculties and
shows dexterity with all Elite weaponry
including plasma incendiary launches and
the chameleon Manta issued for cloaking
purposes what the [\h__\h] Elite pirate
Epsilon exhibits miraculous healing
abilities when injured in six out phase
and deposits and coats itself in the
substance which instantly amends the
creatures wounds the subject which we
are code naming Omega pirate based on
these developments shows potential to be
a new standard for our armies our only
concern at this point is its potential
over dependence on Faison
um
I'm scared
[Music]
you guys said they don't come out yet
right
because I can scan this one in red
oh no
okay it's the other side never mind I'm
so scared
okay this way don't
don't [\h__\h] [\h__\h] at me
where am I
ready
mind I'll help here
probably what what
ah
no that's what I should have come from
there's a door behind this
[Music]
there should be oh there is one on the
bottom
you can do this we have we have so much
HP
nothing can go wrong it's a safe point
before the bus or after
very important
after that is so
after but it's easy what the boss fight
or to get into the same point afterwards
I'm here
yeah I'm right there I'm being slow on
purpose what did you really just show me
what's right in front of me
she's like [\h__\h] come on
hi honey
my mom right there
is this the boss fight room
see a coast I see a ghost
missile super missile is that the one
from the yellow one
[Music]
is that the boss it's not deposited
facing processing and security systems
are taxing the dynamic Beyond safety
tolerances
okay it's not scaring the ninja okay
it's a mini bus okay though the
conversion to geothermal Powers using
using the drain on our systems it is not
enough further power used at current
levels could lead to system failure
[Music]
blah blah blah
do I just do I just jump down
okay
what if I shoot now
what
did I finally fail I thought I found it
a little bit too early
you guys oh
is this like the bomb upgrade thingy
yeah
laughs
wave Buster absolute destroyed
me
okay
this is like a puzzle like a maze
oh yeah
there's even fun music with it
don't get hot
one of the doors is safe on yay so you
could have totally fought him in other
ways too right you don't have to use
this wave Buster but this is just a
the easiest way to do it huh
you say I wouldn't even have had to farm
HP but I feel like if I wouldn't have
the fact that I had so little HP would
have made me so nervous
that I would have [\h__\h] up even you
know when it's not necessary where I
could have totally done it
you know
[Laughter]
just like now
that was not the right path oh no how
can it not be
oh the other path was also noted
bomb the water oh
interesting
careful this feels like a Zelda breath
of the wild dungeon
you know when you have to control a ball
with motion controls by tilting a field
will I [\h__\h] up again yes I will yes I
will yes I will
[Music]
okay
this is speed run killer oh I want to
see someone speedrun this
I want to see something on speed run the
whole thing man
I got really interested in like speed
runs
for games in general like
especially with tunic
I used to just not really
like
get it in terms of like if you ah what
what am I doing if it's only
for the sake of doing a speed run I
don't get it but with a game that you
like really really love and you play it
so much and I don't know
especially a game like tunic
I think I kind of get it but if it's if
it's a speed run where you have to
glitch everything those super glitchy
speed runs
I'm like
[\h__\h]
I'm like nah
nah that sucks do it for real for real
do it without glitches that's what I
want to see
this is where I needed old HP for not
for the mini boss that we saw
we needed for
I need the four dollar this little maze
there are different categories yeah I
know I know
you're getting excited watching me 10 to
the runs the stuff yeah me too me too
oh
blow it up
cute hit that little jump
oh
[Music]
Rumble Chris R to release a power bomb
can destroy tougher materials and morph
ball again okay cool y'all
your thumb
it's a safe room
I am so happy
is it that one
or the other one
there's two
other one
I'm such a happy ball
oh
[Music]
um
I should use the missiles
slowly losing it was slowly losing it
but I wanna do that boss I feel like
after that bus I might end it because
it's only been five hours and it doesn't
feel that long today to me
but I gotta Read Super chats you know
that it's 9 P.M
now we'll see yeah I think it would be a
good point to end it though wouldn't it
be
that's for the hardest part really that
was hard
really
[Laughter]
here she calls flexing again after she
was freaking out for everything yeah
absolutely true but but
but
I expected a bit more oh my God
wow
backtracking okay yeah I guess we'll
we'll go back to the ship at least after
killing the boss
can you not
die
what the [\h__\h] is the matter with these
cameras
box will take a while for real wait did
I say it
did I see it
I did okay
oh there's three cameras
thank you
okay
ah oh there's a ball hole here now
just get this I have stuff on it
it's gone
[Music]
why is there a ball hole here
you can sneak under them and turn them
off
what is this
oh like this
well
I was too late
what's with these boxes
ah you turn them off here don't you
oh man maybe on the way back then
I'm so happy I saved oh
I
was just cutscene this is normal space
pirates
oh no
match words
that's what they wanted to show me
you need to Bachelor for free items no
no no no no no no no no no no you're
just onion sweet though you just want me
to stay long all right you don't want me
to leave
cute
but no we'll go straight unless unless
it's on the way if it's on the way then
I'll get the backtracking things
wait I should have looked what colors
they were
that's
is that yellow
are they yellow
I want
that one's purple and the other one is
like greenish though
uh maybe that one's regular and the
other ones
purple so I'll just go for purple then
oh maybe they're normal
[Music]
okay I feel so much more relieved after
the same file oh my God
oh but now there's some more towards how
I forgot like um last episode last time
we streamed this it was around the end
of it that I dealt with the Metroid and
I already don't remember how to fight
them
it was some special way to do it right
and when you when when they catch you
then you have to turn into a ball and
explode or something all right
Maybe
ice missile
oh see that we didn't have that last
time
okay they don't like cold wonderful
oh is that charge for them
uh super bomb
it looked fancy
oh okay
you're not gonna use engagement
first feel engaged
command panel version oh
quite a disengage force field
you need to you need to backtrack before
doing buzz what
I have to or it's recommended to
you have to oh dear okay
ah my short containment anyway will be
wonderful wonderful yeah let's do it
let's do it let's test our new method
out oh no
[Music]
oh they're coming oh Lord
yes
that's it
not that scary after all
once again
as I said oh this is like looks like a
riser worlds here
I could pick up some items here okay
well why are you so slow again me me me
me
or is it just because okay you're done
with this area now let's go far far far
far far away live growth
sat with the bosses
am I done here is that what she's saying
this place is beautiful though
purple cute
not touch
nope
nope nope nope
go for grapple
ah for here we need grapple
it's amazing oh [\h__\h]
Radioactive Radioactive
[Music]
foreign Towers
I'm done here right
okay
got the grapple on the way out
oh
so Sam that must be something that I can
open with the you are really not lying I
thought you were being cute
so really it's something where I have to
make go boom yeah yeah okay
hope you find the item I hope so true
we're backtracking so that will be oh
some enemies again
little [\h__\h] four of them
oh [\h__\h] it
ah [\h__\h]
that woman is hell
[\h__\h] it
what
wait what wait why why they don't
get
it
yeah what the [\h__\h]
okay
I I see one is so so so slow
oh it's gone okay
okay
let's go
it's good
not so bad you know
it's confusing me a little bit why
sometimes
it's working better than other times
maybe that's just me
[Music]
yeah for five hours in and so my um
I feel like you know at least I'm like
really warmed up now but at least
tomorrow
um
we are
already playing again so there's not
like many days in between
foreign
but not really
[Music]
continue in tomorrow
not before I killed the boss of the day
no
yep I'm stupid thank you
probably won't finish tomorrow
[Music]
well after we end today
would be cool if somebody could tell me
like what the realistic estimate is
judging by my
progress
until
then
10 hours
two streams
where am I
what is this room
up
monsters
[Music]
uh
just the the yellow one would work right
probably
super missed out which one is that the
is that the purple one or the yellow one
probably the purple one
oh yeah the other one okay
what the [\h__\h]
oh oh it's in his hand
oh but the Chargers team doesn't [\h__\h]
that was faster
okay are they gonna send me the other
ones too no just this one really wanted
out
okay
I would have been fine
[Music]
totally
not yet maybe next time I come by here
did you know I miss thinking about
playing my thread this one did she say
that like yesterday or so in their
stream
why don't you say that oh
last stream oh oh that's uh don't don't
leak members to me
don't like that
I mean to me maybe yes but not too
the US oops it really do oh well
be cool though if she plays this
wait I'm I'm the only thing I really
need is missiles
thank you
okay
next room has Health upgrades
just run through again I suppose but
ball because don't I have to go up with
like
side side
power bump in the middle
or this this
what
no not in the middle
wrong spot
oh
maybe here I see some cracks here
right near Dublin
here
there's clear air flowing from this
bindassium grade
hmm
does that mean I should do it there on
the on the gate
okay does that fix the air problem
no it doesn't what the [\h__\h]
huh
jump at the other end huh
what it was a dead end
oh you can't even see that huh
fans online yeah they are they're all
here online
they better not be offline I'm clearing
fumes yay
alive
um
yeah the game is so dark
complete compared to when you played it
oh
also there's like you know just personal
monitor settings but I don't know if I
generally don't know if my
monitor is too dark or too
actually is there something else here
no right
just know that my other monitor has like
completely different
oh
like saturation oh
saturation settings
which will be nice for the boss
okay
whoops
[\h__\h] now put more on
here
too far
I hate this I hate this oh
pinball jaw
not hot
spooky music
[Music]
how to fight them again
all right
look at me doing this with zero damage
[Applause]
yeah
that's how it's done
there's more
music's still going this morning
she on the ceiling
what
you can't reach me from there buddy
I
thought
waiting for him
oh
every time so much Panic it's not good
for my heart
why does more
okay I'll give you a shortcuts I think
oh no maybe not I don't know
why do I still get so surprised when I
know they're coming but it's like I
don't know from whereas suddenly they're
like right in front of my face
I'm sorry they are very spooky okay
uh which way
what's the sign
what is that sign there
uh internet does that sound is an
elevator
what I thought that was e
h
okay
oh straight black
not everyone though
we're back
are you
you know yesterday
which way do we go
yesterday I had this like self-care
evening after
it comes and goes
unopened ice there ah okay okay
that makes sense thank you sorry
yesterday after the cabinets finished
the second one we thankfully finished
way faster than the first one
uh I I cooked
my [\h__\h] it's too dark what the [\h__\h]
and I cooked and it went really well
no but before that I took a nice nice
shower and then I normally when I don't
do I normally don't put like body lotion
on but you know people one of the
favorite gifts people like to do give is
body lotions and stuff like that right
so I have like so many too
but I never use it because my skin is
plenty soft as according to toys and buy
it
my skin is plenty soft without it
wait should I keep my should I keep my
tangent until you guys all hear me
were you crying why are you crying
because they miss me
don't go this way you'll miss grapple
beam
Oh Oh I thought I mean I thought that
was what we're doing
wrong way anyway
uh
I can't see
I love how this ball comes with LEDs
it's like a car
your pals are okay rest or not damn
okay
so grapple is Dooku
the other one door or something
[Music]
I'll tell you the tangent just give it a
moment
purple though okay
[Music]
shut up
I don't wanna I don't want you to tell
me
what
nanny
wow in the distance
I'm dying the only cure is tangents it's
really the most oh you're you're teasing
you're teasing the others
what where is this what the [\h__\h] is this
huh thanks for telling me I have no idea
what that is
right above me
oh
oh man hi hi everybody who's not able to
see me right now hello
[Music]
did I miss it no I've been waiting
U.S West Coast stuttering a lot unusual
Long mobile in Germany still working
fine the stream isn't even cutting out
for that long
foreign
the Europe to na link is down
you can identify who your ebros are I oh
you're sweet
a nice way to meet each other
are you back
welcome back you missed a tangent about
me and body lotion
find an EST
imate
I have this room
you're back are you really bad now
honestly we all complain about
YouTube all the time you know Neil Susan
Neil Susan and all that but I feel like
recently there's a certain other website
that's doing worse than YouTube so I
ain't complaining
foreign
got that one
maybe if I stand here
right
yeah I can't get it
we'll just go for it
oh wow
are you guys for real fine now
I mean if you hear it then that means
you're fine right
anymore there can't only be one
all fine
there it is
come on
why do you not even want to fight me
what's wrong with you you used to be so
aggressive
do we just go down by the way
I love how there's like by the way thank
you so much I love how there's so many
people who know the game by heart
go right
uh here
white door
what there's a question mark in here in
this room
blow up rocks oh
oh
still lagging but you keep going okay
I'll tell you I'll tell you
so yeah yesterday I had a really good
evening so
you know I felt very accomplished after
finally I had those cabinets done and
then I I filled them up first
I had one one
um
that didn't really do anything ah except
for this
do I have to align the yellow ones now
though
foreign
cardboard box
in my bathroom for like forever that I
just didn't
I just did not stand at the top oh okay
but I just never
um
yeah so now is that really nice to
finally put everything into the
to some proper cabinets but
uh the thing is I I'm I we decided to
not
um like Hammer Hammer or to attach the
cabinets onto the wall so they're just
freestanding and on its own they're like
sturdy and they stand really nicely but
when you open
both drawers
then it will lose its balance and like
Drop forward so I can only open one at
once gonna be really careful there
wasn't this one fine the way it was
because I already connected it to the
top one
then I just have to change the bottom
one
yeah they tip they do have like a
attachment thingy
on their back
but I I didn't want to do it because I
didn't want to damage the tiles
of the wild side because I I don't I
don't know like I didn't want to bother
with like having to fix it afterwards
if I've ever move out
so we just left it this way and then on
its own it was totally fine but once
you're like
if you're not careful but I mean I I
know how to use it so I'll be careful
I think I'll be fine you need to do
right again
I'll need to do red again oh I finally
have to do a yellow one
wait so
Nani
top one isn't connected okay I thought I
had to see the yellow one
this one's connected already not sleep
oh where am I going
or Disco
nowhere
but I attracted uh a little monster
yeah it ended promised so I need to do
right again first [\h__\h] how do I get up
again
okay I ran again from the bottom
this time
okay now this will take a while
um okay so I I filled everything in then
I took my vacuum cleaner oopsie stayed
like that and then I cleaned
um my whole bathroom uh I cleaned all
the things and everything and even
cleaned the toilet which I don't use so
why would it need cleaning but you know
I did everything so properly
yeah got so excited having
my bathroom finally looked nice why am I
calling him
and then I vacuum clean some more other
rooms not every rooms just the ones I
really needed it
eh
oh yeah mint bread is misaligned but
like lots where do I bring the bottom
one now then I don't get it
that was blue huh
what this free colors I thought there
was only two
I thought they were only two
can you use a little box
yes meow I told me I'll pop meow
blue blue
well the middle red one is fine for now
right until it reached the top
or should I change it
just Layton okay
[\h__\h]
okay one more time for my attention
so uh clean diver's paint and then I
took a nice shower in my beautiful
bathroom
and then I cooked really confidently and
that went really well too so I was
really happy about that too
and it turned out so good and you guys
were all like oh my God so good quinoa
oh but after the shower yeah the body
lotion is I put body lotion all over
koala because normally I don't use body
lotion but suddenly I felt like using
body lotion all over my chihuahua uh
chozo body because there's so much body
lotion right everybody gives it to the
body lotion even though nobody no human
in this world needs so much body lotion
but this is like the most most popular
present
to give to somebody but if you guys ever
give me a press and please don't give me
body lotion I mean you can't anyway but
if you so happen to be in such a
situation please don't give me body
lotion because I already have a shirt
ton of body lotion
I don't need body lotion generally
anyway so never use it I don't need it
because Toma said I already approved of
my
of my perfectly softness
away now
so on the top is only yellow
so now
the top yellow and the middle yellow is
lined
is that how I wanted
giant skincare yeah yeah so I did body
lotion but I don't really need that but
then I also did
um a whole
whole face facial
uh mask thingy
ah
must point away from a line with the
where is that
okay we'll see
so I had this like gray stuff on my on
my face
felt nice at first and then not so nice
I do it like with a brush I brush over
my face it feels nice feels quite nice I
recommend no no cucumber slices
where do I make it go just say stop guys
how about how about now
just top now it's great to chill on the
bath with a good Facebook yeah it's
pretty nice stop stop now
oh is there a delay
stop
okay
so I did that and then and then then
and then and then of course I also put
after after the
face mask of some lotion on my face some
night lotion some fancy lotion that I
normally don't use either because I
always forget those spaghetto
there we go
so big self-care after that satisfying
Furniture creation but also even vacuum
cleaner so there's it was some
relaxation and there was also some
self-care and also some
the efficientness
efficient hard work yes yes because I
helped a lot
with the furniture put together process
as well
wasn't only my brother I helped a lot
more than I normally do so I am I'm
quite proud okay
very productive
yeah and then and then I made the phone
no I didn't make the phone now but then
put up the Stream
I enjoyed my food it was really good it
was a good evening felt like wow I am
living the life
as it should be
oh is that really necessary all that
aftermath
oh crap
[Music]
one more thing to think about
well I won't use this in battle will I
please say no
Thank you new power
um
don't think so not really okay
cool
yeah
what where's the grapple
which one how do I use it
oh
can it be any of my
any of my uh lasers
oh yeah I think so
should I go this way
close this place
just like a tall talk yeah I'm trying
I'm really trying to get a date
we're working on it actually let me see
did I get a reply no okay but I got
replies on the other things I'm
initiating the Wither thing again I've
been asking for a date and I've been
initiating
um
uh a girls a new girl's talk date as
well
but uh well probably both will probably
not happen until middle or like end of
uh next month
who's this
do I break this
huh I didn't do anything I thought I
could break the glass
so what wait here left no
hmm
uh-huh
now I I realized because I wanted to get
as the next girl guest I wanted to get
good on right
but you know when I was planning some
things today
you know I wrote to the Viva Group which
is basically mume uh fauna good at me
and then I wrote next I wrote to the
girl style group and then I realized on
it
if I invite gouda than with a river
group and the girls talk group is
exactly the same group
and considering everybody's like
availability dates I realized oh
then both will kind of happen at the
same time
and I don't really like that I want
things to be more balanced I don't want
to spam
the same collab Partners in the same
week or two
Snook
so I decided to maybe invite someone
else first before I go down
she'll be there eventually
um so I wonder who who's like really
girly who I should get ideas also fine I
was thinking maybe Zeta I don't know if
she's girly but somehow the image I have
of her is she's kind of girly I don't
know could be wrong though
[Music]
Cali
I guess she has some girly things about
her
Iris Anya
Kyla
I mean they almost strike me as that
girly Cali does some things that make
her very girly surprisingly though yeah
we'll give you a chance to talk to Zeta
more I was thinking
like because I haven't really had
a chance to talk much with her
Smokey wins calm the [\h__\h] down okay
I think it's just nicer to space it out
it's not like I'm like completely uh
giving up on the
on the collab I'm just like spacing it
out
[Laughter]
chill
hmm
no no I see thank you for your
recommendations there's also actually a
secret and another secret guest that I
have lined up for girls talk
but I'm not sure what exactly is gonna
happen but please wait
um maybe that one will actually come
first I'm not sure
no no no no no no
oh you will see and you will thank me
because I am a genius you will thank me
for it that's one of the genius things
I've been planning
last night
anyway what am I doing where am I
there's a safe Point down there let's
just first kill them all was I supposed
to come here is this the ideal thing
come here
[\h__\h] help
yeah be my test object
ah
that's how it should be thank you
it's a shortcut now
let's see this
how does it work again
am I too far
I know it works
where is he
oh look at that
but I can't see him ah yeah
wasted
more
what
you can save now yes let's go
let's go
I mean I didn't feel like it was such a
big issue right now but okay okay
prepare yourself for one hell of a fight
if you are where I think you are
oh yeah I know I'm aware that I am close
to a boss fight yeah
but didn't somebody say I have to get
like free items I only got the grapple
hook so far I think or or did the energy
tank count as one I'm not sure
I am not close I'm one or two hours away
what the [\h__\h]
all right
okay uh
where are we going
you have to go back to my ship
I'm gonna go into elevator
Maybe
I need extra advisor and plasma B
elevator okay
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
for now elevated and life grow
[Music]
let's start for today
um
I just wonder like how much progress
I'll make tomorrow and how much will be
left over
if I knew all of that it would be easier
to plan it all out
and tomorrow you can finish if I kill
the boss today you think I can finish
tomorrow hmm
most people don't think so
I don't mind
finishing the boss today though because
um
are already cooked yesterday and I have
leftovers from it so
funky music
[Music]
made way more purpose than I expected
you might be able to do it oh okay I
don't mind like going really long
tomorrow either I can prepare
some food maybe
how you feeling someone keep going yeah
I'm like actually really feeling fine
like I'm not feeling too mentally
exhausted yet
just have to keep on asking guys where
to go but hey this is where I need to go
is that the very top
foreign
funky funky
basket will give me more energy I don't
know what is this
oh
[\h__\h]
up
to the top
[Music]
whoa
where's next
oh yeah the raindrops are a nice
addition am I gonna play with these
now maybe
that
is this the same spot as before where
I'm like what
where to go
to come pull up the pillar
ah here this is where I went
the last time I was struggling a lot
um
here
[Music]
it's not really it the door I was going
for
oh yes
I had to I thought I had to blow
something up
oh well maybe I do
oh this one
ah
gotcha oh
[Music]
um
I guess I'll go down oh ah okay thank
god oh that's something new
which way
oh wait
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
right away maybe
there's a secret missile maybe that's in
the
[Music]
it's not the right way right it's
probably up on the left
how high can I go no wait
is it just
just somewhere here no
no at the top of the hot pot
but I feel like I almost had it
am I just just doing this kind of wrong
is there like a better way an easier way
of doing it
boosting too early
I don't feel a difference
really speedwall at at the middle
release Boost after the middle
oh
action why do I even
I hate this
can't just not
I don't like it
just the Boost button don't put in
movement
does it get any higher than this
[Music]
I couldn't get this one either
man I don't know
[Music]
this one's hard
ah that felt like that was split but
like
[Music]
oh
well
you know I'm a panic baller
even when I'm already a ball
I [\h__\h] too late
started too early and released
[\h__\h]
oh oh God
ah
[\h__\h] ah I'll never get up there again
I can't look at it anymore
please save me
uh I don't know this I don't know the
timing anymore
[Music]
I understand
ah yeah I'm not moving this I'm not
moving the stick anymore
[Music]
try with eyes closed okay
well how will Noah got there
I got like really high
what
How will I know though
well no better to look
better to look
a shut up
no no no
I'm just getting worse at this now
um
[Music]
foreign
okay and now move on
oh
on it
advisor here
what
hmm
[Applause]
Noni
uh what how do I I forgot how to
activate
oh
really what the [\h__\h]
is bad
I don't see anything
what's hunting
oh
wait wasn't I able to see that anyway oh
yeah
[Laughter]
I thought I like made like a fast
morphobia phasmophobia moment
there's an art effect in here that I can
get
[Music]
yeah in here
in here you say
C for solid material
oh oh wow this this one I can't this one
I can
that's weird
fake walls can oh is this a fake wall
does that mean because I can look
through it it's a fake wall
oh my God that is incredible
is that where I will be getting my ass
my
artifact from
what is this room what is this oh it
doesn't
show up on the map
go in the water
ball big boom
super secret not tonight
no no no no no no
did that just move
oh
that's how our defects look like
this is it
oh finally I thought you guys didn't
exist I thought it was just a myth
I
wait I'll get you
I'll get you
I will get you
wait for me
wait wait
I will get you
[Music]
my second one
seven of twelve what oh oh number seven
oh but so I have it I don't have to like
bring it I can't lose it or so
oh get ready for use the visors
I don't want to see ghosts
is that all that this room is good for
[Music]
the secret one I mean that's plenty but
are they all gonna be hidden in secret
rooms
now I can leave okay
if I if I I mean no I may leave but if I
can
that is the other question
did did teachers in school ever like
answer you like this when you ask can I
go to the toilet our teachers sometimes
were like being extra smart about it and
said I don't know if you can but you you
may
maybe you can still
depends on you buddy
yeah oh can you stop
man
yeah in German they do the same [\h__\h]
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's like a teacher
joke
dad jokes teacher jokes oh wait a second
what is this
just a way to get back or
that's the way back
what [\h__\h]
[Music]
does not work on them
does it work oh yeah bye
only Power beam uh wait was that the
purple strong one
and then yellow one okay oh
all right
what the [\h__\h] oh that's my head I
thought before that like one of them was
like behind me and holding my head oh
[\h__\h]
oh my gosh
so many times I get bamboozled by myself
we're done now because I'm running out
of missiles oh yeah we are
hmm
okay so maybe go to the top again
how did I get there
here
's y'all please
you see the hand signs that are on the
beams icons you can see her hand doing
the gesture for each beam
no idea what you're talking about
[Music]
come on now is there gonna be any other
ghost mobs
any other different type
I don't know what you mean
a hand inside the gun
makes the hand signs
oh
wait I mean
the left hand
I don't know what you mean does it
matter
I'm in the left hand
inside the camera let's see inside the
cannon I mean
the cannon you know never changes
depending on the beam yeah yeah
ah
ah very slightly
yeah very slightly
hard to see
um
that's how she controls it that's cool
cool cool cool
oh no platforming my biggest enemy
but I feel like I'm maybe worse at
platforming when it's
not
first person
I feel like the fact that this first
person makes it easier for me to see
where I am
maybe that's not true
I wonder if there's a girl mod oh maybe
I shouldn't
so turn it into
uh not a first person but like a first
person game
people make interesting things
oh sure
[Music]
like portal oh yeah yeah yeah
hello what is this
huh
[Music]
did you just drop me
just don't
why why does it do that
why does it do that
what does that mean
is there anything we're going up there
for
you way back too what
that look it wasn't the accent it just
threw me there what
what
felt like that was just the most Savage
move of this bird like I make my way up
there and it just drops me down again
I'm so confused
my jump button did not work I need a new
controller
oh now I'm starting to lose it
that was the accident
like it just threw me down for jokes and
giggles
seems like we are done with the bunny
didn't we just let open a wall and then
break through why why can't we just like
go back that way I don't understand
where we are what do we what are we
doing
so
[Music]
I I should go from here again
is that what you're saying
on this swing
oh
by the way well you know it's been six
and a half hours you can expect me to
lose battery and my batteries to lose
battery and my controller to lose
battery and a new you know my controller
to lose control and me to lose control
and my batteries to lose control and
yeah
yeah you know
you know
how to
is it gonna be enough to kill the boss
because I don't know where my cable is
this x-ray here for hidden platform
I have to compare what do I say and what
do I not see
[Music]
uh
no way you can kill this boss of low
battery oh [\h__\h]
it's just getting the final beam and
spent the rest reading the supers maybe
I'll do that if
they'll have to find the cable and
charge
Lorraine gives it away too
oh
well that's even with the x-ray vision
is kind of hard to see
Mommy
okay
[Music]
successfully missed it
again what
is this a ghost
can I you know
alrighty maybe from here
[Music]
why is everything
see
okay I see it
oh
and now over there
let's go one door I have not been
through yet
oh my God what
great that's a good thing when you can't
see
so good
[Music]
what
here
okay come on
how can this be the most frustrating
part of the day
foreign
landed on it
what do you mean
I still doesn't
leave me over there though does it
[Music]
oh first try
missiles
[Music]
mama
yeah that was first try
okay now I continue going back
more backtracking uh here at kfp we
absolutely love backtracking
of course we do
yeah
150 more missile capacitors to go what
150.
divided by five
is like
wait wait
what pretty
what what's this party
what
like what
divided by five
[Music]
okay
whatever whatever
it's been a long day
hmm
am I going the right way guys
where am I going
to maybe say first right
was that thing just swagging his tail
when I went by it
makamura now okay
around allow you to see some space
but even then he only says 75 percent
hey if you get every like if you get 100
or only if you get all upgrades
okay
that's cute
100 for secret ending yeah yeah okay I'm
not gonna do it though I can't anyway
how do I get to Macklemore
here
that's so far my God
is this where I need to go
transport to Magmar North
tell himself
Helen North
oh that's talent East
for challenge faster
should we go for Talon East
it's too far okay
Talon East
Town East
Town East in East
ah it's pretty safe point
about the same space okay
I will take me near my ship is that what
we want well did we get wait we got all
the upgrades I wanted right now right
so
need one more is that on the way
I already saved
it's in magmore but then I should go for
more not for Town should I
or is it close to what
it's easier to get there from there okay
run you got no battery
where are your controller
enemies
[Music]
why am I aim don't go
I missed out low [\h__\h]
I've been so slow
do you need to rest
I always need to rescue
wow always need dressed
myself
oh
and there's a grapple thingy here
I wonder
[Music]
this is the shortcut
oh
[Music]
I already got the missiles here
apparently
[Music]
markmore caves East
JoJo ruins West
okay ah
Marianne thank you hello from MX
family trip we're going to Europe
[Music]
again
what's this with the rise of innsbrucker
these days
what I cannot give you in any
recommendations because I don't think
I've ever been to insul before
but I guess it's nice as I have
found out recently
oh
this Hook is in oh it's like it's the
hip place to be right now I suppose what
the [\h__\h] why is this I like the travel
agencies offering cheap travel packages
to in stock or what is going on
oh
well have fun I really can't help you
though
I don't I don't know much
where where am I where am I going
phase online
chosen ruins
tools are ruined
mock Market oh man so
right next to me on the left
this map
this map is
any thoughts or plants about ever going
to soccer wait isn't that like a one of
those northern northern European comes
Finland or
Iceland or
something
I feel like I'm
heard of it before
left
I got God
it's a meme
that's why I heard of it before
it's all come
on
thank God I didn't say it
you little [\h__\h]
house Kyle Kyle Kyle first
you little shits
should have known because you donated in
US Dollars there's no way you're gonna
tell me about a northern European
convention are you oh [\h__\h] low battery
okay seems like we're not doing the box
today
he was in the room for a year
yes no no eight months
oh boy
I didn't get caught it I didn't say the
whole thing
oh
I'm at 99 missiles and 99 Health what
amazing
so in sync
feels good
you just need to stay once
you and your funny gamer meme jokes man
you look under the bridge here I don't
know
well enough the next Pinterest means
it's really satisfying to kill enemies
with it oh
next beam must be a really strong one
but won't the enemies be kind of
adjusted to it although not the old ones
that I and I have to keep on
backtracking so that's the thing that's
fun
where am I where am I going who am I
I am in magmog
do we go left or right left or right
there's a question mark here do I have
to go here I must go here probably
once again seems like we're having
issues
with YouTube
is there a shortcut here for the grapple
now
no
One Direction
oh they're also streaming
most of people being designed purely for
combat oh
uh is that sign leading me to the boss
fight or to the new
new beam
[Music]
a new beam okay
I think he's thinking
all right this serves as a shortcut now
oh I can't turn directions
and I can't get more momentum either
uh-huh
[Music]
you may want to scan the room
you can't turn the original I tried
maybe only if you're still
there's an artifact there
and the previous room are in this one
no okay even if we can do it next time
[Music]
we're in the room
oh
all right
where's the grapple give it to me I'm
here
give it to me at once
Puzzle Time
oh I see a grab a grapple and what am I
saying not grapple I already have a crap
you know what I mean
[Music]
puzzle oh
um
I got squashed if I
roll out of this
whatever
oh wait what
did something
and even the PGM changed because it's
like I know what you're doing
time possibly damn time
I believed
this is really a puzzle though
don't I just have to bring all of them
to the top as high as they can go
and then I jump on to the next one
well this one's already I already did
now I jump onto this one
more like an obstacle course yeah that's
that's more like it
that's only the first part okay
this is just like
putting the furniture together yesterday
just like that the screws yeah yeah yeah
it's exactly like that legit for real
okay but now
I can't get much higher
what oh wait oh
[Music]
I know
jump over there
what
it
oh
oh my God
what on Earth
don't fall down keyboard don't
good luck enjoy
I'm gonna kill this bastard before I go
there
both of them all of them
[Applause]
I can't think they are immune
only bumps can kill them
should I really just let go
all right let's go
[Applause]
oh no
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] do I get back up
how do you go back up
skip nine hours to see me make the next
room wait can I just go back with a
grapple
okay
and the rest is just normal jumps
oh not so bad
well at the beginning now I'm gonna fall
no more
no more falling down no no no
I'm gonna first try it now
just look at me
look at me do it
if anything the reason I would fail
would be because of my controller
oh God
how do I do this
do I let it go first and then jump
what do I make a bomb I make a bomb
while still holding on to
oh
okay but the problem is there's monsters
here but I can I could fall down here
and then kill them
and then jump back up again
[Music]
it's making this makes my palm swipe I I
thought you meant plants and then like I
don't know because of Palms Palm Trees
but your plants are gonna use money
and remember only bombs can kill them oh
Goodbye Oh
all right but they have like a set tab
okay take this
boom
it's all good
yeah
do I jump at the end
or do I just press that enough I wonder
goodbye what
just hold
oh my God
I'm also very sweaty on my Palms right
now
I went here I just
[Music]
oh
that's such a small space
[Music]
the second like roll everywhere here it
seems
except for like the the mountain part
probe
oh I'm gonna fall but you fall down you
have to do all the skin
um yeah
[Music]
yeah
oh trust fall
yummy
I'll do it here I think
I guess I'll just hold it
[Music]
I'm just a little ball
Mommy what's this
this kind of diagonal are you [\h__\h]
me
uh
play
um against the time with my controller
have I reached it
what if I fall down now
don't be don't be clumsy now
how about first
while I'm up here
while I'm like hanging
how do I use it again or
okay yeah okay this way when I fall down
I can't like like you know oh
ah
[Music]
what's the ever after that first fall
yay
[Music]
yay yay
um
which one is it the red one
whoa fire baby fire
nice basically it's lava I'm shooting
lava
awesome platform thank you my my fingers
were holding on to dear life
okay can I go down and find a safe Point
again now
it's pretty close I could go to that one
I think I'll go to that one
let's go
[Music]
but even if we didn't get the box
I think we still do much much progress
wait wrong way
better still doesn't work
I was just like extra extra
careful whoa
[Music]
crew out that's hard but you guys said
ah this Pine is really scary this part
be careful and be careful about this
part that made me worry so much
thank you
maybe we overhyped it
um
wait
Let's test this out oh they're like on
fire because that one stayed red that
one up there
that do they get fire burning damage or
so
hey they burn
careful better oh yeah
um
okay okay
I mean the game one just once just
suddenly ends so it's okay but um yeah
you know my switch always stays on
anyway
yo yo yo
Invincible
come on do it
or don't
thank you
for the recipe Chad the sequence break
the game and get plasma without
despiteable
let's jump on parts
here we go
[Music]
foreign
game has been saved
pray for my controller that I can charge
it until tomorrow I'll have to find a
cable
s are like everywhere after traveling
no idea what is where no anger wow today
yo
not like what I expected in the
beginning today I was like
something's feeling wrong today
oh you know what tomorrow's first day
right oh tomorrow's my Korean lesson
I gotta I gotta practice after I wake up
yeah but does it really charge
when it's not connected to the switch
can it even be charged when it's
connected just to the to a normal power
outlet
really hmm
I tried that does the same thing apply
to the PlayStation 5 controller
foreign
[Music]
it's a weird cable that sometimes works
sometimes it doesn't
it's a new one though oh well okay
[Music]
apparently the boss was
further ahead than I thought it was
going to be
so
um
let's go I think like we'll go to my
office
or just check
if everything is okay I think so
I think so
ah
muted the wrong thing hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
wow thank you guys again for all the
cool artwork for Samus Wawa I changed
the Fountain of the previous stream but
I feel like it didn't
thank you it didn't change did it change
by now
when I
changed it
I didn't right away change it changed
now
okay yeah part two
and then I still have enough
fan art I think
for the upcoming ones if it's gonna be
one or two I'm not sure
even though I didn't kill the boss you
guys it doesn't now mean I have lower
chances of finishing tomorrow
it would be so nice if I could finish
tomorrow
you can
how many I think I finished tomorrow
come here
like there's like little places where
you can look up
um
you can look up like you can see where
you are now and then how much longer it
takes until we end
what what does that say about me
you're able to find the artifact well
you guys will help me find the other
birthday
artifact hunting is apparently long well
it's part of that game
one hour for the bus two to three hours
for artifacts two more hours to end but
that sounds all right six
seven
oh now we finish at seven hours and I
don't mind going a little bit longer
tomorrow if it means I can finish it
okay no that's that's that looks
manageable
hmm
okay
let's try our best I'll need you guys
in perfect form as well
you guys need to know what's up
to help me
go back to the art of Italian I don't
mean you already back sitting everything
anyway but yeah let's backseat the [\h__\h]
out of the artifacts
hmm
nice got the game facts open
of course of course
everything prepared
I should buy like some frozen food
before the stream so that I can eat that
quickly after the stream and I don't
have to cook
but if I go for like until midnight
after eight nine hours of streaming I
probably don't wanna
chat Vines are more discount yeah
probably don't want to cook after that
we believe in you who believes in US ah
it's such a sweet teamwork isn't it
Backstreet Boys back seat boys
and maybe some little little food for in
between because long stream
okay now if we want to be really
efficient Chihuahua gotta focus on
reading some super chants now
to get that stuff out of the way
[Music]
back seats back all right
mm-hmm
[Music]
just quickly do something
all right should I open up like a
little
should I open up the thing again that I
showed last time
spicy chicken butt last one I read
good memory good chicken memory
there's a frog operating the stove how
do you what what are you talking about
only talking about
yeah I love that name spicy chicken bun
um
uh where do I go here
okay so we go to
that after talk blue
and then we go to the someone remember
the number though
I see special I see it 91 us still still
there 91 in front of Trevor G
unky donkey
no
yeah
dinner is served
[Music]
okay
I just want to see the whole text
and you can have this you can see this
whole text on that you can read with me
makes it maybe easier to
understand what's going on
microphone yeah I love this microphone
maybe maybe don't need
okay
hi I saw someone made like a
joke on Twitter
when I cluttered My Stream yesterday so
much and then
to put a little bit more on her screen
but now it looks fine doesn't it
ah
so apparently here
yeah I think I remember this yeah yeah
yeah and this one I did not read
um
ah
oh maybe I did
I feel like around it too
did I it sounds familiar
not just second stream feeling with even
more stuff
they should go see energy since uh yeah
yeah yeah there's some culprits that are
worse than me
I stopped up okay
look at that beautiful beautiful profile
picture wow
ah
going from fruity showcase to four Fest
shortly after it's surreal would love
seeing you perform more often y'all oh
my controller is dying
okay you can you can die now
okay let me just close my capture
okay
love seeing will perform more often live
band Rock twist to do it was cool either
after bounciness is a great contest to
OG outfit love seeing it in motion
motion
choreo always on point felt like your
move showed up better than usual the
Dancehall with full Yen was amazing as
well said the cameraman was zoomed out
for half of it
here is it the butt buff made it to the
idle outfit ah I don't know
overall great job Kiana so proud of my
coming Oshie thank you
[Music]
yeah yeah
I don't know I mean the camera I heard a
lot of people like criticize in the
camera I'm not sure like
it didn't bother me that much I think
or like at all like it didn't stand out
so much to me other things
or like more important to me and I like
seeing the audience I guess I guess it's
a very different point of view to have
like for us we we love seeing you guys
being like really there
in the audience and and cheering
but you guys want to see us
I mean I think it's also cool for you
guys to see the audience every once in a
while
but we have different priorities or like
interests Maybe
yeah
we want to see you guys you guys want to
see us
so it didn't really bother me that much
but I can understand where you guys are
coming from yeah
I mean I
mean I because if it wasn't for them
um you know before the concert started
they showed so many cave people
and that was amazing I was so happy to
see them that makes you like just once
again realize that it's real
um
yeah on two different days even
I was so happy
I feel like there was like one moment on
day one where they showed pretty much in
the beginning still when it just started
they showed
like one close-up of the audience where
it was like one guy and one lady next to
each other
and then everybody was cheering
immediately I was wondering if they were
hoping for a kiss but the two those two
I feel like they didn't understand it at
all was what was being desired
like they were being dense protagonists
but everybody else was getting it like
oh this should this is a kiss cam moment
I didn't even think that this kind of
like
uh culture would go over to Japanese
concerts because I mean aren't they more
shy
but everybody was cheering so hard like
when seeing a couple on the moment they
didn't show them anymore
it just went completely silent
so I'm not sure what the audience was
Desiring at that moment but it felt like
they were hoping for a kiss and just the
tattoo those two people they didn't
understand it at all like they didn't
even seem confused or embarrassed or
they didn't like like gesture like no no
no no no nothing
if they were like siblings of course
they wouldn't have the kids you know but
but they didn't seem like that was their
excuse for not kissing they just didn't
know what was going on
they were just like
yeah I'm just chilling
being dense I think well anyway it was
funny
sadly no kiss for the kiss cam
thank you those best chicken pots thank
you very much for the feedback and the
sweet words I appreciate it
[Music]
one two three random chats and a yellow
one thank you thank you thank you my God
that's too much
first off like everyone else who said
absolutely amazing job Wawa your hard
work paid off you lit up the stage with
both your voice and moves even without
the fire effects you are the whole life
Dancing Queen your moves are so precise
chef's kiss secondly it's my birthday on
the 19th
of March huh
so I'll be paying off my pretty first
birthday with Wawa invoice a bit early
or I want to say thanks these past six
months have been rough to say the least
and you have helped me through it what
happened
it's been my Haven my little Nest to
help stay warm the travel you okay
and hide from the storms to help
distract me distract me if only for a
moment to help me crack a smile on even
the worst what
[Music]
what health icon face swinging that
makes it even sadder
as always thank you one for working as
hard as you do
uh for being a sweet funny dorky you I
appreciate it now for my birthday wish
for while I'll be happy
[Music]
I was curious to see how you feel about
watching a western film one day
Western
you mean like
I mean like my dad
where they stand in the desert and then
shoot
purple
old west
no
I don't know
have you ever watched the rest of cats
wait I think
we've heard this question before and and
uh sure
I wrist don't count
ah
that oldie
[Music]
oh my God so cute
I don't think I really did maybe it's a
child like a really really small child
so that I wouldn't remember now
hmm
has cats that has friends what else you
need not that France is really like
something I desire
watch it as a kid don't remember
anything but the white cat is familiar
yeah so cute they're so cute those
little couples
I recommended before you seem to like
both
maybe maybe
this one but not I wouldn't watch it in
the watch along
but they surely have it on Disney plus
right
in Europe in general
so no well not instead of watching long
hand though I don't think so
there's so many other things I want to
watch with you guys right now
um
thank you so much travertine happy
belated birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to you
and I hope the happiness or the Happy
Days come back to you
you deserve all the happiness you're so
sweet
you're so supportive you're so
respectful
you're really really kind so I hope you
can
get all that back that you give to life
it's only fair thank you very much for
your support hope your birthday was okay
and I hope that the days are looking
sunnier in the future for you
um
please told you all right here yesterday
you have to be happy now
that all makes me sad too
um
no sad happy the only
I can't be I can't be happy if you're
not happy so
to be happy
if you want me to be happy be happy to
care of me
it really breaks my heart when I see
some sad kfp randomly popping up on my
Twitter feed
not saying you guys shouldn't tweet
about it because Twitter is just being
stupid and showing me literally
everything but it makes me sad
you know
when I see you guys openly sad
and I wanna like you know
reply to everyone and be able to help
everyone but I I mean I really shouldn't
like because then people expected from
me to do it for everybody and I can't do
that of course either
so but I also don't want you guys to be
alone and I know that one message for me
would really cheer you up so
I know that I have that effect
on you guys so I want to make use of
that when I see you guys really down
but I can't do that all the time you
know
so don't be sad be happy
okay let's move on
oh it's back in hand thank you for the
rest of the chat confession as of this
time I haven't seen day one yet
I mean I mean hasn't it like
like
um
that's not a big problem
do AOE healing not targeted healing
I don't have an AOE healing skill I
guess no I do my stream but it's not as
effective on every single person
I should be through the vault in a few
hours though I've seen the screenshots
so beautiful congratulations on your big
show thank you yeah that's a long word
you're done by now did you watch the day
two and Deco Nina as well
wasn't in day two but
um
hopefully you got to watch everything
because everything was really nice
it was really good concert both days
really hype really proud to be part of
whole life
yeah thank you spanking Heim for the
support
thank you sure very much
I'll continue
doing my best to make you proud
thank you for the red super chat I'm so
very proud of all of you and of course
my honestly most of all the concert is
full of dynamic and amazing performances
you've all done great things and I'm so
happy to be a whole life fan there's
only one thing left to say really
thank you Bruce
let's ride back attack
that's the most important question
waffle
hmm
croissant I would say to that
right
one more time it sounds really similar
actually
ah thank you so much
thank you for watching me again forever
forever forever
foreign
that dreams come true I'm going to sit
in the corner and quietly Cry tears of
happiness now
um
yeah well I guess you could say it like
that yeah
it's quite quite a dream come true to
perform on such a big venue again and
again
thank you Studio Rob I'm sure
that if you don't stop believing your
dreams will come true as well
[Music]
do you use whole song and dance came out
really well looking forward to The Deco
27 performance and everyone else in the
day two concert also super thanks for
the memberships super cool to see you
dance with all the senpai
yes finally I was really sad that we
couldn't do that last year but this year
we all got to do it even the new ones
that haven't shown their pretty yet
until that point that was really cool of
them
um thank you soon very much thank you
for money there
what's up
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
I want to concert along with other
chickens
it really was a totally different
experience than watching alone because
we can cheer for you out loud like crazy
I was so moved when you were on stage
because I still remember those early
days
I'm glad you guys had fun together I
wish I could be in that karaoke room as
well with you guys
I wish I need to clone myself
and then I'll send the Clone to the
concert
and just me to build kalahoka room
it's continued oh here since I started
watching you you uh I still remembered
it earlier since I started watching you
you were such a warm person yet you only
streamed and now you are on printing
stage of the idol outfit it felt like a
really long journey and that made me
emotional I really wasn't an Idol
concert person but now oh is it a
rainbow
now I'm here cheering for you like crazy
I didn't expect this to be a rainbow
super chat but I feel a lot of things
sorry to say sorry I can't hold myself
in short thank you for everything and
you did so good on the stage love you
and please allow me to finish this
rainbow
[Music]
oh
yeah I'm surprised he also went all the
way to Japan for that but then only
ended up watching it in the karaoke not
in the actual venue
thank you wow hope you made friends with
more kfb chickens
and I hope that even next year you'll
get to watch it at the actual venue or
again with lots of kfb chickens
yeah thank you so much Timo I appreciate
having you as a fan yeah such a talented
person like you thank you thank you so
much
and continue doing my best so please
continue supporting me
thanks for the beautiful rainbow
[Music]
chat thank you I love you dancing so
much thanks for the amazing performance
no thank you
I really enjoyed dancing I wish I had
like better stamina
not so many breathing problems and all
that but
I love it I want to continue like
challenging myself even though it's
really rough
for me nowadays
only getting older only getting
more fragile it feels like
living in pain every day
but I don't wanna
I just want to push myself with that
I was suffering so much
through the wheel even
and
yeah my birthday and not my birthday my
3D showcase
um
can't make people notice that I am old
I'm not young no but I'm definitely out
of shape in terms of like health
[Music]
don't make me think about it makes me
crying about the pain
just want to ignore it well anyway thank
you moose thank you so much for watching
the performance I really appreciate it
thank Christian for supporting the Wawa
mwah
[Music]
Nini diesel thank you for the pinky
can't see the colors
thank you for putting all that effort
into spreading that stuff and like
creating it in the first place
well the Japanese Bros and girls
I was really sweet of you
yeah
trying your best to
you know
help with the community and all that
thank you so much hope you had a great
time at the concert I'm sure you did
Mimi rapping can't be hard she did she
did
thank you so much I'm saying all of it
you seem like such a fun person to be
around so like energetic and happy and
like spreading happiness to the others
that's the impression I get from you and
seeing you in pictures because you
always have the brightest smile on those
pictures
yeah so friendly man
um
sweet
little place thanks for the pinky I
turned 21 today I can legally drink now
let's go congratulations
I can legally drink now did you
illegally drink before that hmm
now that you can drink legally
still
I want to make sure as a straight edge
Idol to tell you to not over drink not
drink too much
and don't drink I've heard I've heard
this the other day I don't know where
but maybe a movie or so but you should
not drink when you're sad but not many
people tend to drink when they're sad
but you should drink when you're happy
I've heard
ideally
um
because I guess you know you think you
can clear up the problems with your
drink when you're sad
that's what you think but it only really
makes it worse
yeah it enhances your emotions you just
feel worse
you feel like you can drown it out
it doesn't help does it
um
for me it's really easy to just ignore
that like I don't even have the interest
in drinking anything I mean there were
some times where I felt like so so so so
so so so so so terrible
that I thought it would be nice to have
something that helps me deal with this
but
you know
didn't
go out to get it
and we'll never but you know
I've seen
people do this
again and again and again
drowning out there or trying to drown
out their emotions
and depression with alcohol and it
really hurts to see
so I hope you guys can
take my words
too hard if you if I'm your OC and what
I say means a lot to you then I really
hope
that this can help you guys
if there's anyone in here that
you know has some issues with that
maybe chihuahuas
opinion may it be kind of
you know
unexperienced with all of that and then
maybe you know not in the position to
judge all of it but still I have I have
many issues and problems to deal with in
life too and I am look at me I I deal
with it differently so there's different
ways to deal with that you don't have to
rely on alcohol or other things that
just make you feel more and more
miserable
there's different things different
things that are more healthy so
yes also cheaper
cheaper as well
um
yeah
thank you for listening to my TED talk
it's really
really important to me
that
you know
people learn to
not use alcohol that way
and if you're already using alcohol that
way then I'm sure that it's difficult to
get out of that
very sure
that it might be a struggle but then
please please please please please
please please try to get
like other supportive ways like get
supportive friends to help you with that
support you with that
get them to get rid of all of your
alcohol at home
and keep track of you know have them
visit your place often and see if you
have some alcohol at home or so
and I know
if you think that would help go get
therapy priming even if you don't think
it would help it will probably help if
you really have a problem
let's not ignore the problem
and let's not create more problems with
that problem
I'll need alcohol I have Chihuahua
exactly that's how it should be
I mean I really I don't know you guys
that well
to know if anyone here has such an issue
maybe somebody felt
something by hearing that or
has a friend or so
that has an issue like that
maybe you could
help them out I don't know I don't know
if it might be too much you know I don't
want to like
push anyone to like push anyone else
to do things they don't want to do and
all that in the end it's still like you
know
your decision your life
but again
look at straight edge kiwawa
if I can do it you can do it you don't
have to turn straight edge but you know
hey no alcohol club high five
if I've been drinking over a year ago
I'll admit the thought of disappointing
my Aussie and my friends who have helped
me help keep me sober does indeed help
me help keep me from grabbing our drink
that's great yay
it was already straight edge before wow
that's quite a lot of straightish people
in my chat wow
birds of a feather flock together huh I
never drink myself I don't think it's
needed I can't even drink I have a liver
condition oh wow
I don't really like to drink alcohol
either
damn
somebody straight and people
drink only with friends and drink I
don't drink by myself yeah that's
awesome
I would say the right way to do it
um
good stuff anyway I don't know why I
went to this whole alcohol tangent I
just felt like I needed to say something
thank you so much I'll be your friends
for two pinkies AKA one red potatoes
um
day one was even better than I expected
oh so many great and very cute
performances and some blew me away like
the crazy powerful only had to massage
yeah
but the best was seeing your dance moves
on the big stage this time more than
just once thank Yago for that it was
just Divine Exquisite today again I feel
blessed to be careful
that was really his only hot summer it
was like
holy [\h__\h] that like really woke anyone
up who was maybe feeling a little bit a
little bit
uh tired like especially the there was a
lot of shouting in that and damn damn
that's the first time I saw only dancing
didn't know she was also such a good
dancer
um
nice nice nice it was epic it was really
epic yeah
Lost Ones Weeping Aya was that the song
title in English
snapped me out of my drowsiness
it was like uh
wasn't it
wasn't it pretty much around the end of
the
it was definitely in the second half
right
it's really quite something
Bruce
sounds good that sounds perfect
the first of the last bunch of bunch of
songs oh
so yeah
big big big Applause to them and thank
you aviar for surprising me
really it's nice to be on a big big big
stage I wanna treasure every single
moment because you never know you never
know
when that will be
not possible anymore
um
so thank you so much I
next time hopefully
you can be there again
[Music]
for the pinky watching the concert
together with a bunch of chickens I care
about and a few I only met for the first
time what a wonderful experience the cut
open room idea was really worth it it
was truly one of my most special KFC
members so far I
have two
pairo
who knows who knows
[Music]
there were two gangs in Japan
yeah sounds like so much fun I'm glad
you could be there by around yeah
I hope you had a lot of fun there
thank you so much for being such a great
kfb member for such a long time to thank
Christian thank you so much
I appreciate it
foreign
was so awesome everything was just
absolutely amazing thank you I mean you
guys may
I've noticed I changed some things like
for again for like some parts I wanted
to be able to go around the stage
and just wave
and also I'll change like the the
bridgepot love hate all the same if you
know play the game just because like
um same for like at the free birthday
and not perfect
showcase
when preparing for that I realized them
I haven't danced this in a while and I
kind of feel like
I can't do it so well and I want to do
it a little bit differently so I really
simplified that part
and and then at the very end
yeah I changed to home way it ends as
well I wanted to do like a
I don't know
a cool model walk but then I realized oh
the stage is really narrow
I can't even go that far
um
just like was walking while standing
yeah the power spread
on the beat and then turn around and
wink
it was calculated but a little bit
miscalculated
oh yeah I'm channeling my inner Sarah
Gutenberg
while doing that
[Music]
was a surprise yup the en group
performance was so cute it is so Emo or
emotional don't be so evil
to see you and the girls performing on
stage the idol outfit is so pretty now
that one is over can't wait for day two
and hold 27. yeah yeah the island outfit
is so nice
I'm really glad you guys like it a lot
too
I feel like
all the new Idol outfits have been
received very positively
so that makes me very happy too
because uh we did have some some input
in the design as well
um
yeah
I mean I already liked it at the first
draft
so I didn't really say anything but the
other girls they gave a lot of input but
we should change this main color and
this and that and remove this part
um they couldn't like answer to
everything
but they try their best to help out with
it and then this is how it turned out
you send references to base mama no no I
was not like
you know they were doing their own thing
this is like way too big
way too big for something
yeah where they can take
you know I mean if they got if they take
my like ideas then they have to take
ideas from everybody too and then that's
a lot of members to take
feedback from from the get-go
so they just like basically come up with
a draft like a quite an advanced draft
already
probably like a rough draft to show to
management only first and then when the
draft is like pretty Advanced already
that's when they showed us
um
yeah too many cooks in the kitchen
exactly that's like
that would be a little bit chaotic and
asking for too much and yeah
can't always take like my personal
interests into account of course and I
wasn't expecting that anyway
but as I said like I was really happy
with the drafts I I think I like the
the style very much because
um I feel like when I look at idle
outfits from certain companies
depending on the company you can really
see they all have a different like style
General Style
like hello project and AKB but also like
Iowa must like like anime Idols Etc they
all
um have its own like character to it
and I feel like with hours
I feel like the the original idol outfit
really had that character to it
now our new ones I feel like they got a
different character than the OG one
it's not so much like oh this is again
such a whole live Idol outfit
it's kind of different and I see I think
I see some
inspirations
I think I see it but it's not like
like blatant
ly dare so obviously not at all still
has like
original spice to it and I really like
it
forgive me
this year uh Ian's costume is my
favorite yeah I mean I prefer two of the
old one but I still would have liked to
have gotten the chance to wear the old
one before moving on to this
would have been nice but I'm happy with
this
hmm
[Music]
like overall
not only when she wears it but even when
the other members wear it and that's
kind of nice I don't know if that's on
purpose
but
something like I guess the base colors
but also the style of it
um
I think that may have been kind of on
purpose because also those that one is
not designed by Mika Sensei the idea of
the Japanese one and I did the English
one is designed by Rica Sensei but the
Japanese one is designed by the like
usual urugan sensei
right as far as I know if I got it right
unless I make something up but I'm
pretty sure and even then even though
there's two different designers in
charge when standing together
it's like still even though the outfits
are different like the overall Vibe
gives me similar Vibes so that's really
nice
yeah yeah
good job good job
thank you very much Captain me uh
you weren't just amazing
everything about it was perfect
choreography you're singing the
presentation everything is easy to see
that you gave everything and it paid off
be proud of yourself oh Deutsche
thank you
well yeah you say everything's perfect
thank you I'm glad you guys think so you
know you know I wasn't like 100 happy
with it but that's okay
maybe next time I can strive for
Perfection again
yeah
thank you so much for watching it and
supporting me and enjoying the show I'm
really glad you did Max King
glad to have some
Switzerland fans to
one of my very few I feel like I can
count you on my left hand but I'm glad
to have you thank you so much
Annie what did you say
what sounded mean
you retracted the message
you deleted it
now I'm really curious
let's find it
it's gone
Saucy chicken
fighting evidence
okay well at least you
realize yourself I don't know what it
was but at least you realized it it's
okay
[Music]
I'm so incredibly proud of you you
proved once again that you're a top tier
dancer I really love your performance
seriously I'll screaming so loud my
display almost cracked also your MC part
and the way we did was amazing Idol
you I'm glad you enjoyed it thank you
very much
for watching it thank you soon
for the pinky cookie tone spikes on the
pinky as well we're all our own worst
critics but honestly you had a strong
presence on stage really
you gave off a lot of energy and I'm
impressed by that uh it was literally
like that Center dance animation you
retweeted
what did I retweet I laughed when I saw
it you did great thank you
fun cool what did I retweet I don't
remember
every wish to stream it yeah yeah we're
like 20 minutes in
was that animation with the girls around
you while you were spinning
ah the one that I then unretweeted
because I realized ah
is that what that was
it
a gift was it a gift I know
mm-hmm
uh oh no that was a different thing oh
oh okay well I don't know but
[Music]
Pakistan
thank you thank you
I'm getting really tired oh
[Music]
fan animated one
I don't remember that one either brain
don't go
what
laughs
thank you Bruce
come to me no I want to finish this I'm
like really close
Dominique cavings for the pinky you
really showed your dancing skills in the
group choreo and it ended being a HP
song was amazing yes you felt like the
dancing leader and now those tainted
tweets by your cool dances make sense
okay I've been in Japan and overseas are
super proud of you wow and do you too
thank you
yeah I'm really glad we could do an HP
song
um
it was fun dancing together with the
girls
hope we can do more together in the
future
soon Bruce
Jenny Lee duncast
I'm no longer sad about missing your
performance last year I did everything I
could to see you today
and it was amazing what did you miss the
completely last year or just watched the
VOD
I was so happy to see you on the island
stage for the first time you show
impressed me a lot especially with your
choreo good job thank you thank you well
it's not my Corey it's just me dancing
for someone else's choreo but thank you
I put really all my energy into it I was
swinging my limbs all over
frailing them flailing flailing
you owned it though thank you I tried my
best
foreign
[Music]
mmm
um
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
Alex talk thank you for the rest of the
chat
proud of you bye kfp thank you
I'm doing nice
thank you peace proud of me I'm also
proud of you guys
it's just
a give and take and give and take and
give and take
Exchange
proudness Pride thank you Alex so much
for the support thank you
[Music]
ah
e g
um
it's
uh
Maybe
thank you
yes yes
[Music]
foreign
true I was thinking the same thing like
for dance solos
important parts like that
um
should kind of be like in a camera
person's or who not the camera people
but the ones who control the switches
you know camera controlling people are
fine once we switch them
they kind of need a script
I don't know if they have one
um
hope they fix that in the Blu-ray
I think it's fixable
so
oh but I don't know is like actually let
me ask like are they taking feedback
from us for that
question for the inevitable Blu-ray
release of fourth Fest
are they gonna
take feedback from us
the public feedback server is still up
oh but were they asking for such
specific things my feedback in the
service was better camera angles
well you're not like giving any time
stamps and stuff like that are you so
that's kind of like a like a rough
feedback
hard to implement it but still important
to give the feedback thank you
my feedback was asked Kiana really
come on
I mentioned your part specifically oh
okay
thank you guys
I guess
uh where was I did I read this
oh yeah
we'll see what we can do for the Blu-ray
all right
belly down thanks for the pinky I just
came back from Mako honey it was amazing
do you played by a live band sounded
incredible everyone got hyped when the
drums kicked in for the chorus yeah I
mean
that's the only part where I got really
like
you know loud if you know what I mean so
it's like I never look to get hyped
there
I wish the other parts were a little bit
like more
like something happening
but oh well
thank you thank you thank you I'm glad
you guys got to enjoyed in the end
what's important to me is that you guys
enjoyed it
um
ah we were at the venue you think it
sounded louder at the venue idiom base I
hope so
I hope from the audience seat it sounded
really loud what even then even with the
bass boost
still think that something was missing
hmm
well well
that must have been really crazy for you
to experience that in person wow
can we change I want to be in your seat
[Music]
really jealous of you I hope they get a
bigger video next year so that more
people can get tickets for real for real
for real for real
I've known things look pinky I would be
more
more than happy to pay 10 times a ticket
just to see your performances alone
I can't even describe how proud I am and
you made me so happy and proud I cried
I'll definitely be re-watching your part
on repeat for at least 100 times
so at which play through are you now huh
unknown
which one is it now are you done with
the hundred already eh eh
you don't know
you're getting there surely well
still plenty of time for the archive
yeah thank you so
I'm really really happy you liked it so
much thank you for loving kiwawa so much
well thanks for the red super chat the
last Red Super Chat yo
Chihuahua you were amazing I couldn't
help but both chuckling Christine
this sounds so similar to the other one
you guys are in sync
uh are you being the leader of the Yen
group song and seeing you mark the
others with your dance with no don't say
that that being said my only criticism
is that in both songs there wasn't
enough close-ups
um
I wouldn't say we need more close-ups
unless with close-ups you just mean like
upper body or like full body but not
from too far away
because close up with a close-up if it's
just a face then again you can't see the
dancing again and you don't see like the
others maybe maybe they're showing
close-up of your or she but the the
other ones are hoping for close-ups of
their own Oshi so I feel like generally
for classes like these
not so many close-ups is the way to go
yeah just like medium shots
where you see
more of the body but not too much
of the audience like some audience shots
definitely nice
I want plenty of them
what they really should do is Implement
a function where you can switch a camera
angle yourself
why does nobody do that why does no
concert out there do that
why not give view the control over
camera angles what the hell
let you enjoy it
from far from close
maybe at least in like Blu-ray release
wouldn't that be amazing actually
I feel like for hell project concert at
some point they did something like that
actually
nowadays for Kpop they do at least like
or she coming up things like even
official ones like they even upload
official close-ups of uh their members
but you know this is kind of new stuff
but I feel like
I feel like I had a project a long time
ago they don't do that anymore nowadays
I was like why don't they do it more
often but a long time ago for certain
DVDs they had angles
for whole concerts not just one song but
the whole concert
for oshini yoroshi like one one person
only
attention is cooking yeah for real
though like maybe this is less
of a crazy idea than making us huge size
on the screen
but at least for the Blu-ray then okay
you can still cut out some angles that
maybe you thought weren't so good
but wouldn't it be so amazing if you
have the footage anyway
give us maybe you can sell two Blu-rays
you can sell the normal price Blu-ray
with like your own fixed set of and like
one angle you know like you okay of
course you mix them you know but you
know one angle thingy and then you sell
like a super special limited not limited
let's not make a limited but it might be
limited it's super special Blu-ray
version where you have different angles
um
I mean why not why does no one do that
we have the footage right so
use it
isn't it a waste to not use it
but it would be so happy because like
every time you know someone's on the
close-up that you don't really want to
see more I mean there's someone you want
to see more right
so
you should give them the control over
where the cameras are moving to a
different position that would look bad I
mean
I mean K2
worst case you can cut that out and
switch to different place just for that
but I think even that is fine
like we will take that little scarf in
exchange for having every angle like we
don't expect every angle to be perfectly
positioned at all times throughout a
three hour concert
and you don't need to give us every
angle how many angles are there like 20
15 I don't know
don't need to give us every single one
of them maybe give us like five main
angles
wouldn't that be great oh I'm such a
genius
I'm such a genius and yet
and yet
my genius is like not being fully
drained
train me like I think baby
Fang
s double demon friend
genius is frightening
if they can fit all the footage on a
disk well if it's really just five I
think yes
surely
or maybe make it a digital release thing
I don't know man I don't
know I cannot believe you're still
streaming yeah I'm ending it soon I have
like three more Super chats left
basically
um
no worries
but I have to eat my food and then sleep
and then wake up and then practice
Korean and then have my Korean teacher
come in and then access if I totally
didn't just practice last minute right
before she came
yes
it's been eight hours yeah
wow my only Edition
oh yeah or she Edition
oh wait friends maybe didn't get like
his friend School wow catch catch wk.com
thank you guys I am done with this
and since it's past midnight that's
where I will leave it at I hope I didn't
uh
like
make more than I read
this stream
I don't know how much I read
hopefully I
made less
the [\h__\h]
what did I just say on Twitter
he gained fan art edit of takana shikira
dying in a glue trap what like a fly
who's asking for this PK
[Music]
s
YouTube though
okay you guys if you want to watch
something after this
arm is streaming Oblivion after this in
15 minutes
hey can I I wanna try I wanna try and do
the thing how do I do the thing
or we can also do it on fauna I guess
should I do it on foreign
oh
[Music]
is she streaming too
don't
do not spoil her into read
uh okay maybe link copy I don't know
wait
it only starts when I ended on my side
right
in Germany we say avidazen I will say
that now
I'll tell her
honor
[Music]
oh eh what's going on right from
Chihuahua
where do I do this uh YouTube is so slow
give me a moment
give me one moment
where which window was it again this is
the second time I'm doing it
actually no it's the first time because
yeah
foreign
official Channel
did I oh my God genius
I love you guys
tomorrow morning see you there bye-bye
say hi to Paula
behave
foreign
[Music]