[Music]
hello it's just me right now and I'm
scared
go I don't know how to play this game
and we have to find each other before we
do
anything and I'm scared it's happening
it is
happening I think I think you're
supposed to loot stuff also the first
time I played this game I immediately
died to wild
dogs and I tried to light them on fire
but I just ended up lighting myself on
fire also I feel like I haven't streamed
by myself in like forever so I'm I'm
scared that I don't know how to stream
anymore on top of dealing with the
zombies I also have to remember how what
is 197
trophies somebody's honor student oh God
has
perished wa here we are think back to
Dying Light oh God Al I feel like is
game the game is like silent right
now I guess it has sound I might need to
turn the sound up also do I need music
or do you guys just want to like listen
to
the the amb can you even hear the
ambience the zombie
Ambience it's just like
no music I guess
so in the apocalypse okay wait I think
other people are probably finding each
other I'm just finding
garbage scrap
polymers that's a that's a nice way of
saying your recycling
bin is this music I hear it's so
quiet wait there is sound there is
music it's just not always on it's
really quiet
too should it be
louder do the tutorial at the
top hold on it's so quiet and it's
ominous but the game was like really
loud okay maybe that's
better oh is that that
me
painting wait now it's too loud wait is
it sorry I don't remember how to stream
and
I'm I'm being a micro
manager redeem tutorial
challenge
redeem I've done it do I have to read
it it will guide
me okay I can I can gather
punch am I doing it I'm punching the
plants wait now that there's music I
know I was just complaining about the
silence there's a
chicken I was just complaining about the
silence but now the music is freaking me
out I guess maybe that's the point it is
the
redeem it is the
apocalypse food is not
food it sounds so
sad I guess the zombie apocalypse is sad
okay hold on I'm not being a team player
right
now
[Music]
um wait what is that what am I clicking
welcome to the party
YOLO hello party home hello
hi we're so lonely without you welcome I
don't know what's
happening I think we're heading we're
making our way to be yeah
okay okay you're actually around where I
am fa like near a
lake is there a lake oh there's a river
I see yeah there's there's water
presumably leads so far away oh my God
why am I over here
yeah there's like a cabin near a lake
multiple of them
actually oh a
resort pleas S I don't know look like
horror
area she
fancy this game has push to talk oh you
can also press M to find more
bees um oh
okay the tutorial I don't know I joined
the party I thought we were using
Discord well maybe we will use Discord I
don't
know I'm just confused there's push to
talk I'm definitely going to forget to
push to talk but at least it means I
can I can talk and not be
crazy I want to find Shi
we can we can we can Yap I'm doing the
tutorial oh my gosh old sham
sandwich sham
sandwich do you guys remember the Sham
wow do you guys remember the Sham
wow yes sham wow wait the guy that's
like dead wait is he dead I didn't mean
to make yeah he sh dead oh no I did it I
didn't know he was dead I didn't know
either I just know sham wow I seen on
TV yeah what about it oh I found a sham
sandwich oh is it edible or is it moldy
wait I think it's edible can it be
moldy you should try eating it yeah eat
it eat it I'm not hungry
yet it says it's old but that doesn't
mean it's moldy well it's going to get
older later well that's true actually
that's a good point it's not getting any
younger oh no it was made with the heel
the heel of the loaf wait of what you
know like the the butt of the bread Oh I
thought like a heel like a is it called
the heel it's made of heel oh hey you're
near where I am now the end loaf yeah
the end it's desperate desperation yeah
the butt the Des insiration sandwich I
don't I don't like the butt of the bread
me neither I ate it fa is that
you wait I think I oh my go I think I'm
having a bowel movement don't look at me
is there a
toilet it's 30 no no no it's
beautiful how can how can we be friends
if we don't appreciate each other's
bowel
movement I I'm I'm shy I can't go if
somebody's watching
there's there's got to be a toilet in
here this is this is a zombie I think I
heard a a scream it's okay it's okay
it's okay they don't like outside
they're like us introverts hold up I'm
putting clothes on you have clothes I
haven't done anything except eat a
sandwich is it reflected on me yeah oh
yeah there's a there's a person there he
coming he's out there for your B
movement kill them
you already have a
spear yeah I'm
primitive ow and hurt I can light up on
fire wow oh good
job oh she she's still
alive oh that was good can we not loot
their bodies anymore I don't know when
we did the the practice I made a bone
knife but it it didn't give me anything
o when I tried to kill them wow that was
a really loud squish sound okay well we
can look for a toilet here if we want or
we can go to bebs
whichever I'm sure there is the toilet
oh God there's a zombie somewhere hold
on I have to go I accidentally broke
down the door so don't look where in the
toilet it's okay oh okay I'll I'll
distract the zombie I learn out how do
you use the toilet come here zom zom you
actually have poop in this game is that
even possible I think so it's just um
26% of the way to a to
BM are you actually she has a lot go in
the forest right in front of everyone no
I found a
toilet but the whole world is our toilet
how are you going to play the forest if
you can't even [\h__\h] in
it I don't know I can't seem to figure
out how to even use the toilet
oh oh ouch I think if you just stand in
there you'll Release Yourself you know
you leave yourself in the toilet find
your in stand there okay
okay oh there's
two oh man she is Windows so much health
she dead now all right you
may uh remove your sandwich in peace now
I don't
know I don't know is it even possible I
don't think you I don't think you can
actually poop in this game fun there's
there's an icon which very clearly to me
show eventually on its own without
interruption do you need clo do am I
wearing clothes actually you are you are
wearing
[Music]
clothes I guess my my percentage is
slowly going down but the implications
of that are so much worse than if you
just go to the bathroom all right I'll
try making your clothes oh thank
you I just don't like that it's like
slowly all right clothes are being made
um we we have not progressed far towards
beu huh oh but we're getting so much
stuff it's good right CH Cho
old
chair okay I'm about to chop the clothes
here thank
you thank
you you just couldn't bear to look at my
my clothless oh I can hear your bowel
movements or is that a zombie H that's
not me that's not me maybe unless it is
are you sure are you sure I think I
heard it that made a little grumbly
sound grumbly grumbly in your tummy I'm
so
embarrassed I never should have eaten
the old no no it's okay it's okay it's
special it's special oh what's
this wait can I show you guys SC my
character this is definitely
me
beautiful oh
wow we we look dangerous and a little
psych honestly can we can we break this
and did you want to keep exploring you
want to head to Beast maybe something
else this will give us good
stuff we I we getp and iron o I think
you need a wrench if you want to salvage
cars
oh can I make
stuff Stone axe here make you spear too
oh thank you I made an
axe um here's your spear the axe is used
to um to harvest items it'll give you
more compared to
punching
shovel where's my
axe
shovel the
Duke put this here is that lemon water
okay that's taking too long okay should
we go
find
IBU oops Yeah yeah let's go find her I
guess
okay wait GG is not that far from us now
no I'm on my
way yeah should we go find her and then
go
together oh R is also uh nearby she's
right there
oh can she oh wait that's a zomb I send
her a party invite since right there
make it across yeah yeah getting a
Chase they're kind of gross
nice
job yeah we're we're killing it man you
kill so splendidly thank
you look at her go across the
lake an egg do that voice chat only
works like party
wise yeah and it's not
proximity right
[Music]
yeah I can hear you guys
this good can you yeah yeah even though
I'm So Far Away ra ignored this
no maybe she thought we were evil cuz of
our outfits well I mean we looked the
part but that doesn't mean we are the
part let's just follow her she knows
where to go
okay oh this
Stone a
gem I mean if this was mine what this I
don't
know you need a looks important though
shovel
or the axe works yeah yeah it's
working your axe it does look
important all right I harvested some
I'll let you have the rest oh oh it's
just it's just small stuff
well now I have a lot of wait was it a
small
Stone I don't know how this game
works Harvest wood one more
wood oh but I'm supposed to craft this
for my
you
good yes I'm completing
quests oh do we lose
La it's okay she's like headed towards
one area anyway should we should we find
[Music]
Gigi I am walking quickly with okay B
yeah yeah she's uh near the lake area
and everyone's sced up
we can pick you up though if you want
G it's okay I'm on my way I see all
right well we can stay
put where's my
shovel frog oh right in the where it
hurts oh go nice hey shared
XP yeah
redeem
redeem I skipped this
one can I craft it and then like destroy
it just so I can get the XP or maybe I
can sell it to
somebody Pawn It Off
[Music]
um thank you what level am I wait is
that my XP bar at the
bottom there's a green bar and a blue
bar and a purple bar should we just pick
up
Gigi
yes we
should okay all right we're heading
towards you Skyrim style Skyrim
style oh yeah following the the thing at
the top
oh I'm also following it but getting
distracted maybe we should go loot more
houses too it's going to be a while
before we reunite with
everyone did they all make it what is
that I put my bed here though oh you
have a bed oh it's a I think it's a
spawning Point yeah it's my cheat shei
oh is that you guys I make a bunch of
that's oh yeah yeah that's us hi oh hey
what's up hello hey it got close too I
have clo I'm clothed I like that we all
have very scary hat yeah we do look
pretty scary oh hey there's someone over
there now we look pretty wait do you
mean that zombie there's someone
there zombie look at the shotgun I have
running why do you have a gun done
nice how did you get a gun takes a while
this I did a quest
already oh my God I just one tapped him
that's
crazy who are you too bad I can't hear
you I know oh we should add her let me
add okay I sent a party invite
where's even the the gun
Quest I'm in the wooden Club era and
Gigi has already discovered
gunpowder um
crafted
beautiful oh holy [\h__\h]
my bad going to
kill I'm glad she didn't
die craft
this just want leave a
party the real challenge in this game
is figuring out oh can I only make one
how to navigate The Voice in party
system um is that a gun I guess it's
this way are you shooting
Gigi yeah I just shot him in the face
oh do you have
ammo can you take your bullet back from
his brain I wish give me more ammo give
it to me just put it back in the chamber
it'll be fine she towards here and let
me go
right redeem redeem I like how we have
this ADHD oh crap what's that kill exp
exp I have a gun don't
worry White River Outpost that's a waste
of
though primitive folks handle
it okay okay I'm clubbing I'm CL clubing
her I'm clubbing her yeah we clubbing we
partying all night I'm out of stamina I
can't party anymore rest up my girl rest
up another
sandwich what is this building over here
I'm going
inside you guys already L this are dead
person here cell tower oh well R went
through here and maybe the
others oh they left Behind These
electrical parts though they left behind
an office chair they take the office
chair There's a
Zombie e ow it hurts it
hurts die
scum you will not touch these beautiful
women but thank you my my
night jiggling and
blushing o XD more oh no the P
broken I'm never going to figure out my
4.1 person oh wow anything else here I'm
climbing the cell tower so hopefully I
can get some signal on our cell phones
don't jump I'm Dy I'm dying I lived I
lived oh good job I'm hungry I guess
I'll never find out what's in the cell
tower all right
I I should probably eat this egg ra
thirsty you should eat a sham sandwich
so you can also have tummy problems like
fa I recommend
it do you do you have a spare um I have
an egg wait what is
this I have a chili canned
chili oh that's good you found
food I think I spawned with it actually
I didn't find anything have a moldy
sandwich man I spoted with like a death
threat or
something wait can I not wear
these on all right they should be at
this house I think the
gloves
okay they're all just inside of a house
together doing
what playing Family sorority is that how
I say it oh sority
there need two
settlement where is the settlement oh
it's in the other
direction oh it's
CeCe
strange the paaw we look like a cult
yeah we do
wow we kind of look like a
cult I accient
pun all right is it time
to I guess we join the Discord call
now okay can all right I'll I'll stay
here though I'll see you in a bit okay
me too
hello we have someone evil
this I have no control I don't have no
control of my li
[Music]
chaos you look beautiful look this is my
this is my PC do you like it oh
nice garbage oh I can sleep on top of it
I'm reopening the game or maybe I
cannot got this
place I'm to you like it very I mean
yeah yeah it's go what happens
if I like too sure I don't think we need
it we getting anything from it I don't
know to play do anyone want to come I
want to go try going to a farm
oh okay let's
go up home here really quick let's go
okay I come I
actually well then let's wait for shorty
shy did you say you want you come with
us or need my bed roll okay okay got to
set
that let's wait a second
is there a Trader near here or you guys
Trader lless pretty what did you say is
there a Traer near this
house we haven't found one yet we
haven't done
anything take off my hat I like that
even in the apocalypse Trends thing and
we're all wearing the same style I
accidentally clicked fash TRS
even by the way if you guys open the map
you can set a marker for where home is
you can set a marker that's
[Applause]
nice I'm sorry every time I all tap back
in I punch someone oh that's what
happened I don't mean it stay away from
me okay truth truth truth please don't
touch me do you don't touch me
truth go
[Music]
don't H each
other all right I'm going stay
back should probably yeah get him get
him get
that yeah oh legs left we're crazy okay
this way I think was the farm Yep this
way wait wait who am I following
everyone looks the same I'm a little
hungry follow
everybody follow the follow this the the
oh dead corn but I'm going to have
ADH that's okay at any point you want
go there's
cor right
around pick the corn can we this can we
cook cuz I got some meat potato so there
like dead corn with green corn I think
oh that was real
corn get the green corn get the that
forget I feel like we should probably be
play oh they're dead oo let's go yeah
there is real corn M can we get can we
get those to replant them I stole that
from you we don't those are still
growing got to be a good farmer I'll be
find Tre in this apocalypse with corn
that's all I need I'll survive most of
the Corn are dead though yum YN there's
plenty of here can have we just can't
eat the the people what
yeah that that is that
is okay this this area has three three
skulls on it I don't know if we're ready
for that oh oh does that mean like
danger we're going to die yeah I just
green one's probably really good but I
just don't think we're
ready images so I noticed that the green
corns actually contain seeds to probably
oh they do we could set corn they have
something different we could set up a
little farm by our
home can we eat it wrong a seat
we there's a house over here too here
yeah I
see this is be careful this is the three
School area yeah it's a pretty
int there zombies everywhere run run run
you got run what are they going to do
it's okay fine what are they going to do
huh so much
[Laughter]
corn all right I hope the corn be like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of
hopefully where the
farmers I have so much back home me yeah
I don't think it gives you anything can
I eat okay we can eat wait wa don't
leave
me so we just need the big
ones for the green on we found sand on
who wants to focus on getting food maybe
we should split into like yeah good idea
food gatherers this is just
Gathering stay at
home gone so far back in
time let's
go I found a land claim block do we have
to destroy this oh I think someone put
that down I just put that there for the
quest worry
not for a
quest so if you put a land claim box
down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something
apparently so like you're safe in the
zone I guess or something like that or
the player who put it down is safe in
the zone it's like your LP now I would
be a house yeah we have one of those I
put one in the living room oh okay
awesome oh we're in the same uh Ally
group too so we should be good to go it
won't be harder for us to destroy each
other's things if we need to exactly are
we all in the same party I have a
question um um the party is
six how do you level up I'm not in the
party anymore kill I think it's going to
kill
experience oh killing zombies okay yeah
if we find a traitor he gives Quest and
he gives a lot of exp from the quest
does anyone want to go with me on an
adventure to see if we can find the
Traer I know where he is he's really
far have one on my map too yeah okay is
it the White River we have to yeah yeah
want this way point if he wants to trade
he should come to us that's right he's
not going to do that I think but then he
won't have any business be your face by
the way or he's GNA hello oh
hello I found
people welcome welcome welcome welcome
heit you guys are all wearing something
why aren you wear where's your hat
there's a hat yes put your hat on what
we should probably like to it there's a
zombie over there kill
[Music]
it your I will hat anything yet oh oh
wait no I see a hat oh thank you yes put
it on Oh
yay
civilized he's down down I he's not
[Music]
I don't know how to share the way Mark
with you guys what what if you send like
a
screenshot I can send a screenshot
gloves I'm missing
gloves oh that
works can't eat the craft anything just
yet there CRA land claim
box sound I can make a Char meat for
guns meat meat meat is this our base by
our
yeah we should probably do multiple Camp
what is this land claim
Block it's our home base now this
basically zombies won't spawn around you
see it I put it in the channel the map
what if we all put our land claim blocks
like around each other so they won't
spawn with let's protect the house we
get so where can't do anything right how
to make land claim block oh this is oh I
have a land claim block um I don't know
where to put it though uh it won't let
me put it
anywhere they already claim this landim
yeah is there a maximum to can only one
person claim a land
Cecilia how are you cooking oh this is
Mor oh that's not me that's Kell oh here
Tre maybe right there TR to figure out
to put this oh yeah I can't put the land
claim oh yeah it's a pretty it's a
pretty large here I am dying of
hunger oh I found a place we need to
unlock
the all right has claimed this
lands put it by the
river see if we can cook some more for
everybody
land maybe here oh we need cooking items
oh I like placement of this fire right
on the
counter
we just anywhere these days is put at
the fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying pan so
we
okay yeah oh I found a I found a cooking
a grill outside the house I don't know
if GR
some water we have some water in our
inventory here near trees is there a
town nearby oh oh there's a town very
far
away that's some o that the hell that's
I think I'm going to eat scary food oh
by the way it's night time soon everyone
um oh you guys have a nice campire out
here wonderful put more
the idea that I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions together oh that's
a good idea think we're eating it that
would be great
sorry M I want to eat it
I'm
here cover the river she's here I don't
know what to do it's about to be
nightes I'm going to focus on finding
food I want to go I want to
[Music]
go Chet too if anyone wants to go on an
ex stroll I'm going to collect items I'm
going to gather stuff so I'll stick
around the house okay okay I will debate
on what to do I will debating I'm also
debating how how does one the cooking
skill is it here skill tree I'm pretty
sure a cornmeal oh can I eat this oh
oh you need water to
cook yeah realistic it sucks huh finding
water a good idea for us I oh I can more
Stones how do we get yumy purified water
boil
it
eliminated um how
evil why what a terrible
person I think need a pot how do we need
a pot a bed we have to find
it
pot now why can craft cornmeal okay yeah
me too oh they're in the other
VC violence between our allies is
concerning very concerning yeah let's
not know when I'm not hungry how much do
I have to eat I have harvested Stones
what the heck okay I think I'm no longer
hungry it's night your stomach sounds
like a
zombie I'm sorry I don't mean it what uh
I don't know what no your stomach really
sounds like a zombie I don't need it I
don't need it try to get in oh saying
that about my stomach really that one
like I'm going to try to like build
walls or something yeah good idea to
stay
inside oh we're not supposed to sleep
outside but it's so beautiful the STS
they're coming in they're coming in
inside stop talking stomach that way
how' you repair those I'm slapping them
I'm slapping
them oh
God can we s
our oh my god oh who did this to
me what the f anyway I think a build a
building block I
hope this was terrifying change to
something
else you can't what the heck I can't man
building is
hard if I just destroyed us at this
point how bad is 12% dis can I handle
that 12% bad compared to zero that
doesn't seem that
bad
double my
first building block maybe I can snipe
too how I'm hoping to just put a block
here so we don't have Windows that
people can see us through good idea
people yeah these zombies can't watch us
yeah and think about us and think
weird what kind of weird dos you know
weird thoughts can you name why dots or
weird
thoughts I swear okay that's the
building
block okay can I open the door or
no help there's a weird
zombie M there's a weird zombie outside
M scaring
crony I have a candle what's this to put
this dang no fear huh ladies I know who
to
Woo you're not afraid of
anything there you go I hope do we need
any more doors
anywhere I think we're good I think
they're they all look pretty
healed how' you board them up
Kiara H I just want to place a door
somewhere
um scary sound this is
Minecraft
yeah oh
songs the acoustic guitar how do I craft
I have a
kazoo oh is a zombie deer come here deer
don't need don't need the deer can we
just nap it ran away you cannot sleep
like Minecraft
sadly you cannot sleep oh no it's evil
Minecraft if only
just need one more Stone nice I just
need more wood Traer
Quest do I heal if I sleep at least no
no don't think so what's the point of
having a
bed
beatify
things I'm low on stamina and I'm
thirsty how do you Ed this so much is
wrong with you this this fire you guys
experience thirst and hunger turn it on
how do you turn it on God at the right
you see a bunch of wood make sure it has
fuel and then you just turn it
on
oh does this building block even do
anything we have curtains that should be
good put some corn in there destroy a
broken blocks how do you tell what you
need to coach something I have to join a
party a recipe I think how do I join a
party I'll just
definitely uh allies wait no party just
like the
variant invite
meori can invite everyone right wait I
received a party invite oh sick oh can I
get one too I'm currently not in the
party I can't aim this bow and
arrow
yeah thank you and then
you press just press buttons
yipp good oh do I need a party I think
I'm in a
[Music]
party yeah
CR
yippe
yippe probably stick around and uh
Harvest things around here but if people
want to and I am thirsty my character is
like
never wait how do you experience
hunger okay bar too cron it's just very
hard to see it's a green bar beneath
your
inventory so
privileged yeah love you for my
inventory oh now I'm hungry
okay welcome to
the this is good for bodies if you use
the bone knife could Harvest bodies with
[Applause]
rust is it safe to go outside yeah it's
safe yeah you can go out okay yay one
it's not too bad right now yeah because
it's day
one
probably tomorrow we die though there's
a dog glowing eyes you think that's I'm
so excited I think so sure it's not
hoko very that's not a good
shift uh click or shift
click shift
click can't build in someone else
claimed area unless they allow it oh you
have a
curtain place to oh can you not build in
the house area oh somebody in my chat
just wrote yeah we can't place anything
in a claimed area but I don't know they
can allow it apparently I play
stuff I yeah the bed roll locked oh hold
R okay let's try about this one no it
just
rotates animal oh if you like do
this hey that's my stuff wait I I
thought it turned into a wooden
block I'll just I'll just pick it up oh
I got to repair it how does one get
animal stuff animal fat I thought it
turns into a wooden
block I cover up our
uh oh yeah yeah if you want animal F
kill an animal and then if you right
click with an axe I don't see any
animals yeah I'll go hunting wait really
find that bunny again you just need a
stone
a oh don't you need to like upgrade with
stone really I have the axe
yeah
[Music]
quest Quest
oh oh you need more wood I don't have
enough wood I guess I got uh I have 87
Bren
oh so thirsty anyone got a
pot I'm going off on my own I've
upgraded my looting
abilities and I'm going to go find a
pot
um isn't a zombie
[Music]
wait they didn't get that
far the adventurer
party they're like right
there hold on why am I
yellow oh I said the corn fields are
that
way who's racking their shotgun
add
me okay it's kind of scary out here but
I'm not
worried we've got stuff to
[Music]
find that's the UI the UI makes zombie
sounds what do you what do you mean by
that is this the morchary assistant oh
my gosh did did all the Adventure
parties adventurers just die
well that's not going to be
me yes it all
dead all the corn can I
have that seems bad I feel like I
shouldn't wait did I drop
it oh no what happened to my
corn I feel like I shouldn't just punch
all the
corn did I eat it
not sure I don't think that gave me much
food and I don't want to kill the
deer okay let's go this way they're fast
at night
huh you're juking
me I won't die I don't think my my bra
falling build is online just
yet
ow wait I'm going to die wait I don't
want to die I don't want to
die I don't want to
die oh no she's eating me after I made
fun of the adventurer group for
dying oh
no spawn me near my backpack
[Music]
we're going
back my adventure is not done I think
that they are very merciful in the rules
she's still
there take it all take it all take it
all my brawling build is not online yet
I need to find some brass knuckles or
something but I know you saw what I was
silently
menuing after reading all the skills
I've chosen to lock into the brawler
build why is she so
strong who said this lady gets to be so
strong I've suffered an abrasion am I
going to turn into a zombie I am
[Music]
infected perhaps I should simply
die I can't let the
others I can't risk their help why is
she so
strong how many hits is she going to
take it light
out and honestly she deserves to kill
[Applause]
me yellow eyes is
danger feeding her well is she really is
she getting all her HP back when she
eats
me oh
dear no they found
[Music]
me oh
no and I'm running out of
samam why is she so
strong can I lose her
oh my go he's got the Hops and
everything can I get her into the
hole oh I myself have gone into the
hole is she going to follow me
yes is the
answer you see zombies might be strong
but they are not
smart dang it's only 3:00
a.m. is it just going to be this
dangerous out
here oh my gosh she's obsessed with
me she won't leave me alone
get a
life
honestly land I I mean the sun is
rising maybe it's not no it's totally
Rising look over here that that's a pink
Sunrise if I've ever seen
one seeds blueberry seeds they're going
to be so happy that I bring these back
oh is it
raining I can't tell maybe I turned all
the particle effects
off
oh it has a danger rating of two
zombies who's
that R flesh maybe I don't need
that I feel like I don't need that
honestly I've just been looting
everything
but are these heavy because they would
love it I think if
I if I brought some plants
back to decorate our
house I think they would be so
happy
honestly close the
door do they know how to use
doors they know how to break
them but I'm so far
gone I don't want to be trapped in there
I saw my life flash before my
eyes that the zombie jump
scare I'm faster honestly
honestly I'm faster
[Music]
so sounds like morning music to me look
it's morning 4:00 a.m. good
morning what a beautiful
day is that a sound of a
zombie okay I got the loot perk which I
assume is the best perk work as someone
who has read no guides at all for this
game that's what I'm going to
assume so I'm expecting some good stuff
here oh metal pipe
great 7 Days to Die randomly interrupted
by metal pipe sound
effects I mean lots of
gunpowder it seems like I shouldn't
fight the
zombies I mean maybe they're weak now
cuz it's
daytime
but I still I have bad
experiences feathers must be
good but I've got a bow and arrow and
Gigi is already living oh my gosh this
was three
zombies Oh I thought that zombie had pet
bunny I think it did
honestly Gigi already has a gun wiring
101 pipe
baton corn
seed hold on let me read this I'm going
to become the best
wirer ever I'm going to read all the
books I'm going to be the Big Nerd with
all the
plants this is
good it reminds me of
my favorite character from the anime
katako Hitman Reborn which I watched a
billion years
ago and he my favorite character fought
with
tonfas which I didn't even know what
that was until I watched it but it's
kind of like
this you love that I feel like that was
that anime/manga was like a a mass Hall
hallucination
that I've like never seen anybody talk
about but like all of you guys know it
maybe not all of you many of you know
it
oil Stone spear I don't think I need
that but I never see anybody like
reference it literally never heard of
it enter burnt Forest
oh I'm completing quests that I didn't
even know I
had hunt animals when did I kill an
animal I wouldn't do that a do
collector oh gosh I don't think I'm
doing any of this
stuff well I know that this game oh I'm
full some of this stuff has to be
worthless maybe most of
it I got the
[Music]
Elmer my stick inventory time to head
back but I didn't get the pot that was
my whole goal all I got is 11 potted P
plants
pants glue is important I mean all of
this stuff seems important in the
apocalypse maybe I don't need one small
Stone wait I have steel knuckle Parts
wait I didn't even see what that
was I am getting steel
Knuckles it seems like cars have pretty
good good stuff this is scary this
town gas can mechanical
pars I shouldn't be
encumbered mechanical Parts seem
important
though seeds seem
good unless I can just eat them drop the
clay
okay I don't want to head back until I
get something
good 99% of looters quit
before they loot something
good from the
garbage but this place has a real
Sinister
Aura owens's residence well it's only
one and a half
skulls but I don't I don't I don't like
it oh I see that guy but I
this there's somebody's there's
somebody's thing right
here I just want to be
smart wait that's just the burn for
Forest I thought it was
um somebody's fire newly lit fire to set
the
scene oh is cement
good I feel like a sewing kit and a
repair kit are both good
but I'm
incumbered I knew I should have got the
pack mule
trait just give me something
good crushed
sand what in the Minecraft mod is
that what in the teet is that
the dog house there has to be something
good in the dog house
right you can't you can't even look at
the dog
house
oh I just know the other half of my
steel Knuckles are around
here
somewhere they've got to be where am I
anyway
pretty
far it's 6
a.m. lead I don't know if that's even
good don't eat it don't chew on it
cornmeal seems
good I'm not safe
here says who
is a big scary Bross zombie G to come
out and and murder
me better hurry it's 6: a.m. right night
is not for a long
time I guess I can go back and drop my
stuff off I just wanted to read more
magazines it's fine I'm
faster they're just crawling
oh I can still Sprint even though I'm
encumbered why shouldn't I be
encumbered then that guy's just hiking
up the
mountain you have to respect the
exercise wait can you get a
bag a
backpack that could be revolutionary
wait I want more
experience I should
do
quests that's not what I thought I was I
should do
challenges Building Blocks place door
Place storage
[Music]
container
craft Harvest honey okay I don't know if
I'm doing any of these quests
never do Quest oh no need to do
Quest could I kill zombies for their
XP I mean that guy just seemed like low
hanging fruit
honestly not while I'm
encumbered does it give much I feel like
when I did so we did like a test and I
played for maybe
[Music]
50 minutes but I wasn't really doing
anything I was just standing and killing
the zombies that came to me and I feel
like I I didn't level up at
all from killing zombies for 50 minutes
but maybe I just didn't know that I had
leveled
up because because I didn't check my
skill page
little
XP have you guys played this game
before I feel like I haven't I hadn't
really heard of
it that a storm suddenly getting really
Smokey oh I mean
rainy
foggy yes too much you have more than
4,000 hours in
it I'm
dying okay if you have 4,000 hours in
it who is
that it's
Gigi wish there proximity
chat
hello what are you searching for in this
area I was reading books magazine oh
you're reading yeah what's your favorite
magazine Vogue I really like wiring
[Laughter]
101 it's a good magazine yeah it was so
good I read it
twice two wiring 101 I just missed two
point blank arrow shots on this
thing what if I find point blank arrow
shots 101 I'll give it to you oh thank
you I need to learn how to
aim ooh it
I'm trying to explore this stiff tool
shop they have a lot of stiff tools that
looks like it said it was like very
dangerous so I
left it's not dangerous with the both of
us here we already killed two zombies
that's true I am I'm encumber and I
picked up too many potted plants
but what are you going to use the plants
for decoration yeah I thought people
would be so happy when when I brought
home potted plants oh yeah they will
love they're going to love your plants I
think so I can't tell if that's a town
across the bridge I want to go I found a
a burnt Forest down the other way that's
scary this way yeah I'm going to go
across the bridge okay good luck on your
quest thank you good LU on yours thank
you I just know that shi and K I heard
that whole
conversation we're just budding into
them the whole
time we were like researching wait I
have a bone
knife this gives
XP we were
researching if you can do proximity chat
but it doesn't seem like it works
um I'll go home now that it's daytime I
can go
home hold
on oh my
gosh you can make a machine gun with
just iron pipes glue and
wood is that
easy knuckle wraps
iron Knuckles you need wait 11 no wait
you need Knuckles
11 knuckle
wraps you need 20 cloth fragments I
think I can make
that can I have my
fists hold on
am I getting plant
fibers I don't know if knuckle wraps are
even going to help does that help my
brawling my
slapping I think everyone would be so
impressed if I just started
slapping they're out here with machine
guns and I just walk over and go bam and
I One Shot them
my only goal is impressing everyone else
as you can
see that's why I pick up the potted
plants maybe make a cute house that
would also be my
goal I'm sorry to This
Grass this is real herbivore Behavior
right
here what can I say it's so peaceful
during the day when there's non
zombies okay now I can
make can't I make cloth
now
oh
yes I can only make five wait what do
you mean book
oh I need wasted Treasures volume
six where am I supposed to find that is
there a perk that gives me more
books I wish to become very smart I
haven't even gained any skill
points a bookstore is there a
bookstore mailboxes bookshelves oh I
guess I need to drop my stuff off and
and go back out
there I thought I could make
my my
knuckle
[Music]
wraps let's see let's see what people
are are up to here what the I put food
in one storage crate since we'll all be
like
hungry [\h__\h] so hungry we
starving
God seems like I can name it we have a
lot of rocks we can repair it right if
you guys should go near the farm please
collect more corn did you find a pot
okay a pot yeah oh we can not a
pot how are you cooking without a
pot well we can label the crates
let us know down down when you're do you
want to go
to V tree okay let's do it okay let's do
it okay this and I don't even know put
that candle there I am so hungry and so
thirsty and there are so
many
people monsters GG I mean this in the
nicest way possible but everybody's
starving GG you're not the
only the only one Starving in here and I
need you to give me your food I'm not
feeling so well
either stand by tax stand by tax I am I
am starving personally to go forage for
stuff cuz all I have corn and I'm sick
of it
what you sick of
corn although if you go to the farm
please collect more I'm going to go to
the town uh please get me more corn
where do we get
water you have to find a river and then
I think you still might need pot or a
water bottle to collect water from it
are you kidding sow can you turn snow
into water maybe you can drink from
it oh it gets heavy
here all right I'm about to wander off
see you guys goodbye good luck goodbye
have a great
one h i craft
the tin land mine no that's not what I
want corn
Pizza what are we having for dinner corn
Pizza corn again plant
cor corn is a luxury you can be so glad
you even have
corn is it safe if zombies ever come
[Music]
is anything safe in this
world let's
see I found a
hospital a hospital a hospital who wants
to go to the
hospitalit go to the hospital we can
cure your ligma
here
yay take up the supplies oh okay
cool Hospital what oh wow you were
really far oh am I damn yeah I found a
town I was trying to find a grocery
store but there's not one in here
there's a grocery store I love shoing I
love sh we can shop at the hospital it
has five death
schulls wow wow I love that go
there your I love that
I'm sure there's food in this Hospital
of five
friends I am going your
way
yippe
[Music]
yippe so giggy did you already do the
like digging Quest from the trader yeah
I did the digging one wait how did you
get to the trader you went F I walked
yeah both of you oh IIT you guys I went
there how did you you're so damn girl
okay maybe I will walk to the traitor he
gives you a gun for free so friendly
yeah that's that's you got the gun s
nice maybe we should get guns before we
go into the five friend hospital or we
should just go in you're on your way
I'll
wait well well then let's get digging
rather than the gun I'd prefer some
water and food but okay maybe maybe at
the hospital they'll have water and food
I
see they might yeah you're I mean it's a
hospital you would expect the hospital
to have water Hospital see oh that would
be a welcome sight more dead than the
zombies yeah compared to
zombie have Undead
people that would be
terrible
purse oh what oh wait oh that looked
like I don't know that looks like Chanel
maybe Rob the zombies of their purse no
no no there was a there was a purse
lying around
oh got me some Louis Vuittons
maybe got them Gucci
who died and left his Prada bag here for
me oh that's
crazy at this day in age of the
Apocalypse wow apocalpse deeper I'm very
hungry your maximum stamina is reduced
how do I know
that o I love the Chikorita
residence like the
bananas the bananas no that's the
Pokmon is that Chita
yeah I learned about that one today what
why did I pick up an off Chita Banas
Chikorita Chita Chita
bananas I'm eating a raw
egg what what's the goal in this Quest
so
yummy do I just deep dig deeper and
deeper until I find something yeah you
basically just dig down and around in
that Circle until something pops up for
you sometimes it's pretty far
down damn I'm hungry and
thirsty life is rock man I mean this in
the nicest way I know I
[Music]
know we're all suffering
here I'm not what since when maybe we
should just convert to zombies since now
decided to stop suffering oh oh that's a
spirit feel like a Buddhist approach
yeah yeah yeah I'm out of stamina this
zombie is going to take me out of my
misery
die maybe Life as a zombie is
easier
maybe maybe they don't need like water
and stuff so I'm not dying I'm getting
closer somebody's boat
I can probably drink
glue GL probably did you do that when
you were a
child wa I'm thinking myself a grave I
realize go they do have Lou
Vons in the apocalypse come
back seven bucks is the trader evil and
they just like trap you into building
your own grave and once you're deep too
deep they will like cover it up like you
you would cover it up in never mind I
think there is treasure maybe they
weren't
lying they were not lying why would they
lie to you in the apocalypse I don't
know maybe you were in in with them and
and you were just trying to kill
everybody I would never you could
sandwich oh my God there's a dead body
here it's awesome I'll drink that the
front door is 3,000 HP he strong oh
don't worry I'll break it
[Music]
open are you sure yeah by the time you
get here it'll be
open okay let me try right
now do I go back to the trade or
no thank
you fine are you on your way to the
trader yes
vaguely ooh
sorry that wasn't even on
purpose it's a reflex it's only natural
yeah ouch I'm sometimes you just ooh
it's
true ow s like a garbage okay the
vulture is attacking me I didn't even
know that can happen I look like I'm
dead or
what sorry I I'm working on
it I think tell it was done I'm I don't
turn
away she'll be done
soon just get so tired hitting this
door me me
too
I it's just so hard oh oh it's open oh I
think I'm dying to what oh
goodbye you don't die
ooh okay oh he gives you a chice you gun
what did you take uh G did you take a
pistol or a rifle a shotgun oh oh she
Liv a
shot oh that's a lot um this is not did
I did I not get
any any meat from that bird
I can't eat the
vulture it's
Undead wait that's real it was a zombie
vulture and I'm going to turn into a
zombie
myself oh
no I don't know what to do
I didn't even realize I was being
killed I'm infected I think I just have
to die but I don't think I lose anything
from
[Music]
dying you
know so it's not that
bad those were food cans wait
where the gas can it's food if you're in
the universe of cars I
guess on the ground
where wait oh I am
encumbered oh right
here home cooking
weekly no kidding
grilled
corn I hope I remember this after I
die well I
remember
armor in my next
life I
will okay hold
on I did
this butcher an
animal
okay
I I was going to go all in
onler but now that seems like a bad idea
can I even make
the the
Knuckles Sonic and
Knuckles but you can just craft these is
gold
okay where's
my knuckle
wraps more plants what we need is more
plants for
sure search
bar oh
36 how do is that even possible what do
you mean level 36
Knuckles so this is all I can hope for
right now right is knuckle
wraps I should just save the steel
knuckle parts for
later I
suppose get punching how did how does
level ling up even work
though
like do your skills level up
individually or is it only all
together you need to
read oh like bar
brawling oh furious fist oh
[Music]
I
see man how am I going to
read wait am I going to turn into a
zombie in 2
hours what's that saying right
now you can't hurt me more than what has
already happened to
me should I start punching but my fists
don't do anything anything you don't get
XP for
punching
right I'm
thirsty
ow no I don't I don't want to die well
actually maybe it's
fine to die maybe I should
die in fact
I guess I can
respawn
here Cash
Money how are the lights still on that's
my
question a
cooler who put their rancid water in the
cooler be
honest look
up oh
is there a
ladder or am I just expected
to to
climb
painkillers Minecraft building block can
you do that
can of miso
soup customize our fittings mod a
scavenger
outfit legendary these seem really
good shotgun
ammo oh
no and I'm
fatigued I don't need that
anymore I don't know if I should even
eat because I feel like I'm going to I'm
going to
die and I should just
die and try again in the next
life how do I open this without
destroying what's
inside scrap the old clothes can you do
that use an axe is it I'm so strong
though I might just destroy
everything
inside I didn't Forge
steel
cement and Forge ahead I love
reading
okay where's my stupid
outfit weapons
bag big
hitters steel Club part I feel like I
should share because sharing is caring
but
but I'm just reading the
stuff by myself and you know if somebody
later reads
Knuckles and Sonic I can't be mad about
it and I won't
be unless I will
be where did my clothes go whatever it's
not worth that much probably
okay that seemed
good first step to impressing
them a base I have a base I live with
with 20 other girls not 20 I just can't
count I haven't found counting 101
yet I'm wet
M that was
tasty drink from pools of murky was it
murky dis boil murky
water do I get like
the the glass
back is my
question I kind of want to go over here
and search this one and then maybe head
back yes no you cannot breathe
here I understand I have seven
Health well it's about time for me to
start a new
anyway zombie fish wait is there fishing
in this game I would love to
fish they would be so impressed if I
fished something good
also I should spend my skill
points but I don't know what to spend it
on this is the new dredge
DLC passive healing is that a
thing hold
on is that
this oh
that does seem
good but am I going to die now no I'm
not going to
die it's just going to prolong my
suffering oh he's
swimming over
there got to respect
it the Harrison residence
I might find my
sham I might find my death
here and I'm okay with
that this is a nice place do you think
the residents are still
alive they've got a lot to
say his
I thought his T-shirt said
Riz their poor their poor teenage son
who has turned into a
zombie
ouch I'm just so close to
death and yet death will not find
me old old sham s
sandwich is that a real chicken or a
zombie chicken I think it's real chicken
I don't want to eat the chicken
though I just want to find
more
books cloth is good
too
oo I knew it was too good to be true oh
no she was a
doctor I forgot I was low
health no she's eating my spam
sandwich St my spam sandwich I need
that spawn near my
backpack I dying
instantly um
wait isn't it supposed to show me where
my backpack
is
oh is it this way oh open my
map okay it is this
way
okay just be aware oh I'm so fast
now there is a zombie
Doctor
around she sounds like she's in pain
ouch okay this thing seems really
good electrical parts aloe pink dye that
seems
fun somebody's trash
tool
boox steel
Parts I just want more books give me
more books I know books are the path to
knowledge tools digest oh wait I'm so
full and scrapping for fun
why do I have so much stuff in my
inventory
um I don't want to even eat right now
because because I I have I not
hungry for the what wait
when I've obtained all the ingredients
for water wait where
you mean the murky water they're not
talking
about they're not talking about a a pot
right I have not obtained a
pot still need a
pot we can read them directly from the
screen I will try
that you think they got a pot in
there but I'm like out out of stuff and
I'm
encumbered and it's two zombie
Stars I mean does the two zombies mean
there were two zombies inside because if
so I already killed both of
them which is
great it's too quiet in here
I heard
you I heard
you I have any other
weapons I like this thing I left the
repair kit at home
though he's so
loud
ow that's why you got to go unarmed
wait what happened my quest
progressed Bob's Cafe and clear out the
zombies is some did somebody else do
that need to use my
fists search the oven some people keep
pots in the
oven it's not unheard
of corn
meal
cabinet fine folk like this have got to
have a pot
right oh
no old sham sandwich but no
pot it's cuz they have the the cold
beard neon sign that's how you know they
don't
cook nobody who cooks puts a cold beer
neon sign in their
kitchen it would at least be in the the
man
cave
oh it's all
empty is it getting
dark somebody just got sleep apnea here
we should
leave car is nearby
I want to go
home Why didn't it make that
sound I'm so
full I don't need this Brotten
flesh why was it full of nitrate
powder curious
very
curious let's go
home which way is
home
uh wait oh this is home okay this is
home I was like is nobody at home we we
made it kind of far
follow the
road go
east we could we could go here
though can we stay the night there
should I go meet up with
them GG and
Kiara hold on is it this way
yes my what
zombies here okay all right I
loveu uh no I think she's doing the
quest
GG to
you oh okay on your way I'm on my way
it's really scary it's it's dark and
miss all this it's very
scary oh maybe I can't Farm
here a rotting Flash
yeah we need a farm plot if we want to
farm this might be all the man I can't
make my hops does anyone want to go to
the Traer for a quest if not it's
totally
fine I didn't want to I didn't run a
rush I just thought if you're going to
do something else why can I not use I
got to go there anyway um the food is
going to take a couple minutes to cook
but I put I put food might be one
upstairs keep saying charart meat B Bo
take no no no no charart meat is the
food it is the food oh really wow meat
is that you can
eat that's what it say that's the
[Music]
option that's all I can make right now I
need one more book to make make better
going to take both it's okay it's
okay I'll put one back CH stabbing in
the back you're going to eat my Char and
you're going to like it egg O it's so
dry okay I'll cook some eggs too
I'll I'm dying you have water wait why
are you dying should I not be here is
you should be here you should be here
what's happening don't worry wait should
we go into a VC the quest yeah we can go
okay okay yeah which one two four
okay what okay Cecilia you wanted to go
to the TR right
I this isn't four
but wait wait what what are youing are
you going to the Traer oh we're doing
K's Quest we're at the quest but I
started the quest before fauna and Sh
were there and it said if you're not in
the radios you will automatically fail
the quest so does it say anything for
you now no I'm going to make food while
we're here
campfire oh o
I have I have a lot of stuff if
anybody wants to carry
stuff what kind of stuff I don't even
know mechanical Parts iron pipe lead
duct tape polymer Casino coins like food
I've got food you need food and and I
actually I guess I'm somewhat fine with
food but water would be really nice but
I guess you don't have I have water but
I have an old sham
sandwich that's caused my diarrhea it's
now slowly going away so I'd rather not
eat enough I can I can relate to that I
understand it's so with the fire you can
cook yeah yeah you need a pot
though wait I knew need a pot I don't
have a pot damn it
wait I don't understand how do I get
this skill why is it locked why can't
you might have to level up your the main
stat so if it's blocked from getting you
might have to level up strength or
fortitude the big
attribute strength or
fortitude like Master Chef or so
learn
diam this one really
H uh okay I'm dying of dehydration oh
God no is there no water in this house
water
[Laughter]
outside I'm scared were they where why
is the music so scary you're surely
still uh like helping in terms of um
HP take him take him where are they take
the
leads upstairs oh yeah now he's here he
came down I look the water breaking the
windows there's two
zombies oh oh oh no oh I got no stamina
cuz I'm over in how early do you die
after it told you that you die another
one there's another one there's like 10
of them in here we shouldn't be in
here EV way
oh go we left KY alone in the house I'm
K I died I have no ST they're eating me
they're eating me not you respawn
respawn I'm respa I'm running
backwards spawn near my backpack let me
he how close am
I somehow there's more zombies than
there I thought there would
be I went into the
garage come into the garage I I seem to
it seems like I'm going to die because
yeah not even my stamina when I'm this
first I guess dying is theit better
option at this point maybe oh they're
fast now cuz it's night time is there
any downside in dying ones besides that
you have to run to your inventory it
changes the difficulty level of the game
oh to being easier yeah and then it like
changes the loot tables and stuff but
doesn't really matter we're just having
fun
okay I wouldn't mind it being easier oh
my God there's like 20 zombies okay very
ex to the gar it's sa okay just should I
just let her kill me then my diarrhea
will be gone too I'm running to the
garage I'm run into the
garage still on
Dat yeah
just down this is really bad to theall
game there a big
opening the garage I'm opening the
garage
out
spicy I'm going to
die let's all just die goodbye I have
decided to
die but the
stuff we can do it keep respawning we'll
get it okay I mean it'll be daytime
eventually yeah yeah yeah where I
spawned very close to my stuff I failed
the quest do I have to accept it again
oh they're all around
my they're all jumping around my
backpack
uh-oh ow ow oh they're all eating my
body while I'm maybe we should leave
because our Quest is
over yeah no let me just take my
backpack how do I take my whole backpack
there's a there's a button in the top
right of the box yeah it has up arrows
on it uh it says take all uh-huh okay
top left top top right of the box right
of the box so not of your screen but of
the Box what if you die without picking
up your things oh I don't actually top
right top top right up to top I am also
not sure okay let's run away out of here
I'm out we find the house next to the
traitor I think that's a good idea okay
I think I'm in trouble cuz I have no
speed
is it because you're
first it's cuz I have too much stuff oh
oh I also there's so many zomes but I
have so much good
stuff just it's okay you keep dying get
a little farther than last time each
time super a lot of zombies
though oh
no I found a a mining magazine but if
you learn it you learn how to make
coffee oh
how this is I don't know it says a super
strong longl lasting coffee that kept
you warmer than a well digger's ass
canra craft black strap a super strong
coffee should I keep a good Miner needs
to know coffee there's way too many
zombies near my backpack and I'm
freezing is your backpack still in the
in the quest Place yeah oh no no no no
no give me my backpack I see you I see
you oh no ST did you die again oh no you
got okay you shouldn't come over
here no you
again I think I'm in trouble I just
don't want all my stuff to die cuz I
have so much good
stuff I think the house you're next to
we can make home there see oh no I got a
skill on accident
die die die
die this looks like it was a child he's
wearing like teenager cloes I feel
bad someone wearing a t-shirt that said
RZ RZ yeah he's got the zombie
Riz is it a zombie farmer oh my God he's
got a good
Farm oh I I found the house we can make
it's really close
to okay I'm almost there I'll start
putting stuff down I'm
leaning no that our new house it's not
that house I don't think so that's a
zombie house house is it wait distract
the zombies I'll find the right
direction um I can't them
okay okay I'm running towards the house
that where appar found it okay okay okay
okay I'm going to put a chest down there
are zombies in here but we can turn this
into our new house um what more zombies
could you find an empty
house once I kill them it will be
empty won't they respawn there die no
they don't respawn okay ouch they just
spawn around you the Clement residence
oh I leveled up oh yeah yeah I'm in here
okay it looks
peaceful um where's the I might be
leading a million zombies to our new
peaceful
house once I kill them they won't be
here
anymore it's very wishful thinking I
like
it wait did I lose
them hopefully okay I'm just going to
off in I didn't lose them I didn't lose
them oh don't worry I have a four
bullets let's barricade the door
away oh oh you shooting them with the
shotgun I have shotgun shells I have no
more arrows okay okay okay this your
storage crate yeah yeah I put that down
die behind you behind you sorry taking
really long time to reload okay okay
okay okay Cy living
room bed
roll why can I not use the Band-Aid at
this time when I'm
hurt um I think one of the Bandaids is
only if you're
bleeding oh I
think all right well we have a house
so yes is this really where we want to
stay until we find a better place it's
good
enough maybe there's a pot in here it's
pretty close to the trader
too oh I still need to go see the
trader we can go pick up Quest together
understand this I don't understand this
I don't oh there's half a zombie on the
stove
what for dinner have a
zie how do you how do you make a bear
cane um you can make spikes and you
usually plant a bunch of spikes outside
your
home how do you how do you like
barricade the window you want this
tactical Warfare
book what do you learn from that oops oh
assault rifles
I don't need to learn how to make an
assault rifle I don't either I'm going
I'm going unarmed fists what was I going
to do should we make a bed roll and then
place it here or yeah I put one in here
okay just randomly in this
house all
right and what happens to the other bed
roll that we placed elsewhere I think as
long as you use this one this is your
new spawn
point okay h when I place it it is is
automatically my spawn point or yeah I
said it's owned by you okay
um wait a second I need to heal myself
somehow if you die you'll be full health
again that's been my strategy so
[Music]
far oh okay I also make a wooden crate
and place it somewhere we can place it
on the wall oh oh
nice okay
finally
this oh I
see I got my fists
out oh my God there's a zombie upstairs
upstairs let me punch him don't worry
I'm going to punch okay I'll let you
punch it you haven't properly properly
cleaned this place yet punch his face
punching him he's killing me he's
killing me you guys need
help clubbing him I'm clubbing him
clubing don't F
me don't P the F don't die I forgot
there was friendly
fire that is very important to know
fixing
me door is likeed who's in
here say smling in here sounds like
Meagle that's my stomach we have found a
Ed the door is locked but there's like
look look you want to spend time
together hitting this gun box oh wait
zombie I'm punching him I'm punching him
okay okay I think you guys might need
help huh
me we're gting up on the zombie I'm
going to die oh he's hurting me he's
hurting me ow okay I I did the finishing
blow with my sledgehammer nice ooh
cardboard boxs do you want to do you
want to hit this with me H what oh very
scary oh that will take a
while yeah but what if there's something
really cool in
here I believe
it has so much HP something must be
really cool in here I think there's a
zombie
downstairs is this house cursed will
there always be like zombies on
Gathering here no I unless they smell us
I'm scared I think they smelled
me I'm hiding in the
bathroom we have reached Day free by the
way oh three and but we're not playing
today until the seventh day ride that
would be kind of long yeah we're only
playing until day four end of day four
one more
hour or two
two yeah two more
hour I'm still relatively awake even
though it's 5:00 a.m. oh no strong I
heard you were adjusting your sleep
schedule for this oh yeah I I kind of
like messed it up cuz like my 3D live it
was like at 2:00 a.m. my time because I
was trying to be more na friendly for it
and then after that was my music video
reveal so I was just so excited so I I
stayed up long and then I was like well
7 days to dies is in the middle of the
night for me so might as well not fix my
sleep
schedule
yeah yeah we should put a land claim
block land claim
[Music]
block F you what are you doing don't die
hi in the bathroom I'm scared I hear the
zombie aggressively shall we save the
maiden in in the spare or how do you say
it I shall almost I have 17 I have 17 HP
I can't go down there fa sorry I wanted
to place my bed roll but there's no room
in the bathroom you not live in the
bathroom there's no room in the
bathroom Okay wor fancy toilet's almost
open okay is it a safe or yeah once I
break this open I'll come kill that
guy me one or the other I feel so safe
around gigy she's like hardcore yeah
right I have to open this
I have a machine gun now this machine
gun yeah yeah did he give me ammo too I
uh he gave me a few shotgun shells he
might be in there with you
somewhere what of their shotgun ammo in
this chest well I still got to give you
I still got to give you my shotgun ammo
okay you can also put it in the crate
okay okay I got 15 machine gun rounds so
I'm got to be very careful with
my I'll go
like one shot at a time which is not one
I usually would do from machine gun but
okay what was in it did we get anything
I didn't get anything we get anything I
didn't get anything with a waste of time
gig okay oh bad news fa there's nothing
in the chest good news careful it sounds
really scary down we're on our way to
help you
I'll clean up the
attic you're hiding here and the zombies
not even outside but it's so
loud sooud inside the
house don't worry I will I'll kill him
don't go out there it's dangerous was
the zombie just a mirage perhaps he's
here he's just he's just Outdoors oh
he's
chilly oh
sick I want to sneak up on him he'll
never imagine someone coming from behind
to hit him on the head if I can even
find a way out of here
what I have found a coing magazine for
people and cornmeal and a chicken R he
knew I was here I let him in I vampire i
w him into our house he's going to suck
our blood the light in my eyes is fading
no I kill
you
[Music]
stop she can't me I love staying out of
this I love feeling safe and
cozy oh don't worry I spawn on my bed oh
where is he now I him oh
yeah why why are you naked gy sorry I
didn't mean to that was very made me
very
uncomfortable where is a really buff man
he's over here should I let the last
one come
in no I'll use my
Slammer on their butt
no eating
you let let me hit let me hit okay okay
okay
okay 7 HP you go okay okay okay she so
much I got her don't worry I got
her good very good good progress this is
we need to
the the block the block oh the land
claim block I can try crafting one L
land I don't want to do the bed cuz I'm
scared this is somebody's backpack
this's backpack I
probably where's the house I I
purposefully spawned elsewhere now
because I was scared that if
I bed around did you guys already choose
spawn on your bed you were spawned in
the house yes yes you're going the wrong
way right now if you turn around you're
going the wrong way you're saying that
to me oh you're so sweet thank
you thank you you're taking you're
having an eye on where I'm
going Randon
that what that I have no she dropped
loot she dropped rifle world do you want
to learn how to she dropped two rifle
worlds I ha that I use rifles do you
want
steroids uh do I want steroids okay take
it take the steroids off of her body
this will make my punch better
probably wait where are this green thing
oh
oh only 12
minutes I shouldn't have these steroids
I never use
items
yes don't you use machine oh I use a
machine gun oh I oh see I don't I don't
know cooking uh shooting is different
difficult I don't know anything
about guns even after all this
time H oh we have the land clim block
nice I won keep this it's daytime if
4:00 a.m. is
daytime we survived
ew I don't know what I expected to
happen I punched some guts until they
exploded y it was it was very
gross is that a zombie or we survived
the night G we did it is that you where
in the distance yeah yeah I'm looking at
a car I'm opening this car are you
looking into buying a car in this
economy I want a car so bad we should
get a helicopter aim big or go little
too big
yeah you can have helicopter in the end
game o that dream is too large for me
H maybe too large for 7 days I want a
bike I want a bike oh yeah there was a
bike C in the you found right yeah
handlebars for my new bike
yeah what's that let's go get a quest
oh Nest I'm crafting lots of arrows ooh
nice arrows are always good I should
probably craft some more
too generally I haven't crafted in a
while what do you need again for
arrows
FEA wood and
stone wood and stone and Feathers M
pretty sure
yeah okay I've neglected the feathers e
keeps punching they keep exploding gross
gross but I got 80 XP for
that we're going to be so we have to be
the richest people in the
apocalypse I have seven
bucks s
books oh seven books or dollars bucks
dollars I wish I had seven books wait
can you spend money here yeah at the
trainer but he's so overpriced does he
take cash no you have to uh sell the
cash you have into like his kind of coin
dollars are worthless
oh there's actual b b and coins there
is the way you
[Applause]
smell did I just I'll give you some work
but you better not disapp it's a deal
scared to and you'll find yourself on
the wrong end of a ro H
sound
hello hello I got a quest to go dig
stuff up oh is it the ah it's the first
Trader Quest I guess yeah okay good yeah
start there and then we can try the the
the fetch Quest again at some point
I have iron arrow heads do you want that
GG
okay can you use these
brass brass I found brass it looks like
gold
ooh brass but it's brass yeah brass we
can maybe make a a TR bone with the
brass
yeah from a bone
champ I have a quest 100 million miles
away
oh what quest is thats okay um I don't
know if you see it on your map but it's
called tier one
clear no I don't think I see
yours okay I'm going to run over and
kill them oh
maybe hey wait no don't go with me
to oh I'll help fa with digging okay and
then we can do yeah we got let her dig
mhm another
sandwich
M no don't eat that fun dis sand getting
used to it though really can we build
tolerance towards I think there's a perk
you can buy oh but I didn't buy how many
points do I
have uh one point
H chat tell me what to where to put my
point if I want to be able to make
healing items
ooh we need Aloe
Vera right but can you cannot make that
by
default I think there's a book for
[Music]
it cuz this is just boosting your
natural healing rate am I just supposed
to dig
magazine only oh really okay did you
start the quest yes or should I have
waited no you can start
it
okay I let my device
die uh-oh not your
device feel like I'm digging my own
grave you are
I will be burying you
here there's my shovel this my shovel oh
you found it
food here I will dig your way out
there's a zombie I will kill this zombie
instead while you dig your way
out I'm stuck don't be stuck I'm killing
him he has a very cool shirt very cool
not a mustache where are you
oh you're in the you're there you
did
wa how can he
jump how do you get to places so fast
it's almost like you're cheating I run
really
quickly I'm getting him I'm getting him
oh no I don't want to be in
this fin
him oh sweet to eat
exp okay we can go turn in we're going
to the trader again so we can turn in
the quest okay now once you accept the
new Quest I'll go towards wherever that
starts and then we can start it together
[Music]
I have an aloe vera
seed that'll be great for making an aloe
vera Farm maybe yeah I think you need
those for healing right medicine
[Music]
yep
yeah ah okay I put the shotgun shells
into my wood crate you can take it
whenever you want thank
you wait am I going the wrong way wait
is this way right
yeah
s okay I'm out of stamina and will this
automatically be in the same place where
we were before is it like randomized I
wonder they're random Quest you can pick
which one you want to take and then I
took one that's really far west why
would you do that can we get the same
Quest no that'ss in the head I know you
can share
them yeah cuz that's what was happening
when I started the quest and you were
there then we were sharing it actively
but the people who weren't close to it
were not sharing it I
see so we should start it when
everybody's there okay at the objective
what are you looking at now that you did
the job I guess you ain't that D I'll
Goose to Traer for now cuz you girls are
there
[Music]
ugy check what you need to craft better
gear like wouldn't I need a new magazine
for that you might
H this menu is just so much I feel like
rest was easier uh heavy armor like that
one maybe he has books i' tell you to go
[\h__\h] yourself but you but the is so
expensive we can find our own scam
yeah yeah I need an armor
magazine I'll return back to the house
real quick cuz I have 5 million items
again oh there me too actually
oh you
okay I see you I'm here I see you yipp
salvation no no my my you're took it
from the bird I am the bird mother of
all me running away with feathers in my
mouth you have eaten my children
feathers yummy oh God you are the most
terrifying of them all you're so happy
about it
I'm so sorry I can't believe you did
that do we have to just pretend that
like everything's fine because otherwise
she will go against us she keeps
defending us from zombies so I think
we it is killer be killed it's like
we're befriending
Sauron is it that bad it's not that bad
is
it that's a bit dramatic we're just the
befriending
other oopsie sorry F you like Lord of
the Rings right yes you did you try
watching rings of power no I have I have
not is there a reason for it should I
well I people [\h__\h] on it so much but the
second season that just aired it was
pretty good I'm so scared to say it I
think I could like it cuz I really like
I really like fantasy and I really like
Lord of the Rings and so yeah yeah yeah
yeah people will probably like every
time I bring up Lings of power my chat
go like shut up I don't want to hear
what you're saying but but at the second
season was pretty pretty good
so if you just want something more like
you know like fantasy just see it as a
separate fantasy show you
[Music]
know it doesn't need to be good for you
to like it yeah what does that mean wait
say again to be good to be good yeah
yeah interesting wolf is my favorite
show ever you think that's a good show
GGY gy wait don't run out come back did
you see the ammo in in my crate up
here here top left I up
here thank you it's not in the
way
okay well then shall we uh did you guys
already accept the quest from the trader
or did you just I have one Quest I have
not
accepted okay well we can go to the
really far one we'll get it once we're
there for gigy okay okay we can see
there's anything fun on the way too okay
any books to
read uh-oh you're so literate oh yeah
that was
laggy let me make sure that I
have why isn't it why is it on my
compass oh I see it it's 1 Point 6 km
West O all right but let's not get into
too much trouble until then because
otherwise we might just arrive they're
dead we just respawning
infinitely fauna you know what somebody
says what fauna likes Twilight cuz it's
bad no I like it I like it cuz it's
good you haters in the chat you ha
ERS I mean I've never watched Twilight
you've never watched Twilight I
purposely stayed away from it and
perhaps it was the right choice
but I I don't know but you know I don't
know vampires are like a little bit too
tacky for me what about werewolves
Werewolves too you might hat it
then but if you love anything vampire
you probably like
it even in Sims I didn't like the
vampires s vampires little
strange those aren't real
vampires yeah no they seem pretty
realistic to
me have you seen a real vampire in this
they act like The
Sims I I assume that Sims is a life
simulation so everything that is in
there must exist in real life yeah I see
they teleport into your house and then
they play on your computer until you ask
them to
leave have I been deceived is it wrong
have I been
bamboozled real vampires smell you from
a mile away and then they smell your
fair oh
no oh they got a good good nose they do
and then you can smell so yummy to them
wait giggy are you also a Twilight fan
then no I'm a werewolf fan but I like
vampires too but werewolves are in
Twilight no but if you're a werewolf fan
V Twilight is not going to be a good
time for you it's a mushroom Mining
Company mushroom miny how fun there's an
RV in here do you think there's
stuff wait fun
wait are are you should we go in there
without gigy I'm not sure but
interesting wait you left
left I've been Ling for the quest okay
okay okay oh yeah wait where where is
she e oh that way that
way this cool thing got you oh the RV
e yep like Breaking Bad yeah like a
Breaking
Bad ooh I think Breaking Bad ruined RVs
for me cuz it's all I thinko now I
didn't watch Breaking Bad either wait
you should watch Breaking Bad I should I
watched it recently it's good and the
call Sal too is good yes there's a pile
of books there's a a harvesting tool
crafting skill book and a workstation
crafting skill book that's a
lot I'll just take the books for now but
I won't use them so I can share a
picture of one of the game developers
dogs every time I see like a regular
photo of an animal in a video game I
just assume that it's one of the
developers pets does that mean that this
pict animal is it does it mean that the
picture of this bird here is also from
the developer of the game no this is
like a star photo did you see this one
this or that is the developer this bird
looks so human like oh yeah this is a
dog on on someone's lawn and then this
is at why was developer not have an
eagle he could own one I can imagine him
owning an eagle if he wanted yeah is
that
legal probably not but who are we Eagle
it's a legal
eagle have you guys seen the the name of
the developers of this game no idea like
when you copy pasted the permission your
description I forgot to do that what
their name is on that on that copy paste
thing their name is on there yeah yeah
you should look it up huh I forgot to
put it in my description cuz this was
very last minute the fire poost wait you
she's
running what Ki just like runs away and
loses
us got to be fast in
the licks the ground she went this way
she's on a mission I use my vampire
senses can you smell me
[Music]
mhm oh my
God I found Oh I thought this was a
church but it's
not that is not a cross that is I don't
even know what that is wow those are
lights oh it does look like like a the
vultures oh yeah the zombie vultures
Zombie f the vulture please oh we got it
I was so mad cuz I thought it was like a
regular
vulture but then is regular v no it's a
zombie vulture and you can't eat it I
feel like vultures are just always
zombies yeah kind of they're very zombie
like all
right get down get
down oh I can't collect we're doing so
good did I get it we're doing good
indeed I thought you were a
zombie it's about to be there's an armor
zombie in here watch out in this world
it's killer be
killed I want to I want to get in and
punch him punch him hey sled himo let's
go
ow m
M what's inside some's kind of strong
he's slapping me uh-oh he has stronger
fist than
[Music]
you I might be infected by the zombie oh
that's the ammo I need oh it's a
lumberjack he's strong he's very
tanky ah he can
jump oh there was a wow lady can I have
I'll avenge you I'll avenge you dude
no e my I'll stop it don't you dare my
friend he's de he's
[Music]
dead
a I want the dress give me the dress
lady there's a dress she's wearing a
nice nice
dress h
wait did I lose my experience do you
actually I thought you didn't lose
experience when you die I don't think
you do wait what's purple the purple bar
oh yeah it is food take the food is it
lower it is I think unless I leveled up
I level
up oo oh I think I leveled up actually
you're no longer infected so we won't
have to put you down you would do that
you would put me down I might have to
Old Yeller you I don't want to do it
think of the rabbits
Lenny the rabbits are so beautiful we're
going to have a nice rabbit farm just
look at the water and don't
worry I zoned out for a minute what are
you talking about I don't think that's
old
yellow well do you want to be in dog or
human we're talking about um pting po
down dog she has gone through too much
already yeah she has to go through a
little more
why what are these trials you're putting
her through should we go across the
water or should we go around the
water is it smart to travel through the
water are there sharks in the big Waters
noit this guy got a hat get
wet is is this guy did he used to be in
a biker gang yeah right he looks like
the biker in
GTA except for the helmet they
hels damn he's buff he is really BFF
die has to go through a cannon event
hold on guys I want to kill this rabbit
what no I want I want no don't hurt the
rabbit I'm sorry but I need the fat this
is about Survival how will we eat no why
is the bunny it became a
fish oh we killed it it became a fish
did it Fly Away it no it dived away in
the water yeah it just went like onto
the ground in the water and like really
far really didn't want to be eaten by
you has some crazy survival skills
bunnies on the water I guess we can go
around cuz there's so many houses nearby
yeah do you want to look into all of
them yeah who am I to turn down a cool
house a
boat we have that that would be nice
it's kind of a weird boat though looks
like H get on my private
yacht yeah me when I'm inviting women
over yeah I have a
yacht I'm impressed that this is a
shop because there's a neon sign that
says
open but I don't believe it oh hi zombie
hello
zombie ow oh my gosh they have ceiling
zombies in here what ceiling zombies
they came from the ceiling
terrifying like a ceiling maybe it's
hanging from a ceiling fan maybe the
ceiling fan was the curse the the cause
of death ceiling fans nowadays guys be
careful some of these zombies are so
tanky yeah I know is it because we're on
day three
now get strong that bad it's
dead sorry I might have punched you no
no yeah but if we go to so many places
that I I feel like we might be very hurt
by the time we get to the
destination we just we'll just respawn
you know about that
right I just got a [\h__\h] T of money from
the from the cash register we can share
our
findings if you want Oh two magazines a
wood splitter mod we're
rich electrical crafting skill and
workstation crafting skill do any of you
use 9 mm ammo I use
7.62 very specific and I have found a
pipe
rifle a fully built pipe rifle I have
acquired do you want one FAA because do
you have a gun yet no I don't use guns
use my
fist hey weren't guns the the uh reward
for the digging Quest I got a a pipe
weapon oh okay a pipe weapon
book a
that's a great
reward it's the only one that came with
a book it's the only one that improves
your
skills I think it is the best
one Perle uses the same SE oh nice then
I'll continue using cuz I have that
ammo okay
well this I'm running out of space yeah
P up on garbage again yeah that's also
why we shouldn't have you know gone so
far
fun stuff wait we can
consolidate GG do you want my feathers
okay did you run away again no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no I'm here I'm here will we ever run
into mountain lions I have a magazine
that teach that that gives us 10% more
damage against mountain lions mountain
lions do you% is not that much riding FL
okay do you want gas
what's gas what about you're just giving
her your trash we're consolidating yeah
it's called cons do you want clay soil
uh no not really do you want a
splint maybe that do you want um cloth
fragments and plant fibers chanem and
maybe cotton
[Laughter]
how about a sewing kit shotgun shells
I'll take those oh
yeah I have nitrate
powder how do I take one of these I'll
will take that do you want a
mushroom just a singular mushroom yeah
do you want singular
cornmeal okay I'll take the cornmeal oh
my gosh but girls do you know how I
separate one item from another
um right click potentially yeah alt
right click okay does somebody want this
magazine it's a good one four oh I read
a few of these are you ready if you keep
fun then or you could get even
stronger for you oh I read a few of
these too oh you too you did too we both
get stronger you want a seed maybe I'll
take it back cuz I only read you want
seed
okay oh the seeds H I'm leaving gosh
okay we're following we're
following I guess we can go across the
water I suppose okay yes I'm on my way
yippee there's a car in
here who who
drowned guys I can't breathe here the
car drowned what kind of question is
that it's telling me that no way can't
breathe here why not I don't know why
can't I breathe start reading everything
okay this game's
broken can
I my stamina okay this is why maybe you
shouldn't swim across big Waters because
my stamina is uh am I going to die I'm a
little scared I'm I'm I'm ding I'm ding
I can't guys guys making cry just Mak my
stamina Lo it back up okay while I was
drowning how am I thirsty when I was
literally in the
water this question will never leave us
I suppose wait this water looks clean
maybe we should drink it yeah it's very
green I mean
[Laughter]
blue oh nice
shot
die wa
there's another one I would really like
to find a cooking pot I know right they
seem rare for like how much you need
them yeah where's our cooking pot he's
dead don't worry we're only 400 m away
from my
quest it feels like a much longer path
than
that we got so many goodies on the way
it's
true oh this is true I have terrible
news everyone there more water no but I
I can't breathe all of a
sudden that is a
problem just make sure you're full on
stamina before you start yes oh but it
loads back up wor even when you're
drowning it loads back up we'll
survive maybe not and this the stamina
goes down very fast yeah it kind of does
I'm drowning okay I'm back just keep
your head up I'm drowning and I'm back
there's zombie on the shore drowning
here drowning oh God Dodge him Dodge him
and I'm back and I'm drowning and and
now now we're back so well no I'm
drowning too don't worry were you at
full stamina when you left no
no oh oh I shouldn't be sprinting huh I
didn't know I was sprinting in the water
I didn't know you could it's very fine
when you're not sprinting I'm drowning
yeah stting fine when you're not
sprinting There's a Zombie over here
don't don't make eye contact I've
already made eye contact she's walking
in the water maybe she will turn into a
drown in the water how can she do that
maybe let's see did she change no maybe
she'll have a trident when she turns
into a drown that'd be
sick I realize now you're talking about
Minecraft I thought you were talking
about The Witcher for some reason oh
no oh did you watch The Witcher no I
didn't but I did beat with I right I
right you were playing it you beat it
you beat just the just the base game I
still have the DLCs to play I'm going to
play it at some point too should it's
really
fun good
well right now I'm playing Zelda and
then also now I will start
playing Diablo again because the DLC
came
out
yeah g you did you play the you did you
did you play the main story or are you
going to start from the beginning I'll
start from the beginning okay okay and
we can get together for the
DLC vehicle adventur you like AR RPGs VA
what is a
wait did we talk about this what does
the A stand for augmented reality
PG it's like the top down style of game
RPG yeah kind of like
Diablo yeah yeah Diablo 4 what about I
played torch light too what is that a
long time ago I think it's like that's
just like Diablo gy gigy stop pH it's
really far behind wait I'm I'm coming
don't worry Okay
Okay g gy gigy so fast I'm
sprinting I'm be over I'm going the
actually halfway through the main story
so like I'm pretty close apparently to
the main story ending and then I'll wait
for
youy yeah I need to maybe that will be
better playing uh world of warrow
together I don't know we can do both you
guys going to play
wow yeah play WoW I'll play WoW with you
really let's go I knew you were a wow
kind of
girl I only tried both for me wow once
and my experience is it took a million
years to level H and then I got tired of
it so I used like the level boost that
you get when you buy it but then I
switched my class and then I had no idea
what my class did because I was suddenly
like a Max Level different class H well
the thing is I already told gigy we're
not taking any kind of level boost level
boost yeah cuz I feel like it's for the
Nostalgia you got to grind through the
quests and everything go for all the
beginning like areas that you that you
experienced in the past I think when I
played it was like when was it it was
like 2020
or
something no maybe it was earlier
2018 and I think they like teared down
the leveling a little bit since then cuz
it was very long at that point maybe
there's exp like
experience I just don't I mean like the
the something that boosts the rate of
how you get
exp I want to boost the level I know is
this the quest spot or yeah it's the
quest spot hey did you start it yeah I
started it I think I was no am I do I
have it I think I have it okay okay okay
oh I think I have it too
y drop blue
loot a I hope he's got shotgun shells
take more
shotgun oh jeez they're here I thought
they were dead I don't fit for the door
how did you make it for the door I
haven't been
eating lost some weight okay I got rid
of the
door get him get him get him get him oh
there's so many of them oh this is such
a cute like American
Diner not sure about the customers
though maybe we should call the manager
like yeah
that's how you should do a business here
oh I missed my shot I am not throwing
away my shot you haven't missed your
shot with me
yet pointed my fingers can we get
married on wow is that a thing what yes
I'm sure it is we have to have a wedding
on Wow we can invite everyone to our wow
wedding oh God we got to go to the to
the to the
in yeah what is it the server
spicy time and spicy time in the
Inn take off your
armor we to consumate
our and just sit down on a on a bed and
where the walk oh you can literally not
do anything stream it everyone has to
see our marriage and everything after
too yeah otherwise it won't be believed
that you know yeah that we got married
back in the day times on the roof I
think there might be zombies up there
kill them we had to the in medieval
times for royalty you know there was
always people there watching to make
sure that the the air has been placed in
the lady you know I don't want to die I
don't want to die a up here yeah this
I'm also oh my God don't worry don't
worry I'm taking the shot I'm taking a
shot
okay I'm sorry I'm just really into
medieval stuff like wow is wow medieval
I'm ouch I got shot with an
arrow who hit you with the air I don't
know that the zombies can do that it's
crazy I didn't know the zombies do how
to do
that that's what I
get uh anyone still alive we did it we
did it we did it we the we did it oh
shotgun shipping crate why is it always
shotgun gel scrape Digger
mod 25% more damage to get hurt hurt the
hurt the dirt hurt the dirt do you not
want the shotgun shells oh where are
they in the crate ah and there's 9 mm
ammo which I don't think I use do I does
somebody need need the 9 mm ammo I have
some in my inventory vory I'll just
hoard them do you need
7.62
ammo uh I need yes I need indeed oh I
drop here even though I have yet to use
my gun I'm scared to use it there's
another photo of a dog and I'm telling
you it's one of the developer
dogs come look at this dog it's very you
go down there we go
this just wearing an outfit on a couch
so cute this is totally one of the dev's
pets that is someone's dog for sure they
should have name plates too yeah I don't
like this dog you don't like this dog
that's the kind of dog I don't like
where's the cats we need more cats where
are the
cats actually one of them is lying next
to me on the bed I can't believe she's
still here normally she normally she
goes away when I'm talking CU she knows
I
stream like you talking no no no no she
likes me talking but she knows when I
stream cuz whenever I talk to the
computer she gets it and then when I'm
done talking she immediately re-enters
the room yes yes you're give me your
privacy our cats are so smart I thought
it was only I thought it was only my cat
didn't like when I stream and
leaves a but when she's like really
really needy then she will stay in the
room like now she really wants to be
next
yeah it's because like I interrupted our
nap that we were having and now she's
like what the hell where's my nap I was
supposed to have a nap with you so now
she's here cute smothie it's her bedtime
it's kind of late for her it's always
her
bedtime how much HP do you girls have 30
83 83
awesome fin the we can try to go
straight back to the traitor without a
train yeah wait I want to Dr my gun all
our item okay is she dead she dead oh
damn it okay next time we're in danger
I'll test my
gun this don't wor guys we're only 1.2
km away from
home that doesn't sound like much oh oh
I just realized that by the time we get
there he might be close wait he closes
he closes at night he hates us oh well
we can sleep over it should we go to
jimbos wait that store looks really cool
I want to go to
jimbos 800 worms for
you yeah also here is
a there's a lot of zombies at jimbos
wait where did you go yeah let's let's
save my ammo for the Jimbo uh zombies
the jimbos jimbos we are on our
way ah this a good idea yes it's always
a good ide what's wrong with dying and
coming back to life crch it's a
destroyed workbench all mail
boxes steal their
mail he mail boxes are fun three of
them I can learn how to make a
coffin that will be useful ooh wait what
do you do with a
coffin I don't know sleeping them
like a
vampire a
vampire oh ranches or one
wrench oh those are useful I think you
can use them on the car on the car do
items have
levels or do I have three
wrenches maybe both or might be a I
think it's a level three wrench okay we
get inside here uh the door is locked
locked wa I want to be inside
jimbos oh okay I lost an HP on the fence
oh let me break this I'm
dismantling all right my oh you're
you're
crazy oh there you go uh it's very loud
in there there's a zombie behind oh okay
how do we use this oh oh oh no get sh
uhoh uhoh who she shooting there's a
vult oh okay smooy left my cat has
decided this is enough
screaming the vult the
vs out I have a shotgun with your name
on it he has
loot well it seems the gun was very
efficient you want um 6 7.62 mm
ammo oh
yeah I hope Jimbo has a
PO I know how come none of these is tea
I can eat
sand is that what it is
yeah
I
water it water a lot of water like water
we can't drink because we don't have a
cooking pot
I might drink it anyway I have more ammo
for you
kiaha what water ammo oh ammo okay
that's nice thank you I found some water
I found some pure mineral
water can I please have you can drink it
off of me after I kill out of your belly
button yeah you can sip it right out oh
my
goodness that's the best way to drink
water gives it a little bit of a taste
you know a nice
taste get him get him I don't want to
waste my ammo too much okay you can have
my pure mineral water let's
go what's in here oh there sealing
Zombies watch out feeling zombies the
feeling
zombies yum I'm punching his head
oh
no okay head come
on oh yeah oh yeah oh wow that looks
like fireworks oh my
God you
good oh
no I'll be okay where are you don't I
jumped down from that
boom oh wow oh where did she come from
there's quite a bit don't kill me out
a I have one HP one HP all right I
missed my shot she sorry sorry sorry I'm
so sorry I'm so sorry for screaming
don't worry can scream this shot after I
drank water man the water was for
nothing don't worry I won't miss the
next
shot
ah so I will spawn near my backpack
now oh oh
no wait where are okay they're gone we
are safe
scary I'm coming to get my
backpack oh there's somebody here still
oh okay die wa you one shot oh God I you
zombie my
bad Jima where the cooking po I like how
unlike
was it like that with Minecraft or so
when you pick up all of your stuff it
goes back into the exactly same slots
where you originally had it I love
it why are you in a
suit I'm checking his
boats boats boats boats nice
boat he got these homemade boats
too everyone in this work world could
only make
boat can we get it
started I
wish but there's helicopters in the game
I wonder if there's also like any way we
can have our own boat oh I know probably
not worth anymore it probably wouldn't
even be worth it right cuz are there any
like real big like oceans on this map
probably not
that must be good loot oh it's not
really well so should we be swimming
back to the trader oh is it going to get
dark soon yes yeah we should try to make
a way
back wait do we have a fire can we make
a fire I can make a fire or should we go
back we could go back okay I'm going
back
okay am I cucumber no I'm cucumber
I'm so
cucumber damn that's why we should go
back
ladies I want to grill some
corn me too but I don't know if I can
actually I have the recipe but I don't
know if you need a pot
or everything in this game needs a podt
we don't have I know it's like the
apocalypse can't you like improvise a
little bit guess I'm buil now just throw
the corn right on the fire it'll be fine
eles let's make eles you would think
there' be more abandon pops out here too
yeah
right maybe the trader has all of
them all right Trader we're coming back
now he's
s when does he
close I too
early he's probably already close now
yeah cuz it's like 10:00 p.m. now uh-oh
almost he opens really early in the
morning but like
6 okay we get there we'll still need
some time to get home
anyway wait where's I'm following fauna
fauna are you following Gigi no I'm
swimming she swimming oh she's still in
there ah my leg is broken and I'm over
wait do you need to Sprint oh yes I need
one of those flints
of no
don't worry I'm almost there are we
going to have to take you out back and
shoot you no I'm not ready I'm not I
give so much to live
for the splint thank you what is the
splint does it fix legs yeah it's going
to fix my leg also it's actually broken
okay it's not it's not my legs fall I
just have a fracture so it's not going
to help me I'm going to eat this egg
instead oh I can hold the Flint though
since you're over
encumbered okay is a raw good no no does
not taste good at all do you want a lamb
ration um I'm disappointed in you girls
that you're not ready to eat a raw egg
especially you gy thought you were
hardcore you're of corn I'm eating the
eggs you can have this
corn me or fauna I don't need it you
don't want oh can you I'll take it but I
have like I have chicken rations and
peas just one each okay I well we should
get running yeah if we stay in one spot
for too long they'll smell
us just like a vampire will imagine the
smell of us
combined doesn't smell like what do we
smell she's so fast I'm she's too fast
she smell she's killing me I don't want
to die she a she's a
Zoomer did I hit her oh you got her oh
she's still alive
Dam okay I think she's dead good job I
mean we could just run away from her
but we get exp right yeah we XP
okay all right you ready to swim across
the ocean
ah my leg is broken oh no good thing we
have another
splint wait the zombies are coming wait
I can I swim with a broken leg if you
want to survive you will
wow oh hey it heals in 2 hours oh wait
that's pretty good H speed and he your
leg like that oh zombie sprinted that's
why they're so fast makes sense
not scary
like I am definitely swimming
slowly what are your thoughts on zombie
vampires I mean vampires are kind of
zombies right they're
Undead so do you think zombies are hot
no there's only one hot zombie there's
one hot zombie yeah there's one
but like the ones in this game not
really the ones in the dress still have
kind of banging bodies though yeah I
didn't notice that the one of the red
dress I they model them like
that she was a she was a model in her
past
life um when I get out of this water can
I have a splint or whatever it is yes of
course thank you
you I'm almost out of the water too the
one person without a broken
leg so
fast what fauna also broken leg no wait
I thought I thought your leg got healed
immediately by the spr oh no I I think
mine's a fracture I have to look at my
debuff oh it's a sprained
leg jumping or sprinting will delay
healing or even hurt you but the zombies
will catch me this finally made my dream
come true I always wanted to break a
leg really yeah I never had an
experience like breaking something I hav
either but I don't really want I don't
really want that did you never dream of
having a cast and having your friends in
SCH kind yeah kind of oh
yeah and then like I don't know your
friends always carry your backpack for
you like to your next guess class you
know they maybe they would would they h
they better have friends break your legs
necessary to have
friends okay thank you all right uh how
does one use this where did it oh oh
it's it's like a ah I see
use does it go away right away it does
go away but I have like 39 M of a leg I
don't understand what that means 39 me
minutes
light oh I think it's something like a
cap and how much I could run or no I
don't is it
minutes I'm minutes oh well okay that's
confusing because it could also stand
for meters
so I see I can't run or my leg hurts
more
damn this Affliction my stupid buck of
[Music]
life okay okay are we there yet are we
there soon
690 M don't worry we're really
close oh okay well then this place looks
familiar oh we're in America wait this
is the place this is the place that
where we were chilling and hanging out
when
is it when we were um testing it out
like a couple days
ago at least at least the group that I
was with when we were testing the game I
we were just in a field yeah and then
FAA stabbed me while we were talking
staff was talking to us I just got stab
you it's because you punched me you
didn't even notice that you punched me
you should take this to
court hey
self this you have no does it heal
faster if I use another
splint I don't know you should
try kind of want to
try see if it
Stacks oh you cannot use that at this
time okay but I think if I Sprint uh the
time increases for how long it takes to
heal doesn't like a sprinting I hear a
zombie no sprinting with the Sprint
don't be scared eyes are glowing red
that's we're so strong
together we have two guns take r two
fist we have six
fists we can't use them like FAA does
though she she kind of she's kind of the
Fist more than you how disappointing I
know all I am is a shotgun and a bow and
arrow maybe you should give your fist
like is it like a a weapon fist weapon
you should give it to fa like I mean the
not in game I mean your actual fist
there's a there's a dangerous
zombie oh God oh God I can't run okay
I'm going to try wait stand still I'm
out of shots ouch ouch it hurts me I'm
going to die fa stand still let her T
you it's going to kill
me okay that hit oh oh no she's still
alive still still alive still alive oh
oh oh oh reload
faster I'm out of am
[Music]
uhoh oh she's dead she's dead she's dead
she's dead it's cool it's it's cool
we're chill oh level up level
four o oh we're at the Shady Slaughter
RV that's the RV with a
dog it's just a picture don't
worry that's a real dog I started
sprinting on accident
my
ankles if you die do you lose the
quest I don't think so only if you're in
the process of doing
it aren't we in the process of doing it
now it's
done return to Traer there's no way that
we can fail it now knocking on
wood I hope he opens soon how do how how
do I repair my meele weapons and
tools I don't know if you press tab
there should you click over it it should
say repair underneath it really the icon
you just need the M it's gray out cuz I
don't have the materials but it doesn't
show me what materials I need otherwise
I'm blind I don't know I'm not
sure wait where did you go what it
needs maybe there's a popup that tells
you when you try it or you might need
the book for it oh maybe it's high level
why do we need books for everything in
this economy I was able to rep repair my
sledgehammer though I guess the
materials are just whatever you would
originally need to build the gun for
example but I didn't build it so there
are repair kits also I found one
once we're so close I can smell her just
like how the zombies can smell all of us
combined is your leg well enough to be
running no I forgot I
forgot this is so sad the
book zombie but this one's eyes aren't
glowing so it's okay they not try not to
hit you with my bow and
arrow oh
okay he's
dead he's indeed dead you're you're have
you have feathers in your mouth once
again M you're so
good I just love Fe feathers too I don't
know how long I can tolerate
this
more not
[Music]
again you know it's crazy how how many
birds there are cuz they're laying eggs
still and and yet I haven't seen a
single bird I only seen
vultures you think they're only the eggs
yeah that's what I was going to say what
does this tell us about if egg or bird
came first when there's only eggs
around maybe I think the egg came first
yeah but then why is the egg not making
the
birds
if I guess so maybe we should stop
otherwise we're destroying the the bird
line watch me put this egg in my mouth
no give it to me I'll sit on it and I'll
Hatchet I'll
no no ow she's stabbing me you're
killing our future well don't worry I
ate all the eggs in my inventory also I
didn't stab you I sledg hammered you she
sledg hammered
me I'm 14 seconds away from being cured
from my my bad leg are you infected 14
oh I guess I just had a fractured leg D
just my poor sprained leg okay can you
two girls give a kiss on my leg maybe
that will make it go away one oh your
toes are I'm out of
here thank you wow I feel like that gave
me a big healing
buff I'm healing the world is healing
really the world is healing yeah
forgotten about gig eating all of the
eggs Fe why would you remind her I hate
her Orange lady why uh no I would never
eat the eggs on the ground that I
found
never you are lucky that I am reliant on
You Are We There Yet we we're so close
to our house know oh are we going home
yeah the's not open right now oh
yeah we are so going home she's going
toight me I think our session is
basically end is it ending at the at
like when are we ending no Day end of
day four or
what yes I think at the end of day
four cuz I feel like wasn't there like
there was kind of a plan so that we can
time when the when the invasions are yes
[Music]
H Trader opens Trader opens at 4:00 a.m.
10 minutes wow why is so
Random that's so
early it's on all
fours barel just like a were that's the
sound that that thing makes sounds what
apparently I make sometimes what I been
have an example uhoh no wait what's that
called again I might die I'm going to
die goodbye say I sound
don't he has the jumps he can
jump he can jump he can jump
Revenge he he died he died he died a
raptor oh yeah people said I sound like
a raptor sometimes I think when I laugh
or no was it when I laugh or when I I
don't know but sometimes apparently I
sound like a raptor and that sounds like
a Raptor to me does sound like a raptor
right
Vel yeah I need to hear you do that I
honestly don't know when do I do that
Chad when when I laugh really that's so
rud I don't laugh like that I laugh like
a
lady I'm going to kill this deer so I
can feed my dependent wies you found a
deer if I can kill this then my wives
will depend on me more and can't leave
me cuz I Stockholm syndrome them in the
apocalypse are we the wies I missed
every single one of these arrows she's a
little bit
[Laughter]
delusional don't worry I killed it we
have for dinner I do appreciate that
let's let's learn how to cook it
though I'm going to learn how to cook it
for you I want I want to punch it too I
want to get animal fed give me give me I
I think did I no my arrow we're home I
didn't get any animal fat but I got some
steaks
okay so uh I wonder if we if it would be
worth it to not just rely on bioo
cooking for everybody especially when
our teams are often separate yes maybe
we should also learn how to cook we can
learn how to cook I think it's good that
M people know how to
cook does meat go bad like raw meat does
it go bad no I need a stay good I don't
have a cooking
grill it's over it's
over how do we make a workbench oh we
need workstation level
10 this is so difficult I know it's so
much oh I have a like a fire buff wow
wholesome is there an auto
deposit um no move items to fill up oh
there is there is oh yeah on the
bar on your
[Music]
inventory what is this agronomic gra ah
would be easier to use the
gun I feel like we're going to die of
carbon monoxide
poisoning
thing no we have an alarm
her house is filling with smoke right
now it's really Smokey in here F it's
fine it's
fine oh my God it is very hard to see we
have open walls do you see the window
out front we're missing the
window
yeah it'll be okay we'll be fine in
here um question
H although you oh wait
recipes chat is this also from a
magazine is this
[Music]
also
Fu skill
a stone tools should I put a what
need what 46 magazine
oopsies not mean to stab things
[Music]
sest do we have any more magazines lying
around that nobody has read yet that
could be useful I put think so there two
cooking in here if you want to learn how
to cook we have to cook oh yeah they
cook cooking magazine
M who of us should be the cook who who
should be the chef I think I might have
one point in it already oh then go for
it wait do
I where's
cooking there's a lot of cool stuff in
here the
potato why you keeping the rotting flash
will that ever be
useful we just never maybe it will be
H could be okay I need one more duct
tape and 20 scrap polymers and I can
make a de
collector a whole I do have one level
okay I'll read some I could make
cornbread but but yeah but I we don't
have any cooking
items cooking items as in like a stove
yeah or is in like a p
or
grill literally have
nothing do you think the trader will be
open now did they sell like a
pot I think he has some I don't know we
have enough money for it I can make
grilled
meat wait can I no I
can't I can make something
though corn bread chat what should I
[Music]
learn what should I learn
you can maybe buy a pot or grill at the
trader yeah we could put our money
together I think after this trip we have
quite a
bit I'm so drunk right now I'm
fast what are you drinking I drank some
beer seeing double where where are
you just started
sprinting more stuff got to get so much
done while I'm drunk
I don't understand
this so can I not put a skill into this
chat is this magazine only I still don't
understand this whole
menu I know it's a lot
right what weapons do you like so far I
don't really care I mean I think it's
good to have one like weapon like a
hammer or so besides the
gun just in case I run out of ammo so
for now I'm doing Sledgehammer the Traer
open everyone these are the books the
Traer open okay let's go TR oh why you
guys already so
far
ladies we don't have to turn it in at
the same time right but it will it will
feel more
wholesome I turned it
in what
I so
fad what a Zoomer do you think he'll be
mad if I dismantle his truck yeah he
makes a noise and
everything yeah try it can I steal his
stuff why didn't you go carry me with my
broken leg come here he has a cooking
pot for 600 and a cooking grill for 600
wait I don't wait how do how much money
is
that I have 400 on me
oh how much we can put together Casino
token in your I have almost 200 Casino
tokens oh wait that's what it wait
there's some in the um there's some in
the chest too oh we can get a pot he is
is there no way to find a pot out in the
open world I guess is R find it h what
the hell do you want this time it's
probably very rare you sell stuff
oh it's only worth nine the
cash yeah the cash you should sell and
you get the coins that he has is it
worth
it uh I would yeah yeah yeah I don't
think you can use the real money for
anything else the the the the cash the
US dollars or whatever that is I don't
think I got a quest to go to the
mushroom Mining Company oh we've passed
her but that was the Minecraft thing
that you ran away from and me and fall
into for moment now we can kill it for
real wait
he how do I give back the you know the
drill
assho how did you get back the quest I
think if you just talking I just spoke
to him and then he's like here's what I
have for you cuz you completed my
quest oh oh I'm so dumb this menu is so
overwhelming chat I'm sorry tactical
Warfare
proofs assault rifle crafting
skill crafting skill a bundle of free
random crafing oh I think I'll go for
the what did you girls choose I took the
club I took the book what okay you got a
club from this very oh the club book oh
okay oh oh he gives you 400 Casino
tokens too that's crazy how about you
brows your ass right out of my store oh
he's so mean though
why he can treat us like this just cuz
he's richer than us in the
apocalypse He he'll be from my that's
the worst part no once we get our cell
phones working again we can tear down
his small business and leave bad reviews
on Yell yeah yeah are you already going
to the next oh I'm going home first okay
okay you got to wait for us wife we
yeah wait for your wives my wives that
I'm making depend on me and buy a
cooking pot Andor Grill I have 700 coins
now there so many did you take the ones
from the
house yeah yeah we yeah we can we should
we should you know invest in this
together if we get the pot we can boil
our water so it's no longer dirty and
wait I have a water purifier but I don't
know how to use it oh
interesting where is it I don't even see
the
pot oh I took the ones
inside the chest we have 500 or I pulled
it together I have 521 o so maybe we can
get both the grill and the pot we can
make clean water oh okay wait this water
purifier goes in your hat that that
doesn't make any sense I'll buy maybe
you can drink dirty water and it's like
a straw it does not BR attached to your
face I purchased the pot so you buy
theill they're trolling me it
doesn't you buy Grill why would they lie
to you oh that's
and w
how much Italian did you learn with her
um I I feel like I already had a good
amount of knowledge cuz I learned it in
school a little
bit so it was like kind of just
remembering what I learned there like
what she was teaching me was like stuff
I already learned in school but I had to
remember some of it she reminded you
about
Italians I am pretty decent why you take
your hat off it does go in your hat
bright Joker green hair it's just so
shocking was there no better green than
that
no this is the best
green you shower once or twice that
green should fade into a more nicer FAA
green why are you saying it's died it's
natural
I'm sorry girl that doesn't look natural
to
me even though you
nature not very natural do you have 100
coins I can have yes yeah take
some hold on what's wrong with me well
she likes to be barefoot don't judge her
she's Barefoot by default
sorry no Senai respects this girl I got
a cooking Grill I'm going to go back
home okay okay I she so what happened
she's so
intimidated okay let's go I got the pot
you got the grill and we got the girl
also fauna come on and the girl trying
to put my
shoes yes
yes we don't want to moding your shoes
too yeah I was Mo
modding yes modded shoes well you modded
your shoes huh a cool flame on it now
mhm what no way it's like when you put
charms on your Crocs you are Barefoot
still I haven't put them back
on
yet I should just AFK for 24 minutes cuz
my my feet are still
broken
a I'll eat some
pears I Love Pears but mhm I feel like
they're often a Miss like they're either
hit or miss that's very
true real depends on the type of pear
yeah you can make us grilled meat now
FAA I can I think I put some meat in
here so you can cook
it does it really get more if I run
let's
see wait should I cook our stuff does it
go bad no doesn't go bad it's fine it
doesn't go bad so I can just cook it
all
yep let's go making grilled corn it went
up it did go up a
minute grilled corn he
lotes
wow I I'll drop free steaks can you take
the raw oh God
you're cooking them too I didn't I
didn't want to drop in over there thank
God they're not catching fire oh wait I
can't make good meat yet that's okay I
can only make charred
meat should we
wait until I'm better at I guess we can
wait a bit oh I should open this she's
getting better at cooking don't bully
her gotcha magazine gotcha I got
robotics crafting skill two of them an
armor crafting skill two of them and
spare crafting skill two of them
wow I'll definitely learn the armor
crafting
[Music]
skill I'll learn this
too I don't know what kind of Robotics
you can make in this game but sounds fun
can you put the pot in oh
yeah uh how I can make cornbread I think
yeah you put it in the thingy oh
okay so
fancy that's so cute have to learn how
to do you girls sometimes watch like
those videos on YouTube where like
pretty ladies will like Vlog themselves
going camping and like really
professionally like they're like
absolute pros at camping and sometimes
they bring their dog Oro or there's like
a camping one sometimes they have cats
apparently and then the cats will go to
their camp and hang out with them for
the night which is so cozy I like them I
want to learn all those camping skills
man should we go camping
IRL yeah IRL I would love to but does
any of you have experience camping no
should we go
glamping yeah let's get an
rvad maybe like honestly I feel like
glamping is a little bit too much maybe
like an in between between camping and
glamping yeah we don't have any running
water but we have an
RV what IRL or in game I'm not sure what
you're talking about
IRL really we have an RV get the IRL RV
you have an RV or are we no no we could
R investing in one okay we're investing
in an RV I will say that I have camped
in the very very wilder wilderness
be like last year and made a video about
it and have uh provided myself with eggs
from wild
chickens I remember I remember that
video you watched it course I wasn't
okay for what did you like the scene
where I I like cut from like a baby
chicken
to it's cinematic I will definitely say
to so I mean I think you understood what
happened there but no chickens were
harmed in the making of that
video yeah that was the real
Wilderness you can be our camping Pro
you can teach us how to
Camp okay I don't really know how it
works but I have a
tent and a a nice sleeping
bag can we all is your tent big enough
for all of us I think we could fit cozy
not we would
snuggle oh sorry I took all of your
water out cuz it was taking 30 minutes
to
cook what's wrong with my 30 minute
water it wasn't it wasn't outputting one
at a time it was just going to wait 30
minutes to cook all the whole
stack I want to make
cornbread M I've never had cornbread
before we need more cooking magazine you
never had corn we should get cornbread
IRL right yeah I do I do need more
cooking
magazines oh I don't think I have one no
we can run towards doing the mushroom
Quest while our stuff is cooking and
then maybe go to houses on the way and
we find I have a magazine that teaches
you how to make super strong coffee I
think
coffee I thought it was a mining
magazine but it seems like it teaches
you coffee I don't
know well if you're in the need for that
it's in my
crate you can learn become powerful of
coffee there's a lot of H life members
that you could bait with the coffee
that's true you can woo with coffee yeah
rule the world coffee rules the world if
you like corn cornbread is excellent but
cornbread is something like cake right
and for me cake shouldn't taste like
corn it's not really cake I mean it's
sweet but you eat it with Savory Foods
usually oh okay I feel like the texture
is unlike a cake too
yeah huh all right it's kind of uncommon
here in Austria I
think
yeah what's it called anyway mice cook
mice p in German what is it mice mice
mice mice
BR I look it up mice P mice P cuz corn
is mice and bread is
BR chat why are you not telling me
normally you tell me everything I guess
the German speakers are sleeping right
now it's I guess they are I'm my really
well well well oh wait oh no never mind
I thought we didn't go to the Traer yet
but we did wait KiKi where are you why
are you 200 M away wait is she already
run rocks no I'm I'm hitting rocks and
to the mushroom place we the mushroom
Place yeah we should go to mushroom
Place let's go as long as one of us has
the quest we're good right yeah yeah
yeah so okay wait I'll drop two more
things off your leg your leg my leg is
it still needs 17 minutes and if I rush
it will be longer oh no
timber timber are you yelling timber I
was going down I'm yelling
timber
yippe
[Music]
yippe yipp huzzah
huzzah well everyone should come to my
house IRL and then I'll drive you to
both Costco and to get
cornbread you give me my passenger
princess and you can sit on each other's
laps and we can get pulled over what
what no I'm fine
sitting all right I'm going towards I
can't just have only one of you be my
passenger princess are you not the
passenger princess if you're in the
back no you'd be it's like then's an
Uber it's like hello your Uber it's here
to pick you up well that's pretty good
too right is the where was the I don't
want to run all the way to the Traer if
the quest thing is in the other
direction do we know where it is this
way yeah okay okay okay I'll walk where
we need a car I know we need a car so
bad do you see where all of them are
inside that's where our Quest is the
rest of them all them are inside oh
they're
there
ah okay oh there's a bunch of people
there ah the last H cuz some people
already ended their Stream So the
remaining girls uh came together it
seems
mhm we're the last one standing for
today huh yeah yeah well do they have a
cooking grill and a pot we should ask
them we should flex but they'll probably
say yeah should cuz wasn't biu already
cooking was she with her bare
hands
potentially I see that is not quite the
same
make a splint no I I can't use another
splint cuz I already have one on but 15
minutes 15 minutes unless I run too much
then it's more again uhoh this sucks I
regret this already I want for having a
broken
leg how did you break it in the first
place cuz I fell from a high like
mountain
this game is too
real yeah the diarrhea then the broken
legs then the Vampire Zombies and then
the really sexy zombies too it's so
realistic that's so
realistic and then me objectifying the
really sexy zombies it's like can I not
catch a
break I play video games or escapism do
you guys watch horror movies no
scary sometimes I'm sure there's sexy
zombies in there too right probably
should we find
one I hate horror movies oh yeah they're
too scary it is spooky month yeah
October I'll watch a scary movie if it
has a sexy zombie in it we should just
watch scary
movie the first one I scary movie are
you know do you know scary movie yeah
we can watch scary movies I think Dum
movie is it dumb which is that the one
with Jason no that's Friday the 13th I
think the first one is the one with the
exorcism on the lady where she wait a
supply drop wait for it yeah see those
suckers if I hit those first wait I
can't run so fast we'll get it for you
oh they're are really far where is it
okay um oh oh I see see it is so far are
they good I'm not going they might be
good if we get them before they do even
though we're working
together forget
that we're not enemies we're not Rivals
like in roster so maybe we should be we
might die though cuz it's noon right
now it's okay what's a little death in
the grand scheme of things why would we
die oh you're already going for it
she zooming see
you I need drink I'm out of here hey how
much longer do you do you girls
personally want to play today I think
we're stopping at the 4our Mark right
okay so is that in in you mean in 10 20
minutes okay okay okay yeah yeah yeah so
is it worth running there for you
two yeah we can do it m away well then
don't get distracted like a Doomer all
the time and run into other places while
you're going there oh don't worry I
already
did fa stop her I can't I really want to
see what's in the supply
truck you'll never make it in these 20
minutes I'll make it we're so close it's
actually not that far it's actually not
that far we ran further for the quest
but does that mean we're not going to
the mushroom mining place we can still
go we'll make it I don't think we'll
make it
running we're so fast there might be a
mountain in the way oh no Ain No
Mountain High Enough girl a no mountain
low
enough to get me to that supply drop
right now there there's a
mountain okay but what how do we get
around this mountain there has to be a
way around it get yourself a
horse and then oh no just go straight up
think I need a goat hey I haven't seen
horses in this game yet I guess there
are no horses if there was a horse I'd
eat it already what
o well o o the hores you need to feed it
so much you are such a
[Music]
wildering what is this
scarecrow I have Farm is using a naked
man as a scarecrow I have arrived at the
mushroom Mining Company I will just wait
wait here until you girls come because
my leg is heing slowly we're trying to
find out how to scale this mountain oh I
just went right up it oh you go right up
yeah okay I need
food just like goat oh wait I have all
the food oh no egg egg egg egg egg
please please please egg please egg yes
egg
please there's a Hopping zombie over
here fun are you carrying food with you
yeah okay when you come here I need like
at least a piece of something okay thank
you there's some good stuff in
here was worth
it Well's look at the
time plenty of time plenty of time I'm
almost at the other supply drop
okay let me look where you
are oh oh you already collected one of
those supply drops what was this um a
blueberry pie armor plating mod Golden
Rod
tea crafting skill magazine bundle a
blueberry pie and a claw hammer well you
said blueberry pie twice s are to wait
did I oh there just one I just this the
one I really like are you hungry f I
actually hungry
IR the talk about cornbread made me
really want
cornbread gigy what's in the second one
six books and a plaster cast for your
broken foot oh oh a shame that you're
healing in 10 minutes
yeah too late well for next time I next
time I also got
two fisting books for f i want I want
the fisting
[Laughter]
books
nice okay we're heading to the mines
okay actually
[Music]
a yes
yes the mind of
Moria I want to watch The Hobbit again
which one the new
ones the new ones there's a new one
they're not really that new yeah there's
like an old animated movie of the hob no
not that
one no no no
no no I just want to watch the CL so to
say I guess you can't call him classic
but the ones that you know that I mean
the free H movies frean yeah yeah yeah
yeah I do like him as
Bilbo yeah Bilbo
Bings you know for my last for
my up until now all like my birthdays
and anniversaries I have collected
several greetings from Lord Of The Wings
actors have you yeah I did get uh Sam I
think right oh and I do have uh an
autograph of Sam I
think yeah and I got Bill ball and I got
photo too right I have uh like video
messages of three of all those three I
think you have so many of them yeah yeah
and I my mom what almost done with what
you're collecting all of them right you
get one from every single
actor I I don't know I would like gimy I
would like to get one from gimy if he
does that stuff but I I'm guessing he
doesn't cuz otherwise I probably would
have I've already gotten the video
message so you have collected them all I
know I got Pippen I got Pippen St fro
and Pippen that was it right right I
didn't get
billbo pipin was so
funny pipin was like so funny literally
oh do you guys know watch did you ever
watch gilmo
girls no no I remember you talk about it
though why does nobody relates to me
with gilo girls I have yet to find
somebody who likes the show as much as
me I like the
meme what's the meme go piss girl is
that from Gilmore Girls is it not I
thought that's just an internet thing
think
so why would that be from Gil girls girl
there just so many girls oh
God or is it from gold girls because no
they're golden I don't know I don't
think the Golden Girls are telling each
other go piss
Queen oh my god when I when I mentioned
Gill girls to cie she thought I was
talking about Golden Girls and that was
a pretty funny
misunderstanding cuz I was just yapping
about gim girls this whole time in her
head I'm talking about old
ladies hello I made it back you made it
would you like this coming to blueberry
pie oh please thank
you blueberry oh my God sounds aming
take the
fistings yes thank
you I started the quest the blueberry
pie I think gave me a running buff I got
more fisting
magazines so many oh a bow magazine two
bow magazines and two explosive
magazines wow
nice what do the explosive magazines do
let me
check explosive crafting wow okay does
anybody already have anything on
that I don't I I don't think I don't
think I
do do you want spear
[Music]
hunting is that CRA for crafting
Spears yeah oh bleeding damage Spears
have a 25% chance to cause bleeding
damage well that's kind of cool
uh interesting I don't use Spears right
now someone should take wait is she
stealing our stuff no no I took it I
took it got paranoid too I mean I guess
we're friends I guess we're all friends
yeah we're all friends we need to
remember
holy oh I have another cooking book for
you maybe you can make us meet I can I
can make you meat now mm there's a
person inside the quest so I can't can't
start it yet oh I oh I don't know why
but aren't they just leaving right now
cuz two already came out of here yeah
can't i b b also left so I I think
they're done with that Quest now let me
in let us in one of you should take the
Bandit armor mod maybe I have to dig and
put it on your
shirt can you just do that oh oh
so remove your armor and then there's
like a modify slot and you put it in
there oh wait wait don't run so fast let
me try that remove the armor modify
slot is giggy already running in there
yes don't worry I'll clear it out I'll
clear it out for you so you don't have
to worry about a single thing oh that's
so cool ah maybe that works the same way
with the shovel then yeah yeah
ah Faun how did you figure this out I
think my chat told me
wow wait how do I wear it now I'm
stupid okay I got it oh it doesn't
really reflect in the visuals but okay
I'm sure you're stronger now I'm sure I
am
mushrooms oh can we eat them yeah I
think we can at least pick them up for
now and then cook them
XP for for food
oh well I have no ammo at all it seems
so we have to go
meele
melee ow ow ow ow this bone knife is not
so efficient I don't think it you need a
better weapon call was saying oh you got
to get the bull knife it's so good
lik
bones it's for the hunting animals so
you can take their skin and wear it
really no it's just for you get more um
items when you kill an animal if you use
the knife oh F let's go deeper Gigi is
like probably really deep in it yeah
yeah I
am what did you go I guess we only have
we have like 9 minutes 10 minutes
oh yeah yeah we got the r Speed
Run
OU oh
no yeah get
him
ow okay okay okay okay okay here
just swinging at him is he dead he's
dead he's dead I think he's dead
take my arrows from
him do we go up here yep okay I can see
inside of
you don't so
empty empty Holo there's nothing in
there I am full of joy and happiness as
long as I'm with you girls oh I saw that
what you're seeing I think it's just a
mirage stream Mirage stream Mirage
stream Mirage
me
on I'm obsessed with the the sequins the
like sparkles on the shorts thank you
thank you so good I'm glad you like it
Tak new song hey wait I'm too scared to
make that jump with my broken leg Yeah
you could always wait over there there's
knuckle wraps in here should take those
level two oh and ammo and a muffled
connectors mod I don't know what that's
for oh that's my ammo let's go muffled
connectors mod ah to make it more
silent like a do I need to make stealth
kill these zombies yeah I don't
know cuz if they can't hear you then
maybe you can't alert other nearby
zombies or so I don't know think
no it's just a
shortcut you can go back around or you
can make the shortcut to the entrance oh
I'm scared to make the short yeah me too
me too I'm going to break my leg
again I'm scared to use the ladder
though we already cleared
it yeah what was baby Zone what was
there to
clear so easy I think Gigi just did
everything this is just like parkour
civilization right now you guys are
jumping for the chicken we should be no
it's
Minecraft you should watch it I watched
the entire thing at two times speed
yesterday which like hours of Minecraft
yeah Minecraft Parkour
civilization I'm lost perhaps possibly
no never mind I'm fine also I can't
believe I will give you credit because
we still have 10 minutes or 9 minutes
yeah yeah and you've done both thees and
this okay I think we're winning not that
it's a competition but if it was I think
they I don't know maybe the the others
aren't doing so bad either that's true
we'll show up and they have like a
helicopter already yeah no no I think
we're winning we shouldn't get too cocky
also I'm thirsty do we have water at
home maybe we have so much water cooking
right now okay I'm going to drink out of
a pond cuz I have the mod that lets me
drink out of a pond but if you want to
wear it you can wear it yeah my helmet
lets me drink out of the pond I think
how your head
in um I think wait how do I
drink uh open your mouth and then go g
go go go oh you need your
hands wait
I'm I'm 130 M away from you I want to
try to wait don't you shouldn't drink it
unless you wear the helmet I can give
you the helmet yeah yeah I'm almost
there I'm just trying to not to run too
fast cuz I have 1 minute left on my foot
the walking Bri filter
mhm 55 54 53
52 oh I found you girls
hello hello governor
blue is fun fun oh okay here let me
experiment and fill my tummy with water
oo
wow primitive Hood where's
it ah there it
is wow so how do I drink the water in
here uh have an empty hand and then you
can push e at the Ed of the
what but I'm just punching it come to
the edge come to the edge what come over
here H I thought you were just messing
with me again
no e to drink from
crony can't believe this
works
oh is there any indicator to see like
how I think you're not supposed to drink
too much right or you'll get sick sick
oh press E Yeah but I would like to see
like cuz we have a bar for like stamina
and a bar for health do we not have
anything like that for
drinking there's on the on the bottom
right side you see it underneath your ah
the blue one oh wait is it
oh and green
is hunger is it and purple is exp Maybe
yeah purple's exp exp and then left side
is hunger and then right side is oh wait
I shouldn't be drinking this without the
helmet I'm just slurping it up wait here
here it is here it is it's okay in the
water it didn't seem too bad it seemed
fine okay A little bit of fine little
bit what are you doing with the gun oh
that's
be why is she threatening us I don't
know we better go turn our quest in yeah
we should go
and then end it maybe she's telling us
like girl you have to end the stream
today get off of the server now yeah get
off the
server soon soon just giving back the
[Music]
quest people scares me I know why is she
just walking menacingly around cuz we
got the supply crates is that why
they're ours she
mad she mad and well she got to stay
mad oh I think our last name is the
Clement that's a house yeah that's a
house
name everybody wants to talk to this guy
why can't he talk to one person we got
ourselves a real love hero you can talk
to him you have to angle yourself a
little differently from them oh I guess
so yeah what do we have this
time medical journal yeah I'm getting
the magazines again too what do you mean
you're getting the Met does he only
offer one to you I only offered one I
bundles all the time
what maybe maybe this one medical uh
Journal is better than all these bottles
that I'm getting
[Music]
maybe H let's open open Goa time I have
received explosives crafting times two
Sledgehammer crafting uh two of them
okay and spare crafting ah lame no wait
that's the old one armor craft what is
that is it from before I got I think
armor crafting is new okay I learned
these can you
upgrade your weapons to the next level
me I don't know anybody is it
possible I don't even know how how I
would go about doing that you can't you
have to recraft it I
think yeah I got to get the skills
Going H wait did they
leave one of them
left oh oh left it's time yeah it's time
it seems to be
oh they also left the voice chat oh are
they have they ended already yeah we're
behind I want to say I had a blast with
you girls I'm glad we got together
Adventure may I mean I I feel like it's
probably like lame if we always stay in
the same groups but if we end up I don't
know some up together tomorrow again I
wouldn't mind I wouldn't mind playing
again together
okay this is our Clement house are you
back in the house
already running okay I can run now my my
leg is
healed it was fun it was fun yeah we did
so much we
were yeah
yippee we can end once kiawa gets back
home I'm running I'm running I'll go hit
some trees
your
aggressions why you hitting them why
don't you get an axe yeah you use the
stone axe so you are using it right oh
yeah I am okay but if you really want to
let out aggressions you should use your
fists that's B's job to fist the trees
she's the master Fister here that's
right wow you lost your job I lost my
job in seven days to die she became the
fter I saw the tree fall Timber
okay I'm home welcome e a doy M no no no
no but I mean food would probably be
also nice to be greeted by when I come
home by the way that's my job I'm not
that hungry I'm not that hungry I have
some
hairs no it's fine I'm not actually
hungry okay okay is our water done yeah
our water is done
is the water in in the in yeah it's
inside it how
inside
corn oh I I output I put it in the top
chest I can't find anything wow where's
the
cornmeal I've got some cornmeal too I
think in my chest yeah I got two corn
meal we had
more I did not take it maybe we have
been no I'm might wait it's literally in
my
inventory okay I'll put the cornmeal
into this seemingly food focused chest
I'm making a bunch of cornbread okay
okay okay shall we it's we log out is
it's time to go let's get out of here
goodbye my goodbye beautiful
is
fwell farewell thank you guys for
playing thank you I guess tomorrow is
same time is it an hour earlier an hour
ear oh thank God hour an hour early good
I have will collab but if I can make it
I will see you guys okay oh like you're
going to join Midway through or so I'm
might join Midway through if I can oh
okay okay well keep the house warm
I'm going to come back you're going to
be so much more well fisted
no
that I I don't know what other wor
Master
Fister puncher
p knuckle knuckle girl knuckles yeah and
Sonic and Knuck kid
yeah all right all right then good night
I guess yeah good night
bye bye bye take care see you later
bye that was a lot of fun thank you for
watching I actually really like these
kinds of games it's so easy to like get
into them I could have easily kept
playing for like three more hours so
I've been playing this all week long
I've got super chats I need to read at
some
point we will get caught up but thank
you for watching thank you thank you I
had a lot of fun today I already want to
play more I want to level
up it's on if you I don't know if it was
made clear we're doing a schedule for
this because every seven hours a zombie
hord will attack or something so we have
like scheduled time slots planned so
that we you know when the zombie horde
attacks people will be online and
Etc but all right I'm going to go eat
something thank you very much for
watching saplings I appreciate it
appreciate you hope you had as much fun
as I did all right I will see you
tomorrow byebye F well bye
[Music]