[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
that's pretty cute
sorry for the delay oh my God they're
already joining yeah
you're welcome to join us
we're playing with you guys I suppose
um yeah I had some issues guys oh my God
uh but I solved it now bye I'll be
playing for OBS because that way I can
I'll wait that way I can see what I'm
doing and not have choppy sound when I
have the capture software open I get
choppy sound in combination with OBS uh
and whatever else I'm I have opened so a
little bit unfortunate but I fixed it
for the Stream
it doesn't matter if I play for OBS this
is good enough this is good enough good
luck yeah we're gonna have bad pain
anyway yeah
I heard that this game uses different
servers than Nintendo online in general
so that it should be better
should have decent should be yeah I hope
so
and I I okay let me explain to you so
far what I what experience I have
I played a few battles against CPUs with
like normal teammates real or normal
teammates uh and I I won them except for
one where all my teammates were just
slacking off
um the classic MOBA experience yeah
really blame the teammates
have a screenshot too yeah I'm gonna
show it right now I have proof ta-da you
can see here uh Abdul has zero one 141 I
have 146 6381 and then look at this the
GTA has zero two one four what is this
18 what is this it's true let's try see
it it's the truth like they're slacking
off
I think I understand the gist of the
game
um I I know that I gotta use skills I
know that I have to level up I know that
there's like basis uh and you gotta also
kill normal Pokemon not only the people
would you say it's more important to
kill the normal Pokemon or the the
players
um it made it just depends on the moment
in the game usually the first like two
or three minutes you should Farm a
little bit and then after that kind of
group and put I did notice that as a
general pattern being the case yeah
that's just like normal for
uh mobas oh also just quick question
guys are you hearing the audio fine is
is it balance do you hear the game
decently and then fauna louder hopefully
then the game should be like that yeah
all good okay let's hope it goes well
good morning
good morning good morning thanks for
staying up late no thank you for getting
up early
no I I should I always try to wake up at
this time wow I need to remain diligent
I think when I was in Japan for like a
long term I I did refuse to get up so
early but this wasn't my normal
streaming time anyway so I didn't have
to keep that up but you're trying to
keep it up that's so interesting my best
for the saplings so what's the word
disciplined
but I know it will make the jet lag less
bad when I go back and what time do you
normally get up in your usual
environment
usually I wake up like a couple hours
before my stream like maybe like five
hours so what time would that be like
roughly it's a secret secret secret time
zone
but
I'll make my own calculations then but
not morning right not like super morning
like now not like super early no yeah
that's what I was wondering if you're
like a morning person normally
no not really okay you never me neither
never never never
okay so uh for the people who don't know
this week on what day Wednesday first
day
we have a tournament uh
whole life Pokemon unite World
Tournament wow so good
um maybe you guys have seen some info
about it maybe not but
um well it is a tournament between
uh Enid and Japan in on the en team we
have fauna our One and Only Hope
apparently
and Cali and Iris and Ahmed and lastly
me I don't I have only heard from
viewers that you're the only one who has
some experience in the game
I do it's been a while since I played
but I used to play quite a lot okay I
probably
100 hours in this game whoa okay okay
that should help us but but it was all a
long time ago I don't really yeah they
updated a lot I'm excited the principle
is still the same yeah and the problem
is though that I heard that ID and
Japanese team is cracked so on the ID we
have Kobo kaeda
Anya and Ollie and I know at least that
Kobe and and got some mobile Gamers yeah
they're they're I think that's in in
their country's culture like I feel like
mobile games are very popular there
anyway
so we're doomed and then Japanese team
is
is especially dangerous
does she eat does she play she plays a
lot and they've been training a lot too
have they oh no okay maybe we should
train she on his master
she's a master is that a rank
yeah oh God is that yabai what's your
rank fauna
I don't remember what the highest I got
okay what are the what are the rings
I don't know I don't know that we're
even ranks
if I could also played a lot before
the thing is like I I joined this
it's gonna be like you know not so
serious but now it seems kind of serious
now I don't wanna you know I didn't
realize it would be so serious either
I think I was only expert level oh which
is like two below but still sounds but
there's only like five so it's not oh my
God so you were like middle
yeah like middle
that's that's pretty good I would say
so uh okay well let's play and and let's
I guess maybe stay together and you give
me like instructions okay we can lane
together okay
it works or if it's gonna kick us out
I just heard level four wow wow wow oh I
have experience with some of these let
me do let me do pretty nine tails
they're also apparently nerfed my
favorite bond which one
is trashed here now I'm not gonna let
that stop me
do we have to
like decide on the Pokemon beforehand I
feel like I saw some Japanese members
like writing in the Discord oh yeah they
did ask us what we were going to play I
don't know
will I have like a choice of like you
know random Pokemon or do is it from my
own obtained licenses
um I don't know if they'll give us
licenses or not they might give you the
license of the Pokemon you request you
can probably request any of them really
yeah we can buy them so they would be
able to give it to you oh we got a lot
of people with potions on our team the
other team has has other items be nice
everybody be nice
potion is the Newbie item which I also
have oh yeah because most are played on
my other account
is it the that weird icon that I just
saw I also have a potion right I think
yeah use your potion if you get low
Health okay okay let's go in the same
way let's go top Taco latte you need to
go somewhere else why because there
should only be two of us it looks so
obedient thank you thank you
so what's the word uh Cooperative thank
you thank you thank you
what's good and that was like in real
time no delay you're listening they're
listening in Fauna
I don't know if this is like the best
for
them to Jungle for Eevee to Jungle but
it is what it is
the first time I'm playing against not
CPUs let's destroy this this
what's going on Mr mime and here what's
going on
I want to get out of here okay I
committed I committed I thought I
thought we were in I committed
full time
diving they were almost down they were
almost down it's okay I told you to give
back
I will continue to uh
[Music]
oh no no no no Revenge no Revenge no
Revenge oh we're feeding we're feeding
are we losing already what do you think
we are if you're alone don't go in
against two okay if you're alone just
stay back
uh oh you already leveled up
cute there you leveled up
okay now Revenge now Revenge
uh careful
sometimes you gotta commit I come in
thank you for committing
yeah you should choose early on well not
too early I don't know you gotta
sometimes you gotta commit what were
those eyes ran into them but I never
could do anything with them oh they just
heal you do I have to push the buttons
no no
no
maybe
oh we're getting ganked we should get
back
[Laughter]
they hate us
true and yet they do want to hurt us
um
okay that's harassing
okay I died I should have gone back
oh I am not alone we should we should
try to score our points yeah
okay
we'll attempt that soon but the problem
is they can hear our plans
it's true hopefully they're not
listening
and when we're telling you to do
something don't listen in when we're
having secret conversations thank you
oh we're not doing so bad but these I
feel like they're all so aggressive
yeah they are
maybe
yeah let's go score points
don't die guys oh okay we might die
I doubt there are any snipers what the
whole the whole every single
participating member is a sniper it's
true it's true it's a custom badge yeah
but that's fine that's fine it's like
um I finally another game
yeah
I think we're a little doomed
our teammates are
lacking oh and don't blame the teammates
they're they're doing their best on the
bottom I see should we join them or
should we stay up here yeah we should
probably start grouping up as a team but
we should probably defend top because
they have this thing well what is Dad's
if we can't defend it what is that yeah
oh my God he's Unstoppable yeah what
what how strong
uh-oh uh oh
yes we are
Don't Stop Believing
oh my God oh my okay we got one okay
okay okay time for The Comebacks
defend bottom maybe bottom okay
okay okay
a little bit of heel animals
oh he's the old thing on us
oh no oh I should also too
okay okay okay
now we should push push okay push I
haven't scored any points I'm not
helping me neither
yeah nice
oh
unscored points minus 20.
so sad oh God this is already a a good
like look into what the future will look
like in the actual tournament when we're
up against Ian and up against Japan and
I didn't it's true it's true
um
so the points that I'm scoring come from
these random Pokemon right
um also from killing others
they drop their orbs and you can pick
them up
I'm doing it I'm doing it I'm doing it
fine nice have you scored let's go no
let's go let's go fania
okay okay
even though I've only played it like a
little bit so far
it's been quite fun oh okay this is
pretty good this is pretty good yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah okay okay good job
good job oh
hi everybody
I wasn't so many points anyway
okay okay
team we gotta push oh no zero is gonna
just kill us goodbye goodbye
how does the super jump work what do you
press um
you
I think I have to run I'm really low you
just um push down down button and it
lets you jump
foreign
have your cats ever had the like a
rebellious
stage in their lives
no
I don't think so but never because one
of mine currently does
oh and I don't I don't know what to do
rebellious in what way
um normally for like the majority of her
life
uh uh she would wait like she's always
the type who wants a wet food in the
morning and she would wait for me
um until I wake up no matter what time
it is she would wait for me and then
once she sees them away that's when
she's like meow meow meow please give me
food
but recently since I came back from
Japan maybe it's because like other
people were taking care of them uh
but
um they suddenly
we
uh she's suddenly like you know she
wakes me up at 5 30.
5 30. even though I learned like an hour
for example at that point
and she's like she will not give up she
will just not stop I tried to ignore her
I tried to push her off the bed
I tried to blow air in her face
uh and I I sprayed some water on her she
doesn't give a [\h__\h] she doesn't care I
destroyed one of their gold Stones by
the way
amazing good job I don't think I scored
a single point that's a good job
no worse okay yeah and and recently I've
tried to counter it by
oh we're ending already
[Music]
a little bit
um
Maybe
we want a few team fights my kids have
definitely done that in the past I
thought that's just like normal cat
behavior though
[Music]
and now wait let me look at this I got
I got the 100 yeah
yeah and almost almost the most uh
whatever that is on the right side
proud
I'm not zero
[Laughter]
speakers I got some kills and assists
there you see and it's a cute outfit I
want that
okay everybody who was in the room will
leave okay let's give new people the
chance
um to join and we'll play again
uh only once per person
also if you're good join our team haha
just kidding yeah oh can you choose
which one you join
you can
please I think these people were here
before please leave
can we kick them oh yeah oh yeah
poor me Mare and not mine were uh
here right
in the previous round those two oh wait
I think I'm just requesting to change
position with
get out of town okay
thank you for being here thank you thank
you thank you for playing with us that
was fun and let's do it again it's fun I
remember how much I like this game yeah
nice it's fun memories are coming back
oh yeah the thing the problem with my
with smoothie was that I would I would
eventually give in because it's
impossible to ignore her yeah it is
impossible at 5 30 right and then I
would think that would satisfy her but
like an hour later she at 6 30 she wakes
me up again endlessly meowing somehow
she wants food again I don't know what's
wrong with her it's because you give in
the first time and then she knows she
can get away with it but it's so weird
because like I gave her like planning of
wet food how can she be hungry again and
what what what I don't understand
so recently it's breaking my heart fauna
maybe you know uh do you keep your doors
open for your cats oh I do yeah because
like I I I I also normally always keep
the keep the door wait what no
switched me out you requested me uh I
um I normally have the
door is always open but now I I left the
lobby father happy
let's make a new Lobby I love to Lobby
no but I guess somebody else would quit
how dare they they deny my position
change okay I did it I did it he
accepted it
probably because he didn't want to lose
the spot in the lobby what try what are
you left it completely I did because
that guy was spam requesting
stop spamming me
okay this is this is unfortunately why
we can't have nice things so
let's try again
please don't come in yet guys invite
friends on you
okay
the lab is full
um
remove I'm Gonna Keep on removing until
you make it I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry oh I have to type in no
okay we can't do it like this let me
exit
I play for OBS so how am I gonna see
what I'm doing
the code but then I mean I still won't
see it but wait you can hide the code
and then invite me because I'm your
friend
okay oh yeah true true okay
uh the code will be somewhere here
I think
we could also play a regular Lobby
is fine I like playing with people okay
okay
we'll get level UPS if we play regular
ah okay yeah it's good to play with
people is that desirable that we get how
did they
yeah ideally you want to get items you
want to level up your items it's fine I
made it
I thought it was there I
just right now I'm so sorry my mind is
uh yeah it's okay I was fast this time I
made it not faster than pain pickle
though speed pain pickle pain pickle
okay let's go
let's go the slappling is here playing
against the slappling can you slap me
too
oh my God
oh my gosh Mamma Mia
through the internet
I will slap you
okay I will play good draw cause I don't
have many much other choices
yeah in like the item the battle prep
screen you get held items and ideally
you want to get three held items that
are good for Pokemon you want I give you
a special attacker you want an item to
boost your special attack
yeah I don't have them in there on this
account I might grind if I can alright
because they probably allow items in the
tournament right so we would be yeah
items are just regular yeah
okay
yeah I don't have money because I just
started the game but I will I will try
to gather some by making achievements
and stuff yeah I don't know if they're
gonna give us items either for the
tournament they might I don't know what
they'll be sure to make it it might be
fair it must be fair oh there's
apparently the mammal swine is special
because they got a blue metal
oh are they Masters
but the Snorlax has a green model maybe
that's good too
uh-huh
so green what's better green or blue
probably blue
oh well probably blue that doesn't mean
anything
oh true Master is gold
oh are we going up
yeah let's go up
everybody else go down
they know what to do so we're like the
main ingredient you can't think of us
this is our path our only tattoo
[Music]
we can also go over here to the middle
oh
and steal this Pokemon
so we can steal there oh okay I didn't I
didn't mean to come in I didn't okay
okay okay I just wanted to harass them
but he's coming into a territory yes he
is
oh now he's running okay
I think you stole our stole our mon
oh they're we're getting some gank
assist
oh
what's that
uh ganking is when people from other
lanes come to assist
okay now we can score our points
nice gang thank you thank you thank you
you could eat their fruits if you want
but we should get back now
just a really slow slime please leave me
alone I don't even have score points to
show
please oh my God
oh
goodbye it's okay I didn't lose any
points
don't forget to use your potion as well
but maybe I need it for the tournament
with no it regenerates it regenerates oh
okay
Oh I thought it's a one time only okay
don't don't go in don't go in okay sorry
slappling for slappling slappling
useless yeah in general you can like
stay back
okay what do I I'm gonna go if there's a
lot of people it's like safer oh oh we
got a gank ah what
oh you pause the request did I did that
I don't know how I did it
I can pause request
and I got the power
you do have the power am I really yeah
okay we're getting some nice gank
requests or gang stuff here
okay I go up
oh my God so much EXP
yeah in general you want to like
get XP by last hitting mm-hmm
nice
okay
this game's going a lot better yeah so
you only get XP when you get the or you
get some XP if a teammate kills a creep
but it you want to last hit it if the
enemy team last hits it then they get
the experience okay
yeah now we can rotate and go
elsewhere where our team is
okay let's go down
yeah they they can do a big team fight
obliterated although it does leave our
top gate oh God
uh
sorry for my for me lacking in skill
no no I'm a skill issue
Fonda what have you been eating these
days
um I've been ordering a lot of ubereats
girl everybody oh
[Music]
obliterated uh
um have you been enjoying Japanese food
I think I like some Japanese food a lot
of it I can't not eat
oh but yeah I understand I like Ramen a
lot
I love ramen too what's your favorite
like toppings for ramen
um
toppings oh wait no egg for you knowing
but I like well my favorite kind of RAM
is tontamin oh Sesame
oh one of my favorite toppings is corn
oh really but but they most of the time
they only I'll gather here okay
okay so most of the time they only have
corn for like
[Music]
um
uh Hokkaido Ramen I think oh really
interesting
and most of the time my only uh find the
wrong Ramen that doesn't have corn on
the topping so that's really sad I want
corn yes I even consider bringing my own
corn
it's a close battle it's a close battle
people up here oh at the very top I'm
there now
I'm here for you I'll I'll cover you
okay I don't know what my ulti does but
it's like that did that even do anything
I don't know what yours does either you
should you should probably read now
I'm good I'm good
advancing toward an ally who is that
it's um so you can defeat oh my God
and it helps
push for them
it's like one of the main objectives is
to defeat the top and bottom creatures
or the middle creature
where where next oh no
oh God don't just don't go in them but I
can't just let them pick her face
well we can't fight them otherwise they
will be feeding
and don't just gain more experience
because they get a lot of experience
from killing us that's what that means
feeding oh yeah yeah you're like feeding
them your bodies
[Music]
oh my exp
so his ideal to
you're at the top right right now yeah
like laptop I think we might die
we have fallen behind or one guy is
trying
trying their best
yeah ideally you want to like stay with
your team never be caught out alone oh
apparently now we're really struggling
that's changed quickly
yeah things can change quickly
okay but that was we won that team fight
right good timing
we're gonna listen to this guy because
they know what they're doing
and go defeat
this one said it's gonna be contested I
don't think I'm where you think I I
don't think they got it they got it
[Music]
um
well
we have the thing is that I feel like
the people that are joining here to
fight against with us Rayquaza oh my God
I feel like they all have
like experience of the game yeah that's
why I was thinking it might be easier if
we play in like regular Lobby okay maybe
husband will be bringing mashed with
lower ranked people yeah
and we can no no level up I don't know
what I got
can stop
stop please please don't
hmm
okay this is one of my worst batches
I feel like the last one was worse
but for me personally I I was still
I had at least like some kind of like a
vision of what what I should be doing I
see I mean at this this is like late
game so late game generally you just
like stay with your team and trying to
defend together
and push together okay
I respond I see we're all at the base
they're they're spawn camping
they are
oh I made them fall asleep maybe was
that what I did with my old things no I
don't think so no I don't think that's
your old
mmm
if when there's like these experience
balls and I don't pick them up but
someone else does
did I miss out on EXP
won't be holding the points but your
teammate won't be ah oh there's a point
okay
yeah yeah they're like the points that
you score oh no
no 25 points to score button yeah too
late
a kill at least yeah at least we get
some kills
should have dunked I didn't I don't
think I dunked a single time this time
damn
you know the terminology dunking I just
said I just read it in the chat it's so
basketball it's just like basketball
right yeah it is
[Music]
Orange is powerful oh I did dunk I think
you did you did
pain pickle didn't dunk
why paint pickle I mean you know you can
we you can't always blame your team
sometimes I just want the explanation
sometimes there's reasons why they can't
you can't get out by yourself to dunk
okay
mm-hmm worthy opponent no thank you wow
so kind
Let's uh wait I'll move I'll make a new
Lobby
and invite you again
okay have you so far any do you have any
like you know advice that something I
can fix I think you should read your
skills
this is your ultimate so you know what
it does
huh I think that would be good
so you can use your skills accordingly
is that bad
besides that
um don't get caught out alone by
yourself try to stay with people unless
you're really strong hmm
also know when to commit
sometimes you want to stay in if like
their HP is getting low and you think
you might be able to kill them sometimes
it's better to just stay in
but it's a call sometimes you need to
run if there's no chance would you say
there's any files any uh Pokemon that
are like better to choose like for
example this Pokemon I just had was was
that maybe not so good or
I mean I wouldn't worry about the meta I
don't think the meta really is gonna
matter that much okay just pick whatever
Pokemon you like okay you should you
should learn what your skills do though
I'll try I'll try the bird because
I haven't tried that one before I think
if you click on Battle prep and then go
to moveset you can read
uh what your skills it's a very
important very important she keeps on
telling me to read what was this
when the Pokemon's at high HP the
movement speed is increased oh pick
oh I'm probably just picking flame
charges that's the only thing though
where's the ulti
um
the old oh yeah it's the old team okay
no no it's not it's not sorry the one
that's in gold is the old oh I didn't
see it
didn't have time for it Valentine is
good for beginner okay okay nice yeah I
chose it as the the first Pokemon
because well it's got flames
kind of yeah it does fit you it is kind
of Phoenix you can also choose we have
different skills
with a gold one oh yeah really fancy
they have an animated yeah
let's go
we're gonna win fun let's go up
I'm cute I look like
they learn now they know I like the
speed
let's see this one's way more speedy
so if you go out here there's just one
in the middle which is like not on
either side so it's good to like steal
this one so we get an XP Advantage okay
from the other team so they don't get it
the one which is
yeah yeah in the early game it's like
important to get an XP Advantage okay so
you want to like try to get the last
hits on
Pokemon to spawn in the middle I don't
know where they are Oh missing top oh
there they are okay
oh oh they're ganking we can go
thank you
oh we got we we made it oh incredible
you can score your points and you heal
when you score two oh do you heal I
think you do
wait for me I want to score two
it might be too late now
yeah it's too late it's too late
[Music]
fine I'll eat my food I'll keep my funny
little points
hmm
yeah just try to stay with people
as long as you can
and don't go out too far standing in the
goal will heal you yes yes
so it's relatively safe in there
they can still like harass us though
they are harassing us yeah you want to
stay back you can eat the fruit
go away thank you thank you for coming
to our rescue
hey
oh my God I feel I'm like super Speedy
but I feel like I I'm like so low on
defense and yeah you probably don't have
much HP I need to grow up into big verb
yeah eat this bunny
[Music]
may I please may no no okay no
please
I think did you mean these ones
what do you mean this group of Pokemon
uh as being desirable in the middle yeah
see they tried to like you can eat the
berry they tried to like last hit steel
and I think they did something from us
okay
I need to dunk
we gotta be careful though
you know because they're here
I don't know really I think we're still
like
laning okay okay
probably soon we should
okay come on and slam and welcome to the
gym
oh okay don't forget to use your potion
oh don't die don't die don't leave just
leave I I was I was checking the button
you can't hold someone
okay now what you can score
[Music]
there it is nice
come on and slam and welcome to the jam
let's follow this now we can yeah we can
follow I think uh breakfast I don't know
maybe that
whoa
I wish you would read your skills then
you wouldn't know
like to to choose which skill and in
between I have to quickly choose oops
we can take some time though if you want
to read about the Pokemons
I'm out I'll do it off screen off before
tournament
or the practice
if you don't know what your skills do I
just I just I feel like I remember from
normal Pokemon games that uh bright bird
wasn't so bad that's when she was Brave
Bird I'm very different in it's very
different
I would say it's very different
I feel like I did I made the right
choice
where should we go yeah we have a short
I think I chose the right skills
[Laughter]
it doesn't really matter which one you
choose that much but you should know
what they do so you know how to use them
okay
oh what is this I found
yours to talk about
oh our team is split oh you guys are
attacking down there the red G's red
eyes yeah oh you killed it good job I
had friends to help that's good
now
okay
[Music]
hahaha
no one was there they didn't expect it
where should we go
where should we go um they need help I
died because I was stupid should we go
up
yeah
um
let's just go where the team teammates
are
okay oh I can still work with my 18
points
hey
I came here to play not to read
I think this is my first ever mobile
oh really you never planned like donuts
no I don't know none of that none of
that
whoa
I always for some reason
this is a good mob at the start with oh
I'm stay alive
[Music]
a bit
Diane dying dying dead I'm dead
this is a good moment to start with some
people call it baby's first MOBA why
it's like a simplified it's pretty
simplified and it's short I think that's
great though
I feel like we're because they're they
also took one of our bases I feel like
currently we are kind of matched up
pretty well
yeah still
oh uh oh that's the Masters player we
should probably listen to them oh their
scoring it's probably too late what does
the master player say they said defend
our goal oh sorry
oh wait what
how did Mommy
oh well
we lost that goal that we didn't defend
oh yeah we did
hmm
is is wait this one what I do is that
these arrows depending on goals yeah I'm
here oh they got the special Pokemon
that helps them push
we're really struggling I see that yeah
we're doomed even with the Masters
player we can't win oh my God I'm
ashamed
are you using your skills often all the
time I'm like buttonmouth okay good
pretty much good yeah or where do I go
they have short cooldowns usually so oh
yeah my these girls they got it no no no
no no no no no no no no they got
should I go in the middle that I died oh
no probably not
does it anyway
[Music]
it's the Masters player they're fine
just because you're a master doesn't
mean you should be everywhere alone
taking my hand I'll help you
who who says that uh is that like
automatic like we're struggling is that
from the game yeah yeah it's the
announcer
and you could get bonus points at the
end of the game when it's yellow
like that okay I'm not giving up
I'm not giving up we shouldn't give up
on her first we have to leave now they
have to leave but that still means now
we can get our lead back
we do only have 30 seconds no no no no
be nice be nice be nice be nice
oh
oh 30 seconds oh
we do only have 18 seconds the person
was not nice
oh
[Laughter]
dang it I couldn't score sorry
is it clear who's gonna
um win yes it's based on points not on
goals oh
so the points that you score can destroy
goals but you can also get bonuses like
at the end you get double points so
points scored in the last part are worth
a lot more but I feel like we didn't do
so bad
yeah we didn't
it was closer than the last ones
what there's a dash
there's a dash
a dash how do I Dash
oh
is it one of your skills or are they
talking about the one of my skills does
feel like a dash yeah
you should probably read your skills I
would really recommend it if you're just
if you're just pushing them at random
yeah but there's not much time to read
the skills when there's there's we can't
we can we can go to the menu and you can
read
that's such an exciting stream content
pretty important though
pretty important if you want to play the
game
you gotta know what your skills are to
know when to use them because they don't
all just like do damage some of them are
like utility items
open new or
um do you want to look at the Pokemon
the one
well the ones I have or yeah someone you
want to play I said you can go back
soon
can I leave can I leave
you could probably leave do I leave how
do I leave how do I leave how do I leave
I don't see any any button to leave
um you have to wait till the game starts
or you could quit the game does that
give me like any like oh maybe you can't
does that I don't know if it gives you
punishment in the
in the custom Lobby
I'm closing the game I hope I don't get
punishment
[Music]
ah yeah I shouldn't
okay well sorry guys who stayed in the
game
have fun playing with each other
maybe there was something look 4v5 I'll
probably leave maybe a few will stay
banned forever a band for one month and
for one month that'd be so bad right
before the time
against people who just you know would
you say bye-bye it's true I think custom
zombies are different though so in the
main menu you can go
ziel when you get there
um
wait did they add tinkerton to this game
no seems like all the new Pokemon are in
I love tinkerton
time to get it is she in the game or is
she coming soon I didn't see her
no not yet what is this
what
oh oh
what but you should play this one I
claim okay fauna maybe look at my stream
and and give me a coaching okay it'll be
delayed oh yeah true
uh
I can I can show you on Discord okay
okay
uh
oh is this
did it put you back in the game
yeah
is it the same game no my audio would
like oh my audio is lagging when I when
I show you sorry okay no problem
okay
why I went to this game I want to get
out of there oh what's this
what happened now oh
that wasn't even me how did that end
admin oh you closed the game admin
powers
thanks guys see you another time bye-bye
look you won you won oh my God he is
uh main menu okay
okay
now
you said ZL oh God yes and then go to
Pokemon
uh should I read all of them now
no no just whichever one you want to
play you think you should pick one and
then stick with it so you can learn that
one for the tournament
right now I barely have any choice I
don't know if that's what I want to go
with for the tournament especially if
they give us other choices then I don't
know well I think it's good to just
commit to one Pokemon because they're
all really different so you should learn
the skills of one for the tournament and
then just stick with that one these ones
I don't really have them right because I
don't have the license but sometimes I
can still play them yeah you can always
buy the license though if you want
I I had fun being Speedy with Talonflame
but I feel it's more buff with the nine
tails but I feel like neither one is
good you're a really popular choice for
others too especially because that's
like the second Pokemon you get if you
download the game now
apparently
uh what if everybody takes nine tails
can we see what people have chosen for
our team for I feel like Ian hasn't like
I think I said yeah
choosing one but
if you type in the Discord you want to
be nine tails and you get first dibs I
think okay
okay should I read this out loud
snow warning what causes well if I don't
very quietly it's gonna be awkward pause
the snow to fall on an opposing Pokemon
dealing damage to it and decreasing its
movement speed for a short time boosted
attacks and moves except Aurora Veil
slings no and hitting the same targets
of snow multiple times will freeze it
for a short time
um
this screen confuses me so this one that
one is a passive
can you just get it and then this one
yeah this one you choose between them
you can pick either Avalanche or
dazzling gleam
a text with a gush of Chilly eyes
towards the designated area the ice
forms a while that cannot be passed
through on land after a short time this
wall melts and collapses dealing damage
to opposing Pokemon in the area of
effect upgrade also decreases the
movement speed of opposing Pokemon for a
short time okay
so like a wall
yeah yeah I've chosen always Avalanche
so far attacks with a powerful cone no
planning light leaving the pulsing
Pokemon unable to act when this move
hits
uh-huh
no I think uh I don't know I would
prefer Avalanche maybe probably and
where's the ulti oh here unite move snow
globe attached with chili snow and ice
stealing damage to opposing Pokemon in
the area of effect when it hits deals
and creates damage to opposing Pokemon
that are frozen
so and then you have another skill too
oh
which one I see one uh
Blizzard or Aurora Veil
ah are these ones ah
summons a howling blizzard and two
blasts in the forward Direction the
first blast deals damage to opposing
Pokemon in the area of effect and the
creature movement speed for short time I
don't know the second police deals damn
it the second blast deals damage to
opposing Pokemon in the area of effect
and shoves them if the second blast hits
an obstacle it also deals damage
multiple times to opposing Pokemon near
the point of a new point of impact and
decreases the movement speed for a short
time
and above this just above has the user
leap to the designated location and
create an aurora around itself that
reduces damage received by the user and
Ally Pokemon in the area of effect
while the user is inside the aurawa it's
movement speed has increased and it's
basic attacks the conversations
yeah I don't know I feel like I wouldn't
do this
it seems like blizzard combos with
Avalanche because if the second blast
hits an obstacle the obstacle could be
the wall I think mm-hmm
yeah
I want them that would go for that oh
okay now you know what your skills do
so you should be good I guess I'll focus
on nine tails so pretty yeah I think
it's good to just learn one Pokemon
because they're all pretty different
yeah but the thing is I just like
really just played the game for an hour
or so before the stream so far so it's
like I have to first get to know some
Pokemon I first have to get to know the
game I I can't like
do everything
immediately of course this is what the
practice is for yeah yeah yeah okay
um do we want to try or like a with
randoms
I think it'd be good we could get some
it might be easier and we might get some
points we can use but there's lobbies
here too
don't join
ing
don't join guys don't jump before from
the phone that has absolute priority
okay let me
let me bite
I want to choose the sky ruins because
apparently that's what we're using for
the tournament but I can't
oh I think I can choose it oh
that you might get
I don't know how the Ping will be
you got green hair
now yeah wow
cute
ah wait now I should see it right okay
um if you want or we can play with
people in our skill rank oh I already
showed it okay
wow that's that's cute it's got a
peacock it's cute
it's really cute okay ready yes
Ready Set Go
go do they have to be in the same skill
rank the ones that joined now um we
might get matched against another five
stack which might be like a team
so it might be hard oh
that would be fine
oh I was removed from the lobby what why
that happened to me before too who who
decided that to be to remove you I don't
know
well then we kind of have a chance to
yeah behind the cone
and then
oh did I not ready oops oh maybe that's
why
okay uh I give you neither
as you will be our team leader in the
actual tournament too I think oh no okay
you ready I think you can I'm ready you
can like when we're actually like in the
real tournament you can give all of us
instructions like go there go there
okay
I'll try to they'll try to learn yes
please then you can learn you already
know I don't I don't really I don't
really have confidence
just do whatever the teammates are doing
foreign
[Music]
is that a Virgin Killer sweater
no make sure to push ready again
I guess it's not because it does look
like it goes bad it has a back
you know Virgin Killer sweater
yeah
okay does everybody know what it is
Chad gave me the reaction that seems
like they know
I'm sure they know
I feel like it it fell off in popularity
it was super popular yeah
I I didn't have one
I don't have one
me neither
what's what's that
huh let's just uh let's play the game
fan art fan art incoming honestly I
would like to stand up
it's a dead Trend so I don't think I've
ever seen Virgin Killer sweater fan art
before yeah it is kind of a dead Trend
what's up with that come back come
watching kill us weather there were even
like variations of it to make it more
special
um but yeah you know
oh I I remember
I don't know anything
I never heard of this in my life yeah me
neither let's play Let's Play let's just
play up
up okay
we can no longer command them oh oh yeah
right oh wait these people don't know
right
they probably don't I just realized yeah
oh my God I feel so bad if we do bad
then I feel so bad
it's fine we'll do well just be safe I
think it's good to stay safe generally
so let's go over here
okay and get this one
uh and it's good to use your skills your
damage skills to get the last hit
because it does more damage so you can
secure the last hit
thank you
are we commending
no I think we are yes he was alone
it's good very good very good so far oh
sure friends sure it's way fun suddenly
we're like so powerful because we're
actually matched with normal people
who are not overheating a little bit I
feel bad
they're feeding us oh yeah
I feel bad I feel good feel good feel
good
they're babies they might be children
me too we're also children fauna
look at us we look so youthful
we've already grown up though
oh true I love this guy
oh it's another night Tails there could
only be one
I feel like the game just said confona I
heard it did it yeah I'm playing with it
you did because oh I'm in I'm in
handheld mode ah
us I gotta put up the stream reservation
for the tournament after this
should I put it on yeah I think I'll put
it public the Japanese member's already
pulling it up too oh are they oh wait
let's see where he is they requested us
to put it up with him today oh okay
actually yesterday I think with it
yesterday yeah no but don't worry we
were not the only ones who didn't put it
up
it'd be like that yeah yeah I don't like
putting up streams that early because
they're gonna be like yeah yeah they get
lost yeah
oh everyone's bottom we should probably
be there oh that's fine I guess
[Music]
we just destroyed this really quickly oh
there's the guy
[Applause]
oh wait I come to you
I got it
oh
good job oh our team has come up here
with us because we were not happy in
this they complied with our
requests oh
oh okay we should kill this thing
quickly really fast and they'll probably
try to steal it
you should not let them steal it okay
now it will help us push
and I'll score 20 points
oh I never saw that happening before
nice
oh boy
I scored two
yeah it makes you so you can score
instantly now we should back up probably
okay
oh 11 more really deep eleven more and
that one is gone mm-hmm
yeah you can just kill the random moms
to get experience
oh everybody's down we should go down
oh maybe too late
it's never too late
it's not too late nice Chihuahua real is
coming to the rescue
what are you guys doing down there
uh we're defeating this
okay we're kind of stomping them I feel
bad
we got one of their bases
um we're stomping it's not just about
the bases this is
to be fauna I don't think it's how it's
supposed to be
strong
laughs
as you can see we have a huge XP lead
wait where do I see the EXP
um well you can see it in the menu but
you can also just see like their much
lower levels
ah oh yeah because I'm 11.
I don't think I died a single time
yeah
trial by fire at first in the big
lobbies although those will probably be
more accurate to what it will
[Music]
do you guys hear that in chat do you
hear that I mean I have it pretty quiet
but that sounds 100 like I heard several
times oh no he stole it from us what
now we have to kill this thing
it's constantly
I'm coming to you okay my dad's helping
me kill this thing
there we go
no don't don't die I'm gonna die to this
thing no
I'll finish it okay finish it off for me
done
okay just stay back a little bit
I guess we're strong though maybe
actually we don't need to be afraid but
usually we should be a little afraid
you're on fire we have a huge lead yeah
we do
probably can push by ourselves
now this will be gone
yeah see they're like they're just going
in alone they're not grouping oh which
is what you need to do maybe we have the
advantage because we're in voice chat
but we're only two people
so
oh oh oh oh oh oh well now
too much
I'm down
and down
it's okay A Little Too Deep dying once
it's okay
we're winning anyway
it's true
secrecy stretchy fauna
I was watching those whole stream fauna
the whole stream the whole stream I had
nothing else to do
it was wonderful fauna
you did a good job
oh thank you were you nervous
I was nervous to be surrounded by oh I
see so many cute girls cute girls yeah
you were one too cute simple thank you
so much fan service yeah the mv2 holy
moly
quite something yeah right I liked how
you took off your sleeve score I know
you thought was it you see for yourself
sleeves and socks both oh my God I don't
know the Envy was it was really
something
yeah oh
sorry it's kind of stomped then I feel a
little bad let's stop if they knew who
was stomping on them they would be
grateful
whoa whoa whoa whoa
look at us wow
good job team good time
not bad can we get do we get stuffs
we're winning we do get stuff
give me what did I get 200 EXP
erience
Venice Venusaur I got a new license yay
nice okay
well if that's how the tournament goes
then I'm I'm confident
maybe the maybe the the custom battles
were more accurate
or maybe something I feel like it will
be the stuffing in between I don't think
they're all like as good as you know the
viewers yeah well I don't know if all of
the viewers were that good
um
some of them definitely were some of
them were running potions unless they
are using Smurf accounts
number one I I left the lobby yeah oh I
can choose the sky ruins now I could
okay do you want to invite me then yes
always
foreign
[Music]
I just started or should I give you
later again we can start oh I don't need
to be the leader it's okay
but thank you you're welcome
tell me about your experience at the
official stream
mmm what about it tell me a who who you
gotta uh who which Japanese member was
the most
um
I don't know uh oh push Randy don't
forget push ready oh that was close
sorry oh no
oopsie one more
I've been I've been temporarily banned
from participating
what is the 55 is it 55 seconds or 55
minutes I think it's 55 seconds okay
what
48 seconds okay none don't forget to
push push the ready button
once okay wait uh I don't know I want to
hear your experience because like I had
a lot of fun for our official stream
yeah yeah you were another one yeah it
was really fun I was translating a lot
for um and and I don't know we had a lot
of fun playing game oh yeah but you guys
were taking those selfie pictures that
was your game I was thinking I wish I
was there because I I want to show off
my selfie skills yeah
I would be probably really bad at that
but I was uh it was so cute it was fun
yeah throwing was actually pretty fun
yeah was it difficult to think of a sexy
way to throw a ball oh yes yes
I could have thrown more accurately if I
wasn't trying to be sexy wait did you
girls get the fruit in the end
we did although I think most of the
girls had left by the time they brought
out the fruit because they had to cut it
up oh no they saw it unfortunately oh
I'm sorry I wasn't prepared this is fine
we can play okay
well you girls were doing they cut it
after after the stream so it was fresh
but then most of the girls had left
right now quickly ride these remember to
push ready yes pushed but I had not I
had not left so I got to eat the fruit
was that your dinner yes
200 grapes was it really like worth the
200 dollars
no no but it was really good probably
the best grapes I've ever had but they
brought me like 20 grapes and I think
those were like just as good ah I
thought almost as good as the 200 ones
did they have seeds inside
they're green and seedless oh was it
just grapes
their grapes and peaches and a melon
melon what's your favorite melon
honeydew or the the other ones there's
like I like cantaloupe oh you like I
think a lot of people hate yes I don't
hate cantaloupe but yeah there's so many
people who hate on cancer but I'm kind
of a honeydew hater normally but I think
it's just in North America fruit is kind
of bad oh wait compared to like Japanese
fruit honeydew is the orange one right
the inside orange inside is Orange right
how do you do is light green oh that one
oh cantaloupe is the orange one
cantaloupe is the orange one oh you know
I actually I prefer uh honeydew
yeah I think a lot of people do but in
North America I feel like the honeydew
is always like dry it's not juicy and
it's like hard and flavorless yeah I
noticed that a lot and like when there's
like cut fruit
um cups that I buy or those yeah they
always put in like the really hard uh
part yeah the worst but I feel like
that's only because they they cut the so
close to the um to the oh the salad yeah
yeah if it's more in the middle then it
will be soft and juicy
mmm yeah the the honey do the like 200
honeydew is really good
I don't know it probably wasn't 200. it
was probably cheaper I bet the grapes
were the most expensive ah thing did you
guys get normal Bento too
um
they had a few different kinds of Bentyl
they had like a fried chicken one
what are you doing Jigglypuff what are
you doing get out of here get out of
here or stay so that we can get the EXP
erience they're not gonna be punished
for that they want why are they coming
here to die
nice
we can score points if you want I want
to do it quick though people are gonna
leave okay
okay we should leave we should leave
you got it you gotta do it quick you
gotta stay with the team oh
nice potion nice potion
get back get back you want to go I want
to I didn't want to attack that one can
you not like choose our attacking you
should probably yeah I think you can
turn off auto attack
is it just the direction then where are
you looking at
um
yeah
it's like sometimes I notice how it like
drags me back even though I'm trying to
escape and I'm just yeah or maybe just
don't attack
a nice range
it's fine
sometimes you can't that one has a cute
outfit though I know I might buy an
outfit hey
we're the tournament
I already spent money on this game
how much does it cost to get like a cute
outfit in real money I don't know
twenty dollars
maybe less
twenty dollars that's kind of expensive
yeah especially if a lot of children are
mostly playing this game yeah
for me that was four four weeks of
pocket money
inflation kids these days with their 20
Fortnight skins
how much pocket money did you always get
um I didn't have an allowance what
what but my mom would buy me things okay
but did you have to beg for it no and I
didn't no no
hold on that's that works that's nice
she was nice she let me have the video
games I wanted video games
what what video games did little fauna
play
I played I loved GameCube that was like
my time yeah
but I had kind of bad taste like
freaking games
there's no such is bad taste
I played a lot of like movie games like
the Shrek 2 game
I love that one I loved the Narnia one
oh I loved Sonic Adventure 2 and Billy
Hatcher those are Classics but I never
played like Zelda or anything I wish I
had
played Zelda
yeah
what did that one that was I feel like I
missed out
without playing Zelda yeah I think I
think it didn't now you're playing great
games so whatever but I've still never
played a Zelda game I need to yeah oh my
God you really have to
I know
big recommend
maybe tears of the Kingdom or breath of
the wild well okay uh if you start now I
actually I never played breath of the
wild but I watched a million full out a
million hours of full playthroughs
and then I play t-o-t-k it's
ah it's such a beautiful experience it's
so addiction yeah
that's what I've heard
I want to play um Wind Waker too okay I
feel like Wind Waker might be better for
you to start I don't I don't think you
should start playing Zelda games with
breath of the wild or tears of the
Kingdom play yeah Wind Waker I can
recommend one of it's like my favorite
Zelda game
is it yeah
it and it's like shorter way shorter
yeah yeah and it has cute Graphics that
people does and maybe didn't like so
much in the beginning but I feel like
now it's getting appreciated yeah I
don't know why they wouldn't like it
well it holds up so well because it's so
stylized yeah I think so too
like uh Wind Waker when I was younger
um my brother was playing it on the
GameCube my older brother and I was
always watching him and tried sometimes
to play alone but I was always the
Observer for most games
yeah I never I I still to this day don't
really like playing games alone I like
to play with friends or I want to watch
other people play but that's that's like
why I like streaming because it doesn't
feel alone well you mean even when
you're playing a game alone yeah you
have Chad yeah yeah I have chat because
I get like Lonely by myself I don't know
that's true because when I play uh like
solo games I feel like I'm playing it
with the chat because they're also
backseating yeah yeah but I I want them
to backseat me so it feels like we're
playing the game together
yeah good stuff good stuff it seems like
we're winning again even though I'm I'm
personally just like focusing on chit
chatting right now
yeah we're definitely winning
I feel kind of bad we deserve to win
after all these losses
we have the five stack right now maybe
they're Bots are they Bots
they might be Bots
oh no yeah and they give the Bots real
names in this game so you can't tell
okay
I think they're Bots
probably because there's like too much
skill difference in this Lobby they
cannot the other one also might have
been Bots I'm not sure
I died I died to bots
I will give you back up
just wait it will take a while I'm very
slow attacking
Reggie lekki what a name
you have a here no I'm supposed to help
this guy
is there still um Zapdos in this game I
saw one today when I was playing oh
there's Rayquaza
I think Rayquaza if you kill it you get
instant points or was I not supposed to
attack him oh okay
and we really don't want to let it get
stolen the other team will try to steal
it
by getting the last hit that's kind of
sad
it's like one of the most important
things
yeah so when it gets low it's good to
use your skills because you do more
damage in a burst we got it right
oh we got it we got a shield not instant
score ah
so we can all go and dump our points
and we have a shield so they can't
interrupt our scoring oh okay I'm
dumping and because it's the final
stretch we give bonus points and now we
basically just win we win yes we did
yeah
it's good to win
do you ever get like really salty with
toxic salty gamer Behavior
um probably maybe not super something
I've been salty before
I don't really get that salty in Pokemon
unite though even when I'm losing oh
they say yes she does
Hitman
up
Hitman but I don't think I'm that salty
in it I'm not like yelling or swearing
or anything thank God
I'm like internally salty but I'm not
like that outwardly salty
I do get like tilted I start playing
badly oh oh it's ending
yep
okay
I'm excited for the score
I think we won
is this a good sign yes I don't know I
don't know
whoa whoa
it feels
I don't know it feels a little unfair
yes yes yes I must agree
this player did really well maybe you
should add them as a friend no I I only
want funny as my friends
ah 200 XP
oh yeah we still get XP for this noise
all right because this time I I wasn't
able to hide the the cold right let's
one
sure
and we're gonna
we're gonna play against people on our
level
[Music]
we should pick our friends based on how
talented they are yeah that's that's the
implication that's the moral of this
game only be friends with with the
people who play the game the best
is it sad do you feel like Hollow live
is kind of like that
we're all we're all very talented
yeah
and we're here presumably because of
some level of talent maybe
well yeah yeah
we're put together because of it um
did you watch the new girls Advent
I did of course what's your impression
my impression you I don't know it was my
first time getting
true oh my God it's like
there I'm like how can I be a senpai to
these girls they're so talented already
well they don't they don't need my
Senpai guidance their debuts were like
so yeah like they didn't seem nervous at
all most of them it's like they were so
cool
I know right right I feel like like MIP
was like out of all of Ian myth debuts
were like the most questionable
like Cali had insane lag I had a lot of
yeah
it's true yeah I mean I think Ena was
like really stable and fine and honestly
good and Amber were fine too from my POV
but overall I think our debuts were not
only because of how we did them but also
because of what we were able to show off
like we didn't have an anime trailer and
so on so yeah yeah we didn't need that
yeah the debuts are just like so I think
that's just the way it goes
um
the debuts will just keep getting more
and more and they're more prepared
to avoid
I wish I could redo it
and mm-hmm
do you really though I for me debut was
like quite stressful I don't I wouldn't
want to tape you like did you did you
hear my debut stream
true because but dude my mic was so
effed up and and I I
um oh no I want to redo
I guess like for me I just wouldn't want
to like go back to like not knowing like
my fan base to not not having like the
Rapport built up you know I'm not gonna
commit to this I don't think oh maybe we
can just kill him of course we commit to
it okay
now here maybe I don't know about this
one are we doing this one okay
it might as well might as well
I already had a few debuts that's true I
had some free debuts but that that's
just you know jokes that doesn't really
undo what happened in the first place
bad memories it's true when I did my
debut re-watch after one year I I didn't
feel like like our Absol is here oh the
content of what I said I think was like
what I generally said throughout the
whole stream was fine in my opinion
but it's just it wasn't pleasant to
watch anyway
I think it was great it was very
different back then you know everything
was different back then so you can't
really like compare it to now hmm
I think
yeah
yeah with the new members I didn't feel
any cringe
they probably didn't feel cringe
watching your debut
like
I don't know about that I'm sure they
didn't things were so different back
then oh no this was like honestly found
out that's like so long ago maybe they
didn't even watch the debut because this
is like ancient they watched it I'm sure
they watched it
oh I think I think
Larissa right yes she was a fan yes oh
I'm one point short
I did this alone oh my God I think yeah
I think Bijou as well has been a hollow
life fan for a long time
a lot of them talked about how they
tried for a long time like several times
they applied
I think pretty much
almost all of them tried several times
to get in applied many times so I only
apply once how many times did you apply
I played once I guess now there's that
crazy competition and it was over a
really long time frame yeah things are
just so different now just everything
has changed so much I mean when you when
you debuted that was like the start of
whole life English when you applied
whole life English not even a thing yeah
I feel so bad so they're killing this
one for like five times now no
cute pink round one
yeah we're kind of stomping them again
at one point but better than nothing I'm
sorry please don't play
something
I feel bad it really hurt you
so much
they're they might be children okay now
there's like a big group of them holy
[\h__\h] and we do it we can defeat them oh
my God
let's go let's go find this thing what
is that is that a bot because like it's
always coming to me that can't be real
would a butt be better in the game
is that toxic
that that behavior just looks very very
off to me
they're really just running right in
[Music]
oh no
it's the game Pokemon unite Bots or
children you'll never know
ah
you're right that is a bot
he always always goes up the upper path
and goes up against us and if we're not
there he just continues to go up I don't
know
I don't know
yeah he's probably six are you allowed
to play this game when you're six
I think so I think you are is there a
minimum age requirement
I don't know maybe there is
yes yes as in he's allowed to who should
stop them true
it is baby's first MOBA
but I love Pokemon unite I think it's
really fun like I've played it all I
played a lot of DOTA back in the day
I just think Pokemon unite is fun
it's fun to have a more Simple Mobile
it's like short short matches
they're great I'm having fun with it
yeah though the matches can be like an
hour long it's just like who's got time
for that
is that normal with all mobile games no
I think league is shorter like 30
minutes maybe
um
but still
I mean though it is not supposed to be
an hour but it can be
come more too long
I agree this one even has quicker ones
that are like five minutes long they're
also pretty fun oh yeah
yeah if you lose it doesn't feel like
you invested so much time just to lose
you can just start over
it's just very very chill right now I
know right
so walk in the park
is this how the other teams felt when
they were
um
well uh they're fighting up top okay
oh
they don't really need our help okay
well I guess
where else do we go oh
um we can go score our points we can
walk with the this thing
the Reggie I don't know what it is I
don't know is that from which Pokemon
game is that one I sure don't think it's
that new like did seven or six I don't
know
whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
do you hear Coldplay
I wanna hear it I'm playing muted I hear
nothing
I love it it's so cute it's almost as
cute as when you say it
I really would love to do the voice
announcer for this game they don't have
that though
like how augmented paladins yeah that
would be fun one Potion No potion I I
already used it
um okay Rayquaza up here though
oh wait that's movement speed
I think I'm gonna
try to heal somewhere
uh
the take on Rayquaza without me right
maybe I don't know they're dying our
teammates are dying oh no okay I'm
coming back
keep the pressure on
are you a real person
I'm real
you're real yeah we got it
just when I arrived
thank you
[Music]
are you playing with the English uh yes
my game is English
okay
so the coffee now is in English maybe it
says something else in German
[Music]
they have surrendering what happens with
untunked points at the end do they still
get counters no they don't just lose
them
only count if dunked okay
all right last one was very big success
again
is that the random Pokemon that's the
number of points you've scored ah with
everything together
just like the points you dunked so it's
pointy dumped and then it's kills and
then assists and then I think the last
one is your score
overall score okay okay
yeah what what did that um
okay okay
yeah well that was fun I feel like
um I'm I'm gonna be at least
yeah I think I won't be clueless when
the tournament at least
so should be okay right Pokemon boost
mm-hmm oh I leveled up
maybe we should I completed two missions
uh maybe we should observe the
opponent's practice streams and see how
good they are yeah we should
they can't be that that cracks can they
um
I know can they be maybe maybe they play
it
off stream let's study the enemy
it doesn't matter if we lose it's true
I'm just happy to be here I'm happy we
can stream Pokemon unite again yeah
genuinely I genuinely love this game any
Pokemon game I'm happy about streaming
it so yeah
um guys there uh I own my schedule I put
uh for Wednesday I put Pokemon unite or
GTA 4 but I think I'll be fine I was
just gonna do the Pokemon unite if it's
really really difficult for some reason
I'll practice a little bit more behind
the scenes but that day will now be GTA
5 4 I mean four instead are you feeling
confident
yeah I don't think I can win against
jpid but I don't think there's like like
a huge need to do everyday endless
practice
that's true
so
have confidence gonna have confidence
and have fun and and reliable yeah
don't forget to claim all of your stuff
oh yeah I've been trying to but there's
like so much like with these games there
is so there's so much on the screen to
look at
well thank you fauna for coaching me a
little bit and being at my side guiding
me I hope it was helpful this was our
second one-on-one collab bonna
is it yeah I don't think you did you do
many Clubhouse together no we've had
more we didn't really do Clubhouse
together and then we did Minecraft
together was that one-on-one
yeah there was one the Wither school one
well then what then it was the third oh
yeah yeah by the way I found another
Fortress
no not watching oh did you the
underground the the never uh yeah
I found another one it was like really
lucky I made a portal and suddenly I was
in front of one oh you were just there
yeah it just so happened
hey if you need more if you're looking
for one let me know I have okay the good
stuff yeah the cords yes I've got it all
thank you thank you
the only thing I'm really worried about
is
my sleep like will I be like yeah awake
for it I will be awake but like how
awake will you be will I be yeah yeah
you'll be physically awake but will you
be mentally aware yeah it's a game of
of mental concentration Pokemon unite
that's the issue but I'll do my best
Tanya
Euros
I'll do my best too
okay guys
um see you soon are you streaming after
this or what's going on oh no not today
oh tomorrow tomorrow I stream oh maybe
Pokemon you're not Pokemon
it's time limited probably so let's go
yeah
do some more grinding
get those cute outfits and stuff
okay and in German we say
okay
bye bye guys good night thanks for
watching you've been watching
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]