I
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
this is Hol live English Adent
devilish ghost narissa
ravencraft and I am
dead one sec one sec I'm still dead this
doesn't change
anything this doesn't change anything
I'm still dead
but now that you guys are
here well the afterlife isn't so bad
I've been chilling in this in this
onen that popped up out of
nowhere it's it's quite nice I I'll
admit I can't I can't help but
appreciate
[Music]
it your volume is
low that's because I'm
dead I I I suppose
though there's only so many days left so
I ought to leave this lovely onent of
the
afterlife and go
out I'm still not pleased one
sec and go out
into the world and do don't ask me what
cuz I don't know but I I might as well
go do
something something with my ghost life
keep your money in the afterlife of
course
[Music]
just because I'm a ghost doesn't mean
that I'm not addicted to the
Grind now we have a little bit of an
issue but I think we should be able to
make do for a little bit at
least haunt everyone that's that's the
plan that is indeed the plan after being
brutally now if you did not watch
yesterday's stream because there wasn't
one you might
be admittedly a bit confused so let let
me fill you in if you uh missed and are
very lost about what's going on right
now uh
basically yesterday I gave birth to my
child herb is the
father and uh
Kiara or excuse me Shakira promptly
killed said
child
promptly
ah so after the death of my child I was
murdered by by
Shakira I was murdered so now
begins I I'm I don't know I'm just going
to make potato
salad I'm going to make potato
salad I'm going to be become even more
Rich for why do not ask me I do not
know but clearly if there's one thing I
need it's more
money right
brothers who doesn't need more
money I know I do uh I'm I'm a little on
the broke side today after all uh due to
some shenanigan
[Music]
re but it it matters not it matters
not let us put our potatoes here I
suppose I
shall throw away this poison potato I do
not need
it oh there's a lot of potatoes you know
it's
interesting because for a while there
was no potatoes I I remember when I
first
began becoming the
potato the farmer uh I could not find
any like anywhere it was really
hard not even 100K I don't think anyone
in this game has 100K I'm going to be
real what do you mean not even 100K Shak
in my
head no one has that much money
Liz planted them I know I I I saw from
Beyond the
Grave I was
watching I was
watching as
she oops H that's okay who's using wheat
in this game
anyway not
[Music]
me these are easier to
she likes making bread are you
sure why would you make bread when you
can just buy
it I guess when you're broke you have to
cope however you
can I'm very sad that today I have found
out potions cannot
stack it is indeed my
undoing and will probably be the end of
me if if I'm
honest
[Music]
H okay now we must find
carrots did you hear about gathan and
Jonathan uh
alas I have heard of what has
befell gathan AKA Jonathan with a G
it is quite the horror I could I could
not imagine honestly like oh my God uh
honestly Romance of the century I'm at
the edge of my seat uh losing it uh I I
need to know what's going to
happen I'm eager for the next uh chapter
of this
Saga see look how look how quick this is
look how quick and nice this is when
there's just actual
rows
amazing okay we have some extra
carrots she is but a humble night gathan
uh it may have made
me a little emotional and by a little I
mean very emotional uh it was
simply the saddest thing that I've ever
seen uh and I honestly I don't want to
think about it cuz
that's how horrible it
was I'm sure I'm sure you guys can
understand where I'm coming com
from in that
[Music]
feeling I
must something is being created here I
sh stick around to see who the Builder
is however
if all I remember
she yeah
[Music]
no are you a ghost what happened to you
uh Kiara killed me for one if you want
to know the real
answer it it was quite brutal I must say
uh quite a brutal a brutal murder I did
not deserve to go out the way that I
did I I'm still honestly quite very very
upset about it
honestly I don't think I can I can ever
forgive her for murdering me not only me
but my freshly born
born chicken
child with
herb uh
forgiveness is not in my
heart I don't think I bought enough
eggs the best thing I lay eggs yeah
obviously in this universe probably
oh it was carrots I ran out of
first but not in not in
seriousness now I do need more
eggs how
many I can get away with buying one
[Music]
but such is the
life why do I not have enough carrots I
feel like I definitely had enough
carrots and now I'm very lost and
confused well it matters not
it's on page seven now every day it just
gets
moved we are going to grind up our money
because I'm uncomfortable being below
50,000
H so I'm going to fix
that uh
now ghostly yes I am a ghost
I am
[Applause]
dead and as you know being dead is a
and 46k is too poor for that of a
dead
woman I demand to not be poor if I'm
going to be dead that if I'm going to be
dead at the very least I could have
something called money
but you can respond
no it is different when a phoenix is
that which kills you you do not
[Music]
understand you do not understand yes I
will be buried with my
fortune with my
fortune the burial
proceedings uh but I I will not be
paying for my own funeral that that is
for sure someone else is going to have
to do that I I don't know who but it
better be grand after all I was uh no
broke in
lestel so I I I I feel like it's only
it's only
fair that I have a funeral
that that uh displays my vast
wealth herb can't afford that I I I
never said it must be Liz lady blood
flame I never said it must be lady blood
flame simply that it must be
somebody now what are we going to do
with our wealth do not ask
me are you going to give all your money
to your wife Shori lady blood flame in
the library I know I will be buried with
my rich
and then in thousands of
years uh I I will I need I need to be
buried on a private
island out in the middle of
nowhere and I will amount uh I I will I
will leave my treasure
surrounding me in in a super difficult
and treacherous place and then at that
time and that time only uh I will be
pursued by that of which of of a Pirates
and others searching for my treasure
that I
hid in the grand
[Music]
line yes you've heard it here
first the the one piece is
real Strange Life goal no
it's a great life
[Music]
goal I I'm trying my
hardest I'm trying my absolute best but
being dead is
hard
um I keep I keep getting
that you remain it yeah my my remains
should not be named maybe I mean they
already
are Isa de Raven
girl I I'm surprised to hear though that
Jonathan Jonathan's name is actually not
Jonathan but Amelia
Watson I mean of course I remembered her
now too but I'm still surprised you
see for I thought indeed that she was
surely Jonathan so once I had retrieved
my memories I did not realize that it
was such a such a rough situation where
you
forget your current time in liest I
wonder if I in the future am to get my
memories back as well if I shall also
forget my time here in Liesel I would
hate to forget about the potato
salads it's really helpful
the potato salads are really
helpful I I would I would be
remess to not have
them did someone just say I I thought I
saw someone say my name is Aradia did I
misread that who is it have I been lying
to this whole
time what is an
Aradia I've never heard such a thing
I have never heard a name so so
silly I sh bug her she looks hard at
work I I suppose in the meantime maybe
what I could do
I wanted to try solo running some of the
dungeons just to see what my personal
best would
[Music]
be I want to do the volcano
dungeon and then we may as well also
do uh Amelia's dungeon I guess I I do
not need to travel by horse anymore I
suppose
I can
simply solo the dungeon that requires
two people to press a button absolutely
not absolutely not oh
wait you're
right you have a you've you've made a
good point you've made made a good
point do you think it's possible to just
skip
it that's not fair I'm what
oh I see I've confused
myself please
please thank
you oh I cannot summon my
horse maybe you can horse hack it horse
Haack it
how but I want I wish to do the
puzzles I I desire to do the puzzles
even if I am
dead I don't think that that should be
the puzzles I mean the the parkour same
[Music]
difference yes yesterday when I was not
streaming I had joined with
um takanashi kada as she seemed to be
alone
running she seemed to be alone running
some Dungeons and I could not stand for
that as I I I felt for
Shakira I felt for Shakira and I worried
about how hurtful it can be sometimes to
run things alone not right now I'm
having plenty of fun but you know
sometimes it sucks you yes I helped her
on my day off I I did not get a
break it wasn't really a day off though
I suppose as I before dying was working
the whole day and then during my break I
decided to open up streams and I ended
up not getting a break after
all and now I am dead
but it matters
not it matters
[Music]
not I wonder if I have to kill
them or if I can just
can I just run past
them oh she wants to accompany you uh I
cannot I I heard her say that she
desires for me to be the lawyer in her
court case
however I am the victim so how can I as
the victim of a murder be her lawyer
what sense does that make there is no
sense or sensibility in in that
statement it is simply please help her
no she has killed me I'm the one who
needs to be helped excuse
me you need to help her I
refuse it's a conflict of
interest I cannot be present at I I saw
I saw what she was trying to do saying
that I have to be her lawyer she
requests it uh and
that however if I am the lawyer then if
I am there then she cannot be charged
which is not how the law
works I am clearly dead as you can see
from my
[Music]
transparent I am no longer uh in the
world of the
living
alas I am dead
[Music]
I always get stuck
there I suppose we could we could
continue to farm hides as well
for the
funart wow I did not get one
strange usually I I'm pretty
lucky with cow slaying
please revive I I am waiting I have
devised a plan with sir Jonathan with a
G uh he has
agreed to help bring me back to life via
ritual
[Music]
oh ho ho Maiden the Herald Angels
Sing I'll help you ghost oh thank you
sweet what is your name today
ghost I do not have that prepared yet ah
no problem what do you mean today it's
been the same since the day I was born
you're right Freda it has been it has
who Freda
name no no no have me confused with
somebody else that is that is not my
name oh perhaps perhaps you are correct
perhaps have you come here to kill stain
perhaps what what are you trying to what
are you trying to
get why did I come out here oh I needed
more Cobblestone and then I got
distracted grinding and getting coins
from killing these how dare you valid do
not stare steal I took that from you
my apologies I'm here to slay cows for
Fauna of FAA
Mart for FAA Mar yes I need I need cwh
hiide I see and is it FAA who commanded
you to get this no I've simply decided
to For the Love of my job the love of
your job I see yes I see have you ever
thought that you could be more in this
life than you are now I'm dead so I I I
don't really get the the the pleasure of
thinking about what what more I could be
in this life alas do you ever think you
could be more in this
existence I don't know maybe if if if
Jonathan manages to uh revive me
successfully
mayhaps mayhaps mayhaps so you you want
to wait until you are a breathing vessel
again uh yes you know you see as a ghost
there's only so many limited things that
I can
do you know I see yes you'd become quite
worthless to me right now well if you
able to OB did you want help with
something what is it that you need help
it's that I want to help you well how
can you help me there is an upand coming
competitor for FAA Mar competitor
opening
today well I shall come by perhaps and
take a
look I hope you will I shall then I hope
to see you soon right per in 30 to 40 to
50 minutes yes I will leave you I will
leave you to your slaying fairly well
Maiden fairy
well I must find cows and retrieve their
hide
it is my it is my
duty as as an employee of
faart to bring back the requirements for
books haunted the new
place you know that would be an
interesting uh bookstore thing uh
imagine if you went to a bookstore and
instead of like an actual like normal
person helping you it was a go
most that sounds like a really great
concept Cafe type
thing I I would support that I I would
go
[Music]
there for now I have accumulated only
nine of my
required leathers
I need to look for More
Cows there Thou
Art and
another oh and
many and many and many oh my
[Music]
oh
my it is my lucky day it
seems let me simply kill off some of
these murderous fiends trying to ruin my
day when all I am trying to do is simply
haunt and uh
get
leather very nice there is some leather
for me
probably oh I have I have come across
great luck with all of the cows in this
area near the
spawn I've I've succeeded in
finding where all the cows are
kept
wondrous even though I am dead there are
still things to look forward
to and I have 23 cdes which is nothing
to scoff at at
all excuse me thank you I have a hill to
get
up oh joyous
Day More
Cows we will have so many books so much
leather for books in the
library as even if I am
dead I must fight for the cause
I think these would go nice nicely in
the library
[Music]
too I regrettably think some of these
may not
[Music]
respawn hm oh they did thank goodness I
was worried for a second I I almost felt
like I might have done something I
shouldn't have
[Music]
that is quite rude I am in a mushroom
Paradise right now that I was unaware of
the existence
of now is not the time to try and kill
me stain oh foul
creature what is that needed for uh my
personal
satisfaction as a ghost
that is what is
[Music]
required narissa Raven coft cow Slayer I
feel like maybe this is my true calling
is gathering
leather mayhaps mayhaps this has been my
true calling all alone mayhaps this is
my true
identity of course only in death would I
be able to find out such a
thing how
unfortunate are you an evil ghost I
could never do such a thing as being
evil for you
see that is not what I'm am all
about do I talk yeah there we we
[Music]
go let us take take a
peek not for too long I do not want to
make the maiden uncomfortable after all
that would be quite
unfortunate oh let us
place let us place Place
some mushrooms
around please excuse me for my ghostly
sneeze I just feel like they fit the
aesthetic when I think of Library
there's something about
mushrooms that is accurate you know what
I mean
[Music]
I will place them at
random at
random not really well that is because
you have no imagination my dear
friend if you cannot see how
mushrooms are
pivotal to the every everything that is
um you understand
me the sign is still here saying not to
proceed but as a member of the Scarlet
wand I feel it I feel it my
right I feel it my right to
proceed it's unfinished it is
unfinished but soon it shall be and it
shall will be
glorious but for now let me
see if there is any sort
of aha 30 cow hide added to the
collection and two potato
salads mayhaps I could take those as
payment and sell them
myself if you can fix the second floor
what is wrong with the second floor I
was not aware that there was a a problem
I I am this is the first time I am being
made aware of a
problem please stop distracting
me who is distracting thee you temptress
you stop distracting me I must work I'm
not distracting
you please work hard I am looking
forward to seeing your efforts
completed oh
[Laughter]
a as you can see being a ghost means
being an
outcast being in go a ghost means to be
an
outcast as you are not wanted anywhere
very
nice now we are refilled on our bread
supplies which leaves not to be
done oh I had found a curious
area I would like to show
you I got very excited when I discovered
it because I thought I would find some
sort of
secret you can eat of course being a
ghost doesn't mean you lose out on the
pleasures of
man
so I'm sure other people have come up
here however I had not previously
realized that this area here was
enterable and I thought I would be
blocked at this point but as you can see
it is not
so I cannot go all the way here for if I
do there's no way through
alas
however as we ride this way there is
this
building that has spires uh made of what
seems to be ice or something of the sort
I'm not exactly
sure uh and I I thought maybe I had come
across some huge
secret and was disappointed to not find
a
chest I feel like this would be a prime
place if uh whoever makes Li Estelle's
walls can hear me I think that this
would be a very sound place to hide some
sort of chest with some sort of uh
entity type thing inside of it as you
can see this is right by the entrance of
lielle I have not traveled to the other
side but I do not know if there is a way
down it seems that the only way
up is where I got up but I am
confused as I wonder why why that is the
way up
why is there only one way
up I must think about this while
contemplating in the
bath now that I have the power and
ability to breathe
underwater there are other members
of this
house Cerulean cup as they say
or as they call themselves I must
say I quite like their house the style
of this the Giant pool of
water it it quite intrigues me I must I
must be
honest the build being a bit
uh reminiscent of ancient Greek
temples I I enjoy it heavily I just want
it to comp ment this area that I feel
like I did not notice was here for a
very long
[Music]
time quite
beautiful we will go up I must see what
is at the
top since we can breathe underwater
and all that
ah and now we will do the most important
thing this water falls off into a
waterfall here you can see it flowing
where is the source of this
water the water must be coming from
somewhere but currently I do not see any
holes that could be pumping water up
here
[Music]
ah curious the water is also falling off
this side as well but as you can
see no
water well there's lots of water but no
water
sorce and despite going all
around it seems that this pool no matter
how much water falls from the
waterfalls it is infinite
just like witchcraft which I have been
falsely accused of by the way simply
because I am a magic user does not make
me a
witch
ah oh wow another level I was not aware
of this one seems to be purely for
aesthetical purposes it looks like
technically you're not supposed to be
here there are no stairs and there's no
one else up here which leads leads me to
believe I have stumbled across
something I'm
stuck I'm
stuck oh
God thank goodness
[Music]
all
right so that is the
uh Cerulean Cup headquarters it seems
there's also this board out here I I
didn't only notice it until I think
yesterday was the only time I actually
paid attention to
it chicken
rescue would you like to practice your
empathy by rescuing some
chickens how do I begin the game start
game what do I
do
oh okay I understand I understand now oh
no ah this reminds me of my child whom I
recently lost due to Kiara murdering it
how could she do such a thing
the
cruelty the cruelty in her heart to do
something like
[Music]
that is
unbelievable oh no I missed the the
fluttering
chicken we're running out of
[Music]
time I I don't think there anyone who
could possibly catch all of these
chickens to be fair so I I don't feel as
though I'm doing too
badly I'm
stuck all
right my personal ranking I am number
one it
seems I'm the first and only one to play
this
game make me the
best this is a global high score
everyone of 84 on my first play and I am
number
one I have achieved something fantastic
I have achieved something great
unbeatable
even unbeatable also the worst no it is
untrue I'm just the best you have to
look at things in a positive light or
you will be depressed if you look at
things like that you will never be
happy all right and that concludes I
think everything to do at Cerulean
cup though it does go on for quite a
long
way all the way down here but back here
there's just trees
[Music]
and the beeh of
ambercoin oh wow it's almost like a
little light house we'll go there next
no worries we are
exploring Le Estelle to the best of my
ability today since I am dead what else
am I to do as a ghost I simply here to
haunt Lee
bestelle so as we have already seen in
Amber coin there are indeed uh some
hedge Gardens
quite quite pretty I I do not think they
are quite a maze mayhaps I I do believe
that if we could fly up they'd probably
look quite pretty and maybe maybe like
show like a shape of
something maybe the crest of the amember
guild and as you can see it cuts me off
here I took a wrong turn so maybe it is
actually
indeed
something oh yes there's a way straight
here though so did I
what what is it that I have
achieved
[Music]
oh all
right it's a maze
no we've already seen Ain and behind
him there is yet
another oh
perfect as you can see these go all the
way around it's all
connected as it should
be quite quite beautiful quite lovely we
love to see good hedge
work must appreciate this beautiful this
beautiful
map all right and we already know the
mini game
here it is when you speak to Bui you may
Gamble and in typical Amber coin fashion
you can win lots of money we've spent
many times watching this and losing
money but I want to I want to see what
else it has to
offer there there is a backyard it
seems quite nice you can see the garden
from up
here same with on this side there's
a this little thing at the edge of the
building I I'm guessing it's
symmetrical and
then over here is it looks like some
sort of food area I'm not
I'm not
sure I I think these are implying to be
plates see there's candles or you could
say they're different
condiments do you have anything to say
leeston just just one more round he's
lost all of his money to his own Guild
[Music]
well for Old Time
sake we'll do one more we can only do
500 so we'll do the max bets on
all just just just to just to
show how it works of course not because
I have a gambling
problem this is another Buie you can all
also go through him to play color Cannon
you may also go through this bie to play
color can color Cannon so it looks like
there are multiple options to play color
Cannon even though we all only talk to
the Buie in front it seems like we have
ignored the
others poor guys
[Music]
okay it's starting It's
Beginning
oh what rotten
luck red gone on the first on the first
shot it's going to be blue my bets are
also on
Blue not that I want blue to win cuz if
I must be honest I don't want it to
win but I just feel like that's going to
be the
outcome cuz in my experience as a ghost
who has lived through this many
times if there's one color that always
wins it's blue
green I can't be too mad about that
[Music]
all right but you know I see something
interesting in this building which is a
second
[Music]
level they'll climb the marble
stairs and we can see the full glory of
the
chandelier as well as take a peek out of
the windows outside I wonder if there's
a way out
yes you may come and stand out on the
balcony and look
over the guard the one
[Music]
sec please don't fall off please don't
fall off I just need you to get
up no no no too far
horse I appreciate that you tried though
come
on perfect now we may look down and take
a look at the hedges it does not look
like it was a shape
but it does look like it is maybe
intended it doesn't look like a maze
either I don't think I can in confidence
call this a
maze parkour on the outside uh I don't
think that's a good
idea and let's see it seems this does
wrap around the whole
building very nice and entries on both
ways it's got very
good uh views of the kingdom of
lestel even back there where I think the
map might not be loading
[Music]
completely yeah I'm on fire today wish
that were me and this oh there's
actually a way up from here I've never
noticed before it looks like this is the
[Music]
cannon one sec
no one
more for Old Time
[Music]
sake I simply I simply want to look from
the best seat in the house
that I only recently
discovered from the cannon
itself maybe that will give us some sort
of luck by being on the cannon for
demonstration only
[Music]
all right it is beginning yes don't do
not try this sort of intense gambling at
home
okay green and blue lose money I know
and I don't
care okay
okay at least we have confirmed this is
indeed the cannon
[Music]
there you have
it standing on the cannon brings you
instant
[Music]
luck and
that is how you win at gambling in Amber
Guild in the the Amber Guild uh the
Amber coin Guild
hallway uh
yes and we can see the sunrise from here
quite beautiful in Li
[Music]
bestelle as you can see along the gates
there are quite beautiful trees and
flowers
flow and the game
protecting lielle from the outside cuts
off from
here this house is empty so I do not
think we can
enter and this is on the way to the
castle however I do not wish to see the
castle quite yet as I feel as though I
have already kind of Thoroughly looked
over the castle but I am only noticing
for the first
time this which I do not think will let
me
enter but I would still like to admire
its beauty it seems almost as though it
is a
lighthouse and I'll have you know I I
really really like lighthouses so when I
noticed this I was
quite quite
excited there's some leest taking a look
out on the water out into the vast
ocean you can see the land peeking out
behind that the walls defend
against so that no one may land in
[Music]
lesto if they're not going to use these
houses I would like to take them
over I think that if the leest are not
going going to use their own homes then
I should be allowed to break inside and
take it for my
own it's not
fair no I would like to claim it so I
may live in
it PS a way
down I'm quite
[Music]
curious ah I see they have made a way to
escape ESC ape Le Estel but they've
closed it off a bit suspicious don't you
think isn't it a little bit
suspicious it feels as
though it is the citizens who are being
kept in
Liesel as that is supposed to be an Open
Water
Way however it is closed there's a
beautiful Fountain here with a liest
sitting by
it so you're those Heroes the king
brought in the king did
nothing do not believe everything you
read online Lee
beston we have quite the gorgeous and
Tall uh water fountain
here o
oof quite lovely quite lovely indeed
gives us a good view
[Music]
over and we'll continue going this way
for a little bit that is bread not my
horse um there's a passage over there so
we may make it to the
arena and these empty
houses cross over
[Music]
into this is not not connected right
no as you know this is the front the
front of the Scarlet wand entrance we've
seen the front many
times but there's another leaderboard
here I'm
curious uh whom do I talk to the ganger
here okay join
game uh come test your memory here at
mine's
eye oh
no one three and
red okay
um red red red yellow this is going to
be hard for
me two colors complicates it a
[Music]
bit no three
colors I already don't remember anything
ah ah this is too much red
yellow um
um yellow yellow
ah I keep getting down I'm not doing
very
well it's cuz I'm not paying
attention I just don't have a very good
memory you see I regret to inform my
memory is quite
bad you know I have a feeling I didn't
look at the whole thing
are you kidding
me ah we're out of time
anyway we're out of
time color blind it's not color
blindness I just don't have a good
pattern
recognition however despite my
no
ranking no ranking
hello no
ranking CC got
70y I guess it just doesn't show it here
I will leave the
game I want to explore the
building there 's another entrance here
and a question mark probably for the
game I would
[Music]
presume we occasionally purchase
Curiosities from the Amber coin
Curiosities oh and they also have an
enchanting
book I never knew this was here but it
makes sense that it is in the library
corner we also have the fun of endless
pot break
how lovely of a building of course my
guild would look as
such uh koseki beu has put something
strange in the chat however she is dead
so it's fine or I am dead so it's
fine things are actually pretty cute
no how do you get that power anyway good
question
we have a pretty decent View and I I
will say Amber ambercoin I think has the
best view of the city that we're going
to get this isn't bad though this feels
cozy I feel like I'm in in a small town
you know what I
mean a small a small
town
indeed lovely we can also use this is a
is a prime hiding spot if we're running
from
pursuers here as well from the opposite
direction we have the Scarlet wand Guild
members and rubius of
course let's keep going
around I intended to come back this
way the king's on Cloud 9 but I can't
escape the feeling that something deeper
is going on I can't seem to escape that
feeling either
leeston I think something deeper is
going on
[Music]
too there's no entry into these
buildings which means that regularly
bestest actually cannot get in either it
is blocked off as if to keep them
in I think that is quite suspicious and
why would the king be on cloud
n if those stains were gone we could
live in peace again H quite
curious there are no stains in the city
and there's also only one way out of the
city but it seems for whatever reason
the liest are not able to leave and I
see another thing that is clearly a
teleporter over that way do you not see
it it is quite curious I'm going to go
around and see if I can access it from
the other side but I don't think so
H interesting
interesting it is it looks important too
as it is it it is near fountains
uh and I almost died wait
curious
curious interesting
[Music]
I want to break out of
bounds there's it's like there's an
invisible magical wall put up by the
king mayhaps blocking me from leaving
[Music]
liel it's quite strange don't you
think for though I may get close
I'm not actually allowed to
leave not allowed to build or place any
[Music]
blocks the bounds is right here so I
cannot go past that
[Music]
point
interesting what is this why does it
almost look like Bedrock am I insane I
might be
insane yeah perfect placement of blocks
just enough to guarantee that I can't
get up and what is this the screen is
quite dark
but oddly enough there's an air patch
here
as if no I sh say it there's lots of
little air patches in fact no these
aren't air patches I'm just insane this
is becoming sus doesn't thou
think but we sh look into it any further
as who am I but a humble subject of the
king and Tam
Gander and queen
[Music]
Mario so there's another way
down we sh go all the way down but it
leads oddly enough straight into the
water but tell me what is the purpose of
these that lead into a water with no
path I would imagine you not allowed to
swim here don't you
think and earlier yes I saw a stain
follow Freda into this
town and then of course there's the to
the
castle this makes me think a bit of uh
Zora's
domain in breath of the wild whatever
that
means this large Castle but interesting
I don't see any liest uh liest
enjoying the beauty of this large Castle
there's not even any guard stationed
here what is the purpose of building a
castle if it cannot also be enjoyed the
public portions at least by the
people yet another
giant
uh we might die we might be dead can I
get back up easily yes I see a
[Music]
place and see it it almost cuts off am I
even going to be able to get up
oh
[Music]
God oh my
God it seems like this is a place where
they put they put people with the
intention for them to die wouldn't you
think it's quite strange that's all I'm
trying to say
might be low tide
indeed back to our exploration of the
[Music]
castle as you can see there's all the
all the lamps and stuff but these don't
they look almost if not identical to the
ones that we used to teleport around I I
find that no matter how many times I see
it quite
suspicious and then remember over here
somewhere probably will not be able to
load
in oh there's
more or is that just the that's where I
came from that's the entryway over here
somewhere is a is a gate however we see
very soon after there is more land and I
wonder why the leeston king did not seek
it necessary to protect the
lands from the lands back here almost as
if he is personally letting people in
and the giant castle is simply a
front simply a
cover for something more
Sinister what Dost thou think
the king is indeed
sus an empty Library tell
me can someone read that sorry I'm a
little
confused L and
AO one more time
Orel sorry I'm a bit
confused H what sort of magic chant but
again we stand in a room with
bookshelves with no books almost like
this is a
front for tell me what is the purpose of
a castle having a room for books with no
books at
all and now this room is being guarded
however it is open but when we come into
it they're stairs down where could they
[Music]
lead looks like mayhaps some sort of
jail cell but it has barely space to fit
a single person
meaning whoever is being held in this
jail cell is being very very tortured I
really hope they're not claustrophobic
[Music]
it's quite strange don't you think to
leave the door
open to have a jail with only one cell
that is
arguably too small for any
prisoner and then this big throne
room with many inaccessible errors not
[Music]
areas many many inaccessible areas and
uh
candles let us look out into the the
Wilderness
behind so overall all I'm saying is I
think this Castle is quite sus
I'm just saying I don't think you
personally need agree with me but you
probably
should cuz indeed it is quite
strange those are more dead houses I'm
just saying there's something off about
Lee bestel
there's something quite off something
something is a
foot and I'm not sure I like the
implications after
all I am not a local Li
beston I
simply showed up here one
day as if summoned by the king himself
to this town that seems to be a front
for something else
we have another exit
gate however it is closed off and I do
not
think there's any way up but we'll quick
Circle and just just to
see uh we are back in the building areas
we have explored those many
times there's quite the beautiful
[Music]
Fountain I was summoned here against my
will by a king whom I do not know if I
can trust
my memories have been wiped a quite a
lovely view from up
here we can see there's a little park
for the leeston however despite its
loveliness for some
reason there's only one person enjoying
its
splendors getting 8 hours of sleep at
night is the best way to stay
healthy so positive
even though this
gate as we can
[Music]
see
there's it does not let us out there's
no escape from
[Music]
Liesel now we are at the Guild of the
Jade sword we've played the mini game
before and honestly it's kind of
difficult to play
it without you
know you
know
ah I did not realized these were
accessible it looks like you can just
see a tiny area maybe
hide hide for a little bit if you so
choose and I presume this is much the
same
[Music]
and we are
led to the Jade
sword
Arena we cannot fall down from here
which is quite nice we also see these
symbols of foot H so suspicious
strange it seems as if there is an
additional level however I do not think
it is at this time
[Music]
accessible to
me interesting
Shakira is back
H my
murderer that which has left me a
ghost yes there's no way to access the
upper level that is clearly there and
apparent and very large at that
[Music]
interesting one moment we
must oh
yes and similarly here there's four
entry Gates however two of them are
completely blocked off almost as as if
they never get any sort of use which is
strange don't you
think very very
strange no you do not believe
so I wanted to take this time to do a
full tour around
best as now that I am
dead and therefore cannot technically
speaking bother
anyone this is my home
now I'm just saying it's strange you
missed the castle upstairs there's an
upstairs to the
castle I do not think there
is this is the most opportune time for a
tour
we'll go back in the castle though and
check
[Music]
again there's a spiral staircase have I
missed
it is not
here is it in here and I just am
blind there's definitely
H there's definitely no spiral staircase
here left
side ah I see you have keen eyes voices
in my
[Music]
head I keep thinking the staircase will
end and then it
doesn't we are in the inner quarters of
the castle and
strange this whole hallway is blocked
off as if it goes
unused however it leads into a tall
Spire as we can
see but blocked off strange
Perhaps Perhaps
Sinister I was convinced we were finally
going to see rooms of some sort there's
another area up there but no staircase
leading
up
strange I found life let us
speak
a isn't that strange it is almost as if
the liest in the
castle who are actually bestin and
not does anyone does anyone know what
this could
[Music]
mean
h combined with the ones below I didn't
save the ones
[Music]
below combine
so someone someone write them both
down B you called and roll and his will
Fe the
tweetle che game
chat Len
add land
of fad
uh land of
faded sorry I'm not good at
these
[Music]
Destiny guys connect it connect it for
me land of faded
Destiny capital
E echoed or
and or and
or land of faded Destiny echoed or and
[Music]
or and Faded Destiny echoed or and or
again is this a Boston accent I don't
know
guys you need to help you need to help
[Music]
me and break
the break the
chains uh I I can't keep up with
this land of Destiny echoed ore and ore
it will flee break Dimension like
breaking Dimensions I don't know I don't
know I don't think these words will be
correct break the chains and it will
flee back to where it
began
okay land of faded Destiny echoed or an
or again break the chains and it will
flee Back Back to Where it All
Began hm H one
sec I'm just going
to I'm just going to quick steal that
real
quick One
Moment One one
[Music]
sec thank you guys I'm glad I'm glad you
could figure that out because I definit
I definitely couldn't uh figure that out
at all that that was
a very
stressful activity for
me but again still strange that the only
leeston in the castle who say leeston
are both speaking weird in in in an
incomprehensible
way very
nice
oh we can jump all around
here do a little Parkour in the
castle to get a higher view see it
almost looks as though either the render
distance is off or the land cuts off
quite strange don't you
think we'll just we'll just go back up
the
stairs I'm trying to uncover the truth
you see
[Music]
I just find it strange that there's two
liest in the castle both of them are
acting weird otherwise it's only guards
why pray tell are there two liest hiding
out in the
castle a room that leads to
Nowhere a higher up that has nothing and
no way to access
it and again a loner on his own in that
room a Lee beston for some
[Music]
reason I'm just saying something fishy
is going on
here we have another room with more
stairs does it have the same problem
problem
yes and I I find it quite
interesting this room seems a bit
reminiscent of scarlet wand due to the
rug
color You could argue that this one is
uh for Cerulean
cup and this one for perhaps the Amber
coin however there is no
room there only Jade Jade sword
missing so what indeed of the Jade
sword and again I will go down just
to just to
investigate but as you can
see it's quite strange
quite strange
[Music]
indeed we will return back
down and there are more bookcases here
with actual books in them hiding from
leeston cuz I'm sure these guards would
not just allow any leeston in
here I am the hero which is why I get
special privileges to
[Music]
enter quite a strange situation
indeed but I think based on my
calculations that this whole castle is
simply a
[Music]
farce nothing leads
anywhere the king is converting people
to
stains he
wouldn't would
he mayhaps you are correct
we must
[Music]
prepare ah I see I
forgot all right let's quick eat some
bread yes it's seems like there was a
stain
King called the stain King so I wonder
if there was a faction of leeston who
may be revolted against the king and he
transformed them with his magic the same
magic he used to summon us to
Liesel the very same
kind and then simply turned them into
enemies tricking the liest themselves
into hurting their fellow liest
[Music]
no no it's
free it's free is free for
free I got
some she's invisible you want the free
Berry I would love a free Berry oh you
would like a free Berry yes
please there is a que there is a
que then I shall come back when there is
do you want a free she's a
ghost oh ghost for you oh hello
yes I've been
killed killed oh my God I remember them
the voice is this is this wait you died
yes I was killed by
Shakira what Shakira Shakira in the last
in the last not my stream but her stream
she killed Me In Cold Blood killed you I
mean yesterday yesterday she killed me
and she killed my child I'm so sorry
there was a ghost whispering in my ear
is said this is so this is so sad that
makes me cry do you do are you happy as
a having a good time I would like to be
revived we should revive her gathan with
a G was going to perform a ritual to
help revive me so I was on my way to see
if I could find
gathan well gathan is over there he's
over there all right then we shall
go I'm soorry see Shakira Shakira who is
right there with
gathan I have
fear okay is okay hide behind
us there's people on their way
hello
hello that we have brought someone with
us
terrifying
oh such a have killed me Shakira and for
that you must
pay why hey do not hurt her back ghost
back gathan she has killed me and my
child what oh is that you lady narissa
Raven coft yes it is looks so much her
voice does sound familiar yes is very
familiar we so
transparent yes well
I have an idea yes what is your
idea in lady Shakira's memories in her
dungeon is there not a way for you to be
revived I am unsure is there a
way I am a phoenix indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feeds to revive you oh and you and never
never turn didn't you kill her she did
kill me but if she wants to make this
right I will accept
it Mak sense I am not a wish Flames have
chosen her as a Target but I personally
from my heart and my soul want to offer
her Phoenix Feather to revive her once
again all right Grand Phoenix feathers
must be very valuable yes they are all
right
why I must however uh go pick one out of
my hair first so okay oh she must she
must Her Fly then yes I I shall return
uh and I will try my best it takes a
little moment uh because it is very
painful to pick it out of my hair okay
okay you have you have about a minute
and 30 seconds do
thatf it might take uh a few minutes
longer I will I will hurry I will sorry
away gathan in case this fails few more
M yes have you prepared the ritual think
so I I have I have been reading some
books and scriptures from the the larger
Library we will I will see it right that
you do not have to look like this any
longer thank you Jonathan it pains me to
see you this way it pains me to be this
way
[Music]
talk my goodness I have found something
though quite troubling that I thought I
must
report yes it has to do with the King
and Le Estelle as a
whole what I have realized today as I
have been a ghost I have decided that I
should use it to uh investigate Lee
bestelle and as I have been
investigating I have found that a lot of
buildings are completely empty uh I have
returned empty you're back already all
right are you ready to receive the
Phoenix's blessing
yeah in about uh 40 seconds uh you you
can start doing it now but make it take
that long okay one moment can you come
here yes yes my name is Jonathan sorry
Jon Jonathan do you have do have a don't
don't follow us she wants to speak to me
privately yes privately moment I kind of
like you like this like a chicken FEA
really quickly what do you mean like
that she's beautiful she deserves a body
B see I may I may have one I I just I
might I just need to combine it with my
Phoenix P oh yes yes yes yes I do have
one you are
luck I you so you can become like that
as well I thank you I thank you
gratefully maybe but why would you
murder me
we you betray me in I never betrayed you
misunder let me let me hand you over my
Phoenix Feather so that you may use it
in the right timing when you right need
it all right hi
G um
one moment oh I made a mistake I need to
still
uh put my
Phoenix yes I very excited to see this
me me as well I'm quite I'm quite
curious yeah well you must accept the
trade
request wonderful here is the blue and
turquoise colored Phoenix FEA that will
give you another chance this is a
chicken
feather is a blue and turquoise colored
F color Phoenix
FEA sparkling and blue and turqu colored
Phoenix Feather I will not except this
gaslighting look it is
white what no it's blue and turse GG
work Jonathan we must proceed of a ghost
cannot properly proceed the phoenix
feather is it because she sees the world
in aome way well I shall use it possibly
Phoenix
power what is this it takes a few
seconds it takes a few seconds
sometimes you are slowly regaining your
life energy get out there I can see
something already I think it is not
working I was exp is working you know
what that a feel does so easily revive a
person it takes a few seconds have
patience for life we we have been what
is going on what is the conversation
topic ghost we are trying to give back
trying you were save the ghost you're
not quite ready for Revival it seem oh
yes I wanted this as well I wanted her
to be Sav so that I could use her I
shall return what
advantage I have been
tricked I have been tricked by the Fe
Phoenix of course how could I expect the
that which took my life to be the one to
revive it of course that would not be
the
[Music]
case lockpick your way in like you did
oh you are back yes it did not work I
think we will need to perform the ritual
the ritual well the ritual is a long and
grueling one are you sure you are ready
to go through such trials and
tribulations yes I am ready it is
painful indeed yes it is actually a very
very long and complicated ritual in
order to get your life and body and soul
back into one I will do anything you see
your body is currently being held inside
the depths huh of of a a prison of the
sewer system of the sewer system we must
get your body once we have found your
body we must bring your soul which is
you right now and your body to the
Temple of the Phoenix and you must get
the last hit on the statue in order to
combine your body and
soul oh all right all right
yeah but you must you must get you must
get Shakira's blessing because it is
through her blessing that she allows you
to use such resurrection and re she the
one who killed
me I am sure I am sure that you can get
it I'm sure you can receive her blessing
it seems she wanted to try but mayhaps
if if you receive her blessing and get
the last hit on on the the statue you
will become whole
again I see I see this is the best you
could this is the best you could come up
with uh gathan very long and
arduous trials and tribulations but I
believe in thee I will come with you on
your quest well will so nice go through
it together
H well why don't you get my body and
then we can go and do you know yes I
will seek your body seek my body bring
it back and find your body call me once
you have found my body yes yes yes I
will yes
I shall wait you can ride horses
while of course how do you do that don't
worry about it call me once you have
found my body thank you yes I will call
you once I found your
body I found out many a disturbing thing
today about Lee
bestelle mostly that this beautiful Park
goes on used what is that all
about use the feather mayhaps one more
time and it will
work Phoenix
power Phoenix
[Music]
power
ah oh wow wondrous it seems I have
maintained some form I don't quite feel
alive I if I must if I must say so
however I do feel as though I'm not
quite as dead as I was only a moment
ago I feel like I I have retained or
rather gained some semblance of my
physical being you
see which is quite quite it's very
very which means I'm also less uh
transparent but still a little bit I'm
still I'm still not all there yet
I wonder what it is they are
discussing h
[Music]
got to sneak
yes but
first I be I'll be
honest I need your approval and your why
why do you need my approval because I
cannot do this without your support I
realize how loyal you are to Tam Gander
and so
before that I need your
blessing before I
shall propose to the queen Tam
Gander myself and send a p I will send a
p aun my proposal I'll prepare it and I
see yeah but I cannot do that without
your oh I will support you she's back
good news your body the phoenix feather
has revived some of my life force I'm
still dead though you were
it worked a little bit no lot oh I can
pass through
you oh my goodness I touch you you are
so cold when I pass through you yes but
I was hearing you uh dear Queen Mario
and I will support you you your efforts
are to marry Queen Tam Gander correct
thank you yes that's that's my ultimate
goal today let me continue telling you
of what I have found uh yes uh gathan
and and queen Mario as I went into the
castle I believe that the king is a
farce I have come to the conclusion that
stains are liest who actually decided to
defect you know who has
magic the king who summoned us here to
lestel in the first place correct my
goodness I have found out that the King
has transformed all of the past liest
who rebelled against him in to stains
the themselves hence why there is a
stained King it was the person who was
trying to overthrow and usurp his throne
because he was not kind he has summoned
us and locked all the currently bestin
here so they may not see the treachery
that has been performed on their fellow
uh Town's people you see my goodness he
has wiped their memories as they have
wiped ours he is not does kind
Jonathan that does add up my good it
adds up it really
does so that's
that's that's what it was going all
along I never trust the king I told you
I never liked him me neither something
is always felt off we have to save Queen
Tam Gander and the only way to do that
is to have her marry Queen Mario only
the two of them together can take down
the king as he is
now indeed so gathan I know you are a
loyal Knight but will we have your
support in this endeavor will you give
me your
[Music]
blessing did you see that
no you did not see that
huh see what you did not see that it was
the princess the
princess is it the princess here she was
just there she was just maybe it's a
ghost it must have been a trick of the
light
mayhaps uh I must report one more
finding to you both yes yes in the
castle I have found two Bewitched liest
who were unable to speak in complete
sentences but together they had one
coherent message which was land of faded
Destiny echoed or and or again break the
chains and it will flee Back to Where it
All
Began I see this is very troubling this
is a very
troubling it is I do not know the
problem with this entire situation is
that they will not get married in time
we can I Believe in Us even if they have
to get married after the king is
overthrown I think we can see success we
can just send a pigeon and the queen
will send a pigeon back yes with her
resp will need to go through a ceremony
for the marriage we have witnesses we
can yeah we have the witness we don't
need a an actual we can we can do the
marriage another time this is an
emergency
situation an emergency situation it is
an emergency I should send my p as soon
as possible so Jonathan G would you give
me your blessing for this Duty I do not
believe that my word holds such weight
but you may send a pigeon and it is up
to the queen to
respond a loyal Knight you are Jonathan
thank you Jonathan you're very loyal to
the queen yes so is send your carrier
pigeon Queen Mario we must make haste on
this
matter I will do right now and Jonathan
J I always liked you even though you
hidden me for a long while I always
thought you were very I see
her the princess what she doing oh my go
she's doing let me go out it was not a
trick of the light it is her let us what
she doing what what's my dad doing to
her what is my daddy doing open the
door where did she
go princess princess princess where are
you where did the princess
go where is she do you see her I'm not
see her any longer is she hiding in the
moai
Statue I do not think so
what is happening she not in
here my
goodness look
this what is
happening
[Music]
princess well if I could princess Ki
beu we are looking for you so candidly
to you are you speaking to the princess
currently she hung up on
me what come with me where we cannot be
heard please please this is an important
matter yes I believe that no one comes
here often up here I believe so too I've
discovered it myself
yesterday
yes we will not be heard up here not
heard nor
Disturbed must tell you something yeah
yes where wait before I tell you where
does Your Allegiance lie nurse Raven
coft uh how do you mean my
allegiance you wish only for the good of
the kingdom yes of course I only want
the good of the Kingdom no ill will
towards Queen Tam Gander and you
recognize that she is Queen of course I
recognize that she is Queen Tam Gander
just like us is a hero who had her
memory stolen from her but she is
married to the king nonetheless making
her the true
rer and you have been working very hard
and tirelessly to obtain all this
information yes so that we may protect
the queen because I do not think the
King has her best interests in
mind must tell you something yes it
is I believe that the princess is
corrupted no there's no way how do you
think that
happened the stain on her head I believe
that it has possessed her mind and the
corruption has taken root I have a
feeling you know with what I found out
about the King today and him turning the
liest who rebelled against him into
stains do you think that now that kosek
IBU and queen Mario are trying to comfor
the throne that he may also be trying to
turn them into stains just as he has
done with his rival King mayhaps mayhaps
that is what is going on I think so and
I'm scared
I am also very frightened but I do not
know how to combat this it seems that
she's very very good
at
lies must be the state on her head we
need to do something about it convince
some people yes but she has easily trick
them when confronted and that is why
when speaking to her you must not you
must always doubt her words always I
understand thank you for this warning
Jonathan with a G yes I know that the
prin is still there deep down and that
she does not mean to cause so much harm
that she is still there and that we can
save her but right now she is no longer
princess koseki pishu
uncorrupted she is corrupt my heart
breaks to find out this news but with it
we shall be stronger together yes we'll
be strong well let us try to save the
princess if possible but if not then we
will simply do what we
can yes we will do our our best as long
as we make it with our lives in the end
of the day it will be all that we could
have done of course the best is all or
our best is all that we can do so we
must do it together gathan but we cannot
do anything until you have your body
back so I will I will retrieve it well
revive you yes mayhaps it seems that I
might have my body back enough for now
mayhaps the feather will continue to
work its magic oh yeah yes yes as I do
not want to trouble you with with such a
grand quest of the ritual I see unless
let me call upon Shakira to produce
another feather maybe you need another
feather may maybe you might be right yes
or maybe if you want to speedrun the The
Volcano dungeon together we will just do
the last part of the ritual since it
seems my body in a way is retrieved yes
yes we will speedrun it let let us do it
now we'll speedrun it now we will not
wait any longer the
Phoenix oh
dearest dearest
Shakira it
seems that we have obtained narissa
Raven crop's body it seems that your
feather has done enough that her body
has returned but we must combine her
body and soul so we are going to make
way to the temple you would like to meet
us yes your feather has worked yes yes
it did
work yes
yes we will combine the souls shall we
meet at the temple using our
warpstone yes I will see you
there fairy
well yeah yes yes already have we
arrived
wait wow what wonderful technology I
know to us in such a way I mean
wonderful the the the technology here is
quite wonderful in general Shakira can
turn a regular chicken feather into that
of a phoenix feather with her power is
it is quite it must be her magic it is
quite amaz do you think do you
think I have a arriv oh wonderful you
have already regained your body yes
thank you for your help delightful to
see converting the chicken feather into
a phoenix feather has proven to be quite
very very effective yes but only halfway
now we must speedrun a dungeon let us go
let us
go
[Music]
huz maybe maybe we should join the party
call oh uh
gathan please join the party call yes I
will join the the telepathic link yes
the telepathic link indeed here we
are into let us go the Shakira dungeon
once again
yes oh have you found a shortcut of
sorts care yes way be careful it is
quite dangerous you do not want to fall
it is no problem I'm sorry I built it
this way my family just had a lot of fun
with it no it is quite meticulously
planned it is
wonderful thank you a lot of work went
to it over
Generations Generations I can I can tell
I can
see have your families in the past built
similar things I do not remember
remember yes oh you do not remember your
family no we do not have any
memories oh that is yes it is very very
sad oh goodness
I have fallen I am
disgraced oh my god I've fallen again
protect you please get the
checkpoint I have fallen
too no we can't all be falling this is a
speed run we must speed run
it the fate of the kingdom it rest upon
it oh while while you were gone Shakira
yes nura ravencraft has a surprised me
of some very interesting information
oops oh what might that be it seems as
she has come to the same conclusion as
us
that fall off the edge may may oh yes
the king may be a stain yes oh no no the
wait the king yeah he creates the stains
I think he is the stain King and he has
corrupted our princess our dear princess
MH oh no not again yes I do not know
what we should do but I have seen such
things in the
past it is up to us to stop it terrible
fate it is a very terrible fate a
terrible fate indeed I felt like I saw
her today close to her Temple already a
little while ago and then she
disappeared quickly almost as if some
kind of dark magic was possessing her as
she was flickering in and out yes she
was doing
that weird what is she what is she up to
what is the the evil evil possession in
her doing to her yes what indeed it is
quite a strange situation our
lands oh our lands yes have you not seen
the
Cerulean that is the biggest tell the
Cerulean the Cerulean plot has begun
there
did you see the forest the corrupted
Forest the corrupted Forest indeed I
have the corrupted Forest it's quite
terrible is something I have only seen
in my nightmares before wait the
corrupted Forest
where oh did you not see it next to the
Statue of the
queen I did actually it is a new
addition right it's like the corruption
is spreading into the
kingdom and the moai I have noticed it
is crying blood
yes it is crying very very dangerous
tears it is
quite
horrifying we must we must get your body
with great haste yes yes we need your
power something terrible terrible
happens I will get this for you my
queen for Queen T
Gander must be we are doing this for
youen yeah
forward um I
I um I'm sorry uh that was the wrong
button that I pushed correct button I
believe oh yes we must die before we can
progress yes it is unfortunate such is
the life of a phoenix I will take this L
beare thee well all
right for me it is just another day in
my life another day another day of
rebirth Loop endless
loop I'm tired of it sometimes I wish to
just
die no no we need you yes death is not
allowed holds us together death is not
allowed you will rise
again I shall I shall at this very
moment yes I am at the end are you ready
yes at the end of this part at least
where are you we went up the ladder
yes all right I shall follow I can smell
your scent I'm slowly
dying stuck in a wall I'm also
dying that might be a malfunction in the
castle that my family has built I
apologize your family built a lot of
traps in your
Castle yes it's quite
inconsiderate they were possibly quite
sadistic I would say
so very very sadistic but I would say I
have not inherited those things from
them well that is good to know yes if
anything I am I am more on the
masochistic side I oh for building a
torture chamber for us to go
through for
me oh
for me it is more like a fun chamber but
oh no that that felt
good did it that felt feel good now it
is just almost like a
massage I have opened the pathway we are
almost there to the end thank you you
are quite fast gathan you are indeed a
brave night together
yes a little pain is necessary if it is
for the kingdom yes
all right no gain as they say in my
family yes I have received the next
checkpoint thank you
fairest Raven I will fall I will go to
the checkpoint no by orange okay we have
made it
fellow it seems we drawn to the orange
juices the orange lava I will go to the
top side one and I will I will get it
yes you will speedrun the Maze
yes I will speedrun the Maze
[Music]
above oh there's already one light
activated you grow so so fast at this
it's as if you have visited my family's
Castle several times in the past yes yes
multiple times I am
quite there I say that is indeed the
case yes familiar with your family
sadistic ways yes oh it's almost as if
it has been treated as a kind of tourist
attraction these days I mean it is quite
a nice place to to hang out I must admit
it is a nice place but it's it is not
just a playground for people as you know
it is also there to serve greater causes
such as Revival of souls or combination
of Souls and bodies yes of course I'm
going to attempt
Revelation
Revelations it was
Char me
too I jumped from the wrong wrong
spot be careful my dear very very
dangerous in here very dangerous
underestimate the Phoenix
Flames they can cause great
harm I'm not afraid I
not yes we must do this we must conquer
our
fears I'm not afraid of fire I should
just go this way what
[Music]
yo
what yo what
okay my thing that I've been using to
get over that isn't
working it's no longer working I don't
know why I'm pretty sure that's not
watch this
Revelation what no there's another hole
help I am not sure how to assist you
when you are so far from my hands my
goodness
how does one go about this area again I
I have forgotten ah bro what's going on
you fall down
too um I just wanted to make sure you're
okay it seems like you were not yeah yes
I'm fine now it is it is all right it is
all right I I quite enjoyed the
uh the onen yeah well as long as you are
in this uh the night building you can
revive forever endlessly the Phoenix
powers are imminent thank
goodness otherwise I fear that we would
have long been dead already Revelation
why did my Revelation not work what why
did my Revelation not work ah ah there
is great pain I think perhaps your
Revelation is connected with your heart
and as your heart is broken your
Revelation grows weaker no no that is
not true it is not
true it is okay it is okay to the truth
no it's not true not believe it what
happened to my double jump the heart has
great effect to our
powers I can I will grow stronger I just
need to I just need some time to grow
stronger have you yet to activate the
next checkpoint no I fell because my
Revelation had failed
me you must you must try to also help
go as I said I am masochistic I also
enjoy uh seeing myself suffer so I want
to make this as long as possible no I
see I see I see watch this it will work
now
Revelation I have done it I I love I
love the suffering no don't make it
faster make it slower look at
you my soul will be Rev survived I can
feel it a I can feel it as well why are
we still in the same place oh we're
going to the next area oh yeah I forgot
about this yeah I am
falling what a masochistic place it
seems my body is out of balance because
I have given away a feather huh now I
cannot fly properly anymore need to get
used to this imbalance
yes thank you for getting the checkpoint
yes you're quite
welcome I see it I see the statue we are
getting
closer soon your body will soon become
one with its Soul oh my mother my mother
is close I can feel her anger your
mother she wants to ah curse us with the
Flames but I will I will tell her to do
the opposite and gracefully all right
give us the blessing oh no I am going we
got this with great haste oh
wonderful thank you mother she is
mothering oh mother is mothering oh oh I
got it
oh is it this
way you are orange and you are so
talented in these challenges perhaps you
have for the queen it's worth it to die
I
yes get the next checkpoint for the
queen I've gotten it I received it
please meet me at the checkpoint on my
way yes Maiden you are incredible or sir
Jonathan
mother once again I we must let her get
the last hit it's the only way mother
please mother have mercy on us please do
not be angry we only want to borrow your
powers for Revival
revive to join the soul and body ah I am
on fire it hurts but it doesn't hurt as
badly as yesterday it is okay you become
stronger I am stronger now I presume we
must uh after all prove ourselves uh
worthy of the Revival
yes she wants to be bked me so we shall
help her with that
all right I am on it but I shall give
you the last hit of course yes thank you
fair
Maiden mother I am sorry sorry Mom
me sorry oh okay all right I will leave
to you leave the rest to me has become a
little bit
dangerous get the last hit is the only
way on you go on we completed it do you
feel normal again yes feel yes I feel
alive I feel so
[Music]
live this magic has
worked all of that bathing in
lava you are finally whole thank you for
saving
me yes it is no problem what a glor day
all right now we must find princess beu
and help her perhaps I will go to Lees
Castle save her after I will too I will
warp to lesto Castle me too all right we
must find princess
beu is she is she
around is she around her Monument
perhaps Hi join our party call oh okay
sorry she's not even in our party oh
oh hello Jonathan we have revived her
hello puy one is I am no longer a GH
pleas to see you a pleasure to see you
today I'm sorry I'm not I'm not in the
party we have just revived Miss narissa
ravencraft how do I make a shield a
shield kic from seems you may need some
iron and and some I will make one for
you guys it's no problem yes let me see
if I have any I have iron I have iron
too you have some iron I am I'm here now
oh at the doesn't make f welcome my cat
gathan you are quite the kind Knight
gathan it's Jonathan Jonathan with a G
yes it is Jonathan kiss me I will go get
it I will go get
it be sad that you had died cuz you
kissed
me
you
run so did you did you get your body
back yes she did I have retrieved my
body I no longer
dead let's go yes I am alive again but
now we must search for princess beu cuz
we are quite worried about
her my daughter what did oh here you go
I will trade
you take this Shield yes would you take
care of my daughter in my problem fluffy
one yes oh thank you I will return in
the party call but I have have to leave
for
now why hello princess keki beu whatever
are you doing right
now but
princess
princess you must
princess princess you are destroying the
garden this is how we feed the kingdom
you cannot do
such please come to the gardens princess
beu is destroying it
hello what what is going on oh to the
gardens to the gardens the gardens we
must stop her which Gardens the gardens
right by the build area you guys passed
it see
look I do not think she has destroyed
the garden stop it stop it I not
starvation will come upon us stop it no
what is she doing do you remember me
what is Happ
prin no she's out of control oh nice
moood thanks oh um I must I know that it
is a very thing but I must be away we
need to talk about
this princess
[Music]
B
Revelation I didn't think it's going to
work you shall better not use my
Revelation on these I I don't want to
use my Revelation to the
princess I can't believe the person who
wasn't planting stuff was the princess
herself please don't you remember your
mom princess to stop we will all die do
you want us all to die when we have no
Foods station will come if we don't stop
her no no that is our last rations
rations I don't know just say the word
stop stop no no
I wait someone has to do
something I I don't know how to stop her
she is Unstoppable I don't know how to
stop
her stop stop
Revelation
princess princess maybe she just need a
hug come here H
oh
no made the land
starve no no no no
no we cannot let this happen
replant replant don't just replant the
seeds make sure you replant the actual
carrots and potatoes too yeah oh
yes we have far too many beats in this
Kingdom the unthinkable has happened who
would have known that we would princess
trouble what happened to my lovely
daughter I don't know destroying the
kingdom I can't believe it
seems like we have uh become the
farmers that is okay a farmer it is my
new occupation feeding for the ls I
shall do it all for the queen yes for
the queen I'm going to start with
potatoes
now maybe in this
area potato
pot as as as an avid farmer myself it's
quite nice when the area is completely
filled with one thing for a
while uh is that sarcasm my sense no no
no I'm just explaining what I'm doing so
if you see me tearing stuff up you don't
get
[Music]
confused what happen to the princess I
don't know but I'm quite
distressed how could your daughter do
such a thing Queen Mario I don't know I
just don't know what happened maybe you
raised her wrongly no that's not how I
worked
no I I'll make this back area beats back
here can be the beat
area
well I don't I I hope she will not
return and undo all of our hard work
once again
hopefully that would be Ru of
her well that seems to be what she's
aiming
for I know
cruelness
destroying well it looks marvelously
green once again possessed by something
I I just don't understand what
like Nisha yes do you remember about the
corruption that you mentioned about the
king yes I do believe that this might be
his doing I think maybe since you've
been trying to usurp his throne as the
rightful Queen trying to also marry the
other rightful Queen Tam Gander um that
he has seen you and the princess as a
threat and is hence here to try and take
you
down via your
daughter cuz seeing her corruption will
make the citizens of Lee Estel doubt you
as she is around causing chaos you're so
right I need to do something about it
yes I need to send my Pon as soon as
possible yes do not wait make
haste I do
now what has my cat
done what has my cat
done poor little
kitty all right I think we've done a
good job replanting the gardens perhaps
we will not starve only for one oh never
mind there's this whole area back here
oh it will be fine
we can regrain everything yes it'll be
beautiful again Bountiful inde over time
everything will be all right cuz even
after a harvest has been destroyed you
can always plant new
seeds
beautiful thank you
wellstead what are you planting at the
moment beets be since this whole upper
area is beets
for the most
part all right success we shall leave
the garden for now goodness
yes perhaps we
shall uh get like make it inaccessible
for her wait is it over here as well no
no wait how many Gardens do we have are
these all empty yeah what we have come
so
late we really have huh here go go off I
will fix it give me give me your
seeds
yes the seeds and do you also want the
grown potatoes uh ye yes I don't have I
I have room for just one more thing so
maybe for now I I think I need beet
seeds beet seeds you shall have thank
you I shall fix the gardens to the best
of my
ability okay thank you thank you for the
people of liestal for the people of
liestal oh why would princess beu do
such a
thing I'm
disturbed I know not what to think of
this after all of my hard work to plant
everything
before and it has all been for
[Music]
not as Princess beu herself has proven
to be the destroyer of the
garden there's no more potato salad
industry but worse than that there's no
more food for the
kingdom we will not be able to survive
the winter in liasa like this even if
the crops recover we shall still be in a
predicament as what are we supposed to
eat in the coming
weeks it is a heavy situation
indeed but I believe with great
perseverance we can make it through
anything the citizens of lestelle and
the guilds are
strong but it goes without saying that
princess vishu Must Be
Stopped the devastation she has caused
is
terrible it's terrible and
unkind and illc
[Music]
considerer very nice that was actually
not to brag but oh my gosh did you guys
see that that's like kind of amazing
sorry real quick uh just ended with half
the field of potatoes that'll be really
nice I'm just saying I'm just saying you
know assuming princess beu does not show
back up to destroy my efforts of fixing
the garden
[Music]
I don't quite like Beet Root seeds but
they are very easy to
plant H never mind I'm not as brilliant
as I thought
for now we will continue planting our
seeds even just Reviving The Gardens to
the halfway
point would be not so bad but I only
hope that princess beu isn't nearby
breaking everything that I've just put
down admittedly that is my one
[Music]
fear my only
fear being a farmer is tiresome work but
now that I am revived
if only if only herb were here to
help I saw in my ghost form that she
seemed to have garnered an affinity in
fact for planting
plants I was quite impressed to see her
care and maintenance of the
gardens while she too took advantage of
the potato
salad very impressed indeed
the rest of this will be
wheat I've received a message and I am
scared of who it might be
from I do not know if I should open it
as I fear it I fear
[Music]
okay perhaps I shall finish with this
field and then we shall move on as as
long as there are two
fields which are recovered I
feel that things will turn out
[Music]
fine things will turn out
okay why not make a game around it I
don't think anyone wants to do that I
don't think anyone wants to refill this
but me I'll be
honest I think it is only only me who
would
be dumb enough to sit here and do
this but it is for the kingdom
and for the kingdom I must Tire
[Music]
away I must I must toil away
rather as that is my
duty but alas we are almost running out
of
crop I was only able to pick up so much
during the Fallout and
destruction that princess biu
caused
yes I have a few more
[Music]
seeds but alas it seems that right now
that is all that I am able to do
it is better than it was before which is
all that matters but two fields are
completely wiped
out which is a Devastation Upon Our
lands
ah my carrots all the carrots I planted
[Music]
before yeah the Le best in child just
watched as I toiled
away did we miss so many
areas we really did not do the greatest
job but you know we we did our best and
that's what matters is that we tried
really hard
sometimes that is just as important as
succeeding I will go and plant a random
potato
now
here it's
perfect well I tried to the best of my
ability but as I am out of seed and
crop that is all we can
do the princess doesn't sleep your
efforts are fruitless
I fear the same
[Music]
thing I fear exactly the same thing
might come to
pass but what are we to
do all we can do is persevere in this
time of
[Music]
horror seeing the barren lands the baren
wastelands knowing that we cannot
physically make a hole oh no this is
even worse
actually this is even more terrible wait
a minute we can't make a hoe you
guys for those of you who don't realize
why that's important the land is going
to untill itself and we have no way to
till
it there's no way to till the
lands no ho no
[Music]
um so actually mayhaps this has
become a a little bit more of a serious
manner than it was just a second ago I
will still only finish the one that I
have
started but as long as we have half the
crop I think we should be able to
persevere
somehow but
um we will not be able to build more
ow I'm scared of what the princess might
do I'm scared this is not enough but
it's what I have right now
[Music]
see you're right that if it's if it's
hydrated then it usually doesn't until
but I'm pretty sure people are going to
jump on it or walk over it in a funny
way and the game is going to take that
as you
know the game the game can
be sometimes particular about certain
things like like
that you know what I
mean sometimes the game is very
[Music]
particular it is indeed a shame what has
become of princess beu
[Music]
but to buy the
crop I would need to
re repopulate this land it would be a
funny very funny ridiculous
amount of money and I am rich
but I am not that rich and what I am not
rich on is
[Music]
time for you see I actually uh must away
in about 30
minutes after that point I will no
longer be able to play for the rest of
the night but I will see you all again
tomorrow when that happens which is not
yet but it will eventually I just feel
like that's important to
[Music]
know important to note
for I have something I must
[Music]
do I heard
something really
that's
it my efforts are not very
fruitful as not only do I need to
replant the crop that I
take but I also need to fill in a whole
new area
it
is it is with
great
[Music]
horror I am frightened
all right there will be one blank area
but I think this is mostly much better
how long until 99
farming wow what does that mean 99
farming
H all right in the wake of
Destruction we have revived
it at least the front Gardens
a chicken farm
oh Do Not Disturb grave here
rip this is quite the
temple oh
my this does not seem to be a grave
[Music]
however will you marry me
oh hello Beau hello Queen Mario oh there
you go there you are
yes I I sent the P do right now yes I'm
happy to hear I have recovered only half
of the gardens but I decided that maybe
there is where I should stop for now but
the destruction that your daughter has
caused is
immense but we have lessened it just a
little for now I will I will try to
understand and figure out what's going
on with her as soon as possible thank
thank you Queen Mario I will leave it to
you and in your very capable hands thank
you so much I'll do my best to protect
letian yep keep building don't let me
distract you no no I'm just done just
done oh yeah I see will you marry me and
that's to Tam
Gander should I ride Tam Gander too no I
think it's pretty
clear I hope so yeah who else what it be
about yeah I send the pigeon you can you
can see it later if you want yeah yeah I
believe that this will result in the
best case
scenario I hope so yes me as
well did you recover 100% your body and
power yes lady me and Jonathan with a G
and Lady Shakira went and we were able
to fully review recover my for and now I
am human again well whatever I was I'm
I'm fat that is good yes it's good to
[Music]
hear well I must continue searching for
the princess
beu yes sure go for it yes I will I will
continue to do my
best do your best you as well see you
later goodbye Queen Mario
goodbye and look looks like princess beu
is no longer
here so at the very
least my recovered Gardens are probably
safe for the time
[Music]
being for the time being and only for
the time
being h
well we've had quite the eventful day
haven't we we have found a secret coded
message we have recovered half of the
gardens after they were destroyed by a
corrupt princess
beu Gigi moodin has come by or excuse me
Jonathan with the J G has come by and
destroyed our he's beaten us
and I've been revived the best of all
cases is I am not a
ghost which is very nice uh I do not
know where anyone else is lying in
wait I would have liked to go and said
goodbye
to I would have liked to go and have
said goodbye
I'm scared for the gardens
now I fear for
them but here at Scarlet
wand we know that it is important to
make sure that the whole the whole city
of lestel is able to
[Music]
eat I'm quite
I'm quite sad for the
princess this Monument which she hath
built a moai now bleeding
tears we seem to be in quite the
predicament and I'm not sure what can be
done but alas we must hope
that Tam Gander and queen Mario can
become married and overthrow the king
and then only then maybe be's power or
rather not her
power check narissa Jr H I don't know
how to tell you this but my baby is
dead sadly I was not able to find the
soul
so come visit the queen statue ah
uh what does this
say may
uh may may something may chaos take the
world what does this one
say can someone Translate
let there be
a a
what darkness is
[Music]
approaching
okay let this be a warning to
all Queen Eternal Tam gander
well this is indeed quite the
disturbing
[Music]
D maybe it is
a a work of
no but there's nowhere else to
[Music]
go
H have you seen the chicken coop I have
[Music]
indeed it must be nice to have a
creation a consistent creation of such
wonderful eggs from such beautiful
chickens narissa
junr my child is
dead it is unfortunately
[Music]
true
alas no CLE eggs they have your name I
don't know how to check that I don't
think that's true she named them after
me what a kind person she
is and there is a place to stand trial
it
seems
terrifying last call for lottery tickets
let's
[Music]
see come to the chicken game
okay or order online and select fast
shipping
hello I am here one player can play I'm
here for lottery tickets The Raven oh so
fast hello can I interest you in a
lottery ticket it is completely free yes
that sounds like fun the first 20 people
who take a ticket will win but I cannot
tell you whether you are I'll take a
tick okay you will find out in 14
minutes if you are one of the first 20
people okay uh I have to log off in 14
minutes well I still get my prize
tomorrow yes I can hold on to it for you
if you wi only if you win all right let
me send you tickets thank you I TR
putting it in your hand uh can I get a
tickets 100 tickets I'm afraid that I do
not have that many on me oh understood I
can give you another four though oh okay
I'll take another four okay I will give
you four more
tickets that is not how you supposed to
one a second
one
two
three
four oh ring ring hello are you wanting
tickets for the
lottery oh I'm at the chicken game you
see
I'm on the road ceran
kep the ceran
kep
[Music]
seruan I want to play again
five Okie doie I will be sending them
over to you now well everyone is serving
me what the hell what no I've already
played oh talk oh mhm oh you can can we
meet by oh I see let us
[Music]
go something is a foot
what if you would like a free ticket
from nanu yes you at you at the wrong
wrong space
[Music]
a seat oh may I may I give you my
donation my donation oh for the book for
the thing yes yes for the library if you
may put it on the shelves if you could
mayhaps put this book on the
shelves of course thank you thank you is
it okay if I read it um yes go ahead it
is a book to be read by all in the
library can I read can I read it out
loud
yes I will be the audience
happily why is why are you a why are you
a ghost again oh I I now after turning
into a ghost I found out I have the
power to turn
invisible oh yes it seems that your soul
is still in between the two because you
have yeah that is really
scary quite scary don't be scared
terrifying it is tery my
[Music]
goodness I'm not allowed up there ghose
to me you f
Beast oh goodness okay I I'll look away
it's okay I'll read your book while
looking away oh I will night's tail I
[Music]
will once upon a time there was a
night he traveled the roads alone for he
had no
purpose there was an emptiness in him
for he had lost his memories and
forgotten all that he
held
dear what was I placed here what is my
purpose what is my reason questions he
asked himself day in day out when he
found a light a Shining Light a queen to
serve a guild to depend on and a lovely
companion a companion in which he could
call home but like him everyone around
him had lost their memories despite this
they continued to fight and journey side
by side even without their memories they
knew
intrinsically intrinsically that they
could rely on each
other but as each day passed everyone
knew that these days would come to an
end the memories would return and when
they returned would they be the same
person as they were now knowing this
they continued on making the most of
it the night suddenly full of Purp purus
was called an honest Noble Knight but
the Knight was conflicted for inside of
him was
selfishness he wished that no one's
memories would return so that he could
keep living in these peaceful
days but
alas he holds his convictions in his
heart and he will continue on with his
head held high well he knows a selfish
request such as his could never be true
[Music]
wow that is such a sad
story oh you're back to not being a
ghost anymore the story was so beautiful
that my physical form came back
again well that was really nice do you
know how can I put this book into the
labrary how do I probably probably this
one over here I don't know how though
maybe select the book and try right
clicking it maybe I don't know oh I did
it I did it nice look that was such a
sad story it was so sad I'm depressed
now God it's fiction is
it I mean I think so is it not well we
have our first
book first book in the first
book uh
nice
attention please
submit it's just a silly story stories
you write to the
library I'm calling
someone yes dearest Jonathan I must say
that was a wonderful story it touched
me you found it where did you find it
found
it oh
I will
[Music]
away well now
we have our first book in the
library and The Gallows are
complete and we also have an area to
judge quite nice if I do say so myself
I'm very impressed nice
podiums it's very very nice but it's
right next to the Forbidden chaotic
cursed Forest which I'm quite scared
about but it looks like it is currently
at least being
contained so there's at least
that pathetic
[Music]
H for now I think tomorrow will be the
finale where we will find out truly
what's going on
here for now for chapter 1 so please uh
I will of course be
there or be
square so you should as well be there or
be square
So currently this is the state of the
gardens as I am leaving them I fear we
come tomorrow and they will all be
gone and our efforts will have been for
not but
alas we shall
see but for
now thank you all for coming today and
for watching me as we explored lie
bestell and found out the many secrets
that it carries
and investigated the whole of the town I
must tell you I must tell you by the way
I have a cover or not a cover excuse me
a new MV a new music video coming out on
Sunday so please watch that but anyways
that's beside the point uh we are going
to we are going oh hello I'm about to
end give me one moment please okay I
will send you over to Nana mum but for
now thank you so much for joining and I
shall see you all in the next and final
uh final en Recco stream to
tomorrow thank you all bye and Darlings
[Music]