[Music]
[Applause]
wait a minute hold on wait wait a minute
not not again wait wait wait wait wait
wait a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their souls
[Music]
always I mean who is that oh
hi oh hi
everybody oh wait let me fix
this I fix I can fix I fixed it oh
hi oh hi my name is uh
Daren
[Music]
Roosevelt my name is Dar Darwin
Roosevelt
DiCaprio nice to meet you for the first
time okay um I have so much money oh my
goodness oh how exciting I'm very happy
about that I didn't realize I had so
[Music]
much I'm early
today early
by D Ro
D
D D D
D I think is that a good nickname what
I'm I'm I'm not all here today um but
I'm
here the the road the the
roie don't wrote like short you know for
for my
name Junior I forgot the Junior at the
end of my name okay my name is Darwin
Roosevelt DiCaprio Jr okay I have
popcorn and it fell
did you see that did you see that
strange creature that's in the room with
me I guess not okay oh
hi sorry I'm kind of late but I'm not
I'm actually
early by D Roi Junior uh
terms I wanted to play earlier today cuz
I was so sleepy
Yesterday by like the last
hour and I was going to play even
earlier than now but you see what
happened is I did meal prep that I first
prepped for this strange creature that's
in the room with me I boiling a bunch of
chicken legs but I didn't realize how
many chicken legs there really were
there were 10 there were 10 chicken
legs and I uh had to you know shred it
like rip it up afterwards and dry it
make sure like it didn't have a bunch of
the oil still remaining on it so that
took a really long time much longer than
I thought I don't like to waste food
especially if it comes from an animal so
I got as much chicken off that thing as
I could and then I made chicken stock
for myself I put the bones back in the
water then I added like onion and garlic
and ginger and bell pepper and carrot
scraps they're all scraps that I've
had for months that have been in my
freezer I finally put them to use I made
chicken stock and then I made uh I
wanted to try making
mapo tofu but it's not mapo tofu it's
just inspired by m tof CU I didn't have
the fermented
soybean paste and I didn't have the
right peppers for it anyways that's what
I
did
hello hello
[Music]
hello it's so empty here oh my gosh a
person who are
you who is
this who are you oh no I'm going to wait
I was going to ask where are you but I'm
going to I'm going to wait till they
respond
ooh ooh I am shopkeeper fauna from the
Scarlet
W this music it's I interest you in the
lottery
ticket I'm not going to answer that yet
this sounds like a scam um this is like
a popup ad but in Minecraft chat where
are you
where is she let me see you in
person before I agree to to do what to
gamble to enter a
lottery tell me where you are offer it
to my face I am south of the fighting
arena in the free build area south of
the fighting AR does she mean this this
Coliseum looking
thing she's south of it how do I what's
the button that you press to find uh
what direction you're going
in she can't spell close honestly I
would do exactly what she did as well I
would do the exact same thing I would
second guess
myself F3 so she's south of this thing
I'm not press hold on all right where's
it
again oh my gosh it's been so long I
think it had been almost a year since I
did what nothing I've never been here
before I've never been in this world
before this what uh wait I'm looking
where
is where is
it I have a map oh you're so right I do
have a map I have something that's
blocking it okay I'm going south cool
she's south of
here up up up oh so not inside it she's
south of
it oh what is that in the
distance what is that in the distance is
that is that the shopkeeper FAA oh wait
it might not be it might be one of these
people are they my Target right now wait
no they're
not you don't have a horse no I don't do
I look like I'd have
horse and the free build build
area is this is this a free build
area how do you zoom in
again is it
no what's the zoom thingy no
no what what how do you zoom how do you
[Music]
zoom all right it's different I hate
that it's different in this game
that you think that control is Crouch
but it's not
Crouch shift is a Crouch I I cannot
stand
that the z a i know what I think I have
it what is
it there we
go where'd she go she know did someone
tell her I was here is she hiding from
me you guys are really really ruining
the
[Music]
hunt all right
well how come I can't run
now is I'm holding
stuff what the
heck hey oh my God I totally forgot you
can hear me
hello hark
Adventurer welcome to my fine
establishment Park The Vow
what welcome to my fine
establishment thank you may I rest my
weary head yes if you purchase a lottery
ticket I will go it's only 10 gold each
that's all right I'll go elsewhere I'll
sleep under the stars you're you're not
interested in in the big
jackpot the the big jackpot the big
jackpot of uh zero gold is but it will
increase as more people purchase lottery
tickets is this a popup ad how do I
close no what is an
ad you you everything you everything you
are right now this is my my shop I'm a
small business
owner 10% goes towards theft build of
the Scarlet wand who is in charge of the
local library buying a lottery ticket
will support local education efforts all
right Boy Scout whatever you
say so instead of giving me cookies or
whatever what do Boy Scout what's a boy
anyways um instead of giving me a
physical item you're giving me the
option to
gamble yes who doesn't love to gamble
and a place with a side of helping
education in our
lands so
uh how do I how do I give you
money we can we can trade we can trade M
oh my
gosh it's only 10 gold for one or you
can buy multiple 10 gold of oh I see you
can exchange
it okay well this isn't embarrassing but
I don't have any
gold oh I could loan you 10 gold if
you'll use it to buy a lottery ticket
sure or what about this what about
this okay okay okay I'll accepted all
right okay what what numbers do you want
or do you want random numbers wait what
do you mean wait I I'm so stupid I
should have I should have asked more
questions what what what do the numbers
mean what well it's a it's a lottery so
you get three numbers three single digit
numbers and then every day at 5:00 p.m.
I will I will
roll for the numbers to pick the winning
ticket what time is
it at 5:00 p.m. Pacific time and it's
it's uh 5:45 p.m. Pacific Time right now
so I have to wait till tomorrow yeah but
but maybe by the time tomorrow rolles
around more people will have bought into
the lottery and the jackpot could be in
the in the
hundreds have my flower
back you you already bought it what
numbers do you
want what do I choose the numbers all
right or you can have a random
one I don't wait hold on no what wait
wait do you have lucky numbers
lady the odds are insane this what so
it's it's about 1 in
700 it's not that bad it's better than
the real life
Lottery
but
[Music]
I
okay I will do it's only it's only 10
gold for the chance to win
big okay wait a minute but I put in a
flower so what do I if I win what do I
get back well now the now the pot is up
to 10 gold cuz I I put in 10 for you oh
you did oh my
gosh um okay I would like the numbers
774 you can't have repeat numbers what
the heck um why because it's it's like
the balls spinning around in the Bingo
ball and once you remove one it can't be
drawn again
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm choking on a popcorn colel please
help
me May May a lottery ticket ease your
suffering
but I just I don't the best I can do is
784 I don't know that many numbers and I
don't like that one what about 764
I don't think I like that one either
724 dang it I was just thinking how I
really like
7442 dang
[Music]
it I think the issue is that the seven
is at the front Okay so how about
[Music]
274 how about 276
okay okay okay Final Answer Final Answer
276 okay I'm sending you your lottery
ticket make sure you hold on to it in
case in case these numbers are
drawn when I when I pull it
[Music]
tomorrow okay the lottery ticket from
fmart I
[Music]
see and
okay I'm going
okay your your patronage is much
appreciated the local library will
surely feel your
contribution where is this local
library it's it's right over uh in the
red part of town the red part of town
the Scarlet W
headquarters it's the
library is it really there
yeah it is can you show me okay what
kind of books do you guys
have um we've got
TOs and texts um
Necronomicon okay and what benefit does
this provide for me
specifically
well I think the Necronomicon would be
right up your alley personally have you
heard of it I
haven't well it's a book that makes you
go crazy if you read it and it's usually
Bound by human
skin and it can give you access to all
sorts of other worldly Powers if you
read
it I don't know about the going crazy
part I've already called like so many
people
loonies uh since coming to this place I
don't I don't I think it'd be kind of
embarrassing
yeah you think it wouldn't wouldn't help
you understand everyone else get on the
same level why would I what why do I
want to understand them unlock your mind
to the
potential but the what's the
potential you could like learn how to
create
zombies
okay yeah I I haven't read it I tried
but I couldn't get past the first page
so I don't really know what the heck
you're recommending me a book you can't
you haven't even been able to read yeah
cuz I can tell you're on a more advanced
level already oh my gosh you con artist
you what what my good just telling me
what I want to hear except you should
always maintain eye contact with
me okay okay
just good point good point my
apologies you're forgiven
you know if you do some side quests you
could earn money to buy more lottery
tickets could
you some of them are pretty
easy a side quest you say yeah your
chances go up I mean imagine if the
chances are one in 700 and then you buy
70 lottery tickets your chances are
increased a
lot I suppose so and let me get this
straight it's it's one gold bar or 10
gold
what the jackpot no how much the lottery
ticket how much is the lottery ticket
the lottery ticket costs 10 golden coins
okay but do you convert the coins to
bars no no
okay it's just coins I feel like you
should cuz it would be easier to carry
well don't they isn't it so that gold is
just
better than you know like a coin
currency as it constantly
changes
oh yeah I get it welcome to invest but
maybe if you're like clever with your
Investments then you can like get more
than the value of of
gold that sounds awfully
risky so is so is buying a lottery
ticket and yet you've already made that
risk so why not why not take the next
step I mean not so much yet as I gave
you a
flower the flower is worth more than its
weighted gold now you're just straight
up lying to me oh my
goodness there's no putting value on
nature I suppose this is the library uh
I think wait wait wait wait here's
here's the books here's the books here
where are the books here's the
books here are the books oh here are the
books the books here are the books okay
you see we only have one shelf right now
but since your since your generous
donation we may be able to afford more
folks in the future who's in charge of
the funds of this place because it's
quite extravagant there's so many
hanging lanterns and it's so large but
it's a library and all they could do is
allocate this little corner to books to
knowledge well you have to have lights
to read can't read in the dark you need
the books to read through and there's
not enough books there's books there's
at least a 100 books there's not enough
books to fill this entire like what are
there's at least a 100 books here I mean
have you read them all have you read all
of them on the Shelf you just said
there's one available book no there's
there's hundreds there's hundreds just
one in particular I thought I feel like
you're praying on my Amnesia right now
what I also have amnesia how could I
pray upon that which I too suffer it's
definitely possible as I have I have
also you've prayed upon others I have
well then maybe you'd be interested in
taking up a a part-time job at fart we
could really use your skill set
[Music]
okay gang I'm going to accept the job
wait get out of get out are you vlogging
right now are you vlogging I'm going to
accept the job but she's not going to
know that I have alternate motives
ulterior motives and so guys I'm going
to take the job for
now but I'm I'm probably I'm going to
use use it to my
advantage okay
[Music]
I will accept this part-time job that
you have offered me within the last two
seconds thank you thank
you no thank
you we can we can start the onboarding
process immediately all right if you're
ready please please train me teach me
everything that you know there anything
is there anything that you want to do in
particular
I don't know I've never worked a day of
my life I
think yeah I just started today honestly
did you I've been I've been building my
shop from the ground up today it's hard
work wow that is hard work it's very
inspiring thank
you I'm trying to think of what I can
offer you can offer your your labor my
labor wait this this is for for
free
wait actually you can't offer your labor
I cannot you're not in my
guild
what you're not in the in the Scarlet
wand so you can't you can't you can't
help me
[Music]
build but you can gather materials for
me who decides this was it decided by
the gods of this world yeah it was
decided by the gods are you for real
yeah what the
heck that's why I couldn't place the
flower there oh
probably I curse these
Gods but I could certainly use more more
resources if you were off collecting
resources could you
now I could what type of
resources um
Spruce
logs
Spruce logs
[Music]
mainly okay and where do I find
those I can show you okay can you hold
my
hand okay I've never held hands with
anyone before I think please take me to
where the spruce logs are and I'll hold
your hand so I don't get lost okay I
think I I think they're this way okay
can you please maintain eye contact it
makes me
feel you don't care if you're not
looking at
me yeah yeah I understand this
reasonable
request what's that you're holding
there what am I holding oh it's
a a Sakura slab Cherry slab oh I see
yeah I was using it to build my my shop
that's nice it's what it's nice
it's nice very
nice I see this is what I thought I knew
people would love pink pink would
definitely get people to come into my
shop right oh for sure the past get them
to spend money on lottery tickets good
thing there's only girls here yeah right
they're going to love it
mhm you're going to have the entire town
in a
hoot it's only the first day but I'm
imagining the lottery it's going to get
big once people catch
on if it succeeds that
is oh it'll succeed oh will
it it will oh sorry sorry that's okay I
really I I think it's very important for
us to continuously hold hands and look
each other in the
ey it it is I might get distracted
otherwise yeah I mean there's a lot to
see around here don't remind me
have you have you been exploring this
world I
did I I went to the
dungeon mhm and I got a
key me too and I
got
iron yeah did you do the iron side quest
that is raw no oh maybe you should maybe
you should pick up the the side quest
over here here right
here sorry just just running into a pole
it's kind of hard to see
but I'll be your eyes right here here
with this board of quest is yeah yeah
yeah you'll find all sorts of side
quests here on the quest
board hold on I'm sorry I have to look
over your hand for a second okay okay
I need two hands to eat this
bread here's an iron
one Mama
Mia
I'm this happen but I don't have a near
enough help if you lend me lend me a
handle don't don't accept that one you
already have a part-time job you can't
you can't take anymore but this one's so
appealing they opened it with Mama Mia
would you like me to talk with the same
accent I
would would that to help you that would
help me a
lot I'm worried it might come off as a
insensitive if I do it I don't know I
just I think of it more as you're making
fun of the person that was in Titanic
uh Titanic I can't reach all of them
oh oh you could use the the these are
all the same yeah if you use the arrow
oh my gosh I just realized these are all
different ones yeah oh my gosh maybe I
shouldn't speak in that accent because I
won't actually process what it is that
I'm
reading you're
correct there's an iron one but why why
would I do the IR how does this help
you um it'll give you money which you
can use to spend on lottery tickets
which would really help me and in the
local
library you're right I have absolutely
no
coins
M and I see no other reason to have
coins than to help
you yeah
right there's something I mean think of
think of the return on investment that
you could get I don't know like I just
can't get past this little this little
feeling
little inkling but this might not be
very
ethical what's what's what's unethical
about it promoting people to gamble for
[Music]
charity well people love gambling they
there's a Cino on this in this Village
that that doesn't give to charity so
wouldn't it be better that people that
people gamble somewhere where it
actually has real world benefits see now
this is a dangerous d dous hole that
you're falling into going well this is
worse and mine isn't as bad thus mine is
okay I I failed to see the the
problem perhaps
I'm unable to speak oh my
God you failed to see the problem you
say I fail to see the problem this must
mean that I am very
smart you should you should join the the
Scarlet
wands are they smart you Al wait but you
but
you're what what are you what are you
trying to
say but but look at my hat I'm very
smart but you cannot understand the
things that I understand as you have
just admitted and what I understand to
be the truth well that's because you are
very smart I am only just smart and you
are very smart but where are my very
smart people where's the very smart
Guild out in the Scarlet
wands you got sorted into the wrong
house why are we here again oh you
should take the the iron Quest the iron
Quest hello fair oh hello hello lady of
the oranges good day to both of you
beautiful ladies nice hat uh I must say
I am almost en of it I do recommend the
iron Quest highly it was quite uh a good
um uh yes good thing not very useful not
to startle you my lady but there is a
woman on a horse behind you you did
start me I thought I could sneak my
way Scot shad
yeah
yeah what is happening what what is
happening I'm scared what is happening
we speak the language of the Gods what
the
heck so you must respect us we did a
side quest and we learned a new language
in the side oh you can do it too oh
really wait I want to do that I want to
scare how long did it take you it took
me it took us 3 minutes if you guys want
to join I can show you 3 minutes mhm and
we'll learned an entirely new
language uh well yeah yeah it's like a
it's like a it's like a video game
mechanic okay that's so it's like you
it's like an RPG you know where you have
a skill tree oh you already did you do
it did you do it already yeah that's why
I speak uh German M I heard I heard her
say something what did you say oh say it
her name is a m it's
cleop the actually it's Darwin Roosevelt
Junior you changed
it I did not can I call you Junior for
short you can call me Junior for
sure wait what happened with
free who with what happened with the
person you were
yesterday I am the person that I was
[Music]
yesterday names are but a name am I
struck by amnes once again we just can't
comprehend her Brilliance she's on
another level H indeed she might be
indeed indeed my ladies my ladies may I
interest you in a lottery ticket I'm
running a lottery a daily lottery
starting today and the first drawing
will be tomorrow and for just 10 gold
coins you can purchase a lottery ticket
or however many as you would like and
enter for your chance to win big
jackpots is it the other green lady in
your guild too why do I feel like I'm
being cheated on why do you want to why
you did she do the exact same thing with
you she did the exact same thing with me
she's the more people buy tickets the
bigger the jackpot gets it has to be
personalized FAA every single sale has
to be
personalized well let me me just
regurgitating the
same and whenever I look into your green
eyes I see the green of money and I
recall the time we spent in the casino
betting it all on green and I recall how
that casino failed us this is so
personalized I feel so targeted like I
am in the market so that was so much
more intimate than what she said to me
what the heck well you didn't have any
money so oh I that's that's how this win
rates FAA deest um bet oh well it's
about about 1 in 700 although you can
buy as many lottery tickets as you want
700 raise your chances every time it's
way better odds than the real lottery I
might add yeah but you don't what do you
win if you win how much you win the big
jackpot you win money well well right
now it's only 10 gold but the more
lottery tickets are bought the bigger
the jack pot will grow so if you guys if
I the L the chances are yeah but if you
guys don't buy it then it'll be a really
low Lottery and there could just be like
one sucker who just gets a very to guil
us into paying for the lottery it's
working my lady I would like the
opposite quite the opposite oh no one
understands yes yes
myone understands me I was trying to
save them that will be 40 gold please to
save me I was trying to save them do you
have to use reverse psychology 40 Golds
accept how do I accept
I I was just being transparent on it oh
okay being transparent I see you very
clearly okay I have a question no one
understands
me that is not true a figure of speech
you did not
understand perhap some of the proceeds
for the would be used for the V watched
my some watched it wait yes go over here
over here Perhaps Perhaps
10% perhaps there's a chance that 10% we
are going to get in on what's going on
and we are going to use it to our
advantage any I made it I the block I
made it there you go any sign of
friendliness
like that is used for us to take
advantage of others so that we can be to
to the biggest of the
brain three digit combination but each
digit has to be different we should let
her be because they're in the same Guild
and they only like numers Zer you are so
correct let's just let it happen perhaps
we just convinced everyone that is in
the same Guild which is theirs so like
yeah three numbers four times and then
only one of them well the thing is I'm
in the lottery right now it's not a big
deal don't worry about it um but
one of them will win and then I win and
then they'll fight if they have more
than one step in the lottery they be
there to CU they have too much time to
think about it you know they have to
well I'll just I'll just make sure that
they won't there's your there's your sub
would you like for the second one make
sure you hold on to
that click on the Subscribe
button what else should you do no no
everyone wouldn't do that no 657 yeah
yeah and sponsorship
okay # one minute ad
for we don't have any right now okay
okay one one
second okay VPN perhaps okay uh and uh
how about
two
bpn by sponsored
by surf surf GAA VPN yes that should be
I'm n n n n n n n that should be four
stop popcorn is
addicting what is popcorn I only know
corn it is corn that is popped do I have
to do something how I have sent you how
do one do that that seems like powerful
ability there you are upgrades to you
put it in the microwave that's right
what is a microwave it it really is you
can does perhaps work if I just like
burn it like
[Music]
model yeah okay lock into trade
hello our sponsorship has arrived serve
GAA
VPN
huh to the appointed Point hey are you
interested in a lottery
ticket a lottery ticket would you be
interested in gambling and partaking in
a lottery so you buy a ticket and I
guess the proceeds go to supporting the
[Music]
library did you know that once you wear
the hat of the appointed Point your
memories are shared I feel like we've
already had this conversation what no
you're
what no she tried to enter she you tried
to enter sevens but you had a double
seven you couldn't enter that right I'm
I'm a bit fuzzy I had a a bit
ofing watching with
I was watching your Vlog and she was
watching her vog memories
perfectly it's like a high of Mind guys
in mind sorry okay wait GAA think of a
color tell tell us what color think of a
color she's thinking of blue how did she
know it's the Hat of the appointed point
you know you mustn't ever remove that
hat or else you will die get one of
these okay okay what about you will you
die I will also die okay I know I know
how if I remove the Hat you die and if
you remove the Hat I die we both Die
Money leave the Hat on forever then
gotcha gotcha oh yeah I haven't done the
gambling yet I want to
and Co I don't know if that's the same
gambling as everybody talking about
Shing unless there a different one I
think created her own gambling no we
talking and then there's gambling out
already implemented into are we touching
yeah I I saw a vlog about it oh my god
oh you
did who's a
limbo are you liming
under
Li I make
it hello can you
go it works wow we also flexible very
impressive very very I got the
knees funa do you want to show us your
mom Mar I haven't seen it oh yes yes
it's it's still a work in progress and
we mainly sell lottery tickets at this
point but we all going FAA Mart is open
wait it's open oh wait you owe me a you
owe me a place to rest my weary head oh
yes you may rest your weary head in the
floor of the shop Okay I I purchased
that and I I I wish to
have
yes you all right horses weird
I love how like the the horses are so
fast watch out watch out watch out watch
out watch out watch out watch out watch
out watch out watch out watch out
O phone Mar lottery tickets now
available guys this sounds like a good
deal is this entire March is for lottery
tickets well well so far we oh thank you
so far we don't have anything else for
sale really well if you would like to
buy some cherry saplings we could we
could negotiate um and how do what those
benefit for lottery tickets yes what is
the benefit of a cherry sapling oh you
won't fit um you can grow it into a
cherry tree or you can use it as
decoration very beautiful are these not
just available in nature cor I just have
but then you have to go out and get it
yourself this it this is how much
trouble
I'm not sure about I'm not sure about
the safety of this establishment funa
think well it's a work in
progress if more lottery tickets are
purchased then that can go towards the
betterment of fart wait what do you mean
I thought the lottery would go towards
what the library does it not go towards
the winner goes towards the library was
this mentioned before well check check
the fine print of your ticket m i will I
think you should put a a sign down where
it says like please wear hat when
entering like a hard hat you know like
when a reserves the right to 30% of all
what um excuse me miss the fine prin
says it says that you get 30% of the
jackpot winning yes but you just said
10% no no the library gets
10% there is more there recently so 40%
doesn't even go towards
an the the jackpot is
huge huge jackpots big wins in the
lottery every day okay then after taxes
what well I don't know if you have to
pay taxes the king doesn't know about
this Lottery and I'd like to keep it
that way and I think you all would
too oh you wait you just wait until the
queen hears about this queen
the queen is the Queen the future Queen
the future you shall treat her as the
current
Queen the The Tam tenders lady
oh the King was trying to proposed to
her so she's accepting his proposal then
of course a banqu of course she is oh we
have to think of what what would we give
as a present for the like a betral
present how about a lottery card no
two lottery cards two lottery tickets
yeah I don't know I feel like that's
embarrassing I feel like there's nothing
you can really give to someone who's
going to be Queen when you are the
status that we
are
indeed like what like a blenders if they
can't get one
themselves but it's the thought that
counts and you could put a like as long
as you make get personalized into a
blender I feel like you should give them
a card or something please no fire ins
sorry sorry that's just a phoenix
happenings every once in a while I'll
turn the AC on oh yeah I can't again wo
W it was the
[Music]
AC anyways F that's messed up man what
you what you you're taking advantage of
people that can't
read that's what the library is for
fun like the
library you didn't mention they You'
have reading
lesson it's a library of course of
course doing something for the local
businesses M what are you doing for the
local buiness why are you on her side
because my team Scarlet one she was just
trying to scam you my hat sorry what she
was trying to scam you though no on my
team so as long as she wins I win Oh no
you're one of those people that's like
well but she's she's my mother she's my
brother it's okay if she takes all my
money we will expose this scam on her
Vlogs and then you will go
down sounds like sounds like free
advertising to
[Laughter]
Meer so everybody
knows well no I'll hold on on my
ticket I tell the queen about this wait
wait before you tell the
queen would would you be interested in
joining the
lottery no it's only it's only 10 gold
per ticket I think it's a really good
deal uh you get a German
discount you say you get a German
discount a German discount the heck
what's a
German a German is uh it's like one of
the side quests that I mentioned earlier
yeah I want I want to go on this side
quest to learn ger Germany yeah
Germany of Germany don't fall for
another scam of theirs I can teach you
Germany
privately all of Germany but I feel like
don't we need multiple P
sources what if your Germany isn't the
right Germany my Germany is the best
Germany in
I have the superior
Germany don't say that don't listen to
her my Germany sounds
beautiful La lying over there okay I'll
show you the quest are you ready no no
no no no no you're not ready cuz you
haven't bought a ticket yet right that's
yeah you bought the ticket you you can
just I wait are we all going to are we
all going to learn about Germany now
yeah okay okay um well not about Germany
we're doing the side quest to learn
German yeah that's what that's what I
meant okay okay uh this way
okay okay how do you say okay in
Germany good question
okay number one okay okay you have to
talk to this
NPC okay oops everyone gets on their
hor what he doesn't say anything in
particular it says I can pee your Shield
if you want me to now also says it in
German no no he doesn't look look
closely it says it right
there
scam this is just another scam over
there I understood perfectly he said I
can beat your Shield if you want me to I
can understand German we're absorbing
she did it oh wow that is very
impressive okay next one next one right
this way wait a minute wait a minute
wait I'm not okay I'm ready I'm ready
I'm ready sry I'm absorbing
everything Cara get on your
horse
no no come with us nine come
[Music]
99 why would we need these NPCs to teach
us German when I can teach her German
privately cuz real like this is a video
game and this is a shortcut it really it
takes too long but this way we learn it
like it gets like translated into our
[Music]
brains can't argue with
that okay the next NPC is right
here I can't keep up I can't keep up
where where where right here
[Music]
go horse
go oops every
time oh speak he's
[Music]
saying did you understand what he
said I understood it I what what did he
say I'm getting bits and pieces here
[Music]
uh it says I'm supposed to be
working
oh what was that what was
that wow it's working it's
working wow I think M already finished
the quest
yet oh
work that what does that
mean um um she's saying it
worked it means that I speak German she
says wow M you you're natural
right with me you'll get the quest
[Laughter]
[Music]
reward it's
working he's your quest
[Music]
reward what do you get for learning
German
[Laughter]
wow she got some
bread
[Music]
thank oh I'm so I'm so happy we need
for H it's so easy to learn
that was
amazing I learned so much really has
everything I'm so happy that they
implemented this honestly I think it's
very nice yeah I feel like very they
should they should set this up with more
[Music]
languages um where car go yeah where did
you look I'm I I'm out of place now I
feel very
uncomfortable I don't know I don't know
she went backwards I think or I have no
idea I wish we had like
a locator like a like a radio that we
could use to call her and ask her to buy
a lottery
ticket something like think she was
almost folding I think she was very
buying the lottery ticket I think if we
hadn't got distracted by this Great
quest I think she would have bought a
lottery ticket you know who hasn't
bought one
yet my my fellow pointy I don't need to
buy one if we share the same I I
I that's what you might think but in
reality you do need to buy one for even
your
contributions for everybody
else
sounds that sounds like an automated
spam
call so can I can I get you down for
four
tickets four for four
tickets count mation of four tickets get
out of my get out of my head hat wearer
listen we got to set some boundaries
here I'm very impressed my I think you
are it's only once a day and then I
won't bother you about it again until
tomorrow after the drawing yeah it's
really Co I will buy one to the tongue
one ticket I will start with one
exposure see how you feel after that and
then suddenly yes you just got it it's
like something clicked in your brain
it's very impressive I think so okay
what numbers do you want but I have to
clear my throat a lot before I do it so
I'm not going to do it again for a
little bit three numbers yeah it's a bit
of a difficult setup I was
like just no is difficult for to I would
[Music]
like of me what the he I would
like how do I I don't remember how to
make myself busy wait what number what
to what numbers what to what what's the
maximum oh one to N I make myself busy I
don't you're not
disturb let's
[Music]
do
three sorry that made it sound like I
was going to speak German I thought
okay you're quite quiet I keep putting
you UPS right so quiet I'm quiet don't
know why I you
okay okay my lottery ticket am I still
quiet in the mail you should you should
you put me up I'll put you up that'll be
just 10 gold I'll put you up please oh
that's why you were trading now you're
I'm put up now you're up I understand
now can I tell you five fun fact five
wait five entire fun fact oh a fun fact
no no just one fun fact just one oh okay
okay that's good just one fun fact yes
thank you for your the day I played a
game to our local libr called I mean the
memories of a foren I should get paid no
matter what right tells me that the
other day I played a game
before back right yeah yeah and you know
at the beginning when you sure when you
say yes exactly and then instead of
boy the options are you want an as and
the Ops everybody in oh baby I'm so high
up and goodness I'm
Sor but you know when when one of us
succeeds we all succeed
right
Rising I don't know that I can hear
smiling when they talk I I don't
get what were those the two options full
of joy yeah of girl B if you pick those
are the only options that they give
you either so if you say goodness I'm so
high up you turn into a girl and if you
say oh baby we're so high up is notur so
don't worry no insurance they trying to
say boys were babies not insured I don't
know I think it has to be enthusiasm
about but
it's wait a have you ever seen the thing
that's
like that's like boys love to drop
things from like giant Heights is it
based on that like dropping rocks from a
cliff like that that
bed I don't know I saw a video the other
day I was like this group of like 10
guys all carrying a rock just to throw
it off the cliff and they got so excited
about it water
yeah ice breaking yeah the ice breaking
ice breaking voice will be
like 10 grown man throwing a rock in
face no it's a thing there's like
compilations of it like satisfying
videos but for for men I guess fish fall
be like I support it the the pool fish
they get their heads bumped in I kind of
get it I saw this video where this like
these people were bouldering and they
had to you know loosen up or get rid of
the really loose rocks and they got rid
of this one like part of this rock and
you it drops and you're like oh it's not
that high up but then it keeps falling
and it keeps falling and you realize it
is really high up it was
crazy I think the ice breaking is really
satisfying I think when you go somewhere
and it has snowed and the snow is
totally untouched and you put like your
first footsteps that is very satisfying
oh CR
yes especially when like no one's been
there so so far so it feels like you
know you're the yes because it get so
gross PL it gets so gross after like
enough people walk through it it's extra
seasoning no not that wait like the dirt
all the dirt it's shaped ice it's shaped
ice real real real real
snow yeah yeah the picture is better
than what you can get from the
machine and the
nutrients
nutrients it boosts your immune system
eat some dirt
oh the third
chaman Ladi ladies I have a question
would you so be so kind to accompany me
I would like to see if I can also get a
red a pointy hat I have 359 money how do
you guys is this a guild
thing no it's a gamble thing yeah okay I
want a hat too wait why are you now so
excited about gambling yeah for happened
with the lottery I don't care about
money I only care about hats you know
what can get you a hat
money but what about another guild what
it's just a library there's like Barnes
and& nobl you can just buy books now
Kindles I got a
Kindle what's a Kindle I did it I
haven't I got it like a month ago
you keep talking about how you have a
camera but it's still in the
box have you at least ripped off
theil I like looking at
it
I didn't put it in the case no I I
bought a case and I and I put it in the
case I didn't activate
it turn it on yet did you did you put on
a protective for
no is there
one I think so
actually still has the factory peelies
on it it it has like the default thing
on you could turn it on and like read
through the instruction manual on the
Kindle I even traveled
with I had I had to take it out of
TSA okay hey at least you have one
exactly yeah soon you'll read from it
let us know when you use it let us know
when you turn it on I also brought like
a real book with me did you read the
real book I did I read a little bit of
it oh my god Till I could read no
more he used the Kindle as a bookmark
for I don't remember I want hat where I
think the gabbling was here
this way Main Street where'sa does Ki
want to
hat I won't I won't speak German anymore
I don't think she likes it yeah so the
it is gambling just so you know M so if
you buy one there is a chance that you
don't get a hat I already bought two is
it the surprise
box yeah yes okay I bought it I bought
one too good luck how do you open
okay so you have to put it in your hand
and then right click it okay ready okay
3 2
one and then you have to it didn't
work wait you pick
one you have to hold it in your H bar
hold up I think I'm doing something
wrong oh there we go holding
it you pick only oh shoot you pick
one and one of those has a hat but only
one has a hat oh four four of those I
think what else can you
get a box I didn't get anything dang it
what are these no I got the Hat no I
didn't get the Hat I didn't get the Hat
what I get I don't know what I got alert
what we doing wait what I get what I get
what I get what' I get what I got the
Hat you the hat I got the Hat you got
nothing you got nothing I got the Hat
nothing don't worry about it it's not
going to work no no what there's no
point in wearing it what H wait what's
going on what's going on the hat is so
ugly anyway did I get all these things
even want to wear did I get everything
no you only get one only one of these
it's just showing you what you didn't
get it's
like did you wait she has the head think
very hard before you put that on your
head think very hard wait wait a minute
why can't I put it on my head don't
don't do it don't do it
what
is excuse me right CLI right click right
the Hat of the the the Hat of the
[Laughter]
appoint okay well now you guys have to
stop talking and only use uh T
telecomunication okay here's here's the
deal
now the head of the appointed Point has
been has been dawned by a member outside
of the guild which hasn't ever happened
before in the history of the Scarlet
wand haven't really been here for
day it's fine it's fine it's fine um I
knew she was sorted into the wrong Guild
I knew it it has to be Destiny it has to
be M I was lying when I said it on
another level wait am I being tested now
am I
creative would you say you're a genius
knowledge do you seek
knowledge I I do do that I mean you have
a
Kindle I I do do seek knowledge but an
unused
Kindle yeah but it's like she's seeking
it still you know I still seek it it's
just I I got a little distracted as all
yeah because she's so creative and
creative types often get distracted yeah
I was sleeping I was sleeping a lot and
dreaming and dreaming
and I was having the craziest
dreams yes the craziest dreams I've ever
had I think we have to all three of us
should touch tips and and and finish
the The Da of the the Hat of the
appointed Point
ceremony in the tri
formation real like flamingos wa a
little bit back down a little bit back
moving a little bit okay okay
down all the way down look further down
all the way ah there you
go wait a little closer a little closer
a little closer we can make a triangle I
can make a
triangle wait back
down triangle oh dear and it points to
CC I mean the green
one can I go in the middle
can now this is my TP
[Music]
I live
here what was that what was that power
my instant TP can I do that I no me only
oh only you oh I see your TP special
thing I sensed a presence
around the presence of death well
welcome to the Scarlet wand m is that a
safe way to hold a knife
what up
[Music]
I guess I guess we've multiplied what's
the word two time in wait I I said this
earlier I'm doing a different type of
two time and two time and hat wearing
I'm a two time in h and cape cape Ador
and just just just know if you take the
hat off all three of us will die
really I believe you don't
okay no I believe don't test it I'm not
going to test it I don't want to
die that's that's that's cool and you're
totally wouldn't use it against the
Scarlet one Guild right that would that
would potentially potentially eliminate
two of the members the existing members
of the Scarlet one and that would be
catastrophic
catastrophic all of all
of
all I don't think
[Music]
I'm totally going to be using it to my
advantage they'll never
know oh they know what's going
[Music]
on what
now watch out
did everybody I think everybody
went you went where I supposed to get
iron a are you going are you going are
you
[Music]
leaving yes what I'm a horse I'm a horse
I'm a horse wait
I'm by myself I want
money I don't get very much from these
do I though
seven where oh ow I'm an
owl am I I
was I think was I I don't know oh my
gosh do you think they can kill can you
kill a chicken can you kill chicken oh
oh they might hurt me oh they're going
to hurt me oh they hurt me me not that
much they're in the tavern oh where's
the
[Music]
tavern I just want a little more money
just a little more money just a little
more
money so I can eat dinner at the tavern
I want to eat dinner at the tavern
die I should oh my
goodness I really don't like the sounds
that they make there's so many of them
they sleepy e oh look at the Bak
up cute
what the where did that one go it's
still
there stop st stop what what squid
noises squid
dies
[Music]
okay I'm going to kill all these then
I'll go to the
tavern oh you wait for it to reload I
see I see that makes the process a lot
faster I see
my nose is so itchy I see I see ow hold
on I'm hungry hold on I'm hungry a good
thing I got more BR what that is that
you said
[Music]
it I
got
hooray not hooray ow
hey so much money I don't have to do
anything else except
kill
yeah so many okay okay where's the
tavern they are at the
tavern are
y'all are you still at the tavern
[Music]
Hey Now where's the tavern I have no
clue the thingies aren't
listed do you guys know where the tavern
is all of
you you Collective
you that occupies my I mind
[Music]
you on the left ahead to the left
okay this
one
[Music]
no this
one I mean sounds like it you'll never
take me
alive oh it has like 30
seconds no hey it wasn't a scam now I
have to delete get all these
tickets what's
that what's that hey The Profit no she
took the money wait she took the money
she took the money now I have to I have
to I have to take back all the tickets I
sent her I can't believe they would scam
us like this what color uh G are they
from
again wait is there no stone are you in
their Guild who Guild do we have a spy
what oh wait Scarlet hat adorned spy I'm
of the coin of Ember no Amber I see and
who's in your guild uh the lady of the
orange the B
one which which one which which orange
the phix of or the kiaha of the orange
Thea of the orange
oranges and the
ba and the really cute
cat oh the really cute cat yeah like the
super cute cat yeah she's very cute
Hatchy purse oh very cute that cute cat
very cute cat Okay well that means that
she can't be with the with the messenger
of death she can't be on the messengers
of death's side because they're not in
the same Guild m
was kava of the oranges
with was kava of the oranges with the
messenger of
death yeah oh that's a little concerning
for me Isn't
it do you think they convince kiaha of
the orange to purchase a lottery ticket
to a wait a minute what did I miss you
both now are for this whole lottery
ticket
thing but you're part of this sc one no
because of your hats give the Hat wait
24 hours and you'll come around what
benefits do I get now that I have the
Hat in relation to the lottery ticket do
I get a percentage of the percentage
that you keep of the 30% do I get a
certain percentage of that
30% well when the library wins everyone
wins yes you got to sell me on this
Library a little bit
more it it looks like a laundering
scheme at the moment you can put where
all the where all the resources have
gone to and how little books there
are but the lottery hasn't even had a
single day yet to benefit the library
but why is the library already so large
with so many riches except so this
happened before we arrived in this land
we're just trying our best to to repair
the damage that has already been done
for education system but do you have
trust in this Library that's already so
sketchy
or did you remove the people that we
have to change it from the inside M we
have to be the difference we have to buy
physical books by encouraging people to
gamble and throw their life savings
away yeah we only ask for a meanly 10
gold but you encourage even more that is
but I think this is part of the Hat
taking over oh my gosh am I feeling
empathy am I sympathizing for those that
fall into gambling patterns which I
cannot relate to because I got the Hat
on the first
try well my the Hat has one more super
crazy buff yes whenever you losing in an
argument you can say but I have the
point and then you win
automatically this is true that's right
this is
true so quick you guys say I have a
point so that she loses at the library
pum
yeah I have a point I have a point I
also have a
point well we have two points and you
want one point so but I have the
point she's right she does have the
point kiaba of the oranges kiaba of the
oranges but you I got a hat for us I did
it for us huh really I got a hat for us
how
what how is it for us well it's for it's
for our
Guild to me it looks like you are in two
guilds now minimum that's what I want it
to look
like I got that's why because I in free
guil now oh you you're
[Music]
bad oaner yes yes someone they can lend
us money but I only did that
because we can't look suspicious we
can't looks how dare you how dare you m
leaving our guil behind to join this
scammer Guild I will never forget this I
will Revenge and I will tell the
queen uh-huh I understand everything
then just happened because I was I was
reading your mind throughout that whole
conversation
I
no my hat tells me these are not real
tears is real snot but why would she
laugh my hat tells me that that that is
real
snot I wish She's So Mean
[Music]
uh I she maybe she was jealous of your
hat probably I said that I said I look
look keep one of the ores I got a hat
wouldn't you say that I have the point
and then I was going to go and tell you
guys that she said I have the point but
then she she wouldn't did
that are you okay you sound like you're
choking I'm I'm
okay I'm I'm
[Laughter]
um it's okay I'm sure Kara will come
around uh you just have to say I've got
the point more often like a you're also
taller than she which would gives you
gives you more more more dominance I'm
higher I'm
higher you're much taller yes yeah you
guys are right have the higher ground
you guys get me I'll never betray you
you guys totally get
me that's my says otherwise but I
appreciate
it is the had thinking further ahead
than I
am it might be or are these false mind
is very powerful like in I do have
intrusive thoughts that I think that's
something you guys should consider I
think things that I don't want to think
sorry I just got a really weird urge I
don't know if I should act on it are you
guys influencing each other in a
triangle we might one person has an
intrusive thought and then I that window
looks so
breakable I wish it
was yeah it just looks it it isn't
actually I know oh I how do you throw
stuff again
Q I don't think they even throwing is
not allowed in this game you can't throw
in this game cuz because you get fined
for littering did you know that oh
really five coin fine for littering wait
how do I test
this I don't know but there is a fine I
believe you I believe everything you
say that's good it's I think it's
because we are the heroes we are
hardwired not to do crime maybe there's
like some Force inner Force stopping us
from doing badad
things that's what it's called
yeah I think it makes sense and
also I thought about this since last
time M did you do the dungeon the first
one I did do you remember how in the
entire dungeon there was not a single
stain yes do you remember how the queen
and the all the people in this town and
country are like oh you have to defeat
the stains they are be really evil and
then they send us on a dungeon mission
and there's not a single stain don't you
think that's the skeletons not count as
a stain the skeletons were not stains
there were skeletons they were just
skeletons wait mm some some maybe they
were in the walls with the King somebody
does somebody did say something weird to
me actually I can take you to them oh I
want to hear weird
things a break in the in the Matrix or
something something like that follow me
[Music]
I'm
fastest
wait the hottest part of the
game
the follow the beacon that is on
her whoa oh
is okay he said something weird oh you
say to you you see oh sh he saying
something weird there's a break
something is happening
NPC talk text cute 3 I feel like this is
a message for us that we need to
decipher NPC talk. text. 3 what could it
mean what could it wait I think that not
everything is what it seems perhaps I
think the three stands for the fact that
there are three guilds that are probably
in cahoots with a
king and that there's only one Guild
that is doing the truth that's what the
text stands for you know text as in like
scripture the the truth yeah talk talk
lying and all NPCs except for us
except it's falling together I
think in this Kingdom a mystery is a
foot and it's to us
this one what is three backwards
three uh ear h e
right wait the number of the
word it is e e could it be saying
QT could it just be calling you a cutie
is it maybe it's not that
deep why would it be on known well yeah
unknown stand for
mystery I've heard of people having
names that basic mean unknown like just
saying what others are saying no name
yeah I feel like I feel like she's she's
putting us on a red herring like on a
wrong path I feel okay I might just be
wrong I'm sorry I just I just I just
she's bargaining I just won't contribute
I guess okay
no no no no no I don't know what's worse
making me feel stupid or making me feel
like I'm betraying you guys like I don't
know make it could have been C I'm sorry
the Hat gives delusions of paranoia and
it does it
does the Hat oh the Hat it's yeah it was
the Hat
sorry it wasn't me it was the Hat I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry too
thank you I'll consider forgiving
you NPC the ansers in the next
dungeon oh it just might
be perhaps it could
be maybe it would be that opens in 2
minutes in 2 minutes maybe it would be
worth exploring that dungeon so that we
can shocked I thought it opened get to
the bottom of this conspiracy
time is for
enough I have to leave you I will not be
doing the dungeon today you're leaving
us to the dungeon I'm sorry I'm
leaving to scared to go in
there oh we'll Scout it for you and then
you can go in there different time it is
with a guide we'll write you a nine-page
document that guide thank you thank you
we'll miss you
healer oh God no we're going to die
don't leave we need you we won't miss
you terribly but it's okay can I can I
lend you the
apple don't worry I wonder I have
something to remember her by wait no
where did it go did you take it from
me where where' it go oh it's in your
trade
box my trade box the chest if you click
on the
chest that's oh what oh what
now oh let's go to Atlant A
Healer do we have food do you have food
I have I have a lot of food I have food
okay that's good wait but I can get more
food if I can cook
it I I think as long as you have enough
to survive the dungeon you should be
fine it's 58 bread enough to survive the
dungeon I think
so are you sure is should be yeah of
them have which makes them
stronger this I think this is the German
bread
too what's the machine called that cuts
bread in ger in
German
Mach
what that's
amazing bread cutting
machine I think yes that's it D how do
you say it is oh it that's that's
is that's is yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
mhm yeah is D is v d is V dust is
V that's wow our star student everyone
she really is the pride of our Academy
I'm so proud I'm like a
sponge she takes in knowledge you have
three extra tiers now to store brain
stuff in so take advantage of it hat
weer shall do I got to pick my next
language carefully
maybe it's the whatever this Li and
talks maybe that's not if you learn this
language you might be us out of this
simulation I think it's ruined for
me I think any attempt to understand him
is ruined you guys maybe not feel too
good about about my decoding attempts so
I just it's
okay oh that's okay I'm sorry
yeah is a dungeon let go the dungeon
okay good luck my fellow Scarlet wands
win it for us there thank for making
money for us thank you thank you for
teaching next wait next let's make a an
MLM
okay in the shape of our hats of true oh
yeah um all right do you have go to the
coast and speak to Corin of the Scarlet
wand as the next
Quest probably not I do how do you say
at the top how do you check oh go to the
oh I do oh I do I do I do okay where is
people
hello okay it's this way how long do the
dungeons take I have about an
hour the first one took like 30 minutes
so we should do this but did you guys
have big
brains the well my Scarlet wands the
well be the th
farewell farewell Fair ma farewell
farewell into the darkness we going in
the same direction it's kind of
awkward which way do we
go
this
this I feel like I
was we must go to the next area the
coast to the coast to the
coast we're in
the so bright sunlight it is
[Music]
bright oh oopsie
yes I got so much money from killing
things
[Music]
which way that is the best way to make
money I mean I only made 50 but oh well
it seems to
be if you can get stronger
weapons
eventually can you hear me has I can
hear you can you hear me
no what okay I will no I do it's Turing
in and out the the horse to horse
connection is not very good no it's not
we it travels faster than the speed of
sound
the speed of horse oh it's
this I think go go to the co go go
go
um oh this the I see the coast oh it's
so
pretty it is pretty way more
horsey he's so cute it's one of people
yeah he has the
Hat wait this is this this is your
people it's the Scarlet W Guy this is
our people
M People investigate the mysterious
light you can see it they're rising from
the waves the locals are quite a stir
with curiosity we are short something of
great import lies therein mayhaps a way
to unlock more of your
memories
mayhaps but you're not mayhaps as is our
duty and our calling we have been
speaking with the locals and gathering
information in Intel to would seem there
exists a magical object known as a
rainbow Coral cluster which would allow
one to breathe underwater we believe
this to be no mere rumor as the Guild
Master was able to find texts among our
archives that corroborate this story
where are you should one obtain such a
what talking to the I'm not getting the
same text wait where am I wait am I just
behind hold
on should should should according to the
text you can be crafted from Rainbow
Coral shards and refine magical energy
you need not concern yourself with the
latter good hero our Guild Master will
gladly provide it but will you Aid Us in
the search for Coral shards that are
iridescent as a rainbow cute so we got
to find Coral shards and bring them wait
he should have said iridescent such as
our coats you know our little capes
they're iridescent too when you move and
they kind of look cheetah
print what oh yeah that's
true they're
teed they I'm going to
understand okay did you
get oh Coral 10 rainbow Coral
shards okay I can swim I can swim okay
okay it's just
this oopsie I fell it is just this we
all have to get our own right oh what me
yeah wait that's not that many uh-oh wow
very difficult I'm getting
them I love cor W oh they respawn okay
pH
oh yeah yeah am I getting them I'm
getting them I got them 10 okay yay I
got them okay okay easy I'm very fast
yeah that's good easy
[Music]
peasy oh God I stood in the
it's okay wait how do you give him the
how do you give him the
shs uh you you just talk to him oh
oh oh oh no oh we have to give it to
rubius all the way back and talk to
there too many people to keep track
of
theg you must go back and forth
wee here
okay oh hor you o
[Music]
ory rubius rubious which one's Rubi it
really feels like RPG actual PCH
Quest all the way back eat my ladies
would you per chance what which oh ow to
to which to what uh form a party so we
can be on call in the with the magical
call device sure that
sounds useful Okie wokie okay let's
let's do it once we get you
R which way this
[Applause]
[Music]
way
way hello
okay hello Oho wait why is your so
little oh never mind it look like a pony
for a second it mean little my average
size it was Tiny what was
that for the
que it's okay oh
hello hello wait what the heck listen K
listen to me listen yes yes I am a
better Queen than better
tender bear tender listen you cannot
support you cannot support
that um I I I have to because like she
seems to have the power to save people
from the scammers I save people from the
scammer too and I also I as destroy the
scammers in fact I actually want to kill
all the scammers oh okay okay all right
I I if if I see it in action I shall I
shall support whoever brings Justice
she's a
scummer she's a
scummer what you mean I got got to
believe me yeah I I mean I would believe
you she did she did however say that she
is um like she's she's I'm
telling you she is
is Bo is this o this you who are you
oh oh
where' they go where's rubius where's
rubious rubius this
way what are you talking
about which way this
way what are they talking
about what are you talking
about not talking about me are
[Music]
they talking about the scammers the
scammers where the heck this
way this way I
don't of course hello we were scared we
must have we could have lost you you did
lose me but I found my way back that's
okay don't worry that's nice oh I've
been expecting you good let's see what
NBC has to say oh do you want to do you
want to read it out loud for me as well
Mo oh
okay she I can't tell what accent this
guy is this the British no he's not the
British one is he no that's not a one
this is the Royal one oh Royal okay so
okay upon receiving word from my
colleague on the coast I immediately set
about making the necessary preparations
for
crafting with these shards you have
brought the preparations are complete
now if you will give me but one moment
whoa ping ping ping and finished I do
say more Arcane prowess astounds even
myself so this is that's okay so this is
a rainbow Coral cluster an object I had
only read of now brought into existence
but don't laugh at me but miss it but my
very hand sorry that's okay
[Music]
ah I can't hear him anymore Rubi is
please I'm sorry
sorry sorry I had a quick screw stuck in
my okay but I should not sh should
not I
[Laughter]
[Music]
someone else do it do do you want me to
like you know like hit your back like
yes yes
please oh thank
you ah but I should not bore you with my
exhaustion you need this exaltation
exalt exaltations exaltations you need
this Warrior Quest do you
not here you go this will allow you to
freely explore the depths of the sea use
it well and to think nothing of payment
or reward as far as I am concerned
curiosity is its own reward quiet no no
I hate that I know it's so
overused ah but there is one thing I
would ask of you and that is your safe
return from this Quest I can think of No
Greater way to repay me now then off
with you I expect good news upon your
return Excel s
exelia
Exel
exelia exlc
or what oh what xlc xlc or what oh what
M or that oh sorry
Junior oh wa that was whoo whoa whoa
whoa that was that was weird that was
really weird your name is Junior my name
is Junior yes short for I didn't know
that what was a short for I shall try to
call uh shorty one more
time okay Darwin
Roosevelt Caprio
Jun wait should Darwin Cecilia and I
should we make a
party oh before we go back I've never
been to a party
before you've never been in a party
before it tickles a little bit but
tickles okay yeah okay I'm eventally
preparing
myself you have to press the T and then
accept but there's there's nothing I
didn't mean to do that on you no no no
oh no we started the Tea train there you
[Music]
go
t let's you guys' favorite tea flavor if
I may ask hot cinnamon spice wo
it's very
good Pinon one I don't know what my
favorite is cuz I put so much honey in
my tea it just tastes like
honey honey sugar
water it's basically sugar water sugar
water you said that Yumm sugar
[Laughter]
water okay uh investigate the Ocean
Temple dungeon then speak to the scet G
okay um uh I don't I don't want to
decide what we should do next so someone
else decide I will stand on my horse and
ready up I will let my horse
Grace okay should we do the dungeon do
we all want to do as three or should we
try and invite we can only have one more
person I think we can have so long as
the dungeon can be completed within an
hour I can do the dungeon um yeah I
think yesterday only took us like half
an hour and we were only three hopefully
this one isn't hard
yeah I'll try calling her one more
time we can have five total we can have
five people five total five total
without a call for the the oh my God my
throat I can't finish the
sentence you can do
it let me see we can shieldy off the
Scarlet
wand please we are summoning you my
calling
she already here run to the who's here
wait where oh not here I meant I just
meant here in this
world yes wonderful she is she she is
hello oh that's not shoting dear there's
a lot of people right now hello hello
hello please call again okay I'm going
call her
again I want in on this
hello hello
ding ding ding ding ding ding D ding
ding
ding hello oh
hello hi hi member of the Scarlet wand
would you like to join us on our
[Music]
Expedition trying to think of what to
say to that oh she's doing the dungeon
of the underworld uh gaura of the red
head
ah I see okay we will discuss I wish you
the best luck we will discuss and call
you
again good luck good
luck uh okay she said call for insurance
next
time um okay I guess she's doing the
other dungeon for
now should we try it as three should we
try okay I think that's okay I think
everyone there's a lot of people online
so I think everyone will
find yeah I think it's okay yeah okay I
think everybody will at least have a
group of
three yeah because I think two is too
little would that be so
impressive and Nissa is online later too
and she's probably going to also have to
do that one again so we can see maybe
I'll be online and then I'll join them
again too okay let's go back to the
ocean shall we get the sea away with us
I don't trust my I'm going to follow
follow
somebody Whoever has the map go
go yeah so we should be fine yeah I
guess that just happens kind of
[Music]
uhoh uhoh where is
[Laughter]
it listen for horse
noises
way yeah yeah back in the okay are you
out okay yes
everybody's going are we all going
together I think so be
group watch out watch out do your horse
have
turbos have
what does it have what turbos oh
turbo yes how could you tell
so
fast oh I have found you again
hello who
aters wait
a I sure hope I regain some memories in
at land oh my
gosh wait that's crazy
coincidence is
[Music]
crazy it is the the Hat of appointed
Point think very carefully if you ever
have given a chance to Dawn the Hat of
pointed points think carefully suck out
your thoughts something like that just
think very carefully it sucks them out
and spits them on someone else with the
red fiery hair I already spent all my
moneyy oh Elizabeth you're here
long oh it's it's I don't know yet
sometimes it makes weird nois but I
forgot isy what's your name your hair is
today my name is Darwin Roosevelt
DiCaprio
junor Roosevelt DiCaprio J yes you can
call me Junior for sure it no don't
worry about it what you want to call me
with a four legged star you can call me
whatever you want I'm just going with
the full you know see I
see are you that's what does up the
Scarlet
wand yes I was also surprised I like
your hands a lot I have a family member
who is part of the Scarlet one
I'm they look like father his cousins
popsicles yeah like Ram yours is Ram
popsicle yeah I
see your yours
is is yours
[Music]
your
I FL was else I'll get it again I think
I'll I'll take part in this dungeon and
then I'll trying money and buying
another chance for a hat oh please don't
drown I don't know how to
drown
Quest you fair maen you break the leg
you can breathe under water
now fair I can I could do I I thought I
could do that already it's okay it's a
nice
[Music]
horse taking the
rainbow I have to hold it in my hand you
can breathe under waterer you are
free as long as it's in my hand I think
so pleasure to meet you you work these
AR this isn't working is it yeah I think
so if I reach this part with my
horse yes journey together to the
dungeon this way on my
meat I'm sure I'll be done by the time I
come back can you watch this for me oh
wait you have the no I'm also going
you're on a mission I was
the can we hear each other in the
water
[Music]
question pardon me you okay I'm okay I'm
just dying you need a headcut yes please
that might give me a little more
life oh my gosh it it smells so good
thank you thank you thank you aome I
hope you feel better thank
you
theost close CL I'm lost I'm
lost where' they go where did they
go the phones work
underwater hold on a second just a
second I'm going to call them but I have
to prepare myself I have phone anxiety
hold
on why why is why is my preparation not
working my my breathing exercises
[Music]
okay I feel ready now to call
wait if you could oh I was called hello
you
couldve um um yeah
hello temp we're both trying to get to
the Ocean Temple dungeon we don't really
know we are in like a little island but
we are on our way there so do not fear
we are going to be there soon but where
am I but I'm not with
you where are you I don't know I'm at
the coast I'm scared are you with the
fire where you tried making meat yeah I
can go back there should we come back to
you
maybe okay we come we're coming back
yeah she was can't believe she killed
her horse okay we'll be the end of
second you killed your horse no no um
yeah let's go
here okay um but yeah no you can't we'll
be there in a second M oh
okay uh you can't you can't grease me up
but if I I have a request if I turn off
at any point would you mind rewinding me
please thank you okay then we're good I
think okay let's go girlfri
M this about greasing up yeah I run on
crank power yeah it's all automated I'm
a
machine so sometimes um I can crank my
windup key
myself but um sometimes I forget and
then if I run out of juice it's kind of
like I go into a
coma
so so if there's any malfunctions like
salt water then sometimes I need
Aid do you want do you want me to know
this am I supposed to be hearing
this it's okay I think I believe in you
yes it's okay moment I don't know how to
hang up you're almost
there yeah I'll hang up we have to crank
that soldja boy I'm sure that that
that'll help
right don't cck the s m like am I
supposed to hear this right now I was
some things oh I just I I you answer the
phone you go no you can't grease me
up yeah you can't grease me I can't
grease you up no you don't need to
grease me up okay do you have your meat
are you ready for a joury yes I'm ready
I have meat too okay let's see I think
it's just right here if we follow those
lamps maybe that wait let's make a
boat a boat a boat that would be safer
for me oh you're right
how do you make boat true
[Music]
true boat I made a boat can I swim I'll
swim behind you guys I don't know how to
make how do you make a bat how do you
make a bat do you want to make your own
or do you want to sit in mine like a
passenger princess only two oh only two
people can sit in one
bow said oh you want to you want to okay
I'll be passeng your princess what if
it's at the bottom of the
ocean oh then we'll have to jump off the
go for a dive
we'll make it really quick so the water
doesn't have time to set I'll cover your
ears so that the yeah the water doesn't
go into your
brain yeah rest automaton
brain oh my boat on land I want
chle this way give me Chipotle I want
Chipotle Chipotle I've never had
Chipotle how does it taste like tastes
like
salt salt in a good way yeah
the the spice tastes like salt yeah it's
salty okay at the
map okay
Donuts feed your passenger
Princess uh okay I'll get you done we
can get you Starbucks is that something
you like like I'll another thing you'll
settle stocking Donuts what's your
favorite donut I can give you plain
PL and uh that's perfect yeah yeah yes
that's good plain donut okay I think
we're going the right way SCA still
behind us can back I cannot hear her I
feel like she would also be contributing
to this dut conversation could she hear
us uhoh
see okay let's be in a party call so we
all oh she is there she is hi there she
is wow huzzah no I swim huzzah this way
this way
I they look like a
ship with the when I have this hat with
a cone yeah with the
hat oh my gosh I can't remember my words
right now I forgot what it's called
there's like a wall around it oh maybe
we have to dive okay let's try World
ready there's also an island over there
is that is that it oh there's multiple
islands are
I plop
I think we have to follow the light
down oh where guide us creature of the
ocean please this way
what this way w
we this way
okay here I how do you swim fast in
Minecraft I don't remember I control
like up down maybe oh no it's space Oh
control it's control yeah control and
space up we can
that's how you fly does it work for
swimming we're going to do a group call
now so that we always can hear each
other oh yeah follow the light down down
we go down
down ringing any bells
here wao something's starting to
itch is that gold
[Music]
shiny that's so cool I don't think I
have the right pickaxe for this never
mind
ooh
ominous here is it
here
oo
oh M can you accept my call so we can
have a group call so we can always hear
each other I didn't get an invit PA oh
dang it so I think you just go into your
own phone call and then you press on
group call on the right
side
oh now we're in the group call GAA would
you want to also join the group call so
we can hear each other when we're like a
little bit separated oh yeah yeah yeah
how do how do I uh so you click with the
phone and then you press on group
call this been falling an awfully
lot w
y thank you nice very nice thank
you nice I wonder if we are going looks
really cool that was really cool like
the wall of water and then we go into
nonwater I think that's very coolly done
it's like
atlantes what that
word does it mean something to me and my
brain at the lamp that kisses oh before
we ready I just want to get some water
one sick okay okay do I have water I do
have water I have a lot of water there's
lots of water here how much water can
you drink at once I think chug drinks
like water and I haven't tried but I
think it's like 14 like red plastic cups
of water is like the max you can drink
before getting water poisoning or
something you can
drown you have water
poisoning isn't it drowning like above
water drowning isn't dry wait what am I
Dr dry dry drowning is a another yeah
it's like if you drown in a puddle sort
of thing no no no that's not what that
is dry drowning is like you get too much
nose yeah yeah yeah you get too much
water like up your nose or in your mouth
and it goes into your
lungs and then you die like after
swimming in the pool yeah dry drowning
bral scary slurp slurp slurp slurp
slurp drink your water ready
I'm
ready go wait I'm not I'm ready
ready ready wait you're not ready oh
you're ready okay
ready ready okay let's go in okay Enter
dungeon did it work did it work did it
work did it work it work it worked
y
o oh my ooh Atlantis oh a preate
strategy meeting what's your special
attack it's the Winds of
civilization 3 AC DPS DPS yes dpsp and
tank wait who's tank who's tank good
tank I believe I am tank you're tank
okay what is she has CC she has Crown
control not me CR control is yours do
mine is like a point I don't actually
know a point she has a point autom
attack she has a point I have a a
different
point
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait there
can be multiple points
made yeah because I'm also part of the
scallet wand so it's
fate this this world is too complex for
me the noise is really deep it really is
I
fell oh my goodness
look at this this perhaps once existing
civilization it's very Mossy I don't
remember that oh wait there's a book
here oh in ages long past there was a
land of Untold
Prosperity its technology and culture
stood at the Pinnacle of civilization
but then who catastrophe struck and what
had taken a thousand years to build was
erased in a single night oh no oh no for
me it's still rendering how did that
happen it start it's still rendering too
it's loading how did it happen that
within one mind it all oh my goodness
are those aircrafts or
Dolphins I think the aircraft I think
that makes the most sense with the theme
wait they're not they're do it's a it's
a boying
747 it's it's like a beluga plane you
know oh I've seen that
enemies oh yeah Dolphins wouldn't
dolphins be a shark's enemy they would
never be Dolphins at the center of
Atlantis that would be highly offensive
oh wait wait wait you are right look at
this the so they're sharks the the the
fin is this way not the other way that
means they're sharks no I think it's a 7
fo7
it might be shark PL it's a
Dreamliner I see I see oh my goodness is
this one a
[Music]
hammerhead or is no I think he's just
this just
ugly hey don't say don't call the plane
like that he's not a
plane he's he's a perfectly normal shk
the plane of the ocean okay wait but
riddle me this if you hold on to the fin
of a shark's back and it swims and then
it jumps out of the water and it goes
like isn't that technically flying and
isn't that technically a
plane don't you think I have a I don't
think it's flying I feel like it's
exertion and then immediately
falling so are you saying if you're on
an airplane and it crashes it's not it's
not flying it is if it is going down it
is not
flying okay good point well cuz that's
why there's flying fish flying fish can
suspend themselves in the air and that's
what gives them the title of flying fish
versus any other fish that will breach
to uh eat something for exle I
mean that makes sense I see okay maybe
they are not
airplanes we we will need further
Evidence lots of good points here yeah
lots of good points made today what that
this is is it a puzzle um Arrow key
Arrow these look like baby blocks and
I'm not sure if I should be offended yet
hey wait nice job oh the Rings the
Rings oh the
Rings they're baby blocks who built this
freaking oh oh we have to like oh okay
but what are we doing what which way
does it want us to I think it has to go
to the middle so you have to wait you
guys can do it too wait can I can I do
it I want to do it is that it Tower what
what is that we have to make a tower I
think green bottom yellow and wait
that's like our colors kind of oh can
not at all can you not St
[Music]
opposite and I
don't I think it has to be so we have to
get
[Music]
the green
bottom how do you move it though yeah
how do you move the one from the middle
away that doesn't make any sense it
won't let you stack them the opposite
way it has to be the big one on big
bottom only one way to
go maybe there's another button
somewhere maybe there's another one a
secret button a secret secret but wait
wait wait wait wait wait no never mind
yes yes wait I got it I think
she's got it then can this one go back
and then oh this one goes
here maybe and it go and then it goes
there and this one goes
there and then you pass this one all the
[Music]
way y we did
it you did it nice thank you for the
brain power civilization
I remember I remembered how it how to
stack baby BL
Memories the memories the
memories what I guess this is some type
of what that do is just for is it just
for
show I think it probably opened the
way
oh just like the airplanes woohoo just
like an airplane
I landed
that the
entire audience clapped all the
passengers clapped when I landed I can
have you ever been on an airplane where
the passengers have clapped yes yes
really yeah yes during a thunderstorm I
always thought that was like a oh okay
that kind of makes
sense okay um please read for USA with
the land sunk to the depths of the ocean
one like think this was the end yet
where one people had been wiped out
another took its place and lived a new
happy and peaceful
life ah this place is so
boring perhaps even a bit too peaceful
I'm getting out of here you'll see day
after day the little girl planned her
Great
Escape
little little girl
okay Escape she really said get me out
of this town this place is boring
oh I'm
remembering oh time trial no parkour
Park parkour
parkour um one of the one of the laws of
the Scarlet wand is that every time you
do parkour you have to scream par oh my
gosh this I I was doing that yesterday
it's like par it was meant to be I was
meant to be meant to do this dungeon
with you so
cool oh do you think this is the reset
maybe is this a dummy lever what does it
do oh it probably if we fail Okay who
wants to go first wait but there's a
thing that might hurt will that hurt
wait no no no it's a blue lever that
turns off something over there oh really
they're color coordinated how did you do
that
oh oh then the yellow one is here oh
wait how did you do that wait what okay
I right clicked
it ah oh wait oh you can't have your
item equipped okay oh yellow is open
yellow's open oh you're right it is open
yellow is I thought it was just a glitch
for
me purple maybe it's purple this one
that's green or do you think that's the
reset oh wait wait that might be green
over there no wait what yeah oh wait a
minute okay so so we have to split up
probably no I
see if you you see if you go over there
the green ones oh wait but there's no
wait can you turn the L back because I
think I removed the blue I might have
done that well I might have removed the
blue oh dear oh I'm stuck okay I think
this is now do you see the purplle
somewhere um over there you see across
the p over there oh all the way there oh
yeah I think I mess it up over there so
I ruined the
blue can we back okay I think no no wait
moment you stay
here where you stay there
here there there no where G is like in
her
Direction I press this button and then
the yellow floor should come back if I
do
this Gove to here oh she can come back
can you so you should go to her are you
able to undo the blue one because I
think that I didn't I make this blue
disappear I don't think so I think that
was just reset I can make the blue
disappear so I will turn on the red now
and then no
wait are
[Music]
you
okay okay the blue is on now yeah so I
can switch the
green so someone can go through
there I will go through uh you should
keep the GRE yeah okay there now I can
turn on the red and so GAA can go to the
purple no to the blue to the blue you at
the blue should I go to the yellow
through this yellow
one um uh let me see wait wait wait look
no I think no no no no no just yeah do
the purple okay should I go through go
there yeah I go through I'm going to
kill kill myself please don't kill me oh
I go hold on I'm scared I don't want
what happen to girl happen to me
yeah okay okay I'm on my way back about
what about the pink one over there oh I
guess it's set up oh I see I see then
which one is that there's three doors
sh is it that one if we get to the check
if one person gets to the checkpoint and
everyone kills themselves we could also
just do that yeah that's we could do
that if somebody's at the start they
could do blue I wish I could I can do
the blue one yeah I'll do it it's like
blue yellow please don't stand on
anything I'm activating it did it work
okay
yeah
nice is it it I think so I will touch
touch touch wait there's no checkpoint
to
touch yes
here okay you can it was nice serving
you can
[Music]
thanks did it work you die yeah I'm here
I'm here with
you ho wow so smart Geniuses of the
Scarlet wand very
impressive and Junior
this reminds me of did you guys watch
that
show where legend of the Hidden
Temple is that is that is that the one
that was in niclodeon is that that is
that that one yeah I remember that is it
like a reality show all the faces like
in the show yeah it's it was a yeah it
was a reality show where kids would
essentially do exactly what we're doing
right now and then they would win really
lame prizes like
and roller blades yes stupid
stuff hey that's something yeah like
imagine squid games but they don't die
and they're all
kidsat tuna sponsored by Sun and then
their fight and then they are get really
hungry and it was called The Hunger
Games yeah they grew up and then became
the hunger game then they became the
cast of The Hunger
Games in season 2 episode 4 Jennifer
Lawrence took part in the temple show
she was on the silver monkeys team the
purple monkeys are are you guys messing
with me or did she
really no she was there what she was
cilia says that it sounds like it's true
I know it's not wait Google here I need
a try to deep l i mean what what what's
deep L Jennifer Laurence deep under the
ocean help can I Blast for this lore
real quick oh my gosh she she is good at
lying
wait
what o Challenger
approaches there was no nice way to put
it the girl was sick of the underwater
Kingdom and she tried constantly to
leave it behind no they got me
again yet with the guard being ever
watchful this was anything but easy
she'd probably been caught by 100 time
100 times by now oh wow even so giving
up was the last thing on her mind each
failure instead served as inspiration
for a new attempt am I just going about
this the wrong way yeah I know what I'll
do next and so another day of planning
[Music]
begin she was busted oh you'll PL I mean
this
person this young girl is planning
little girl little little girl is a a
planner I respect a plan honestly
sometimes you got a plan what's all this
look at this mumbo jumbo is this another
puzzle it what appears looks like mouse
trap it looks like you got to do stuff
over there to unlock stuff here and then
there's treasure over
here what's going on oh that's so cool
what is this so I think we have to make
the guy go here the the the the guy that
stands here in this little trap if we
press this button he follows the arrows
that's so cool wait that is actually so
cool so now we have to make it so that
where do we want him to go do we want
him to die in here uh we want him to go
in here I assume yeah is he going to die
if he does that no he probably activates
this so that it opens and we can
activate it so it open something else
okay
okay okay can we interact with it
oh okay what do you think happens when
he goes on the gold do you think that's
a wall what if it electric
GI yeah should we try test round test
round send him send him go forth
Warrior oh oh he has to light them up
okay he's stuck he has to light them up
and most likely you can't have him go oh
wait no he's going over it multiple
times and it doesn't turn off okay
oh oh but you can't do you can't do all
of them oh no no it's just because he's
out right now how do you oh okay reset
he's an Atlantean
guard so okay so we have to do it in
advance so he touches all the gold
[Music]
ones my brain hurts I understand now so
should you
go which way should he go maybe this
way this way
way here go here it goes like this here
and then did I go through
here and then here I can't remember what
I just
did and then it goes like
this through the
gold this way wa oh I think what about
this way like here
M here here wait no no no what I do what
did I do hold on hold on never mind
never mind no you're right you're right
and then he goes to the right here yeah
and then he goes here he goes through
this one yeah and then he goes here and
he goes here and then I think here yeah
and then you go
there and then
here okay yeah send him let's s send him
wait which one wa I don't know which one
send him and which one reset the right
one oh right one right the correct one
the the correct one
okay that's so
[Music]
cute wait but
still oh oh W okay it opened this but
there's nothing in there maybe it opened
it on the other side too it's a it's a
it's a lever like the floor is a oh it's
a it's a lever a button is it oh wait
does someone have to stand on it or
something what happened over here it I
think it opened
this
did no it
didn't there's a chest yeah o can
someone stand on the pressure
plate yeah I'll do it but I think we can
just send another guy and make him go
this way instead I think you have to
stand on a pressure plate then I stand
on this one and somebody gets the
treasure maybe okay I'll stand on it let
me see let me know what what
happens oh are you standing on it I'm
standing on it nothing happened okay let
me try sending him again oh numbers you
see this
mov in the first dungeon you remember
this was like you have to fill the thing
up oh
is it that
again I think so cuz the lights just
went out what what turn them on we need
to hit it five times to open the door 1
2 3 4 5 oh did I mess up should I not
have done that blue two green we're
missing
two wait what numbers are you seeing I
saw it light up I didn't see the works
the blocks are the numbers we have to
have all of them light up for that door
to open so 1 2 3 4
5 two them are open
for now none of them are one
two this there should be oh wait is
there's an arrow here maybe there's
something up here
too did it turn a light on okay turn two
there oh there's something up
here
ah I think it's a is it a mze what is
this what is this oh it's another
pressure another here
but is this water the water water it's a
water elevator no is it is it TI
H okay so water comes out here we
probably still have to do something here
where you guys were so we definitely did
the first one
correct I think we have to activate this
what is this here let me see three of
them were you able to do anything when
you pressed anything here I think it's
the the thing over there is what made
these three light up can somebody come
stand on this so I can go up the
waterfall okay I'll stand on it pretty
[Music]
please thank
you
oh what's up there do you want to go do
you want right to I want up these yeah
please wait for all party members before
proceeding it's a door but oh is it the
last thing you have to do oh maybe it's
the last thing
so now we can see what's up
there wait do we just have to make him
go in a
circle if he goes through the the dots
twice oh a little guard man oh is that
it I feel like maybe we can make him
walk here and then we can make him stand
on the platform wait but if we want him
to go in do you want him to go in a
circle cuz can I can I try making him go
through it just to see if it works at
all go through it real quick okay after
an idle
meeting actually no I'll hold it I'll
hold it I'll hold I'll hold off the
meeting just let's see if this if he can
stand on it at all
[Music]
there's no way
what and it now we
go wait but what about what about this
thing I think that is a treasure that
might be something extra but I don't
really know are you running thing
here oh my head is
spinning I think I don't know how though
because like here is an arrow as well
but that Arrow automatically goes up
there so I don't know like I don't think
we can go in here right
ow no no we can't can we stand in his
way so you can't oh should we try that
can we not switch this when
it's oh
can you tell me what happens when what
happens when I stand on this does
anything happen anywhere no oh wait do
it
again okay I'm not standing on it oh
never mind never mind there's nothing
and now I am standing on it no there's
nothing do the pressure point turn the
arrow somebody has yeah can you wait is
it pressure If you reset it can these be
changed okay let me try turn them off
yeah I'll
try cuz maybe after it's reset can you
change it uh no you
can't okay well so there's L lanterns
here right here and when we turned all
three golden squares this opened up and
then on the other side there's let's try
what you said where we like Loop it so
he walks over the gold more than once
make him go in a big cgle okay yeah
he is in a loop oh no that didn't work
because earlier we tried making him go
over it and he kept walking over it but
nothing happened wait oh this can't
happen
wait no no wait
what okay let me try standing on this
one more time what
happens I messed it up oh is GAA can you
check if the one that's the Pink Arrow
is now editable the one that is like in
the
middle it is not
oh we need to find more
lights
yeah oh what about that
one what about this one here that's the
check oh that's just the that's just a
checkpoint I'll do some
investigating outside the box everybody
split up
uh it's time to look for I'm seeing
something
shiny
[Music]
shiny oh there's a golden wall
entrance oh oh I think that's just for
the the backing of the treasure like ooh
gold oh uh girls what if we reset
we make him turn on all the lights yeah
and then we stand on the no I just don't
know what it what happened when we stood
on the pressure plate you know don't
know what that did oh this one on this
this one cuz I feel like this one opened
up this
door don't get it the
FL pleasure plates have to do
something what do they do should we try
this again let's just see what happens
exactly okay so let's make him go
through all golden ones so go here did I
messed it I I feel like I edited it but
I can't remember what I did did you guys
fix it it's
okay
remember um so he goes like this and
then he goes up here and like this and
then like this and then like this and
then here and then here and
then how many plates are there it first
here first goes through here like this
way should I edit it goes this way then
he goes here then he goes here I'm sorry
for making fun of the baby block game I
want to bring it
back and then this way try wait wait
wait wait I'm sorry I changed something
I shouldn't have I changed something I
shouldn't have sorry okay he he he goes
this
way yeah can I press oh my gosh wait I
can't count
okay yes okay
[Music]
yes the thing is like we've already
figured it out we're trying to go for
the extra treasure yeah right want
treasure not everybody can get oh yeah
you're right yeah oh we it's just for
the
treasure oh oh wait this isn't going to
work loop I messed it up I messed it up
what I
do do you think if we go through the
doorway it'll bring us to the next room
or is it in here yeah I think so I think
this one is just treasure so
let's
uh I think I missed okay so I think it's
like this so he goes like this this this
this this this imagine there's a button
back here one this through here here
here all the ples are W what I'm
thinking but we can't get to this one up
here and then there I touched the
shiny I'm okay are you okay yeah
yep okay if we can't make it we we just
keep going it's fine all we can role
play getting the rure
[Music]
yeah oh
no wait have him stand there wait did I
do that why did did I do this wait wait
wait wait why is he Loop oh do we want
him to Loop do we intend for this to
happen um looks it only lights up one at
a time
like um and send him in
here uh could I could you stand on that
platform for a second in the middle one
this one yeah just let me see if
anything
happens we have to make him stand in the
one next to
me yeah but nothing happens when you
stand on it so I don't know if that's
really it you know yeah and when we made
him stand in this one all it did was
open up this
one if you well we can try
okay let me see somebody save him he's
in a loop I killed him I killed him he's
fine okay so let's do this do you want
have we got have we tried getting him to
go in
here in the middle we send him in this
one somebody stands there he stands
there does that make sense does that
make sense
um do you want him to go in the which
one I don't know I guess there's no
point because some because somebody
could just stand there I don't yeah okay
let's make him go in the right in the
right
one un he has he's like special in some
way my brain oh my God we but if he
goes okay so he goes he starts here he
goes here and then he goes here and then
he goes here
here he on this
one and this one and then this one
standing on this this one this one this
one okay
remember uh he has we have not made him
stand on the middle but we have made him
stand on the right and when we made him
stand on the right the middle door
opened
up but we can try it again mid wait but
do we yeah oh wait but he's going to
Loop now didn't we want him to go into
the
middle oh he's he going loop again yeah
he's going to
[Music]
Loop
okay
sh everyone's
waiting okay let's see
this oh like that
wait okay that was something we needed
to do I guess it did doing but nothing L
up and how come you didn't how come you
didn't complete the
thing wait wait undo undo oh does it
completely reset everything is that what
it does wait no it doesn't completely
reset it because oh my gosh I'm stupid
do that I get it we have to make him he
has to light up
everything Bing three let's I get it I'm
stupid I get it but he can't go this way
now if we want him to go through here it
can't be the way that I add it so it has
to be here turn here up here okay up
here up here and then and here wait am I
okay to change this I wait what I think
it completely resets everything wait can
I do thing can
I hold on he can't we want him to go
through here so we can have him do the I
don't see how he can go to the middle
and also you know what I mean yeah
because also do the Because unless we
find a different
way go
here go try
something how come it how come if we go
here it doesn't do the ding but if he
does it it does the ding yeah it's
messed up he has favoritism gr cooking
hold on what's with that okay okay
[Music]
wait
no wait no he oh wait wait it was
almost uh just reset it and then move
this
one I think you got
it wait no
wait I legitimately don't see I don't
understand I don't see how he can go
through everything oh wait wait like
this okay do it again wait go through
everything and go into here or go into
where oh the
middle but he has to do all of
them I don't think he can he's not going
to get that one though oh he's not going
to get that
[Music]
one
wait see it does the ding if he goes in
there but what is the ding doing it's
not lighting it
up I'm firing in all cylinders and
nothing's happening what if we um um
light let wait should we try working
backwards so this one has to be like
this uh and this one can go like this
this I don't don't think he's supposed
to go to the middle
what to the very middle I don't think
he's supposed
to yeah if he goes to the very middle
then we can we could just keep going we
can't get all of them if he goes to oh
that middle If he if we do that middle
then yeah we can keep going we just
won't get treasure we won't be
cool what I want you want the treasure I
want the treasure okay okay let's use
our brain power okay so we want him to
go here in the middle so he starts
this has to happen this has to go here
um and then he goes like this like this
like this like this like this was good
this was all perfect the only problem is
I don't know how he can go
here if wait which way do you do you
want him to go into this one or do you
want him to go into this one yeah yeah
where you no no no the the one you want
him to go the middle still yeah okay
yeah but he also should touch all the
golden
[Music]
once oh I think it looks like this no
no I mean chat says it's possible but I
don't I don't see how it's possible
because they hit all of them and also go
into the
middle
yeah yeah cuz you can't do this cuz
it'll go there yeah I don't think it's
it's I think it's actually impossible I
think this is the wrong I don't think
he's supposed to you canot change it
while it's moving no I
yeah
um he just does the ding thing for him
cuz he's special so he's supposed to go
into here and somebody goes into here
and we just have to figure out what it
is that both of us going into there
activates I hope it's not a thing where
you need more than three
people no no they said it's everything's
doable with just one person with one
okay nice yeah
actually I don't know how the puzzle
earlier would have been possible but I
doubt there okay I'm going to reset it
so that he goes into the F right one
okay well that one
though oh wait what was it he goes this
way this is kind of easy who says this
is easy they think it's easy cuz they
don't actually get
it are they fibbing they're
fibbing are you uh guys do we try
standing on this platform while he's
standing on that platform have we tried
that have someone standing at oh I don't
think we did should we try that does it
have to do with the story at all the
story you want to try okay I'll stand on
it at the same time okay let me just uh
move
him I guess it okay I'll try standing on
it and nothing happens on he stands on
it and go will be your eyes looking at
the lights I will what am I supposed to
do send him uh no just look if the light
anything happened to the lights nothing
has happening now nothing's
happening wait is no one sending
them here I'll send do you want me to
send
him I was yeah send send him yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah wait but the do
no wait wait wait wait wait you miss it
you didn't miss it wait wait wait what
happened what was that he went onto the
thingy did it not light
up hold up it did it just doesn't no it
didn't why didn't this one light up hold
on does any want to light up when we
standing on
this wait what wait what happened wait
hold
on why did he go this way wait wait wait
he's supposed to go this way why was
this one oh hold on wait let's try let's
try that
again wait what why is it change oh no I
did that okay I'm going to try it again
no no no no no no no this
works cuz now yeah left this is the s
D ding D wait something light up by
thing this are you talking about this
yeah dude yeah
dude okay we
have three still just three what up what
do this do wait wait
wait what happens if I stand on this
okay wait don't do
anything stand there now stand on the
middle one but mum is already standing
on one yeah I'm on the middle one the
one outside what one
outside like I my chat is gaslighting
me I saw people in my chat that didn't
realize like never
mind H I think they thought we were just
trying to get the three of them to light
up but didn't realize we that was like
the first thing we
did wait what if
you stand on one at the color B no the
one at the color B just opens up this
first door I think I'm going to stand on
it anyways let's see you didn't mean
this one nothing
happens this is just for this door I was
for the previous puzzle I don't know why
that was wait does it have anything to
do with this one go
go no you can go can you figure out this
puzzle he's definitely supposed to go
well I don't is he supposed to go he
must go
here but no this is just if you don't
want
that where is it is it even
that I don't
[Music]
know's dungeon wasn't this hard what the
heck
man wait I saw people say other remember
already cleared it wait
wait no no that would be too
complicated guys not it's not guys guys
there's arrows in the Maze too we have
to make him go all the way around here
shut up oh we didn't I even went oh it's
a maze but then I was like oh maybe
look oh can you reset can someone reset
the thing the guy wa where do you see
can it didn't even give us any hint that
it would include the previous puzzle
though doesn't walking through a door
usually signify that you know that
puzzle is
over wait what the hell it's from out
here we have okay okay okay we got this
guys got
it okay um so we make him
go
here send him out this door maybe maybe
but how does he okay so we make him go
here
instead right is is he is he lined up so
he would actually walk here wait go
where go where here where could I
standing oh so he goes this way he goes
this way you want him to go out there oh
my God but he still has to go through
the all the colors doesn't he okay so he
goes like this I can't think I need to
go to
an okay okay okay it's okay I can't
think like this oh gosh
thought it wouldn't take an hour it's
okay okay I'll be back I thought it
wouldn't it's okay we're I thought we it
was too difficult it was CU you you guys
have fun yesterday isn't it oh are you
are you going to go to The
Mastermind are you going to Google oh no
I'm going to just go to an island
meeting I'll be right back okay I'll be
back do you want us to wait for you no
no feel free to consider thinking of
what the solution could be fre oh okay
we will ponder let's let's try going
this way and try if we can fix it
make this man walk through this hole so
we can get that damn box I'm tired of
waiting for this puzzle man puzzle man
walks I was wondering what these little
doors were
for then he walks through and he hits
another light but he can hit the light
that's that's fine this is no we want
him to hit this
one are you kidding me oh that's what
you mean oh yeah okay okay yeah and then
somebody has go here I'm going to go
here to see so once he's okay I'll
activate the green oh God okay are you
safe I am
safe okay so he goes over
there know we has to get past the yellow
Bridge we have to turn the the
red oh this is
complicated okay um um yeah can you
go oh oh can you activate the blue one
for me
[Music]
meow and then I hit the blue again oh
the green right uh I think the yellow
one yellow one you go through are you
safe you can go through I'm fine okay
and now go through the yellow one and
then activate the blue one there the
blue yellow one blue yellow okay so now
he will go here so we're going to have
to do that while he's walking I
think oh my
God shall we just try let's just try
okay I think you should handle these
colors on that side and I'll I'll I'll
carry the handle the colors in the
beginning
okay uh I think I remember yes okay so
he's going to come in here he's going to
walk over here and we're going to use
yellow
first where's yellow can you reach
yellow oh it's there where yellow oh see
I can reach okay don't do it yet okay or
or actually can you do it once just so I
see what
happens oh yeah okay okay okay that's
and then hit it again and then he goes
through ah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I
think this is good isn't it yeah I think
so okay I'll press
I think this will work I will press the
button and I will walk with him press
the button let's do
it close to the
collors he can pass your lasers you he's
very
strong I'm pressing he's walking but
he's first he's walking over the first
three Golds ooh he's walking he's
walking he's walking okay now he's going
to come to the
Maze and then he's going to he's going
to go through the maze oh my
goodness okay he's going to be where you
are oh my goodness and then he's going
to go this
way yeah I think this is it oh my
goodness that must be it that's I don't
think we have to do anything let me see
if it lit up
the yep yep that's it here just has to
light up one more
s it worked it worked wait a minut but
you can come to us SCA I'm here oh
you that it's lit up
but
yay you bigger than their hats
it's it's what is it mixed oh it's of us
we all get one
right we all get one right I'm not it's
reflect o wait how do we use this is it
movie
time not yet now we have to go through
the middle oh okay right right that's at
the end wait how do one more phas what
do we how do we use this can you sing it
for us if you want to you don't have to
uh do remember how it goes um oh hry
Amia I remember how it goes oh she has
Amnesia I have amnesia I don't remember
now we want him to stand on the thingy
right because we all have to get up
there yeah so just turn that one send
him but what the heck I'm sending am I
is it ready uh is it I think so
uh is it yeah it is
ready is
it as long as he comes this way yeah
yeah I think he's coming
oops I cannot believe that's what that
was no wonder we couldn't I know I would
never I no I wouldn't have either I
would have assumed like why would it be
stuff from the previous
level but that door that or that opening
that Arc shaped perfectly for I
estimated I un estimated how much credit
they're giving us I would I thought like
there's no way they would do something
from the level before no cuz I'm always
like it can't it's not as complicated as
I think I'm like looking stupid it's so
it's probably so easy but I'm making it
so complicated and it's making me look
so
stupid no I to be fair the it was a bit
complicated oh that was it oh that
was it could be your powers I think it
is cut scene
time down stronger I got to download
it you've recovered a portion of your
memory
stronger I
remember um okay should
we
wait so she's ready oh you all want to
play it at the same
time yeah yeah okay I'm downloading it
sorry one second one second
that puzzle it wasn't even that oh when
you think about it it wasn't even that
hard if we oh you know what to do it's
not hard but yeah the puzzle itself
isn't hard but using your being like I
guess we're so used to
playing video games this felt more like
a real puzzle compared to like a video
game puzzle you know yeah there were no
giant arrows pointing Us in the right
direction no in-game Maps so no light
tricked us just a just an AR Arch thingy
perfectly sized for him I guess us too I
was wondering what the mini doors
were yeah I didn't even register it to
be honest I download can I point
something out though again no stains
just saying the kingdom that's fighting
the stains and trying to make us destroy
all of these D I'm tell like they're in
the
walls they in the walls they wear the
golden Stepping Stones
yeah okay I'm ready if you guys are
ready
I
ready I got to turn my music off okay
I'm
ready everyone ready cut scene want a
countdown yes please oh you want meat
who who yeah you you countdown you no
you know I feel like gura should do it
oh G should yeah that's good H uh a
three a two a one
[Music]
go this
stinks I'm out of
here what the heck what the what the
heck yep every time time King's force
field is just too
strong that's when I had an
idea I may not be able to break through
but I bet that Geyer's old Fork could do
it bre break and then I'll be
free or so I
thought
uhhuh wow
[Music]
I see what this thing can
do wait does that
mean did you destroyed L wait did you
destroy I did
not finally entire civilization My Story
begins here
oh my
gosh why did I think you were like the
queen of Atlantis you were just a little
kid that
stole that just stole the king's
Trident he wasn't using it anyway I
thought you were like royalty or
something no that's not true didn't you
see I was I was I was in charge of
multiple different events I Banquets and
and organized paperwork and and Royal
meetings were you a
secretary no I'm I'm I'm I'm just a I
was a baby I was a I I I didn't steal
anything wait so I could have asked but
I didn't you borrowed just borrowed I
borrow so you stealing their their
protection Weapon made it so that
everything broke
afterwards
oh and that's how I don't think that's
what happened they didn't have anything
to protect themselves and you made it
really easy for the enemy to destroy
because you took their weapon no they've
got a force fail didn't you see they
they're safe the whole patched up
afterwards then explain this quick say I
have a
point I
um you know I don't remember remember I
wonder if we're going to have to wait
for the next episode to uncover the rest
of the
mystery oh she has a point good point
good a good us have a point a that's
true
yeah well that was fun toit my brain
hurts it was nice to visit home oh that
was lovely a little brain fry but oh
well I'm mad at how simple it ended up
being well simple but it's very
complicated it's
complicated anyone colors it's a type of
thing that when you see it you see it
but when you don't see it you're very
confused yes exactly when you're in the
thick of
it yeah then it's kind of when it all
falls on your
shoulders where are we now oh we're back
at this place yeah we we want to leave
do we have to swim back
out I think so yeah you want to go to
the tavern once we go to the tavern I'm
going to eat some mutton and then I'm
going to using a horse just to get to
there want what do you mean time money
time is
okay oh wait give me give me off this
thing give me off this thing is XP in
the world of
[Music]
RPG oh wait you guys can hear hear me
we're in a
call I was
just back here get hooking back here
what do you
doing I'm just reflecting on
memories just
made reflect just like
the she gets it a boat oh there's so
many boats I don't think we're the only
ones in that D we weren't really the
only ones that thought of
boats no but that's why you have the
coral so you can leave under the water
can I be the passenger princess again
what's the name of the one who drives
the
driver captain Oh that's the I'm the
captain please call me Captain oopsie I
laughed at you for what I just did I
laughed at you and then I went and did
the same thing you think these are other
people's boats oh wait wait actually I'm
going to take this boat so that it's
probably someone else's so that they
have to swim yeah perfect how do use Bo
again are we the first ones click oh
there's no way we were the first ones
through that no there must have been I
saw people say others got through it and
we were sad but did they do the extra
stuff or did they just keep going no
clue I don't
know my gosh wait you're such a fast
swimmer first one's with the treasure
ah are we yay okay I feel much better
about myself oh my good because we got
we we could have finished really early
but we decided to go the extra mile
exactly we got
reflect Tak I Recollections what are we
supposed to do with
it go to the tavern and we blast our
Tunes is that what you do you can blast
Tunes at theuk box we can play it here
too or we can go back let's go back
let's go back let's go to the tavern
Tavern
wasn't as far
as you guys know after you work out and
then your your muscles feel like tingly
and
weak that's how my brain feels
[Music]
right hey hello Fair me
that yeah oh my
God like no our brain is going to get
stronger now my name is Junior it should
yeah Will strong sink further into the
future Junior oh my lady you are being
ambushed oh my lady they really love you
here I'm getting my butt kicked
Queen I will follow Wherever You Lead
okay follow the sounds of the
horses way Victory
music is the previous
did the previous dungeon have a song
reward I so oh I did not get it but I
didn't pick it up I remember seeing it I
don't remember it wait where are you
guys
leaving I didn't even see it if there
was
one wait where what are these great hats
you guys
have uh the tavern is
gambling oh you can gamble it's the
gacha gacha I got it on my first try
oh my gosh lucky you that
hat all right let's play this bad boy
want to listen to some
tunes it might be if you haven't in the
dungeon it might be a spoiler oh oh
spoiler alert
hi hi I think can
dungeons no it's okay I I have a party
later also have not cleared it but thank
you fair maiden of course Scarlet wand
yes Scarlet wand together strong what's
listen Okay I'm going to mute my own bgm
wait I can't hear it oh because I turned
the didn't we turn oh music off wait oh
I hear it oh my
gosh it's not style it's just
it let's
go I got good sub subwoofers here
yeah oh my God what beautiful voice is
this what clubbing feels like where are
the
[Music]
stes W St
light oh that's so pretty
that's enough how can I sell this for a
million dollars can we sell it doing but
can we sell it
yeah oh never mind I was wrong I didn't
see the I didn't see U moris one I just
saw these the non-fiction and St again
you can buy them but you cannot sell
them oh wow lame shop can we sell
anything to be honest
don't know shopkeeper
fa although she's she's not even we
should ask her to come back she's just
selling lottery tickets her coin
[Music]
o how much money do you
895 coins you to do a trade I to gamble
would you would you would you like to
give me 300 I can give you 64 Mangrove
blocks no what I don't want M girl BL
steal I have a you want I have 2 how
many coins do you guys have I have
59 what how are you guys all so low
because we
d32 I could I haven't figured out how to
gamble gambled in our life we have never
gambled in our lives I would remember
gamble I want a cute hat like this like
you guys have oh got buy one buy one
here with this guy yes I just buy them I
just buy them no no it's a gamble you
you it's not guaranteed but you can do I
do the Box yeah oh God
no this seems like a mistake I get it
did you buy one yeah oh that's a lot of
money what you get what you get what you
get I choose oh oh God oh God oh God oh
God I got construction supplies box oh
okay yeah
yay y
good job good job turning our money into
more
money I have the how you do that should
we try
show no I haven't I no I haven't it
better not be the lottery
tickets no no no no no no no no no no do
you remember the library I think do you
remember where it was was it here it is
taking me to the library this is this is
sketchy it is this
way yes I shall follow you you wish to
Triple your earnings yes I do that
sounds nice I wish to Triple mine no
quadruple mine I join a party and then
you can join a party call Nissa yeah
okay I'll have to leave later but I'll
Jo for now I have to leave in like
soon uh yes I'm in quick quick quickly
double quick quick quick quick is where
did she go oh oh yeah I don't know where
she is in the pit pit okay okay I'm
coming we're coming okay to the giant
Yellow
spers we're
coming oh so ready to to gamble all my
money away yeah let's do it can both do
it you don't know that you could be
making all of your money back and then
some that would be nice I want to get a
cool hat too really you can get a cool
hat I don't remember what it is I don't
remember what the fit is what is the pit
the Pit's not this right the pit no no
the the other one uh yellow one yeah the
yellow the EM coin people Fair Str oh no
I know who you are now F do you know
where the pit is the pit oh the pit the
pit I remember but I can't remember
that's okay junior is is a horse girl
name again P what happened I don't
remember I I don't remember I don't
remember what you named me but my name
today is Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio
Jr Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio
junun was that it
pun there's a side quest for a
res oh here it is Bow Bow Fair bow
bow I think they ended the
party weed I think it but m
is
she's oh it appears that my party has
found it but I have been distracted by
your beauty
oh beautiful Ramy fingers ROM popsicle
Fingers um so we
can
with we wait for good good
B I'm so sorry I cannot listen to
everyone at once where are you guys we
are calling for thou Fair Maiden where
are you what do you see I am around the
Coliseum huh okay drive right around the
Coliseum try finding the white yellow
building the
yellow yellow building around the
Coliseum oh God how close to the
Coliseum no the Coliseum it's not at the
Coliseum wait oh that's okay you guys
you guys do that and I I'll go how Cho
what what's going on I've done a full
circle
stand still I will come to you come to
me choose your
color where what do you see I see trees
of
green enter your that bar and then
take okay oh I was not going to find
this
okay yeah okay I I bet on
two oh that's the pit blue and
red ooh wait both yeah to to hide hide
to hide my chances you can just go for
the next one we'll we'll let them we'll
let them feel the odds out and see Canon
firing the Cannon's
firing okay oh
wow okay
[Music]
oh it might be over for me if this is
col you my mind what color did you
do I did red and
blue I picked
green green always
wins it's uh it's in the
cards he seems like he seem like good
odd except if it's red I would have lose
my mind
wait are you betting on which one
stays
yeah oh my gosh how did you bet Nissa
just 100 wait how do I get it how do I
get it okay M you can talk to him you
got it automatically you can talk to him
and then we make a bet and you talk to
him again color you want to B don't
decide how many coins to bet the again
and will start firing taking out SP
colored sequences with each shot after
six shots only one squirrel remain
players who bet on winning players will
receive a payout based on the multi
multiplier listed for the color they bet
on
okay
bet I'm going to
bet okay I bet okay so red is times 10
yellow okay I'm going to bet green
yellow I did
Green how many green I'm going to do 100
on all I'm doing
100 wait how do I do this how do I do it
I don't know how Minecraft works okay
right click it and then do you what do
you see do you see the paper and the
little window see I see paper yes
there's there's a little line and you
have to type in 100 or whatever you have
to be really fast and then you just
press on the that's it's over that's
that's you have to join next round okay
it's okay I'll help you it'll be fine
it's this one was the bad one take the
paper take the right grab from the right
oh I see I missed it
okay
green this is let's go any
color
green which color wait which color did
you do not despair believe
o green will win I believe in it mhm
uhoh now watch
this I'm watching watching very
closely oh I would have won woo 500
coins I'm out of money oh made narissa
ravencraft could you lend us some money
maybe wait I want to we are one I have
to become I have to become Ren joing the
game choose color I'm sorry why do I now
this time this time I'm going to do
green I'm going to try blue this time
just blue okay I think I did it green oh
okay
okay or should I do two should I do two
different
ones I N Go all I don't know try
it I need money I'm so
poor how how did you all become poor
you're looking at it I probably did this
the wrong way I reversed it a little bit
that's okay took all my money that's
okay all right I voted on Blue what did
everyone else vot that's okay I did not
do that the right way that's all good
that's all good build character if you
if you picked up the papers then you did
it right no I didn't
know oh
no oh boy
oh that's not
good oh I really I really I really I
really I really I
really what did you bet on what did
everyone bet on green and green no what'
I do I did green and
blue okay green shall
win come on Green
if I lose this I'm doing one on each
color oh Green in the bag let's go I I
make some stuff back maybe it's not it's
not totally over okay that
sucks you kidding
me no freaking
way I think if we give back our Quest we
get some money I lost 50 but it's okay
I'm going to go and get some money cuz
I'm broke
go get some money wait how much did I
have before this didn't I have I had
like 500 something R I think I lost I
lost
50 what color did I just vote
on I don't
[Music]
know always fun now now now try Mr Mr
Big firing Cannon surely I can't lose
this time one of each one on each go
yeah let's go I can't lose now yeah you
have to
win surely I don't even remember which
one I did shoot me now which one did I
do this is my last my last one I don't
know that's what I'm saying I don't
remember what what color i i y I'm not
sure I think if you press T you should
see what you
did no it just tells me how many coins
it says how many coins yeah oh never
mind okay
okay wait if it's red and you bet one on
red what do you get if it's 10 times and
you get
a that's
bad
[Music]
that's
the the D
[Music]
did you bet red M I bet
yellow I got 10
points 1 time 10 oh my God that's it I
can eat tonight I'm so happy that's it
did that's it for me that's it I know
what I'm doing tomorrow but that's it
for today yeah I have
1,495 coins let's go don't tell FAA
she'll send you a lottery ticket yeah
she'll be like o this girl sure will
fall for my little I in your pocket
narissa I wish to sell you something it
might be oh I buy a lot of ticket from
fa
oh I'm going to go turn
my I'm I'm going to go
goodbye
goodbye wish to make it
bed what
that's that's that's
it hello
bookie oh yeah I can I see multiple
bookies I
see all right it's okay it's so easy to
make money back it's so
easy here book you sit in my
lap oh wait you're kind of in the way
you're you're in the way
if your name is in the
way one more I forgot about the
background music that's
okay I think this is better without
suspenseful or the music is not
suspenseful let's just stare what did I
do
green
okay okay
fine it's going to be
blue it's going to be
blue no there's still a chance it might
be
blue you never
know dang
it you never know you never know you
never
know okay that's it for
today for me from
me I'll do some grinding later I'll I'll
kill a bunch of stuff and I'll make it
back and have more money than I had at
the start of today I think I had like
700 something
today thank you all for joining me again
I don't know if I will be here tomorrow
or the next day I don't know when I'll
be back just again just kind of depends
I do want to do at least like one or two
other streams this week that is not
just this but this is kind of the main
thing going on right
now yeah yeah yeah thank you all for
watching I'm going to go eat more
food and sleep
thank you thank
you go enjoy whatever the everybody else
is doing
goodbye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye goodbye goodbye bye bye get lost
[Music]