[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
burn
Butterball hello
sorry I got a little carried away
it was a little weird guys it was a
little weird
apologies
my apologies
how are you guys hi it's it's cloudy
Maury
we're playing we're playing jump King
that's for the usual Maybe
I'm jumping into the jumping into the
jet
hi hello that is weird why are you here
I'm working out right now get those
gains you can do it
I believe in you
Ah that's right I need to plug in
the controller because
can you imagine playing this game on
keyboard I bet you can I think it's been
done on Speed Run via controller in the
past
[Music]
let's see what happens
and there it goes
and there goes the sound see this is
always what happens when I plug in the
um controller
it just goes ah yes there we go
the computer goes ah yes you want your
controller to be the audio output and
I'm like I'm like no
are you stupid
on what in what Universe would that be
what I want computer
how am I doing
I'm great I just had a bit ahead of a
bit of a meeting that I had to take care
[Music]
take care of all good preparations
happening
um right now so don't don't you guys
worry uh I'm sitting in VC right now but
um I know from from Bay at least uh she
has a chatting stream she's got to do so
she'll probably huh no don't turn on the
PlayStation
oh boy
um do I have to restart the [\h__\h] game
I swear to God man
um they has a chatting stream she has to
she might come afterward here let me try
this again jump King try it again
don't turn on the PlayStation I wanna
oh my God
Madness
his Madness
so yeah she might join afterward
Maybe
possibly
potentially
okay now game you're going to recognize
that I'm using a controller you
understand you understand
I swear to God I'm gonna lose my [\h__\h]
mind all right
um
one second it doesn't normally happen
[Music]
all these [\h__\h] cables It's gotta be
somewhere
[Music]
so annoying
foreign
[Music]
I'm about three seconds away from losing
my absolute [\h__\h] mind
[Music]
um
okay I don't get it
[Music]
all right using a different controller
um
[Music]
no problem
oh good come on
[Music]
don't lose it how will you find it
um
I wonder if it's uh it's probably a
steady thing at this point I bet I
plugged in the steam controller that's
broken
and um
I bet that that made this impossible to
work uh
but the PS4 controller okay all right no
problem
good
see if the steam controller is actually
broken or not
[Music]
okay
I think it should be fine
[Music]
um this will definitely tilt me
I think
we will be going back to the sewers
five million percent but
getting really tired this
no it's not a steam it's not really a
steam controller it's like um I couldn't
get a steam controller they had like a
controller that works with steam
so
yeah
how do I jump again
all right so we're gonna use a
this Gamepad is different holy [\h__\h] oh
man
um
keyboard will do anyway yeah
now this controller is very similar to
an Xbox controller but
it's just the movement it's just the
side to side movement I'm kind of
worried about
um we'll see though
okay
all right no problem
I can get it to work
I can get it to work we're fine we're
fine we're fine no worries you guys
sorry for the the weird tilt in the
beginning we'll be okay though I don't
know who's gonna join us today
um I don't know if anyone will join us
but I'm here I'm waiting with open arms
if anyone does want to come it took us a
while the first time anyway for folks to
come around but we shall see
you're the way to go if you can get one
yeah I'm still waiting on the um
on the Xbox I'm supposed to get
and I believe I'll get it someday
all right
oh that was too much okay
okay we should remember how to get
around here anyway
okay I'll see if we can remember how to
get to that top one
it's probably gonna take a while guys
how are you doing today
I should uh note for you guys new song
is dropping soon
um it's not on my channel it's the one
that's out on uh Boogie boxes Channel
I'm gonna do like a little watch along
if you guys are interested in checking
it out
um we'll stop the game to do like a
little mini watch along thing
did 3am woo I'm doing sleepy sleep well
you might hear me scream at some point
I'm doing all right how are you
I'm okay
um
I took a little rest woke up did a did a
meeting
yeah it was interesting I played um back
for blood because they had like an open
spot
and I was like oh okay well I'm not
really doing anything before jumping so
I uh
had some fun with those guys and we're
gonna keep playing it next time I'm
gonna stream it on my perspective too so
look out for that
um
yeah played that we played for way
longer than I thought we would because
it was super fun
um
and then I took a little nap I went to a
little meeting and here I am now during
that nap I um
I had a dream that like I was super late
for a jump King stream but like I didn't
care and I kept sleeping it was really
weird I'm fine
EP with Cali song that's right that was
announced too this this may take me a
while guys I'm being extra cautious um
that was announced as well
um album featuring both me and so you
say Senpai so check it out aliens EP I
sing a really like
fitting for like Club setting song it
sounds like you're blasting off into
space kind of song thing
um
and I think you guys may be a bit
surprised because my voice does sound a
lot more processed in it but I think
it's good to do like it's nice to have a
song like that under your belt every
once in a while yeah a song that's like
quite processed and maybe different than
what you're used to but it's not for the
whole song either everything's mixed and
Blended very well and I hope you guys
like it
what I'm trying to say is yeah there
might be there might be some auto-tune
in there just don't worry too much about
it though it's good it sounds great
um it's just I know that's something
that my fans like
it's something something they talk about
not not something that my fans like the
opposite actually it's something that my
fans mentioned occasionally that they
like how my voice isn't very processed
and I agree for the most part um
but I think that it's just it's done
very Tastefully and very well in this
song so
I hope that you guys will enjoy it and
have it like as like a new take I guess
on my voice yeah
always good to try new stuff you know
yes okay
always good to try new things
yeah
what a child
see pain let's go yeah my only regret is
I can't figure out how to make auto-tune
work on the go XLR what a shame
all right
there we go
next
um
okay
all right
now this is where okay I remember this
is a very windy area
we'll do like a full power jump this way
and then next I wanted to get on the
platform
over here
okay
um
I remember what I was what I did last
time
it definitely wasn't going to the right
no way
I think we went to the place over here
I'm pretty sure
we went to the right not the left
yeah if autotune isn't there to help you
just because you can't sing it's okay I
have I have to agree on that one um I
think that it can be used Tastefully and
to make something that sounds very nice
um but
you know being able to sing is this is a
good thing go right yeah I kind of yeah
I figured that was it
how's it going have fun thank you
there's probably some YouTube guy on how
to get that auto tune working I'll look
it up um a bit later I feel like the
last time that I did it was like kind of
confusing but I know gura did it so I
could also ask her
he needs to be used properly exactly I
agree
is this gonna stop yeah okay so what I
ought to do
uh I'm I'm [\h__\h] up somewhere uh
there's something that I missed here
there's something I'm not doing right
um
because there's no way that I can jump
from there to that pole
I can't remember just a light hop
yeah I kind of thought maybe
first you go to the left
and oh boy no that's not what I meant to
do okay
okay and then let's try it uh yeah
that's not gonna work
um
and the most right jump to the left with
full power
yeah
okay
cut it tap it in
just gotta tap it in little tabby tap
um
hold on let me think let me think what I
did
you know what
I played this game before
give me a minute
I don't like to go watch my past runs
but
if it's a tool at my disposal and I did
it before I'm gonna use it
let me just see what we did here
okay okay it's this part
oh I see I see so just be good at the
game gotcha that was the answer all
along the answer all along was just be
good at the game Kelly you silly dummy
here we go all right
my brain just it's very it's not very
big you guys but we're all cool with
that at this point I think if you're
still here by now you're pretty much
cool with that um here we go
all right now all the way
there we go there we go
the thick snow prohibits calculated
leaps no it doesn't only if you're an
idiot it's like if you have a math
equation and you have to do like your
multiplication like times tables and
[\h__\h] but then at the end of it you have
like plus six you just gotta do PEMDAS
man
yeah that really kind of had nothing to
do with anything at all that I was just
doing excuse me that was weird
all right
here we go now this is where stuff gets
wet
um
real confusing
but bodmas did you learn something else
yeah PEMDAS it's math
yeah
gotta remember PEMDAS
um all right so let me see how we did
this before we had to use the wind to
get up to the second stage
your call correctly we have to be super
careful though about jumping the same
direction the wind is going always have
to pay attention to that [\h__\h]
here not right now it's one of these
ways
one of these weighs up
I wonder if I could Bounce Off the Wall
let's do a simple jump upward and what's
up here
we go
okay
nice little gargoyle friend
no
all right there is a little moment where
there's like no influence from the wind
which is pretty nice
[Music]
let's see what we get if we just jump
we'll power oh wow that was pretty close
oh that was a close one
wait wait
all right
um
I try to jump yeah it'll just make the
jump like really short I think
all right there's a lot of calculation
you have to do here what I meant to say
when I was talking about the PEMDAS
thing is that like you can calculate if
you add in the factors
like um how fast the wind is going the
other direction
so just how you would normally do things
but then you add like an extra plus
something something at the end like
you're doing math okay well that's fine
I can live with that
uh I can live with that
all right don't don't forget about the
wind is the thing
you can't forget about the wind
all right
wait no no
there we go that's what I wanted
okey dokey
I wonder how far we'll get today
hmm
I'm really really cautious about jumping
like with the Wind
so this could take us a bit you guys
we'll get it down
we've got to figure out what's the best
what's the best way
I can use going against the wind to my
advantage too
Pam this is my favorite jump King
speedrunning technique I'm glad someone
remembers PEMDAS
a whole lot of years I have gone without
thinking about math
no worries better safe than sorry agreed
I also am of that mentality we've got a
lot of time today guys so I'm thinking
it'll probably be probably be closer to
the The Seven Hour Mark
um in terms of gameplay not including
super chats
um just because I played I played a
shooting splitty game today is a lot of
me sitting sitting in my chair so
plus I Got lyrics to write as well on a
bit of a tight deadline these days but
am I right guys once this month is done
quote unquote
once this month is done I'll be good to
go
what I ought to maybe do is just just
simply let the wind take me
not worry too much about
adding in other factors after all uh
zero plus six is very obviously six is
it not
I don't really know what I'm saying but
thank you
no
zero plus six am I right guys
all right
and that's a new month begins
uh vitoy skis because you saw that
horrible fall
you can't uh get much more of more of a
Chad than that ouch [\h__\h] my arm
it doesn't get much more chad-like than
that um
wow
alrighty
and here we go sewers baby I feel them I
smell them
smell those sewers it's almost time
oh it's fine
F like right when I get it I'm just like
you gotta jump off yeah
like clockwork baby thank you guys very
much for the support
yep yeah we're definitely hitting the
sewers today
foreign
did it really have to I don't remember
what we did
I wish I did but I don't
um
here look
all right
no wait
this is why it really is better to play
Jump King and uh like intervals
thank you
oh boy
I mean it's it's why you shouldn't play
it far apart playthroughs should not be
very far apart from each other
yeah I know this but I just I just don't
listen
all right
pain
one step forward 10 steps back you know
it that's how we roll on this train
so we roll
[Music]
one sec
papa papa
I think Yara also expressed interest in
coming to say hello
okay yeah thumbnail's fine
but we shall see
people are pretty busy
right
so it may just be you guys and me for a
little bit
it's fine now I can talk about all the
stuff that's going on really kind of
surprised you guys huh
with all the stuff that's happening of
which there is a lot
there are a lot of songs coming out
um
a lot of them I couldn't really talk
about
like uh for example the baddest coming
out tomorrow
you guys are looking forward to that
I hope you uh find it interesting
yeah k-d-a
I'll let you guys kind of speculate on
what I chose to do for that song
yeah with whole Live ID very excited um
it was something I kind of did a while
ago but the MV took a while to make
because it's just it's literally so good
like I think it's one of the best mvs
I've like ever seen for anything from
Holo damn it
it's like that good
um
so please look forward to it
is super amazing
no
F that's so far
yeah no fooling no fooling
no fooling you guys
yeah I kind of saw that coming
no please I don't want to go back to
[\h__\h] bargainberg please don't do this
to me just don't make me shoot hoops
again please I'm not Kobe Bryant
I guess this is just kind of how it has
to go we have to go all the way back and
then eventually we start making progress
so
yeah
yeah oh
there we go
right
oh
all right
and Boogie Vlog song is coming out and
um
Boogie box and I got one more surprise
it's not really a surprise everyone kind
of knows
um
ah coming out this month
not on their Channel but on my channel
if you guys want to check that out
that's the new song thing
because I mean it only makes sense we do
two songs
no one for each of us
for one for each of our channels rather
oh
and uh The Vibes are completely
different by the way for each song
so
I like Kobe yeah dude can really shoot
some hoops
feel the jump
yeah Halloween is looking
really hype
yeah three three nights in a row with
song releases that is like unheard of
but I told you guys a while ago I was
working on a ton of songs like I
couldn't really damn it talk about right
so don't do the same thing again Kelly
you know what you're doing wrong no come
on that was so close you know you're
doing wrong
I like Kobe I'm just I'm not Kobe is the
thing that's what I'm trying to say
no
can I beat perfect cell and free throws
though uh I don't think so
I'm not a very good basketball shooter
you're killing it with the music thank
you very much is the thing that I enjoy
the most for sure
yeah I should have figured that was
gonna happen
in the memory aspect of this game I'm
just uh really not
not really not really very good is the
thing
but we try our best it's all about
muscle memory in this game I find no no
please come on I can't again with the
basketball [\h__\h]
no
yeah this is gonna not go well for us
guys I thought to myself there's no way
that we'll really go to the sewers but
no I think we might we might actually
really go there
like actually for real for real
go to the sewers oh
okay
[Music]
no I can't remember uh okay
it's fine it's good that no one's around
right now because this is the part where
I need to remember how to do everything
okay
not a worry in the world deadbeat it's
not a worry in the world
we can do this
all right here we go
no come on come I should have gotten in
that was a perfect basket
come on game now you know you know that
was a perfect basket game
you are aware you're playing games with
me games playing games with you who
would have thought
fine
all right let's try it again
no that was also a perfect basket
didn't piss me off sometimes when I tell
you what
come on man you can't do this to me
you just you can't
we're fine
no it doesn't all right
oh Cali it doesn't matter if it's not
what you meant it's what you did
what
is that not the way
huh is it this way oh that's right it's
this way see this is when uh the bad
short-term memory long-term oh boy now
we're [\h__\h] oh now it's sewer time Lads
that was it that was about it
for our chances to maybe not go back
down to the sewers but now we're
definitely going
[Music]
come on
gotta stand on the edge okay there we go
all right now
okay
sick Bargains I don't want them
like those are some really cool Air
Jordans my man but I'm just like kind of
I'm not really into that right now
pick up stuff have you have you tried
those air calories though once you get
some of those air Callies in then maybe
maybe I'll be interested
but for now um I'm good my man all right
here we go
oh come on that's not now you and I both
know that that was very silly
it was too good to be true
that's fine I'd rather overshoot it
I would rather overshoot it than
undershoot it
[Music]
the best would be hitting it perfect
okay
oh
where can I pre-order them God wouldn't
that be a cool piece of merch
in the future some air Callies
I mean isn't that like a rapper right of
passage
Maybe
something really easy
um
am I allowed to say I just kind of don't
really I'm looking like not into them as
a shoe I think I already said that in a
song
I like censored it in the music video
and everything didn't want anyone
sending like a screenshot to Kanye
that'd be really embarrassing it's just
a little joke
it just it makes me like feel like a
moon man like I'm an alien which is
maybe what he was like going for but
Thursday's got some converse that's true
I saw that I'm gonna be getting a pair
without a doubt
oh so say and I are meeting up
next month
we're gonna
hang
I'm excited
sit
I bet Kanye is a deadbeat I'd be
surprised you'd be really surprised of
Club not just hanging
talking about stuff
you know
yeah
I'm excited I'm a bit nervous but I'm
also excited you know
because I've been I've been meaning to
I've been meaning to ask and I finally
was just like
Jay Chad was like you should ask
I was like okay
so I did no no no no no
all right there we go
so I did
and yeah
sometimes all you really got to do is
ask
yeah
no that's the worst that's the worst
thing that can happen is that
[Music]
all right nice at least no fall I love
the lag on the chat it just makes things
so much more uh funny and interesting
really
let's see all right
there we go
am I a gamer drink with me
I'd also have another not so gamer drink
it's a um
it's my favorite vanilla vodka
with pineapple mix
I have a Shaker now so I've been using
that a lot recently
it's more like a pineapple mango
smoothie that's super good though Shaker
light will change your life man if you
like making drinks
yeah recently I like tried a recipe that
called for stirring the alcohol and I
was like this just tastes terrible like
this is just bad
you guys know what the big difference is
between stirring and shaking because I
way prefer shaking drinks
for whatever reason
I can't really tell what it is but like
when I taste a stirred drink it just
tastes like low effort like you really
could have done better but
aeration
shaken not stirred makes a huge
difference right I noticed that
aerates the drink oh
shaking scares the alcohol
oh I see
more thorough mix I guess I would think
so faster mix
shaking drinks are really good I agree
it's with the ice you know
shaking breaks things up oh I see I see
my gamer drink is whiskey nice choice
it tastes better for me
and just wish hot beverages could be
shaken I'm sure someone's tried it but
if you do though then it makes it rather
cool right kind of takes away the heat
when you shake it
um I was thinking today you know how I
said Papa Reaper really likes to drink
um like Red Bull and vodka
what if I made like the Cali version of
that which is like
um
vanilla vodka and bang
what would that taste like I'm kind of
curious I think I might go try it out
during the stream I don't know kind of
waiting for a buddy to get here first
but
no
oh no I'll just sip it guys I'll lightly
sip it okay
birthday cake and Vlog I only have blue
res actually
but vanilla vodka and birthday Bang
that would be the best
everyone's saying no in chat just makes
me want to do it more
well maybe I'll try it and I'll just
take a little sip
yeah I mean if Papa Reaper can pull off
Red Bull and vodka what I mean though I
think Red Bull maybe isn't quite like
Bang
I have to to bang left in my fridge I
don't know what to do with them
F see that one's a lot less bad if you
undershoot it it's not as bad as if you
overshoot it
get in big trouble if you overshoot it
no
all right
f
name the sewer level
that's what we call it guys that's the
official name thank you thank you for
the suggestion the sewer level I like
that
I like it very much
all right I'm excited to make it
this is really clever
shotgun a bang is a charity goal now
that's a good idea
I'll save that one bang in the fridge
along with the bread wrap it's gonna be
fun
birthday cake bang made my teeth hurt
I'm not surprised
genuinely not surprised about that
yes perfect okay
F that should have been longer now we
get maximum punishment that hurts me
it hurts my soul that the game says you
know what you deserve the maximum
punishment for that
I'm like why
I just can't understand but you know
what it's fine it's jump King so
I do really like this game by the way
it's like maybe one of my faves in a
long time
I'm starting to see a theme in some of
these games that I talk a lot about like
no wait no no
um and it's they're all really quite
hard even though I'm not super good at
games
I need to rephrase that I need to stop
saying that um I'm not super good at FPS
I'm pretty bad at FPS and I'm okay
at Platformers there
I was thinking about this the other day
like it's because you like suffering
um uh I mean despite how it may seem
sometimes
taking the easy way out occasionally I
do like a challenge if it's a game that
I like a lot
you may see me trying to take the easy
way out if I'm not having the maximum
amount of fun that I could be with a
game
damn it but otherwise um I do enjoy like
a little challenge every once in a while
that may be kind of hard to believe
because
of like in the past we have tried to
take the easy way out but
for example um
what was it
what am I what am I remembering
uh everhood everhood but I really liked
that game so I don't know what was going
on
I think I was just uh seeing before me
an eight-hour stream turning into a 15
hour stream
but we did it anyway we didn't let that
stop us
say you're above average at Platformers
well they they are the main game that I
played desid as a youngin so I suppose
that might make some sense I was
thinking about this before but
I used to play so many games
I know I'm not like the gamer
but I used to play so many games
to the point of where
I was in fact so one of those children
that got made fun of a lot because I
played a lot of games
um it didn't stop me from playing the
games or anything it's just um
how do I say this
I stopped having time for it
at some point
I like thought to myself well you know
what Kelly if you want to
if you want to be anything you got to
work hard
why play games all day which is silly
because
it's nice to unwind with a game you know
it was just that was a time in my life
where I thought that
I had to do something great
to like
have any worth which is stupid
stupid stupid stupid
do I stop playing games
I was really hard on myself games are
made for fun though exactly I was a lot
harder on myself back then than I am now
actually if you can even believe uh that
is the truth
um
that is the truth
I put him away
um
but I do like playing them
trying to remember what I did here
whilst having a thought
um
there was a time where I was pretty good
yeah
kind of in the distance now though
but it's cool that I can do it again
with you guys
you know
it's just kind of neat
I guess no
did it really have to be that far a game
I guess it did you can never tell in
this game when jump King's just gonna be
like you know what you want to go all
the way back idiot
um
anyway
it's just nice that I can do that again
with you guys
revisit a part of protest
um that I put away for a while
to quote unquote
work hard or whatever
now it's like it can be a part of my
work I'm just uh really lucky
thank you
no no
there's gonna be a lot of nose
gonna be a lot of no's this gameplay
I was thinking about something else no
come on man
all right
no
it's not time for the sewers just yet
this is the lowest we've gotten though
so that's not a great feeling
it wasn't no from this corner you go
this way no wrong from this corner you
go this way there we go
and then this isn't a full power jump
It's like a half power jump okay
I see them but they haven't taken my
soul yet so I'm not saying anything I
ain't saying [\h__\h]
if we get to the sewers I'm making that
that drink
I'm making it
it's called the sewer levels for a
reason baby
oh no Chad's just full of oh no
oh no
sounds good this game seems evil
definitely but it's also fun
it's also fun
all right
here we go
foreign
[Music]
okay
no problem guys see look already on the
road again
I'm worried for your liver
thank you uh we might be fine maybe
I'm more worried for my sleep schedule
what are we doing tomorrow ah yeah
that's right ASMR
um for members I'm writing
uh a spooky whole life English fan
fiction
because I don't know if I can read
actual Creepypastas unless I can find
actual Anonymous spooky stories
um on the internet which I bet I can
um with like completely Anonymous
writers I'll look for some of those but
I'm also writing um tonight I'm writing
a spooky whole live English story to
read to you guys for members only
um
so yeah
what
yeah
so if you'd like to come and check that
out
um
SP Maybe
Apparently that is really difficult for
us to do
especially for members who was phone
what a classic
yeah a real dojin writer exactly
so wish me luck I do have to do that
tonight so
yes okay
no it was like half a millisecond too
long
no okay it's fine I'll take that
no wait hold on oh boy
in this game if you're like half a
millisecond too short
and half a pixel off where you're
supposed to be standing you get in big
trouble it's that kind of game
we want the Babe though we want to save
that babe from the fire she's real hot
right now
I just I just I worry about her you know
she's burning
but yeah that's tomorrow's stream
ask hachima for help with your cursed
pasta cooking
oh yeah I am making cocktails
um no cooking recently but I do have a
nice kitchen to show you guys that's
just been made by a re-mpc looks great
I'm very excited for you guys to see and
we will be we will be using a camera for
full immersive experience no
um just like how Kiara did the pumpkin
carving yeah
I can't wait to go watch that VOD she
made a great looking death sensei
yeah
it was really cool who knows camera
let's go what will I be singing
um songs that I can sing how about that
songs that I am allowed to sing on
stream and to leave an archive I think
you can guess
what that means then there won't be a
lot of songs it's just a little singing
um
maybe a little Halloween wrap
I think you can probably guess there's
really kind of um
a main song I can sing
that is owned by the company that I am a
part of
Irish to try my cocktails that's a
pretty good idea I think she's kind of
busy but but that doesn't mean that I
won't in the future because I've gotten
pretty good
you guys are gonna see I test made some
of these cocktails and they're very nice
yes okay
um I test made some
uh I did last night as well it was fun
because I bought a new blender to make
one that's kind of like a dessert drink
right and so I made it I was really
proud of myself
um I bought some like expensive ass
orange sherbet and I was really proud
and I was like oh this tastes great when
it was in the blender right well I
didn't realize that the blender was like
connected in such a way that the plastic
part that like holds the liquid doesn't
have a bottom or a top so you need to
screw on the top turn the blender over
and then unscrew it from the blender in
order to have the the contents contained
in the plastic right so let me paint you
a little picture what happened was
um I unscrewed the top
um I unscript the middle the middle from
the blender
and because it doesn't have a bottom
right because it doesn't have a bottom
because it's apparently supposed to be
nice and convenient a nice little juice
container for you to blend your juice
and take it to the gym
um I unscrewed it and you can guess
where all the delicious uh contents went
right over my hands and onto my kitchen
floor and a little onto the sink and
over the blender which has a USB charge
port that it decided to go inside
am I winning dad not really I definitely
wasn't that time that's for sure
um so that wasn't great but you know
what we live and we learned and it just
made me happy that we didn't do that on
stream
because that would have happened on
so I test things out guys that's why you
test things out
so I've been test making some stuff yeah
recently
okay it's just a little tap it's a
little tabby tap tap tap taparoo
here we go
yeah
oh how many F's did you say that time I
screamed pretty loud
I screamed pretty loud but what else can
you do at that time then just clean up I
guess
it's getting kind of hot in here hold on
it's good
um
foreign
I want it nice and Frosty
let's see if we can make it snow in my
studio
we can summon some snow
because you're in the room homie
oh I get it it took me a minute to get
that little compliment there it's very
sweet of you
thank you kindly
thank you guys
I do wonder how far we'll get
huh
we've only been going for about an hour
so
look at that Crow down there mocking me
nope I refuse I won't do it
I will not do it you jerk I refuse I
won't do it
you can keep sitting there with the ring
looking like a big dummy idiot
and I'm gonna go get the smoking hot
babe
I love that chat was like get the crow
get the crow
you all knew it was gonna happen
you knew
you little scoundrels
you scoundrels
no
what should I balance
no clearly not
I'm standing in the wrong position
you guys are a bunch of Rascals
sometimes
I still say get it
I don't know maybe
you know if we come back here a lot
which we might I'll consider it
oh yeah buy the buy
um
Boogie Box is doing
um a one-man show they're gonna perform
Our Song
they have 3D models you know
um it's very cool I'm probably gonna
have that on in the background
um
like not necessarily like
like listening to it but watching it in
the background kind of
um
let me watch the VOD later but I'm like
Curious they're gonna sing our songs so
excited about it so I recommend you guys
check it out too if you have time
I watched their 3D reveal me too it was
so cool
okay anyway I just wanted to let you
guys know about that
because I'm gonna be there for that for
sure checking that out in the background
it is an hour and a half I'm excited yes
in an hour and a half
that's right yeah the new song the new
song It'll be revealed real soon we're
gonna do a little
mini watch along here many listen along
I can't wait
the MV is really cool too it's just it's
just it turned out really great I don't
know I'm very excited about it
okay let's see from here let's do a full
power jump nope that was not the way to
go that's fine
now I know to not do that let's see if I
can remember though
it's all about remembering that path you
guys
I'm excited
sleeping at the time yeah that's all
right it happens to the best of us and
you should at least check out the
the live seems like it's going to be
super cool
did I see Russia's 3D stream yesterday
where she wore sunglasses used for
ecommend voice and looked up at the
camera as if she was looking at someone
taller than her
well now you've got me sold
yeah that sounds like something I have
to check out
I totally can I'm just gonna take
it we go
no all right fine
a lot of times in Jump King I feel like
the punishment just don't fit the crime
you know
but it is what it is
this is this is their world I'm just
living in it
come on man
I just don't agree
[Music]
watching you succeed is always a
pleasure well welcome puzzling
I don't know how much success we're
gonna find today but
hopefully have some fun with friends if
they ever show up but everyone's really
busy so I'm just kind of chilling I know
Bae will maybe come to hang out but
I don't want to bother anyone too much
you know most I can do is be like hey
guys I'm free but if anyone's streaming
right now then don't go bother them and
say go talk to Cali
because I'm happy just talking to you
guys really
um I know that I called this like Jump
cast and all that like a like a podcast
format but there is actually a real like
for real podcast idea that uh we're
tossing around and talking about you
guys so
good morning from Argentina hello chat
welcome
maybe they want to do Potter
they always send a little at again but I
also don't want people to feel too
obligated you know and go man Cali's
real lonely she's really looking for
someone to chat with her oh man I guess
I better go say hi you know just if
people are free I think I think Bay will
but she's a little busy right now so
after chatting
oh I have trash taste yeah but like
talking just about anything
with some so maybe it is actually just
kidding
except we are us
good afternoon Cali good afternoon
I'm studying like a good rat but I'll
come by I promise you keep studying but
studying is important only if you feel
like it too I know you gotta stream so
you take care of business
we've got we've got plans you guys
we've been we've been we've been talking
about plans so
I don't know choosing to hang out with
friends while playing this frustrating
game was like one of the best like ideas
that I had had I thought it was going to
be kind of stupid at first I was like
let me just jump into VC and I was like
this isn't gonna
turn into anything so I don't know it
was really cool
but that's fine we can learn this time
to we can use this time to relearn the
game that I forgot how to play
no uh just a little bit longer okay okay
I think no wait ah
okay I get it now
I get it now I get it no wait
here I'm here there we go
all right so I just need to hold it a
bit longer no wait wait wait wait that's
not what I meant if I say hold it a bit
longer my actions will mimic my words so
I need to be careful
it's always a dumb idea at first right
it always starts off with like a dumb
idea then something cool happens no wait
stop
no come on the punishment doesn't fit
the crime
there was no way that punishment fit the
crime
but I guess this is just that game huh
this is the game where it doesn't matter
they don't care if it doesn't fit
you have to remember what parts are
going to punish you very strictly
I don't want that drink
I'm gonna make it though I will if I get
to the sewers I will make that freaking
drink
I will do it no one will be able to stop
me not even anyone in VC will be able to
stop me I'll do it
because that's what I deserve a nasty
disgusting drink for for falling a long
ways in Jump King
no
always important to remember what jumps
they're going to send you back to hell
foreign
all right
there we go
you say nasty but you know you'll like
it
called out
you got me I probably will
though it's blue Razz if it was birthday
cake bang with vodka maybe maybe I would
like it but because it's blue Razz I'm
like on the fence you know we just won't
know until we try it is what I'm trying
to say
so
you get through those parts pretty fast
now that is true it's because the muscle
memory is kind of starting to settle in
which leads me to believe you can Brute
Force getting through this game
I think you can
but
it's just gonna be super hard
I prefer not to is the thing
I'd prefer not to
okay
I do have a little news though my
friends who played this game before me
um
it seems that they have since given up
which is a [\h__\h] oh what a shame to hear
what a shame but you know what that
means dead beats it means we get a
chance to catch up
yeah
you get a chance to catch up
gotta take advantage of that you know
what a shame shocked why did I hear why
did I hear that with sarcasm from just
reading it did they beat it oh no no
they did not they gave up
they said too hard
I don't know what parts they gave up at
it might have been the snow
hey I mean I don't blame them I mean do
you see this BS
do you see how ridiculous this is this
game
and maybe it kind of looks easy to like
the untrained eye but
hahaha
turtle and hair type beat they aren't M
oh hey what does that mean
Cali does not lack conviction in games
like this possibly
oh but the good news is the Wii is here
and Earthbound works
so that's exciting I just I'm waiting to
finish do maternal first
yes okay
okay nice
so Earthbound is happening guys and I'm
doing that a little bit differently when
I start playing Earthbound
um it's gonna be like two Earthbound
streams in a row uh per week until we
beat it and like decently long ones I
would say long for me
um to try like a different format to try
and like Clump games together uh to get
like some good progress on them kind of
thing
um and I think after this crazy October
is over
um
I'm considering uh maybe moving in the
direction of
like like five streams a week but like
longer I guess
because this has been kind of nutty you
guys
this has been pretty nutty
um especially with I mean if you
consider
um back for blood if I had streamed that
and also there's another stream that I'm
sitting it on
um but not streaming that the other
girls are doing that would be 11 streams
this week if I was streaming those but
it became only nine
the song doesn't really count I guess
but still uh kind of crazy funny you say
nutty because November is rolling around
ah yes I'm excited to see those
particular antics
so
yeah it's crazy how long it took for you
to get the new Wii U we did go through
four this being the fourth iteration
so
this goes to show I really really wanted
to play EarthBound
so
it's gonna be fun
sleep was never enough to only nine
only nine I can't believe you do only
nine streams Cali
I can't believe you two holy nine
streams it should be 12.
11 that's baby stuff
no but like if you think about it though
think about it this way guys
we really are only required to do three
to four they say three to four but does
anyone do that
no
[\h__\h] no
a lot of times it's cause I can't help
it
a lot of time 24 7 stream 24 7 and only
for me you betcha
but you guys realize like
like what what that means right if you
only streamed
imagine living in a world
where you're just in front of your
computer but like you can't even like
surf the web or anything like that
and you're just talking and talking and
talking and you never please
you never go
out to do anything
at all
what do you talk about
I think I think Kiara touched on this
like what do you do
like like what do you adjust Cali
I mean I understand that like there are
some folks out there that can do it and
like not have a problem and I really
admire that I think that's a really
crazy skill to have and like I don't
know how you do it and that's cool do a
flip
um I think that's really neat I'm
certainly not a person who can't but you
run out of stuff to talk about at some
point at least if you're me I don't know
I really am like an introvert by Nature
so it's hard for me to just like come up
with stuff to talk about on the spot if
nothing's going on and if I haven't been
outside you feel me
Kelly I'm bored at work back to work
it happens sometimes
RPGs
[Music]
I am hoping I can Inspire one of the
other girls to become a DM
because I'd love to
all right we're fine we're fine I'd love
to play in someone else's campaign
I think that'd be super fun
no
ice cream fauna wants to ooh I bet that
she'd be a great DM
I could see her narrating stuff really
well
now that I'm thinking about it
as a DM would be amazing I feel like if
she really like got into it she could do
it
like she wants to play but not be a DM
oh I see I see DM dungeon master I
personally use GM game master
um at least for myself because I run the
game
um
I I guess you could find the dungeon in
it occasionally
I also prefer God God is fine too
God of this world
that works just fine for me
I'm joking
okay we will shoot the soup
it's okay
oh just barely
all right guys
now we gotta try and remember where it
was that I
have to have to uh take that big gamble
if you can figure out where like the
biggest gamble is uh in terms of jumps
and if you play it safe I feel like you
can keep yourself from going back to the
sewers that's just a theory
just a little theory of mine it's not
based on anything
It's just sometimes for example if you
overshoot something or undershoot it you
have like a higher chance of not eating
[\h__\h] you know
get that Crow's ass
I see you hiding beneath that ledge
I wonder how punished I would be if I
tried it we'll see we'll see I'll be
back here no doubt
what happened to the progress It's Gone
all gone
but we'll get it back we always do
we always do
huh
right
reduced to atoms
It's All or Nothing what a source of
pain it has its fun moments
like making progress
it's always fun
doesn't happen often but it's fun
and when it does it feels great
no
no wait hold on hold on hold on no no no
no no no okay all right fine I'll take
it I'll take it you can get back
I know the way
all right here we go
no
I disagree but okay
you saw me like basically make that
basket and then it forced me out of
course it did we're fine we're fine
we're fine no problems here no problems
no no no no no no no okay
all right
no
you see me enter that basket but the
game says no we have to be difficult
this is Jump King where do you think you
are idiot
understood excuse me I really messed up
um
okay
yes
no
it's fine I knew that was gonna happen
as soon as I as soon as I made that
little jump I knew it no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no that isn't right
jump King is just that kind of game man
like you think you're doing great and
then suddenly you aren't suddenly you
just you suck and the game lets you know
that the game reminds you
that you're a worm you're an
insignificant piece of [\h__\h] and you'll
never make it to the smoking hot babe at
the top got me good jump King got me
good got me good
foreign
at least you know the way
yeah I kind of do kind of
we'll see we'll see if I can remember
I do remember a time where I was like
excited to even be in this area so you
know with that being said we just got to
take that W guys we just got to take
that w
we take that we take that here
send me to the bottom send me to hell
all right
I love that they make sure that the
sewers are like the most likely place
that you'll end up if you like really
mess up badly
it's like very clever of them very
clever of the devs
here we go
wow
I mean you guys have some very profound
advice in chat it's very sweet
I do appreciate it this is one of those
games
um
I feel that like
it feels really good to complete
and I'm not saying that I didn't like
Bennett foddy's commentary
um but there were a couple times where I
kind of felt like all right man I get it
I get it this is very deep
it's a very deep game
about you know trials and tribulations
got it please be silent
okay I know I know I know why he exists
to narrate
I know that there's a reason for him to
like purposefully make you mad to make
the game harder
Etc
um
but it didn't come off that way to me
I should just be honest I thought it
felt pretentious
me sitting there thinking should I say
this should I say this now just be
honest
yeah I didn't I don't know I didn't like
it uh in that sense
I should take a page out of my um
out of my channel Facebook because some
of them are very honest uh it came off
as pretentious to me I understand why it
existed but
um I don't know
which is why I like
um yeah purposely there to know you
exactly I know that it's there for a
reason but it's just kind of why I think
I have latched onto this game a little
bit more than that one no disrespect to
dude for making like a really uh
interesting and challenging game or
anything
I just was not really a fan of that I
don't know I guess you could maybe you
could just make the argument oh Kelly
you're just butt hurt that's fine too
I accept that
except that
that's fine though because we're playing
jump King baby
no
that's fine
I wonder which is harder which one do
you guys think it's more difficult
out of the two because I know we have
some deadbeats that have played both
probably even deadbeats have cleared
both I can imagine it
but
I mean I've seen some people play
getting over it for like five hours
eight hours but
of this for sure
body is easier
it is a difficult Choice jump King is
way harder
um
but see I also see some people that
think the other way around so I think it
might it might depend on like your
perspective but when I've seen I've seen
some getting over it gameplays that like
can range like five to eight hours but
every gameplay that like I see like for
example I really only have pecora
senpies to go by
um but like just in general if you look
for like
somebody playing through jump King
if they complete the game it takes a
long
time how did it take pekorescent by 24
hours 21.
it was just really awesome
no
it was ever so short come on I don't
think I deserved that and now we go to
sewers time to make a drink Lads here we
go are you ready everyone stay here I'm
gonna be right back
first we get the ice
foreign
hey
and now we put in a raspberry Bang
sounds like death
and now Labs we shake
oh yes
I forgot
the bang is a carbonated beverage
Bang
carbonated beverage
ah
well that makes sense
is she okay
not really
oh boy
I like my drinks shaking not stirred
shaken not stirred she says
energy drinks aren't carbonated are they
possibly potentially
well now the floor is nice and safe
the repeat of yesterday
I'm over it I'm angry anymore
um
anyway
it's two L's in a row that beats two L's
in a row
oh boy I really do need to clean the
floor it's gonna be sticky otherwise
um
damn you in it
give me a minute
yeah I don't really know why
um I don't know why I thought that uh
would work
don't really know what was going through
my head there it might have been pure
adrenaline from losing so terribly but
anyway
all right that should do it
the truth moment of truth you gotta
taste test this bad boy all right
ah
there are vodkas on the floor not just
vodka my friend
raspberry Bang
all right let's drink it here we go
cheers everyone
clink
it's actually um
really tasty
that tasted uh
tastes really good
actually
oh wow
that's nice
kind of tastes like cake like like I
made a birthday cake Bang
yeah it tastes like I made a birthday
cake bang you guys
blue Raz is good yeah definitely and it
mixed as well I didn't expect hold on
a second quarter is too long they didn't
expect it to mix well guys
we knew you would like it oh no she
liked it
ah come on guys I never try to
huh no
that was not the time to readjust my
screen
well I suppose I deserve that for liking
the Abomination I just created
that's fine this is what I deserve but
you know what
sewers no problem
we've been here before
oh [\h__\h]
I forgot where I should be
this is bad
all right fine
guys we're in trouble
yeah I'm in big trouble
because I don't remember this area at
all
I mean I have a hundred percent
completely forgotten it
oh maybe not look this isn't the worst
there
no problem
Speed Run stress
oh I feel
wow there's like a there's like a little
fire in my brain
wow we oh man that feels strange
wow
hahaha
please don't drink that again but it
tastes good though
I don't even taste the alcohol honestly
I think that um bang and vanilla vodka
is like the new generations Red Bull and
vodka
I'm gonna tell my dad about it later I
bet he'll be proud of me
it'll be excited no
it's fine I'll do it again watch me do
it again game you think that's a threat
to me I'll do it again watch
no
here's another rule of thumb game
doesn't like when you uh challenge it
like that
almost like it's got a mind of its own
no
this game has a mind of its own Lads no
foreign
yes
yes okay
no problems guys no problems
yep I knew that was gonna happen if you
go to the edge that's oh
well
just one of those days guys just one of
those days
foreign
how are we here again
we're fine
don't worry guys
when you said you'd have to relearn the
game with this controller I didn't think
you meant from the very bottom that's
some dedication right there we are using
a different controller but it's fine
it's fun
happens to the best of us you know
we'll make it
I just have to focus a little bit more
there we go
all right
this is a game that takes a lot of your
time if people go on and on about
certain games they like that have long
gameplay times like persona for example
hey you know what
I raise you jump King
this game's got a lot of play time
if you're like me
no now I disagree with that but okay
ah Boogie box song in an hour gotta
remember that it's happening but I'm
sure I'm sure if I if I did get
sidetracked you guys would certainly let
me know but
baby baby baby baby baby baby baby baby
baby baby baby baby baby
[Music]
I'll just go ahead and drink this gamer
drink
I got a caffeine free version actually
which I don't really know at that point
with the what the point of it is but
they do have caffeine free versions this
kind of tastes like juice really I don't
know if it's like weaning people off of
gamer juice but
yeah
gamer drink
Persona unarchived karaoke went oh it's
such a good idea
I think next month is um I have another
themed karaoke plan but it's not persona
um
I might save persona for December
thank you
yeah you do it from this corner yeah
yeah I remember now
game OST in general works yeah
ooh Guilty Gear karaoke is also a really
good idea
right
foreign
nice okay
now let's get back you guys let's get
the heck
there's so many games that like you
could have a really awesome karaoke with
I think
congrats on beating the sewers I know
it's my first time I wonder what awaits
us
I wonder what awaits Us in this
beautiful game jump King I wonder if
there's perhaps a village level and a
snow level gosh gagali G that would be
amazing if there was
all right
we're fine
I am exceptionally uh excited for
December
however I do have plans to take
um
like um a vacation that's probably gonna
be
a week or so long just so you guys are
in the loop
just follow the holidays
yeah
but until then I'm gonna really gambaru
especially because we're getting really
close to we're getting really close to
um 2 million
I really I would love to reach that
before I go
um on vacay but I don't think it's gonna
happen
as much as ah oh as much as I would like
for that uh I don't really know if
that's like likely but we'll see we'll
see
I'm gonna work really hard for that but
if it doesn't happen then no problem
just when I come back you know
yes okay
yeah
with the KDA song Anything is Possible
well I do wonder what people will think
of that I hope you guys like it
yeah
two million Moe Mo baking
what time do I have I wonder how I can
find that out
come on start
12 hours 25 minutes
not bad not bad
it's a decent amount of time
[Music]
thank you
all right
the baddest is a great song oh yeah I
love that song
like I loved it before
um Luna reached out to me and I was like
yeah let me do it
I'm in
turned out so cool
f
foreign
that jump has less of a uh a penalty
than overshooting it
is what I'm realizing
using Gambler brain
I'm not a gambler
but I do indulge in some Gambler media
[Music]
come on and slam if you want a jam party
people in the house let's go
oh man
on
all right now let's see if we can make
this dunk
this slam dunk guys
I've never really liked rap ball that
much but yours is an exception thank you
I think um
yeah it does sound rather different huh
it's definitely more of like an
alternative rap approach I would say
rather than straight hip-hop
um but I mean I want to try new things
you know
there's one pixel missing in this roof
that I'm about to jump into on the left
side and it's bugging the shed
whoa
gamer drink
gamer drinks are so funny to me
um
isn't there funny
here we go
okay chaos dunk let's see if I can pull
off that chaos dunk you guys
oh okay it's fine
there we go
chaos dunk destroyed the the b-ball
World long ago
you gotta be careful
now basketball has outlawed in another
timeline
man that feels good
it's a real good feeling oh the cross
Crow's getting me tilted
Kobe
let's go she got the ring not not that
ring but I got a ring
a basketball ring
okay
let me look at
how to approach this Crow
put them
[Applause]
I threw my hands up in the air like I
just didn't care for that one
yeah
yeah sometimes when I'm streaming you
guys can't see it but I do throw my
hands up in there until deaths
oh man
yeah must have been the gamer juice am I
right guys
making me extra focused
turning me into a serious gamer
wait there we go
oh bang juice I'm not drinking too much
of the the bang and vodka combo it's
like sitting off on the side but I'm
just I'm barely sipping on it so
it is tasty I will admit but I'm
drinking more of that gamer juice
instead
super hydrating I don't know maybe
full of electrolytes gives you tons of
focus
I
arigato
[Music]
yes okay
now
let's go jump oh my you've got to be you
are [\h__\h] me
can you am I chasing you all the way up
my man
no wait wait wait wait wait wait I
totally forgot that was gonna oh okay
we're fine I can deal with that
we got him a second time can you just
drop it now my dude wait no hold on ah
damn it
ah no we're fine we're fine all good in
the neighborhood
okay
nope
no
maybe the hot babe is crony
crony
[Music]
oh
that's my uh my karasu impression
no
hold on if I go all the way over here
and hold it no no no
okay we have the Dual bounce there we go
just bouncing off the walls Lads
bouncing off the walls
just bouncing off the walls
okay
this is a full power
foreign
well
I'll take it we scared him away
I can remember what we did around here
Maybe
okay
no problem guys no problem look look at
that
look at that
see
so should I grow down give me a
slingshot I can do it maybe
I kind of suck at that kind of stuff
never mind
e
um
full power
okay
almost full power
and
almost full power and
decent amount of power
slowly inching your way back to where
you started it oh my God
this Crow is literally everywhere now
and there we go
that's fine
We Can't Stop Now
foreign
but knowing this game and knowing how
difficult it is I think this is gonna
happen this is going to go on for a
while
all right fine fine
fine
yes
oh boy okay
oh boy oh boy
no
oh
you guys
okay
yes all right well
easy jump yeah maybe
yeah you don't get punished super
hardcore for okay
I was about to eat my words on that by
the way
all right worth it to scare the crow I
guess
all right
now where next okay
foreign
there was not a lot of margin for error
for that
okay
stop come on
foreign
I'm holding it for too long
yeah that's right out of here
and there we go okay fine fine fine fine
is that Crow gonna be on every single
screen
no no no no no no no no no
fine
stop
this is rough Lads this is real rough
hold it a bit longer than that Cali
a bit longer you can do it
no that was not a bit that was much
longer it's fine
punishment fit the crime so no problem
punishment fit the crime
see I'm a sheriff so it's just it's just
what it's just my principles you know
punishments gotta fit the crime
otherwise there's something real real
dastardly going on
you feel me
there
okay
next Which Way aha
no
all right well yeah
principles weren't we a gang at one
point let's not talk about that
what could you possibly mean
you know a game I really really wanted
to play with gura but I still haven't
heard back on
westerado
you guys played westerado before
it's like a two-player like pixel art
looking Western game
God I want to play it with Gira so bad
what is that I recommend you look it up
it's on sale
maybe we'll just play it with their off
stream
I'd love to do it on stream though I
thought you were going to say a River
City girls we're trying to figure out a
time to get it to work she's worried
about the lag though so we're probably
gonna test it out again just on our own
first to make sure it's playable
if not well apparently the second game
is going to have online co-op so it's
cool
I'd like to play the first but
maybe if she can come visit sometime
we're gonna try to get it to work
because I was having a lot of fun with
that game
that was a lucky
okay
thank you Kelly I'm having fun thank you
I'm Japanese Yokoso
clutch
has the same type of online as strive it
should work like a charm heck yeah
that's good to hear as long as there are
no lobbies involved I guess but I'm sure
that strive is working on that you can't
have it all and I think uh
the gameplay itself is number one in
terms of how smooth it should be so
personally
hell yeah
foreign
okay here we go
no I need to hold it longer
a little bit longer a little bit here
a little bit longer than that no okay
preemptively saying no
we're fine we're fine
okay let's what do we do this time
uh
getting real high up there huh
no wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait I didn't mean that no
stop
I want to see like an artistic rendering
of the entire game from bottom to top
like what does it even look like this
place the map
I want to know
I'll check it out after I beat it
because I want surprises
I want to be surprised you know
okay
no no that was too much I knew it was
too much
uh it's very punishing
f
we'll make it through this together
ah pain
have you not beat this game yet uh no I
haven't it's taken me quite a while
I mean it's fun don't get me wrong but
just a lot
you got to be real good at jumping
there we go
please
no please
ah in this game you really do have to be
you really do have to be perfect on some
points and if you aren't perfect you get
in big trouble no okay
we're fine
we're not fine we're boned
okay full Focus full Focus mode guys
we're gonna make it
gonna make it just bought this game
gonna play alongside you and join you in
the suffering LOL wouldn't it be super
funny if you beat me my dude
I mean I think I saw the speed run
record was like
around three or four minutes wow
people are determined if they can do it
that quick surely you can too
first try first try
I believe in it I believe you can
and there we go
I believe you can
I have to hold it longer
but 500 hour practice
also true
would it be worth the cost of lost
sanity I mean it must feel great when
you get that Speed Run uh record though
I will say that's got to be the best
feeling in the world
okay
f
all right so it's obviously much better
if I can hit the the sticks up like that
are facing up like the first try
I just barely missed it
because doing it from here is kind of
hard
it is really hard to judge okay
no
foreign
it's cool guys we'll be here all night
we'll be here all night
if we have to be now it's morning for
some frog for some folks
or rather a lot of people will also wake
up and join us
you're very patient Callie I remember
you when you used to throw a tent from
it over Trump
I mean I did used to yell pretty loud
foreign
just barely
there we go
no oh that was so close
wait what
okay
this is relaxing as a viewer actually
well at least it's a relaxing experience
for you
I can understand what you mean though
I kind of get similar Vibes honestly
okay
when I'm not falling
that'll happen
please
this could take us a while guys
okay a little longer than that
there we go
now we have snow
oh
we have snow
no
is the game part of my Reaper training
um
if it was
I can I can promise you one thing
I'd be a much more effective killer
because this game right here oh man does
it really prime your senses
we love that gamer Jews
oh boy
okay
just focus just focus
no problem
foreign
gotta do another level of this
um
what the [\h__\h]
I'm in Pam
okay
no
see nothing to worry
I'm gonna shut up now every single time
every every single I'm jinxing myself so
much
I
no
I don't think I deserved that I just
don't think
what a surf that
no maybe I did
[Music]
all right
yep yep I saw that was gonna happen yep
I knew yep I knew that was gonna happen
it happened last time didn't hold it for
long enough
got it
[Music]
okay
we're gonna Master it at some point guys
that's what this game is about is if I
repeat in the same [\h__\h] over and over
and over and over and over again right
and then eventually we get good right
right
did no one show up to the Jump cast lol
I mean not yet
I hope they will but I mean people are
busy also this is like bad timing for
overseas like really bad what time is it
in
let me check what time it is overseas
right now but since I'm doing this for a
long time there's lots of potential for
others to show up
if people don't show up people don't
show up
let's see for example
leave Los Angeles 2 32 A.M
central time it's 4 32 A.M
it's really early
so um no I know Bae wants to come by
we'll see
I would like for folks too but if people
are busy it is what it is
no
maybe last time was just like a really
lucky kind of coincidence
timing Etc
well I will still be here in VC I'll be
waiting
[Music]
uh yes early I am quote unquote up early
I don't know what time Kiara gets up or
if she wants to
drop by but we'll see
[Music]
for now I'm using this opportunity to
remember all the places where I uh died
you're not rather not died you were you
where I fell yeah
that's what I meant you can't die in
this game sadly
for the jump King
because I bet my man wishes that he
could
I right let's see
[Music]
no
can you imagine this game had fall
damage
[Music]
I want to see it jump king mod where
there's fall damage and if you lose all
your health you go to the start of the
game
it's like a Nuzlocke version of jump
King
[Music]
come on man
all right now I'm getting tilted now I'm
getting really tilted okay
Focus
I don't want to be the baby the top I
want to get up to the babe at the top
drank no no drinking game
not this time guys not this time
okay
and don't hate the player hate the game
iced tea
you gotta love him hitting me with that
falling in such a long way
quoting iced tea at me thanks Bennett
foddy appreciate it Big Ups
[Music]
no
final ticket
[Music]
I'll sit here forever
I will never leave
that's fine how about we stay in this
corner for the rest of the gameplay does
that sound fun to you guys sure it does
you need to answer that
foreign
this is where we began the game today
today's gameplay
this is where it all began
feeling good
[Music]
now we're gonna Focus
foreign
no
ah come on
[Music]
we make progress we back at the start
pretty much the start but
it's fun this is that type of game
[Music]
we'll get there we'll get there
it'll take a bit of time
no
okay
[Music]
that corner is uh very anal
okay
foreign
gotcha
right now this [\h__\h]
oh
the magic yeah I saw yeah that dude
tried to sell me some air more he's
never offered a shred of evidence of
their supposed abilities yeah I know
that guy's her real Trickster
that common man must have taken me for
fool yeah me as well man uh good looking
out good thing we're not stupid haha
right my man
nice too thank you
p-o-g-p-o-g
oh gamer move let's knock off air
morries
we're not there for that okay
oh my God
ah no with the crow nope not doing it
not doing it right now I want to focus
on progress haven't gotten past that
part this part so I'm not gonna do it
now I remember how this works I'm gonna
start moving Against the Wind unless
it's something that oh boy
unless it's a big jump that I'm trying
to make I'm gonna be moving Against the
Wind
I'm gonna try to do it by just um
I'm gonna try to focus on doing this
um
just by uh
like this you guys see what I'm getting
at here
foreign
so by letting the wind do everything
and it's a good thing that the snow is
here to stop me you know
just gotta time it properly
ah
just gotta time it properly we could be
here for a while guys we can be here for
a while
foreign
guys this is the furthest we've gotten
um
so you can make some pretty good bunny
hops
I wonder what's up there I'm not I don't
want to find out right now
oh
all right let me wait till it goes the
other way thanks guys yeah baby
oh okay so very clearly we can uh
okay okay okay nice nice
you just do a little oisha
okay hello
there's cute little gargoyles
no ah so you can really you really just
don't make like a lot of uh progress if
you're doing like a big jump in the air
uh I'm gonna be right back my hands are
really sweaty hold on one second guys
I'm gonna put my controller in a very
safe place I will be back shortly if if
anyone comes in and tell them hi I don't
know if that'll happen because it's very
late in some places but tell them hello
hello
I went to put on my pajamas
it's fine it's not like I can move or
anything
sorry I wanted to get comfortable
because they're gonna be here a while
I can just I can tell
this is gonna be rough
oh boy okay
did you see that um
Cali and PJ's pajama welcome back that
was the closest one
yeah comfy Reaper yep I'm back yes who's
back back again Callie's back tell a
friend guess who's back guess who's back
um
what was I gonna say
uh hold on
oh I'm like exited out of the game okay
um
what was I gonna say
hold on
maybe I should get up here
um
I lost my train of thought
happens to the best of Las Vegas
oh
I see I see
um
man
we're gonna be here a while
should I go over here
what
I guess that would happen huh
if you do little hops
I ain't that bad
nice
okay
no okay that's fine
I just got to figure out how the wind
works here you know
yeah yeah I like that like that like
that
and then um
okay
anyway the wind blows anyway the wind
blow
it seems to change from time to time
yeah I can kind of tell
10 minutes until MV thank you for
reminding me thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you guys we will not
forget
but we'll make sure that we're right on
time for that
don't you guys worry thank you for
reminding me though
okay no wait there was an accident what
no no
yeah we'll be here for a while guys
foreign
look at the chat Zoom
[Music]
okay
take a sip no drinking game tonight no
drinking game tonight I wanna
I don't want to die quite yet
maybe I don't know once we eventually
someday beat this game we can celebrate
foreign
we did this part before so we should be
able to do it again maybe
Maybe
I was really cutting it close there
okay
people say those statues give bad luck
oh I saw a lot of them
would you be mad if I started calling
you fall if you Mori
I mean it's a pretty good job
with your high tolerance it shouldn't
affect you too much I guess
but
kind of just not in the mood I guess
yeah
I'll sip some water though
yeah people were getting real worried
about the the bang and vodka situation
so
I think maybe we just don't
get to uh
influenced by it by drinks and stuff
tonight if no one has been to the top
uh-huh no many have many uh speedrunners
then where would the Legend come from I
don't know
it's a good question maybe they did make
it up
maybe it's all fake and it's really
impossible
we got close though
[Music]
F come on man
foreign
[Music]
this is a pretty rough start
you are really into this game huh I like
it
it's fun
[Music]
no
hang on
I'm just gonna
do some real quick
yeah
just went ahead and changed the title
we'll change it back if anyone comes but
for now I'm just gonna keep it oh
waiting for friends
[Music]
okay
my keyboard sounded clean I like ones
that make a lot of noise
I know what it is they're just like
therapeutic for me for some reason no I
knew that that was too I knew that it
was too short
[Music]
oh I don't need the pinned message
that's a good point
thank you
okay
[Music]
that's not where to do it from oh my God
the punishment does not fit the crime my
man the punishment does not fit the
freaking crime yeah
but I think I know how to do that one
now
I know what I have to do
that beats no worries five minutes five
minutes guys until the premiere of the
new MV
you go into uh
YouTube Type in Boogie Vox and look at
the MV that's being premiered there I
also retweeted it
you guys can get to the premiere room
I'm gonna go there in a sec
let me see how far I can make it before
the premiere starts
come on surely we can get back to snow
yeah
wow that's pretty clean okay
hit it we got back to snow
we go back to snow
I'm gonna do it from here
that's the the best way to do okay
and now we're in trouble
nice
okay just kidding we're not
[Music]
uh okay
okay
no please Mercy Mercy
yeah
yep
okay
so doomed
yeah
[Music]
come on I just don't I disagree with
that okay fine it doesn't matter though
it doesn't matter if you disagree with
that Cali
this is the game devs world I'm just
living in it
yep that was too short
[Music]
probably should tweet yeah
you should tweet
about the Envy that's happening
guys music video is about to happen
I'm gonna go tweet
[Music]
bomb
in the meantime if you guys want to go
check it out oh wow chat is really going
Burr
it is really buzzing over there here can
I Discord
see it
and now I'm gonna show you guys
the cover
just gonna watch the uh I mean you guys
have already seen it probably but
this is it
quick little watch along before we
proceed back on the path of pain
crisp what a crisp sound
here we go
what did you do
share real quick
oh I'm hype
if only I knew how to type sometimes
a like type something and I'll think it
isn't in all caps and then I'll like I
look at the keyboard when I type
um
because I'm just that kind of typer
right
and then I'll look back up and it'll be
the first letter
is uh not capitalized and then the rest
is just all caps
pretty horrifying stuff
foreign
you guys ready oh the premiere is going
the premiere's going
high five five pipe
all right
I'm gonna mute my speaker
all right there we go
wow they have like new premieres lately
huh like new little Premiere screens
here we're not playing games put those
hands away
from away
oh boy
man we've been working on this music
stuff for like a while because you know
two two songs there's a lot of songs to
do
believe it or not
that's a plan and organize between like
two groups
it's a lot
mm-hmm
all right Gamers take a sip of that
gamer juice pin the link oh yeah I guess
I could
no problem I got it I said yeah thank
you
here so you guys can go to the premiere
it's in the chat
Callie more like God gamer oh yeah
there we go offended
oh by the way
by the way
there are English subtitles
English subtitles
you can turn them on
I'm gonna turn them on
English subs oh just kidding there
aren't they'll be added later
they'll be added later
lafra's rap is so cool
afraid my homies don't be afraid my
homies
here we go here we go
it's me
that's a that's a Brendon Urie this
okay let's look at all those fire emojis
thanks guys
ah the chorus is super good too
it's very uplifting
and the horns I love the horns in the
beginning too
it's like almost like old Kanye
that's what it reminds me of
the horns
oh man I can't wait for the
for the subtitles to come out
I'm into chat
oh this part's really cool
now that back that back and forth is so
cool
God the horns get so good in the second
verse too
uh there are also lots of Easter eggs by
the way guys
in the background art
I recommend uh you find them because
they're kind of cool
I just did it I just did the Caps thing
that I told you guys about
ah
yeah
man what what an uplifting
final chorus oh man
yay pgb
[Music]
atch
that was cool
so good
ah man I love that song we all worked uh
real hard
we all worked real hard on that so I
hope you guys also enjoy
listening to it if you want
it's got uh some real uplifting vibes
so uh
yeah it's different than anything I've
ever done before as well so
heck yeah
Big Ups to bgv
o what a blast
and
ah
that's one out of a three out for the
world now for the world to see you guys
[Music]
foreign that must have been so much fun
to make it was a blast especially the
part where um where fra and I kind of
did like the back and forth
um because we kind of wanted to do
something like that like it's fun like
just separating doing the verses in the
chorus and stuff like that but it's even
more fun when like you could have a
little back and forth like with each
other and um
yeah it's kind of cool
I had like a little little
conversational Senpai kohai banter
yeah
uh
I know I wonder if
folks have kind of like
felt it out by now but bgv and I go back
like a long way
long way so making that song was a
really special thing for us you know
yeah
a very long time they are uh my Senpai
like every cent
the positive boost to get you to the top
of the mountain that's a good way of
thinking about it
yeah so
I
I owe a lot to those two
they are great
they have some good work
so
yeah this song in general kind of has
those kind of Vibes of hey
you know back in the day like Aisha you
had to go through a lot of [\h__\h] we had
to go through a lot of [\h__\h]
but but now we're like doing our things
respectively and you know they're pretty
successful as well and and um I've also
found success in whole life and so it's
like a celebration song You Know
I thought it was a really neat idea
a killer Jam
[Music]
like a we made it kind of song yeah kind
of yeah kind of like that yeah because
you know obviously you can always do
better you can always climb higher you
can always be a better person the next
day but it's okay to like chill for a
minute and celebrate what you have
succeeded at there's nothing wrong with
that either
otherwise what's the point
I kind of realized that I was living in
this weird Loop of like
work hard so I can get to the next goal
work hard so I can get to the goal after
that work hard so I can get to the goal
after that with no time to stop and be
like hey you accomplished a lot
nope none of that that's the kind of
loop I was living in so it was cool to
make a song that like I don't know
kind of went against that and said hey
let's celebrate the stuff that we have
done let's celebrate
the good things yeah
kind of like that
Big Ups to bgv
they are great and I can't wait for you
guys to hear the next song too
appreciate yourself that goes for you
guys too
that goes for you guys too
I know we're all like trying to work
towards the Mountaintop and whatnot but
oh boy
um
but it's okay to stop and be proud of
yourself for a minute
you know
but in this case I guess we might as
well just die
no wait I can explain
and even if you stop playing this game
for like 10 minutes you're like boned
it's fine we can get all the way to the
top again I've got the motivation
my release
yeah anyway uh the song that's gonna be
on my channel is uh completely different
not in like an opposite kind of way it's
just a different vibe so
foreign
it's also completely different from end
of a life
motivation
be proud of yourself obviously but not
of that jump
true enough true enough
let's see maybe we can make this hoop I
don't know let's find out
well maybe we'll make the next one
Maybe
I I felt that one you can feel it too in
this game What's really interesting is
once you start playing it a lot you can
feel when the jump isn't gonna work
yep yep yep oh boy
we got to the snow we can get back to
the snow
we know that we can
okay
no
come on man come on
this game demands perfection
that's fine we can do it we can do no we
oh good I'll get in the neighborhood
damn that track was fire thank you for
checking it out
if you guys enjoy it it's on their new
album too they ship overseas if you're
like into that but I think they sold out
a lot of copies actually it might still
be some though
yeah bgv is killing it too
they put out some great stuff
oh no
come on
the song is celebratory and uplifting
but the stream is the balance to balance
it out by dragging you to the sewers
precisely perfectly balanced as all
things should be
it's a great way of putting it
well timed
foreign
yes okay
[\h__\h] it up
okay
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
heck yeah that beats
come a long way still making moves from
the views we knew from back in the day
ah
no okay no problems
one rip cover finalist collab ticked off
true facts everyone in that collab was
so freaking talented is so freaking
talented the same with the new one too
the spiral tones one hmm
I suppose spiral tones also kind of kind
of counts because uh me and pretty
patterns did attract together uh end of
a life
another podcast maybe maybe I'm not
branding it as such anymore though
because I'm starting to realize a lot of
people are definitely asleep
I guess um maybe we just go into the
morning
but I have a stream I want to be
100 for
please go until morning
I don't know I'll go for a while though
I'll go into the morning for some folks
but also you know a lot of En members
don't wake up until like afternoon so
just kind of some rough timing
but so many so many of my deadbeats are
around at this time so it's like a rough
kind of trade you know
but
can Fran she jump onto the Jump cast I
wish they could but they have a show
they're doing in like 30 minutes
celebrate Frost's birthday so it would
be cool I'd love to do some kind of
talking collab with them to like
celebrate the ah releases ah ah
no way
um we'll see what they got a show to do
which I'm gonna have on in the
background but you guys we won't I won't
be listening to it but I'll be watching
their 3D models
because I want to see him
and they're gonna do the song so
it's just I won't be like singing but I
won't be singing it
but my verse will be in there you'll
hear my voice but they're gonna perform
it so
okay
no come on
what time zone is this based I mean for
me it's 7 P.M
I think 11 13 minutes that's right sorry
I meant they're on at 30.
what yeah
do I bring back the ASMR streams again
oh to the public sure I have one
tomorrow but it's members only
um I don't know I feel like we've gotten
a lot of ASMR recently so which is you
know not totally an excuse or anything
but
um
I just kind of want to do other stuff at
the moment but you know
I will definitely bring them back
because they're fun
again it's like a million things I want
to do this is how I end up filling my
schedule
is there a million things I want to do
I all right
okay
well that time the uh
undershooting it was worse than
overshooting it but okay
it just depends on like what pixel jump
King is standing on
because if you're like one pixel off
then uh you're in trouble
it also doesn't help that I'm standing
at a different point every time so let
me maybe choose a point to stand on
maybe on the edge
and just see how that feels okay
no
all right hold it for a bit longer
oh
getting a little Hasty there
3am shout out to my night shift Bros
shout out
shout outs to everyone working the
graveyard shift
s
uh e that's me nighty shift gang
that beat's working now that's me
graveyard shift folks
here they are
you have an English essay due tomorrow
and you have a started start
just mute this stream start writing it
and then after about 10 hours when
you're finished with it I'll have made
progress by one screen
which should make you feel really good
about yourself because you will have
made progress and I will have not
good luck good luck on your essay
on that
graveyard shift gang what is up oh I
forgot I'm supposed to full power well
now I'm in trouble okay
got distracted
though even last time when like friends
came to hang out
um
even though I was quote unquote
distracted
I like I made progress
weird that works out it's a pretty
repetitive game relies a lot of muscle
memory I think
foreign
that was too long
no okay
no it's too short
[Music]
too short
nice
okay
all right now let's do this
that was way too short
just uh just chilling while watching the
stream yeah feel feel free to just kick
back relax
um it's gonna take a long time
with this game one screen is progressed
honestly true true it really is
it's just that kind of game
but
we got pretty far you guys
we've gotten pretty far it's just you
know you're definitely gonna fall back
all the way to the beginning many many
times
just gonna make your way back up
at least you won't be seeing the crow
again anytime soon
yeah but I can hear him in my soul no
oh boy wow that was lucky
[Music]
really lucky
you can kind of tell when someone has
been further though
in the certain area that we're in
by how fast they run through certain
parts
some jumps around here are like nothing
others are a little more difficult
no
you need to hold it for long I'm so
afraid of overshooting it
no you like that and actually that
didn't really get me in much trouble
intriguingly enough
no what okay
you can't really get too hasty in this
game
it will punish you for that
time
why after an hour am I still at the same
spot uh first incorrect it's been three
hours uh second of all it's because I
fell many times all right here we go
okay here we go
you ready
sometimes you just gotta go for it
very motivating yes okay
god it feels so good to make that bar
so ridiculous though
just an absolutely ridiculous jump
okay
okay nice nice nice all right here we go
no that was too long oh boy
yep yep yep that's I I don't think the
punishment fits the crime right there
but okay
yeah that also was not very good I
remember how to oh man
that did though
that was just bad overall
yep here we go we all knew this was
gonna happen from snow to sewers baby
[Music]
yep okay
the game said no no no you cannot full
jump there
you're gonna regret it Cali
[Music]
all right no problem we'll just make it
back up again
no I got Hasty again this game will uh
punish you for being hasty
puppies
this is why I came here
all right
okay
nice okay
all right
okay
yes
bargainberg
we got this
got it now unlock deadbeats we got it on
lock
no we don't no we don't we're gonna
we're in big trouble wise
we're gonna be here until 8 00 A.M
no
that wasn't as bad as I thought it was
gonna be sorry if I blew out your ears
though that was very rude of me
painful fall even from watching
well glad that some of you can also
indulge in on the suffering
all right here we go
[Music]
yes
God I have the biggest goofiest smile on
my face you guys
goofiest dang smile on my face
my face okay
everybody's always like yo how'd she get
here but nobody ever stops and asks
why did she get here
getting real deep at 7pm
[Music]
7pm on Friday night
we've done it before so we can do it
again we still have to do it kind of
different we want to survive
no I I felt that that was too okay it's
fine
we're fine we're fine we're fine but
don't let it happen again Cali don't let
it happen again
don't let it
don't let it happen again
okay
all right
nice that was the wrong oh okay just
kidding it was right my muscle memory
went out again guys occasionally we have
moments like that
okay
[Music]
I'm playing a game where are my gamer
hands they went away
I'll bring them back
occasionally there are moments where we
go pretty quick
occasionally
let me drink some more gamer juice to
increase my focus
just on my lap oh true but now I want to
hold them in front of your face
so that there's no doubt in my mind
in your mind
all right
[Music]
that was too long but we can we'll take
it
we'll take it not a not the worst spot
to be in you know
I got to make sure that this audio is
muted
because even though I'm gonna have it in
the background I just I need to get
muted
it's Frost birthday
fra
and to make sure this this bad boy is on
mute though
if you want to watch the show you got to
go watch the show
yeah I hope someone joins VC too but I
don't want to be annoying
the last thing I want to do if no one
wants to join I want to join
we'll see people are busy too they got
their own lives
but I'm always open to the possibility
I might just stay super late to like see
if anyone comes at all
I know I know they will no no no stop it
I can't no that's not no I don't want to
Amelia's Drag Me to Hell watch along it
seems like it would be fun but I'm not
gonna watch it right now
maybe later all right here we go back to
jump King
okay another distraction yeah
people have their own lives oh God this
changes everything
can you believe it
okay
3D Live starting yeah To Go mute it all
right
all right Kelly that was a Bop thank you
for enjoying the song
hope you guys all enjoy listening to it
and also the one that's coming out on my
channel
on Halloween night
[Music]
here we go
foreign
[Music]
I was really hit or miss with these
little stick things here
f
come on man all right
fine
I'll take it I'll take it
foreign
yes
oh it needs to be a little longer
a bit longer
just a little
bit
The Falls always happen after saying
here we go
I
that would appear to be uh the trigger
oh man
okay
just okay count I wonder
no oh no
it's okay I'm overreacting we haven't
every time I scream no these days it's
not
with like a big fall and then when I
stay silent it's a big fall
maybe it's because with the big Falls
they're so rage inducing I just can't
say anything
the best way to know that I'm like Angry
Angry is when I like don't say anything
at all
the exact same maneuver
five times
[Music]
that's how you know like when I'm
actually pissed
all right
[Music]
oh we see snow again
okay
no
[Music]
foreign
gotta be awake gotta be awake
you can't really you can't really tell
perfectly but if something rough happens
and there's just no sound from me
that's a pretty good indicator
it's a pretty good indication you guys
and there we go
you know uh
the consequences of that with not making
it on this jump to the pole is not that
bad so
[Music]
I lied I lied it is it depends on what
pixel you're standing on sorry excuse me
I forgot all right well it's fine
[Music]
foreign
see if you jump high enough it's not
that bad
[Music]
these polls aren't even the hardest ones
the hardest ones are in the snow place
we gotta get on those two
oh boy
a satisfying smacking sound
okay
[Music]
no
I reacted strongly to that one because I
felt like I got it at first but then I I
didn't
game I just want to see snow again
[Music]
slowly but surely deadbeats we will beat
this game
a hundred percent I promise you we will
beat it
it will happen
it will probably just take a very long
time
very long time
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
we're fine
yeah I should have seen that coming
and I should have seen that coming as
well yep I just yep
can we play basketball again
let's find out
can we make that sick three-pointer
again
let's find out
okay
Hui
all right
yes we can do this
no don't say that
and don't definitely don't say here we
go because then we're in big trouble
on the bright side imagine I said
something positive wow you know what
that's a really great point you made
thank you so much I feel much better
about this now
we can definitely do this
I um
that's like that isn't even a hard jump
to make
let's just
how would be
all right
okay
foreign
[Music]
why'd that actually work
and down we go
[Music]
and down we go and We All Fall Down wow
I tried well I tried
well I tried
oh my God oh my God
that's a tried but a lot
hmm
[Music]
well never again never again
gave us two shots
back of the head
and we're all
dead
no
[Music]
tread well I tried
oh come on Cali you know exactly why
that Woodward punishment doesn't fit the
crime punishment does not fit the crime
there lads
that oh that makes me upset it just
makes me upset
all right
try it again
the sheriff wants the punishment to fit
the crime
that's all there is to it
[Music]
okay
please
no please
yeah that's not gonna work yep yep
this is the part I'm really grinding out
right now I feel
they're really really grinding out this
part
[Music]
it was close
I was also close
[Music]
okay
huh
Sigma grind set
don't rush Kelly
I do feel like there are some parts
where I can go faster
but not this part this is not one of
those parts
his kicks must be worn out by now nah
they're like
the strongest in the land
deep breaths
yeah
no more gamer juice Where's my water
I gotta be careful about grabbing water
though I need to pause the game
we pause the game and we take us
objective get to the babe at the top and
it never changes it never changes
they're those air morries that's right
it's air Maurice
you gotta love those air morries
okay
[Music]
that was very close
very forgiving
no
uh
that's fine
[Music]
I need to try and actually like really
try to judge the distance
properly
see I bet I can
okay
that was too much that was very
obviously too much
foreign oh boy
[Music]
huh why'd you do that
could have been bad
I don't know why I did that
okay
[Music]
yes
okay
oh
no problem
[Music]
huh
Focus
which way was it again okay
gotcha this is gonna be fun
oh boy
no it is a full oh it is a full power
thing huh okay
well if it isn't then I'm gonna find out
so
I don't think that one is
don't take too I'm not messing with the
crow I won't do it I just won't I just
won't do it right now but
when I inevitably come back it will
[Music]
okay okay
no problems no problems
no
[Music]
ah I see
I see I see
I see I see I don't see I only see a
little bit
maybe like two percent vision
here
okay
okay nice that stopped me I had a
feeling that would stop me
now then
okay fine
this part is still like decently
confusing for me so I just kind of have
to get used to it I think
oh that could have been bad
oh man
huh
not for this
um
oh really really close though
now where we messed up was that we went
too strong
the opposite direction the wind is
really going to like help carry us so we
don't need to hold the button as long to
go the other way
we do need to hold it a little bit more
though we need to hold it a bit longer
just a bit just a little bit
oh boy
just a bit just a little bit I didn't
know you were Santa no I'm not otherwise
Iris would never come to these
that's why
that's why she's not here now
maybe because she's where'd Santa will
show up
or because she's busy
okay
oh boy oh boy okay okay okay understood
understood this wind man I tell you
oh the wind
[Music]
ah no no it's not gonna work that's not
gonna work
trying to just like let the wind Carry
Me
it's tougher than it is
okay
there oh
that worked I I know I know I know I
know
it's because I'm trying to scat out the
area okay listen
let me see if I can get a good look
wait let me see if I can is
let me see if I can get
hold on a sec
let me get enough
I mean obviously I can't bounce off the
wall
without sweater
okay if I go
if I go to the right
um
maybe I can I need to use maybe the
power of the Wind
like kind of leap
Propel my jump
okay
um
fine
if I kind of do the jump more towards
the beginning the wind is a bit weaker
I've noticed
and become The Last Airbender Cali
I mean I'll try gosh I'll do my best to
do the Airbender prep hang proud
the wind is pushing me
I need to jump a little higher it's not
the length it's the height that's the
problem
I get it
okay
got it understood
oh
what if
okay
I mean from here
can I jump somewhere from here
all right I don't know like when to jump
to check
I mean if I go the opposite direction
and that's obviously not gonna oh boy
I messed up I messed up okay
understood
God that's rough usually when you when
you're looking for a new area
um
it's like
you don't have to oh I should have
jumped harder
when you're looking for a new area you
could just like full power go to One Way
One Direction or the other
but not when this wind is blowing you
just you kind of have to just guess huh
isn't it
thank you
oh that was close
thank goodness for the snow
but I know this game has ice mechanics I
saw it in the DLC the game can't lie to
me
now we're gonna use the power of the
wind to do the little wall bounce let's
do it again
okay well yeah yeah uh-huh understood
yeah okay fine
let's just do it all over again we can
just do it all over again whatever
I wasn't close enough
I wasn't close enough okay
work the first time though which is
usually how it goes in this game I find
what okay
all right
all right game
oh I see okay
maybe just let it pull me here okay
no no no no no no
come on man
all right that's fine
let's do it again
nope uh now we're boned now we're boned
now we're boned now we're boned this is
it this is the end this is the end oh
man
[Music]
so much closer though
much closer
foreign
[Music]
oh man that was not the thing to do that
was not the thing to do either
and now I'm kind of uh
I messed up from the wind thing
so now my jumps they feel like they have
different weights
that's really bad
that's a really bad thing
it's a really bad thing you guys
we're fine though
from here from here no no no no no no
that was too short
but I'm gonna lose my [\h__\h] mind all
right
I'm not gonna have anything on in the
background
I'm just gonna wash the
I'm gonna watch the replay of the
concert later it hasn't even started yet
I just I can't with
hearing distractions is one thing but
like watching something
I just don't think it's possible
I mean it probably is but uh not for me
not for me
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
you can just hear the internal screaming
it is there
it is prominent
that wasn't my neck
foreign
[Music]
no
we are really grinding it out guys we
are grinding it out
[Music]
it's not a failure we're just we're just
learning
how to do this area real quick
so when we come back down
okay we know how we know how to do it
perfect
[Music]
that's all that it is
all that it is
[Music]
oh man
hydration check
it's a good idea let me pause the game
though
before I set my controller down you ever
wonder sometimes like if I didn't make
that one mistake there when I put my
controller down what if I would have
beaten the game by now just by process
of like butterfly effect and stuff like
that you ever imagine that because I do
I think about it all the time and it
hurts me
it hurts me
why do we fall to get back up again
of course alternative timeline Chaos
Theory ecoso
oh man
oh man how's everyone doing holding up
fine
been better been better my man but you
know what
just going day by day or rather screen
by screen
it was pretty close though
no
[Music]
you can do it
all right game I know you're demanding
Perfection I can give I can give you
close to perfection
watch this
watch this game I can do it
all right
wow all right
um
okay didn't expect that
but okay
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
that was kind of weird but okay what
hour is it in right for the stream it's
almost been four for this it's been 14.
hours this whole game
oh
okay sorry
okay
full power
who could live in such harsh conditions
you my man
be like training for the babe no A lady
could never live up there
yeah but I doubt that it's called the
whole like a cold where she is right
yep and there we go
it's okay we did it before we can do it
again
no we can't we're boned
yeah now I'm tilted now I'm real tilted
okay
[Music]
if
okay
[Music]
try this again
oh
[Music]
foreign
come on
he
okay
no you can't do that
understood
[Music]
gotta control the power of my jumps a
little better in this area
ah because it's always too much or too
little
it's always too much or too little
[Music]
okay
no probs guys we got a ledge have I been
up all night uh no this is uh I mean
I've been up all day but
yeah
it's actually a hot babe I've seen it
really
oh man
oh the concert's starting cool you guys
want to go watch the concert off in the
background I recommend it oh they look
so cool
very neat
very excited for them
heck yeah
I'd love to watch it but I gotta I gotta
be careful what I let distract me right
now
[Music]
thank you
right
the power
there is no proof of the babe
dang it oh it was too short I knew it
was too short
I don't care if there's no
she's on fire I gotta help
ah it was too short really okay if I'm
got it
[Music]
again the punishment just doesn't fit
the crime man listen
hear me out
on the bright side
there are some screens that are just no
trouble at all anymore so that's cool
but there are there are still super
difficult parts
here and there it's they're sprinkled
enough around so that it becomes a
problem
no no no no no
sometimes I jinx myself like in opposite
directions but I think that the reason
for that is because uh jinxing yourself
just isn't a real thing
sometimes it could be for the better
sometimes it's for the worse
but the fact that the Jinx exists in
both directions is proof that it doesn't
exist
I just don't think you really can
let's see
God damn it please why
yes what was that
is what it was not that beats
that is what it was not
I love their energy so much yeah they're
awesome
I can argue there's a placebo effect on
the Jinx yeah I think so
I would say so
I would argue in favor of that
Crow nah
I've had it with the crow ah
that Crow is going to keep leaving me in
the dust laughing at me you know what
you know what would be so funny is if
you get to the babe and the crow is
waiting on the last level and you get to
The Crow and the and and the baby's like
right there and you get to The Crow and
the crow just flies away
uh and you never get the ring
yeah that uh that would be the best if I
made this game
I would do that
I would follow it
the crow was the babe
yeah
yeah it's the best role of them all
but at least you like give them a little
achievement at the end just to be like
hey sorry man how we fooled you but
here's a little achievement hopefully
it'll make you feel better it doesn't
but you appreciate it anyway
[Music]
oh
you need to make your jump jump Cali
game harder I saw some of the
work progress on that it looks really
cool
I would love to play a fan game
featuring your boy
in the jump King Universe I play the
heck out of that
but I do have to defeat this first
yeah I saw that coming A Million Miles
Away I saw that coming the punishment
just doesn't fit the crime you guys
already know that though
the sheriff has made you all very aware
you guys know
you guys already know
you know what fine it's just more
opportunities to practice
[Music]
no
foreign
[Music]
no come on man come on
I'll be here all night
[Music]
foreign
no
[Music]
okay
this game is really dedicated to
destroying people's will and patience
yeah I can definitely see that
I get those vibes big time
big time
don't don't
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no
foreign
[Music]
we just have to endure
you know
foreign
[Music]
welcome to the Mountaintop
foreign
yeah
come on
[Music]
you hear that sound in my voice guys
it's acceptance
acceptance of my fade
[Music]
foreign
yes
[Music]
he's losing it
he's losing it she's really losing it
oh hey
my feet are really cold right now
it's probably because I decided to try
and make their room into like an ice
world to like match the game it's like
maybe summon the ice world to us I don't
think it's working I think it's just
making my feet really cold
yeah that should help a little bit yeah
maybe
no ice worlds today
none of that I don't want it
turn on the snow setting on the AC it's
a good idea I don't really use it very
often I ought to use it more often
though
so I'm tuning into a little bit of a
concert
oh they look so cute
I can't wait to watch it later
anyway
we're fun
[Music]
my headphones are really no pause the
game again because I'm gonna move
somewhere probably my headphones are
really like
bundled up very strangely
let's try this again
okay
[Music]
thanks for always being here to make our
days better life is so much better with
you here I'm glad you're having a fun
time
I'm having fun too despite how it may
seem I'm having a having a good time
having a good time
[Music]
go go go go
boom
yeah Kiara
your cat's in the background hi why you
gave me a little spook did I surprise
you you did you gave me a big old
surprise cake
back up on me he snuck up on me
oh man
good morning did you just wake up
yeah oh good morning good morning I'm
tired I saw you uh playing jumping again
yeah why
that's a great question yeah the reason
is because I can't stop I'm addicted
um you're you're addicted in a positive
way or in a negative way you know it
kind of it just it depends it depends on
how I'm feeling
um but to be honest uh
I don't know I don't know this game is
hard
this game is really hard I see that like
I I like playing games for a long time
and all that but those are usually a bit
more I had to say they have stories and
stuff like yeah yeah it's more just more
than just jumping up and then falling
down yeah somebody's got like a little
story but it's not it's not quite the
same I get you
um yeah there's at least there's a
smoking hot babe at the top right yeah
apparently there's like a girl on fire I
gotta go save her so I'm that's what I'm
trying I'm fired that's me I'm here wow
maybe she looks like you maybe it's your
long-lost twin Kiara she's on she's on
fire is that what they said well smoking
hot so I mean I I just assumed that
she's smoking hot then she must be on
fire so I gotta go save her you know
that's exactly what it means yeah yeah
yeah so I gotta we gotta go help I can't
I can't leave her on fire oh God really
[Music]
like in those boot camps the trainers
drill sergeant Kiara yay
yeah I mean if you're gonna call me a
[\h__\h] idiot over and over again please
do it because I love the way that you
say that
that's like uh I wish I could swear more
in English I should I should have gone
to your swearing class didn't you do a
swearing stream like I did with hot
chicken yeah yeah teaching bad words or
yeah yeah it was it was okay yeah I know
there's a bit of a there's a bit of a
lag which makes it even
it's fine it's fine I'm not I'm not back
at the worst part yet so it's yet yet
um Kiara you're gonna watch me probably
go all the way back to the sewers uh
which is just it's this is a rough game
you know um
didn't you play this last time for 10
hours uh I played it for like eight and
then the time before that I played it
for four I have a total of let's see 14
hours in this game so far yeah um but
I've made you know I despite everything
I've made a bit of progress I have made
I mean I've I've done pretty decently I
can get through some parts pretty fast
but uh yeah
yeah
oh at least maybe do you feel like now
you have like a like a feeling for the
controls like how high you need to jump
for certain jumps I would say so that's
at least something it's a lot of muscle
memory the only problem was when I
started up today's stream I realized
that I couldn't use the controller that
I've been using uh to play the game the
whole time so I had to relearn how to
use this uh steam controller it's very
janky but it works like oh no Ah that's
kind of uh yeah difficult that makes the
whole thing
more challenging exactly but oh that
that jump was kind of sick
um oh
we haven't even gotten to like the
hardest part of the area yet Kiara I've
been I've been to some crazy messed up
places in this game
um yeah yeah I've seen piccolas if I
play a bit of this game too and I saw
her also and so I'm really difficult
areas I think that was probably higher
than where you are but yeah you are
already looks High yeah um how far are
you away from the top do you know
um I saw somebody in chat say that I was
like a teeny tiny bit over halfway
oh Cali
[Music]
I should be more I should be more like
motivated you are totally gonna get done
with this in the next one actually at
least you're honest at least you're
honest
I appreciate the honesty thanks
we'll see we'll see something more
supportive it's okay it's nice just to
have friends here to help so it's just a
realistic type of person you know yeah I
know I feel yeah yeah I thought that was
too short really was at the top
would someone not hey ah dang it no this
is not what he says on that level I
wanted to read that oh sorry yeah that
dude talks a lot of [\h__\h] so like I just
kind of ignore it
[Music]
exactly someone would have talked to I
suppose oh no yeah it's pretty bad uh
situation yeah it is
yeah it's uh riveting is a word for it
that's a word to describe this entire
situation but it used to be a lot worse
the level design is the the whole like
level I mean yeah like the art and stuff
yeah it's cute yeah I love the pixel art
for this game it like makes me want to
play it uh cause I like it so yeah yeah
pixel art lover aren't you yeah I really
like it have you played Outlast before
yes I have I've beaten it help me
no I beat it a long time ago yeah did
you play it alone obviously back then
because it's a single player game I
suppose uh how how give me advice please
I'm scared mommy oh are you playing it
soon
I'm playing it tonight and it's like
kind of like a
um
situation where I'm only playing it
because good uh
asked me to play it and I hate horror
games so much I've never really like
I've played last year on Halloween I
played a really really shitty Halloween
game on uh uh horror game on my channel
and that was the shittiest horror game
ever like it was really wasn't it was
just some kind of like Indie uh um game
that was made by students I think oh I
see uh it really wasn't scary it's
called Uh something Mansion oh okay
gotcha and all horror games called
something mansion
ah no wait does that matching Craven
main nodes like really nothing but
um so the jump from jump from that
shitty horror game to outlast is immense
yes yeah well LS is actually a really
good game
um and it's like very like uh
atmospheric and it's scary but like it's
good
oh damn it oh well I was lucky
um it's scary but yeah it's super good
um and I think with gura they're with
you I think you should be fine I think
it'll be more funny than anything but um
uh I mean just uh I have inside sources
because she was yesterday playing at
last in like the new scary even scarier
mode oh and she was I think she was like
saying stuff like she's looking forward
to me losing my [\h__\h]
I think you'll be fine yeah I know she's
not really there to support me oh oh she
is she there to laugh at you apparently
I need her to be there to support me
otherwise I'm gonna die I see well I
can't deal with that stuff I can't do
horror stuff you'll be all right I'm
sure you'll be fine um I would I mean
I'm all right I'll definitely be played
the RPG for too much yeah I know right
yeah you'll you'll be all right on the
mind
um I mean I'll probably let's see I'll
probably you know drop by and chat to
cheer you on
um no thank you and she's not gonna be a
long stream probably
um
it's uh my mom I I was talking to my mom
on the phone last night and she also she
was like I think she also played at last
before because she seemed to know her
stuff and she was like telling me to
turn the audio down to just not hear it
and that makes it much much better with
horror games yeah
but I can't do that like for the sake of
a stream like I can't just play the game
muted what if I were to only muted for
myself yeah so I was gonna say turn up
the game for for everyone else and then
keep it low for yourself but I get what
you mean I mean I feel like it's a less
authentic experience for sure no I get
where you're coming from
um
yeah I would say just cherish the
moments where there's nothing going on
try to remain calm um you can do what
iris does I don't think it was Iris that
does I forget who who does this um no
bae you knew what BAE does
um where uh you don't look at the screen
that you're playing the game on but you
look at the OBS because it's smaller
screen is smaller yeah I wonder if that
really works Maybe
right here
um Kiara now this is where the [\h__\h]
begins oh it's just where it's slippery
right uh this is where the wind blows
you oh the wind oh that makes it oh damn
uh yeah can you get like an extra from
that blue crowd that was sitting there
the crow yeah the crow really likes to
troll me
um and just uh it's consistently like
running away
um
why would she run away from you
um because the crow just likes to troll
me
the crow the crow just loves to troll I
think oh oh oh oh oh okay
[Music]
fun what did that was what was that
killed it was bad it was bad is what it
was and oh boy it's fine it's fine I
just please don't stop me back please no
you're not that far back it's all good I
just gotta be really conscious of the
wind
um I made it really far in here before
in this area oh that's a switch between
left and the right oh it does yes I got
to pay a lot of attention to like when
oh that's messed up yeah this game is
cruel it is very cruel game
um
I like it a lot don't get me wrong but
uh it is very unforgiving
you have to be perfect
yeah
you can do it I believe
thanks thanks for the encouragement
surely I am
um I believe in you hey what hey I don't
like the way that ah I don't like the
way you sounded there
Kiara oh
that crowd is like there to protect you
it's like a guardian angel uh you could
say that more like there to mock me
though you will not pass this point you
will not fall down any further yeah it's
it's here to mock me
laughing at me the whole way
so what did you what did you have for
breakfast today
yeah I don't think I ate breakfast but I
had lunch I had like a little sandwich
it was good
I've been trying you don't have
breakfast and the lunch is automatically
breakfast oh yeah I guess so I just made
myself like a little peanut butter and
jelly sandwich
peanut butter jelly time you make
yourself a peanut butter and jelly
sandwich yeah
so
is that weird still I know I don't that
is so like to me that is such an
um like North American pieces
yeah I can imagine I can imagine it no
one eats that come on in my continent oh
yeah
no one
yeah I suppose when you say it when you
put it that way I can imagine I mean I
don't I don't really I think it is
definitely a very sort of underworldy
and American thing for sure yeah
like even though I I mean we put we put
marmalade we put jam on bread but and
maybe some people I guess I've seen some
people who like peanut butter as well
but it's also pretty rare yeah like eat
peanut butter on purpose what about nuts
too what is that you've never had a
Nutella before
no Nutella of course of course yeah I
saw a big jar of it at your house
yeah I love uh I love Montella yeah I
knew it it's been one of my base
components of my life
yeah good taste good taste I used to
really like making sandwiches with like
uh Nutella and peanut butter and honey
and banana
yeah
wait that I mean that I mean that's like
it could be good actually I'll give you
that that sounds extremely sweet so that
your two teeth would fall out but
besides that
yeah I like my sweets you know that I
like my sweets though
me too I have a huge or a hat is a huge
Suite of recently I've noticed I've kind
of changed yeah you know how like I love
chocolate croissants
I would never eat empty croissants but
for some reason
recently for the past couple days I felt
a craving towards empty croissants just
like the basic croissants without
anything inside just the normal like no
no real flavor aside from croissant
flavor croissants yeah but it's like so
good like I've realized there is a
beauty to it
simplicity
it's kind of cool
yeah what a nice metaphor for like life
I guess
a nice metaphor for trying to get
healthy yeah
do you like um like BLT sandwiches and
like stuff like that I love BLT
sandwiches oh they're so good I remember
when I was in Japan whenever I would go
to the Colombian and I want to choose a
sandwich most of the time I would choose
like a BLT kind of sandwich yeah they're
good
I'm also a big BLT fam
they can let us tomato just just the
simple things in life just the simple
things in life lads right here we go
yeah that was not good enough ew someone
said durian croissants are so good what
croissants Dorian d-u-r-i-a-n
you know what because you're doing
endurance you should be eating a durian
durian maybe yeah
if you don't get fruity endurance
successfully you should eat a Durham
it's a fruit
it's extremely stinky fruit it smells
like fart yucky that sounds nasty I
don't want that I don't want that
I don't want tastes it's good and
depending on where you buy it
um there's like better quality durians
like it's a really big hit and miss with
durians oh I see I have to put uh I have
to protect them a little bit because I I
I I wrote on Twitter that like why why
would a fruit like that exist and then
the people
um from the country where the durian is
like the national fruit yeah they they
all came at me and they were like durian
is good okay Kiana
[Laughter]
wow they got really angry at you for
that hug they got a little bit angry at
me for roasting a fruit wow don't don't
mess with the durian folks
um scared I'm scared they might be
listening right now at this very moment
I can't diss them they'll send like the
durian ninjas to hurt you
gotta be careful I mean I never I
I gotta be honest I never ate it either
but because it's not really available in
my country but yeah
but like I don't know if the food has
like a bad smell it's like I just kind
of don't want to eat it unless it's not
though yeah not those really tasty
ah see it's kind of like not though like
there's like so many people who dislike
it and so so many people who like it
they're a big reason why they dislike it
is because of the smell I guess oh I see
I see that makes sense he
yeah
if you were to hold your nose while
eating natto I think it for the people
who don't like natto it would probably
make it a lot lot easier on them yeah
but then a lot of people don't like the
texture come on man really oh yeah
that's true too yeah it's like a slimy
sticky yeah I think it's nice
he's very tasty how do I
ah Kelly I'm having technical issues
what's wrong
how do I um
what are you trying to do
how do I move from
it's a question that I can't really ask
you here on okay riddles you just type
it to me
I wonder if you know the answer how many
monitors do you have uh let's see I have
two one is extra wide one's like a
drawing tablet oh [\h__\h] I am okay oh
actually you know what what if what if I
have something on one monitor
um like a program uh how and it's like
fixed on on that monitor but I wanted to
go to the other monitor
um like a game
let's let's say it's a game it's just a
program that both you and me are using
oh I see so you have to go to the gear
um oh and then
uh and then you have to click dang it
what was it I can find out
all right you press Escape arrows pull
up all the stuff uh pull up the gear and
then uh make it like yeah it's there's a
square and it's got a bunch of arrows
coming out of it click it once click it
again
and then you should be able to uh oh
you're trying to move it well you need
to put a background monitor you need to
put a background
and then do the same thing yeah oh you
know how we're like transparent it's mod
really yeah you need to give it a
background
oh
I had no problem here to help
Mr help we're ready to help
oh my God that's a big brain Galley move
right there that's fine took some
finessing but you know no problem
who told you that did Ina tell you that
strategy no I've had to figure it out
myself back in the day a long time ago
damn
yeah how's how's it going how's your
jumping going
um I've had worse jumps so you know it
is what it is
no okay oh no no
[Laughter]
Jinx in trouble yeah oh man
um I would I would like to take this
pain away from you somehow oh man that
really hurt me
yeah there's really not anything of
suffering it is you made some cool
pumpkins though
oh thank you yeah I saw that they were
uh quite fun to do have you ever carved
pumpkins yeah a long time ago with the
family oh that was my first time oh
really
yeah yeah well you did a really good job
for your first time yeah thank you I
kind of like because I made five
different
um symbols well our our Hollow myth
symbols um I started out with Kotori and
then I did takodachi those were both
pretty simple but then I I continued
with uh uh bloop and I realized okay I
need to step up my game and I kind of
started improving by trying out
different techniques and then they
looked pretty good I would say my last
three the deadbeat
Sensei I really liked how that one
turned out because it has a really nice
silhouette and the projection the light
projection is also so nice looks like a
ghost yeah I love what you did with the
sunglasses too yeah thank you it had
toothpick yeah that was like a really
good idea did you come up with that
yourself yeah I did very smart very big
very big brain
Academy big brain and Innovative
sometimes exactly yeah especially when
you're doing something like carved
pumpkins you know yeah so that's pretty
cool heck yeah uh please don't send it
to me though
and I already sent it too late no well
I'll know where it is based on the
stench
it's great
excellent
you should arrive in uh uh free to six
business days wonderful
right just in time for it to be nice and
right
joking right
please be joking
I'm not joking no stop
I put it in like a like how do you call
it like a vacuum bag oh my God so that
you know it will stay okay longer and
also I I sent it with this uh cold
service where they sent like freezing
Goods uh offices you really thought this
out huh
of course I did I want you to respond
oh my God no I didn't it's a joke it's a
joke
you had me go in there for a second I
will say he already had me
oh I didn't do something else maybe my
my socks or something yeah what I was
gonna say like some Halloween candy from
Australia but okay
have a cheer way my man
your way
the Halloween is oh my God it's on on
Sunday it's happening very soon huh have
you seen in the Underworld uh have they
already put up like Christmas decoration
slash have they been starting to sell
Christmas decorations ooh uh you know
what I just don't really get out much
these days but you know it wouldn't
surprise me
it would certainly not surprise me if
they have
for sure because I saw in the
supermarket here they already started
selling Christmas stuff even though
Halloween hasn't even ended yeah that
sounds about right same honest every
year
yeah I think what I do that not not that
I'm not not looking forward to Christmas
but right
I feel ya it's always rather early but
some people just like to do their
shopping early I guess just fine you
know whatever
who would buy it now I guess is it
someone told me it might be cheaper now
than than closer to Christmas oh that's
a good point
that's a really good point actually
Australia yes yes yes I can't wink right
now but maybe Kelly you wink for me this
is on behalf of Kiara
wink
no problem happy to help thank you happy
to help thank you I need that wink
otherwise people think I'm really from
that that kangaroo uh Australia oh yeah
that's right the not real Australia
yeah ain't no kangaroos in my Australia
the real one the real one that's that's
the fake Australia they're thinking of
very silly um
I want to visit the fake Australia one
day oh yeah me too yeah
Australia is like beautiful
yeah it's not that far from where I'm at
either so I feel like
it would be possible yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's why I feel like a lot of um
students that
um are live in the Underworld
um go on a trip to Australia somewhere
at uh they're like in their in the point
somewhere in their school time yeah yeah
definitely a lot of underworldly and
students uh go to Australia yeah I can
imagine it's probably a pretty popular
location
I'm making a thumbnail right now by the
way
not 100 percent
focused no worries I'm just dying so you
know take your time
I know I know but if I'm like oh dang it
I [\h__\h] Ed up I'm not supposed to use a
direction I jumped that way oh there's a
lot of memorization in this game is it
like if I don't memorize certain things
it's like bad for me
then I feel like actually you're
sabotaging Yourself by having people
call it no no talking is one thing but
like watching something is impossible
for me ah
this is asking anything yeah but last
time when I had a bay and Iris here
um I made a ton of progress
it's weird how it works like that with
the with the voice chat very odd I'll
take it
well then that's good yeah it just works
has anyone else like showed up until now
before me no not yet but if you think
about it it really is kind of bad timing
you know yeah yeah yeah over in the
states it's a real estate yeah
yeah well how long are you planning to
do this today long time probably like an
extra four or so hours
um so maybe they'll wake up but yeah
don't you can you can leave whenever you
want by the way but this is just here
open because I know you have like a
stream to prepare for and whatnot but
maybe until like
talking to you yeah I'm actually really
slow at this I don't know how you
because you said you're you don't mind
talking to someone while playing a game
yeah
Focus I guess it just depends on the
type of person you are you know for some
folks it's like easy for us to focus
even if we're just chatting but that's
because you know back in the day I used
to do like a lot of drawing Hangouts
with my friends
and we would all be drawing and chatting
at the same time so we all just kind of
got used to it I guess
um
watching something is uh impossible like
my friends are doing a concert right now
and I cannot watch it at all
a concert yeah my friend's Boogie box I
like released a song with them
yeah we're doing a concert right now
yeah they got a 3d concert because it's
one of the members birthdays
um oh yeah they're doing that but I
can't really watch it because that's
just it's just not a good idea yeah yeah
idea we're fine we're fine
yeah unfortunately
but it will is it online only oh yeah
it's on YouTube
no no wait what okay fine
if I knew that that was too hard of a
jump okay it's fine
I've wondered Kelly recently you've been
doing quite a few enduring streams like
and you're planning to do another
Minecraft endurance yep maybe next month
why why what happened why are you doing
so many endurance you just messed me up
this is your fingers [\h__\h]
uh that was awful I went down like 10
screens
um
I don't know it's okay we're going all
the way down
um oh no I'm real tilted right now it's
because if you if you go to the wind
level and then you get knocked out of
the wind level it completely changes how
the game feels
ah yeah it's bad I understand if it's a
game that I like I kind of want to
endure but otherwise yeah and Minecraft
is just kind of fun because like there's
so much you can do and like the time can
really just kind of fly away you know
yeah with Minecraft that would
understand
yeah I mean with this game you kind of
need to try and do it in Long spurts
because you can very easily forget how
to play the game and forget how to jump
in certain areas so it's recommended to
play for longer times yeah
that makes sense
it do be like that
but I don't know I'm having fun and it's
gonna feel great when I when I beat it
someday
Maybe
one day
today is the day I don't know about all
that but I sure will try
that felt good yes and like you can feel
you can feel when the jumps were correct
dang it oh
so it's like a good feeling when you get
like a jump right but yeah
dang it
was a rough game
I mean I like it a lot but there's no
doubt it is difficult
you ever play getting over it Kiara
no I haven't yet like I was gonna like
play it at some point yeah kind of just
not super
um
it's frustrating I think this this game
is harder though now that Chad's kind of
said no this game's harder I can see it
no
[Music]
if I run out of all other games to play
I would play a game like this okay so
it's like the last game you'd ever
played the last one the last one would
be horror games and and perhaps FPS
games I see I see understandable
understandable
yeah
and yet I'm playing a horror game
depends on the horror game personally if
it's more of like an action-oriented
horror game I'm like more interested in
it or if it's like a pixel art horror
game I'm like really down with that but
yeah well I liked Outlast a lot it like
it's not a game that I would play if it
wasn't Outlast it's a card to explain
but like I'm not really into like 3D
straight horror except for maybe Outlast
and amnesia the Dark Descent those are
really good games oh Silent Hills that's
like I don't know a Resident Evil maybe
I do like horror but
um
but I think I'm a bigger fan of like
horror action action horror games
oh what's your favorite one Resident
Evil
oh Resident Evil which one aren't there
a couple the whole two yeah two remake
to remake is super good yeah yeah seven
and eight are fun play that one on
stream did you no I didn't I just did it
by myself
hmm yeah
uh no recently actually just for fun
that's cool you play games you have time
to play games in your or like even the
motivation to play games in your free
time I like I've made time for it
because it was so fun
oh that's how fun it was because like I
I don't like I kind of I would kind of I
guess somehow I would like to play games
in my free time as well but like since
this is like I play so much on stream
already that I just don't really find
the motivation I guess to play them off
stream I totally feel you honestly I
definitely I'm the same way but like
if it's a game I really like then I'll
find time to play it you know
yeah otherwise I will probably drop it
but
I'm playing a lot of games these days
for for streaming so I get where you're
coming from for sure
[Music]
I am not motivated
did you feel did you did you finish
Tales of arise
not yet but ever since that last stream
I did there there was like a cut off
point so I'm not allowed to stream until
the very end it's just like oh pretty
close to the end I see and so I needed
to stop there and ever since then I've
been super super super super busy so I
couldn't finish it yet oh I see I see
yeah even though I love it so much but
I'm gonna finish it soon okay yeah well
good luck I hope it goes well for you
yeah you don't need luck you'll be
you'll be good you'll be good at it
um
heck yeah uh what was I gonna say you
you've been streaming like I don't know
how you stream for a super long time
yeah it's kind of awesome I mean that
you can you have that kind of endurance
I'm like
uh longest I can go eight hours call it
a day and that's like once in a while
you know
eight hours is when I'm playing a jrpg
that's like normal for me
yeah but
um as I said like it's it's just kind of
different with games that have like a
story and especially if it's a really
interesting story that was really stupid
you fell down again yeah I messed up I
was really stupid
I completely forgot where I was oh well
oh
I'll get back I'll get back
I'll get back up there it's all good
I can make it back up I've been there
before
it'll just take me a while
oh Kelly I'm looking for like Graphics
or outlets for thumbnails but like here
it says Outlets bundles of Terror is is
that like a different game it might be
something I I haven't heard of that
before so maybe it's something else oh
no no this doesn't sound like a Mainline
game
maybe it's like there's the one that
says whistleblow I guess these are like
whistleblowers a DLC
oh you'll see stories
yeah what do I use and there's an outlet
with a completely different locals his
Outlast there's a sequel as well I don't
know I haven't paid much attention to
the series beyond the the first two
games but
that's DLC okay
oh come on that was so close all right
fine
uh this game demands perfection
absolutely demands Perfection
[Music]
oh wow wow okay freestyle
all right
yeah wow you really busted out that
freestyle there I'm very impressed you
got some bars Kiara
Cali has been real quiet since I busted
that Ram
yeah
yes yes I have
hard to hard to beat those fly Rhymes
recently I've been trying to bust more
freestyles but it's hard bad
we saw the flat but I should probably
just get better at it
you just gotta drink some whiskey or
whatever
yeah I can write wink wink yeah I can
write lyrics real quick wink wink I all
right
yeah that's all you need sometimes all
you need sometimes is just a little sip
you know and then you're just you're
flying you're writing all kinds of goofy
lyrics
that doesn't work for me because I don't
drink alcohol but is there a reason
yeah are you just not a big alcohol fan
or
I hate alcohol
I hate all of it I don't like any of it
what was I just doing is it the taste or
what if you drink like a really fruity
drink it had alcohol in it I've had a
lot of people trying to like make me try
things because they're like oh but this
one you'll like I'm sure you'll like
this one this one very like this one
doesn't taste like alcohol at all give
it a try and then I try it and I 100
taste the alcohol I just don't like the
how to say is it like a like a
fermented taste oh yeah maybe you've
just got like a sensitivity to it yeah I
get that I mean if you think about it
you are technically quote unquote
poisoning yourself when you drink
I mean makes sense right yeah because
some people I guess just kind of don't
really notice it as much as others I
drink mostly for the feeling and it's
nicer if there's like a sugary taste to
it because it makes it easier to go down
but at the same time if I'm really just
trying to like end it all
um for the night
um for the night then I'll you know I
can drink like a couple couple shots
and just drink out of the bottle that's
fun too I think most people just kind of
really as you said drink it for the
effect yeah
I mean I feel like that's the most
common for sure I drink because I need a
kick
yeah however you wish to interpret that
I guess
I get you I get you
Soju is good for that I like Japanese
alcohol it's good
enjoy it you also like that cup sake in
one cup
um no thank you I'm good actually
the uh the 100 yen they're like wine in
in the in the convenience store that's
like yeah you know 200 yen what yeah
like the cheapest wasn't it in like uh
in like a um
uh paper uh container yeah carton
yeah yeah like a carton wine yeah they
do that for sake too it's uh it's pretty
gnarly it doesn't taste very good at all
but I didn't imagine you using the word
gnarly gnarly yeah I have a very wide
vocabulary
you know
I broke up I got a wide vocab Erickson
[Music]
vocabulary sure
you'll probably just hear me randomly
use it though like I just did that's
when the best words come out
gennarley
is it gnarly no it's gnarly the G is in
fact silent
uh-huh all right all right
wow that was really cheap oh my God 80
off oh that's that's a good deal
it's a good time for me to buy the game
I guess at least it's cheap yup
it was good timing gnarly price come on
you're silly
[Music]
um
uh uh snow boots I know right some nice
fashionable snow boots for the jump King
yeah better better grip with the drip
yeah
true facts true facts
I want to make myself another drink but
I made this horrible concoction here you
know how some people
um some people like to drink for example
Red Bull and vodka it's like an energy
drink plus uh alcohol hard liquor yeah
yeah yeah some people like to do that um
including uh Papa Reaper no it sounds
extremely healthy yeah definitely I mean
listen he's still alive slash dead slash
a Reaper so I mean I kind of figured it
wasn't a big deal but ciao was really
freaking out
um because I put together a drink that
is technically the same thing but I
thought more accustomed to my taste
right it's um
is that bang energy drink with vanilla
vodka
um
people are saying you know what bang
tastes like uh bad but you know what oh
no
I'm not Kelly it's fine no no no no no
no there is like no way to control
yourself when you're like mid-air in
this game so it's really difficult
uh um anyway I made that concoction
because I went all the way down to the
Sewer level which is just bad it's not
where you want to be
um and so I said if I go down to the
sewers
um then I'm gonna make this a horrible
drink and so I did I went down to the
sewers and so I had to make that drink
um I took like two sips it felt like my
brain was like on fire but people say
that bang is really strong so it's like
not quite like Red Bull it's a little
more dangerous
um so now I have it here and I pretty
much can't drink it I'm looking at it
and it just looks like poison to me now
so um I mean
I don't really know what to do with it
I'll just throw it out
they should drink some normal water
I only have tea in my house right now
unfortunately
ah you can't drink the tap water I
always drink tap water oh no I can it's
just um
they don't want to go to the sink right
now
because my mouth under the faucet yeah
not right now maybe later
real good thing you need a when you play
these kind of endurance streams you need
to Mage that like mentally supports you
but also gives you like whatever you
need like gives you a foot massage while
you're doing it or brings you a sandwich
or sings a song yours sounds so good
right now I haven't eaten dinner yet so
I'm wondering what to eat
I heard he had a sandwich today though
well two sandwiches even better double
double is better yeah
yeah why not why not having a hard time
finding like the lunch meat that I
usually like to eat at the store these
days
it's always sold out neat yeah like
turkey chicken that kind of stuff oh
yeah
like turkey and chicken hey are you well
you want me to choose chicken
no I want you if anything to choose
turkey oh why oh because oh I see I see
because the kfp Hey listen
I'm not eating the KFC I'm not eating
the kfp employees all right you're doing
a good job I don't wanna I don't want to
harm them I'm the only one who's allowed
to eat them I'm just kidding oh wait
what the [\h__\h] what if she's not just
kidding though guys what if she's not
no I have to I have to share my chickens
with people because we're a fast food
chain and oh but of course you know how
it goes you know how it goes business
really
mm-hmm yeah I feel ya
I feel ya
oh this is getting really difficult
you trying to make a thumbnail with you
looking kind of frightened
I'm trying to add like a blue dryer yeah
oh yeah spooky effect nice nice nice
blue blue forehead makes people look
scared yeah that's right
that like freaked out look oh dang it oh
wait what
fine all right game I see this area is
just really tough got it
you need to focus should I leave no no
please stay it would be worse if you
weren't here but I mean it would be the
same don't feel bad about leaving
don't feel bad about having to go this
stuff
don't feel bad about if you have to go
but but you're not a you're not a
nuisance
oh
my God
oh no oh this game
this game
and it's fine why can't you use the
audio control is it broken yeah so I was
playing a game today with um I mean dang
it with AME and Ina and Iris and I tried
to plug in my PlayStation controller
something weird happened the chord like
made a weird noise and now it doesn't
work uh oh no my computer anymore and I
have to use the steam controller that I
just got and it's fine it's just it's
not what I'm used to so
of course there's going to be like a
little
a little debuff on me yeah
no
that won't stop you well no uh maybe it
might oh boy
yeah and now we begin The Descent again
and again
[Music]
four two years KDA cover isn't that
coming out and it's like how long was it
yeah tomorrow it's tomorrow night so
it's like maybe less than 24 hours from
now but I'm excited
I can't wait for you to hear it I do
some rap
obviously I think you I mean yeah the
the girls
name is literally Kelly so like it would
be silly if I didn't
oh wait Kelly
yeah but she says Cali and I'm like hey
that's me whoa what a coincidence it's
like it it would be odd if I didn't
feeling a connection
yeah
oh no we'll make it back I know we will
someday
I have you have you made
progress in this oh yeah
okay yeah that snowy level I like hadn't
gotten to the higher upper levels yet so
yeah
so a little bit of progress yeah
little by little that's what's important
maybe late League of Legends long time
ago yeah oh a little bit but have you
ever played fortnite no no uh
unfortunately I have not
unfortunately have you
you affordable Kiara no no no never
played that or a League of Legends or
any of those games oh
not not saying they're what uh what do
they have in common come on the reason
to play them
yeah Oh no you're so low no yeah this is
just this is the nature of this game
what I like that the name of that area
was called bargainburg bargainburg yeah
arguing about the game
to the top that's like a nice way to
think of it it's really just because
there's one guy who tries to sell you
like a bad pair of shoes I mean they're
not bad but like they're just they're
just like they look cool they're not
actually like helpful or anything so
you don't really need to get them it'll
be cool if you could but
I'm sure they can't beat the air Maurice
oh definitely not there's no way
you can't beat those aramores you just
can't
you just can't try as people might
those are the shoes to beat
[Music]
place
yeah slip and slide and ride that rhythm
[Music]
so glad you joined in with that
yeah it's a good song
you're gonna pop up pop
good old memories that movie is like so
old if you really think about it
like when it came out yeah
it really is like kind of old
does that mean we are old maybe I mean
we are oldest time so I mean
I guess it makes sense
maybe it really isn't all that long ago
for us then being Eternal beings and
[\h__\h]
yeah exactly you always gotta consider
that yeah our sense of time kind of gets
you know skewed
stuff like that you know
that was way too long okay
okay you gonna beat Outlast tomorrow
Kiara
uh today but no why not wouldn't I yeah
no what if you really like it
I will not like it what if you like the
game and you think wow these monsters
are so cute I can't help but I want to
see him again
he's probably not gonna get even close
to halfway through but I don't know how
long is that game anyway um when I
completed it it took me about six hours
which is probably kind of long but
[Music]
um are you gonna have a heart heart rate
monitor
yes I bought one for this purpose oh I'm
gonna ask I need to ask you like where
you got yours and what program you're
using because I wanted to for the final
Journal yeah it's pretty simple and like
um like the the app that I'm using it
works with all kinds of different heart
rate monitors so you don't have to get
the exact same one nice heck yeah
because like I have one like I bought
one but I just I don't know if it'll
actually like work or like show on
screen kind of thing you know so
I see yeah
I'll hit you I'll hit you up later and
I'm gonna watch it
I'm happy to help thank you yo put it on
your wrist I wonder
ah there's like different types but the
one that I have I put around my
um
they have ones like that huh that's
where the heart is okay true you must
probably get the most accurate reading
there oh dang it
a lot of times
wrist oh I see I see you know less etchy
versions I see
now there's really nothing edgy about
that though it's just normal yeah your
heart's there there's also you know some
some other things there but
nothing weird nothing weird about it
yeah that hey did you know that uh buba
is the name of a Pokemon in Japanese
yeah it's it's the fire there's like a
fire Pokemon I think it's magma yeah
yeah I recently I randomly I randomly
found that out
I know that in Japanese they do like eve
even more punny names than in in English
and German and so on yeah like Japanese
names are really really
funny puns you know what I'm proud yeah
is it because they like have like Fire
come out of their mouth and they make
like a
boom sound I wonder I just thought it
was kind of funny imagine if they kept
if they kept that um
[Music]
they can't they couldn't keep that in
the English version they just couldn't
no it's because they got booba on their
heads don't say that no way
like a butt to me
I
oh man
it's a very astute observation that you
made there
I must say
incredible oh man what a beautiful sight
if you wear a Pokemon Kelly which one
would you be ah Scraggy
no just kidding that's a lie Scraggy is
my favorite because it has like it's
like the pants down like like saggy
pants uh looking purple yeah and I like
his face
fairly useless one yeah but I like it it
looks cool I mean I buffed mine up to be
super strong on my team but that's
because I like it a lot I think maybe
Dustin Noir or Duskull I think is really
cool
no that's that's quick yeah that's cool
the school looks like death Sensei look
him up
go ah
oh he's cute yeah right straight up
death sensei in Pokemon form
this makes me really happy I love that
Pokemon
full death Sensei team
[Music]
yeah what about you would you be ho ho
is that yeah like people say like um or
Moltres or so or would you see Moltres
yeah that's really badass I like that
yeah Firebird I don't really have a
favorite Pokemon for some reason did you
play it a lot
um I played a couple ones yeah yeah
[Music]
which ones
and some on the Game Boy Color in
advance and someone on the GameCube I
played that Pokemon Colosseum
that was so good I love Coliseum I love
that one yeah
it was so different from the other ones
but it's freaking good it was very well
made I think like a 3D Pokemon game I
miss it Pokemon Colosseum yeah good
story too very cool characters yeah
yeah and then um from the recent ones I
already obviously played the switch one
and I played the the one on the DS the
most recent one the Sun and Moon one
yeah
um but I think in between I might have
not
played many hmm you ever played until
like the I don't know GameCube fans I
see do you ever play Pokemon like
Sapphire and Ruby
Emerald all right let me look it up
those are my faves
those are my favorite Pokemon games
[Music]
well that that's on the Game Boy so I I
probably played it a little bit at least
yep I remember playing on my Game Boy SP
oke Pokemon pinball yeah
whoa little pinball game I've never
played it but it was fun remember that
time when PCS always came with that
pinball game nowadays they like the
windows doesn't
um sell Windows anymore with a newer
Windows doesn't come anywhere with the
pinball machine yeah I remember playing
that during like uh computer class
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah or whenever we
watch a video about the theory of why
pinball is not being included anymore in
the recent windows versions there are
theories about why yeah
like what
I forgot
well you can't just drop that knowledge
on me
now I want to know just like a business
thing
it's very unfortunate because like I
love that too yeah I remember dream Dad
yeah I could
yeah I want to stream Minesweeper do you
know Minesweeper yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
fine sweepers we've been joking about uh
playing mindsweeper sometimes yeah but
uh yeah well someday again uh very low
on the list of games
priority would you play Jump King before
that
no you'd play Minesweeper before jump
King
understandable probably like
um get over it before mine sleeper oh I
see gotcha
I don't know get over it is like
like at least you can like fly a little
bit I don't know like when you get in
space you get this
you get like you you you you like float
right yeah but Kiara there's a guy who
makes fun of you the whole time
I like that you like that
you you you think you will
but then then it'll happen and you'll
just think to yourself why why
it's there to make you angry but you
know
yeah but I like that kind of like
humor of of making me feel shitty
[Laughter]
maybe understand we will see one day one
day I'll play and get over it and we
will see yeah I wanna I will be there
um it's going I guess it could be worse
oh I always I always undershoot those
parts oh come on that was unfair that
the punishment did not fit the crime uh
wow that's oh that was a big drop like I
don't believe I deserved that I
understand if I go down like three
screens or so okay I probably deserve
that but that
I just don't believe it I mean the good
news is I'm grinding a lot though so
like I'm learning uh all of these parts
like really well so that like it's
muscle memory now at this point
and I can do them very quick but
one one thing that shows I'm making
progress is that most of the last
gameplay I spent in bargainburg you know
grinding instead of up here so
you know slowly but surely
someone wrote
a really smart comment in Japanese let
me read it to you okay
uh jumping is I'm trying to translate in
Jump King it's not about becoming faster
uh with like climbing up it's about
becoming faster with your recovery uh
yeah that's exactly that is the truth
that is a hundred percent true yes yeah
yeah smart
exactly it's not yeah just about
ascending quickly but yeah you every
time that you fall
um you can like if you're recovering
quicker and quicker and that's a good
sign shows that you're learning the game
yeah no I suppose you've been getting
better at that yeah but I still have a
long way to go like why like really
gonna fall six screens come on man come
on game I just uh what are you know do
you like you don't have much control
over your body when you're falling right
yeah you have no control when you're in
the air only when you're on the ground
you can choose what direction
even a little bit of of like like when
you're falling like can you like not
move at all like at all yeah
you can't you have to decide oh you have
to decide
um what direction you're going to jump
and how much you're going to jump before
you jump and that's it
[Music]
yeah it's pretty rough but it feels good
to play it's hard to explain it's hard
but it feels good to play like it's a
well-made game
I say oh that was unfair but it really
wasn't it's just me not
getting it perfect like the game wants
that's all that it is you know
you know at least you're like still
nice to the game because it's a
well-made game I I can recognize that ah
it's just if I suck at it that's my own
fault I gotta get good at it
[Music]
uh it's just just like life small grind
ever forward ever up
yeah
oh
[Music]
oh oh yeah see how Megan there we go
slowly but surely what what do you have
planned for today Kiara just playing out
last
after I'm dead with this
breakfast
oh yeah and then I don't know I gotta do
some things though gotta record
something
[Music]
there's always always some things on my
list yeah yeah always something actually
I got a call you got to give someone a
call before the next
40 minutes I think oh I see I see busy
busy bird
just gotta make a doctor's appointment
oh yeah yeah yeah recently I made like
all my appointments like a chiropractor
and like other like doctor appointments
that I got to do
um and I felt really proud of myself
because I didn't get to do that at all
this month because it's been busy
was a good feeling I feel that yeah it's
a good feeling to get your [\h__\h] out of
the way you know
indeed
this is not correct that's not where I
need to be a little further
okay
that'll do it
oh this area is so nice and slow like
the snow part that it makes it really
good for like talking people I think so
I'd prefer to stay in the snow part when
bae comes in
like I need some tea you should make
yourself some tea my dude
he's good for the soul and for the
throat and really for the soul
honey yeah good for the throat
I was singing way too much this month
you were singing away I was singing way
too much this month Oh you mean in your
Coyote's or yeah
yeah and like I did like several karaoke
too many especially if you count the rap
karaoke too kind of like cut
the endurance as well yes I was learning
how to rap really difficult songs
like nailed it before even though like
yeah but it wasn't like perfect you know
I wanted to make a perfect
yeah
yeah I don't know it was fun though you
underestimate yourself
e it was fun but whoa okay what if I
bounced off the wall here I bet I could
I I'm a good rapper Too Kelly yeah I
noticed when you did your little rap
about me playing this game I was like
wow you got bars oh no I can I can do
like Fergie wraps oh yeah yes I bet you
can't I was gonna say do one for us now
but clearly you can't
um
you can't because DMC it when I when
I've been when I've been rapping my
Fergie songs oh yeah my my viewers were
always like yo Cali's been real quiet
Cali's been real quiet
it's so funny because there's no way
that I'm better than you at all but like
it's I love it it's just kind of funny I
agree so ironic I agree that is funny
[Music]
the part where I always freak out
because I don't know this is being quiet
and of course she's quiet because she's
not in the streams yeah
yeah I'm not there to to be like hey
do you feel that like because like when
when
people think about you they think about
rap and like obviously for example
they're at the KDA uh cover or the one
you did like the the original that you
did with Fatima and all those like you
keep on getting like in invited for
rapping do you ever feel like you want
to be more seen as a singer or are you
fine with that
um definitely rep 100 oh yeah I mean
it's just
I like singing but it's like
I don't know I feel like rap is the
thing that I love the most you know okay
yeah
that's good it'll always be my fave but
um
oh that jump though that jump the oh
wait I didn't did I see it I flew across
the screen oh my gosh this is the
furthest I've gotten
yeah hold on can I chill for a minute
uh option you can save
um yeah but it's not like you can just
like uh like save your progress and then
restart it if you like fall a lot it
doesn't work like that you save it and
then you quit
um
so like you come back and it's like it's
that kind of thing like um but like
couldn't you like quit and like every
time you fall down like you just quit
every time yeah you quit and then like
open it again isn't that
um that work Chad can you save scum this
I mean I'm not gonna do that but
hahaha
that's like I mean yeah exactly you're
good at this yeah
in other games so yeah yeah saves coming
you can't save scum okay gotcha see I
figured there was something that
something about it you can't gura hey
gura no it deletes the save when you oh
I see I see okay
you have to it's safe yeah I assume it
deletes your save yeah
then what is the saving for
so you can save the spot where you're
ending to go take a break
oh oh my God yeah
can I I know I can't stop here I know I
have to keep playing but I don't want I
mean I want to but
you don't want to fall down again is
that what it is it's an interesting like
little like
Slice of Life thing in my opinion
because in a sense it's like life
you know like it's a life lesson
a lot of times we don't jump because
we're afraid to fall
all the way back down there is a saying
that you should end things when they're
at a high point not when it's like at
the like lowest you know what I mean
yeah that's I know you should quit now
but yeah yeah yeah exactly
song cost fallacy you guys
they call some calls fancy
yeah deep yeah I know chat deep right
real deep
no way oh
one thousand almost
1400 Falls you had quite a few yeah
yeah
that sounds like it destroys a person
at its core yeah I suppose so I can see
that
I don't know which way to go
um
taking a million years at this thumbnail
I saw where I'm supposed to go
presumably
oh you didn't fall down though good job
I didn't but I saw like a step but I
think I need to try and get on
um
oh man
punishment at one thousand five hundred
well good we have already I I've
suggested to her because this is an
endurance stream that if she doesn't
finish it the game today then her
punishment will be eating a durian
because of endurance you know no I don't
wanna ah okay it's fine we can make it
back up again we can make it back up
again also yes this game is the
punishment yeah true fact
no no I don't want to eat that I don't
want to eat that yeah I believe you
even though you didn't even know what it
is but trust me it's better to not eat
it
or maybe you'll like it because you know
you like natto
true
that is very true so who knows you know
always possible
always possible Anything is Possible
thank you
oh they're gonna go in the chat again
durian is good during this okay okay
okay but you gotta accept that you know
other people don't like it some people
like it some people don't like it same
with carrots for example love of
zucchinis or broccoli or or or even
strawberries so people don't like
strawberries which is unbelievable what
the [\h__\h]
wow that hurts me
that people don't like strawberries yeah
strawberries are great
strawberries but it's very very very
rare breed
okay
Allie
[Music]
you get in there eventually
I forgot the wrap that I did before so
sorry oh just kidding that's not what
you were talking about okay
yeah you had you had some good Rhymes I
kind of like forget what they were but
they were good
the stream is not
where the stream will be I completely
forget the lyrics but they were popping
they were flames
absolute flames
we're gonna make it I know we're gonna
make it
ripe durian has alcohol in it hey
what really all right and you get drunk
from a durian you can see it
yeah like you can get um I mean well if
you think wine has grapes in it so
I mean I can kind of see it
yeah look
well I mean
grapes
um
oh man
foreign
yes you can get drunk from drink eating
too much durian
how about a a durian eating endurance
stream where you have to eat it until
you get drunk from the turkey
follow my stupid ideas
wait that was your idea
no yeah that was my idea just now but
don't don't don't know nah
could be good content oh boy
all right think about the content
I gotta think about all for the content
I believe in you but I think I feel like
I'm I'm distracting you no not at all
this part's better to have uh people
around with but if you gotta go then you
gotta go so don't even worry go get that
breakfast I don't
know my best
can come around yeah she might be busy
though but if she's around I'd be happy
to have a little chat
I'm just here suffering you know it'd be
like that I'll leave you here then
because I I'm I still have to finish my
phone bill and breakfast and call a
doctor and all that stuff so yeah good
luck
thank you I'll do my best make yourself
some be fast yeah I'll do my best thank
you little Kelly make it to the tab yeah
yeah
[Music]
I'll do my best thank you
later Kiara
there she goes there she go is he busy
bird
all good though
now we're definitely we got this you
guys
I do feel like this is a pretty good
area to like talk to people in general
though
just because it's nice and kind of slow
moving you know you got to wait for a
lot of stuff ah you gotta wait for oh
come on a lot of stuff
you gotta wait for like things to pop
off for the wind to finally turn in your
favor you know stuff like that so no
okay fine the wind is pushing me
into the currents again I feel the blood
in my veins
here we are the Dank and no
oh
yeah
I wonder if I should change the title
again
yeah Dragon inside of me
waiting for friends that's awaiting
it's awaiting
all right there we go all right guys we
got this oh
pausing is giving me all kinds of
anxiety right now because when I unpause
it at that one time oh man
yeesh
I almost uh almost lost it there that
was bad
[Music]
yeah okay
not an all the way full power jump if
the wind is going full power but this
way yes
a little more okay
ah bad I should do full power at that
time
come on come on oh
I also gotta just pay attention to where
the wind is blowing you know
okay here we go
that was very close
I was very close
you're getting really close to the next
safe space awesome thank you thank you
for letting me know good luck with the
last few jumps thank you my man we'll
see uh we'll see how it goes
I'll keep doing my best
I'm not giving up
we've come too far to give up
here we go
right now I kind of want to just
yeah yeah yeah that works
instead of this way what if
trying to see the The Bouncing
trajectory here
be this way but rather maybe the right
let's see I think I got this
no not quite not quite not quite okay
understood understood
I'll remember how I did it at some point
but it's fine this is nice and chill
right now ah no no wait wait okay
nice and chill Jesus
this is nice and chill
get it haha literally chill because
there's snow got him
bottom
it's max power unlike power while the
wind is blowing right well up there okay
well we'll give it a shot
no why did I think that would work I
don't really know why I quite thought
that but uh I was wrong
hey
oh let's get the [\h__\h] out whoa
Sunshine what's up hi I'm playing jump
King how are you I saw it
I spoke too I thought there was a ghost
in the room because you made like a tiny
sound and I was like
okay
just say you didn't really jump as much
as I thought oh yeah
yes
how are you doing are you almost done
with the game
um you know from what I've seen from
chat it looks like I'm
like some people were saying 65 70 done
with the game
so it could be worse
it could be worse
I'm gonna look up a little map
yep I was thinking about I wanted to go
look at the map
um but I'm not letting myself go
spoilers
but yeah go check that out
okay yeah yeah yeah yes
set 70 I would say seventy percent
yes ah yes okay good
oh thank goodness because I know okay
good man you made it so far what the
heck
I like games like this I don't know
what was that
I was gonna ask if you're playing on the
switch
oh no I'm playing on a PC but I'm using
uh like a really dinky like steam
controller
mm-hmm yeah my PlayStation controller
broke sadly
oh no I saw that you oh my God like why
would that happen
all right well now I'm [\h__\h] all right
cool that's great awesome fantastic yep
we love to see that all right great
down we go and down we go I've already
been to the sewers I've already been to
the sewers today so that's my sewer trip
yeah no more no more sewers please game
I think
I saw that you did like a the Basu game
playing this
prank calls
yep that's where the Lightning McQueen
one came from
did you did you like write did you like
write that
girl
no
no I just took the hello ma'am do you
have a moment to talk about our Lord and
savior oh Jesus
Christ and uh I just replaced it with
Lightning McQueen I pulled up the
Lightning McQueen Wikipedia page and
then he's right off that such a thing
exists such such a thing exists
yes wow
I'm glad that we're living in this
timeline
it's a great timeline
actually seen the cars
um I think I saw the first one yeah many
years ago yeah have you seen yeah a
marathon watch ah it's a good idea
no please I didn't mean to okay
I forget this area so it's been a while
since I've been down here
um yeah I'm always down to watch uh a
little cars I also recall watching the
movie in theaters it's been a long time
since I've seen it oh my God it was like
one of those like weird situations where
I think like my dad was really busy or
something and so like he had like one of
his friends take me and my sister and
like their kids and it was like weird
it's like I have like I have like a
weird memory of that I'm like why are we
here together
who are you people
yeah this is my weird sweet Tweet Summer
of o6 yeah back in the day
back in the day when cars was popping
off and then I remember it became
relevance again because like for the the
new movie they had like a really
dramatic trailer
[Music]
yeah I think it was cars three the one
where like Lightning McQueen retires or
something like that
yeah like the poster for it like made it
look like um like a drama like car movie
like it was extremely dramatic looking
like they took them out back and
yeah something like that like it was
like a car crash or something yeah cars
four cars Four Guys four okay
it's like this is a design Cars movie
let me see go check out The Branding for
that the advertisements
cars four
uh oh that's where they had uh
oh no oh geez what is this
this is like some deviantART oh wait
what oh no
wait I gotta show you something
okay can you take this guy what is this
if it's some deviantART [\h__\h] hold
on let me adjust my chair
that's what I think
so wide wide load isn't that at the name
of a deadbeat oh my God it looks like
it looks like the um like the ass part
is like um dead bodies
yeah I feel like really look close
why is this what did you look up to find
this girl
cars for poster
I totally like them
and see 17.
most of it is like this
oh my God
oh yeah no I don't know I couldn't find
the
here I bet I can find is that when he's
in Italy
I'm actually not sure I didn't know that
Lightning McQueen went to Italy a lot of
SEC
um
as far as three years
could chill like
ciao
it is for trailer
drama
where the [\h__\h] is it
fire sport
it was super dramatic
now it's cars four
cars four he goes to Italy Italy was
cars two oh my God there is no cars Fork
huh
Cars movie drama
oh here we go found it
found it here hold on
Cars movie
Lightning McQueen die you're tired
McQueen dies
this is the official it's from the
official oh my God he did die
oh my God the rubber yeah the trailer
was apparently really dark the first
teaser trailer for Pixar's Cars 3 is
uncomfortably dark
they killed him
oh my word
yeah yeah that's it that's the one from
this moment Everything Will Change
like why did it need to be this way
so yeah that's uh that's all I think of
when I think of cars
um
yeah that's right one and only the only
one who could direct a movie like that
incredible no lightning it looks like
Owen Wilson maybe that's it yeah because
Owen Wilson voices the character
yeah okay
yeah he does I only just figured that
out actually so
yeah I had no idea
wow
iconic
absolutely isn't he in grown-ups too the
grown-ups oh yeah yeah the Adam Sandler
movie of course I know every Adam
Sandler movie yeah he's in grown-up
what's your favorite Adam Sandler movie
Mr Deeds either that or uh Happy Gilmore
have you ever seen Happy Gilmore
uh I think so that's filming the gulf
yes the golf movie yeah
yeah love me some happy girls
feels like you would like to move yeah
yeah good old Adam uh not a huge fan of
the recent movies but um also naughty
there's some there are some stinkers in
the old ones too
um like Billy Madison have you ever seen
Billy Madison
Billy Madison the one where he like goes
back to school
he has to go through all the grades
no I haven't seen this one uh maybe skip
it unless I mean
I mean it's just it was a lot funnier to
me when I was younger I guess I'll say
but if you want to if you're bored one
night
um and you have had a couple drinks
why not
why not top 10 worst Adam Sandler movies
oh boy let's let's see what are they rip
the Band-Aid off
um
[Music]
well yours is not on the list they say
number 10 is you don't mess with the oh
I remember that one the Zone yeah that
thing yeah
that guy number one is
Just Go With It just go oh just go with
I mean I didn't think it was good but I
think it was terrible either
it was like fine this one with Jennifer
Aniston okay
my embarrassing
um I saw
a click oh yeah in theaters yeah and I
cried no dude me too
okay
no most that's the reaction of most
people
um yeah to cry so don't worry you're
good
um yeah me as well
um yeah that's a little sad one oh
there's that one good movie though good
movie what about um have you seen I'm
trying to think what other Adam Sandler
movies you may have seen uh have you
seen uncut gems
with a new one uh no it's on Netflix
it's uh it's not a comedy it's uh I mean
I guess it could be if you look at it
that way but Adam good old Adam is uh
kind of doing more of like a dramatic
role he does a really good job actually
like
it's actually a really good movie A lot
of people were uh oh dang it I forgot a
lot of people were uh surprised at Old
good old Adam
little he's he's holding a
he's holding some ice
um and it's a golden Furby yeah
I remember that yeah yeah golden Furby
interesting yeah
yeah he he plays like an interesting uh
role in that movie I don't know if you
have some time to kill recommend that
it's not bad yeah it's actually quite a
good movie
um which is surprising because you know
Adam said a good old Adam not ripping on
Adam he's just uh
you know Adam
I I wonder how he feels about that
though like how I guess the general
internet feels that he's like oh Adam's
saying like I wonder if that gets to him
I wonder to be more than just
oh Adam Sandler movie you know yeah yeah
no no I definitely damn it uh I
definitely [\h__\h] I'm sorry I feel that uh
for sure he
um I mean he gets to vacation with his
friends and make cool movies so that's
nice but I mean cool to him but you know
movies that he makes are just like
vacations for him and his friends which
is I guess damn it uh
an interesting
interesting way to look at it
um but yeah you know you gotta wonder
he's actually kind of like a private guy
so like you don't really hear like a lot
of how he feels about that kind of thing
I don't think
I think he accepted an award one time he
got for like worst actor I'm pretty sure
he did he's got to have like a like he
has like a good sense of humor I think
unless I'm wrong unless I'm thinking of
someone else
but I feel like he did I think he's
accepted all of them but he's I feel
like he took one of them
worst actor who even has an award for
that that's so cruel yeah
yeah the worst actor
yeah I mean it was like
I mean he's fine I wouldn't say the
worst but
man just the fact that somebody's like
yeah let's let's put somebody on the
pedestal for being the worst of the
worst so you can laugh at them yeah
here's an award for sucking idiot like
thanks
yeah especially if they do the thing
where they like you know how they call
ahead and say like hey you won this
award can you show up it's like hey Adam
you just got worst actor can you show up
and accept it prank call are you sure
this isn't a prank call my man yeah
I mean I'm sure it doesn't feel good
dang it I'm sure it doesn't feel great
but
he takes it in good spirits I mean he
gets Adam gets the last laugh you know
vacations with friends just chilling
making a movie yeah like sick I don't
know it sounds kind of nice
it does sound nice even if people are
laughing at you like cool
at least they're reacting right yeah
exactly exactly sometimes it's just
about getting a reaction you know hmm
yeah
well best of luck to him I guess anyway
that's uh my guilty pleasure uh Adam
Sandler uh movies if anyone asked me
that would be my answer
yeah
thank you Happy Gilmore Happy Gilmore
it's not a bad movie
still gave me some laughs we did a
little watch along uh here on the
channel
um so cute yeah it was fun I can't
remember why we did it
um but we watched Billy Madison first
and then Happy Gilmore and when we
watched Billy Madison I just uh I felt
really bad because I was like ah this
movie is not as good as I remember
you ever have movies like that where you
just like remember it being good and you
watch it again and you're like oh
oh whoopsies um
[Music]
did recently do that with a movie yeah
or actually do you ever do
you watch movies that you watched when
you were younger and you watch them when
you're a bit older
yeah and you're like wow this is about
this I had no idea I thought this was
about something else like I watched
Stuart Little for the first time in
years and the one of the main actors is
the guy from Hell House oh yeah yeah I
remember that guy
yeah remember that show and it's about I
think when I originally watched it I
thought it was it was like oh it's about
a mouse that is a kid and then it
actually turns out it's about an orphan
who gets stolen away by imposter parents
uh-huh and then
almost eaten alive by cats and then he's
abandoned by his adoptive family and
abandoned by his kidnapper family yeah
um I'm like wow that's kind of traumatic
for her wow to go through that [\h__\h] is
dark
but in the end he's reunited with his
adopted family yeah ah now that you're
oh my God you're open oh my God the
doors are opening holy [\h__\h] I'm
remembering scenes from the movie now oh
my gosh in in the gutter and then the
fake parents they come and take him away
and they say we're your real parents but
they're not his parents oh my God holy
[\h__\h] girl what have you done and they
Zoom away in a toy car
yeah I remember that and he almost
drowns in the washing machine that was
traumatic I remember that scene
yeah
I remember I was like yeah that was
really messed up I was like I did not
like that
Stewart Good Old Stuart Little what was
the reason for watching it again you
just kind of felt like it
I know you just see it and you're like
wow it's been a while since I've seen
that let's watch it
nice wow that is a movie I haven't
thought about for a long time
well Stuart it was a boat race too I
remember the boat race
M Night Shyamalan directed that movie
huh the same guy that did Airbender wait
no way
way dude
I might have no
thank you for enlightening me girl I had
no idea oh you got it F movie trivia
for movies we haven't seen in a long
time
I heard you're playing uh Outlast with
uh Kiara
I am so excited
yeah did you just think who would be
spooked with this game let's let's laugh
at Kiara
well I actually don't remember how it
came about exactly but she maybe maybe
chat was asking her like oh play horror
movie and she's like no no no no no I'm
not going with her no no no no and then
I popped and I was like Hey play out
less
play out last oh get a heart rate
monitor play with a heart rate monitor
let's see yeah
I played with a heart rate monitor and I
maxed out at 140. wait what that's
pretty high
I was pretty high am I resting my
resting my normal resting heart rate is
around 70 ish but during the stream it
was like a hundred I started the stream
at 120 I was like oh yeah oh no
yes that is spooky that's a game that'll
get your heart pounded I guess huh oh
absolutely and then even streaming gets
your heart pounding or am I get to mine
do you have a heart rate monitor have
you used one I do but like I don't know
how to get it to work on the Stream So I
was gonna ask like you and Kiara later
like what you use but I need it for do
maternal finale
which one do you have let's see
I'm gonna go look at the name sorry I
know you're trying to game but I'm
asking no any excuse to not continue
jumping up this mountain for like a
little bit longer one second
um let me find it let me find it hey
Chad if she doesn't jump then she
doesn't fall so technically it's
progress that's right this is progress
know it
let's see
um
[Music]
one sec I know it's around here
somewhere
hang on I'll be right back one second
anywhere
don't say anything weird
hey check guess what
did you know Calliope mori's favorite
animal
is a ring-tailed lemur did you know that
somewhere on the internet there's a
fan art of calliope Mori as a ringtail
lemur
I'm not I'm listen I'm not telling you
what you should and shouldn't Google but
[Music]
love you Maury
tail lemur oh
[Music]
oh
I know it's around here somewhere I'll
look for it more later but let me look
at the name of it
I wonder if Kelly likes to move it move
it huh wait what hold on a minute I'm I
return what was that you just said what
was that quip was that quip right there
do you like to move and move it
um wow what a question
um depends on how I'm feeling gura how
about you do you like to move it move it
occasionally
yeah
um
I'm never gonna live that [\h__\h] now did I
tell you about uh
did I tell you about
I answered like um like a question
about like what
like
animal I'd be
like I didn't really think about the
question
no no no what are you talking about so
because you guys got ears right right uh
for your models so I thought I wonder
what animal I would be because I don't
necessarily want to have cat ears I feel
like everyone has cat ears I'd like to
or not everyone but you know two members
already have cat ears I don't really
want to have cat ears so maybe I should
do something else so I was just thinking
out loud and I was like what
theoretically like
like what animal would I be
I believe and then somebody asked me a
question and I wasn't really thinking
about it but I believe they used the
word fursona and they said what is your
fursona and I said a lemur
I said uh a ring-tailed lemur
and people I was just thinking like cute
tail and ears right that's what I was
thinking but that's not what uh everyone
else was thinking and I lost I think
like 5K followers after I responded to
that question yeah I mean honestly
though best best 5K followers I ever
lost because it was worth it but like
that that uh that happened yeah
gotta weed them out you know
gotta wait out to me
yes weed out the people who aren't fans
of lemur people you know
that was a word I hadn't heard in a long
time too
oh I
well I mean you have one
I refuse to answer this yeah good
because you'll lose 5K followers on
Twitter
so just be careful with what you say
yeah
it's a smart thing my man of our already
part shark so I guess I mean I don't
know but let's go I want to see like
full-on gura like is a shark like not
like a cute anime girl shark I want to
see you like a shark shark
oh this
there's that picture somebody has I
think they did it with kodone as well
but it's just a shark wearing the the
hood yeah that's right just a real ass
shark yeah yeah that's what I want to
see
that's what everyone wants to see so the
world needs to see
all right yeah
I don't know about that one well just
listen I'm just letting you know you
know just so you're aware of like what
the public news
I think the public needs more discussion
about uh ringtail lemurs Callie have you
seen did you watch zaboomafoo
I've heard of that before but I can't I
have no clue what you're talking about
but I've heard of that
what is it
is a a kid's show from PBS Kids starring
a ringtail lemur name is Abu mafu and uh
the Wright brothers I think which were
two guys that would teach kids about
like wild animals and their their
stuff and they had a closet full of junk
and they'd always open the closet being
like let's go get each other closet and
then they open and it would shave it oh
no and it would fall on them oh wait I
remember this now right I remember the
ringtail lemurs now
you probably remember the theme song if
you heard it
I bet if I heard it I would know what it
was but yeah oh my God
wow
um
okay
thanks for reminding me of that
um watch on yeah I'm down if you are
I mean I'm down to watch anything really
can we do that we already have to watch
The Matrix too though
oh that's true
yeah what was the other movie oh never
mind okay no we can we can talk about it
we probably can't watch it but um yeah
Kung Fury
I'm gonna look that up because yeah
yeah it's uh that's a movie yeah
pong Fury story David Hasselhoff
yeah
Kung Fury a fury yeah Kung Fury I just
feel like uh you should just I just want
you to watch it that's all
that's all I want can I watched the
trailer yeah
sure watch the trailer watch the trailer
and I'm gonna cry as I try to figure out
where to go from here
come Fury
oh wow
yeah Miami
what is this oh no what is is it CGI
what is this
um great question
can you just kick flip a police car yeah
yes he did
this is uh this is Kung Fury
a lot of things happen in kung fu
it's like uh 80s inspired kung fu movie
it's not it's free
on YouTube
oh my God
I like how the arcade machine just flips
them off like yeah yeah I mean I mean he
did it first so
that's true yeah
foreign
no I don't mess up okay
I'll do my best
no damn it
you should mess up yeah I did it's fine
though it's fine
I'm gonna go for it
we're fine we're fine we're all good in
the hood
oh my God
so I recommend you like watch it on your
own time I was probably gonna do like a
Members Only Watch along but
I'm okay it looks good I reckon I
recommend I recommend it I've seen it
like three times uh it's pretty good oh
my God yeah a couple couple laughs a
couple Chuckles
definitely got away
yes we will watch
the other Matrix is that's right that's
right we do
what
oh
the game saw what I was trying to do and
was like no no Cali no you don't
do not
wait I was watching the movie not the
trailer the movie's 30 minutes yeah it's
short
oh I was like this is a Long Trailer
geez oh I was watching the movie yeah
yeah that's the movie it's a short movie
it's a very short watch but a good one
My High
yeah
oh
I think I may have done it
let me pull up the stream
ah yes
wait
I got lag
or that delay hold on it's fine
I just want to savor this moment
I see you you're about to you're about
to enter the red hole tunnel yup Chapel
perilous baby we're in the chapel we're
in the Train table we're in the chapel
oh
man this feels good feels good if we
fall down the hole though I'm gonna be
sad but I think it should be fine
uh-huh if we fall back down to the
sewers I'm just gonna cry I'm just I'm
literally just gonna burst it
don't [\h__\h] don't mess with me game
don't mess with me game the game heard
me talking it knows man we are also good
at jinxing I mean it's weird though girl
because sometimes I'll jinx it like good
and then also bad which leads me to
believe that like it just Jinx thing
isn't a thing
okay interesting yeah it's my theory but
do you jinx yourself
oh all the time yeah
all the time do you believe in the moon
landing
oh holy [\h__\h]
um
you don't have to answer that I mean we
can move on I merely said it for comedic
effect I know I know it's funny
my only fear is is uh is polarizing my
audience not not someone watching
targeting me I gotcha I just said it for
funnies no it's okay no I did it's I'm
always I'm always laughing inside girl
you're good oh that's good do you
believe in the Illuminati
as a triangle right yes the triangle
with the i in it
yeah
do you uh what are your thoughts on that
every time I think about it I think
about the people that respell naughty as
n-a-u-g-h-t-year naughty funny
yeah the Illuminati oh Twitter yeah
the place eh do I need a Halloween plans
I want to get a custom made cosplay of
Dante Oh I thought you're gonna say
Crash Bandicoot but that works too
that's exciting no heck yeah
I'm excited I want you to do that I want
to see that
I don't think oh yeah oh oh I could take
pictures yeah yeah yeah yeah but I was
thinking you'd probably be able to hear
it on stream like the sound of the Fake
Plastic rubbing together oh hell yeah
oh hell yeah what are you gonna be for
Halloween me
um let's see
for Halloween
I'm gonna be myself but but for when we
get together that's a secret so I uh
can't answer
oh that's true oh yeah yeah I'm just
gonna make like a pumpkin stew for
Halloween
in Japan oh yeah yeah they're green but
the inside's orange yummy yes yes yeah
you like you cut open you get like a
little pumpkin right and then you cut
off the top and then you like you know
like take everything out like dig it and
whatever and then uh you make the stew
that way but like it's pretty like
standard stuff you use like different
vegetables as well you can use like the
inside as well because in Japan like
eating pumpkins is like it's a lot
easier than uh in the states
and um and you just you use the pumpkin
skin as a bowl
yeah and then you put this like the
bread bowl yeah like a bread bowl except
it's a pumpkin
that's healthy yeah I mean you don't
really eat it you know you don't really
eat it but
yeah
I don't know what the [\h__\h] to do here do
I bounce off I used to buy it yeah
what was that and then East but and then
you you stab it a bunch you put in the
microwave because it's really hard to
cut right yeah when you skin it
depending if you want the vitamins and
nutrients or you want the vibrant orange
color yeah oh and then you cut it up
into pieces and you you you you stir fry
it with some onions and butter and then
you blend it together with some
vegetable broth or chicken broth then
you add some cream and then you get like
it sounds really good though
I should make it for you sometime please
please please make some for me I hear
that I hear you that you're a chef is
this true uh
I mean I had a can of beans for today
last night so I don't know I mean I
think that counts personally oh thanks
back open a can of beans and a dream
when you were in it the other day oh
really what was I doing uh we were all
meeting together all the myths we were
all coming together for the first time
and you gave me a tour of your your
place it was like MTV Cribs oh nice
and then I started snooping through your
cabinets and I'm wondering about the
accuracy
I look through your kitchen cabinets and
it was
a lot of ramen mm-hmm
but that's pretty much it oh and then
you had like One Singular cup and one
plate
yeah a big booze cabinet it was mostly
booze
um yeah
and then wait what else was it
a lot of Tupperware ooh okay nice in
your fridge your fridge was energy drink
uh-huh and yogurt oh okay
um interestingly interestingly enough
you're actually pretty accurate uh for a
lot of that because recently I I
accidentally bought like 50 packages of
like uh these like squeezy yogurt packs
that like I didn't realize I was getting
50 of them
um yeah so that was kind of weird and
now I still have them and like I don't
eat them very much
um but yeah recently that's how that's
kind of how it was before I started like
deciding I wanted to cook more often
instead of you know just eating instant
stuff all the time I still have a couple
cup noodles though I'm like thinking of
going and making one in a second here
yeah you got me you got me thinking
about cup noodles man
um you could make the yogurts in the
smoothies you could like add them to
Smoothie as like frozen if you freeze
them yeah I bet that I can but um I have
like frozen fruits as well so yeah that
would make a nice smoothie now that you
mentioned near me yeah thanks for the
idea girl I didn't really know what to
do with them because they're just kind
of sitting in there so
you eat healthy
um I mean sometimes I'll have a salad
you know but
I'm more a fan of like making my own
pasta and stuff like that
in fact maybe I want like from scratch
pasta no I don't like make the noodles
for myself like a I would like boil it
here let me see you should get a pasta
maker
a pasta maker
oh my God you could take the pasta for
me
it's so easy I've seen videos I saw this
person or I guess it was like haha meme
to make different flavor pasta you add
the flour and the water and then
whatever flavoring you want inside like
I saw somebody made pickle pasta so they
did flour and then instead of water they
added pickle juice and food coloring and
it pushes out noodles and then you just
boil it
how though that ah
Magic
I mean that sounds cool but
what the [\h__\h]
it sounds like a pain in the butt to
clean though yeah maybe I want to try
ghost pepper pasta you're at ghost
pepper you can make it yeah oh it sounds
bad do you like spicy
um that's a good question it like it
depends I like spicy noodles especially
clear noodles
um and I like like spicy uh sometimes
spicy like black Curry is really good
um
maybe I'm just saying that because I'm
looking at
I'm looking at Chicago pizza have you
ever had Japanese Chicago pizza that's
probably a dumb question but
you should look up Japanese Chicago
Pizza it just doesn't look like anything
I've seen in my life
Japanese Chicago Pizza
it looks like soup is it wait what
yeah
it looks like a soup right
yeah like what the bowl of fun dude yeah
like what though like it's just
why
is it black on the outside what do they
do to it did they burn in I mean I think
it just it kind of like depends on what
you want I think maybe this is not like
Squid Ink I don't know
squidding yeah squid meat is squid me
it's squid meat I see oh no
you would be you'd be surprised what
kind of stuff they have
um
oh I know they have like
corn on their Pizza
yeah yeah and mayonnaise yeah sometimes
they do things
yeah yeah all kinds of stuff
um you should have a pizza party yeah
I'm gonna send you a picture of like
this one thing on the menu
yes I'm not gonna like say it out loud
but I'm gonna show it to you it's just
ridiculous they have like all kinds of
ridiculous Pizza in Japan interestingly
enough I wouldn't be surprised if there
was like popcorn pizza or like
stuff like that
weird it's just like odd
yeah but anyway I think I'm gonna get
pasta let me let me get past it
yummy pasta just read the description
like what the [\h__\h]
yeah
oh no
no no no no no sometimes the
descriptions for like things that you
can get in Japan like uh like food wise
it's just like huh no no no like they'll
claim to do things like like ridiculous
college and pizza colleges
no extra electrolyte smoothie that makes
you jump that makes you jump like really
long really far you can do parkour off
of tall buildings
like sometimes I'm just like really
hey you want laser beam eyes eat this
pizza
[Laughter]
all right
I believe that
this could take me a while this Chapel
here I was thinking I was in like the
safe place but like this is actually
tough
as long as you don't fall down you'll be
good yeah yeah I think yeah for the most
part with this game yeah
I think that's definitely a thing no
pressure though
what did you think about the game Gira
did you enjoy it or a game this game oh
this game yeah uh
I was kind of having an out of body
experience when I played it so I didn't
get very far I didn't play very much
either I see I'd like to try it again
though yeah I recommend it I bet you
could do it
oh I bet you could do it
[Music]
you're like a gamer right you're
um
I think I'm about as much of a gamer as
I am a chef so okay
with beans for dinner equivalent of a
gamer I see
that makes a lot more sense now
I can pull it out when it counts but
don't expect anything fantastic to
happen yeah oh that's a nice way to
think about it I'd like to become that
kind of gamer someday a can of beans
gamer yeah someday no you're more than a
can of beans gamer you're like uh
I can only jump gamer gamer who can only
platform
only push button one button
I love the the falling animation on the
right side of your screen oh yeah isn't
it super super good
yeah Facebook
please yeah
yeah maybe I can go from that corner all
the way over there
yeah this game makes me want to face
plant quite a bit
fun it's fun I like it
um
we'll see we'll see if I can beat it
anytime soon but I would like to this
seems like um like a really nice safe
spot though
[Music]
back in the cold I just like I don't
know what could happen to like make me
go like down here and then like fall off
like down from down this like shoot
right here I can't even imagine a
scenario where that happens so
I mean I don't think you'll fall too far
yeah
it should be fine that's why the chat
was really hard
yeah
The Final Countdown though yeah
[Music]
sorry I was
saying hello hey hello open up your
volume Bae is here with us today are you
okay
oh I'm good I'm just a little bit sick
you're sick I know I thought you sounded
kind of sleepy
you caught no no no
are you doing good yeah
thanks I was uh I was very worried but
um
it seems like it's kind of working out
you know I didn't think I'd make any
progress yet again today but here we are
isn't the chapel like this
awesome power off to this and that's
you're nearly there yeah
thank you thank you so much hey you
helped me get through a lot of it in the
beginning so
oh my word that's
big
yeah can I change your images because I
have that power
oh
I have that power what do you change it
to can you change it to the funny oh man
if you give me if you give me a funny I
will girl oh
if you already have a funny for like Bae
then I'll do it if you send it to me
oh for Bay would you like one for you
girl would you like me to change your
icon to a funny uh I would like yes all
right then go ahead and you just send
that my way and I got you
oh power
[Music]
um there she is oh I'm no longer funny
hi guys yeah hi
regular just a regular Old Bay
Mr regular Old Bay I'm stalling for time
because uh this game it terrifies me
sometimes but anyway
yeah
oh there it is
all right here we go
how many hours I know you love it as
much as I do
yeah it's nice this is looks like it's
saying it's a pretty cat oh God
oh God
I've already used it so much it's good
though do you have is this uh like you
want this for both open and closed
talking yeah
yeah yes please all right
any any time for you my dude
here we go
oh I love this choir music in the
background
while I'm looking at this image I don't
know what it is about this image
it does something
does it trigger your fight or flight
response it it does yes yes it does
really truly uh horrifying but in a good
way in a good way
let me find
all right
here we go this one's for you
yeah I do kind of want to run yeah I do
kind of want to get away right now there
we go from this
but it's very cute you're a real cat now
you know hello my jumbies you're a real
cat
the funnies yes there it is
hello my zombies and dead bees how are
you today
[Music]
it's too much
no it's just enough don't listen to me
don't listen to me it's perfect oh my
God
that is what you're saying
that's what you're saying
I like how the person who drew this I
think they just were like oh I'm
sketching around in pain
and it's like yes well I have chosen
this this is now my favorite picture
thank you
and now they don't get to decide
they don't get to decide whether this is
used for good or evil this is just how
it has to be
the best fan art is the stuff that fans
just make like oh I spent like you know
15 minutes on this just a quick scribble
to get this idea out of my head and like
it's fantastic yeah it's great I will
use this forever kind of thing yeah
yes
that's harder than I thought it would be
oh
yeah they really kind of fooled me with
the oh yeah you're finally at the chapel
what a nice like calm safe place
and now I'm like oh [\h__\h] this is
actually really hard
what are you guys yeah how are you girl
what are you like up to these days yep
yep uh these days just you know
streaming and sleeping feel that
you're back yes it's alive
[Music]
yeah I heard you're hanging out playing
some some games with Kiara today any
other plans
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah that's right I'm gonna
I'm gonna peek in on you guys doing that
yeah
yeah you can try and join
um I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do like
VR or anything and I'm not gonna stream
it but I am gonna come laugh at you guys
I mean that's like VR
yeah we're gonna try and get the VR
yeah you know and are you also gura
oh hell yeah yeah I want to put on my
heart rate monitor maybe I should ask
you guys on too that's such a good idea
good idea yes absolutely that's the way
to do it
yeah yeah I know that Watson uh was like
not really wanting to because it says
you know it's been spooky so I think
she's a big chicken ah
that is also possible
the big possibility over there
yeah
definitely
um that's fine I'm gonna be with her
though so I can't really say anything
I feel like the only way I'd get Watson
to play a really scary horror game is to
off collab and I strap her to the chair
I say play this game uh
she's not a big like horror game fan
no I don't think so understandable she's
a big chicken which is so cute but I'm
gonna eat I want to hear it yeah that
sounds bad no that's cool I don't know
that'd be good some people just have
like nice screams that you just enjoy
listening to it's hard to like like
describe why but they just do
yeah you know
you guys go with like legitimate scary
games
um Define legitimate scary Bay
I can't even do non-legitimate scary
games
I did peek in on the uh game you were
playing with mume
oh my side scroll walking game yeah yeah
yeah
I know it's quite the contrast of you
losing your mind and mume oh
okay
[Music]
completely understand non-plus that's so
funny okay
[Music]
I feel like I'm just I'm like too
separated from it I feel like if I
played it in VR it might be different
but like horror movies no way horror
games maybe sometimes I'll get a little
scared
uh uh phasma had me scream pretty hard
one time but other than that it's like
I get scared but I don't react very like
visibly
even when I was playing Resident Evil 8
I was worried that was I shouldn't be
worried because you know I was just I
was just being mean but I was like ah I
didn't really scream very loud
I say Resident Evil 8 isn't much of a a
scary game
what are your thoughts on that girl what
do you think because then you played it
yeah it's more action yeah I would say
yeah
you're playing Seven right now aren't
you I finished seven I would also say
it's more action yeah I agreed what'd
you think about it it doesn't
yeah I like I feel like horror games
that you can't defend yourself in and
you are just a prey object throughout
the entire thing is definitely going to
be scarier but you can fight back with
Resident Evil so yeah
yeah what about Amnesia if you played
amnesia the Dark Descent girl yeah yeah
I like amnesia
the first horror game I ever played was
amnesia
what a classic did you guys play Slender
Man yeah of course the bakken's a day
do you know Slenderman
you haven't played the game right
I don't know if you'd enjoy it
quite the Fright
the fry I know we can't play it but what
about SCP
you guys played that
yeah
I remember SCP oh um
let me think
the stairway that you just keep going
down and down and down and down and
there's like a face or something like
that that pops up yeah
I thought that one was crazy is that a
creepypasta or an NCP no that's an SCP
the the stairway is the SCP
it sounds like a creepypasta but that's
an STP
I like 999 what's that one
he's like a super cute squishy orange
blob oh
that's cool what kind is he
I don't know orange oh
no
I forget what the types of SCP are but
there are three I guess one's like
threatening to threatening one is like
non-threatening and one is like a hybrid
kind of like yeah like herbivore
carnivore omnivore kind of thing
oh there's pictures of it eating cookies
so I'm assuming uh
herbivore safe okay
yeah it's Euclid ketter and safe safe is
generally that sounds like a safe like a
safe boy me
[Music]
more difficult now that's fine that's
fine I'll take the UPS uh difficulty for
the fact that I'm not
that oh but you know what really sucks
is that um
when I get higher up than this I am
going to have to come back and deal with
this [\h__\h] again
oh my god oh
I'm kind of figured out
[Music]
it's the really long long like look like
I don't know I don't know the number
though
it's not gonna work there either
shorter one
[Music]
you're looking it up
what honey
I'm sorry I thought you were talking
about STP I was very focused for a
minute I completely I flew off to
another dimension excuse me
yeah you guys are playing games
I don't know the name of it I can't find
it but it's the really really long like
Loch Ness monster type-esque
SCP noodle
yeah
the whole history of that series is like
really interesting I think
three thousand scp-3000 apparently try
to sing I don't know the deep sea like
really interests me it's terrifying but
it's very interesting how's the Deep
seeing gura it's dark I have trenches
and stuff
it's dark it's dark
yeah yeah you're a big fan of the sea
girl that's a dumb question
it's all right you like the beach
I always wondered oh I like the beach
but I don't like the sand oh yeah
and that for sure
you know how like whenever you go to the
beach like you could just like it
doesn't matter what you do I don't know
if this is just a thing that happens to
me but for some reason sand always ends
up in the butt I don't know how that
crevice yeah how does that work like I
could literally be doing nothing but
sand would still get in the butt I don't
understand
yeah it's well they it's
just bound to happen
yes it's it's unavoidable
unavoidable it's the price you pay for
enjoying the beach I dare you
um anyway I just popped by really
quickly I don't think I can stay too
long because I'm losing my sanity yeah
you sound sick
yeah I'll be okay I just I'll I'm still
gonna watch you from bed yeah I will
wish you luck in
thanks appreciate it thanks for letting
me
yeah of course see you later babe go
sleep oh I had some soup on stream
actually
it's quite yummy
yummy take care now
[Music]
take care bye thank you later
later
oh [\h__\h] hell yeah I think I did it
hey can I read your super chats sure
yeah
absolutely
charcoal as uh head pet dad rat and oh I
missed him uh because Bae just left
sorry uh and we watched Top Gear
oh that's uh that's Tom Cruise the last
Top Gun sorry
I hope that
uh Maybe not maybe I have not seen that
up gear is that cars
what
it is cars what the [\h__\h]
I see
it's nice
babe she's
oh dear
uh
wait what's so funny is it not about
cars
hold on I have no oh let me get to the
bottom of this
otherwise still have gear
okay Top Gear move
what you think
well somebody asked asked all of us but
then you left but they asked all of us
if we had seen Top Gear have you seen
Top Gear yes Top Gear fan
sorry I just had to come back and say
that because I'm a big fan of Top Gear
what is it today
yeah it's cars it's like a car review
like TV show
um yeah more recently um so Topeka used
to be the original show I don't know
what channel it was on
um but then they moved to Amazon and
they changed their name to I think Grand
Tour or something like that
um
literally it's just think three old men
bickering about like just life and
bantering but there's really nice cars
oh I'm looking at it right now okay when
gura said it's cars I thought that she
meant it was like a cars sequel like a
sequel to the movie cars or something
like that and I was confused okay
understood okay got it wow cool
it's really funny it's really good cool
exactly oh no anyways meme comes from
anyway yeah yes definitely that's that
sounds very Clarkson I feel like that's
a great Clarkson thing
um yeah but anyway I just came by to say
that okay okay okay later babe holy [\h__\h]
girl holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] bye do you see
it you see
oh lee we're going to the top today boys
[Music]
oh man no freaking way
I hope it is okay
lots of rest she needs rest and soup and
she's got a chill
I'm like I don't know
okay let me just calm down because I
don't really know what to do here if I
bounce are you shaking
a little bit the heart rate monitor yeah
yeah forget Doom like this is the game
that I need
this is the game heart rate monitor for
hahaha yes okay let me just calm down
let me figure out where to go
foreign oh wow that was that sounded
good that sounded smooth
ie
yeah
um
I know jump King I know you want to go
just give me a minute my man oh wait I
gotta see the map jump King Matt
holy cow what are you gonna do if you
finish this game no girl f
oh wow well that's fine that's fine
oh cool no I'll take it
there's got to be an easier way than
what I've been doing I mean
you are like 80 there for a second oh my
God
I know I can do it though
absolutely you made it this far yeah
I would feel very silly if I gave up
oh not giving up
until I beat it probably
oh and then Chad saying I jinxed it
maybe
no it jinxes aren't real maybe they are
magic do you believe in magic depends on
the magic
if it's in a young girl's heart Maybe
um but otherwise I don't I'm so [\h__\h]
lame otherwise I mean it just depends it
just depends on how I'm feeling I guess
yeah I know I actually asked a friend of
a friend of mine that recently and I was
like do you believe in magic and they
said uh when things are going well for
me I do uh when they aren't then I don't
like all right that makes sense I guess
no that's fine let's find deal with that
girl you know Chris Angel La Mao
of course
do you know I wanted to be him
you know Chris do you know um street
magic
street magic yeah is that a show
um it's here just uh one second
also apparently King has reached 10
million views Castle Abby says yes
I'm so happy
wow that's really awesome I'm glad
wow thank you for letting us know guys
yeah
well always thank you
I appreciate it sorry I was I was
looking up um
I was looking up this video real quick
uh do you know David Blaine Street magic
yes okay oh here let me
you've probably seen this
thank you for the congrats you guys
sorry I was kind of in a different
Universe for a minute there yay I'm
really glad that it reached 10 film
though I had no idea that it would blow
off so much
but it was fun to it was fun to do a
song together gura
oh it was fun yeah
is he British
[Music]
um
I'm not sure actually
yeah these these videos I used to watch
them a lot
um
I don't really I don't think they're
real
but like no David Blaine no
you've seen this before
you know this okay good I was worried at
first oh the foot is here BRB one sec
okay guys now we're going to talk about
uh Calliope Mori and the great tail
wait she's still moving
okay we're good
um
today we're going to talk about
I actually don't know what we're gonna
talk about
have I eating breakfast I have this
candy
hey did I mention my tooth no I'm just
kidding my tooth doesn't hurt so that
means I can eat candy again
I'm gonna wait till Kayla comes back
though because I don't want to eat while
I'm alone candy is candies whatever you
want it to be it can be breakfast
it only matters is the calorie number at
the end of the day am I right am I right
anyway what's up guys what's up Chad
my favorite trick-or-treat candy or our
favorite trick-or-treat candy I would
say
um
[Music]
uh the Reese's Reese's are kitkats the
king of candies
and my favorite soup is
also I like I want to make corn I want
to try corn soup and then also uh I made
some roasted tomato soup the other day
like I roasted it from scratch it's
pretty good
it's pretty good
yummy I don't know what food
did she say what food she got I don't
remember
she get chicken nuggets
what's my monitor smell like
I don't know
what do you guys talk about usually the
beets
headmates listen up and then Obama
coming in the night for you
wine
[Music]
Wine's all right
talk about random stuff
talk about
more what
Mori scent if Cali had a perfume like a
uh like a body spray scent what scent do
you think it would be
uh final would be honeysuckles
nectar and honeysuckle scent
Cali would be Old Spice
yeah Callie would be like miscellaneous
soap
Fiji yeah yeah yeah Old Spice Fiji
exactly
Sandalwood Old Spice
although I do like roses wine and Cherry
like that's actually really good like a
like a dark
I don't want to say musk because musk in
the scenario I don't mean it as a bad
thing
a good musk like like the
you know what I mean
that was actually really good
like dark dark Sandalwood Rose and
Cherry a top scent well what is the top
scent usually the top scent is the sweet
stuff right and then with an under with
an underlying uh scent of of dark
Sandalwood
oh yummy
or like Old Spice
Old Spice like the way that people think
beaches smell
like that
like a tough smell yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
not just sandalsund
no flurry no God
I haven't mentioned it
sorry flurry I don't think I've
mentioned it
um but hey look Cali's back hi Hi
Something weird happened they gave me
two pastas and I'm like gura isn't
actually here with me I wish you were so
I could give you the extra pasta they
gave me
oh my God maybe it's because they knew I
don't know
I'll be over in 10 minutes
great waiting for you
what's a God in it let's see I mean I
got like a just like a typical tomato
pasta but
um the other the other one is like um
it's like a carbonara do you like
carbonara oh
uh I think so uh it's like cream sauce
right
it's like kind of like a cheesy sauce
with like bacon and [\h__\h]
oh oh yummy oh yes yeah it's [\h__\h]
good I make really good carbonara by the
way I'll make you some when you come
visit me someday
oh yes please oh yes please mm-hmm
oh yes please we were discussing uh if
you had a scent what would it be and uh
chats chats uh first initial thought was
Old Spice Fiji yes
uh but then somebody actually said uh
like uh dark dark Sandalwood or like a
Sandalwood
cherries and Roses which I thought was
actually pretty accurate
a nice scent like for a natural sound
wow like something a little sweet just a
little sweet a little girly florally and
then
a little something like uh good musky
like you know like uh tough yeah yeah
yeah
yeah the nice the nice kind
yeah yeah
that's right actually that reminds me of
um
a long time ago
I used to work at um
let's work at a restaurant
um
yeah long time ago and we started doing
this thing where um we would have a
little background music we started doing
this thing uh where customers would
leave like reviews about us and it
became a competition where um
where we were kind of like you know
trying to compete to get good reviews
and if if you got good reviews
um you know you got like a little bonus
a little bonus money
um which was cool so you know I was
doing my best
um and at that time you know we would
get some good reviews some bad reviews
I got a lot of good ones but I'll never
forget
I'll never forget one review that I got
someone wrote me a poem
uh um yeah they wrote a poem about me
and about you know my my pink my long
pink hair like swaying in the wind and
whatever and then and then it was this
nice little poem and then out of nowhere
um
out of nowhere they said
Cali's booty stank
got me got me tripping is literally what
they said
and I was like what and I asked my
sister I asked my sister about it and
she said yeah that's like that's slang
for like when you have a really like
thick uh like back door area and I
looked in the mirror and I was like I
don't really think it's
I don't what dump truck in
so you're actually the post the car's
poster that I said yes the Cars poster
that you sent me that's me apparently
um
yeah I don't know when you said the word
musk it reminded me of the bartender who
was like laughing and reading it to me
and he was just like what this is what
is this like a nice musk I'm like never
say that word ever again
dear
God yeah that's a memory that I have
um
all right
yeah and I learned a new slang I wish
Kiara was here she was asking for new
slang I could tell her that one
yeah
would you like me to relay the message
yeah if you could send Kiara a quick
message and like let her know
about that all right what would you like
to say give me a word for word okay uh
tell Kiara I remembered some slang
I remembered some slang okay booty stank
equals
large behind
large behind yes feel free to use it if
you'd like
feel free to use it if you like okay
that's all yeah yeah give her that end
of quotation yeah
yeah I never forgot about that customer
I hope that uh they're out there living
their best life
yeah um appreciate the compliment I I
think
I looked in the mirror I was like it's
pretty normal looking I don't know I
guess
all right thanks Calliope Mori is Bunky
bone and ladies and gentlemen I keep
trying to remember like who was it the
whole day I thought to myself which
customer was that
which who
I mean
I mean what's your what are your
measurements me my
my three sizes
oh man those are they're a secret
but the top top and bottom are pretty
much about the same I would say big
titty little ways
[Laughter]
huge huge upper measurement itty bitty
like a Dorito man
yeah that's me
it's me
I love the pear shape but what about the
Dorito shape that never gets any love
come on now come on have a little taste
you guys
no no no no you're you're hourglass
and don't joke yeah
I think it do yeah be like that what
about you girl I told you mine now you
tell me yours
plywood
oh like like plank from Edd n Eddie no
it's me yeah yeah
perfect I mean there are a lot of people
who like that though you know yeah
I don't know if I told you but I don't
yeah we can trade I don't know um I told
you I don't know if I told you this but
um in the beginning
when I was uh still a Reaper but uh
Mother Mother Dearest was uh creating a
body for me I had a wish
I want it to be a flat-chested tomboy
yeah but then I saw this body and I was
like I can't hate this this is beautiful
what's it like having cleavage
um tough on your back
okay that's that's what I hear yeah but
last time I said that uh in front of
like Ollie and Lucia they didn't like it
very much they got very angry at me
um so I I stopped telling them what it
was like
oh no no no no you can you can indulge
with me
I don't know what it's like and I would
like to know I've actually one of my one
of my like literally one of my
one of my like little oh
I don't know let me know anytime I'm
happy I
I always wondered what it was like
to have boobs that touched you know
clear
I don't know what it is what it's like
um hard to manage
especially during the summer
isn't it is it nice to look at though
okay it's so maybe
yeah I would say so
yeah really nice I'm envious I am
incredibly envious oh well I would
happily give you half of them
I wish I could rip them off and give
them to you
but I will take them
if only if only
yeah
man it must be hard with like shirts
though because
yeah nothing ever really fits quite
right I feel like yeah yeah and like
every time I don't know every time I see
like
my sister's wearing like a cute dress
I'm like I want to wear that and then I
try and I'm like this was never going to
work
oh yeah it's rough even going back to
the home world it's like I can't
there's just never anything in the
stores it works
you know
you gotta like get that [\h__\h] custom made
it's rough
but like button shirts so you can button
around the waist and just leave the top
open yeah yeah yeah yeah
I would assume it's also tough though
because I I get embarrassed usually like
I don't want to I don't like walking
around like having it visible so like I
wear like big hoodies and stuff like
that because you know because it's like
that because it's like kind of you know
kind of large up there like that
situation uh then it's like the hoodie
like goes to like it goes out and then
it goes straight down so it just makes
me look chunky you know ah I see yeah
I see well I um
mine just go I mean my um
all right I'm eating right now as we
talk that's why I'm not moving but I
wanted like some choir music in the
background as we talked about uh our our
chest yeah nice yeah yeah I mean I'm the
same with baggy clothes but uh without
the the tent effect I guess
I wonder if I could stand inside your
hoodie and stay like safe from the rain
ooh yeah you could probably slot right
in
yeah when you come visit we can give it
a try if it starts raining and we don't
have an umbrella I got you
Calliope more is my umbrella yeah let me
know anytime
I can help you out yeah I mean I might
as well be useful somehow with this with
the situation I'm in I might as well be
useful
yes well you're useful no matter what
don't worry about it
you're useful too a good company while
I'm playing this this game that scars me
oh always a good time hanging out with
Calliope Mori yeah thanks if you got
stuff to do never feel bad about being
like all right Cali I'm ditching you bye
peace look okay well every going a
little bit if I can hang out for a
little bit more yay alrighty
really when is your outlasting
uh in a couple hours
I see I see yeah I'm eating pasta I
don't remember the exact time oh pasta
pasta
do you cook a lot by yourself these days
or do you um mostly do like delivery
stuff
uh I actually don't really do I used to
do a lot of delivery but not so much
anymore now I'm just
uh
like
um
no I knew it
I knew it I just don't really eat
anymore I'm just like oh hey that's not
a good thing that's not a good thing no
it's it's not a good thing but you know
you know it's you go through phases of
okay I wanna cook and then your eye just
can't be asked I can't be bothered oh
totally I'm not even gonna pretend like
I haven't been through that yeah
I'm in that phase right now
what's your um what's your stance on
like fast food
oh I love it
give me McDonald's hell yeah
hell yeah I mean I like it every once in
a while but so many of my friends are
like very staunch like no fast food
people
so like oh I'll be like yeah I got my
monthly McDonald's and they'll be like I
can eat that and I'm like like once a
month some nuggies are nice oh oh I like
to have a word with them I'm all once I
just do once a week it's a week isn't
bad at all actually but one time I did
it twice in one day which was a little
not great even Watson was like dude no
no
that's a little I mean you're fine now
thankfully but you know if if you
suffered some kind of damage from that I
wouldn't be surprised
listen I'm a big believer in the good
old calories in calories out as long as
you keep an eye on that then it's all
good yeah although nutrients I'm sure
yeah I'm probably deficient in about
every vitamin you could be but my soul
is fed with nuggies the nuggies you can
always uh order vitamins and stuff like
that to like force yourself to take that
[\h__\h] in the morning and then just eat
whatever you want I guess but wash it
down with a McFlurry yeah that's fine
all the essential vitamins and nutrients
wash it down with the McFlurry
sounds good that's fine yeah people that
are like oh my God McDonald's because I
used to be one of those people that was
like oh my God you ate McDonald's ugh
yucky I was lying to myself I was living
a lie
I mean love it I mean at least at least
you've come to terms with um
with McDonald's absolutely that's
wonderful that's like a really um that's
a really happy success story a book you
know I'm gonna put this away real quick
I'm living a life of clarity now
Clarity and hot mustard yeah hot mustard
huh
what's your nugget dip oh
barbecue sauce
I'm boring okay interesting I'm boring
what about you you like honey mustard
honey mustard hot mustard Ranch anything
with sweet and sour Ranch is good Ranch
is really good
have you had Ranch Water
Ranch Water
I can't say I have what's that like
uh Advantage tequila and lime juice oh
[Music]
I mean I'm interested I'm like intrigued
Ranch Water
[Music]
oh my God
oh spicy ranch water that sounds so
awful it sounds delicious
yeah it's a it's a mixed drink though ah
I don't want to just try it like for fun
I'm curious now
what's the most wild thing you've ever
eaten girl
um
oh that's a good question absolutely
crazy wild because in Japan
there's this thing called shirako
yeah so like uh like white and then like
cool is like uh like a child like baby
oh excuse me
um oh no no it's uh it's a it's a fish
thing it's a it's inside of a fish
it's the part of a fish where
um
it's it's the white
the white thing inside the the male fish
and and you eat it it's a delicacy in
Japan what's that
it's [\h__\h] can you be more specifically
no no it's uh it's the white so white
stuff inside the male fish that they use
when it's time to when the babies for
making the babies
what
you'll be more specific please
it's it's fish use it in a sentence
wow this shirako is great they took it
right out of that male fishes
uh area below the stomach and we ate it
it's silly bun juice no it's not it
um she already knows more I know she
knows but I'm not gonna give it to you
I'm not gonna give it to her it's it's
fish
there we go
oh you got my some of my Reverb effects
on there yeah well I censored up
I censored the word
what's that taste like
um it was all right
I mean is it like coagulated
um a little bit when I ate it it kind of
looked like brain a little bit like
someone's brain but it's not yeah you
eat it and it's supposed to be like
creamy and whatever and like it tasted
fine it didn't taste fishy it just it
had like no taste but it was like the
texture of it just made me want to stop
and so I stopped yeah damn it
yeah so I so I didn't yes I didn't need
it I Takes the Cake yeah it's kind of
hard to beat that I think
um
I know that's incredibly hard to be
you should try some when you come over
[Music]
I double dog dare you I triple dog
I don't know about that one all right
beautiful dog
which means you've got a dream okay
sounds good I'm down King Delicacies on
stream yes crazy crazy nutso ridiculous
Delicacies that you wouldn't think you
can eat but then you eat them
and it's like ah exactly why did we eat
that okay wow that was wild oh man I
actually I thought of something that
I've eaten before yeah that was pretty
it wasn't as crazy as that
um it's kind of wild but now I can't
remember it oh
alligator
no uh I'll eat it tastes like chicken
I've never tried alligator
I recommend it you can have it in
Oklahoma
where are the uh the where are the
something and the something something
yeah
there's a whole lot of potatoes that no
that's not that's Idaho excuse me I
don't really it's been a while a lot of
taters it's been a while
I kind of forget [\h__\h]
man I I had an answer to this
oh let me see I can draw another weird
stuff have you eaten
um let's see in Japan there's a lot of
them there's a lot of weird things
um
sea urchin
similar to the shirako thing that I told
you about most of the Meat part of the
the sea urchin is in the reproductive
area
and you eat that why
um why because I guess they think it
tastes good and that's fine they
certainly may think that I disagree but
uh you know everyone's got everyone
Everyone's a Critic
well isn't there there's like sea urchin
sushi right the yellow stuff yes that's
right
is that what you're talking about um
maybe it's orange it's orange actually
so maybe it might be yellow
I'm like that sounds yummy yeah it's
pretty good
I used to eat like on the um uh what's
the uh oh what's the the fish
roll pasta oh tarako
oh yeah yeah that's what it is oh you
like that
yes do you like the isn't it kind of
spicy
yes yeah I used to I used to buy the bag
version
oh my word that's a first I don't know a
lot of people that like the fish egg
stuff
pasta is it's so good
all right now when you when you come
over I'm gonna eat tarako pasta which I
have avoided like the plague and you're
gonna eat shidako and that's what we're
gonna do together
oh I love not though that's easy for me
but I would love to I would love to see
your reaction to trying not so for the
first time
oh oh this is called mentaiko yeah is
what it is
slimy I think that's the thing I
couldn't
I won't be able to get past is the
texture oh that's right so you know
about like the the sort of like
reputation of not though right
um bubbly yeah slimy also nice at the
top nice thanks what good God damn it
that's fine
just a little bit uh we can do it
you can do it I can do it
you like okra I love okra
it's a little slimy it kind of reminds
me of that a little bit
it's a slimy texture yeah it's fine you
don't like okra
no The Taste is fine it's the texture
it's like booger yeah you might have a
rough time with natta then I don't know
if you'll like it very much
mm-hmm no yeah I don't know this is kind
of hard I'll beat it though I'll beat it
what's up what's your spice tolerance
like girl
because we can also eat ghost peppers
I want to go to
cocoa Curry yeah
one of my dreams oh it's so good Koko
Ichiban yeah
that's some good stuff
they get really spicy too in Japan if
you like spicy stuff
they have like high spice levels
uh
you got a good spice tolerance
I'm sending you a
spice tolerance level I would say I'm a
let me see this a three or a four oh let
me see this
because I like spice but I don't want it
to interrupt the flavor of whatever I'm
eating I see
I like I like level seven
[\h__\h] ah oh my God I'm okay so so I like
three three is probably good
hey because you still want to taste all
the other stuff I don't want the spice
to just overpower everything if the
spice overpowers like the whole flavor
then yeah I think there's like no point
pretty much so I agree
yeah and then you can't taste anything
for like 10 minutes after yeah it's sad
I totally agree
yeah I'm glad you feel the same way too
Vera
yeah
I keep forgetting what I did the first
time let me try and remember
um
all right getting up is like not too bad
but it's just that one part
staying up there that's the tricky part
yeah and apparently I'm gonna fall a lot
from here because
I know it's gonna get slippery I just
know that it is because uh chat told me
when I went to the bonus area they're
like ah you use mechanics here that you
learn later in the game so it's harder
and I'm like ah looks like we're
stepping on Ice then great
but we will see what happens
oh man yeesh
it's quite a game
thanks for being here with me if I will
I suffer
hey you got it yeah
you were like Kelly can you not focus
I'm like no I can it's what I'm watching
something I can't focus that's the issue
what just talk are you a good
multitasker uh it kind of depends I feel
like when it comes to watching stuff no
so for example I can listen to like
podcasts and stuff really well while I'm
drawing and like working on stuff like
that but if I'm watching a TV show it's
like no way yeah hmm unfortunately
I can't what about you
you multitask master
if I'm like doing stuff like if I have
to
like if I'm cleaning and cooking yeah
I'm vacuuming and like
scooping cat poop and then doing the
dishes laundry and then also have
something on the stove and I'm usually
all right oh I see
I'm also not good I don't know it
depends
[Music]
I guess streaming is considered
multitasking because you're playing a
game but you're also talking to chat and
keeping up with Chad making sure nothing
technically weird is going on and
playing a game I already said that
memory oh yeah that's true I guess it is
situational yeah
so but I don't think I can really
actually focus on two things
it has to be one main thing and a
secondary thing
that hasn't been so bad
hey have you played stardew Valley I
love stardew Valley
did you see uh the haunted chocolates
here wait what
you haven't seen in no that sounds cool
I think it's in a it's a new game by the
same
elephant I'm curious now
I actually saw the trailer and it looks
pretty good you like run a a chocolate
store and you have to go and collect
ingredients to make your chocolates
that's really good what yeah
kind of thing
I perhaps I'm not really sure I'm really
excited 1500 Falls nice 50. oh yeah wow
that's that's a lot but you know what
even more jumps right
even more yeah yeah
look at that babe
yeah
all right well I guess I'll go I'll try
again
I want to check out this game later is
it out
uh I can send you the trailer yeah let's
see thanks
okay it's funny because I'm not really
too into
stardew but this actually looks really
oh neat
into wasting cool
yeah please don't get mad at me for
saying that it's a fine game I just
couldn't get into a person it's okay
everyone's got their own personal pace
holy cow did you make it I did
I'm very afraid
I won't say anything don't worry um
did you fall no I'm fine
no it's bad bad okay we're fine we're
fine
we're fine oh the music is so serene
no no no no no no no no okay
thank you
how do I let's see what's up there
oh I see if I go all the way there we go
Chinese so heard about the drink since
I'm so proud of you look at you thanks
it's okay Kara it's not your fault it's
all it's always me
jinxing isn't real we've already
established jinxing isn't real it's all
right it's not super hard to get back up
there so
no worries you've been trying to get
back up there for the past time listen
it's not it's not that bad well I've
been trying to get this far for the past
six hours so you know what it's all good
all good
I think it's not really
shop chat
no you guys are fine you guys are fine I
love you don't worry you just
having a little have a little summer
temper tantrum we'll get over it we'll
get that babe don't you guys worry
I'm getting over it haha get it that's
another game where you want to die and
not play anymore
oh did you play that one I did I did not
finish it though
it wasn't for me and
isn't it like the same as this one yeah
it's somewhere but there's a guy that
like says [\h__\h] at you the whole time
Bennett foddy not saying he's like a bad
dude or anything but like
you know like like shut the [\h__\h] up you
know like
there's not what I'm doing though right
now no but
I mean it's different you're you're very
I don't know I consider you to be pretty
like down to earth person benefit is the
god of that world and he's like yelling
at you so
Maybe
well I wouldn't stop you if you did but
but
[Music]
fine I can I can do it
I can do it just this jump over this
screen is not as hard as I thought it
was it really is just like a full power
jump both ways
here we go okay
be careful be careful okay
all right all right
okay okay oh wait I just thought back to
that food you mentioned yeah
um
yeah oh me and the chumbies we watched
uh oh God one of those oh God what was
it blue
uh blue ocean yeah one of those
documentaries right where they teach you
about
yeah
uh yeah
nature yeah Mission stuff oh yeah like
blue planet and stuff yeah yeah yeah I
always pool Planet I think it was the
original when it was talking about yeah
a blue planet okay gotcha
cool I was talking about the the life
cycle of the certain type of fish yeah
I asked the Herring bless you by the way
thank you and there's this one type of
fish the Herring that when it's
um is mating season only swim upstream
or Downstream I don't remember and they
they they you know they make their next
life cycle uh-huh
um
um you can see you can see the the
shirako from like your own footage
Oh you mean like it's up in the sky yeah
I'm curious like up in the sky it's just
like yeah they're cool
yeah I want to see that that sounds cool
yeah science is crazy isn't it yeah
science is for all kinds of mysteries
yeah planet Earth is crazy wow
oh that's all
of wow that's a really what a season
everyone's kind of in the mood huh
all right nice you like hearing though
anybody in Harry yeah I think I've had
it before
it was fun
you big fish fan I mean that's a dumb
question of course you are I love it of
course yes oh yes yeah number one fish
fan right here
Go Fish
eat your fish
oh wait is this what they make the this
is charming out of have you ever had
that before
what what is it this it's the
sistrumming food
strumming
it's
um fermented I think it's fermented
Baltic caring oh smells like death wow
cool there's like all those videos of
people eating it like there's this one
guy who opens it and eats it in his car
and because it's fermented and sealed uh
I think you're supposed to open it under
water so it doesn't squirt everywhere
but he opened it dry in his car and it
squirted all over his car interior oh
moldy fish
it's I think I uh smell like moldy fish
no all right I'm just saying
now we're gonna build some Rose and dark
wood
um and slightly sweet nice scent and now
we go to fermented old moldy fish gotcha
[Music]
um
yeah it does sound really disgusting
yeah let's do it
I'm down
I'm down only if you eat a ghost pepper
with me though
okay I'll bring the milk all right cool
yeah I uh I had like a little bite
um at a friend's house and it was
probably uh the most horrifying 10
minutes of my life
so I think it'll be fun
I should bring those they have ghost
pepper chips yeah yeah I heard about
that
yeah or just straight up ghost pepper
yeah maybe we go with the chips and make
it like a movie night or something like
that
yeah there's only one though it's one
per per package oh I see okay so yeah
you know it's gonna it's like hardcore
gotcha okay cool well I'm done if you're
down
I'm done but I'm going to cry
because I can't jump there huh all right
gotcha all right game I understand
that'll be fine we can cry together
it's always more fun crying with your
friends
yeah and then we can stuff for the
stomach aches later on that'll be cool
[Music]
yeah
yeah nice idea
oh thank you for telling me about those
I didn't know that existed we gotta hire
them we gotta prepare them yes when
everyone gets here and we can all do it
together
uh maybe maybe only you and I
I don't I don't want to hurt them
Eno's go with spice I think Ena would be
oh I had no idea cool
yeah right she's I might be wrong I'm
sure chat knows I think Kiara might be
in trouble though
yes yeah
all the way
watching watching
are you sure
[Music]
ah it's not a good noise oh it's not a
good noise
it's like you know what's gonna happen
before you even see it
oh modded this game
I bet they have I know someone's making
a version
um the same person who made small AME is
making a version of the game with me in
it
oh nice I was gonna ask that I'm excited
let's say I want to play as Cali yeah
I want to see you play as me
want to see how we'll play this game if
I can play as Kelly yeah
yeah maybe maybe they maybe maybe all of
us can be it that would be cool oh I
want to play as everyone climbing the
mountain
welcome to the Mountaintop
[Music]
welcome to the mountain
that was the song that I wrote
oh man is it the hook is the hook the
part that gets stuck in your head all
the time oh uh yeah I think so yeah
that's the one
that's the one because you're good at
writing those oh ear worms all right
thank you
appreciate it you too
heck yeah no yeah
I'm not you are though no you are too
we got bangers here's some more bangers
I want to hear you do fish or stuff yeah
wait is your is your Boogie box gone out
again yeah one of them one of two the
one that's on their channel is yeah and
then I haven't listened to it yet oh
it's it's an interesting one it's it's
kind of got like a
it's got a lot of horns in it
I like songs with horns yeah it's got
horns
I'm gonna go listen to it yeah
I hope you like it
foreign
just a lot of music coming out recently
very busy yeah
oh warrants yeah they're the horns
they're very prominent
foreign
also Japanese rap
it's really good
no wait no no
Blue Ruin no please I want to go
eek to the jumps he came out to the Jazz
yeah I get it get a geek to the jobs
okay so Steve so Steve Jobs you know who
Steve Jobs is right
right he's like really smart he was a
geek right
so you go from being a geek to like you
become Steve Jobs it's like leveling up
right so from Nemo like the small little
fish to the Jaws you become like a shark
so he's like talking about himself and
like how he went from like nothing uh to
being like the the big [\h__\h] yeah
oh it looks like that
it's like that
cause I'm nerd [\h__\h]
I'm a nerd [\h__\h]
oh yeah
thank you Steve I like this yeah
this is like car
road tripping music yeah road tripping
music exactly I was thinking the same
thing
there she is yeah that's me
I'm not gonna cry I'm not gonna cry no
no I'm not gonna cry I don't want you to
cry
foreign
Hey listen
ah okay I'm gonna turn all red
yeah do it yeah
all right
I'm looking forward to the day that we
can we make a song together
let's do it do it
let's do it
no this is really good good job guys
thank you we worked really hard I've
still got another one coming out it's
gonna be on my channel it's coming out
on Halloween
oh that's
uh two days from now yeah it's pretty
soon actually
I'm thinking about it
yeah October went by so fast I can't
even believe oh my God it did yeah too
fast right
I scheduled so many freaking streams I'm
really trying to only do like five a
week but
recently because it's October and
there's so much [\h__\h] going on
eight to nine
a lot oh I want to chill for a little
bit
I'm going on a vacation
November okay yeah sometime in November
I've got like
a vacay here and their plans
get away from it all for a little bit I
think it's important to do that every
once in a while you know oh yes oh yes
yes I keep forgetting to go outside yeah
yeah you're a fan of traveling girl
I yes
hell yeah yes oh yeah I wanna yeah kind
of hard to do right now though right
yeah yeah unfortunate
have you ever been to Glorious nepon
before
no
I know I'm gonna need you to show me all
the good stuff I want to I can't wait
I can't bring you over some some hot
Cheetos or something yeah it is really
hard to find those those kinds of things
here you can bring Cheez-Its yeah you
know Cheez-Its
of course I'm going cheeses yeah bring
me a Cheez-Its or something I don't know
some kind of
whatever is like a good chip thing that
you can just find and bring for me I
will eat any of it
because there's it's hard to it's hard
to get every kind of chip here you know
it's hard to do I have chips star though
chip star is good right that's like the
what is it it's like um
Pringle kind of thing it's like Pringles
but they're not Pringles they're like
they're like the salt is like a lot less
salty it's got like a it's made with
like a different oil I think
yeah I don't know something like that
yeah yeah yeah yeah
um
God this part of the [\h__\h] eyes no
that was so lame that was such a lame
way to fall too
all the way down Lance
I'll get it
I have no doubt in my mind I'm gonna get
this
I believe in you
thank you
sport
I will I'll do it I'll do it this Chapel
is just it's way more terrifying than I
thought it was going to be foreign
because I keep thinking I can like step
on the candles or the fire but no that's
pretty dumb because then you burn and
hurt yourself oh you know what
makes sense I guess
this area is much easier than I thought
it would be
okay and now
we're in space no okay
okay
all right all the way over now this part
here is rough because I'm like all right
I need to maybe jump
again no what stop stop
why I should do a full jump from the
corner okay I'm gonna try and do that
okay about so much memory stuff but I
have no memory ability
at this point it must be muscle memory
hour eight yes you are correct actually
it is a lot of muscle memory
interestingly enough
which is better than my regular memory
so I guess I should be thankful
my memory's bad too absolute trash yeah
yeah I always had a hard time
remembering things especially when it
came to like school stuff
oh yeah how are you are you a good test
taker ah I'm like fine I think I'm like
a straight up okay when it comes to
English no problem leave it to me but
anything else like science and math it's
like no way
no way
yeah
see I I had a feeling that you had a
tough time with math as well
what makes you think that huh
no no particular reason
just kind of got I just kind of got math
this is my specialty Vibes hey I'm the
same way maybe even worse listen
good old math wasn't my favorite subject
it's more of like a literature person
we should do a
uh
like a yeah you know this time table
worksheet says to give you yeah I
thought you were gonna say like a math
decathlon demathalon or something
together I think is this the best of
math which is just a competition to see
who's the best in math
oh plus alcohol yeah yes only if there's
like drinking involved let's do it
yeah I'm down and we should have Ollie
be our um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah she can like Wrangle Us
in yeah because she she knows the math
have you tried watching her her math
streams yeah I've been there every once
in a while when she's like counting pie
and stuff like that
I I sat through an entire one I was like
I'm going to sit here until I understand
this I had no idea not even the first
slightest clue I think she was answering
uh questions that fans had sent in oh
I see
yeah
oh
quick save quick save the game all right
I'm Gonna Save it real quick
[Music]
I didn't know it was that simple the
whole time
yeah
and just like save yeah
oh man all right
um
well but nice knowing you guys
no wait stop
stop I see why this part is so difficult
for people okay
gotcha no problem no problem look no
more sewers okay just keep me out of the
sewers and we're fine I beg of you
or I can't what the [\h__\h]
oh no
okay for the sewers
[Music]
as long as we're just chilling here it's
fine
no wait stop
[Music]
no oh no it's fine it's fine it's fun
and we're chill we're hanging out in the
chapel now and the chapel it's all good
sewers can't hurt you anymore
the jump King sewers are not real
they're not real I can't hurt you
he can't hurt you yeah
yeah no problem I feel like if I if I
did end up going back to them I'd just
lose my mind
like I just I just lose it
sounds like good content
yeah
they are very real but far away all
right that helps I guess
helps me with my sewer trauma
[Music]
ah there's yours
no
all right we're fine
I really really want to beat the game
tonight
I really really want to do
it maybe
like
[Music]
two and a half hours yeah it's a nice
estimate
we'll see we'll see
oh wait
no uh okay we're fine we're fine we're
fine
okay we're fine
where am I supposed to jump from here is
it a full yeah I can do a full jump okay
you can do a full jump nice
that's good to know that's good okay
okay no problem no problem
full jump
we'll jump
make sure I oh okay okay well maybe not
be careful just be careful
[\h__\h] ice man I tell you what
nope I can't
I have to do I have to do I did a full
jump the first time so maybe maybe it'll
work I don't know we'll see we will see
Pro Gamer yeah
she gaming boys you know it oh man
oh man well Facebook face down first
thing please I I know I can do it
I know I can
I believe thanks for belief
I still got DLCs
[Music]
seven hours
I thought that it would be more like six
just because like I did the back for
blood uh stream earlier like I didn't
stream but I played with them it's like
me I've been doing a whole lot of
sitting down today right
um but my new chair is really great so
um my back actually doesn't hurt anymore
so it's pretty cool
yeah what chair did you get it's um what
is it a Hermit uh Hermann what is it
chat you guys remember
Herman Miller Herman Miller Herman
Miller which one yeah Aaron Aaron uh
Herman Miller oh nice yeah it's it's a
nice one I can lean way back like this
I'm leaning very far back
yeah Herman Miller it's great
but it really keeps you from like
sitting comfy oh no yeah yeah
like I said but when I sit like it's
hard to explain sitting comfortably is
like it doesn't hurt my back very much
but like using a gamer chair like yeah
that'll hurt my back quote unquote gamer
chair
because it doesn't have any lumbar
support yeah exactly I read that like
they're supposed to be like race car
chairs
someone told me that
somebody told me they're supposed to be
like like race car like uh you know the
chairs or the chairs that are seats that
are in race cars yeah
um right to like simulate like our race
our Racing Experience so you see like
Pro racer and stuff like that on some of
the
pillows and whatnot
um it's supposed to simulate that
experience
um but like the back is really flat and
there's like no shoulder support
buckets yes yeah bucket seats exactly
that's what they're called
yeah
you ever have a gamer chair
uh yeah I got a gamer chair
um yeah and then I swapped to the I have
the same chair as you the error you're
on oh nice that's a good one it was
really nice I like it what color is
yours oh just gray I just had whatever
they had in store
oh yeah I was like I just need a new a
new a new chair now
what about you I hear you
beige beige gray fish okay okay that's
nice nice calm the same thing thank you
it was like whichever one is not back
ordered or back ordered the least
whichever one yeah yeah
I mean sometimes sometimes that's just
how it'd be you need to get that good
back support like ASAP you know
yeah it's important especially because
we sit so much yeah we do we do do this
as a job there's a lot of this that we
do
it's like good Orthopedics for your your
back when you stand all day at work we
need it for our butts yeah exactly
precisely very very important
depends on like what your job is I guess
certain things are
deal breakers you gotta you gotta get
like a really good share if you're gonna
be doing lots of desk work
I believe in that
oh yes
okay okay okay okay nice nice nice nice
nice
okay
okay no no no
all right
here okay
no
do a little bunny hop okay
now
full power
just don't there we go
oh I'm not gonna say anything I'm not
even gonna look
I'm gonna time out
[Applause]
what am I gonna do no I'm I'm fine it's
just
I like don't I don't know what to
oh
okay be friends okay deep breaths gamer
mode gamer mode okay all right we're
fine finally this is the hardest part ah
maybe we shouldn't have said that
um
yeah oh well um that's it's okay it
could be worse could be worse could be
worse
no it's not your fault it could be worse
could be worse
it could be worse
yeah
let's run back okay you gotta run it
back
let me Bounce Off the Wall all right go
all right
oh oh okay all right well that yeah
uh-huh oh well there we go
yeah
I I think I put beans on French fries
no but that sounds good
yeah never never tried that
I'm sorry I haven't had breakfast yet so
I think I'm thinking about yeah what you
want for breakfast like beans and fries
uh maybe wow yeah I just might yeah just
just be wild like take a chance you know
yeah sounds good actually
the Wild Card day yeah
you got a spike you gotta spice things
up you know the the those rooms and
normalness of day to day spice it up
with some fries with beans for breakfast
here you go yeah
it all right we're back
okay
oh she's jumping now
okay uh Try Again full power
run it back run it back okay
we're going to bed okay
okay
yeah it's not quite wow is it just just
chill it's chill there my man okay
that's fine I think I know what I have
to do
just full power
just
yeah I mean yeah
it's real cold here
cold and unforgiving
okay though make it work
okay
oh [\h__\h] that's fine it's fine it's fine
this is four or five we're fine
oh
I'm not giving up
no you're good at endurance streams
you've done a lot of endurance streams
actually I've done a couple recently
thank you
easily done the most
in the end might be Kiara
he does like a lot of like RPG games
like uh eight hours at a time which is
pretty crazy
that's true yeah but in terms of like
hard game yeah maybe not saying that the
games of QR plays aren't hard just that
it's like a little different I think but
not like this you know not like jump
like junking
I didn't know this game actually came
out like a long time ago I didn't
realize that then I was like when was it
it was like 2016. I say a long time ago
it's not that long but
to me it kind of seems like a while
especially for me to like just learn
about it recently I learned about it
from you actually
oh yeah I saw you playing it and then I
was like well because you you called me
and I was like huh
oh
that's right that's gonna hit you with
the Lightning McQueen instead oh yeah
yeah
or maybe it was 2019.
yeah 2019 I don't know why I thought why
I thought it was 16 but
yeah so I'm kidding I'm gonna say 2016
was half a decade ago
birds birds
yo I am glad though that uh that you
know answered the the call because I
couldn't have come up with that Mickey
Mouse response
um at that time in the morning
I don't think I would have had I wonder
how you would have responded it's a
great question I really I'm just not
sure to be oh [\h__\h] that was way too much
okay that's fine
all right my man
um yeah you know
why does he fall like that
um
yeah I don't really know what I would
have said because I was dead tired
like I woke up and I was like ah a call
from gura
we'll call you again wanna I'll time it
so it's morning for you and I'll give
you a range to see what's up all right
I'll make sure I have my my notice on so
I get that call from you I'm not missing
it next time
I'm not
[Music]
this might get kind of grindy I just get
the feeling
this whole game is grindy though yeah
this part's really surprised me though
foreign
thanks
eventually
that slippery ice though if I can just
get past the slippery ice
and I keep making really over
exaggerated stupid faces because I think
I've got my
my camera on but it's just voice oh
you ever do that oh camera no
no like when like when you you know like
you know yeah
oh you were like
do you find yourself making more
exaggerated Expressions oh that's what
you mean that's
um
like out in uh out in like Society
nah not really but but when I'm like
this yes
I feel like I have to to get my point
across sometimes you see
I wonder like when you make thumbnails
and you pose for things like I look
insane right now I've done that like um
at the hair salon before
like taking a picture to post on Twitter
um
and I'll make the most exaggerated face
and they just look at me like are you
good
I'm like uh don't worry
sorry I'm fine because it's like it's
not even a selfie face it's it's a
selfie face for me like this like in in
this way yeah so it's like it doesn't
look like something that would be
flattering okay
exactly no yeah it makes you look
I'll just never understand
I'll just never get it
I look so wacky oh my God I'm just so
I'm so lucky he's so wacky so quirky
thing that like the other girl she's an
understanding I'm just so crazy yeah you
have no ideas sorry I would tell you but
like you probably wouldn't know so yeah
you probably like never heard of this
like thing that I do oh my God you've
never heard of this band I listen to it
sorry it's just so
yeah I'm sorry I just like yeah there's
no way that you know them
there's just no way
yeah there was a time where I was like
that
oh no yeah oh yeah there was F
you were a quirky she's just a quirky
girl yeah real quirky she kind of quirky
though
yeah she's so different I don't know
yeah once upon a time
things may or may not have been like
that
no don't don't freak out don't freak out
okay now we go full
all the way no all right well that's not
the correct answer but you know what we
tried so I'm glad that we tried we just
have to be good at the game all right
that's fine easy enough solution it's
easy enough solution
it's fine I got close
okay
all right
actually I gotta bounce pretty soon okay
no worries thanks a lot of fun yeah yeah
it was nice of you to come cheer me
of course anytime some interesting
conversations all right oh yeah pretty
interesting topics it's always kind of
it turns out when we when we have a
conversation though
yes
yeah yes I wonder what we would talk
about if we uh weren't downstairs yeah
um that's a really good point
I guess we'll find out someday because
things are slowly getting better day by
day
So eventually
yeah the floodgates will be yeah they
won't be ready for us they won't be
ready oh yes
I'm excited yes well I hope you make it
to the top thanks gura I'll do my best
I'll I'll let you know I'll send you a
little screenshot if I do
yes yes who made it to the top baby
get that babe I'll get that babe girl
you take care of yourself you get that
Kiara good and scared I guess oh yeah
really do a little trolling for me and
uh I'm gonna go watch uh that when it
happens
all right I'll see you then later
goodbye
bye thank you goodbye bye there she go
there goes gura
that was so nice to talk to her
ah man
so much so much more fun with friends
you know
just fun with friends
yeah
I mean it's fun with you guys as well
but it adds like an extra layer of fun
when when the homies come say hello you
know and cheer me on as I suffer I say
suffer but it's fun it's fun it's fun
don't don't you guys worry
I know State all right just just don't
move don't move no you don't have to
move well that's fine too I guess
I won't lose my mental result you and
Guru get along so well yeah we can't we
can talk pretty casually with each other
I think
occasionally I do I do forget that we're
on stream
glad that you guys can join in
always glad to have you guys listen in
on our
broadness sometimes
where do I even go from here we go
all right we got this we got this guys
we're in the final stretch I can feel it
yeah
sanity at 100 nothing
we're great we're doing real good right
now getting that
getting that babe though
I even know if I really didn't
I don't even need to do that part I can
probably just jump right from there to
the right one huh
yeah I don't know
I feel like testing that theory going
with a tried and true
you see this Chapel dead beats prey pray
pray for me
you got this
[Music]
we got this I gotta do it for for me and
for all my friends
Blue Ruin baby
that was not what I meant
you don't have to fall like that my man
foreign
it wasn't what I meant to do but it is
what I did so we have to live with that
we got to carry that weight
nolly.com
oh
wow oh that's not quite yeah I don't
know why I did that
that's fine guys I think for the final
stretch it's all good uh
thank you
I'm just glad um
I'm glad we got some friends today
it warms my heart
my man
okay
yeah it warms my heart to see some
friends here so
I was glad they could come and enjoy a
talk
those two holes scare me yeah
but even if I fall through them it's not
like it's not the end so
the good news I think
I just gotta remain positive what if I
did no I would bounce off I'd Bounce Off
the Wall if I did that
here
what a calming Chapel
Chapel perilous
Ollie
Ollie's here
Ali
except I have you eaten seven hours in
did you eat yes I'm having pasta
I'm having pasta
Ollie I'm in I'm in VC but I'm in like
um
what is it
I'm in the the VC that's uh
it's only in Indiana so let me
if you'd like I wonder if I could just
drop into the
I'm gonna sit there in zero zero let me
let the others know so that anyone can
join now anyone can join
yeah if you'd like to if you're busy
though whoa oh my god there you are
you okay hey oh yeah I'm doing great
yeah no worries I'm I'm fine thank you
for your concern are you okay are you
doing good
I'm I'm doing fine I saw you uh started
streaming from like noon yeah and you're
still going yeah yeah I gotta be I gotta
beat jump King
have you commenced a Glock lug what is
that you mean drinking
yeah a little bit in your throat yeah I
mean I did but uh I started drinking
like um something that everyone in chat
said was like a really bad idea to drink
so I stopped
um we did what did you drink okay so
have you ever heard of like a Red Bull
and vodka before Ollie
ma'am when I ask drinking I meant water
oh
uh yeah
um I kind of need to order some some
more water uh from the convenience store
in a minute I was gonna do that actually
haha yeah
that was the plan uh definitely don't or
don't you worry about me guys
I'm so worried no I'm concerned it's
okay I'm just I'm jumping to the top of
a really tall mountain is the thing so
like I'm it's I'm trying to look for
like a hot babe like there's a really
hot babe at the top of this like at this
castle Yeah I want to get there oh why
would you
spend seven hours just to get on top of
a castle when I'm right here
I see I see what you did there I see I
see but here's the thing Ollie
apparently the Babe is quote unquote on
fire she's like smoking hot which leads
me to believe that she's like on fire
fire
um and I need to rescue her yeah you're
not on fire right now so I think it's
fine yeah I see so ah I see you're
always attracted to the fire like
there's also a Garrison pie yeah that's
right oh wait huh oh no she she's she's
a great friend
we're we're buddies but I mean friends
you're such a cute Joker Ollie
I'm alerting everyone now I miss anyone
and we can join yata
um
anyway I'm happy to have you here today
to visit me
um as I play this really difficult game
I'm almost I almost beat it I'm very
close to beating it you're close like
when when it comes to person like how
close are you I think I'm like 85
percent
done
oh yeah so like this icy level right
here is really difficult
um but if I can beat this icy level then
I'm just I'm so close so I can taste it
now I can taste it Ollie
good luck I I I won't talk too much I'll
just support you right thank you I
appreciate it thank you for chilling
with me I mean it's like chilling yeah
chilling how I get it because it's cold
um yeah I mean it's not really like oh
dang it uh it's not like a distracting
thing when people come in and talk to me
because it's not like I'm watching
something if I was watching something
then I'd be like distracted but
no it's been pretty
yeah
you don't get distracted when people
talk to you while you play a game nope
just kind of doesn't happen yeah Reaper
skills I guess it is kind of a skill but
when it comes to watching stuff it's
just because I used to chat with my
friends a lot when we would do things
like uh like draw Hangouts and stuff
like that like hang out and draw
together kind of thing yeah
[Music]
I've been following a lot in this game
but the good news is
I'm gonna make it I have more jumps than
Falls and that's what's wonderful about
this game
awesome I feel good about myself
also uh congrats on that uh cover with
my uh ice advice that's right yeah yeah
uh baddest the baddest the baddest the
baddest yay I'm excited for everyone to
see it have you haven't heard it yet
have you ollie
no oh I can't wait for you to hear it
you like it
I do some wrapping I think everyone knew
that already
[Music]
but like she calls herself Cali and I'm
like hey hey hello I also have that name
that you have
yeah
yup very coincidental but I worked
really hard
yeah that's right
yeah and the MV is really cool too so
I'm excited for you to see it oh we were
waiting for a long time for it so
um yeah hope you like it
oh my gosh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
you made it yup damn it
uh I can do it
yeah okay
problem
okay okay oh my God okay
nice yes
oh yeah you are you witnessing this
craziness
yeah yeah
yeah oh wow I just don't just don't move
my man just don't move okay as long as I
don't freak out too much
I do have a question though sure
uh what made you decide on doing this
and you're in stream
um I just really like this game a lot
that's kind of all that there is to it
yeah it's a hard game but I like it
um and yeah I really just I want to get
to the top of the mountain
have you been in it before nope
did this game and she beat it so I want
to beat it too
oh
I'm very close
very close yeah got this thank you I'll
do my best
yeah
we'll see it's funny how uh this little
night Sir man hmm
uh he doesn't break his legs yeah it's
because his legs are really strong like
Tree Trunks and they're full of muscles
that are good for jumping that's why
he's the jump King oh
yeah he's got like really really thick
legs that are like good for jumping
that's why he's gonna get to the top to
get the Babe instead of any of the other
like characters in the game they're like
oh you could never get the babe because
it's impossible they don't have legs
like tree trunks is the thing
yeah but I do
why is the babe on top of the tower
anyway I don't know I'd like to ask her
when I when I meet with her our faded
meeting
asked her yeah I'll be like hey babe why
are you up here
yeah a lot of Falls happen in this game
though like it gets to a point where you
can make a ton of progress and then
um
yeah you make it like a ton of progress
okay there we go
um and you go all the way down uh like
several you can end up going all the way
down to like actually the start of the
game
um please don't try doing that right now
no no I don't want to I actually don't
think that I can is the thing
um because at the bottom of this level
you see they're like two holes there
yeah you have to like fall into those
and then walk to the side to like here
see look I'd have to walk to the middle
of that to like have to go back to the
first one yeah yeah getting kind of
risky now I'm fine don't worry about it
was that like an example yeah yeah I was
just showing you that it's really
impossible for me to go back to the
beginning but uh what if right
please don't Dixon I don't think it's I
mean I'd have to try really hard
here we go
you didn't have to show me an example
nah it's okay I mean I was already down
here so I was like yeah might as well
[Music]
plus it's been a while since I've been
out in the cold so I mean I'm just
kidding I was up in the ice but like the
windy icy cold yeah I kind of missed it
so for two seconds not anymore though so
you want to do that warm yourself up
with the candles yeah yeah exactly
that's right this is Chapel perilous
it's a nice place to to pray for Cali's
soul
are you playing this game yeah you can
pray for my soul
easy yeah
I'm gonna die
it's funny
yeah yeah
that's the joke yeah yeah yeah
that's fine
I'm excited to do some fun stuff with
you and education Senpai again
yeah it's going to be wink wink long
soon right yes soon it's going to be
soon Mario Party there's a new Mario
party as well which I didn't know until
recently there is yeah I think so isn't
isn't that right yet there's a new Mario
Party yeah
oh yeah we should play that together
that would be fun yeah definitely
see you also Halloween's coming up
yeah that's right it came out today yeah
the new one
um yup Halloween is coming up indeed
that's right
sure is I've got all kinds of fun stuff
planned
um
so yeah I'm excited making drinks
Halloween drinks Halloween cocktails
fun fun they're very good they just
taste they taste like dessert they're
very nice
drinks oh yeah well I mean if it's me
it's probably gonna be drinks
wait hold that's not what I wanted to do
that's not what I'm about to do yep yeah
little mistake like that can send you
all the way back down
it's fine oh and go all the way back so
it's fine
yeah it's always uh fascinates me how
you can drink so much yeah I mean
it's like uh I don't know it's just
something that I kind of got used to
over time I feel like I just kind of got
used to it yeah
but I also genuinely liked it I like
good tasting drinks and they make me
feel happy
ah not all the time not too much
good it's not necessary I don't think
it's very fun to get smashed personally
I think there's a perfect level at least
for me a personal level of drinking
comfort you know
funny drinking stories oh
there's um there's this drink that got
um like it's not it's not outlawed in
America I think it isn't um I looked up
looked up the statistics and I guess it
isn't but I thought that it was
um a long time ago
uh I was I was drinking some of this
because my sister told me to she said
just do it so I did and it was really
bad
um and I threw up yeah it was awful and
that drink is like if you it's also like
it's basically poison it's the thing
um it's called yeah yeah Four Loco used
to be outlawed oh okay I see ya
um yeah basically it's like you throw up
like a toxic green looking like nasty
it's really bad you just you could swear
that like it would like glow in the dark
anyway
um so yeah I threw up and then many many
years later I come to Japan right and a
friend tells me to drink this thing
called strong zero
drink it and I think to myself oh my God
this is that same drink but it's under a
different name in Japan it was bad it
like made me go what why why has this
happened what have they done and
apparently it's incredibly popular in
Japan and a ton of people love it and
drink it like it's nothing and I'm like
are you guys okay with boys like this
are you are you good
yeah that's that's more of a concerning
than funny yeah yeah it's really a funny
story but yes concerning
um I was gonna also tell you the story
about I made like a dessert drink today
not today the other day I was practicing
making drinks for my Halloween uh
cocktail making stream yeah and um so I
was making like a dessert one and uh the
blender that I was using I didn't
realize that it was like a like a juice
making blender
um and like it's it's made in such a way
that the plastic is like it doesn't have
a top or a bottom you unscrew it and
like you're supposed to put the cap on
it first turn the blender over and then
unscrew it from the blender right
um I didn't know that so I made this
delicious drink I tasted it I was like
this is the greatest drink I've ever
tasted in my life and so I unscrewed the
thing I don't realize that I have to
have a cap on the top or like it's gonna
come out the bottom so I unscrewed it
and then uh it all came out the bottom
it came flooding out and it got all over
me it got all over my floors my floors
were nice and sticky and the whole
kitchen smelled like oranges for a while
yeah I mean there are some plus minus it
is it's true there are some pros and
cons here the the cons were probably the
sticky floors but it did smell kind of
nice so that's that's the good part of
it I guess
but yeah I try to make like cute drinks
because I don't really
I it's not that I don't like hard liquor
I mean my deadbeats can testify I've
drank you know whiskey out of the bottle
good old Johnny W who's no longer with
us yeah I mean just for fun and when bae
and I reviewed some rooms together uh
she was drinking like a Asahi beer just
one beer and she had a good time that
she got very very uh
in a state of sorts she had a good time
and uh she would take a sip of beer
every time I took a sip of whiskey yeah
like
how whiskey yeah yeah yeah like uh just
just out of the bottle with like some
ice maybe in a cup
yeah I mean I've heard of whiskeys in
the cup but out of the bottle yeah I
mean it's just easier for for me to
drink it that way when I'm like trying
to just like take a little shot you know
like just just take a big step out of
the bottle you know just easier that way
more convenient
I see yeah a bay is like an ultra
lightweight so like we had a Time
yeah
I hope she's still okay after that she
probably she's probably fine but you
know it's me being concerned
I was concerned over over my cohai you
know
yeah
Listen by being concerned oh you've
reached despite I did I did
no don't don't follow oh my God no way
no my man oh boy just stay here don't
don't stay okay that's okay that's
understandable understandable
it's cool it was bound to happen
I'm learning things though I'm learning
as I go I'm learning as I go along
yeah that's why this game is hard
because it takes a long time to like
like figure out exactly how to
how to get through it
can't you imagine anyone's been running
this uh oh yeah the speed run is about
like four minutes or so yeah what yeah I
haven't looked at it yet because I've
been waiting to watch until I've been
waiting to watch it until I finished it
myself
I remember this Chapel part because I
saw picoda Senpai play here but ah yeah
I want it to be a surprise I was
thinking I didn't know an hour or like
at least 30 minutes four minutes yep
they just fly through this level but
they do it like perfectly I think
because like if you if you have to like
Speed Run I can imagine like if you
speedrun other games right they have to
do everything perfectly or they have
like glitches I don't know if you can
glitch this game or not though like go
through walls and stuff I don't know
maybe someone's figured out how to do it
because like this game is all about
perfect jumps right
yeah I mean you would assume that they
have to get every single jump perfect
someone out there has done it I'm sure
because you gotta you gotta get that
record you know if you haven't done it
perfect yeah
you haven't done it perfect you can't
get the record oh no I [\h__\h] up I was
supposed to do it from the back dang it
I forgot
ah
this is a this game takes a lot of
muscle memory
does
by the way oh I'll see it feels like a
tomato just like a basic tomato pasta
just kind of felt like like a eating a
basic pasta every once in a while yeah I
feel like you can just
a basic pasta
yeah what kind of pasta do you like do
you like pasta
I like
oh yeah the uh uh
the ugly the ugly allele uh
Cleo tortellini
oh
okay let's see I'll I'll I'll
uglio
uglio aglio
I'm like trying to chat do you know what
this is pasta de aglio Olio arugula I
know arugula is a is a
I think it's like a
an herb
what the what are you talking about it's
a it's a Ollie Ollie pasta yes I like
that one yeah oh yeah it's got the same
name as you then that's kind of cute
it's cute I like that I'll eat yes
oh how adorable
it's very cute
I'd love to cook pasta for you someday
it's basically the only thing I can make
that's like consistently good love
yeah yes please yeah make like really
good carbonara and like if you have a
pasta you like I can learn how to make
it so I'll learn how to make your uh
agolio olioli
Pasta Pasta yeah Ollie pasta I got you
just leave it to me
so then if I ever get
treaty
[Music]
yeah the underworld uh-huh of course
I'll be waiting for you okay
yay
okay it's a promise then
yeah
okay I'll figure it out I'll figure it
out
I'll figure it out maybe maybe I won't
a little bounce and then there's just a
little jump and then
I don't know and just all right chill
stay still stay still oh as long as we
don't go back down
Stay Stay yeah
struggle
super slippery yeah it's pretty slippery
here I'm starting to figure it out
so
so it begs the question
like this is a castle with lots of
platforms how did
the hot babe get on top anyways maybe
she climbed there herself I bet she has
really strong legs too she just wanted
to see like a really cool View
and then she kind of like got stuck up
there she was like oh dang I don't know
how to get down from here so he's just
chilling up there yeah I gotta go find
her
help her out we both we both may be like
jumping a lot
yeah I bet that's what it is I don't
know I'm not actually sure
yeah yeah I bet she's got like really
thick tree trunk size as well oh [\h__\h]
there we go
yeah tree trunks for us yeah
that's fine you fall a lot in this game
sadly
yeah you just gotta kind of learn how to
deal with it I guess
but my fingers are like they're feeling
the impact of the buttons quite a bit
are they okay yeah they're fine nothing
like hurts too much or anything like
that it's just like I can feel like
button kind of like little button
indents in my forming in my fingers
ah I see yeah it's not that bad though
not the bed don't don't worry don't
worry I appreciate the concern though
it's very sweet of you
I hope
um you can meet the hot babe thank you
as soon as possible I'll do my best
you're planning on going like is there
like any time limit like oh it's this
time I think I'm going to hit the hay or
something I'm not sure I was thinking
well let's see it's almost been about
eight hours by now gura estimated that I
could meet the Babe in like two and a
half maybe about half an hour ago maybe
she's a no she said two and a half I
think so yeah maybe two more hours I'll
try
um I think I might be able to do it but
if I get really close I just I just
don't know if I can end the stream until
I do it you know I'm so close so we'll
see we'll see
hmm we shall see I don't know
yeah
so close to the you're so close
everyone's like you're so close
I know
uh I've been working really hard to get
far in this game so oh oh oh okay oh
that's fine oh okay
that was close I'll make it work I'll
make it work
just gotta try again
some jump
there
back back it up
run it out I need to do it hard enough
that I bounce off the top of the ceiling
that's my issue yeah
[Music]
the lag is so good
it's like I've fallen down yeah I fell
down maybe five seconds ago but you are
now experiencing me falling down I
it's like getting hit with it twice
welcome back
oh my gosh the Reverb is so good
thank you
oh my gosh wow Chapel noises no way way
longer it's warm here no hot girls at
the back no I can't and no tacos I just
ate pasta but thank you very much I
appreciate it
oh man this is cute nice Chapel noises
wow
that was such a good idea
I'm gonna turn on reverb too for when
I'm in the chapel
yeah when I'm in the gym
Chapel noises yeah Chapel noises
big fan of Chapel noises
yeah
and now they're gone
oh they're gone because we're at the top
whoa for now
for now
yeah
that may change very shortly but for now
we're here
okay be careful there we go okay be
careful there we go
[Music]
we here oh
yeah run it back okay
no wait okay
I need to remember how I did that last
time
oh oh stay here
no no no no you don't need it that's
fine hey
and we're back here again
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man I love it
we have some guacamole too if you want
welcome ah you drive a hard bargain
mysterious voices from the chapel that
are definitely coming from Ali man
I don't know you drive a hard bargain oh
we're out we're outside now there's no
Echo
ah man have you ever had like homemade
guacamole
guacamole before
no I I bought one once but uh
I don't think that is supposed to taste
too plain
oh I see oh I gotta make some for you
next time because I make some good
guacamole
we
can guacamole guacamole
guacamori I like that that's a good name
for it very smart yeah sure guacamori
you betcha please look forward to it
I'm getting the jumping time wrong these
days lately not these days lately
really it really is only like midnight
so it's not too bad right now but you
know
bye
um usually at two because that gives me
like uh eight hours of sleep but it
depends like I gotta also read super
chats as well so
oh yeah and a lot of people have been
very excited and cheering me on so
there's quite a few so it might take me
a little bit but that's fine
we just gotta make sure that this
doesn't go over the 12 hours Mark or
yeah
exactly see that's the only thing that's
the only thing we really gotta worry
about yeah oh I like staying here
because this is where I haven't fallen
off and died yet I mean you can't die in
this game but
hmm
yeah all right well let me see
dang it I was just a little bit off I
keep feeling I was just a bit off
maybe if I
um
that was also way too much okay I think
I have an idea I'm gonna try it again
I'm gonna try it again welcome
back home we're back home again
it's nice and warming it is lots of
candles very roasty toasty
yeah it's nice but I would like as well
you know it's also hot though the babe
babe at the top
she's smoking hot and I want to meet her
I don't know why I did that
[\h__\h] sound you might just roast me yes
yeah I hope she spits like some flames
and is like a good rapper
that would be awesome
you have quite the taste when it comes
to women thanks I guess
thank you for the comp
strange voices
what an ingenious idea though thank you
for sharing that idea good idea
you're welcome
is that like a Mickey Mouse
a little Mickey Mouse in the in the
chapel
the door
all right
what the [\h__\h] you left
again
I can't
oh man incredible
[Music]
oh hurricane you can do this I know
I'm coming
oh I'm coming
oh I'm on the way
maybe right now I'm having some trouble
in the chapel though
usually I don't have this much trouble
in the chapel
because it happened like in the taste of
the guacamole no I don't want the guac
you're trying to distract me with the
guac you want to keep me away from the
babe I won't do it I refused I won't
fall for your trickery
Holiness before hot babe
holiness
Holiness before hot babes I'm gonna uh
remember that can I get that on a shirt
Holiness before hot day
yeah I want that as a jump King official
merchandise
yeah very good I like that Ollie good to
you you're welcome yeah
Ollie are you really good um at math
uh it depends what kind of math you're
talking about
uh-huh not okay
forgetting yeah I see
um because girl and I were kind of
talking about like how you're super
super good at math
oh shush yeah and we were like dang wish
I was good at math like not a girl Ollie
dang it f I got really close though
that was really close yeah I think I can
do it
that's right we're back
we're back in the chapel
good I could maybe mention some numbers
from the pig sure hi yes send us send us
some numbers from the grave
oh but but you're out of the capitals oh
dang it maybe next time when I
definitely fall back in
yeah which will be very soon I'm sure
I'll start spitting the digits once
you're down thanks yeah send me those
digits girl
send me those digits
all right we got this
but I mean if you don't like pie then I
can just give you my number wink wank
uh-huh
yeah but that that sounds like a a
little hassle for me to international
calling fees I went oh we're back in the
back of the shaft all right what were
those digits great points
five nights
whoa whoa
whoa how do you remember what two six
four three three Chapel knows I gotta
get out of here I gotta get the [\h__\h] out
of here
oh man we gotta get out of here one six
nine
oh it's not the [\h__\h] left
get it no no it's no there's nothing
funny about that number
there's nothing funny about it
Ali
there's just
nine nine three seven five one
oh five eight
[Music]
no actually five
ah Noah
ah
f
aha the holy tacos the holy tacos
yeah you know you know
yeah the Holy Ghost the holy tacos
[\h__\h] the Holy Taco
oh my God
this is what this game does it makes you
go crazy it makes you go literally
insane I've been saying insane [\h__\h] this
whole stream
and like I'll say it and I'll be like
Cali
what what are you doing
most of it was when girl was here
I see yeah
he's really goodbye things it was about
like like an hour ago
mm-hmm yeah she's good at that though
getting like getting me to say like
crazy [\h__\h] but
you you got me acting funny too
is it because of the triple holy noises
that must be what it is
amazing okay thanks that reassures me
I'm worried that I've oh
I'm worried that every word that I've
been saying has just been like the
ramblings of a crazy Reaper but I mean
it's probably the truth but as long as
you guys are having fun and that's what
I care about so
I mean I I think that's what everyone's
here for
kind of true enough yeah
not only they're here to see me one
that's okay I'm joking I don't think so
I mean I mean there's a little of both
there's people that come to watch me win
and people that come to watch me not win
so you can't please everyone so I just
do my best
okay here we go nice run it back run it
back my boy
we go and okay all right now here
oh ah dang it okay okay stop moving just
stop moving all right that's fine we can
redo it
I guess you can say that it's hard to
let it go oh my God dies
I get it that's uh Frozen
all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right
yeah no problem no problem
oh well that that no
okay
all good
am I press it too late all right let me
try it again
the timing is it's all about the timing
you gotta time everything perfectly
right wait no why did I hold it so wow
that was definitely my fault oh man I uh
I forgot how to play the game for a
second
I mean it's been eight hours kind of
yeah
that makes sense yeah
but you like me to create some more
number seven sure might as well
three nine nine three oh boy five one oh
man five eight two oh it burns four nine
four four five oh okay we're at a chapel
just narrow leaves it's narrowly escaped
numbers big number
laughs
I
the Church of Pi the Church of Pi
you love to see it
you love to see the church
it's fine I'd rather it be the church
exactly it made me feel like I had to
get the f word out of there so thank you
for that I appreciate that very much you
helped me
you're welcome well I guess I'll be
taking my leave now then okie dokie well
thank you for dropping by to to wish me
luck my dude
hmm good luck Senpai and please remember
that the Holy Taco is
all right thank you bye
thank you
so cute
Ali
adorable
so cute bye Ollie there she go
there she go
yeah the pie method is like really
entertaining and like helpful to make me
want to get out of the chapel so it
comes to her for that yeah
haha chill
ah too late
we're in the final stretch though Lads
um I just don't really know like what's
gonna happen here run it back run it
back
all right
uh pain and suffering likely on the menu
okay oh
oh my God
foreign
I can't go to the left
there's no way
because then I'll run into the door
then there's that block right there
[Music]
all right well that's fine that's okay
I'll take it I'll take that
um
we're gonna have to learn how to do this
over and over again guys so it's fine
it's fine
don't hey what okay I saw you clip
through that my boy I don't agree with
that
whatever
all right
we'll just we'll take it guys we'll take
it
run it back
yep
and okay
all right
okay no problem
okay that's not great I just don't move
just don't move okay
fine we're fine
ah the final stretch is a bunch of five
screen Falls
yeah love to hear it
that's all right though we can do it
together I know that we can I know we
can do it
that's bad that's bad well
that's all right I guess
I'll take it
might go into a bit of a focus mode but
that's all right
still be here just chatting away kind of
I didn't think anyone was gonna come
I'm really glad
we had one two
three
four guests
it's a lot
it's a lot of people
so I'm really I'm really grateful
ah I should have full powered it I
didn't
yeah we came yeah exactly
yeah
four talking guests
plus many many many many deadbeats and
Friends
so thank you guys
thank you guys for being guests too
guests too
we're gonna do this
though my confidence does get quite
quite higher when the possibility of
sewers becomes less so
we just we take that you know
we take that
all right
just don't overshoot it oh oh okay all
right all right all right
no no no
go back go back go back no not not that
far okay fine
okay bring it back
foreign
you got this
thank you I don't believe in the sewers
anymore
we're the first to guess I missed them
uh Kiara
and then
um I think gura came in but then Bae
also came in and also said goodbye uh in
the meantime so yeah
right
foreign
let's do this
immediately Falls
oh wait
okay okay
so perfect good beats
all right that was my bad
I mean it's all my bad but that was
especially my bed
all right
um
just focus Kelly yes
oh okay
okay
all the way
and a little jump there
okay
power okay gonna jump
and we bounced off the wall
okay boogie
oh
[Music]
okay
come on
hold on a minute hold on right there
hold your rooting tootin cowboy shooting
horses
if I go
is it a wall balance I wonder or maybe
no maybe it's all the way to the left
it's either all the way to the I don't
know if it's a wall bounce though that
doesn't seem very likely but
[Music]
I don't know
I would think left yeah I think
full left I kind of got that feeling
through because I just don't think a
wall balance is going to be powerful
enough
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
no wait okay that was very foolish
foreign
[Music]
my hands are so sweaty my hands are so
sweaty
[Music]
what if I could just oh
my bad my bad
looks like I just skip the one in the
middle though
like I don't I don't need the one in the
middle do I
feel like I could jump over it but I
just don't
you gotta believe
hang on I need to get water uh I don't
have any water with me
that epic music has to stop for just I'm
going to my fridge hang on
oh yeah
going through my fridge
oh my [\h__\h] god sorry hold on
I'm just gonna
go into my fridge
yeah I'm getting a drink
Nikes
drinkies
oh there's tea
hold on go whiskey
whiskey so I can celebrate if I make it
I got water I got water uh not water
it's teeth I got tea as well so
okay
um
[Music]
well now we have to beat this tonight so
I'm I'm gonna bleed out real quick
to let the world know
just letting the world know
gotta check Twitter
anything I can do to not play the game
for a minute now let me drink some
tea
it's hard but fighting once again thank
you
believe in the me that believes in you
you're still going yes I am
bad
hahaha
[Music]
that felt good it didn't but you know
what it's fine
we're gonna have to do that a couple
times
it's fine
it's fine guys I can do it again I can
do it again
I did it before I can do it again oh
God damn it
this game will not defeat me
it won't defeat me
I promise it will not defeat me
[Music]
at least we learned that full left was
not the way see you're always learning
something new in this game
always learning something new
[Music]
like maybe let's not do full left over
there you know
foreign
wait that was an accident I didn't mean
to do that
I'm a bit tilted now you guys I'm a bit
tilted getting a glimpse of not getting
a glimpse of the end dang it
it's like uh it's messing with me guys
it's messing with me
that's okay
I can do it
[\h__\h] how would I do that
I gotta compose myself
is it possible to get like Victory
tilted like you get close to a victory
and so you like get tilted in a way
and then you are unable to play the game
I think that's the thing right
[Music]
just follow just follow your instincts
we'll do we'll do I'll do my best
we call that choking
yeah regularly I figured it was a normal
thing
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
foreign
okay
[Music]
I like how Ted kept saying Jinx doesn't
exist but then keeps chasing it I just
don't really believe it
but I get why I get why it seems like a
common thing
remember what we did before
okay
not quite full be careful
now all the way here remember a little
jump
full power and run it back
off the top
a little jump and then a wall bounce
next we're gonna go as close to the edge
of this ice as we can
possibly can and then do a full jump and
run it back
now all right all right nice now full
jump to the right
okay
this is also yeah to the right
bad
[\h__\h] no no no I can save this all right
I can save this
so I can save this I can save the Run
there full jump run it back
bunk on the top little jump wall bounce
get to the edge the very edge
oh no there's a little too much
nope get to the very edge
full jump run it back
big power jump
all the way to the right
okay and this part I still don't
understand so oh
that part is just instinct
foreign
that part is pure Instinct so I'm not
even gonna try but the ice level I feel
like I'm figuring out
I feel like I've kind of got it but I
don't know
babe is waiting
just gotta be waiting
while not very punishing the chapel area
is pretty frustrating
foreign
there we go
you are so so close good luck Callie
sadly also good night have a good
evening
anyone who's got to leave no worries I
hope that you can check out the VOD
hopefully I will have achieved Victory
I'm praying
we're in the chapel Ray
you Deadbeats
[Music]
there's some interesting noises I make
there we go
you will have I'm sure oh I'm Not Gonna
Let You Down
baby
I think we can do it
I don't want to reach the stream limit
but
I want to get there
[Music]
wow pie
you missed the first six hours so you'll
check the VOD anyway
hope you'll enjoy there have been many
ups and downs
but thankfully with my friends uh it
became even more intriguing intriguing
is a word for it I suppose
side on the edge ready for the little
jump
okay we'll jump run it back
on the head little jump wall bounce
get to the edge
take your time getting to the edge
run it back
it's nearly 1am and JP yes nothing I go
to bed at two usually
thank you for your concern
I'm all good
that was too much yep I knew immediately
that was too much don't move
walk on the head
little jump
wall bounce
run it back
dang it I really could have gone more
powerful there I'll go ahead
little jump wall bounce
get to the edge
take your time though
don't Don't Force It don't rush it
get a dash
full power run it back
more powerful jump than last time all
the way to the left okay
okay
and they ramp up the music
[Music]
all the way to the left
okay
nope
it's mine
all the way to the left
okay here we go
this part is pure instinct
that's rough
all right Bonk on the head
well balance
[Music]
hit the edge
full power running back big jump
but not too big
you got it
no
don't move
the edge
power run it back
a jump
hit the left
damn it
okay fine that's up the wall
power run it back big jump
all the way to the left
no okay fine oh
no oh I knew that that was okay no
problem no problem no problem we're fine
foreign
that's pretty rough
a part right there
[Music]
all the way to the left
oh
I'm gonna guess
[Music]
[Applause]
look at that big Fireball behind her
she's burning
okay
[Music]
thank you guys
thank you
yeah
we got a
babe
we got the babe yes come here wait she's
not on fire a smooch get
cake
king of the world baby yeah yes fly away
yeah here we go
yeah blasted off my man
let me take a picture
I want a picture
[Applause]
yeah I got the babe I got the babe I got
the babe I got the bed oh my God look at
the rainbow
you guys are nuts what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I Wanna Cry
foreign
[Music]
we did it
yay thank you for playing
I'm gonna cry
[Music]
the dumbest smile
thank you everyone
oh my [\h__\h] thank you everyone I'm
taking a swig of this vodka you guys are
the best thank you for watching me and
for cheering for me playing this game
this crazy crazy game
is everybody cheers got it gotta clink
cheers everyone thank you so much
you guys you guys deserve a sip too for
being here with me
we're coming to support me
you guys are the best
oh holy hell
oh man that was fun
man what a ride you guys
well there's the record I mean it's not
it's my record but
I don't have any words guys but just
I'm really grateful
um to you guys and also all the friends
that came to chat with me and cheer me
on along the way
um every single step of the way
I'm glad we did it I'm glad we stuck to
it
um just yeah thanks so much everyone 22
hours let's go
oh 18 18 hours
18 hours
we did it I think just about
thank you so much
um thank you thank you thank you thank
you a million times over everyone
um
I'm glad that I played this game
DLC oh yeah oh we're not done with jump
King yet we will be playing the DLC and
and new babe plus I want all the babes I
want every single one of them for me
um I was surprised that she like wasn't
on fire-ish but that that's cool
um
sub 20 hour run super puck
thanks guys
I gotta play that DLC agreedy for more
babes indeed
no babe Plus
I did it super tactical leaping
Adventure other babes
new babe plus
sacrifice crown or remain a king
um
before I decide what we're gonna do guys
can you tell me which one is better I'm
not gonna play new babe plus tonight but
um I don't know what each one does is
the thing remain a king
you are King you deserve the crown I
agree
[Music]
your crown and find your own way to the
other world
find your own way
what does that mean
just different skin oh I see I see
you are king
[Music]
I see a sacrifice always pays off
you found it before oh that's right I
did find it already
[Music]
to find your way to the other world yeah
yeah we'll do it
we can do it ourselves
um go back to the DLC anyway hey idiot
check this out I have a crown look at
this I got it you have heard the legend
yet uh-huh yeah look at the crown yeah
yup this is the crown my boy check it
out
what a funny yellow hat
can I have it
[\h__\h] no my man
you out of your mind
I kind of like that though all right
save and exit
guys this has been great thank you so
much everyone I'm gonna go ahead and
read super chats now which there are so
many you guys went nuts though thank you
so much thank you thank you thank you
um for all those heading out I'm your
Mori hope you'll remember me
um and I'll catch you on the flip side
I'm gonna read these tsupas it'll
probably take a while I'm hoping that we
don't hit the 12 hour mark we might if
we do it is what it is
um but I'm gonna go read these now so
yeah uh you guys the best make sure that
you guys rest well this has been a long
grind especially those of you who have
been with me for the whole eight almost
nine hours yeah eight and a half hours
all of you who have been here since the
start you guys go rest you guys go chill
um have yourselves a good day for those
of you sticking around for super chats I
will see you shortly uh with that being
said guys thanks a lot
um for everything we're always cheerful
we played a hard video game and I feel
good about that
um
thank you
bye guys
see you shortly for super chats
[Music]
stay frosty groovy
Hail to the King baby
thank you for jumping with me bye
according to DLC
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
start reciting pie for you
no it's a joke I don't know why yeah I
don't know it
I don't know it guys
hey I'm back congratulations beating the
game have a good night thank you I'm
gonna be reading your supers hope you
guys don't mind if um
I keep kind of like a
a lower more chill voice for these
supers I'm just gonna read out your
messages and uh
and whatnot and do some shout outs
because I didn't realize I shouted quite
a bit
I shouted uh rather loud
getting that babe so um
the numbers Maureen what are the numbers
mean
I want to know what the numbers mean oh
Lord oh wow oh
oh
yeah you guys went wild
thank you so much uh thank you thank you
thank you everyone you guys went nutty
and you guys are the best
ah thank you for the huge support this
time you guys
um
man
I've been having a really good time uh
streaming lately I think I've mentioned
that before to you guys that
um I've been like enjoying it a lot more
recently
um and so I was really glad to um
to do this nice long stream with you
guys
um
and um
doing endurance streams is not so bad
you know
um if you got like fun friends and chat
to talk to so
um yeah you guys are a big part of that
thank you
thank you for being my chat thank you
for being my dead Beats thank you for
sharing for me
Echo
all right it's off now though River on
purpose oh yeah definitely
Gigi and otsu thank you very much and
thank you for the hearts you guys
that payoff is always great
yeah
I hope those enjoying the VOD also enjoy
seeing it happen
oh man we got um
a big UPS to Max Maxwell
Max Maxwell
I'm sorry to hear that you're gonna lose
your job soon that's really odd I'll
have to start over again for like the
third time I'm sure that you know what's
going on behind the scenes and whatnot
but I'll send some supers while I can
love you don't don't worry Max Maxwell
you take care of yourself right now okay
um even if you feel like you gotta start
over
um
I know that can be frustrating so good
luck to you my dude don't even worry
about it you watch out for yourself
first and the pickups to the Kevin kfb
thank you very much you got the babe
nice
hey you wait you really got the babe
I did it I got the babe and the feeling
standing there at the top of the world
was Indescribable I was in Bliss
thinking about deadbeats and you there I
was thinking about live stuff a lot
while playing how we all jump and fall
and Rise yeah exactly see Kevin you get
it you get the the theme I don't know
maybe there isn't the theme but that was
the feeling I got you gotta jump you
might fall but I think it would be worth
it to try anyway
yeah I understood my past self wouldn't
pass this challenge but after I met you
I also Met My New Self and yeah Cali
it's not a matter of will or skill for
you it's a matter of time Ah that's
that's so cool that sounds so cool when
you say that
also yes I will be playing the DLC thank
you so much for the big support Kevin
and the Big Ups Too then thank you very
much good luck on your exam a pickup
thank you very much last week and we're
still getting it's the last week we're
still getting endurance streams take
care of Cali and do your best will do
jotita a big UPS to Elsa Le Pen thank
you oh jump King on sale today heck yeah
totally renewed respect for your efforts
didn't appreciate the struggle until I
played
uh half the sewers do your best Elsa Le
Pen the babe will be yours to yakimoyomi
thank you and the biggest Shadow pencil
we deadbeats don't eat a smoking hot
babe on the tower because we have the
Empress of death with us we support you
on your goals nonetheless mori's dreams
are our dreams too you can do it thank
you Shadow pencil very sweet of you from
Pierre gotaku thank you very much and
the Big Ups to action thank you enjoy
the VOD thank you Marcus Meneses and a
big up to donger bread heck yeah I don't
want to jump to conclusions but I have a
feeling about the progress you'll make
today snow is a better s word start than
sewers true facts
we definitely uh made progress so to
speak to beat the freaking game
sorry still a lot for me to process
right now
lost the finale got to watch the VOD
later yeah yeah check it out anytime
a big UPS to Sombra Park thank you and
bunny game thank you very much I made us
to gilamax the space beat and a huge
huge UPS too the one the only infallible
Franklin the bully Hunter
Franklin what is up
thank you so much thank you for the fat
we got a party
party time
Franklin
nice to have you back these days thank
you so much for dropping by jeez I
thought I was late time to save that
smoking hot babe thank you for joining
us Franklin I wonder if you stayed the
whole time thanks a lot Franklin but I
wouldn't I wouldn't blame you if you had
to check out the VOD later so
but just thank you in general for for
coming to hang
appreciate you dropping by to say hello
and I hope the bully hunting's going
well for you I'll hold out a long note
for you usually I'd like try and hold
out a note by like whistling or
something like that but
um not gonna do that
because you've got to protect the throat
so we're gonna play it soon on the
recorder for you here we go
[Music]
oh
for the absolute Chad Franklin the bully
Hunter thank you so much
and a big UPS to jprs NSR thank you
draconic Insight thank you very much
fire holder one big UPS to you I hope
that was a long one
I had to have been a long one had to
have been over 30 seconds
that was long at 38-ish nice 33 not bad
between 33 and 38 I'll take it I'll take
it was it a new record
um probably pretty close
pretty close my friend plays the
recorder better we already resolved this
this uh Arc
character development
my friend plays the recorder better I'd
like to invite your friend to play
recorder together someday
it may be a long time from now
but I would love to challenge your
friend in the Underworld someday someday
in the future when I come to get them
ah Big Ups Too kikito had a big UPS to
rev and Maury's deadbeat in space glad
that you enjoyed the back for blood
collab heck yeah was meant way more fun
than I thought it was going to be yes
I was surprised by how much I love that
game and I will stream my side next time
I really only joined in because it was
like oh we you know we have room for one
more person you want to join Cali and I
was like yeah sure but it ended up being
so fun so I think all of us as a crew
are gonna finish off that game and um
play together
and I'll stream my side next time so
yeah
a big UPS to Cali fans and a Big Ups 2
rev and more is deadbeat in space thank
you very much
801 thank you a Big Ups 2 copy and Big
Ups 2 the one the only Tyler Vaughn
hope you've been doing well Tyler
finally able to catch a stream live
again good luck Cali
thank you for coming appreciate the good
luck I definitely I definitely used it
there was some there was maybe a little
bit of I I did have to learn the game a
bit of skill
a little luck I don't know about I don't
know maybe maybe not but when people say
good luck I get what they mean so I'm
not gonna cry I greatly appreciate I
appreciate the support thank you for
being around Tyler I hope you had a good
time during the Stream
a big of two uh Canyon a big UPS to iori
suichiro thank you
you're a lyric competition that's very
sweet thank you I'll take us to say
thank you
um
um Amir
kazia thank you
a pick up Sedum Slayer Dragon and thank
you pixel art student thank you again
pixel art student for the wonderful
pixel art that you did of me in jumping
jump King streams the best to watch
well-drawn Good Luck Cali by the way I'm
collaborating with at Kevin cow oh yeah
the creator of small AME to create a
Cali jump King game which will be
released soon hope you'll enjoy it we
gotta play it
I will absolutely play that game
whenever you guys finish it a hundred
percent
a Big Ups 2 brain trash congratulations
on the one year
I I hope it continues to be smooth
sailing for you A big UPS too it's got
my success a big Upstate insufficiently
Anonymous thank you very much
yeah
it makes sense you joined the pack for
blood kid given how few streams you've
had in October
yeah it's been there's been a real
drought for content
thanks and sufficiently Anonymous a big
of sedan Sullivan thank you I think it's
too Johnny h and a Big Ups 2 and
sufficiently Anonymous thank you very
much a Big Ups 2 crash override
especially Anonymous says Kelly using
the Memento Mori power to check past
streams
indeed but but only only that one time
it's a look and see which direction I
went
pickups too crash override thank you
very much we have to sell sausage boots
and the Big Ups Too
you ridiculous Chad you
V
mother F wording toy ski
vitoski
how can
I think I had a really big fall
uh and then
vitoski jumps in with the the fat akaspa
no message
what a chad
but you did
thank you be toy ski big freaking Ops
biggest of UPS see you thank you for
celebrating my fall it's uh it did to
help you a little bit
uh was I was a bit down on the dumps but
you know what the thing about this game
is that what I learned eventually is
that you just gotta just gotta keep on
keeping on and take every every second
is a learning opportunity it's a lot
like um
my time here in Holo
yeah anyway thanks a lot you freaking
Chad you
I'll take a big old sip of tea for you I
was gonna say I'll take a big old shot
but you know what
you might want me to take a big old sip
of tea instead
I'm gonna hold that a long note though
that we don't get to decide on that's
going to happen I wonder if I can beat
the record the record that we just did
the stopwatch is out here we go this
one's for V toy ski
hold on foreign
[Music]
that had to have been close though that
had to have been glow
Maybe
I don't know but anyway vitoski thank
you so much for the for the sudden huge
support I didn't know her after that
really big fall
I appreciate you
oh Big Ups Too berserking
heck yeah berserking thank you so much
for the red super chat
thank you f
only
what a chat
though all these messages are pretty
chad-like but I just wanted to
I mean it's just an F I mean yeah I sure
did fall
do a flute endurance stream Cali not a
bad idea
not a bad idea
maybe for my lungs it might be a bad
idea
I gotta be kind of careful I think it's
the Jimmy Two
book
thank you Johnny H big ups and a big UPS
to it messed up brain
Spike
yeah
thank you very much for the Super Chat a
big Upstate evil hero a bf2 is Zach lath
a big obstacle and the biggest to dark
Cinema gaming ah Big Ups Too
a big UPS too
crabby a Big Ups Too Michael C thank you
and Shane Armstrong a big of Suits thank
you
foreign hi Kelly as always you are
awesome if you're thinking of merch
ideas I'd kill for your other outfit's
hat maybe for your birthday I'd wear it
everywhere hang in there and sleep more
that is an actually excellent idea
I'm gonna I'm gonna slide that on over
to J Chad I'm sure that she will be
interested in hearing that because we've
been talking about like different little
merch ideas and stuff like that for
future stuff so
yeah that's a great idea thank you so
much for the suggestion a big UPS to
Eric Gomez
not bad just inexperienced that's that's
a very kind way of looking at it thank
you a big UPS to Michael C thank you
very much times two
oh I I see you're giving thank you
Michael C for the Bennett foddy
commentary that I purposefully ran away
from there are no regrets in life just
lessons Jennifer Aniston oh yes she was
in Just Go With It with Adam Sandler
which we talked about today uh with gura
Big Ups to chop suey 28 and thank you
McLovin
is awesome
do you have any trick-or-treat stories
I'm saving them
I'm saving them yes yes please
anticipate
probably we'll tell some during the
chatting portion of the Halloween
uh celebration together look forward to
it a big episode thank you
a big up some Michael C the pain I feel
now is the happiness I had before that's
the deal
s
a pickup suit take 22.
thank you ryuji big UPS
the tree you guys are doing a talk show
we are talking about a podcast
a big up suit Devin Dean thank you the
broom heck yeah
lizard wizard pickups to you what's this
old trick our DM used to spark the light
of dming inside of players have a PC
player character control DM a dream
sequence their character is having with
other player characters no consequences
weird results 100 guaranteed that's
actually that seems like it'd work
ha maybe that's how we yeah that is how
we light the fire see who we can get
interested in it
a big UPS to Mr spacebar thank you very
much have I tried any other Storyteller
world of Darkness games or other tgrpgs
in general
oh let's see
um
the only other game that I either
participated in or ran was uh Geist the
senator
that was a long time ago I forgot a lot
of the rules which made it rough for me
to include some of the I really wanted
to include more like Geist stuff in the
last session but
it's like all of the sources all the
resources that my friends and I used
back in the day are all gone not on the
internet anymore so I gotta gotta try
and grab those those PDFs I think you
can purchase them uh on websites online
but um
gotta go grab some of that material
there's a lot those books are huge but
full of like you know great stuff to use
just there's so much you can't possibly
use all of it so you can kind of pick
and choose but
anyway thanks a lot uh Mr spacebar Big
Ups to you
I'd love to try some more stuff in the
future different ttrpgs I really like
kind of one-off style ttrpgs or like
um games that be that can be um
contained within like one book and um
leave a lot of room for a Storyteller to
kind of build on top of so
owned a couple of them back in my my
Reaper school days I don't know what
happened to them I got them off like uh
sale rack
it's like another celebratory
let's see thank you very much Michael C
and a big UPS to donger bread thank you
Michael C again
thank you berserking for the f and a big
episode thank you
they goes to fume aky and a big UPS to
mix latte thank you Bradley and a Big
Ups Too will thank you Elsie Le Pen
sending four CL floor cleaner instead of
Flesh water thank you Marcus manesses
Big Ups all right since you did it I
made one two sting energy drink and gin
50 50 mix tastes pretty good eh Marcus
Meneses
apparently it's not great
but I'm gonna regret this later but I'm
drinking with you Kelly I'm at peace
with you and bang for now
be careful out there Marcus Meneses a
video of satiety and Cafe legal eagle
the real reason she likes this game so
much you challenge it and it does
whatever it wants to despite just like
Cali herself yeah actually Tyson
actually
yeah
you're correct
that is really funny actually if you
think about it yes my best rival this
game Rivals me itself
I'll pick up stuff Fireheart 47 and a
Big Ups 2 green go thank you
Big Ups 2 insufficiently Anonymous and a
bagels to Nick s makeups to axios thank
you am I gonna play Elden ring next year
I will play it um I won't be able to do
it on stream but I will play it yes I'm
very much looking forward to it I hope
you guys will enjoy it as well
it goes to Brutus salad thank you jotita
heck yeah a big UPS to Ally a big UPS to
sin [\h__\h]
thank you axios my cat says hi deadbeats
hello axiosis cat
a Big Ups 2 Ren Chong
Michael C last one don't hate the player
hit the game iced tea that one hit the
hardest honestly
that's pretty cool you're building a
ttrpg that's neat designing 10 000 years
plus years of History a lot of stuff but
will allow DMS to build off rather than
being strict yeah that sounds good I
kind of like ones like that I prefer um
like RP in general but also kind of it's
good to have like a rule set in place
for sure because then you know it's a
game so you should have that but I kind
of like when there's more role play
involved than just playing characters
you know
yeah the magic about that I don't know
all right let's see
[Music]
let me go to big Ops 2. Mr Simple Thank
You My Chemical Romance you changed your
name don't hate the player I hate the
Crow from me
thank you very much too
marzura Vel
thank you for the red super chat
merzeravel heck yeah glad to see you're
enjoying having fun glad to see you're
still determined to complete jump King
didn't think you'd pick it back up again
after the first stream but man did you
prove me wrong good luck you are almost
maybe halfway there
it feels nice to read now knowing that I
didn't I wouldn't let you down on
mercerivel we did it
we did it we beat the game
well thank you for continuing to watch
though big ups and I appreciate you
thank you everyone who sent me some love
while I went to wash my hands I think
it's too Lahar and a big UPS to crayon
can crayon Cannon thank you hey hey hey
smoke
greed every day
hey dog every time Kelly overshoots a
jump when they have to fire holder one
thank you Big Ups 2 low vay love and
thank you crayon Cannon yeah Crown was
such a jam Hear lyrics are on point as
per the usual of course and this
uplifting feeling instrumentals had this
nostalgic funky feel that reminded me of
Summer Nights With Friends
I totally get those vibes too and what's
funny is that it's called crown and we
have a crown
we got a crown today guys we got a crown
as the jump King jump Queen jump King
jump Queen
we got a crown and crown came out today
very funny funny coincidence it must be
faint it can't be anything but fate
thank you so much crayon Cannon and a
big extra draconic insight draconic
inside
thank you so much for the red super chat
draconic draconic says that was
fantastic I absolutely loved it I'm
going to be looping this a ton I can
already tell you and boogievox killed it
on this Cali well done thank you for the
many emojis
Big Ups to you draconic thank you for
enjoying it I'm happy that you'll be
able to Loop it and have fun with it and
um yeah
yeah
thank you so much I'm happy that you are
a fan and there's still another one
there's still one more to come
one more to come so please look forward
to that as well draconic Big Ups to you
and a pickups to berserking thank you
very much
happy that you enjoyed the song
um and hopefully there will be subtitles
soon um because I know that the song got
translated I know that it did I just
don't think that the subs got in there
in time they've been really busy so but
that's why you should check back later
to see English subtitles there will
definitely be English subtitles on the
one on my channel though so be sure to
turn them on if you want to know what
they're saying uh yeah
at that time oh big up stew berserking
and a big up to jpr sinusar thank you
very much dry Stan and big hubs too the
one the only crazy Chad Franklin
the bully Hunter
again Franklin you're crazy
this Franklin can't be stopped
no stopping this bully Hunter
it'll be released on your channel yes
oh
Franklin says that was incredible can't
wait to listen to it over and over again
in the coming weeks yay please enjoy it
continue to enjoy it Franklin big
freaking UPS big freaking Ops
heck yeah my dude
thank you for being so supportive of all
the stuff I put out
whether it be streams or songs I
appreciate you man
warms my heart
well I should take a little sip of tea
excuse me
oh
we put our hearts and souls into that
song and uh it's a special song for us
because
there are a lot of You Know lyrics that
point back to our our long friendship
with each other
um and it's it's really cool
it's just neat to make it with them so
um a Big Ups Too the shadow pencil I
think it's the g c k e and the Big Ups
to Marcus manesses thank you guys for
enjoying the song feels like a perfect
follow-up to follow up to end of a life
and a super uplifting yay please enjoy
the one on my channel is very different
from end of a life but it's like
you'll have you'll have to wait and see
um
happy Halloween and happy Halloween
yeah
such a great song Thank you for enjoying
it
happy Halloween guys Happy Halloween I'm
taking a sip
I'm taking a sip
when is that
coming out day after tomorrow but
tomorrow night actually
um cover of the baddest
by KDA
oh
my Knox
happy Halloween hope you're having a
good one
hi Kelly how are you I'm great thanks
guys
excited for it yes please anticipate
look forward to it lots of music
happening guys
is there going to be a New Year's stream
need to plan my holiday
um yeah I'll do something to celebrate
New Year's and I'll also do something to
celebrate the holidays but I am going on
vacation for actual Christmas so um
yeah
yeah Halloween is skeleton season
exactly which is why it's one of my
faves
yeah very hyped
hey you're gonna kill us with all the
hype lots of stuff going on
Atta
you heard it thank you yeah it's been a
while since I had a little Christmas
vacation so didn't have one last year
actually like not not a real one because
you know it's hard to like travel around
and go on vacation especially back then
but things are kind of you know getting
a little better so
this we'll still do something fun to
celebrate the holidays it's just it
won't be on the date or even close to it
really but but that's fine we'll still
have a little celebration together so
don't you guys worry
let's see I got a big UPS too we're on
one two seven thank you like a nice
counter perspective of sorts to end of a
life yeah I can see that for sure
that's a nice way of looking at it
actually
we got a big Ups 2 Julius tops big ups
and a big UPS to Mr Simple okay goes to
Max Maxwell thank you
randomly tuned in right on your verse
LOL what are the chances of Big Ups 2
salary man thank you very much it's
gotten cold recently hope you're doing
well personally my health tends to dive
during these months I prefer cold over
hot weather good luck getting the Babe
need to catch up with your streams too
thank you salary man big ups and you
stay warm too okay
videos to the Mario addicts and the Big
Ups to Eric C and take us to the Booty
Call of Cthulhu I still love that name
it's just kind of I don't know it's
smart
hey pick up the technical at 7336 and
the Big Ups to a cure a bag of said
Georgie thank you and the biggest
and MOG I bought this game an hour ago
and at one point we were on the same
screen at the sewers
ah yes
bonding through suffering a big UPS to
Vicky thank you very much you're so
talented I find that amazingly pursued
that talent and have shared your amazing
music with us thank you for listening
Vicky I've always found you and Coco to
be inspirational to me because of all
the things you accomplished thank you
heart emoji I'm just trying to you know
do my thing and also follow my senpai's
advice and try new things
um I don't try as many new things as I'd
like to to be completely honest but I
still feel like um I'm getting more
comfortable streaming and trying other
things that aren't within my comfort
zone I feel like you know it's those
little victories right so yeah Big Ups
to my senpai
yeah I'll keep doing my best
thank you very much Vicky and a big of
the cow slip poetry heck yeah
gotta keep my favorite DM her do phrase
for another great episode of Myth
Breakers thank you for enjoying thank
you thank you I'm still shaking off some
of that DM rust but
we're getting there slowly by slowly
that last episode was a bit of a mind
breaker I had written down how I was
going to explain the situation to them
but I messed up on one part I like
accidentally switched a description of
something with another thing
um that made it kind of confusing and it
was like ah but I also hadn't slept
I do that to myself though it's my
responsibility to make sure I'm sleeping
you know
we got a big Ups 2 KH or sorry k
has been squared heck yeah and a big UPS
too let's see what this name is I want
to read this I can't I can't read it but
I'm gonna translate it
let me make sure it's okay first
it's in Korean
no novu
you can do it thank you very much for
the Super Chat Big Ups
we got a big UPS to water thank you I
recommend this really good motivating
song while you play It's called Crown by
Boogie box featuring Maury Calliope you
give it a listen maybe I'll give you a
cut through this part we did get the
crown though thankfully
heck yeah
wow nine hours and it will continue
until we read these supers I think it's
to Master Chief five six oh six eight
thank you
heck yeah glad you're just here Reviving
big up stupid Mr smoofington and a big
UPS to akina 4869 glad you like the
music it goes to berserking and a big
UPS to potato Sensei we also got a big
Ups 2 Mickey p
thank you as always for the support
Mickey P really appreciate that red
Super Chat Nikki P says how is everyone
doing holding up fine we made it Mickey
we did it
we did it we got the Babe Mickey
[Music]
we got the babe
hope you get a chance to see it even if
you gotta catch the VOD
um or if you're here now thank you for
sticking around but
yeah I appreciate you dropping by Mickey
p a big of Centennial at 7336 thank you
very much robe a big UPS to Young Astro
sad boy Enthusiast that goes to Kevin
Stevens uh thank you very much for
making that game heck yeah
she wasn't smoking or on fire though
yeah good point I was a little
disappointed in that but you know what
we still have new babe plus don't we
heck yeah a big UPS too
let's see Titan kfp legal eagle and to
pick up the Soccer Academy
Sakura akemi
thank you so much Sakura akemi for the
red super chat no message
what a chad
heck yeah appreciate the heck out of you
Sakura kemi
H it wasn't like she wasn't the crow
either
it's fine the babe was still pretty cute
Big Ups 2 Fire holder one and thank you
tentacles 7336 they up to page guy 300
Big Ups Dallas pen and thank you Wolfie
Chan
Wolfie Chan
thank you so much Wolfie Chan for the
red super chat no message what a
chip appreciate you Wolfie Chan
the next three hard games beaten by you
Cali next is Doom
do maternal next you guys we're beating
games left and right left and right I'll
do my best I'll do my best
and if it goes to Dr Zilla thank you
Nick finlinson
please be joking was so genuine
a big UPS to
s17b32 heck yeah a big UPS to berserking
thank you bunny game and a big up to
Charles thank you Seth hath and in Vegas
to berserking heck yeah and a big UPS do
insufficiently Anonymous
consider it tamezi over Minesweeper of
playing because becomes a serious
thought it's the same game but actually
good puzzles here
kametsi I haven't heard of that before
but okay cool
same game but actually good puzzles that
start easy instead of constantly getting
screwed over by 50 50s yeah that is a
Minesweeper thing huh
time to take Doom out hmm
let's go I'm excited then we can play
Earthbound I think up to Tony bones
thank you and it pickups to J.M Henry
thank you very much arnofo Mendes just
listen to Crown you a fra and she did
awesome thank you very much our nofo
Mendes more to come
a pickups too Joelle joelera thank you
almost at the final checkpoint lilies
hope because there are no fa Mendes and
thank you Crimson nine five seven thank
you Sebastian and a big UPS to
berserking thank you ghoulie XX and the
Big Ups Too
Super Boy
congratulations on 10 million views for
King with gura thank you for the
congrats a big UPS to nightmare King
thank you jprs NSR and a big of two
reworks thank you
Max Maxwell thank you ephemeral memory
my biggest jpr snsr and a big
obstetriconic Insight thank you bailing
Baker and the Big Ups to Alex at goeli I
was thinking your last name was maybe
like the pasta that um
that Ollie was talking about I was
trying not to say it because she kept
saying Coley akoli and I was like a
koili Alex that's a deadbeat
big ups and thanks for the hype sticker
the metsy's on sale on Steam right now
for a ludicrously low price well then it
would be a crime to not grab it
you have Big Ups Too a cure thank you
and sufficiently Anonymous pickups to
you welcome to the cathedral your new
home and you're safe here you will come
to know it very well in the coming hours
Big Ups to the cathedral and the taco
demons that live there Big Ups to Marcus
monesseness and the Frog spawned one
heck yeah it goes to vampiric otaku and
a big of the Sharko heck yeah because
the Talisman G1 thank you very much
tell as Benji once as in my opinion
horror is a lot like spicy food yet
something way above your tolerance level
and then it becomes a craving
ah yes
actually yeah though that's how I was
with spicy noodles like spicy clear
noodles I have I am really into spicy
clear noodles a big UPS too
Nine Cats
thank you Nine Cats as always really
appreciate the red super chat today left
for a workout around the time the stream
started and was sad and missed I'd
missed it only to come back to the
stream still ongoing damn looking
forward to the rest of the stream and
all the upcoming music coming from you
thank you Nine Cats heck yeah
hope you had a nice time at the gym or
rather working out I guess it doesn't
need to be at the gym but
hope you had a good workout hope you got
those gains keep doing your best nine
cats and I hope you still uh had fun and
enjoyed what you did get to see
a Big Ups 2 Barrel rack thank you very
much a big UPS to Road Forks you hi girl
big UPS to ordinary and thank you Mrs
Castle Abby thank you very much megumi
carrot
let's see a big Ups Too me
espos
oh
robotics
keep going cat lady thank you doing my
best the upstairs gum is success thank
you it goes to sogeki and a big of
student nimnam thank you very much
see
what was the first game that made you
think oh damn I am really enjoying
playing video games I'll Crash Bandicoot
but that's pretty obvious I think it was
one of my first ones thank you
zekinator77 who says thank you very much
Eldon Dan heck yeah they have to Devout
blade and the big up stew
um oh
oh something Chad you can so pug dad and
shark
motivated makeups to sithiran thank you
very much
just got to believe in yourself and if
you can't do that believe in the gura
that believes in you
she did stick around for a long time and
threw a lot of Milestones always cool to
have for a round everyone who came was
just such a freaking treasure I think up
to j s thank you very much because the
Steven favorite season favorite
trick-or-treat candy and favorite soups
I'm gonna be really biased to the season
and say pumpkin soup right now because
it's all I can think about because I'm
gonna be making some pumpkin soup for
Halloween so I'm like yes
ah anything that has potatoes
um probably yeah for Soups and then
trick or treat candy
hmm
I like chocolate but I'm also a big like
fan of gummy stuff as well pumpkin soup
sounds delicious it's great I gotta try
that I recommend
all the topics girl brought up
Unforgettable
yeah
she knows she knows how to take the
conversation in a fun Direction
Reese's Peanut Butter Cups yeah those
are really good I bought some when I
went back to Overworld in America I'm
all out of them now though it's too bad
also like uh like Warheads I don't know
maybe I do just like to suffer but I
have some fun with those as well
see pickups to ryco3 thank you very much
a bit about Top Gear anyway meme after
one of the presenters nearly got killed
in a stunt and later recovered the three
jokingly made a vow that if one of them
really were to die during the filming
they would announce it on the show then
say so anyway
oh God
sounds pretty silly
I like the way that bay uh described
that show though made me interested in
it best trick-or-treat candy is Apples
but you use onions instead of apples so
it's a trick I get it
nice
never thought of it that way
see a big Ups 2 flurry bolt and a big
UPS to Prince rock girl with the
cultured candy taste thank you jpr
sinasauruses ping pong thank you Saku
and a big up stew Taco number 3476.
appreciate the red super chat takodachi
slash deadbeat thank you have ever
played medieval I've heard of that
before
you play a skeleton yeah yeah I know
what this is going around defeating evil
creatures Cali might like it
I'm curious because I've seen that but
I've seen that skeleton character
Sir Daniel yeah yeah Sir Daniel that was
the name yeah I've seen a little bit
about this game always down to play a
cool skeleton
yeah that's an old PS1 game
cool
heck yeah
best OG dead Pete the original deadbeats
from the same era as crash great
platformer
oh I'm interested now
hold on
I want to see what this game looks like
ah yeah yeah it's like a yeah I've seen
this before
this is cool same era as crash huh
what a cool looking skeleton
let's see oh Big Ups to kikito thank you
very much
what a question for girl
yeah I can't wait to go back and listen
to All of gura's answers there's a PS4
remake if I remember correctly me oh
heck yeah
a pickups to AZN
four
Rife
thank you very much
pickups too Holo night and the Big Ups 2
diminishes biggest road Force you thank
you very much
Maury is cute streamer she has pink hair
and big personalities would watch again
three stars they give her the three
stars what a generous review
thank you JS and a Big Ups Too Prince
rock thank you so much gura
a pickups to a dressil Cali is pink gura
is blue Charlie stank is sweet like Old
Spice Sandalwood
what a poem
what was what did Kara stable
I'm so curious but I gotta go find out
for myself Taylor's shot
gosh you deadbeat so creative
my creative little Deadbeats
Dorito stop skipping leg day Cali says
JS no
no maybe I want to look like a Dorito
Big Ups Too no
tosa thank you for the cultured content
glad I'm alive
it always turns cultured when girls
involved pickups to Tony bones thank you
very much
don't mess with the natural order gotcha
well we're dealt we're dealt with the
hand that we're dealt when we are born
into this planet
so it is what it is hey grass is always
greener on the other side you know
a big UPS do berserking thank you very
much
three sizes of three million Subs
I'll think about it big UPS to LC Le Pen
I can't guarantee a serious answer
though
Ponder
Big Ups do need more DACA a Big Ups Too
a dog or bread and a big UPS two
notoriously hard to pronounce I've
watched the stream from the very
beginning I like the cultured subversion
into the form of a plywood cat shark
yeah plank girl big UPS to Marcus
Meneses thank you very much a very
informative summer Mori discussion
thank you for listening in
I think it's defrudo thank you very much
a gorgeous ornate hourglass ooh that one
would find in a temple fit for a queen
filled with the Sands of beautiful music
with the booty the don't quit
yes yeah the poem went something like
that
wow what a great Recreation Frido
I got a good laugh out of it it was
pretty funny
Big Ups to Abraham thank you very much
this is me or is it funny they're
talking about food and choir music it's
in the background the choir music is too
good
the choir music in the background of
anything that girl and I were talking
about at that part was
uh just really it was it was something
pickups tawalu PG cubed thank you very
much looking forward to catching up on
the VOD later please enjoy the climb
they go to the broom thank you very much
and a big UPS the road Forks you it's
just fish spam oh yeah that's right
Maybe
the pickups too
it really added to the conversation I
thought so as well
did you know that Sora from Kingdom
Hearts is finally in Super Smash Bros
ultimate I saw that I saw 50 of people
extremely excited and 50 of people uh
Angry enough to punch a hole in the wall
uh there was no in between actually on
my Twitter feed
um a big UPS too
our boy
wait for it
shrugging emoji
thank you so much our boy not gonna lie
that white stuff inside the male fish
tastes okay you've tasted uh shirako
before
well everyone's got a different opinion
I didn't think it tasted bad either but
it's not for me if I think about what it
is when I eat it it's bad
it's bad
I was neither of those people that's
pretty rare then rave
because um
my my Twitter feed was very very uh
divided
let's see anyway don't eat too much
shirako our boy waited for a striking
Emoji thank you so much for the support
though appreciate the heck out of you as
always our boy
a Big Ups 2 our Thane
dartiren thank you
a big ass too
jotita
who also took a crack at this poem thing
see what jyotsita got for us
pink hair that sways in the wind like
Sakura blossoms that follow in the
spring eyes red like passionate Flames
that hypnotize those who look into them
oh how your beauty blinds me and causes
me to admire how such a human can exist
that booty stank though
yeah it went a little something like
that
there it is
well done
wow what what a memory
such a way with words
killing it with the pen please consider
a future in poetry
very well done a nice Recreation I like
it
a biggest
Channel I think of Stewart reeux thank
you
an alligator omelette it was God tier I
can totally see that being sold in like
Oklahoma or something I have been there
before
but pickups to zekanator77 thank you
very much
it's a shadow pencil
my cheeks hurt yeah you and me too you
and me both
thank you very much for the wand I just
want to donate some money bro
thank you very much I bet I can
translate this too
Young
I really [\h__\h] that up thank you very
much for the Super Chat a big of two
cheeky m s h t s
enlightened not so Liker more Calliope I
mean not that was good guys listen thank
you Dr Zilla Big Ups glad that you're
enjoying the stream so much uh even
though jump King is over we're still
gonna do DLC so there's more chances for
people to come in and hang out
a big of two gut a big UPS to a PSI
chaos or Psy chaos and a big UPS to
relevance 91 heck yeah
jinxes aren't real except gurus here and
gurus and hers are real and painful good
for Content though
heck yeah
a big UPS to song Hoon thank you very
much big ups and nice to meet you uh Big
Ups Too marsura Vel
thank you again marzuravel appreciate it
huge Ops to you hath thou Fallen nay I
jest lest thou desire to fall and they
banished thy thought thou imagine Castle
emoji
you have a way with words too Martha
Ravel thank you very much
I appreciate the heck out of you
appreciate the red super chat and the
it's not really like a poem but I do
appreciate the castle speak considering
this is Jump King
does give me a nice little chuckle deep
inside a big UPS to Mr John Carlton
thank you we already have a hot baby
here wonder what will be at the top
um a dude with really really thick
jumping thighs thank you very much
Double L and a big UPS two Alex
sure knob
Alex Journal
thank you so much for the red super chat
Alex no message
what a chad
as always Alex with these chat like
super chats just out of nowhere
appreciate the heck out of you man thank
you
oh Big Ups Too Gary with a capital four
thank you pick up sasaku and a big UPS
to drunken juice thank you Nacho
Miss
thank you very much to Mr pie thank you
you and Kiara help me the most thank you
it's the best thing I could ever wish
for oh Mr pie hope you're doing well my
dude
oh Big Ups to Celery Man thank you very
much thank you technical 7336 and a Big
Ups Too
heck yeah thank you Shadow pencil and
the Big Ups Too Cali is rabbit
oh I'm in trouble I saw you and Kiara
Minecraft collab that you developed a
taste for rabbit meat
should I be concerned
not if your Cali's rabbit though not if
you're my rabbit if you're my rabbit you
don't gotta worry come on I wouldn't
roast my own rabbit you silly
you're silly
no it's fine I was mostly eating The
Roasted Chicken anyway so
don't you worry nothing to worry about
nothing to worry about at all
thank you very much for the red super
chat
you punched your cat and authorized
Kiara to kill your diet did not
authorize Kiara to kill my dog that is
not true I said if you need if you need
to not be nice to the dog that is that
is okay but that did not mean you may
punch my dog
now punching my cat was an accident I
wanted to give the cat a piece of salmon
didn't know how the Minecraft controls
worked kind of slapped the cat in the
face with the salmon but it was fine
because the cat ate the salmon later so
it's all good okay I love my pets that's
all I'm gonna say a big UPS too
Joseph thank you
hey Callie I was one who started the
game with you at the beginning of the
session just wanted to say that I made
it to the top just now babe is indeed
smoking hot good luck Cali and you can
do it woot is that a fact
congratulations you're really quick a
big UPS to our nofa Mendes thank you and
a big UPS to Devin a Big Ups 2 a c x
thank you very much
have you eaten anything since streaming
take care of yourself yeah yeah I got
dinner no worries guys a big UPS to Saku
and a big UPS to elsila pen thank you
you're so close I know you can do it I
did my best thank you TBC Studios and
zekanator77 a big up to Dragonic insight
and a big UPS to Lord Ashton the
unbanked thank you very much Duke Von
distant let's go Cali you got this
let's see uh Big Ups Too insufficiently
Anonymous in sad news you're no longer
the fourth most subscribed YouTuber what
no
my number four spot I hope you can make
something of the constellation of being
the third most
is that really is that something that
happened
I'm incredibly honored
uh if that is true I I am incredibly
honored thank you
um
wow
oh I'm very happy thank you for the
support everyone
um everyone works really really hard
um in in Holo and as V tubers in general
so I'm just uh very humbled by you guys
just doing my best uh Trucking along
here
so um thank you
I wish everybody uh success so
we you can only just uh do our best but
um I'm not gonna I'm not gonna make it
weird I'm just gonna say thank you
thank you for the support everyone uh
let's keep having fun together making
music doing streams together
um
this is like uh yeah the best thing
that's uh ever happened to me yeah
I have like a weird way of saying it
sometimes
because I'm
I'm just like I'm really shy and
embarrassed person but
but I do appreciate the heck out of you
guys
thank you
um if if I was to if I was to be for
again it would be cool
I love the number
the number four is great though listen
always keep it in your heart Big Ups to
you guys thank you for the huge support
look at all those hearts
can't do it without you guys thank you
heck yeah
ah
all these big smiles and celebrations
lately
wow
um a big UPS to jprs NSR we never
doubted you Cali you got this thank you
rokenji you can do it pick up satanical
at 7336 so close can feel the air
heating up because how of how close we
are to the hot babe go Cali go
thank you very much Dean Richards whoo
wow you're super chill about this I
would have raged and thrown my
controller by now see um I might have uh
if the cathedral wasn't uh so well
fortified
that probably would have happened
a Big Ups 2 you should have seen heck
yeah what if the real sewers with the
drinks we made along the way
[Applause]
you just fall all the way back to the
sewers and the smell that wafts up is
that of vanilla vodka and bang
a Big Ups 2 wada thank you thank you
torellian
I am experiencing critical levels of
palm spaghetti just for watching this
thank you very much zekanator77 a Big
Ups 2 jpr Cinestar and duck em duck
thank you Dr Zilla 337 Nick finlinson
somehow that's even worse
yeah somehow
um yeah
yeah even I'm afraid of Patrick please
no more now I'm gonna pour it out I
didn't even make a ton of it so it's
fine but bang is not for me I don't
think the gamer drink is fine the
powdery one even the one that has quote
unquote energy and it isn't so bad
um it doesn't make me buzz like a banged
doesn't make me vibrate a pickups to
pretty's rock go Mori go
thank you vasia Patrol go more you're
the best
friend he's Rock going to the top baby
Road Forks you go more you go I believe
then I go at 7336 heck yeah final Dash
let's go thank you very much
thank you
pick up the Silver Shadow and a big up
suit Kina 4869 to take some rest to get
some sleep I'm worried I will don't
worry I'll sleep well I will sleep well
tonight a big UPS to okay composite the
Epic background music kick so much ass
it made my morning alarm highly
recommended I do really like it that bgm
was so good but I was like this is a
distraction because this background
music rocks I love that it's like
like the the background music kicks in
really hard and it's like kind of louder
and more in your face than the rest of
the bgm because it's like the final test
you know you ought to be able to make it
past with some bgm in the background
right
yeah pure instinct
I really liked that part
instinctive it all was just it was great
I'm so sick
oh Big Ups Too Gareth Thompson and the
Big Ups to Bubba simp thank you very
much I know the whole your boy isn't
good at games thing is a meme but your
perseverance and drive is truly amazing
I was rooting for you during the
bloodstain playthrough and all I can say
is you got this thank you bubba simp
yeah I know it's I know it's a meme but
you did incredibly well
my five tries
yeah the sour part yeah I mean if you
give me something based on pure Instinct
I'll do my best also games of willpower
I think
um I have I have a lot of sheer
willpower uh in general
um so I think it's like a slight Edge I
might have like a slight Edge on that
but that's about it but it carries you a
long way guys sometimes it carries you a
long way if you've got sheer Power of
Will concentrated power of will as some
may say
boy is good at games just needs practice
that's that's a nice way of thinking it
nice way of thinking about it thank you
Kyle Ember and a big UPS to lushin thank
you says congrats and this is where it
begins
a big UPS to wada and thank you very
much Road Forks you
for that red Super Chat huge UPS to you
Road Forks you thank you so much for the
support I knew you could do it in all
caps
and because you knew I could do it I
knew I could do it too
thank you so much roadworks you
thank you thank you
blushing it's not just the vodka
we got a big UPS too
Freddy
Rock
thank you pretties Rock for the pet
vet
heck yeah for the many fours
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you
thank you for the fat
big freaking UPS
big
Bernie's Rock Says
you are jump King hold on
you I forgot the effect sorry I'm very
happy right now
you are jump King
thanks for the incredible stream the new
song with Boogie box and also to the
ladies jumping in to keep you company
it's been a pleasure watching you
improve and overcome another challenge
sasu
go I'm sorry that was a weird that was
like an odd guy that I just did Sasuke
my Oshie heart emoji thank you pretties
Rock whoa heck yo no sorry my oh my
charm
[Music]
I always appreciate your continued
support praise Rock whoa
you have you have been here for a long
long time watching the street
Big Ups to you for sticking through it
along with me my my confetti is Frozen
but thank you for staying till the end
thank you for cheering for me till the
end Prince Rock I'm holding out a long
note for you are you ready let's see if
we can beat our record
let's do it
[Music]
I almost lost it to your B emoji
Bernie's Rock I I see those bees
are I could see those bees
I see them
the lungs
the lungs on this Reef
the lungs on that Reaper though
it's tradition that is true
the bee has become a tradition at this
point
I I kept it I kept it moving
thank you for the laughs and thank you
very much for the red super chat for his
rock also glad that you like the Boogie
box song we still got another before I
do it but yeah
thanks thanks for tuning in to the
Stream
I know I still have effects on
thank you for tuning in as always
printing Israel I hope you're doing well
hope you have a good one get some rest
after this heck yeah oh Big Ups Too
Gareth Thompson thank you Zeta 24.
you guys are so sweet with the
congratulations thank you oh
I know I've been doing this a while but
I did not expect I did not expect uh the
reaction to me getting the babe
um you guys went wild thank you
thank you so much for cheering for me as
I got that babe
heck yeah
I think it's to Zeta 24 and a pickups to
joera
thank you Tony bones you did it Maury
I think up to the Frog spawned one
the Legends were true so babe
thank you edgy sketchy I had a big UPS
too tentacled seven three three six
big freaking UPS to you tentacled
congrats on making it to the very top
we're once again back to the Mountaintop
time flies by so fast when it's so chill
and fun also glad we get another chill
chatting with friends while nailing
jumps love watching those fun chats
thank you tentacles heck yeah I
appreciate the red super there will be
more of them
there will be more of them
um whether it be jump king or other
games that have kind of like a a grindy
sort of feel to them
you can find me in VC
100 percent
I'm glad that it turned into something
like that and also cool podcasts that me
uh me and some of the others are gonna
do hope you look forward to it something
so cool was it was born out of that and
um
yeah
it's really nice I'm glad you guys are
enjoying them we're happy to just you
know chat your ears off all day if you
guys are willing to lend near so yeah
a big UPS to
mapler9021 great work Cali let's go
thank you zxy 101 let's freaking go
thank you I think it's tagaruda panzor
let's go
Azure 604 thank you very much
draconic insides
thank you so much
draconic Insight I didn't mean to turn
on the hard tune it chose to go on by
itself draconic inside thank you for the
red super chat jump King
more like jump Empress well done Cali
never died you could do it your
determination and willpower is a
constant inspiration for all of us
congratulations
thank you draconic
Big Ups to huge conic
jumpers
jump press jump empress
oh
sweet I like that jump empress
very nice
thank you for sticking around uh for the
stream thank you for cheering for me as
always
and a big UPS too nigodam thank you Nico
damn you did it Crown thank you for the
crown
wow what a nice ground
cute crown emoji
a second I gotta check something
we got a big up suit TBC studios Okay is
a Pro Gamer thank you very much donger
bread oh
mountains Quake before him and the hills
melt away the Earth trembles at his
presence the world and all who live in
it it's the jump King with those those
thighs thickest tree trunks the biggest
ghost machine thank you let's go thank
you Flack armor and a big UPS to master
xylophone hope you're well Master
xylophone you did it pickups to V dragon
three four eight you did it
uh pickups too
rossiferous
thank you for the red super chat for
sephorus
thank you for the Aqua Spa all hail the
jump King baby Hail to the King baby
this little Evil Dead reference we
watched those movies this month
hey thank you so much brocephus for
stopping by thank you for the support
thank you for saying hello thank you for
watching uh the grand Victory appreciate
you
mountains crumble and Hills melt but
that booty stank got me tripping
not some things never change
All Hail to the jump King
Cal you're still streaming went to bed
when you started and went to work and
here you are yeah it's been a while huh
almost 10 hours
fish but a fun 10 hours they've all been
so
a big UPS too kudosa thank you
thank you Argent tonight and a big UPS
to Mint Stone a big of two armor and a
big Up's too big
thank you for the congratulations and
the many emojis thank you jpr snsr and a
big UPS to Alex
thank you Dr Zilla 337 Nick finlinson
and the Big Ups to symptom
thank you robe here's your babe bucks
congratulations a big UPS to yellow rice
thank you Evan and a big up to chewy
Dewey a big UPS to duck em duck thank
you
pickups to quiet use and thank you
kikito uh Big Ups Too
Kyle Amber
thank you so much Kyle Ember for the red
super chat you did it heck yeah
congratulations you're becoming quite a
very enduring gamer Cali proud of you
thank you
thank you Kyle Ember uh it's fun and
it's a lot more fun with a combination
of people to talk with and a new gaming
chair that isn't a gaming chair it's a
good it's a good chair a good decent
chair that helps me with endurance
streams I'm finding that they're much
easier to do with a good with a really
good chair
I didn't know if there was going to be a
difference but I'm really seeing it
anyway thanks for coming along for the
ride Kyle Amber Big Ups to you
heck yeah
chair for a gamer
been watching the stream since the
beginning and I got a lot of stuff done
with you LMAO Big Ups to you Rocky hope
it's been a productive day for you
hope you have a happy dream after
playing this crazy game I will thank you
oh my God I love you all subscribe
goodbye tomorrow I'm a big lazy bone
today it's okay welcome day fan
Big Ups to you
they make gaming chairs too I'm not
surprised
new babe plus when
um let's see
let's see what did I want to do I need
to finish do maternal first
um I'll probably do it
um
I don't want to make any promises
um I'd like to do it within the year but
we'll see because I love me some Junkie
this game has been a blast this this
game has been a blast I can promise that
I will do it but I won't I won't say one
um I want to focus on do maternal first
and also put a lot of time into
Earthbound as well that's very important
to me so make sure we get that done as
well I'm very excited about EarthBound
see thank you very much for the for the
TWD you did it thank you
a pickups too bin and a big up to Jorge
Leon congratulations thank you crayon
can and you f wording did it and a Big
Ups Too
serotonin thank you let's go Cali thank
you Marcus manesses Rejoice deadbeats we
believed you did it you got the hot babe
you conquered the tower and you are now
the jump King a big obstacleappa ghost
now do it again
thank you Michael C
pickups to you you did it Cali you
persevered in the face of defeat and
came out on the other end as the jump
king with a smoking hot babe under your
arm so glad to have you watched to have
watched you achieve this feat
congratulations sorry if the quotes were
annoying no no no no Michael C no
worries at all about uh infinity less
times annoying than than benefit you are
all good rather inspirational actually
don't don't you worry
a Big Ups 2 let him and a Big Ups 2
Talisman G1
talisman
G1
heck yeah Talisman G1 Who says let's go
what a chad
thanks for being here to cheer for me
Talisman G1 hope you had a good time
hope it wasn't too stressful for you not
too Palm spaghetti yeah
when I started watching your stream it
was noon over here and now we are
already night and the Moon is quite
beautiful in honor of the chump empress
wow nice imagery
a big UPS to Art of Elliot the big goes
to pk5 ire thank you Alona and a big UPS
to Omni shred a big UPS to Space Cowboy
thank you for the Podge punch punch
Space Cowboy Big Ups to kaija Spartan
you made it Mori so proud I'm at it
though thank you very much kaija Spartan
oh Big Ups Too our boy wait for it
shrugging emoji
Who says let's go
what a chad
nice one nice one our boy thank you so
much for the big support this stream a
big UPS to Elsie Le Penny says
congratulations thank you hoshizora
congrats and Brutus salad thank you
because the king crestfallen and a big
UPS to sharielle woohoo thank you
Hail to the King baby pickups to Cole
Polo this is nice thank you very much
Varden and a big UPS to Jay Hikari thank
you I was here great job Cali we always
believed Sasuke
thank you very much Berto yes thank you
very much dark Fang yes
thank you Luca umbrio and a big UPS to
dunier
thank you Brian J in a big UPS to mina
mimoto66. thank you very much you mirix
kfp's deadbeat kfp's deadbeat lizard
thank you Franco and a big UPS to pow
Foo thank you very much Leo Sue and a
big up Sue vidalgo Let's Go Gigi Cali
OMG you speak Japanese it's so cute
thank you I'm still learning but thank
you big UPS to salary man thank you
injury to insult in a Big Ups Too Susie
Shido we did it congrats Dad thank you
Hiro Neko Hiro Neko Neko
foreign
let's go congrats thank you Jay sorry g
c k e Big Ups you did it we got the
smoking hop hey we did it with the
deadbeats and Friends along the way
exactly which makes it even better
oh Big Ups Too
Snee
let's go home congrats Cali thank you
for the red super chat
Big Ups to you usually appreciate you
dropping by hope you had fun
oh Big Ups Too
python kfp legal eagle
heck yeah Tyson appreciates ya thank you
so much for the red super chat and for
the watching of I think
most of the stream you were here for a
while thank you Tyson the babe you got
the babe I can't believe it okay I can't
believe it because nothing is more
powerful than you when you set your mind
to it I'm so glad I woke up early to see
this seriously you are terrifying when
you set your mind to something thanks
Titan it's because I'm real stubborn
especially when it comes to myself and
uh and and trying to do things like this
thank you for the support Titan thank
you very much for the cheering thank you
and thank you so much lazy owl what a
very sweet what a very sweet message
thank you
thank you very much Bonnie see same chat
I went to bed when the stream started
now I'm here awake after a lecture dang
I really have been streaming for a while
huh
as ever but I relate to that elbow I I
think it's I think it's pretty relatable
nothing wrong with getting a little
stubborn especially when you want to
prove yourself you know
but with you guys with you guys uh
standing by my side
when did my back dead Beats
it makes it a lot more uh fun and easier
thank you I think it's the moon dog
thank you smoking hot babe it's yours
congrats so DLC won oh very soon
thank you very much Jam Henry a big UPS
tonight 3603 and a big UPS two one cup
thank you one cup sake yeah
pickups too Kina 4869 so proud of you
omit it though thank you a big UPS to
Elliot you
a big UPS do Ange and a big UPS to not
applicable
thank you very much to judge Grumble and
a big UPS to Maxwell the first thank you
nimu 90 what is up a big UPS to Mr J
dog1337 and thank you very much Jabba
let's go James Jackson thank you and a
big UPS too thanks
thank you very much rioting Soul thank
you raven5911 and you must consume
congratulations thank you for the
amazing stream thank you for watching
heck yeah OMG you've been streaming for
10 hours I have
we're almost done though a big of
suspect Jack good effing job Cali
because to Jay Severson and a big UPS to
Palm top tiger
sorry I'm proud of you Cali you really
pulled through thank you big UPS to me I
suppose so
yes epic my boy thank you very much
berserking heck yeah wait the Babe
actually isn't on fire I know false
advertising right how am I supposed to
cook these s'mores looks like I have to
use your wraps again
this cute berserking thank you awesome
job beating the game see you at yomicon
that's right yomakan
very soon very soon Halloween night for
me yeah excited excited excited it's
gonna be a fun time happy that you're
going berserking heck yeah
big up to Jackie Chen a big UPS to Duke
Von distant congrats Cali amazing you
did amazing
it goes to youngboy330 and Astro y h Big
Ups really love these Jump cast streams
I think Ian needs more podcasts like
streams it was fun yeah I think it would
be amazing we'll try to get something
like that popping off we're uh we're
talking now so don't you worry a biggest
two of the few goals and thank you
Stella cavalini let's hacking go thank
you for dropping by Sala cavallini thank
you Sai chaos Big Ups thank you very
much to Serge heck yeah here's some
wedding cash appreciate it
thank you Julius Topps heck yeah your
determination is amazing you got the
babe we did we got the babe we got her
we gotta get the rest of the babes now I
think it's the Silver Shadow thank you
very much Bruno Schubert and a big UPS
to tan ton thank you the Frosted Firefly
and a big UPS to a captain a pickups too
uh p-h-a-t boy STEEZ who says babe in
all caps thank you quib and a big UPS to
Gardon nine two one you could do it
you're awesome thank you so much for the
support a big up to zinrust proud of you
Daddy did a great job and the chats were
very entertaining glad you had a fun
time Big Ups thank you very much missed
Fist and the Big Ups 2 arthane darshiren
thank you very much
congratulations on preserving and
conquering the tower that has brought so
many other Holo members to tears let's f
word and go yeah the tower well the
tower is just pure like uh 100
concentrated power of will uh pure
Instinct driven
yeah I mean I feel like one the only
reason the tower was like not as
difficult for me I feel like it's
because I really kind of uh
figured out a Surefire pattern for the
ice stage which really helped me a lot
in terms of like doing it over and over
again so
yeah
that is a beast went to sleep wake up
still stream
cast either the tower incredibly well
thank you
also the ice hey thank you very much
um I feel like uh it was a good thing
though that the chapel had those floors
there so
was it the nerves Maybe
congrats you rock thank you very much
see
a big episode King far thank you a big
UPS to why am I here nice deadbeat photo
thank you very much marsuravelle
who says nice
thank you so much for the red super chat
thank you for the amazing support the
stream merzeravel you were you were
going nutso I appreciate the heck out of
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you
a big up to toasted and a big UPS to
Eric McDaniels thank you very much Ain
and a Big Ups Too Doomsday 87.
congrats on your Victory glad I was here
to witness it I would have gone insane
ages ago thanks for the red super chat
and thank you very much for the
compliment did my best
did my best we have more babes to
conquer though we gotta we gotta find
and save more babes uh from Burns and
potential fires in castles that's what
we have to do we just have to
so I hope that you'll join me on those
Journeys as well doomsday 87 appreciate
you dropping by uh Big Ups to Wolfie
Chan thank you and family reunion97 Big
Ups to Lord of smug and thank you devote
let's go you did it thank you very much
FRS thank you not English speaker
congratulations Kelly thank you very
much
we totally gone monkey and calipated
it's pretty nuts I will say that was
craziness
but it felt so dang good I knew it would
too so worth it pick up the Lord Ashton
the unblocked thank you common writer
kfp thank you puyo Pio fever and thank
you cayate a big UPS to Mali s like you
jealousy and a big UPS to Prince Rock
never had any doubts my dog amazing job
as always appreciate you as always
pretty rock pretty Rock pretties Rock
I still love that icon
same it's the same icon that art that I
[\h__\h] love
[Music]
maybe one more one more congrats shot
for good measure
apple vodka I gotta save some of it
though for the the Halloween cocktail
stream the vanilla vodka that I bought
for those cocktails for our party uh I
drank a whole bottle of it
uh oh so I had to get another one
ah geez when will I learn
okay now play it again speedrun
um
ah
jump King speed run time huh
um
maybe not
uh let's let's conquer the DLC can you
imagine me trying to speedrun jump King
I mean I could see myself doing it in
like an hour no that's wrong I'm totally
wrong what did we just do 18 maybe next
time I play it I do it in like 14.
I can imagine but that would take so
everything has to be so perfect
um
maybe maybe with another game Crash
Bandicoot maybe jump King uh I don't
know
it's a little victories right it's not
Big Ups to mofuton in thank you and a
big UPS to the guy big UPS to scraps
thank you super born and a big up still
the one the only
hiccups to you bakawagi as always let's
go congrats Cali with your indomitable
will thank you so much for the red super
chat bakowagi big freaking up
appreciate you dropping by to wish me
some luck or wish me some congrats
rather
I appreciate you if you didn't get a
chance to catch up uh catch up the whole
VOD I check I check you out go recommend
it's past two
it's fine though we're gonna finish
everything
thank you so much
oh thank you for joining membership whoa
heck yeah yeah she got the babe my
two-year-old likes your pink hair hello
hi do you like my hair
I'm having a good time
either today in what like eight hours
that included going back down to the
sewers you could do it again for sure in
under five hours without sweating Maybe
would be interesting to see how fast I
could do it again I would like to see
but
uh maybe that's the thing for the future
want to check out those other babes
first you make a good point though
let's see a big Ups 2 Donna cat bus and
thank you R can x a big of two to you
and Tonica Vegas to Adai koala that was
a very smooth final run it was fun
pickup Stick Of Steel and thank you very
much Rudy met Menchaca a big UPS to the
fool let's go thank you Patrick
abrahamasin thank you big UPS to furudo
long live the king thank you xtg32 and
fire the elements Big Ups thank you
skyraven HK and a big UPS to Dan
Sullivan thank you very much
isido
thank you for the red super chat big
freaking up screw the wallet I need to
send this congrats Maury
heck yeah thank you so much takida
I appreciate the support thank you very
much for the congratulations
always uh well I'll always be you know
very very much like uh Thai setsu nisuru
your wallet but
but I do appreciate the big support
thank you so much
heck yeah
all right well Big Ups to deadbeat
number 69 420 Cali
thank you very much debashery Panda Big
Ups to Hayden Sanders a true gamer never
doubted you thank you very much Joe
Lamar 2020 and a Big Ups 2 at gbrt thank
you to a forgettable dream for a super
chat you did amazing new Legend thank
you for coming to support me thank you
very much to ice Sean thank you and
coffee addict Big Ups well done thank
you for the congrats a big UPS to
Cleaves and a big K.C akisu
mom get the camera Ted got the smoking
hot babe wait a minute hey hold on a
minute
well hold on a minute
I do love me some Cali vods please
anticipate them
a Big Ups 2 prey mayor Gigi Cali thank
you and a big up the dingus
thank you to zephathan and the Big Ups
Too dust
what is this dust Club
cool profile picture too thank you so
much for the red super chat congrats on
getting the hot Phoenix
I mean hot babe at the top Cali here's
some money for the honeymoon
yay wedding cash oh you guys are sweet
thank you thank you
thank you for the for the big congrats
sunglasses emoji
you you rascal well thank you very much
dusk Claude for the support hope you
enjoyed
thank you very much lazy as
Contender you're the jump king of all
our hearts a big UPS to whip and a big
UPS two twin tail thank you the castle
part was incredibly fast congratulations
thank you very much it was a blast it
was pretty fun to do actually like a
real challenge
it was fun and I did it pretty fast but
challenging
thank you very much turelian you went
all the way from the fourth stage to the
very end in a single session you can
never say you were bad at video games
again congratulations on the win Kelly
thank you turelian I will say um I am
allowed to I am allowed to say that
about FPS but I'll I'll try I'll tone it
down a little bit
I'll tone it down
I'll tone it down for the future
especially Platformers another stream
can you say something in Russian
I want to hear how you say it uhm
that's that's all I can do
sorry
let's see a big UPS too ocl 73150 thank
you to Z aone
Big Ups 2 Q thank you very much let's go
GG thank you it's 10 o'clock 7336
ah
thank you technical at 7336 thank you
Crim Polo and a big UPS to vampiric
otaku heck yeah Cali you mad woman you
pulled it off
they're my best
Cali's Journey on becoming the game
master
a victims to I am doc Thor thank you
dongerbread a big UPS to David Wynn
thank you Memu thank you iron Souls
thank you jimothy and a big UPS to
Eternal Idol thank you Zephyr Mack thank
you for the many emojis thank you Ed to
sketchy woo thank you and a big UPS too
calby great thank you Arthur thank you
Shannon congrats on getting the babe
thank you very much a big UPS to Joe
gimblet Big Ups to you heck yeah
see
10 hours we're almost done I guess to
Max Maxwell tickets to Cali fans thank
you send sweet and a big UPS to Dolan a
big of two heon xiong thank you very
much for the wand I knew it
I knew it thank you
see who eats faces and a big UPS too
yay congrats pickups to Astro month and
a big UPS to una mama
huh
[Music]
yeah make sure you're taking care of
yourself no worries no worries I did a
lot of gaming today huh
back for blood and jump King it's pretty
nuts up we got ASMR members only
tomorrow so a bit of a break I would say
a Big Ups 2 sawgren and a Big Ups 2 a
cure thank you very much Tomo and a big
UPS to kappamer uh Big Ups to the Booty
Call of Cthulhu and thank you very much
CDR zurion thank you a big UPS to
Stephen McCool or sorry Steve McCool who
says cheers and a Big Ups Too a rock
thank you as always erock for the
support really appreciate that red super
well done Loved These streams these have
been my some of my favorites of yours
and the guests really helped both
entertain and lift your spirits hope you
find something else to do a stream like
this within the future DLC maybe if
you're feeling masochistic yeah
definitely definitely I want to get all
the babes I I want to become a babe
hoarder yeah
it is really nice just getting to like
play a chill game and talk to my friends
and I mean you know jump King is one of
those games where it's like repetitive
enough and like grindy enough that I can
like um
just kind of sit back and talk with
friends if I ever am playing a game kind
of for a long time and realize that it's
uh
it's kind of um
this sort of game where I can sit back
and like repeat stuff a lot or grind
then I'm definitely gonna keep doing
this because it's so fun getting to chat
with friends
um while doing some of the
the heavier Parts like grinding getting
exp
Etc so uh
or repeating the same thing over and
over again committing it to muscle
memory when we do jump King DLC it'll
definitely happen again so really glad
you're enjoying these kinds of streams
though Eric appreciate it Big Ups
and we got a big UPS to John L Al vizuri
John alvazuri
thank you for the red super chat John
let's go shed them well-deserved tears
now an even greater gamer I really was
like I felt myself tearing up
and my my nose was like
uh sniffling a little bit
I felt a big swell of emotion
but I'm I'm glad I'm glad I did it
oh what a ride that was thank you for
cheering for me John hope you had
yourself a good time the videos too a
cute penguin congrats thank you big UPS
to hlg congrats Maury Victory Screech
thank you Cat fluff and a big UPS to
Thomas congrats thank you
Big Ups to Robert L thank you bunny game
and a big UPS to Baby lit Leo a big
upset David Moore a fantastic work Cali
is such perseverancy gazelle thank you
to sock and 93. thank you very much
s17b32
really appreciate that red Super Chat
thank you for the support this stream
congrats on getting the smoking hot babe
Cali you showed some really impressive
platforming to get to that point you've
had one heck of a trip up that Tower Big
Ups to you for going the distance who
says Dad can't play games ah
it's just me being too dang hard on
myself
but you know what
um every time I play one of these games
like it's the same for everhood and
crash four and um even Blood Stained and
and now uh jump King these are all games
that I really love and it feels good to
to beat them you know when I was younger
I really loved playing games but I never
really beat a lot of them the idea of
like beating a game
never really like uh
like crossed my mind a long time ago I
got a really sad memories
it's kind of
I don't want to bring everyone's Spirits
down because it was a long time ago but
uh my first game clear experience was I
borrowed a game called Kirby's Nightmare
in Dreamland
it was for uh
it was for the Game Boy and I actually
borrowed it from a friend a friend a
long time ago
um and uh it was just like a a quote
unquote friend at school our parents
were friends so it was like neighborhood
buddies kind of thing and he kind of
introduced me to the game and let me
borrow it right and so I beat the game
and I recalled being really excited that
I beat it
I was really I was really excited that I
beat that game and uh I think I was like
what
what little like fifth grade Reaper
Maybe
um
and during school during school I like
came up to him and I was like guess what
I beat the game I beat the game
and and the dude was like with his
friends
and gave me like a weird look and like
walked away and I was like Oh okay
that's cool I mean that made me kind of
sad
um anyway I beat this game so thanks for
cheering for me uh everyone here uh
instead of giving me a weird look and
walking away
say
I mean I'm not like I said I'm not
bitter about it because you know when
you're when you're fifth grade Reapers
you've got all kinds of insecurities and
weird stuff going on in your head so I
mean
it's cool it's not
it's not like a you know
it was a bit of an embarrassing memory
it being the first game that I beat
um like I said I had a weird childhood
but uh it's cool thank you you guys
that thank you thank you for being here
and sharing for me it gets better y'all
um
if you have days like that too or
experiences like that as well it gets
better you never know when um someone's
gonna kind of do that to you someone you
like feel like is a friend but maybe is
like embarrassed of you and that kind of
thing
um you never know when many many years
later you're going to be streaming in
front of like 16 000 people uh that are
happy to beat a game so that's that's
how we turn it into a good thing yeah
that's how we turned it into a good
thing so it gets better that's children
for you true facts
yeah I learned a lot of a lot of lessons
during those times though you never stop
learning through your existence you know
true facts
16k dead because cheering and cheering
loud it's a happy ending to the story
you know
story's got a happy end
that's all you guys cheering pickups to
you guys thank you
yeah
you've had one heck of a trip at the
tower Big Ups are Going the Distance who
says Dad can't play games
s17b32 big ups for your support
I think it's a Sombra Park thank you
very much World Arigato gozaimasu thank
you Candy pop97 CMP Big Ups to you and a
Big Ups 2 clue
R I was here
p-o-g-g-e-r-s Big Ups Too High
foreign
oh two
got it though
big of two x add or maybe zad always
down for more Cali podcasts I think of
Dark Viper zero zero seven heck yeah
congrats thank you
a big UPS terrain maker a big episode
444 thank you very much terrific Mr T
end to pick ups too
albino
for the red super chat thank you very
much babe god let's go heck yeah thank
you for dropping by what a freaking Chad
hope you're doing well
Big Ups 2 Kaiju fighter whoa that's f
word and go Cali
oh Big Ups two let me get your name I
can translate this
[Laughter]
ah
in Korean huh
very nice congratulations I'm impressed
your severe endurance I hope you have
fun
the cute name and picture very sweet of
you thank you very much
a big UPS two birder Joel thank you very
much Lord of Oblivion heck yeah dropping
by to say congrats on your new cover
song the upcoming song releases and
completing jumping at exactly 11 59 pm
here you completed it saving the
princess before midnight thank you for
the hard work Callie thank you Lord
Oblivion thank you very much Saku and a
big UPS too
bounce you egg thank you pickups to
Gareth Thompson a big UPS to feedback
Jack and a big UPS too
oh this is uh Cali is a superb student I
I know we're I know it's you because I
see your uh Cali teaches hella excellent
student
S
I finished it I remember your icon
congrats welcome to the tower top and
happy Halloween very sweet of you thank
you a big UPS to David let's go pick up
some meatball Divino thank you very much
cygnus gob
yes you gotta admit
what's this
and what I had to do with those jumps oh
yeah I was kind of calculating them
I was calculating those jumps what was
it again okay
um what was it hang on go uh bounce off
the top
uh run it back no it's it's full to the
right run it back uh Bonk on the head
uh little jump bounce to the right get
to the edge
I had it all figured out
I think I'm still use cygnus pickups to
tentacles 7336 and thank you very much
C two six one six oh seven five thank
you for the many many
no message I mean it is technically a
message but ah forget it what a chad
thank you very much T appreciate you big
UPS to dragon and Dante in a big UPS to
feign thank you sin Yen and a big UPS to
big hat Lexi thank you Orson Carton and
a big UPS to Dinosaur Satan I love your
name maybe the next babe will be on fire
pickups to assass thank you very much
your boy's got a good video games thank
you very much Jeremy how big of a tiger
see a deadbeat and the Big Ups to Walid
thank you yakimo yomi a big UPS to arto
47 my first Super Chat to you congrats
on beating the game Cali thank you very
much
a big UPS to bailing Baker Hail to the
King Baby thank you very much berserking
she's not bad but I prefer the girl with
pink hair on the screen the one who
actually puts in effort I do appreciate
that that's very sweet of you however
however I'm gonna defend the babe for a
minute you never know maybe she jumped
herself all the way up there you never
know you never know what the Babe's
backstory was maybe there was another uh
like super hot being at the top of uh
the castle and she had to jump all the
way up there
yeah but maybe the super hot being was
like already gone by the time she got
there so she became the super hot babe
you never know
a big UPS too
insufficiently anonymous
thank you very much for the red super
chat appreciate the heck out of you as
always and sufficiently Anonymous for
hanging out with us watching and
cheering what a time to be alive not
only has this been a great day to have
this on at work all day with some great
banter all around I've just got back in
time to see you clutch this out in a
genuinely decent time and the birthday
merch finally arrived incredible timing
yes I'm so glad you guys are finally
getting your merch really have you got
yours as well and sufficiently Anonymous
hope you enjoy uh the vinyl the docky
all the good stuff that came along there
was a lot of good stuff that came along
with it uh so I hope you enjoy thank you
very much and also good timing as well
glad that we could uh maybe make your
work day a little less a little less uh
monotonous and samey
whatever we can do to be helpful thank
you so much
a big UPS to rev and Morey's deadbeat in
space you did it can't wait to watch the
VOD throughout the day I bet it was a
trial by fire oh you'll see Revan it was
uh something all right hope you enjoy it
Big Ups Too Vasily don't forget your
crown King a Big Ups 2 Road Forks you
yet again thank you for the amazing
generosity this stream appreciate the
heck out of you as always Road Forks you
who says 10 million views on king crown
premiered today and you got the Babe I'd
say you deserve the crown Empress Morty
it's kind of been an amazing day
uh full of full of victories in in many
ways so thank you for bringing that up
now that I'm really thinking about it a
lot of great stuff happens huh
ah my face hurts from smiling thank you
so much Road Forks you
appreciate you dropping by and being
here for all the chaos and Madness it
was a blast
a big of two draconic Insight thank you
very much
really proud of you oh draconic thanks
for dropping by dude a pickups to dog or
bread absolutely amazing Maury and a big
UPS to Nick s Kiara had Faith you would
finish it and you pulled through
congrats she sure did huh
everyone who had some faith in me gosh I
really appreciate you guys Big Ups to
jprs NSR and thank you very much Kevin
what an amazing stream Kelly was here
for most of the stream and it was so fun
to have on and see the babe at the top
you did so well you are King
[Music]
did you clear I did girl I did
yes I'll I'll send you the screenshot
later
but yes I cleared it like here let me I
did
maybe you can you can watch the Beauty
if you want but uh yeah we uh we got a
babe all right we got a babe
here
I'm shooting them over
so you can see
you can see the babe
I did it let's go Gigi thank you gura
thank you thank you for the yeah thank
you for the company as well
we clutched it out at the end Tower
there
thank you thank you
yeah you are cute
thank you very much Kevin and a big UPS
to space Turtle 20 with a chat and a big
of two Aiden you did it long live the
king that's all for today whoa we got
through the supers you guys are awesome
you guys left so much love and support
for me cheering for me all the way up
you guys rule thank you so much
seriously
um it would not have been half as fun
without you guys and the girls jumping
in to hang out and chat with me
gosh what a blast
um thanks for everything you guys really
truly
I mean this [\h__\h]
We're not gonna do the outro again I'm
I like the outro that we have I don't
have another thumb ready but that
shouldn't matter I know but
um sometimes you just want to fade out
to some whole live Lo-Fi
oh my throat is a little tired I guess
the Vodka did not help very much also
the constant talking for the past almost
11 hours but you know what guys let's
all get some rest
let's all get some rest because we've
got a fun
uh next couple days full of Halloween
festivities new songs new music
um
new events New parties
um all kinds of fun stuff is happening
you guys for Halloween so let's make it
awesome okay I'll see you guys really
soon again I'm your Murray hope you'll
remember me you guys take care of
yourselves
um
maybe the real babe was all the friends
we made along the way etc etc
um it's nice to it's nice to have this
this crowd
a nice a nice Crown a nice jump jump
Crown also check out Crown it's pinned
in the it's pinned in the comment
section it's a new song Me and Boogie
box
um check it out
I love you guys
take care okay
peace
bye everyone
you guys the best