[Music]
do
oh my god hello
[Music]
hi evie hello
okay oh my god i've been i've been going
for the questions for like
an hour and then i was like [\h__\h] i still
gotta eat food i thought i would get
probably earlier more than an hour and i
finally would have time to eat but i
didn't and i started making lasagna and
then i started eating lasagna while i
was looking at the questions now i
didn't even finish the lasagna and also
didn't finish going for the questions
but
um i hope we have enough uh questions i
wish
it should be enough but but
still ah
i'm kind of mad that uh i couldn't like
you know like
i don't have like ocd like you like many
of you guys do whenever i do something
in minecraft and you're like oh my god
this is
horrible but when i like start scrolling
for something
i need to scroll until the end so
places like i don't know twitter and
instagram
are toxic for me because
i i cannot stop scrolling and then now
there were so many questions
uh i shouldn't have kept it open for so
long
i i just also was just simply out of
fairness
and wondering what i would be missing
out on what kind of good questions i
would be missing out on
i just really wanted to scroll until the
end but i couldn't
uh well
i might i don't know maybe maybe i'll
keep some for
part two at some point or or
i i guess i could answer some in the
karaoke stream like in between
yeah actually that would be a good idea
slow motion oh let me turn it on
you're like a snitch in the classroom
yeah
i think we need to do uh i think we had
some homework to do
uh well i got it i don't know about the
others but
i i have it so uh
that happens doesn't it like oh my god
when the teacher actually forgets that
they gave you homework
and then it's usually that one person
like most of the students didn't even do
it and they're like
really [\h__\h] glad that the teacher
forgot about it
but then there's this one snitch that's
like well i
i have it so and sometimes they even do
it
because they know that the other
students don't have the homework so that
on purpose they're like
well i'm gonna drag them all into this
[\h__\h] and embarrass them for not
having uh the homework ready
i was in such situations before i feel
like i was no i feel like i was in both
situations before
like but mostly the one who didn't do
the homework
yeah like i would i would uh
often uh do like
usually i do the homework but not for
math for math i often
didn't do the homework
yeah just because also just because i
don't
underst i just didn't understand it okay
i just could not
understand it
well everyone sorry for the delay as
well uh i guess we should get right into
it
uh who does homework you should do your
homework
get those good grades go get em one two
five
well the only thing i can tell you the
only thing that i understand
is four plus four is eight me plus u is
fate
uh so i also didn't have time to
uh save each question as an image
because they give it to you as an image
but
i i didn't i couldn't save it
uh because that takes too much time so
we're just scrolling through
the page okay
so let's start let's get going
are you ready for some question time we
haven't done a q a in a long time so i
thought this
was gonna be uh would would would be
some fun to
go for some questions again so let's go
uh let's start out here
[Music]
okay so uh
what kind of work does the whole life i
don't have to do off-stream
like i guess that it's not just starting
you see my mouse here
i know you actually don't see it and not
just starting a stream goofing around
and then ending it what is the before
and after there must be some hard work
that we don't see
uh so you can be our talent potential we
love
what
oh you see something else
oh interesting white white white white
white white white right right
i'm like what do you mean wrong question
uh should
be this one
[Music]
one sec got it got it got it got it got
it okay
now this is okay here we go okay
what kind of work does a whole life i
don't have to do off-stream
and like i guess that it's not just
starting a stream goofing around and
then edit
ending it what is the before and after
there must be some hard work that we
don't see
so you can be our talent attention we
love to watch in any case thank you for
work we appreciate it all thank you
um so i think this
really uh depends
this really depends on
the streamer i guess like you can
totally be a v trimmer
and or a youtube or whatever uh
and just not put so much work into it
but you can also
put a lot of work into it and i would
say for example someone like
kelly puts a [\h__\h] ton of work uh into it
i think for kelly it's very obvious but
for other people it might not be so
obvious you might think oh they're just
streaming and that's it
and besides that they don't know
anything and that might be true but in
other cases it might not be true
sometimes uh you know they do much more
behind the scenes than you think
uh but i think it's a general
misconception
that people have uh thinking that we
don't do
anything and which i guess i get because
because all you see is us streaming and
maybe every once in a while putting out
a video
and maybe tweeting something but yeah
i personally would say that i at least
even when i don't stream eight hours a
day
that i at least with other work that i
do get up to the eight hours at least
if not more actually like if you see
like like
i feel like as a beach social media is
part of your job
so like taking care of it and
controlling it all
and and you know that kind of stuff i
would consider it
work as well so then to be honest
it's probably like 12 hours or 15 hours
per day but
those are like more relaxed and chill
hours where
um i'm not under much pressure so
i don't really see it so much as
the tough work as streaming itself
can be very much but yeah so
what happened where i go come on so bad
are you kidding me
looks okay to me boss please stop
stop i can't do anything about it so
just ignore it please
um what was i saying oh yeah
so i personally stream long hours a lot
uh but besides that i'm always like
planning other stuff
like um you know some
original songs or some song covers or
collaborations or holo talk for example
holo talk
the preparation for holotalk the
questions
going for the questions and translating
them and putting them into a graphic and
all that
that simply takes me already like two to
two to three hours depends
and and
recently i've also like sometimes it's
necessary
to practice uh a game
for example like we had i had a pretty
uh
sponsored stream before uh like total
spell bubble
so i wanted to practice it a little bit
or it was actually even necessary for
some games it's just necessary to
practice them before streaming
and then for touhou spell bubble or
puyo puyo attaches i have like at least
one
two three four hours no not not four
maybe
maximum three hours of practice so that
is kind of also part of the job because
you gotta
be prepared especially for sponsored
streams um
uh and also it's like sometimes there's
like uh things that you probably don't
even
see like the other day i did like this
uh this
chart of how i i am like related to
other hello live
members i did it because i was requested
to do it for
a show on the whole live official
channel the japanese
channel and it took me like two hours to
do it because i
wanted to make it pretty because i
thought they were just gonna use the
exact same
graphic that i showed you guys turned
out they
didn't use it so it didn't have to look
pretty
but i put like two hours into making
that
uh uh so yeah and there's a
obviously okay i guess not obviously but
there's many things in the background
that you guys just
don't really see so much i guess um
that we're working on which is a good
thing
good thing so yeah anyway it's it's a it
turns out to be a full-time job but
i guess if you choose to put less work
into it then that also
totally works
ready for the next question
let's go i'm just going to scroll
oh you don't even see the whole thing
wait
[Music]
hey yo tanjo i was wondering if you were
interested in reading fan fiction about
you not particularly on stream
but in real life too and if you are on
which website would you prefer to find
and read them
also you know i love you you're great
and amazing and i feel like you
becoming my aussie has brightened my
days like never before so thank you for
everything really
really really thank you ah also
since you're a big fan of school with
that and that you
and that you made me fall into this hole
too you need to take responsibility
and absolutely have to sing tata thing
or 20 ah
9 p.m
and while others are needed to obviously
obviously need to obviously for that
okay thank you for this
question um first of all you're welcome
i'm glad you got into that music after
my recommendation
and that makes me quite happy
unfortunately schoolboy is not around
anymore so
it's a bit late to get into that fandom
yeah but still they have so many songs
out there and so much content so many
like concerts concert dvds and stuff
that you you gotta check them all out
so anyway about the fanfiction um i'm
gonna be honest here
first of all i don't read any books
or anything at all i i just genuinely
don't read
okay so keep that in mind and the second
of all
i personally if i think about reading a
fanfiction
about me or any other whole life girl or
like a special
especially one where i am in could you
relate
if i say that that would be a bit cringe
[Laughter]
i don't know like i am so happy that
people take the time to write those
and it's cute like it's like fan art i'm
happy that you guys uh want to create
something and
and i love this kind of investment that
you have
in it but reading something about me
that other people fantasize
about you know like i know it's kind of
weird
and i don't know i just don't like to
read
if it's like an anime or or a movie or
fan art or a manga manga is still i
guess
yeah comic pages stuff that's that's
still something i can
get into when i go for my art tag every
now and then some like manga pages pop
up and i'm like
oh let's take a look and it's always
pretty cool and okay gotta say like
those are badass those are not i guess
maybe it's not cringe i don't know
it depends i guess i guess it can be
cringe but about the
manga pages i've never really felt that
they are cringe
so hmm they're really cool
like i like those stories about me and
kelly you know
uh or any other whole life girl they're
pretty
pretty dope mmm but fun pictures i'm so
sorry i just don't like reading at all
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
also i'll be honest i probably won't be
reading them
unless you send it to me in the fan
letter and then if it's
if it's too long i i won't read it if
you sent me like a short version of it
okay maybe i'm just being honest because
i don't want to get your hopes
up okay next up
uh you mentioned before how chunkers and
not as jonkers uh both from her name is
smokey now okay
i'm not from the same litter do you have
any uh special reason or story behind
getting two cats from the same lily like
that did you ever get permission from
falcon games like
trails or the y series now i don't think
so
your streams are great and fun even when
horrible techno functions or other
shenanigans happen
those haven't happened for a while
though i feel like those that's well
that was a big thing in the past but not
so much anymore now
please never lose confidence in that
people enjoy watching them
thank you i love you well thanks for the
question
um i just wanted to answer the question
because it's about my cats
honestly you you were smart you were
probably like thinking
okay i just want it doesn't matter what
what it is about i just want kiana to
pick up my question i don't care what
i'm
asking so how do i get her to pick up my
question
very smart asking about my cats do you
otherwise automatically make me pick up
the questions just by asking about my
cats because i love talking about my
cats
so when i got myself my own cats like i
i used to live with cats
uh with app cats usually always uh
singular uh when i was uh
living with my family with my mom um
but when i i wanted to get my own
at some point and i was
thinking well i want to get to
because so that they can play with each
other and the more fluffiness the better
right obviously
um well but but getting them from the
same litter i don't know it just seemed
like the most logical thing for me to do
instead of
getting like them from different places
but yeah eventually i want to add
one or 10 or 20 more cats
and those can be from different places
but it's going to be interesting how to
make them get used to each other and
it's not going to happen
so soon it's going to happen slowly
gradually over time
i'm going to rescue all cats in
australia all of them
yes yes yes well thank you for your
question next we're going to go through
them
quickly and good afternoon boss hope
you're well when it comes to cleaning
and storing things
how do you go about sorting items too
far away
as much uh it's as much it's a little
embarrassing to say even though i'm not
27 year old guy i have a corner filled
with old spongebob
blue plushies from my childhood that i
can't for the life of me
seem to part with but i do wish to
shrink what i have
and hand things to people who could find
use for them thank you for your time
thank you for your question um
i think it's a good question because i
personally
uh used to
first i still somehow a little bit do
but
i used to keep like everything um
i couldn't really part um
things that well okay it wasn't like
crazy like my room was exploding that
was not the case no no no not at all
but like especially when i was moving
um inside of australia i still brought
all those things along with me but it
was like
so much stuff and i was looking through
them and i was like
okay it's like it's not like i need
these things to live
uh to continue living but still i
kind of you know can't throw them away
so i had the same struggle to struggle
gentle
trouble struggle um
what i've but that but i've also had
like a [\h__\h] ton of plushies like on
right now i only have one alpaca alpaca
that's chilling on my bed but i got rid
of like
millions of plushies and uh recently
moving from australia
to japan and then one year later moving
from japan again to australia
i threw away so
many things and i'm proud of it and i'm
glad i did it
because ah there's just so much
unnecessary
uh things um
yeah it was hard sometimes but the only
thing that i really kept
is um from the far
far way past is uh you know those
friendship books i don't know did you
guys ever use those
when when you were like in i don't know
when you were like really young
those friendship books like we had uh
these mostly diddle
how do you have diddle in other
countries
we had these uh little friendship books
yes we did yes we did a lot a lot of
people were asked
i oh my god wait is that a boomer thing
and
zoomers don't have friendship books
because they only have like phones and
they don't even use paper
yeah d-i-d-d-l-e that was like super
popular when i was uh younger and i
loved collecting stuff from diddle but
also there they had these friendship
books and everyone in my school had
friend
i mean only the girls to be honest every
girl had a friendship book
and uh it would be like so much fun
every time you got to know someone or
everyone in your class you would let
them fill out your friendship books and
you would
give everyone like a week you would be
like okay i'll give you my friends a
book you give me
your friendship [\h__\h] i'll give it to
you in a week okay please fill it out
okay and then you would get it back it
would be so dope and i still have a
bunch of them and i looked back into
them
the other day when i when i came back
from japan to australia and i was
you know sorting out things uh throwing
away some things again
i saw these friends of books again and
they're so cringe
oh yeah do you want to hear something
okay let me let me get one i have them
here do you want to hear what like um
super super young
kiara and her friends were writing into
friendship books
wednesday
[Music]
okay
it's so cringe it's so cringe okay
i you know i'm eternal but um
i must have been just did i write in
how old i was i must have been
wait where is where's mine
where's here did i write my age
no just uh-huh
how old was i wait did anyone
write the date
i got no idea i was probably um it was
probably my
uh yeah it was eternal myself except now
it was probably
my uh you know i lived many lives so
let's say it was maybe the
the 10th 10th life or something like
that
or less maybe nine nine eight eight
not sure okay so my hobbies back then
ice skating
roller skating playing i don't know what
that means
playing what was i playing watching tv
what uh playing pc my favorite school
subjects
german and drawing
i am a fan of diddle
and music
uh this should be this should exist more
often um this is all in german by the
way i had to translate this uh
uh uh spinach
spinach peanut knockout spin spit i
hated spinach but there was just one
dish uh
i don't know how to translate it spinach
something something
with cheese sauce and the big break in
school
instead of the small break i don't know
did you guys have big breaks in small
ways i think that's a normal thing right
i wanted more big breaks rather than
small breaks
okay so the the coolest movie
uh slash the coolest serious uh
finding nemo and charmed
oh it's so cute that's so cute
uh my face oh oh [\h__\h] oh no
my favorite singer slash my favorite
band
you must consider i was like maybe in my
9th or 10th life okay
justin timberlake
and the next two you probably never
heard of because i think those are
groups that came
out of a german uh pop stars show like
making them in
playing you know in a tv show you know
that there's groups that come together
um pre-loaders overground
no idea who they are and now these two
this one this one's really surprises me
what the [\h__\h] that was not my take i
think i was just trying to be
sound cool like as if i had more variety
and taste but
i don't think i was a fan of them the
rasmus
have you guys ever heard of those people
i think they were
what genre was that like metal or rock
or something like that
or like wasn't that like emo i don't
know something like that oh my god
i don't think that i actually like them
that much i just wanted to sound cool
and then another one was shot
oh my god uh
the absolutely best song this is so good
we should do a whole stream about this
i have another one two another
friendship
the absolute best song and i don't know
what this song is i gotta listen to it
again
the first day of my life you know what
let me google it what song is that
the first day of my life
what
melanie c maybe
no that's from the restless as well what
oh god let me listen
i don't remember this song it's from
oh yeah
oh my god he looks like a crowd
oh my oh my
[Music]
he has feathers in his hair maybe that's
what i liked
say i'll kill you if i do something oh
my god
okay maybe i'll remember the song but of
course
ah still feels like the first time
to stand here by your side ah
together regardless oh yeah yeah i think
i remember
little rock fruity darkness together
we're going to walk for the darkness oh
my god
oh my god wait that is so foreshadowing
that is so
foreshadowing to oh my god
that is the cringiest thing ever okay
now here
uh the best game oh here we go oh wow i
was quiet the game were bad batman it
seems
uh young young kiana writes best games
according to young kiara zelda
dr bieber i think that was not a pc game
that was an actual like board game kind
of thing
mario kart double dash what
and sims of every kind
dr dr beaver is like a b-i-b-e-r in
german though
doctor with k i don't know what is that
i'm gonna look it up
doctor bieber wait
no ah yeah it's like it's like one of
those games where you operate
on a body and if you uh get it wrong
then you get like el exercise or
something
things that i can do well german drawing
what i can what i don't like annoying
people
and food that's um moldy
or disgusting or like disgusting things
wow okay who i like the most my friends
my mom um someone else
and my cat someone else was my
my mom's
my favorite animals cat
horse bunny hamster
okay my favorite food okay we got the
the spinach thingy again
even though i hate spinach fascinating
my favorite
dessert ice cream what i want to be
what i want to become when i grow older
now in german i wrote kunster kunzler
which can mean artist
as a drawing artist but it can also mean
artist as in singer or any kind of
any kind of uh creative thing
that is that is uh
inspiring and my
my biggest wish ever becoming
okay i was i was young okay it says
becoming rich everyone wrote that [\h__\h]
in their biggest wish becoming rich and
uh and be able to do magic
and uh mary
[Music]
i love this oh my god don't you guys
want to hear from the other book i think
i was younger in the other book
oh my god it's oh no that's oh my god i
actually wrote my
my age here this is um kiana from
her ninth life you know what i mean
oh my god
oh my god it says
he like there's a there's a field where
you could fill out your your mobile
phone number
uh but this was a long time ago okay
standards were different back then
and and uh chiara from her ninth life
writes i can only have it when i'm 13
14 or 15 then i get one
13 40 for 15 life
my mom was uh holding back with giving
me a phone for as long as possible
i think nowadays people have phones when
they're like five or something
it's like so early oh my god okay
oh yeah i can even see in the
handwriting i was really young and i i
started out
using like a normal pen and then i then
i continued using like sparkly pens and
the grammar is off too okay
so my hobbies back then were
reading drawing and so on
i remember this was the french book that
i was bringing along on the on the horse
uh
camp trip for one week and so i was like
really excited so i wrote
soon riding horses but that was like the
i know back then i liked reading back
then i liked reading
yes yes i was reading books from like
terry pratchett that was
uh something i really liked um
yes yes it's true but yeah i was getting
really excited about getting
uh getting to learn how to ride a horse
but that was the only time i
ever was uh able to ride a horse because
after that it was like too much of an
expensive hobby i guess
yep so yeah my
favorite school subject is art and
i am a fan of music and and riding
horses
uh this shift exists more often
ah suppose i wrote down a specific
uh horse race that i don't know what
it's called in
english but it's island horses but
he's not bad at i don't know what
they're called in english
um good music
and a brother who doesn't annoy me
yeah me and my brother did not get along
well back then
oh man me and my big brother
the the best movie or the uh best
serious
again charmed uh kiara in her ninth
life here uh in life will
really like charmed the best singer
again preluders
and ridiculous i really like this pop
star show they had in
german tv and the absolutely best song
okay here we go i wrote i don't think
this is the correct title
i wrote every time
from britney without the e though
i wrote britney without the e
see how when i was younger i liked
britney spears and then i got like what
one or two years older and i was into
the rasmus i was getting into some
emo face
the best game okay
the best game according to
995 kiara
does that even exist in english industry
industry giant too
[Music]
it's like sim city
industry giant yeah it exists in english
it's like
sim city i was playing that
at that age oh my god
what oh my god so self-aware
so self-aware what i can do best cry
draw and cheer someone up
cry
[Music]
what i do not like when i am angry
and myself oh no no i think it's a when
i'm angry i don't i don't like myself
i think that's what i meant
um who enacted my
family my favorite animals
cats and horses again the horses
my favorite food there's a lot my
favorite sweets
chocolate and so on this is what i want
to become
what wow that changed a lot
this is what i want to become in the
future job wise
professional horse rider
or waitress
wow okay i had some really uh real like
not not necessarily the horse rider not
so much but waitress i was really
realistic with that age once
waitress what i think i know why
because my mom at that time was doing a
job like that and i guess i just thought
it was cool
because i i used to like go to uh where
she was
weight dressing at and i just felt like
she was so
cool and like she would give me like
like
uh orange juice and stuff and i would
sit there and look at her working i
guess it was just really cool to me yeah
yeah makes sense my biggest
uh wish becoming the thing above
and becoming rich and doing magic again
ah this is so so precious this is why
i'm not throwing this away
ever ever ever
okay that was a big tangent oh my god oh
my god oh my god this stream is gonna be
long
that was so precious oh my god
whoever sent that question wow
thank you thank you who doesn't want to
be rich exactly and i feel like
most of the children who wrote into my
book just wanted to be rich
oh well 40 minutes already only three
questions oh no
okay okay continue let's let's go speed
what happened to the twitter series
stand up kia it will come back uh i
agree
i kind of forgot about it i need to do
it again need to do it again yeah
i especially remember it when uh
april the first came up yeah sorry i've
been too busy i need to
get to it again carefully loves you uh
so most of the messages you get on
twitter and youtube are positive and
about how we loved your latest video and
how
fun or insightful it was there's always
back to me
so i wanted to ask if you get numb or
about reading our messages since many of
them
can look like each other i do not
surprisingly i do not
i love reading all your messages
endlessly as i said i cannot stop
scrolling anyway
so on twitter i go for all the replies
mostly so
it goes on and on and forever and i i'm
i'm actively looking for them
so please continue i'm not getting numb
not like that super uh super awesome
song numb from lingam park
hey kiana a huge fan of your streams
and you're awesome thank you question
if entire halloween were to plan a road
trip together who would be
who would best fulfill each following
realm and for comedic effect what would
be the worst rules to fail for each girl
number one drives the entire trip stops
fights they'll break
out
has any hollow life english member
mentioned that they have a driving
license
i feel like that would be inado uh
like i'm a good at me and kelly fighting
and inna
would be the one you know she would be
the most chill ones you'll be like
[Music]
chill i'mma does callie arena
cali has a license kelly has a license
wow what what
no it doesn't matter who had the license
but i would i feel like that would be
enough maybe
select playlist pack snacks for everyone
ah
that might be good what do you guys
think
pando's paper map suggests suggests
shortcuts
[Music]
what do you think kelly ramen
yeah i wouldn't i wouldn't dress the
kelly's uh shortcuts anyway because um
or her handling a map or anything yeah
actually
yeah i wouldn't trust her judging from
the trip we went on she was
like she planned uh everything but when
it came to like
um transportation as soon as we weren't
going with a taxi anymore
with an airplane that's when she would
get lost
like she wouldn't like uh
be very uh
reliable anymore i remember when did you
know that story i think we told you guys
when we're like
stuck stuck in the snowstorm of uh
sapporo and uh we were trying to get to
the shuttle but
do you know how we got to that situation
you know how we ended up there to begin
did i tell you with part two
but yeah
yeah so we got into a cab and
kelly gave them the name of the
the supposed name of the
um shuttle pickup place
no address uh
just a name but apparently there's like
two places with that name
in in the city so we got brought to the
wrong one
and we were waiting there and waiting
and waiting and
eventually the too much time passed and
we were sick of being
like freezingly cold so we start we
started calling the hotel
and they didn't oh my god this is
another tangent if you want to
hear the whole story please watch the
hokkaido stream i need to answer these
questions
so and then uh takes pictures of the
trip picks the final destination
wait no such as card games looks up fun
facts about locations wait the foot this
one's yours
suggests card games looks up fun facts
about locations
yeah i don't know hey what do you think
who would be number four
four is you for zina
yeah i see how eno could be that too or
me i mean
i don't know any card games i would
probably be sleeping
or i don't know
yeah but i would probably also be
looking up like places to go
um i i would i would i don't think
anyone would pick the final destination
i think we would always like
pick together though uh but yeah also i
would definitely take a [\h__\h] ton of
pictures
and movies um in
in my trip with cali to hokkaido i was
definitely the one taking the most
pictures
and asking uh kelly for pictures
and taking pictures of her as well
and she'd be like can you send that to
me can you send it to me
i was definitely the photographer um
uh so i i relates to five maybe the most
yeah but final destination we should
pick together
although i do feel like always when i go
on trips of people that
i do decide a lot somehow because other
people just
don't don't seem to have this strength
to decide so i'll just go with it
yeah thank you for the question love
back to brazil
hello kiana and this is more than one
question sorry but how to
how do you feel about knowing that
people from all the world watch your
videos
also how's life going on in australia
are you happy being back home i really
hope so truly
also how is it like to live in another
country far from everyone you know
i have never left my own country so i
don't know how that must feel like
anyway hope you're doing fine regardless
another one for brazil yo
so um yeah well life in those australia
is uh going well going well everything's
cool and i'm i'm quite happy being back
home
i have some mixed feelings uh some part
of me also wants to be in japan but
that's nothing i can do much about um
yeah how i feel about people watching my
videos from all over the world
that's awesome like just the thoughts
that um
like conventions all over the world
could invite us as guests and you guys
would come there
and it just makes me so happy i wish we
could you know have like a
world tour uh where we could appear
uh for everyone so everyone could like
meet us basically
that would be so dope it's it's an honor
to
have so many fans from all over the
world thank you all so much
and yeah living in a completely
different country from your own is uh
it can be very challenging especially if
you go on your own
alone then it's a big challenge
and but i think i think i have another
question about this somewhere in there
where we can talk more in depth about it
but
it makes you grow as a person so much
and makes you realize
how different other countries and
cultures are next to probably more open
for other cultures as well
tantra i'm interested in traveling but
i'm nervous about doing it on my own
what are some tips and tricks
that you can give for this sort of thing
thank you for your question
and so
generally i've traveled a lot on my own
to japan
but besides that i told you that on my
own
i traveled maybe to germany but also
but germany is like not a big deal like
germany for going to germany is like the
same
as staying my own country almost so
there's not much to worry about
but for example i did this one trip to
spain
on my own and i was very nervous about
that too because i don't speak their
language and
i thought that they over there speak a
lot of english
but maybe just the one city that i went
to in particular
didn't speak much like the people there
didn't speak much english like at all
like the most people i talked to barely
spoke any english
so i did feel a bit lost uh
but maybe from
my maybe from
my experience you can get some
ideas so basically for example i was
since i went alone i felt a little bit
lonely i didn't wasn't so sure what to
do but for example you can go on airbnb
and not only look for maybe not right
now maybe in the future but
you cannot only look for a places to
stay at but you can also look for
activities and there will usually be a
guide
to show you around or tell you about uh
the city or go like on a bike tour and
all that and it will be
you get the help and those people are
really friendly to people who are
traveling
on their own as well and uh i think
um there's also there's also sometimes
like if you want to take cute pictures
for your instagram
and but you you're alone so you don't
have anyone to take them
you could probably also book like photo
tours
photo like the people show you around
the city
while taking cute pictures of you that's
really cool like there's all kinds of
things like that
uh in each city on the world on airbnb
as well and i really recommend that i
made use of that
several times and it was a lot of fun
because those people usually also speak
english or like whatever language
uh you need them to speak mostly uh
yeah they're really good guys as well
and it's not expensive like okay some
people
some things are expensive but others not
so much for example in japan you can
do like really cool traditional stuff as
well like probably
i think there's like some stuff like uh
putting you into a kimono or traditional
tea ceremony
and all that kind of stuff really uh
recommendable and that
should make you feel a bit more safe and
warm warmed up in that
particular country also google maps is
uh your hero as it was my hero as well
without google maps i would have died
yep
continuing
we read this one yeah
uh young bombastic energy is what got
what got me into her life and for you
introduced me to the rest of the young
girls
thank you and what type of content do
you most enjoy making most rewarded by
thank you thank you thank you i'm happy
to hear that
well i would say
making music feels
the most fun and it's the most exciting
and it's i wish i could do more
uh yeah i
i want to do more music it feels
i'm not sure if that feels most rewarded
um me i'm not i'm not sure about that
but i want to do more of it it's my
favorite thing to do that i get to do
uh up until now in her life
uh why is switch in light mode i don't
know what your problem is with that
first of all i don't know i didn't even
know that there was a dark mode on
switch
second of all i just like it that way
first of all why you guys always get so
worked up
over dark mode and light mode it's
ridiculous
ridiculous now i just on purpose want to
trigger you guys with light mode on
every single app that i have
how are earthquakes in japan do you have
any stories about them i gotta be honest
no not really um japan has earthquakes
pretty much daily
and uh they're they are
mostly really not a big deal often you
don't even notice them
and i am lucky that
in those years that i've lived in japan
i pretty much only experienced
one rather big uh
earthquake and that was the one that was
like fairly recent where all the
i was reading about it uh too
but yeah mostly it's not a big deal uh i
guess it depends on the area where you
live in but i was lucky enough to
not be affected by it much so yeah it
was fine it was fine but
i i was a bit uh
[Music]
surprised about it that there are so
many earthquakes because
and where i'm from we don't have any
earthquakes ever
at all the time for earthquakes is uh
way way past in australia we i guess we
used to have lots of earthquakes in the
very very
past but nowadays nothing at all so i've
never experienced an earthquake
until i came to japan but it was not
not a big deal
[Music]
next question is in originally japanese
and you see the rough translation below
i think
[Music]
the thing that i was most surprised
about in japan is how freaking
hot it is over there like i did not
think it would be dead hot like it's
like
tropical weather weather over there and
i would never have imagined that it's
a country with tropical weather with
humid as
hell weather and i threw up the first
time when i came to japan
it was summer and i threw up and my body
was like
going crazy i could not handle it at all
i mean i saw it in the map but and all
that but i would never ever expect it to
be that hot
god damn
um
[Music]
one more thing that i was also very
surprised about in japan is how
quiet it is in like subways
um it feels like super safe super clean
everyone's just
sleeping no one talks at all not a
single word
unless you there's maybe a couple there
but then they speak super quietly like
in my country no one gives a [\h__\h]
so that's that's something that i really
liked and i wish we
would have it in my country as well um
or a cabbage one of the cabs for
something special
[Laughter]
the cabbage was different and what's the
situation of yakuza we're gonna pick it
up soon as uh
as soon as i'm done with the raiza uh
i'm not sure if i will start from the
beginning again or if i'll continue
though
not sure okay what what is that this is
a long question here
uh tanza since this is anonymous i
thought i'd take chance to tell you that
some people in the usual room have
become numb to what's inside
i'll become so numb and so i thought we
should implement some new features
all the following have been approved by
the logistics team and are just pending
approval from you bus the hand
and the list is as follows having a
power bank in the room with many cables
but only one works so we must really try
all of them only to realize at the end
that there's no charge
ah okay if nothing works at all
okay okay okay if it doesn't charge at
all then okay okay okay
oh wait ah wait let me just move over
here there we go
if it doesn't work then okay we can we
can implement that since
wait uh
wait
there we go
ah then
since we already have tens of streaming
constantly in the room
due to hashtag real question guild i
suggest we make the audio for the left
and right speakers desynced for maximum
discomfort
okay any bags of snacks
served will be open from the bottom and
will be 85 percent air instead of the
usual 50 of you think you think there's
gonna be snacks in the usual room
no way a painted image of the missing
puzzle piece on the floor
[Music]
so that they think oh that's it and then
they try to pick it up and it's like
what what what what it's like
implemented in the floor
okay yes yes yes i think that sounds
very good
nice uh almost everything approved thank
you
would you rather be on vintage things or
retail verbs but i hate
boobs and i cannot stand
people burping around me um
and i don't i don't i try to never burp
myself so
sneezes the moment when i will ever burp
on stream if that would ever have to
happen
i would first of all feel so embarrassed
and try to overplay it
and i don't know no no no
no no titanic because i've never seen
the notebook
uh i'm having to take care of my
brother's cats for a few months
but wait let me let me move that around
again
so it's a smaller
so and having to take care of my
brother's cats for three months but i
have absolutely no experience in this
kind of stuff do you have any advice for
a first timer
first of all and thank you for taking
care of your brothers
uh cats for such a long time and second
of all
no worries cats are easy
cats mostly just do their own thing the
only thing you have to do
is give them food and water fresh water
clean their toilet as often as possible
and maybe please play with them
every once in a while yeah that's
mostly all they need and if you could if
you i don't think you can resist anyway
but you should pet your cats and give
them lots of love
now let me tell you one thing um
i think i've told you guys before that
in this one year that i was in japan
um not only my roommate but also another
roommate who was like living in my room
for that one year
took care of my cats thankfully i'm
really grateful for that
and that one roommate who moved in only
for one year
she told me afterwards
that she was so so happy
to have these two cats in that
time because you know of the whole sea
thing
she had to stay at home a lot and i
don't know
i guess it kind of eats you up sometimes
and
um she just felt like they were so
precious
she was especially addicted to chunkers
they were bffs she was carrying chunkers
around the whole time according to my
roommate
she said that she was like constantly
carrying her around the apartment
just as a stress uh relief kind of way
but she told me that yeah the cats
really helped her
with her mental health in that time
and and she loved taking care of them so
so much she
she had like her profile pictures on
social media where also with my cats
and she posted stories uh on instagram
with my cats and all that
so yeah um i think it made her really
happy so you might find
even though it's the first time for you
you might find a lot of happiness was
like a she
especially because she also said that
she um likes
dogs way more she used to be a dog
person but by being with my cats for a
year
she definitely appreciates cats so much
now and loves cats now
so yeah i think i think
you'll be fine you'll you'll fall in
love with them and it will all go well
cats are really just easy
yeah also be careful of what they eat be
careful that you don't have any weird
plants that they
might not uh go along with well look
look up what kind of plants are
toxic to cats and be careful that you
don't leave like small objects on the
floor or anywhere that they can reach
uh cat proof your apartment maybe a
little bit
and so that you know
i don't know there's all kinds of things
yeah but these are
these are many important things don't
feed them human food
yes yes okay uh continuing
and
[Music]
has living overseas in japan changed you
as a person and if given the opportunity
is there any other countries you'd be
interested in living abroad and for what
reasons
it has changed me very very much yes
um it has made me so mature
the first time i went to japan first
time i moved to japan i was quite young
and it forced me to grow up
and get used to adult life and used to
reality
very quickly and
i've made so many amazing memories and
so many friends and
and saw so many places because of that
and learned a whole language
even i mean i kind of was able to speak
it beforehand but still
i feel like
i would have i've just i've just grown
so much as a person
living overseas is something i would
recommend
anyone if you can do it doesn't matter
if you're young or old
do it it makes you see
the world in a different light and
ah it's just it's just precious memories
to have
very recommendable given the opportunity
is there any other country you've been
interested in living abroad at the
moment no not early
um as i've talked about it before but i
just
i don't feel like i want to live in the
country where i
i where i am in right now
i don't feel like i belong here that
much either
but i also wouldn't know where to go
next so oh that's something i've been
um thinking about at the moment anyway
and i don't know the answer to it yet
thank you guys for the super chat thank
you ever thought of planning to collab
cover or make original sounds of other
members in the whole life
yes i talked about it yesterday too uh
i'm planning working on some things
right now which will come out
this month
and then besides the things that i'm
planning i would love to do something
with nana
because we're orenz and i would also
love to
have an original song with cali at some
point that would be really dope
i think everyone wants to see that hear
that
yes takamori
and this whole live english as a whole i
would be so excited and happy if we
could just have a
original song together as whole live
english
at some point
uh besides how are you yeah i have
another question are you happy i really
hope you are and if you're not please
remember that our that there are people
out there caring for
you sweet okay that's not productive
think about a tangent
to avoid getting bunked do you ever do
you want to collaborate with other
artists for mvs or short videos more
often ever thought about that
i know it's uh still a lot of
coordination overhead
but you'd be surprised by how many
first-class creative fans you've got
so um up until now
hinotoni and heart challengers art music
video art has both been made by
the glorious one and only mama
nissan and i'm so happy
that she did that for me and
she's just the thing is she's so easy to
work with
so in some way i wish i could just only
go with her forever
because it's just so simple and easy and
uncomplicated with her
and she gets my vision and i love her
style
but then again i am
forcing myself to go with other artists
for
upcoming projects because
i personally also want some more variety
in the looks of my music videos so
yeah there i will i will go with other
artists as well don't worry but it's
just mama i don't need the sun it's just
so easy to work with
this is so such a relief yeah but no
there will be
other uh artists involved as well
thank you for your question and i am i
am fine thank you
hello what would you do if when
you died but you couldn't be reborn
i would first of all
never leave kelly's side as a ghost
i would be like because she can
obviously see me
now yeah my first my best thought when i
read when i read that question was also
i would be dead i wouldn't do anything
but then i realized i could be a ghost
and spoop spook around so i'm gonna
annoy kelly
and then i will um haunt
people who have
not been nice to me
i will haunt them until the end of their
lives
oh nice yup
i think i found good use of my ghostness
but
unfortunately this will never happen
uh would you like to do another little
crashes team of members
yes yes i want to do it
that was uh very fun and i know you guys
liked it a lot too
let's do it again hi girl i love your
streams if you could go on a vacation
together with everyone in her life and
where would you go
and what would you all do of course
obviously we all want to meet up in
japan
at some point that would be awesome and
probably inevitable
um but besides japan i wish we could
like
maybe it would it would be awesome i i
don't think it'll happen
because it takes a lot of organizing and
all that and everyone taking time off
but i feel like it would be amazing
if like at one year or second year
um anniversary we could take
a week off and together just go to
some beach paradise some vacation
paradise some some beautiful beach
for a week and just relax
throw our phones away
except for taking cute pictures but just
you know
don't don't don't even stream
and maybe prepare some videos beforehand
so that you know we get our quota
going but no streaming just
just you know going on a little trip
together and
relaxing that would be cool
that would be nice
[Music]
if you had to describe each ian member
as a character from friends who would
be who and why so for this i love
friends but i need a visual thing
uh to do this okay
so um
okay is there there's uh let's
start with phoebe pb is
a very specific very funny
kind of weird person
who could that be wait this is six
people by the way
phoebe
[Music]
you're you're mew
this is so difficult well then let's
let's
first think about it a little bit more
then there's uh uh
uh wait okay joey
joey is kind of uh an idiot but in a
good way in a funny way he's kind of the
comedian
i don't know you guys say good eyes
yeah okay i can see that i love joey by
the way
so no hate yeah okay good nice jelly
okay
um chandler chandler
is how would you describe chandler
chancellorism
he seems uh kind of you guys think
chandler is amen so yeah chandler is
sarcastic
ah callie kelly
wait my chat uh like is having issues
count yeah i see that i guess i see that
chandler could be count yeah kelly
i can't see her in any of the other
girls
anyway yeah then
ross ross is kind of
how would you how would you explain
ross's personality
here is rachel
you think so ross is
derpy
smart dummy
russ kelly's more like ross
rachel's ammo rachel is on it
i i can't i can't see that no rachel
um this is so difficult i think they're
very different from us i can't make
these decisions
you guys think about it and then come
with the final results to me okay
that's your homework and i will not
forget about the homework
next do you have any ideas for outfits
you'd like to have i thought it would be
funny to see you in the colonel
standards inspired outfit
isn't that what i'm wearing right now i
don't know maybe not i guess not
also while you're uh reading this i
might as well ask is there only one
usual room or are there multiple ones
uh for future outfits i feel like
well some obviously some casual uh
outfit
would be nice then something
more elegant would be nice
and maybe i don't know something idlish
would be nice
maybe a dandel at some point would be
cute
like there's a formal traditional attire
at the other would be cute
[Music]
a chicken suit no some kind of like idol
wait did i just say that i already said
that i think
japanese traditional clothes would be
cute too
and
[Music]
um emil dirty outfit black
version of kiara
like like emo scene kit kiana
and then oh wouldn't it be fun to have
like like a theme
costume party like one one member gets
like a matress one gets like a like a
shrine maiden mikko outfit
one member gets a school uniform one
member gets a
i don't know vampire outfit one member
gets a witch outfit like as if you're
going to a costume party or something
like that
that would be cute
magical girl outfit oh that would be
cute too
i hope we get a lot of outfits in the
future a lot
yeah or like all of us could get a
school uniform at some point
anyway and then usual room so the thing
is there's only one usual room but
you're always alone in that usual room
so if i if i
send in like 100 people everyone still
gets
like to be alone because
the door to the usual room is at the
same time
a very very complicated system
to millions and millions of dimensions
each usual room is its own dimension so
you open the door sending 100 people but
each person
gets in their own user room which is in
some way only one room
yes you are alone in there yes of course
you thought you were going to have fun
and have a party nah
the yours in the room is not there to
have fun you dare to be alone
and think about what you have done
i noticed that you always not aware of
it when callie was making her moves
so my question is why are you simply
being oblivious towards kelly's advances
uh honestly i don't
i don't remember or recall any moment
where she ever
made a move on me what
so i don't know what you're talking
about uh we'll care if we ever add
phoenix and waffles to mario chicken
and waffles is a good pair but i would
like to try the combo with phoenix as
possible
so i only talked about this dish before
chicken and waffles
it's a work where's that from again
chicago or what where where is this dish
from again
i think it's a crazy idea
to eat that together in one dish
the american south i i ate of the fall
because my friend wanted me to eat it it
was
okay but i want to get it separately
but we can i guess we can implement it
in our menu
i guess so
[Music]
okay oh yeah
but i would always eat it separately
it's
[\h__\h] oh god damn it no
wait i clicked the wrong button and now
i need to verify myself again
that i am not a robot one second
i am not robot uh i'm phoenix no i'm not
human
see this is a problem with those
captures it says i am human like
he proved that you're human well the
thing is i'm not human
but i'm also not a robot so this is kind
of like racist
these captains are racist like what
about the phoenixes what about the
deaths out there
what about all of us huh
how racist but okay
what don't you agree
what about me
oh sh okay we go
okay one second let me move that up
that's a big one again it's japanese
[Music]
foreign
yo
[Music]
in the past seven months i feel like
you've grown a lot in terms of your
talents
uh as a live streamer such as the game
skill and games like near what's
happening on mario kart
in what way they believe you've gone
since you started this job well as i've
mentioned yes i've definitely like
learned so much like my whole setup has
become so professional
like i got a mixer i got a stream deck i
got better headphones i got
uh you know this whole setup with the
camera i got obs
instead of streamlabs i started out with
streamlabs because streamlabs just
looked prettier but now in obs
i know how obs works properly i know how
to do like a
color key chroma key and i know
like so much more stuff my microphone is
professional
so yeah um i'm glad i improved with all
that
and other than that um
i've ah that's a good question how i've
grown since i've started this job
like personality wise i'm not sure have
i
have i grown
um
one thing that i i've noticed is that
i'm just so much more um
have to say in english fly sick like i i
work
so hard because i'm so passionate about
this
and before i was like really lazy
like it was really hard to get me to
work on something
um because i just didn't have the
motivation or the inspiration
and even if then it would only last like
one or two days and then i would
go back into being lazy but now
diligent maybe now i'm just like
constantly streaming every day for hours
and hours and hours and it's been
like this for over half a year now and
i'm just so impressed with myself
because
that is something that i had big issues
with before
so yeah i'm happy that
it is like this because i didn't expect
it to
be like this i didn't think i would be
streaming that often as i've said before
since we have like a minimum of of like
three times delivering content per
week i thought i would be around the
minimum
i would maybe upload a video and do two
short streams per week and that's it but
no
i'm so passionate about it and i want to
do my best at it so
i've dedicated my full
time every day for her life
um it's crazy it's crazy i don't have
time for anything else anymore which is
actually kind of sad
um continuing i hope you're doing well
canada if it's not the personal do you
remember the most tragic way you've died
in one of your past lives didn't have
anything to do with
part-time warrior business so there's a
lot of
a lot of stories how i've done in the
past
and but the reason why i i
liked uh i saved this one is because i
wanted to remind myself to do a specific
stream
where i share a lot of stories
of how i've died and how i've lived in
previous
lives before actually i was not gonna
answer it
today but i want to keep this for the
future
and i noticed how you make mistakes and
aspects for help when
speaking english are you still starting
to improve your english no i'm not
studying at all the last time i was
studying
english was back in school and yeah
nowadays it's just me picking up some
things every now and then from you guys
um but i feel like i'm not really
learning much more i'm like i i don't
want to be like cocky but i feel like
i'm
pretty damn good at english the only
thing that we need to fix every now and
then is my pronunciation
and sometimes i forget some words but i
would say i'm pretty good
yeah it's just refining some refinements
do you guys think though that my english
improved since like
six months ago i feel like generally
my english is pretty much the same but
the way i speak on stream might have
changed a little bit
because i feel like it had a lot to do
with being nervous and all that as well
in the beginning you guys say yes
all of you say yes i've improved father
was your first language frankie i'm so
happy to hear that
vocabulary expanded
all these comments oh my god what
i think your talking has improved just a
tiny bit if
you're better with figures of speech
like puns and stuff oh
gotten a bit smoother but that might be
comfort
i think your vocabulary has probably
gotten better well
maybe you i think it's it's not so much
my vocabulary being increased i think
it's more that i'm
more used to streaming now and speaking
english
that it comes uh
that these words come to my mind
more easily like before i knew those
words but
maybe i i didn't use them uh because i
couldn't think of them or
because i used easier words but now
maybe uh
i speak a bit more uh articulate i don't
know
maybe i'm more confident i don't know
i don't think i improved much though i
mean i was already good to begin with so
i i don't have water to drink my my
throat is starting to hurt but i don't
want to leave right now
[Music]
is it okay if i get uh something to
drink real quick
go get water okay don't leave stay here
[Music]
oh my cats are so cute
hey i have a cat i'm holding my cat
she's so warm because she's been
sleeping
my baby oh
which one i was holding smoothie me and
smoothie have been cuddling so much
and john cruz is also just super cute
okay guys continuing
catching me onto the microphone and
normally they're pretty quiet like a
smoothie only gets like really really
annoying
when she wants uh wet food besides that
she doesn't talk much
anyway um
so here's a big one good evening
so i hope you've had a wonderful day
with the kitty cats yes
i've had a wonderful day for them thank
you
you've created a fast empire with
hundreds of thousands of chickens
at your command and disposal but there
are a few members and followers that
claim to be something else like
chairs or bear bears or cats or even
other birds like eagles owls ducks and
keys
my question is how do you feel about
these other animals in kfp
and are they legit if you have confirmed
them to be
the animal they claim what does that
mean for the memberships
if they have one are they adopting a
chicken with the membership fee so the
chicken will grow as food
in their place that is uh
such a good question um
that that is such a good question
wait i i i missed this one i'm gonna
answer that one too oh no
no i did i did after that oh yeah um
i will say
they are
indeed
chickens but they
think that they are something else just
don't tell them just
let them think what they want to think
they're just a bit confused but in
reality they're all chickens
the moment they join the membership
especially then they're
definitely chickens but some chickens
are just confused and don't have as much
brain power as the
others so um they're not so
self-aware let's just say it that way
delusional chickens
but it's okay i i like i i don't have no
i have no problem with them thinking or
something else that's okay
let's let's uh adjust to them do you
know how like like lincoln
like an old grandpa who
well i don't know it's talking some
weird stuff
you know we're just gonna adjust to our
grandparents and be like yes yes grandma
yes grandpa
yes yes i know you are a car
apparently according to pre-chat but in
reality you're a chicken
about the birds about the other birds
there might be some
not chicken birds uh mixed in uh
those could really be those birds but
the people who are claiming
their chairs or bears no but the chase
for example
a can't beat chair is basically just a
chicken serving as a chair
he's letting me sit on him now that's
that's
it is what it is he he's a chair in
in his functionality
he just you know bends down and lets me
sit on him
it is what it is but then there's some
people who think they they are
i don't know a cat and in reality
they're a chicken but it's okay we're
just gonna say they're
oh okay yep i didn't
let them have their little joy
let them have it
first of all i love you so much and to
know that your personality and
interesting content always keeps us kfb
and players coming back for more thank
you i love you
question if you wear a pokemon gym
leader what type of pokemon would you
choose the battle of
fire
are you ever going to use a boxing ring
minecraft that's so funny thank you for
bringing that up
that is a long time ago that i built
that uh boxing ring
um i
built it for the polka senpai collab
because uh she was supposed to come to
the en minecraft series i was supposed
to lead her
and i uh was like damn
our survey is still pretty boring
i need to add something interesting so i
quickly built a boxing ring
where we will uh we were going to fight
and have a death match yes
however it never came to it because the
tour never really happened
because my game was just crashing the
whole time while i was streaming
and unfortunately but nowadays
it seems stable i mean i haven't really
collabed in minecraft
for a long
time except for the no one on the
japanese server but that has
seemed fine so on the
answer we should give it a try again
maybe yeah maybe i should invite
uh poka senpai again yes yes yes to give
her a proper chiller
i've been wanting to do that eventually
anyway
yeah yeah let's go do it at some point
after realizing that it turned into
turned into a chicken the moment i
joined cafe i went into a philosophical
crisis within the various themes i
thought about my own mortality as a
chicken
so i'd like to ask if you don't mind
what vision of death do you have as a
phoenix has this changed over the
millennia
and what advice would you give us simple
mortise to live happily
well that is a very deep uh question
i obviously
do not fear death and
don't don't think much about i mean i
fear
i feared it before in a sense that
like whenever i died i
ended up in a different dimension and i
had to start all over again and over and
over and over but i was also at the same
time looking forward to dying because i
could meet
cali every time i was dead but a little
bit only for a little bit so in some way
i was looking forward to it and in other
ways i wasn't looking forward to it but
it was fun to like always explore new
places and
um learn more and looking looking for
other phoenix's you know
because uh most dimensions i ended up in
didn't have any other phoenix's and i
was
usually the only one but sometimes i met
other phoenixes
anyway yeah
so i'm probably not the right person to
ask this question
i i'm not sure what advice to give you
but and if i put myself in your shoes
as an immortal i would probably be
scared
and but i would probably just try to not
think about it as long as i can
and i think that's just how most people
live their life i guess
right just not think about it
until you get confronted with it
and i think i guess that's just okay i
guess that's okay
uh read the rules please
thank you
no thoughts had empty i think you
shouldn't live life
thinking about death the whole time
because
i mean it's good to live each day
thinking that it could end soon so that
you will use it better
because yeah it could legit end any day
and you don't want to regret it i mean
if you're dead then you can't regret it
but
just make make best use of it and make
your dreams come true try
try travel a lot and stuff yeah
i guess so and just don't think about it
yes
[Music]
um
what game seasons have you had game
systems
um uh so
okay i've had very long time ago
i remember having a nintendo 64.
i barely remember it but i remember it
i don't think i've ever had a
playstation
i think i if we had one
then i don't think i used it and it
might have only been playstation 2
maybe then i definitely had a gamecube
and i loved the
gamecube and we had a after that we had
a nintendo
wii but i've never had a nintendo wii u
or something like that and i've had
nintendo ds
and playstation portable and nintendo
3ds
and after that i guess
only came in nintendo switch
all kinds of game boys i guess obviously
all kinds of game boys
yeah ah good times good times
hi kenna i want to ask have you ever
heard of sunderland chronicles series
well i've talked about
uh accessibility a lot of times yes i
have and i guess i plan to play it at
some point
when have you felt reverse cult shock
being in australia
after living in japan for extended
period of time i ended up
waiting the full time on crosswalks when
i go back home to us because everyone
does it here in japan
to be honest this time around
i haven't really experienced any kind of
culture
shock because i already like i've done
this before
um but i was
really like and i i just i adjusted very
well again this time around
but what i was weirdly scared about is
going to the supermarket
you know because now i was just like
scared of doing things wrong
because you know each country now has
different kind of like rules i guess on
how to handle the current situation i
just didn't want to do anything bad and
get yelled
at and so i was very nervous before
going to the supermarket but everything
was okay
if people take it very lightly
everything was okay uh and everything
else is just i don't know i haven't
done much anyway besides going to the
supermarket
um no
so reverse culture shock really
nothing to be honest it's just
i'm i'm used to it i guess and nothing
really much happened anyway
[Applause]
[Music]
what kind of game they want to
collaboration with olavian
i suppose you mean like actually being
integrated into the game
[Music]
brothers can we yeah one whole live
member
into super smash brothers can we do
it can we get the invitation who gets
invitations we're probably going to be
like soda senpai
if anyone summarizes
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah like one character that can turn
into different kind of characters
um that would be cool other than that
i mean it's this is probably really
unrealistic
[Music]
but i don't think tails off does that
kind of thing
like including like doing crossovers
like that
i know it's unrealistic
[Music]
what could be realistic though
what's something that could actually
[Music]
happen
that some kind of gotcha game
[Music]
any kind of gotcha game i guess they do
a lot of those
[Music]
crossovers fortnite
minecraft i dude does minecraft do
crossovers like that squirtly
again according to
world of warships
we're talking about games that would
actually seem possible that they would
include us
and i feel um
final fantasy 14 soho please yeah like
you know the uh touhou spell that we
played
it would be cool if we would be
characters in such a game like any kind
of like touhou
project um game
not the not the og i guess but like any
kind of like you know side game
yeah ah club
penguin what
fall guys oh yeah i guess uh
got into four guys that's pretty dope
um maybe your whole life english can get
into focus too
i am just so bad
because every time i get i
i played i played fall guys two times on
my channel
and both times it was not a pleasant
experience
so i i
i don't i don't
anyway next question
what was the most rebellious thing you
did as a kid i think
i might be wrong mama if you're watching
this stream correct me if i'm wrong but
i think i wasn't very rebellious
i didn't drink alcohol i didn't smoke
i didn't even try i hated all those
things i didn't go
party i didn't go out in the night i
didn't do anything like that
the only thing that you could maybe call
rebellions
is me every once in a while which is
something i guess
every child does uh
acting as if i was sick so that i don't
have to go to school but not because i
just didn't want to go to school
because i had laziness or so but it was
evil because
of getting bullied and me not like
feeling well
in in those situations
or because of a test that i was very
very scared of
so yeah uh
other than that rebellious
i i wouldn't describe me being
rebellious i mean every freaking
teenager goes through some
kind of face but rebellious
i i don't think so um
yeah i don't think that was rebellious
although mom correct me if i'm wrong
when you make your 3dw
can we build you 3d objects to interact
with if needs
be for it casey will truly even build
you an eu based studio for a whole lot
of
talents or something like that um i
gotta be honest
that's very sweet of you to offer and uh
that would be cool somehow if we could
implement something like that
but if i ever get to get to do a 3dw
i think for the 3dw we wouldn't
accept any kind of like fan-made
stuff it would i think i'll be made
in-house
but maybe like after that uh
if we like after that would ever get
like home 3d
then maybe we could implement something
like that
after that i think it might be a
possibility just
how i like to use uh some
improvements for my stream whenever i
receive something from you guys
like the opening and the ending or uh
how for example kelly has been using the
controller hands
uh yeah i've i haven't really seen
anything like that for the whole life of
japan talent is happening
but i think if you guys were to make
anything in 3d that we could use
and i won't say it's impossible
i honestly don't know but i don't see
why not
and but probably not for a debut
afterwards possibly
and good morning casper crew hi guys
growing up in the ancient times trillion
of years ago
did you ever play with toys as a child
if so what
are some of your favorites and do you
still own any uh as we have seen
and heard in my friendship books
and the beginning of the stream uh i
early on was already playing uh a lot on
the pc
i was playing a lot of these um like
barbie online games where you can like
style yourself
up put on makeup and clothes and all
that and then go
go hang out or
[Music]
i don't know i think there was like some
kind of polly
pocket on the watergate well i don't
even know i don't even remember
all these things like girly games yeah
[Music]
yeah and i uh other than that
do you guys know volleyball kid
other than that i can't remember much
when i what toys i played with as a
child but i don't own anything anymore
no
i definitely don't own anything from my
childhood anymore except in
those friendship books yeah which are
not really a toy but
i also really really really was into
diddle and i was collecting all these
little sheets and
blocks and all that kind of stuff yeah
and then one one time you know i had
this whole collection
in uh great what i called school before
junior high school
what's the school before junior high
school grade school
see most of you guys don't know what
diddle is i guess that's there's a thing
that wasn't year round
in switzerland germany and australia and
so on elementary yeah elementary school
in elementary school so i had this this
collection and uh
the other girls in my grade also
were collecting these little sheets
and uh it was really popular and i had
quite a lot i was pretty proud of it and
then there was this one girl
who stole my collection i had it in the
folder
okay and the thing is she was my friend
yeah you're still in my collection
and i was i was never popular in school
to begin with
so the only really thing that i had
going
in grade school was my digital
collection
the only really thing that i could flex
with
sometimes was my dental collector and
then someone stole it and i had to start
from zero that was absolutely horrible
and the thing another thing is i have i
had this
cousin
who was
possibly a bit spoiled
a great only child
raised by my aunt and
a boy and he
had millions and millions and millions
and millions and millions of little
sheets in his collection
and his whole room was full of it so i
wanted
link i would have appreciated some
support
some sharing but nah
nope
nope now he was around the same age as
me
maybe like one or two years old i'm not
sure
yeah ah
the whole little face was horrible
horrible horrible
continuing hello kiara in the whole
attack of
you i wonder i wanted this stream to
only be one hour but wow now we're at
two hours
yup almost and you talk about having a
goal to indoors what is your goal now
you guys keep asking what is the deal
then google it
it's so hard to google
it's written d-i-d-d-l yes
a german version of hello kitty yeah you
could compare it to that yeah
it's mostly like paper but there's like
all kinds of merchandise but mostly
people collected like these
small paper blocks and uh like even
even one piece of paper would be traded
and you would put it into a folder and
some of them even smelled and some of
them were sparkly and all that
and yeah some of them were really
rare and cool i would be
so excited whenever a new design would
come out yeah it's just pieces of paper
they're stuffy still yeah and and pens
and
all kinds of stuff it was so popular um
i get like a notepad yeah yeah but uh
people would mostly collect like one
piece of paper from
that notepad and like trade it like when
you have a like a block then you give
one of
one piece of paper to someone and and
yeah
trade
my goal now why did i pick that question
i don't even know the answer
uh like there's no like
no like um super inspiring big huge goal
that i can really think of right now but
just
like clear goals that i have in front of
me right now
is getting out and never single
and getting a 3dw and
traveling again
either to japan or anywhere else you
obviously can't be world's domination
[Music]
getting out those covers that i've been
planning on
getting more and more hello talks done
and improving
in all kinds of ways
i don't know
i don't know reaching 1 million
subscribers which is soon
let's go
how are you kiara everything is okay
in the land down under named
my emu after you
love your stream take care
so are you serious in fake australia
people actually have animals as pets
or are you just trying to be funny i
need to know
i need to know
please tell me do you guys
no yes i do
yes i do
they have emu forms well okay i get that
oh my god if you really did that then
you are wonderful
thank you for naming your emma kiana
that is so cute that is so dope please
send me a picture
if it's true then you have to send me
i'm waiting i'm waiting
send me a picture of kiara
yay and i'm not sure if anybody asked
you this question already but
but if you could have any other job
other than her life what would it be
and i would if
if it doesn't have to be realistic i
would love to be an illustrator
professionally
[Music]
and just live from that that that would
have
been amazing that was my goal originally
for a while anyway not waitress though
uh an artist you know illustrator
for rpg games but i think
eventually i'll pick it up again that
hobby and uh
stop with the waitress
eventually i'll pick it up again and
hopefully it will go well but i don't
know
i don't know if it will hmm
with the audition of halloween clothes
what is your advice for your cool guys
that are preparing for appearing
honestly once you have uh your layout
done because we have to prepare all that
kind of stuff on our own
i have to prepare my first streaming
layout on my own and
if you wanted the logo you have to do it
on your own like all this stuff it
doesn't come like
they don't give it to you for free and
this my own logo that i have down
here on the bottom right side now
also is not something i just got gifted
to
it's stuff that i pay for um
so anyway in the beginning i obviously
didn't have the
the funds for it that's okay um
just try your best to prepare something
nice if you don't have the funds for a
try
i mean it's okay it doesn't have to look
super super awesome
and maybe get some help from
if you debut with someone else
get some help from genme so get some
help from us your senpais and to
build something together if you can't do
it on your own
so that's that's about you know and then
plan your debut that's about the
preparation that you need to do that's
about it unless you want to be crazy and
and release an ep on debut
but besides that i just want to say
enjoy the time the free time
and the the quiet
silence before the storm
enjoy it treasure it maybe do it like me
and go on a trip before it go on a
vacation because you won't be able to
have a proper vacation for a long time
just enjoy it just chill
and yeah
yep enjoy being uh
the time enjoy the time when you're
still
normal don't have all these
streams that you need to do every
goddamn day
sounds like uh i i honestly enjoy this
doing this every day it's awesome but
before you dive into it
enjoy the time for it enjoy the the
whole
form
because who knows when it will be that
quiet again
and enjoy your privacy
and uh oh oh try to uh serious talk
if that's something you cherish and
think is important
then try to protect your
privacy yes that was a real
real talk
next question i'm fairly new to how
davian and i love
everyone i started watching uh
everyone's minecraft videos and in inaz
she said hanekawa is your favorite
monochromatic character which makes
sense
i noticed in your dnw that you also love
lunatalia so i have to ask who is best
i've mentioned this before my favorite
character in monotony i love them all
but my favorite would be
nadiko and i also love
hachikoji and sodachi oikoda
yes yes yes nakiko but she's so she's my
favorite character
but she's so insane she's so crazy that
i i'm not sure if i would give her the
title of that girl
she as much as i love her she doesn't
exactly fit the description of best girl
[Music]
party cleansing gets pretty close
to best girl i would say
i also love shin i love them i love them
all
such a great anime if you haven't seen
it please watch it
please watch it it's there's so many
seasons too
like one thing that i love when i pick
up a new series i
i'm very happy oh yeah that's good super
chatting hope you don't get lost
and one thing i love is if if a series
that i start picking up
already has a lot of uh
seasons so that i can binge watch
as much as possible hmm
ah my face hurts i'm talking so much
wow and i still got a bunch of questions
man
and i was like worried that i wouldn't
have enough and stress myself and
delayed the stream oh my god
um when life translating for whole talk
do you translate directly from japanese
to english or do you go from japanese to
german to
i go there do people think i do that i
go directly from japanese to english
and i i write it all down i write some
memos and
actually
uh do you wanna do you wanna hear
what kind of
memos i take very professional
translator
one sec let's see
it's just i tried to type really
really fast so
it's sometimes actually
surprisingly a lot of sentences i know
that professional translators don't
really use
sentences when they like write down
uh what they're uh translating
but like for example
um
[Music]
okay let me
let me just show you a picture
[Music]
wait
wait oh this why won't you
why don't why won't you not why won't
you just let me throw in the picture
like that
okay i'll do it complicated okay so for
example
here uh her hometown traditional song
i forgot how to read that now even
though i wrote it
she wants everyone to know about it
early her typo
so she released the debut she can't
really talk about it since it's
complicated she likes uh
uh mean so close songs
and she wants to sing more like that she
wants to do more in that language and
style there was an english version too
so there is a meaning to it please don't
think to hide about it please enjoy it
that's that's that's such a simple uh
it's not professional because
i am because i am not professional
uh but it's good enough enjoy enjoy
lots of typos and chaotic chaotic memos
yeah but i'm trying my best okay
i'm trying my best i hope
like i also i also want to apologize if
there's like ever mistakes to my
translation or if it's not like 100
correct i of course
aspire and try my best to make it as
correct and
and as accurate as possible but i'm just
human and i'm not a professional
translator but
i would say that generally i i
no i i would say i would claim that i
have never wrongly translated someone
um maybe there's like some tiny tiny
nuance uh differences
but generally i think i've never uh
translated them wrongly
yeah okay oh continuing i'm not gonna do
much more questions i guess i think i'm
gonna end it soon
and when are we gonna get a family
portrait drawn potential i'm not talking
about the chickens we all know what they
look like that's boring and that would
take too
much time i want to see time to draw
herself with kelly and their children
and maybe
a special hookup i designed by genji
what would you want it to look like
so i want to do more drawing streams of
course but i don't know i don't feel so
confident about my art and
and uh streams kind of distract me and
make me feel nervous about my art even
more
but i do want to do more um so there
there will be more
and i want to draw the hello and girls
that i want to draw myself as well
and you the idea of giving hugh papa
like some kind of like persona is
pretty cool because i guess he doesn't
really have one
um like when he was in minecraft he gave
himself
uh like the uh blackrock shooter
hatsune miku um outfit
so i guess in some way that is his
persona
if anything but he doesn't really have
one does he
so maybe i should make up one but i
wonder because
i can only really draw girls i wonder if
he would have a
problem with it if i would make him into
a girl
rather than a guy
because i can only draw girls i don't i
don't know
about that
make him into a cute girl
[Music]
make everything into cute girl rule 63
what is rule 63 that's something
little
what's wrong 63
gen gender bent huh
oh okay why is that a real 63
wait in what book or what
anyway whatever thank you for your
question
uh hey keep up the good work i may not
have the membership or donated but i
will try to support you in any way this
might be my only way to communicate to
you
see this is one of the reasons why i
wanted to do these marshmallows
is that some people who just don't have
can't afford like sending
these super chats and still have the
possibility to
get read out loud and and send longer
messages so
i'm glad that you sent a marshmallow
thank you thank you for
uh taking the opportunity
for the question any parts to collab
with other youtubers or personalities
from other branches companies are in
these how long does it take to prepare
either
cover originals okay let's go one by one
oh my god let's go one by one
first of all the first question oh yeah
i do have interest
in it i don't know when is it if it's
ever gonna happen at the moment i'm just
focusing
way more on her life but eventually like
i have mentioned before that i
personally like baby because she's hot
and i love her voice and
the way she speaks and she swears a lot
too i feel like we could get along well
she's cute and now she now we even have
the same papa
soon even though you might know her she
has like a 3d model but now she got a
live 2d model which is debuting soon
and it uh it turns out to be rigged by
the same papa as mine
so we're going to be half sisters
i i just like her uh
sense of humor and she's just sexy
um i like her um
other than that i'm not like
not open to it but at the moment i'm
just focused on
where i am right now
and how long does it take to prepare
even a couple original song if you
do not want to disclose it how about how
long it takes to prepare for karaoke
but for kind of okay i also want to
practice a lot each time so that i don't
disappoint you and that the clips turn
out good
so for karaoke i also practice like
hours and hours because i want to sing
new songs for you instead of singing the
same songs
over and over and over again so
preparation for karaoke usually takes
like five to eight hours
yeah it's a lot actually and for your
covers depends on if it's a solo cover
or a collab cover collab cover
in my experience takes quite long
because
of the schedules of whoever
you work with um
which takes some time and then the video
and art creation also takes like quite
some times i would say
the the beginning of like when i choose
a song
and who to do it with until the point of
releasing it
could take three
two two to
two to four months for a cover
and for an original alone
solo original from the moment where i
say okay we're doing a next song with
this person
with this uh producer uh
there's a minimum of
usually five months to
six months
something around that uh
because for like original songs it's
just way more um
planning and uh way more involvement
[Music]
so you never know i might already be
working on something right now
you're planning that earlier he was a
bit of an exception
but he don't thought he was a bit rushed
as well
uh he totally didn't have that much time
yeah
i started planning hirotori after i
debuted that but now it's like
we have to plan this alien okay we can't
do it when kino tony anymore so
hard challenger i started playing ha
planning heart challenger
uh right after hinotoni
yes and who knows maybe i'm planning
something right now
and what is the fun process in making
each week's schedule
i probably think way too much about it
i try to cater to a lot of time zones
uh and i try to
have lots of variety in the games i play
and then in the streams i do so
yeah especially for this week's schedule
i as i wrote on twitter i was wrecking
my brain
i feel like like gura ahmed and ina
have like this this specific time window
where they all usually always stream in
and they rarely rarely move to another
time window
um which i wish i would have done
from the beginning somehow because if i
would start that now i already have like
so much of an audience that's like all
scattered all over the world all over
all kinds of time zones but if i would
stop
having so much variety in streaming time
now and would only stream in a specific
like five hour time window then all
these fans that i had before would be
like
kiana why and i would also feel like i'm
so sorry i don't want to leave you guys
i don't want you guys to never come ever
again so
i have to keep this up i have to
continue streaming and all kinds of
times
but now at the moment it's okay because
sometimes i stream at 1 pm my time and
sometimes it's free
storm at 10 pm my time it's okay
genuinely for me but in some sometimes i
wish i had just one specific time window
where
um i always stream in i wish but now
it's kind of too late
to do that because i should have done
that from the beginning
but it's okay i like having uh an
audience
all over the world my
my uh my my peeps from
the the land down under i will never
forget you guys
you stayed with me a lot while i was uh
streaming during japanese prime time
and my my uh fans from asian countries
yeah thank you guys
and now i got a lot of new european
viewers i think as well
and my american viewers canadian
everywhere everywhere thank you all so
much
i'm trying my best to continue making my
streams uh
watchable for anyone if possible
how many things uh could you ask i'm
gonna skip that question
lastly sorry for being too greedy or
selfish how to convince myself that i'm
not useless in this world
you're not useless no one's useless
everyone has a
cause or purpose you might not know
about it but everyone has a role to fail
in this world you're not useless
please and also i i also
sometimes think or thoughts that way
but and it's okay
you don't anyone has that those kind of
faces it's okay to think like that
but i'm sure you're not and i'm sure
there's a lot of people who appreciate
you and maybe you just don't realize it
and i'm sure there's many people who um
appreciate you
and want you in their life you're not
useless
no one's
[Music]
oh
yes
[Music]
um
this uh japanese mirror was asking about
how to
relieve stress and and and uh
it's not exactly stress but like when
you look too much
at pc and phones and phone screens and
all that kind of stuff
how to relieve that kind of stress
and maybe like pain in your
eyes and says that
a certain type of uh chocolate in japan
always uh because they're so stressed
out and like
uh exhausted strained a certain type of
chocolate in japan
looks like cali to them
so asking me what what i recommend to
relieve that kind of stress and screen
fatigue yes yes that's it
and i need to say like honestly i don't
know
but i guess in japan what i did a lot is
going to massages and going to spa
and since japanese people love
taking baths i'm not more of a shower
type of person but
i love large bath bombs so i recommend
those a lot i love
lush so much in general and the
bathrooms
are awesome so try them out yo
okay i still like maybe five more
questions um
my voice is exhausted too
is this streamer you are now the kind of
streamer you wanted to be from the
beginning
no no but
i think it's better than what i wanted
to be
because in the beginning as i mentioned
before i thought i would only stream
like three days a week
and be more of a video person rather
than streamer i couldn't imagine
streaming the whole time
i really thought because uh we were told
that we can also just upload videos we
don't have to stream the whole time
but turns out editing videos is a pain
in the ass
and takes a lot of time and streaming is
just kind of easier
and i love the interaction that we have
live here
and it's it's so different so ever since
i
started streaming after my debut
review guys i
just completely my idea of what i wanted
to do what i was planning to do
changed a lot
so yeah it's definitely i'm definitely
very different from what i
thought i would turn out
and i like character wise as well
i'm not exactly the kind of character
like person personality that i
i aspired to be
uh i don't know i was i was more like
i wanted to be cute says old type of
girl
i wanted to be like a more and more type
of girl with
a cute voice and like
i don't know a lonely face maybe
i don't want to be like i don't know
i wanted to be cute
um
[Music]
that turned out well shut up
you say so if you say exactly
um i'm i'm saying it's alright you're
cute
you are though what really
not i mean maybe but not the way i
wanted to be originally but i'm okay
it's okay it's just
it's okay the way everything is now
is probably the way it should be
i'm safe but i recommend it i didn't i
mean i didn't recommend her
i just said she's my personal preference
and when when we talk about v env
individual ones i i just feel like she
she fits me
uh um
honestly when i see me i i i get help
she gives me hope that being
loot uh like saying loot things and
and swearing a lot is not a bad thing
she gives me hope
um since it's almost six months i would
like to thank you for continuously
making me happy you're welcome
i started making new friends with people
like v gamer judas and your most
annoying enemy oh who could that
possibly be
anyways your free was also coming soon
and i want to give you some special
something special for you basically the
other question that i answered pretty
much answers this one
uh also it's interesting how you say
my pretty w i didn't know about it what
am i reading
soon what i didn't know about that one
well good snow i'm gonna go and get
ready
uh but yeah same answer um probably not
for the 3d w
but if that ever happens but maybe in
the future would be cool
uh if i could implement that is that
jago
telling me about my w that i don't even
know about
cool i didn't know
cancer if you could hand pick one member
from each generation whole life to be
part of your own team
to fight and save the world out of
dragon quest who would you pick and why
noah senpai because she just fits in
like look at her foreign
in her life which was another question
by the way that i think i didn't say it
uh but fernando also just also fits i
almost almost
honestly hold my phone first generation
is whole like fantasy and they just fit
in there so well all of them
i mean heckler but doesn't seem very
strong though to be honest
lucian senpai in senpai who they are
senpai
known as senpai seem kind of strong
but my beloved peculiar senpai
i'm not sure how how
like she's good in games she can kick
gas and games but if she were to
actually fight herself
i am very sorry becca at some point
you can come along anyway because you'll
be the the cute
main protagonist
that uh i run after
and uh love and protect i will protect
you
come to think of it i'm also with my
with my story in my my shield i'm also
very
perfect to be in that kind of situation
cool cool with a whole live
fantasy third generation did you know
that hawaii first generation
hall of japan fourth generation is like
uh called
all live fantasy did you know did you
know
noodle armstroke shut up
i got fire down i got a belt and i can
transform and
i will burn you to ashes okay
because once i am in in such a situation
where i have to save the world and i'm
sure that my papa will allow me to
transform
okay okay okay uh
i think you know what we have to maybe
uh
skip some questions
um because i need to
end it soon
and you have an incredible look
incredibly strong and beautiful singing
by some
notable families of mine being your
karaoke because of you and into the
unknown thank you
those are fun to sing have you gotten
vocal training in the past if you aren't
currently receiving any would you
consider doing so in the future
currently i'm not receiving any but i
have received a lot of
vocal training and other kind of
training like dance lessons
in the past yes vocal
training was in the beginning kind of
tough
because uh there was a lot of breathing
lessons involved
uh but after
after a while i kind of got the hang out
of it
and i was not alone in that local
training so
my teacher would sometimes even tell the
other girls
to uh like
copy me sometimes even like in specific
i'm not sure what what it was again
but uh
things i did very well it seems
yeah flexing flexing a little bit
wow wow wow yes
i was doing well i think the teacher
liked me
it was fun having those kind of lessons
and
uh although i did have a lot of trouble
in the dance lesson
uh in the in the beginning also at least
like
[Music]
but it got better it got a little better
like now now i can learn a
choreography really quick and uh
um i think i i mean i haven't done it in
a while but i think i can dance better
than i did back then in the beginning
and uh
i thought i didn't have a problem with
the teacher
because uh the teacher was a a japanese
and uh to me back then it was all
you know kind of confusing and new
and uh
i i there's a big difference between how
you interact with a teacher
in my country versus how you interact
with a teacher
in japan
in my country when you don't agree with
the teacher when you got any kind of
opinion or
anything at all you want to say you say
it you say it
and you speak out loud and and and yeah
it is very much encouraged encouraged to
have a conversation
now in japan you are supposed to stay
quiet and mostly and
disagreeing with your teacher is
kind of problematic oh
so i mean i didn't really get scolded i
think they were very
considerate of me being
well a foreigner um
and i later on realized that
i might have should have stayed a bit
more quiet
every now and then rather than
always speaking up in the class
being like fat but actually
but there's a reason for that this is
why i did that
this way yes but but but
uh actually
[Music]
hello hello hello hello
oh we're back oh youtube youtube what
did you do
well you got the gist of the story
didn't you
i'm back okay
yeah that was all i wanted to say anyway
and i don't really plan on taking any
more
singing lessons or adolescence i think
what it's is it is it
buffering again
[Music]
back again should we end it here i mean
i wanted to end it now anyway
is this uh gonna continue
like that youtube
[Music]
uh
is
that's a good question and japanese bro
asks
and what is our actual fan name
because kfp is kind of the name
of um our
store our chain but i think we can say
that our general fan name is also kfp
because like
i think you can talk about all of us uh
as kfb as well no it used to be it used
to be kiara fan club
but i changed it to kfb didn't i
it used to be kind of fan club but it is
there was a joke
in that name but it also sounded very
general if you didn't get the joke
so i changed it to uh kfp so it's just
kfb
the
[Music]
all out then you could say kfb employees
but like i mean i mean
if there's like hmm if people talk about
the fandoms of paul lavien
i think people usually say kfp only
anyway
yeah we just which is kfb in general but
you can also
say carefully crew or can't be employees
or whatever i guess
i think kfb is fine
yes we are kfb
and with that uh unfortunately i'm sorry
for
uh all the questions that i couldn't
reach but unfortunately we're coming to
an end
right now thank you all for asking the
questions um
i hope you learned some things maybe
i feel like someone said this uh also in
the marshmallow but
there's there's not much to ask because
i guess i tell you guys
pretty much everything already anyway
but i think the the friendship book
thing was uh definitely something new
uh yeah i do share a lot already so
there's not much new but
i hope you had fun anyway and maybe here
it's one or two new things
i did the doodle thing i guess was also
very new and me being at the rasmus fan
apparently
was very interesting
there might not be many new things but
still
well thank you for coming today tomorrow
is uh minecraft
or uh is the other minecraft stream
yeah okay okay we are going to
continue where we left off and trying to
free
everyone from that house and hope that
they move into the smaller houses as
well
i hope they don't all just run away when
i open the door and i open the gates
we'll work on some things so i'll see
you tomorrow in minecraft um if it's
okay for you i will not read the super
chats
now i'll read them tomorrow after the
minecraft stream but thank you everyone
who sent the super chat thank you so
much i love you well thank you for
support
thank you and everyone who sent the
question also thank you sorry if i
didn't pick you up
i also saw a lot of funny questions in
between that
um were sweet like like like also like
do you need to take a cat break stuff
like that
and a lot a lot of questions also didn't
get picked up because there were things
that i talked about a lot before or were
even answered in
in other q a streams like for example i
i get
questions so often about how to learn a
language
advice on how to learn a language i'm
sorry i'm not picking up those questions
anymore because i answered those like a
million times
so yeah uh thank you though anyway
for sending in your questions
foreign
sometimes i answer a lot on twitter as
well
so if you got like a really really
important question
do you ask me you can also ask me on
twitter sometimes
i might answer i don't know maybe
nope
okay probably speak chicken ass
it's easy to scum
[Applause]
noises
just copy that and then you're good to
go
all right thank you for tuning in please
uh
keep on supporting talking to kiara and
kfc i love you all
and see you tomorrow and in germany
[Music]
hang
bye bye love you
[Music]
foreign