[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
300k 300k
hello hello you can hear me right hello
hello
[Music]
woohoo
celebration sorry for being late okay
thank you for your super chat
thank you sorry for being late i was
still practicing
because today i'm singing for you guys
as you can see i'm
using papa's microphone again
[Music]
mic take one two one two mic
take
so yeah yeah yeah i'm singing uh for you
tonight i
i was um i asked on twitter what you
guys would like to see
for the 300k celebration well i reached
300k right before today's collaboration
which i hope all of you have seen you
know we did a minecraft collaboration
with all the live members and um
that was angular's channel and right
like a few minutes apparently apparently
i i just woke up like
right before the collaboration and then
when i checked twitter it was all full
with like congratulations i was like oh
did we just reach it like a few minutes
before the collaboration
wow thank you everyone for your support
thank you everyone for subscribing
[Music]
thank you so so so so much and i was
really hoping to
reach it before the week ends because
this uh today
or or tomorrow i don't know officially
marks
the one month anniversary too
thank you so much everyone
oh so many people thank you for like
partying with me
so yeah i thought um of course i i would
love to also play some minecraft and
mario kart and this and that but i found
the most fitting thing the most fitting
way to celebrate
this occasion would be with some karaoke
and i chose some actually i think today
i'm only singing new songs i don't think
i'm repeating any song i sang before
but let me let me pour some tea i i got
myself some tea with
with some uh uh
honey because to be honest my throat
doesn't feel so
good today either um both me and kelly
apparently aren't at their bestest right
now
but i want to celebrate
salah i love you
yes t tt it's tea time
celebration i only know the song from
the
from the do you know that the chocolate
snacks
from like celebration not sponsored
i love you okay let me let me see if
this is too hot
i'm actually really sensitive uh when it
comes to drink
drinking hot things like
i'm always so amazed when like i eat
with someone
and they like they eat this burning hot
food or a drink or whatever
and like drink almost drink it like they
just eat it so quickly and i'm like
what is
still too hot
did you hear that
i'm like for real like if i make tea
how long how long does it take you guys
until you drink the tea when you make a
tea for me it's like i wait like 20
minutes
the window the time window between a
hot tea being drinkable for me or
like being too hot or being too cold the
time window is like
so short
five minutes wow you guys are like
badass you all must have like really
thick tongues like burned from so many
hot
things wow
thank you for the super job thank you
for your support everyone thank you for
coming here
so as i just mentioned i prepared many
many many new songs
a lot of anime songs uh one or two
idol songs and one very
very special song from a very
[Music]
but let me just say the person who owns
the song
might be watching later
and i i practiced the song but oh please
excuse me all of these songs i never
really sang before
on stream so i might be messing up a
little bit but
[Music]
i will sing the first time but first let
me do some audio check please i i did
not
i wasn't able to to do anything like
that and in the end it always turns out
to be like
different on stream
[Music]
can you hear me echo
wow
[Music]
and uh what what what was i just saying
oh yeah this stream will be archived
of course i got all the permission don't
worry
okay let me check with you guys
uh no youtube don't show me your ads
skip ad okay i need your
i need everyone's opinion uh
because i don't want to mess up the
audio today
so the audio check show
[Music]
okay could this have been louder or
quieter
why do you didn't even hear that at all
okay you didn't even hear that
wait but you heard something
did you hear btm or just my voice
oh yeah you only heard the voice right
okay one more time
okay here we go
[Music]
and now you should have heard some music
btm what oh my god this is so quick
manager can you write me a message if
this audio was okay because the chat is
like
[Music]
wow
too silent louder louder louder louder
louder
okay one second
how about this
are you ready yay
it's okay if the if the music
overpowers my voice please let me know
ok
oh should i write it down actually
sorry sorry sorry for the blog i'll give
you the titles in japanese somebody will
for sure be nice to write them down
in uh in romaji
later on in the comments uh i only have
them in japanese right now
where is it okay
first song
for the music
[Music]
okay
yay
[Music]
money
oh
[Music]
sweet
make it louder
[Music]
music
sweet
[Music]
yay
music
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
thank you thank you that was the first
song it was from sweet potato it's like
a magical girl animated opening or
ending or something like that
good tea please tea help me go for this
together
i hope you liked the song did anyone
know this song
yeah was it the ending
pretty cute the particular songs are
also energetic and fun
so i thought they would be really really
good too as a first song to get
everyone's attention and hype everyone
up are you hype are you hyped
poop
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
okay next
[Music]
let me change the title
no no no no ads no ads or it's giving me
pizza ads
pizza so so
this happens when you turn off your ad
block
by the way everyone turn off your ad
block when you watch my videos
i think all of you know this song
probably
i'll be checking out the chat of course
that the opinions are always different
some say the audience find some is not
but if it's too bad let me know
[Music]
yes
oh
[Music]
foreign is
m
so
[Music]
i'm getting dizzy
foreign
[Music]
is
hey
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you everyone
[Music]
since i was a little bit late i gotta
keep up with the speed so i can sing all
the songs that i wanted to sing
well well well well well the next one
uh also everyone shouldn't know
yes yes yes yes shampoo add thank you i
don't need any shampoo i wash my hair
with gravy
no thank you i don't need any fancy
brand shampoos
one day i'll make my own shampoo and
i'll sell it all
over the world and it will be out of
gravy so you can you can like even use
it like
not only for your hair but also for your
chicken and whatever
yes one day next song
if you can read japanese you already
know
from young wow that anime i watched
when it came out it's been such a long
time
who was everyone's favorite in kion
actually now that i think of it
[Music]
maybe moogie muniza maybe
is really cool and she has a really cool
voice too
[Laughter]
well well well now that we can all uh
connect with each other through the love
for k
on let's sing it together if you want to
sing with me sing with me
[Music]
um
m
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
um
here we go let's go here we go some more
time okay
some more instrumentals almost there
almost
[Music]
oh
here we go
[Music]
foreign
you
[Music]
[Laughter]
well now you had a little taste of my
epic
wrap skills
oh i got so much tea i'm sweating too
this is awesome welcome to the
membership
welcome to kfb i hope you guys are all
aware if you join the membership you
automatically are an employee
of kfp however you're paying me
i don't pay you this is how we go
okay okay okay okay okay okay
no no well i fired you all but i also
hired everyone back again
let's go to the next room right away
because we don't have so much time
apparently
next song is an old nostalgic one this
one
i don't think many of you know uh
probably many japanese people should
know this song it's an
old i don't i guess i guess you could
say idol's song
princess princess
i really like those oldies you gotta
when the stream is over you gotta listen
to the oldest that i sing for you okay
where is this where is it where is it
there we go no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
who's calling me a boomer huh i'm just
is
[Music]
foreign
m um
[Music]
me
down
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
la
[Music]
thank you four three hundred
i'm not done yet though
is so much fun to sing
[Music]
very good oldie really recommend it
let's keep on drinking the tea amelia
thank you for listening the whole time
amelia collab with me please i love you
and hope you're enjoying it so far
wait how many times one two three four
five
and we have 20 more minutes hmm
i feel like i have to kick out one song
probably maybe i'll kick out this song
it's kind of
i want to go full full high tension
today anyway so
i'm gonna kick out the the chill quiet
song
because you guys are just gonna fall
asleep anyway
next song
rip that song yeah maybe another day
everyone knows
[Music]
hey
my
[Music]
foreign
yummy
[Music]
at the same time
m
[Music]
okay
my
[Music]
she said my name
actually like this wouldn't have
happened if i wouldn't have just kicked
out the other song that i was supposed
to sing i think
is so epic i wish i was on your side
right now
guys i wish i was one of the viewers
connector
i felt her voice up until
here i heard it i heard it
i felt it
that's so funny what the hell i was like
i was seeing the comments saying like
nana is also singing this and i was like
oh did she sing it like uh
yesterday or another day but i know
she's singing a karaoke stream right now
but i didn't
didn't think she's like actually singing
it right now and as you guys are saying
even like
like synced up how is that
possible
[Music]
well i mean the next song cannot
possibly
be synced up okay although that would be
absolutely funny
foreign
hey that's so funny i want to be a
watcher now i want to be on your side i
want to experience that
miracle that just happened where is that
song where do i have it
where is it what
there it is
i love this anime i love this anime
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
um
this anime is so ridiculous y'all
[Music]
thank you very super chat
foreign
[Music]
okay look at the ending we don't have
time
next song is a surprise so i will not
write the title
i wonder if she's watching
ah thank you very super chat
but i will be doing i will be doing a
super chat reading after this so thank
you all for your support
today and for every every every stream
ever
you know okay well uh
pretty much all of you are wrong with
your assumptions
i am not singing cali song yet
because i have not practiced the rap
enough yet but
okay first of all i'm sorry if i mess up
the song
i really really love this song so please
listen uh i hope that audio is fine
[Music]
foreign
uh
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
go
sexy beam yeah
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
oh
i was watching i made so many mistakes
[Music]
i really love your singing i really love
your songs thank you for letting me sing
your song
so happy she's here but i was so nervous
she made me so nervous
oh
this song is so busy many senpai is
amazing for singing it live really
really really
thank you for coming down thank you
i have one more song and i want to sing
it before it turns midnight here
so saigon
i love
i love you i love you
last song is a bit
chill but very very looking forward to
the future
morning
[Music]
me
is
thank you everyone so much for coming
today last time
[Music]
you know
foreign
[Music]
you have to check out the lyrics for the
song it's my feelings for you
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
me
yes
[Music]
foreign
this song is about moving forward and
having you with me
to support me i love you all so much
thank you for being besides me every
time
and being my ten thousand dollar
[Music]
mattress
la la la
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
no
la la la la la
[Music]
[Applause]
that was the last talk thank you so much
for listening today
i'll do super chat after this but ah
thank you thank you thank you i'm so
happy that after one month uh even
though
i i went through a lot of troubles a lot
of changes
and technical difficulties
and well many many issues that i had to
figure out myself and
well also i had to move apartments two
times in this one month
but still everything uh i was able
to do somewhat safely thanks to your
support
i love olivia thank you thank you for
000 subscribers thank you for your
support and i hope from now on too you
will support me don't forget to follow
me on twitter too
yay
let's see now it's actually probably a
bit cold let me see
okay now it's a bit too cold well
i really enjoy singing thank you guys
for listening to me i
i really i'm i'm glad i have an audience
and i'm glad that martin senpai came to
actually the other day we had uh the
phone call together like we were
on this girl talking and i told her how
much i love her singing and how much i
love her songs
and she sent me the karaoke so i can
sing it on my stream she's so sweet and
she told me
when i sing it i shall tell her so she
will come over and even though she did
two streams today i'm sure she was busy
she came anyway thank you so much thank
you for the super chats too everyone
thank you thank you thank you i love you
all so much
i'll do my best to improve from now on
to
to become the perfect version of myself
we can keep on improving everything
[Music]
before i started to stream i was i was
opening the chat window
and i saw that my papa donated a red
super chat
oh my god my papa that is not the first
time that he's super chatted
he's standing super chats like
yeah that's so funny
i love my papa thank you for the super
dance i'm like smiling so much that my
face hurts again
[Music]
so let's turn on my own bgm i guess
yeah just a papa supporting his daughter
and i want to support him too
thank you thank you
[Music]
in germany he knows how to say thank you
in german
they also know how how to say [\h__\h] in
german choices
okay gotta i gotta
[Music]
get me those super jets so i can read
them to you guys
oh by the way tomorrow i think i'll be
streaming
[Music]
maybe minecraft and like build a house
possibly and um i also have some
collabs planned for next week but i'll
not tell you about those yet but what am
i doing my brain is not working
my brain is not working
one second please everyone
[Music]
honestly um
we all keep on saying that i think and i
uh
i i just have to keep on saying this
when when we um
when we made it into whole iodine or
when i made it into hololens
i really really really really really
never in my whole lifetime but i would
or we would um like gather so
such a big sweet audience like so many
of you
i i really did not think this would
happen of course much of it
is thanks to our our senpais who built
apollo life but
i never thought we would have such a
huge english speaking audience
that's i just thought that youtubing
is something that well of course there's
people who's interested in that all over
the world but i never thought there
would be so many
english speaking people of course second
language english speaking as well but
still
i never i never thought this would like
be such a huge thing and i'm
i'm really happy to be part of it and
experience it together with all of you
and yes
really really really exciting
really amazing without you
without all of you this would
not be possible so thank you for
supporting all of us girls
every single one of you with your help
whole life english will grow bigger and
bigger and bigger
and we will become one big family thank
you so much for the super chat
thank you
actually like the growth is so fast like
honestly i thought
in my mind in my tiny little brain i
thought okay one month maybe
maybe 50k maybe at the at the very most
50k
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
did you guys think it would go this
crazy
what did you think guys it it it was
probably
had probably also a lot to do with like
timing like if this would have happened
months ago maybe not
yeah we i think me and ame and all the
others
we were talking a lot about what we are
expecting uh
of what is going to happen before we
debut that
we were like talking how will they
how will they welcome us and honestly we
had no idea
we have no idea oops
i really can't multitask oh my god okay
here we go
send that to the manager and so blah
blah blah
okay i cannot multitask
i'm getting the super chats checked
should not take too long please take a
little
wait until if you want to chill with me
until we're done with the super chat
reading i would be really happy yeah we
are all very talented i have to say that
that is true that is true how the echo
is tough
god damn it okay probably you guys were
telling me that since like 10 minutes
ago
okay how long were you guys telling me
this
10 minutes ago oh
well it's been one month so i would like
to make some announcements but there's
not really anything
i mean i have secret things planned but
there are and they are set in stone too
but
i can't i don't think it's the right
time to tell i wish i could tell you
already but
let me just tell you there's some
exciting things coming
i would say i would say at least at
least two
very exciting things that i'm very
excited about
[Music]
the time
nothing about collabs something bigger
bigger than a collab
yes yes yes
[Music]
something that i have been planning for
a little while
um and then i i am working on
actually yeah so two things one one
thing should happen earlier than the
other one
actually one thing should happen in
october
and one thing should happen in november
yeah late
late november but i cannot tell you
not even amelia knows not even a
millionaires but amelia
i'll tell you if you want to know
actual fast food franchise opening that
seems a very a quick
no no no no cali wedding
this is gonna take some more time i it
will take a bit more time to get kelly
to marry me guys
free pretty well well well
well i mean you think okay let's be real
i mean i
i can't say yes or no but let's be real
you think that's gonna happen like
in the second or third month are you for
real
look at look at how fast it was for
other talents look at it
no no no
you guys are too fast you gotta be a bit
more patient
thank you for the super chat i'll be
reading all of them
slowly and i think today i'll try to
read more messages than usual because
normally we do it like um i try to read
every message that
like stands out to me because of its
length
and i try to read every message where i
can see that it's a red superchat the
thing is like
uh the list that i look at
does not have any colors and the the
currencies are like totally mixed so
only for some currencies
i can look at it and see ah that's a red
super chat
and but for many others i'm like what
what is this
so yeah i don't really know
so i tried to just uh
yeah pick some special ones but today i
think i read a few more
actually restaurant review reveal
oh well i mean one day maybe hopefully
eh
i forgot to put on my second hat
today
hey
i forgot i took it off i took it off
it's in the collaboration because i
thought it would cover up kelly's face
too much when i lean to the right side
because she was right next to me and i
was like ah i gotta take off the right
hat because like it
it uh pokes her face
on
[Music]
now i did the whole celebration stream
incomplete
half naked
300k celebration stream how embarrassing
all these people seeing me half naked
no yeah i have to redo it all
damn yeah
while i was singing i saw some comments
being like top right
top right top right and now you guys are
back to bottom left huh
you guys change your opinion so quickly
probably okay
when i sing karaoke i'm top top right
and
all the other times and bottom left or
what
madame thank you for the super chat i'll
be reading them all
thank you
[Music]
everyone who joined the membership the
graph is
14. we really have to do the uh to redo
the graph at some point
because i feel like already i mean
i feel like a lot of those positions
were
not quite right
now let's do it again next year but we
need a more complex
complex complex graph that describes our
personality a bit better
yeah more access more axes more axis
more x's 3d graph
chad is projecting there the bottom left
ones thank you amelia
thank you
eight directions
oh my face hurts
my face my face my face recently starts
hurting
during stream because i smile so much
thank you for the super dad
i wonder i wonder if i can ask a senpai
for advice
how to how to not smile too much my face
hurt after the clap
my my hand heard it after the
collaboration today
my right hand actually there's there's
still like a huge red spot on my right
hand
from like too much mining
[Music]
too much mining i mean
i'm glad we have the tunnel now that i
thought it was i thought we would get
that done so much quicker actually i i
really underestimated
how far away uh gula was
i really underestimated that she's like
because like
everyone uh when i when i streamed
minecraft
people were like or like i think during
the collaboration with cali we asked
where gura is and everyone said oh she's
not so far away
she's just like a five minute walk away
huh
and yet we had to mine for two and a
half hours
i get okay well now if you use the
tunnel you could make it
in five minutes a bit more than five
minutes
if you use the tunnel but yeah
going going overground
no two minute walk but but kelly said
she timed it and was like five and a
half minutes
you found the speed hack what what is
the speed hack
what is it is it the is it the mining uh
the
the track that's your train track thingy
or the ice
it but i did i did the jumping and then
yeah i did that too
two in two square tall and i mostly i
mostly also
did that yeah but uh but actually yeah
when me and kelly went back i stopped
sometimes to wait for her
because she was a bit dragging behind
probably she didn't know how to do that
while i was like
zoom zoom speed sweet speed speed i was
like going really fast
and it looks behind it was like oh
kelly's so slow i stopped and then
waited for her and then i went again
like zoom zoom zoom speed speed
and then i looked behind again and the
cali was still so far behind
yeah that's probably yeah you can
definitely do it a bit faster i think so
yeah
yeah and uh with uh with some extra
tools like
train track and whatever
oh super chat
checking is done but actually let me
since my tea is now empty i shall get
another cough drop
because my mouth already hurts from so
much talking what the hell is
wrong with ew why does my amelia does
your does your
the inside of your mouth start hurting
after talking too much too
much
about
[Music]
hey but i was drinking a lot i'm
drinking a lot
yeah my jaw my mouth everything hurts
okay well i'll start
it's because you spit so much dirty
stuff
shut up that's not true i am i'm i'm a
pure idol i'm
say so as [\h__\h]
they hate the hate is too strong but i
will not give up
my title of pure say so idol
i'm sure jago was proud of me today
why don't you say so
okay here we go
maybe we should change um this thing
here
i thought super chat
reading now
okay let's go whoa
[Music]
300k and still no promotion what must i
do congrats i guess that
you guys you guys hired yourself you can
also promote yourself
wait my chat just exploded
where did it go where did
it go everything just
error there is an error in this web page
for sure my friend for sure
you cannot take these comments away from
me i will keep them
and i will look at them forever
i see you again chad don't write
anything stupid
three hundred thousand nights have come
spares shall be shaken
shield be splintered also day a red day
er the phoenix rises what right now
right now right to the world's end viva
la chiara
he's a real real general for real
say say say how do you say when when
someone says something like that
do you say say or something like that
yeah this gives me like lord of the
rings vibes i want to watch lord of the
rings with you guys soon and membership
only
no endurance but we talked about this a
few times before that
i want to do a movie watch along and it
must be lord of the rings because it's
like my favorite
one of my favorite movies but no
watching them all one after another oh
my god i'm gonna fall asleep
12 hours is it 12 hours if you oh my oh
[Laughter]
and i'm sure that many of you will also
not
watch the whole thing so let's split it
up let's split it up okay
thank you for the super chance okay here
we go continue
12 hours but only with no breaks
amelia you want me to suffer
amelia don't do this to me
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
watch it at two times speed it's only
six hours i don't watch movies
actually i don't even i know many people
do this but i don't even watch youtube
videos in double speed i know so many
people do that
i'm not no
i don't use that function
[Music]
thank you congratulations on hitting
300k subscribe
i'm not really a fan of parties or
karaoke but this karaoke party is
something that i'll never miss always
stay
happy and bottom look i mean stay
hydrated
thank you so much for your support
always you're here from the beginning
and i really appreciate it well
being here from the beginning right now
is still nothing too
special i guess nothing nothing too rare
but
in a few months time all of you who were
here from the beginning will be the cool
ones
oh yeah my hat i should maybe get back
my hat
so that's a little [\h__\h] for the
mother
[Music]
and actually i also would like some food
foreign
[Music]
you from congress and foreign k your
spirit and energy are inspiring and i
hope everyone has fun with your stream
today
i will unfortunately miss it due to work
but i'm sure it will be great love you
thank you so much thank you
i got the meat would you like to
nibble on my chicken
legs drumsticks would you like a bite
never mind i'll eat it all on my own
i'll eat it myself
you're still here i love you you can
have a bite on me
would you like to nibble on my chicken
leg
goddammit i feel like uh me and amen are
the
maybe the lootest ones out of the group
other gives me a kind of am i wrong
i'm getting a few luge vibes from
from ame am i wrong
bottom alliance yes form an alliance
with me
ame but ame
is smart so she should be bottom right
okay i guess i'm not wrong you guys seem
to agree with me
[Music]
okay you deserve it and much much more
it's hard to even fat
fat from two sides of the same axis
how many people that is all of um
i can't say these english words
love and support what you do thank you
thank you
very much by the way i have a secret
that might come as a shock to you but
so i hope you're sitting down because
i'm about to blow your mind i like your
streams i know you never
started coming funny thank you
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed them
[Music]
i finally finished drawing i want to see
i want to see did you upload it did you
guys see it
thank you shout out 29 thank you
congrats on 300k your enthusiasm always
keeps me motivated
i've never gotten attached to a victory
but you stole my heart
you have a towering personality and i
really adore it i wish i could super
chat more but i'm broke don't worry
about it thank you your support really
really means a lot to me thank you
thank you thank you channel
[Music]
and for some people who don't understand
because there's always like some
especially nowadays there's new people
who don't quite understand
what these things mean my papa is not my
i mean well yeah my papa is my papa my
papa is the person who
gave me this beautiful looks
papa that is the person who is in the
chat sometimes the moderator
here's here he is here right now
and he designed this beautiful human
form of mine
and he he also created many many other
really special works so
amelia you got it a little bit wrong but
that's okay
that's good that sounds funny it sounds
kind of like
a german uh accent from like
from like uh what what how do you say
in english again what was it it had like
a special name
maybe someone a cologne cologne cologne
cologne isn't that like a perfume for
men
but yeah yeah for some reason has a
really weird name in english
cologne yeah it is right what the hell
let's move on
papa
[Music]
some of the same issues as me like um
lack of confidence and
i know how that feels
i don't know what exactly is causing it
for my papa
but i'm really proud to have my papa as
my papa
and i would not want anyone else ever
ever ever hontani
is
[Music]
foreign
congratulations kiara and thank you you
have inspired me to retake japanese
lessons and many old projects because
i can't let a bird brain beat me
hey i'm looking forward to teasing you
in japanese in the future oh we will see
about that
thank you thank you so so much for your
support and i hope you're
getting the just out of japanese if you
need some help
don't ask me
[Music]
congratulations on 300k you deserve them
and much more i love your stream so i
wanted to thank you for all those good
times
i can't watch all of them but i will do
my best to support you so do your best
and never give up
well you know oh you know i'm never
gonna give you up
never gonna let you down you know
thank you thank you
[Music]
you guys way too often i need to do it a
bit less
yesterday i sang the full song
in my stream
one day 3d ww
takanawa comes out on stage stream
starts
and she goes
[Music]
and we're gonna give you up never gonna
let you
down
[Music]
thank you so much you deserve all the
support from us
the kfp crew i'm so happy to hear you
sing kfb
kfbk
[Music]
thank you for listening and thank you
for your support thank you for joining
the kfb crew thank you so much for your
support
hell yeah kfb
sausage foods thank you sanji skipper
thank you
and patrick chandan congratulations 300k
subs yay thank you we all love and
support you continue
doing what makes you happy tonight's
stage will further show us
what an amazing idol and person you are
thank you and i'll always be cheering
for you thank you so much
thank you thank you and airborne
now on to 400k gets to wake up and see
my goddess is going to do a karaoke
stream
good start for the sunday love you
canada kfp for life yeah
thank you okay happy
thank you for bringing joy to so many
i'm eager to see where this journey will
take us
indeed you may not understand the impact
that you've made but watching you
overcome your tribulations
has inspired me to become kinder and try
new things what
what yeah that is actually really really
hard to understand
that that something like that can have
an impact on
someone
[Music]
thank you so much thank you for your
support thank you for the red super chat
thank you
buy another player uh
thank
[Music]
thank you so much for your support thank
you mwah
thank you but please next time write a
message
vrc congratulations have a school sunday
continue to be happy yay thank you
thank you for coming to all of my
streams pretty much
thank you for joining the membership
thank you welcome
i love refrigerators thank you
congratulations on 300k
thank you so much for your support
really
i also love refrigerators very much
not as much as you probably but i also
really appreciate the existence of
refrigerators
thank you for your support thank you for
the red super chat
[Music]
thank you the great rv zero thank you
so much
[Music]
thank
you deserve it and so much more thank
you so much
it's much more than i ever expected
really it's insane
thank you especially yesterday super
mario 64.
but if you don't want to play it anymore
it's fine we're here for you but not the
game i think
i'll probably play it again at some
point
but maybe i'll practice a bit privately
and then get back to it because
to me it has reached a point where it's
not funny anymore
it's only pain for you guys it's
apparently so fun which i do not
understand but for me it's only pain now
play a rhythm game oh i never
i don't think i ever played a rhythm
game before
the
yeah i don't think so so i think it
would also
only create pain now never
i'm trying to think of it but
but not one thing i did once
um when i was um at a friend's place who
had like a
uh what do you call those things again
the goggles where you see like lots of
crazy things
oh
a vr could have thought of that
yeah that that friend had vr and i think
it was beat saber
i tried it like a little bit it was
really
weird oh my god it also also to
introduce me to the vr
thing and i sat down on the chair and i
put on those vr
things and my friend like moved the
chair while i was going for some roller
coaster thing
and oh my god that was crazy that was
crazy that was my first experience with
the vr
thingy oh my god it was screaming it
really felt like a rollercoaster because
like my friend was behind me and moving
to jail like really fast and up and down
and i was like
oh my god it was so insane
that was fun but also scary
i was really feeling like i was in the
real roller coaster
boomer why are you calling me boomer
what what about that story was
making me into a boomer
anyway anyway
thank you soon thank you so much please
eat well sleep more
eh i do sleep a lot and like i actually
have a sleeping problem
every goddamn day i take a nap
pretty much every goddamn day
and it's like i'm like in this hell
cycle where
i i stay up too long until about
5 a.m because i
just cannot sleep earlier and then i
wake up around like
somewhere between 12 or 1 or 12 or 1
o'clock
and uh if i try to
if i try to wake up earlier than that in
order to sleep earlier
mostly it results in me taking a nap
because i just fall asleep i cannot stop
myself
so and even i tried it without a nap too
sleeping less waking up early because i
cannot fall asleep early but
but waking up early like maybe okay
early for me is like 11.
um so then i get like really tired
really early too
but still i just cannot stop watching
netflix
yeah well
someone
[Music]
it has been like this forever i swear
and then sometimes i had to force myself
in the past few months sometimes i had
to force myself to wake up at like
eight or seven in the morning to do
something and important you know
adult stuff so i wake up early in the
morning and
slept like only four hours or something
you would think you would
think that i could manage to sleep early
on that day because i would be
[\h__\h] dead so i come back home
[\h__\h] dead even managed to not take a
nap
but still i wake up i stay up until like
the end of time until four a.m again
five a.m it's
unbelievable unbelievable you will sing
i already said
oh it's over i'm super chatting now i'm
super chatting
yeah adult stuff um excuse me
if this has nothing to do with phrasing
okay this is just you guys thinking of
bottom left things but adult stuff can
mean adult stuff like
going to an appointment
[Music]
laying eggs i don't lay eggs
ah only the japanese bros think that i'm
pure
and you all think i'm so empire
[Music]
congratulations on the 300k looking
forward to more streams
more singing and more collabs in the
future thank you for the hours and hours
of fun
thank you too thank you for watching
thus craven 377 packaging
thank you for waking up early for me
something that i cannot do
they don't actually understand they
don't exactly understand the loot things
that you say that's why
well yes but
um
i'm trying to think of some excuse but i
can't
[Laughter]
thank you for thanking
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you for
watching
don't push yourself too much if you feel
your fraud is not good and you need to
stop we understand no
no no no no no
tomorrow night never stopping whole
alive
i keep on going my brother is fine it's
hard no mama
it's all right thank you thank you
hand over the congratulations on the
300k
the kfp grill crew across yay
my first and second ride superchat goes
to you thank you can't wait to hear you
sing thank you so much for your support
mate
hey mate thank you oh wait that that was
canadian right
what's australian something australian
koala kangaroo
ah um a
thing reef what what what's with the
word again
what's the word again something reef uh
coral reef great barrier reef
swim swim swim swam dive dive doop doop
dangerous spiders dangerous snakes
dangerous land beautiful land australia
good day mate
the land of where when you hit a spider
it turns into a million small spiders
have you guys seen that video i'm not
sure if that was from australia
but oh my god
oh oh yeah the land of hachama cooking
that's just spiders eh no that's an
australian thing that's not a universal
thing that's an australian thing i know
it
[Music]
thank you
smith
[Music]
for making me move so smoothly i keep on
getting all these
compliments about moving so nicely and
like moving like a 3d character and that
that the bounciness
of my model really reflects my
personality so
thank you so much
i love watching your streams because i
find your energy to be so contagious
can i ask what sparked your feelings for
calliope
yes you may ask i have answered this
question before in the q a i think
um but when i first met kelly
she first of all i fell in love with her
looks
but i think before before i saw her
it was first only like you know uh
her personality and her way of speaking
she
surprised me by using such funny words
and like speaking in a very interesting
manner
and i was like oh she's funny she's very
interesting
and uh then i saw i saw her her looks
closely and i was like
holy macaroni
i am aroused by this
[Laughter]
i was like damn she hot oh
then like i keep on learning more and
more about her and every
every time i learn something new about
her every time i talk more with her i
just love her even more
she's so talented she's so funny she's
she's such a kind-hearted and sweet
person
ah i'm so glad i met her
thank you i haven't really enjoyed
watching you find your bottom left self
this past few streams
shut up you're always the most say so in
my heart
i would think so thank you thank you
for thank you
[Music]
thank you for uh joining the membership
guys thank you
super poke plus zhang
[Music]
is
in
[Music]
oh i think that's certain someone
spoiled it in it oh she did
and madin chan already said in her
stream
that i will be singing her song
thank you yay cool that you were
watching her stream and then came over
to mine
uh
can i get two number nines number nine
large number six of extra dip a number
seven two number forty fives one with
cheese and a large soda oh jokes aside
from it's on 300k
thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you i don't have much to say
except keep on smiling and burning fresh
thank you
thank you soon kevin salazar geraldine
florian's florian's ice champion
[Music]
i'm not gonna lie a loki hopefully song
afterwards uh um
one day when i do an unarchived stream
i will sing a german song for you but
for my archive streams i have to use a
certain list with certain songs that we
already have approved and
all of those songs are japanese which
for me is no problem because i prefer
singing in japanese
uh but we don't really have like an list
for english songs
yeah it's it's difficult to get
permission for all of these songs that
exist
over the world but one day i'll do an
unarchived stream where i can just sing
whatever but today i thought i wanna i
wanna do the archive because it's a
celebration anniversary whatever
so yeah no no ramstein
no no way no
[\h__\h] way your name here danke shen
s 17 b 32 dan kashing
here congratulations please accept this
humble gift from one small bird to the
mighty feelings thank you aye because
you're
kiwi now i'm gonna leave this stream
running on my pc and go to bed because
it's past
three a.m in new zealand and it's monday
new zealand i
wanna go to new zealand i wanna go
it's so beautiful i've never been there
but i wanna go
i wonder i wonder if it's expensive
[Music]
two three one
friendly neighborhood
[Music]
foreign
this person is drawing like uh
especially like takamori fan art or like
a fan out of me and kelly like every day
but this person
usually like most most of the time they
they just scribble something and then
they don't
use a hashtag but i have noticed so i
keep on checking out their account every
day
even though they don't tag me or they
don't use hashtags i just
i know i know they draw something every
day so i just opened their
twitter account i already remembered it
and i'm like oh let's see what they draw
today
thank you for your support always thank
you for the red super chat
oh my gosh
zero five six zero
[Music]
congratulations on 300k your voice is
amazing as always please take care of
yourself though this is your fourth
stream in around
30 hours oh that's nothing
it really isn't though thank
foreign
[Music]
thank you
read the night one dankeshen you and the
other halloween should put a smile on my
face when it comes to singing
ah thank you i i also really like to
listen to the other members singing
everyone's so cute
when they sing well
we are real idols after all
let's drink some water warah
how much do we have left i wonder
ah still quite a bench okay let's go
[Music]
thank you ready night thank you thank
you
the nikko in your backyard muffin hydra
duncashin weekend warrior thank you
i love your stream since your w your
update
i love your stream since your debut
thank you your upbeat and happy
personality is like a ray of sunshine
thank you
keep shining brighter and brighter you
wonderful cheap phoenix
what is that chi what does that stand
for huh
close close close we'll save this out
there
phoenix indeed very much phoenix
i haven't been smiling a lot lately
about your positivity and energy have
inspired me to try again yes
smile thank you and shout out to my
fellow kp employees for supporting our
attention
hey shout out to kfp okay
crew what up where are you at
thank you thank you thank you for the
super chat which are still coming in
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you shane you can love 67 mine
thank you for the super chats
[Music]
thank you just a little something to say
congrats on reaching 300k
thank you so much your positive attitude
and
determination is inspiring both to me
and to others
keep up the amazing work your treasure
to us all thank you oh
you guys are so sweet
thank you for the red super chat you
deserve it and thank you for the music
what is your favorite tells hi ogi have
a great night phoenix
i don't really have a favorite like
actually look
i'm really bad at activating them
usually
when i play a tales off game i mostly
don't use those because i forget how to
activate them
but it works without thanking
people
[Music]
to
this is a super jets when i sang a
collaboration with nene
miracle collaboration i gotta watch
nana's archive later
actually i really really love nanette
i really love nina and so i asked her
for collaboration
coming soon
on
i really felt especially because of
today's miracle
i need to become friends with nene
senpai
i love nana she's so cute actually
um when when uh when the fifth gen
was debuting in me and the other
whole libyan girls we watched the debuts
together like each and everyone they did
one every day right
so we all like came together
to watch them every day and went into
voice chat this
[Music]
and we like we were sharing our feelings
about the
new gen and it got us also really hyped
and really excited about our own demuke
and also i felt like a lot of pressure
because the fifth gen
they were all so well prepared and and
they had so many
cute personalities so many talents
and so it was like i personally i was
like oh my god i love all of them
they're all so great but also
oh my god the quality the like the the
bar the
the bar of what expectations or whatever
it keeps getting higher and higher with
every
whole life generation that
[Music]
is so sweet
anyway let's move on i talked too much
we will never finish this at this rate
thank you for the membership yeah oh and
also
shishido botanpai even said
that like like we're equal
uh because like we debuted like around
the same time roughly
so she said that and for like i i'm very
um
um i lived in japan before so
i i have uh quite the experience
with uh japanese like society and how
this whole kohai senpai thing works so
hearing something like that from botan
senpai
really hits me deep like her saying that
i really i really appreciated it
[Music]
really really sweet really really nice
of her so kind
thank you thank you for welcoming us in
holla life
thank you
thank you hopefully i can collab with
everyone
from the fifth generation
they're all so great
um
every now and then have to say senpai
because
even though she says we're like equals
it still feels like hey they think that
means before me and this whole senpai
thing is also kind of
i'm really used to it so
it's hard for me to leave it out also
marine senpai also
told me uh to call her by a nickname
so i got the permission to call her
marin-chan
but still every now and then i feel like
it's inappropriate to say malintan so i
have to say money in senpai sometimes
again
[Music]
what is your username what does that
mean
injury to insult thank you shin thank
you
please dante
and heartfelt content really cements you
firmly as one of the greats
thank you so much i'm glad i'm glad you
liked my content thank you thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
foreign
well thank you for the super chats that
keep coming in thank you so much
will will smith thank you soon
[Music]
it makes me so happy when people like
change their youtube usernames to
something related to me
or when people on twitter uh put my oc
mark my
um how you call it in english again like
the the
the sign the chicken side
in their name or in the description or
when they put like a
kiara fan art as their icon
makes me so happy to see that
oshima
[Music]
hey
doctors find a faint pulse returning to
jago's dream
it's a medical mystery that as of yet
cannot be explained as to what happened
someone please make a movie out of this
thank you welcome to the kfp crew
welcome to the membership
thank you servant jonathan garcia
a square thank you so
[Music]
i made so many mistakes singing marine
song because
seeing her in the chat made me so
nervous
but yeah it was fun it's like such an
energetic and fun song but i also love
all of the other songs that marin put
out so far
and also that the touhou related songs
are really really really fun i love them
or the song where she um
had like all of her uh members from the
same generation
like backing her up
destroyed mario yesterday i really enjoy
celebrating friend okay with you today
lovely voice you have my support from
texas yeehaw
thank you
[Music]
thanks for being awesome love you mama
thank you too thank you for your support
thank you red super chat kiss
thank you for tanking
[Music]
the chat died for me are you just not
typing guys
it's dead where is everyone are you
sleeping
hello wake up
keep on spamming the tanki shoes we're
almost there guys
we're almost at the refresh point
the kimberson
[Music]
genuinely happy that i can watch you
rise to stardom
and that you can get to meet with your
senpai and live your dream oh yeah
that is really awesome that is really
awesome best part of joining whole life
keeping yourself kiara thank you so much
thank you
shoot anime girls are the best thank you
kids
and here we go here comes the refreshing
mask
scrolling where was i already forgot
dammit
[Music]
here oh i
yeah here okay found it
why are you calling me microlife that
sounded nothing like a microwave what
the hell
the rest of each other
[Music]
friendly little your days are brightened
by your fa
our days are brightened by your fire
thank you thank you for
and your hard work we're with you all
the way so keep placing your trail thank
you so much
actually let me drink some water and
thank you thank you so much for your
support
for all all the sweet love you sent
over to me thank you
thank
it might be only for me but you'll fill
me with so much energy that i don't
even feel tired thanks so much for all
your hard work the journey is just
beginning and i can't wait to see how
high you
start together thank you you guys are so
sweet
i bet all of you have a girlfriend or a
boyfriend
because you're just so good with your
words
right you all have a girlfriend or a
boyfriend don't you
don't you no
ah
this is okay you have me
you have me what else could you want
what else could you ask for well you
better actually yeah
don't date anyone just watch my streams
every day
because once you are in a relationship
you'll probably not have time for me
anymore
and if you're trying then your partner
would probably be like
what don't watch kiara
focus on me not not not
nine nine nine
me don't
get yourself into a relationship it's
very very bad just kidding
do whatever makes you happy but i would
say the thing that makes you the
happiest is watching
me
[Music]
are you guys chanting just kiara in the
chat
wow nice just kiara just quiet
numbers the popularity of halloween took
me by surprise but the quality of the
talents was way more surprising
you all have all greatly exceeded all of
my expectations and then some
yeah thank you so much it is indeed very
surprising very shocking but the whole
live idea members are also really
talented and really adorable
and they also speak a lot of english as
well so if you're ever like
hmm what should i watch right now you
can you should definitely also check out
the whole life
indonesia goals while you're at it
whole life channel as well and hololive
japan obviously oh
she had a really nice neck crack really
nice
probably didn't hear it but yeah
just kiara oh yeah that kind of doesn't
fit what i just said
uh but with just kiara i mean like don't
don't get yourself into a relationship
because you won't have time to watch
features anymore
maybe like in 10 years you can get
yourself in an into a relationship
minor 49ers fire fire in the fire danger
[Music]
before but i've been watching all the
whole live en members from the start and
you're all amazing
thank you also congrats on creating k
thank you very much thank you thank you
thank you thank you for supporting all
of us thank you
we're really happy to have you behind
our backs
supporting us
your voice is absolutely amazing thank
you i love the karaoke also converts on
300k subs and the capri empire will
cannonball you past 1 million subs in no
time
i kind of doubt that but okay keep doing
your best we love you thank you so much
[Music]
well i mean i don't really think like i
don't really
see one million subs is a goal to be
honest i
it's not like i um
i mean i should always aim high i know
but i'm not really aiming for one
million i just wanna
i just wanna do my thing and i'm happy
with what i got already
but of course we gotta keep on growing
we cannot stop
registering thank you guys on the phone
case up and super enjoyed your single
hat curly stream
your singing voice is just super comfy
and made my sound ten times better thank
you
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you i'm so happy for you you've
quickly become one of my favorite people
to watch and i'm so glad you've reached
your friend okay thank you
welcome that's right
thank
[Music]
yeah kelly is sick but don't worry i'm
taking care of kelly don't worry
saki waita
foreign
she kissed callie hence why kiana is
kind of sick
but if you remember right uh the other
day i i was the one
who was kind of like sickish
it's possible that i kissed her and she
got the sickness from me
i'm sorry very sorry hope you feel
better seeing wife
well i was very close to her in the
minecraft collab sleeping
next to her bed every goddamn night
no surprise she's sick now
ahead for two hours of suffering thank
you thank
[Music]
foreign
ah
what do i say
enough to play
um
[Music]
japanese message it says it was
translated for google so i'm not sure in
which language to reply
but um
i'm i'm really glad you
enjoyed my stream and i'm really glad
that
it gave you some happiness and
um
i don't know i mean some of you guys say
it's a copy fest or whatever
it doesn't matter if it's true or not it
doesn't matter i always think
it could be true
i wish you the best and um
what do i say um
um be strong and
always always think that
that will be another chance given to you
in the next life i think this is
think of yourself as a phoenix
again
you're phoenix just like me
i'm looking forward to your revival
look forward to it too we will meet
again
phoenix is unite
i love you thank you
and don't worry about uh
like some people like i don't know some
people
are like don't send send messages
it will make the streamer like unable to
reply or whatever
but i've always been like very
open with my own feelings crying a lot
so don't worry about it don't worry
about it and um
i honestly really don't know what to say
i'm really sorry but
yep thank you for watching my stream
i'm glad you spent your time with me
as well
[Music]
oh i can't read your name since it's in
korean but
thank you hello from a female fan from
korea me and my girlfriend
your girlfriend allows this okay that's
nice
love you so much thank you for making us
smiles you have lots of female fans in
korea wow
[Music]
thank you
wow everyone loves some kfp chicken huh
yay fast food fans all over the world
simp for kiara
300k thank you my last super chat was
when you opened super chats and i said i
was looking forward to everything you do
since then you and ian have blown me
away we appreciate your effort and
content and you bring joy to our lives
thank you
thank you so much for your support thank
you for being with us
all the way hopefully also in the future
thank you
thank you yeah
and cute anime girls are the best thank
you sundar and wait
time kashan sir
[Music]
asking me to do like a drinking alcohol
stream
and um actually i hate alcohol
but the thing is i i never really said
this before
but there was a fan art a while ago
from someone drawing me and callie
and cali in that fan art was drinking
wine
no wait i think it was like
me looking disgusted by wine but liking
juice or something and yeah anyway it
was like me and cali
with juice and alcohol and i was like
how the hell did they know
that i hate alcohol because at that
point at least i definitely never said
that i had i hate alcohol but apparently
this person
just kind of like guessed it and how you
guessed so
right yeah
oh
how did i know how did i know
i don't i don't ever drink alcohol i
never actually and i was never drunk
before
alcohol is very bad for phoenixes
very very bad because like inside us
there's a burning fire
and if we out if we drink alcohol it's
like
pouring gas on myself
does that make sense
yeah it's not really not really good i
cannot drink alcohol
makes sense nice
optimus prime thank you a cape
co cab cr1 too many more celebration
streams i'm looking i'm
really looking forward to lord of the
rings watch along i didn't extend it or
theatrical version
uh whichever is on netflix uh but by the
way
i was thinking about this um have you
guys ever seen
a stream uh a movie watch along
did you ever see something like that
before with a feature watching a movie
together
yeah enough did one but do you guys like
if i would do that so personally i hate
it i hate it
when i watch a movie together with
someone and that person keeps on
speaking like even if they say
one in a two-hour movie if they say even
one single word i get so irritated
but if if we would watch a movie
together and i was just
for two hours would say nothing
i guess there's no meaning in doing it
so i'm going to ask you guys do you want
me to speak a little bit
or that's it
uh if i watch with someone else and they
talk i get really irritated but talking
myself i guess i can do
especially if it's a movie i've already
seen if it's a movie i haven't seen
before i want to be a bit more quiet
[Music]
i'll be speaking then
as long as you guys are only chatting
and not speaking to me that's okay
if someone is like speaking to me while
i'm watching a movie
i i'm i'm going crazy
yes just shut up okay just shut up mina
we'll do one next week okay
oh titanic
actually besides lord of the rings i was
thinking of um
two other movies to watch with you guys
i know one of them sound of music
i want to watch that with you and then
i'll i'll keep on singing
with the movie the sound of music i
wanna watch that
i've seen it before but yeah
it's so much fun to sing along
and now this is a
this is a bit attacking oh thank you for
the super chat this is a bit tacky but i
want to watch
high school musical with you
i want to watch high school music
i'm not i'm not the biggest fan of high
school musical but it's just so
nostalgic and tacky
and the songs are like so cute
so i want to watch it again just like as
a joke
i love the songs but first we do a lot
of drinks
watch some good movies first before we
get into the cringe
yeah it's cringe but it's fun but first
we watch a good movie
lord of the rings
yeah favorite things we had yeah i love
all those songs from
from sound of music
it
[Music]
i need to watch someone else's movie
watch along
to see how they do it but most of the
japanese talents
they have it on members only
well i am in one membership
privately you know on my secret account
i am part of one membership you could
probably guess which one
but yeah
so i'm going to check that out see what
she did
membership
yeah well you promoted yourself
congratulations what are you promoting
yourself in onto
perspective dan kashan sold out a 94
congratulations for friend okay i'm
happy that i gave a chance to hold live
again
because you just turned into my favorite
streamer i hope to see lots more lots
more of you in the future
your bright light in our everyday thank
you so much actually it's funny that you
say that you gave us a chance
because like obviously i did a lot of
researching before we debuted it
and before we were announced and i left
and like many
many people were like uh english
youtubers english whole life no
thank you but so many of those people
are now like
i love whole life english i love whole
life myth i love all of them
i'm a sim i'm
so i'm really glad that we changed
everyone's opinion
but i mean i know i know that i kind of
could relate to it uh because i
personally like i also love like
it's like it's like watching dubbed
anime
i personally always watch the original
dub anime is not really my thing but um
i'm glad that we were able to get
everyone
hyped up and interested in us
[Music]
thank you people thank you even brown
duncan
we're almost reading super chat for two
hours now so i'm gonna hurry up
a little bit but we're almost done
with
[Music]
in your w trailer it said that each time
you're reborn you wake up in a new
dimension have you been to ganso hill
yet and
maybe met a fellow white-haired phoenix
oh i've been in a lot of dimensions yes
yes yes yes you know normally
normally phoenix's when they revive they
just revive
in the same dimension in the same world
but i've been in all of them
i've been in all those dimensions some
something is bugged
there's like a bug in my system that
every time when i revive i'm in a
different dimension it's so
weird it is so weird i've been in some
really
weird weird-ass worlds
oh yeah maybe it's my galaxy ice
[Music]
well i hope i can stay in this dimension
for a while
[Music]
thank
foreign
just explained the whole karaoke thing
again why i don't think german or
english songs because of the archive
thing
but yeah in the future i'll do some
english german songs too
i mean i have to say
there's not many okay
there's not many
good good
german songs that i
like okay
yeah okay german is my first language so
i'm allowed to say that
and yeah and also i just feel like
um this is a weird thing i've been
thinking about this before but
hearing songs in my first
language it's so weird for me it's just
it's very awkward and it feels cringy to
me
but hearing songs in english feels so
smooth and natural to me
but i wonder if english-speaking people
people with english as the first
language
they don't feel that way that i feel
about german songs i guess
but probably because they're for them
it's just normal because like english
songs are like popular all over the
world
it's just a normal thing so probably for
english-speaking people
like that's just the way it is but for
someone whose first language is german
and grew up with english songs
being popular all around them all the
time
it seems like probably the society kind
of
the society i was raised in probably
like taught me that english songs are
cooler than german songs maybe i don't
know
but yeah it's also just the fact that
german songs
just don't seem
so good to me um
yeah i don't know it's weird it's weird
i mean there are some
good german artists i guess
i've listened to a few in the past what
was it again
well who are they called again now
they're the ones that sang
[Music]
does someone know i wonder
uh i don't know
via sent him for example i listened to
many years ago i really liked their
songs
what was it again
[Music]
advice
is one of the few german
artists i don't know if they're even
still active but one of the few that i
like
and then there's um oh i don't like
german rap now
and then there is um
there's a an austrian rapper
i usually don't listen to rap but i
don't really like this this guy's rap
but he's austrian but he raps in english
he writes his own songs and all that
it's called left boy look it up
left boy is an austrian rapper actually
quite popular even outside
you know usually some the artists that
that are like
that come from germany and austria they
usually only stay
popular inside the german speaking realm
it's hard for them to like get out there
but left boys seem
seems to have made it a little bit
outside of austria and germany as well
yeah yeah
[Music]
i can't i can't but he he changed his
name oh yeah he changed his name
but you will still find it if you type
in left boy
bug i listen to all kinds of music i
guess
well now that if you if we talk about
austrian german
music yeah that's that i guess
despacito
i know there's this japanese guy singing
in lederhosen singing
yodeling i know i know i'm aware of that
i'm very aware of that collaboration
coming soon
actually we're pretty much done with the
super chat say no doctors thank you
and kyle williams thank you one soon
refreshing
oh thanks nice timing for the superchat
everything that comes
after my countdown will not be read
imagine
foreign so
count down for the last super chats for
today
10 seconds in german
[Music]
i don't like saying this number uh
no
you can still send super jet now but i
will refresh now and everything that
is not in my refreshed list
thank you everyone thank you
where was i
[Music]
okay found it thank you
and the silver tongue slacker thank you
congratulations from your youngest staff
member and his family yeah
is that the one where we talked about
before
uh what was it two months old or
something like that
thank you for joining the membership no
from him yet though
thanks for keeping our family
entertained thank you
that's so sweet that's so sweet
[Music]
i hope you're enjoying my cussing and my
swearing
i just i just honestly i cannot control
it in english
in german i can totally control it i
just swear
a little bit in german to like make you
guys laugh but actually like
in the in the mario kart stream it was
actually hard for me to swear like
many of the german swears are so
tough that i don't want to say them
in german i just feel like so bad about
swearing there's some swears that i just
use way too easily in german as well
but generally i try to not swear but
yeah chai said
i do i probably use that a lot in german
when i really speak german
hopefully again hopefully your child's
first words
will not be [\h__\h]
[Music]
tnt tn trooper dan kashin
thanks for flipping them burgers mario's
entire family
please don't hurt us
will see about that
is all i can say
[Music]
thank you good choice thank you for
streaming i struggle with my mental
health and your streams always make me
feel better i'm so glad to hear that
i know how you feel i always i always
feel better when i watch pekula senpai's
streams thank you oh thank you guys for
joining the membership
cheer up please thank you alex
jerky
without any words
what are you doing write
something in your red super jets
so i can react properly
don't
otherwise use it all
i don't know what to do with you
thank you soon
[Music]
that's all i can give you since you
didn't write anything
lucasgamer123
a cardinal will clock sankishan
blizzyadan
you skipped my first what do i i'm sorry
here's one more i love your japanese and
your streams and i enjoy your rpg
play for the tone thank you keep
believing in yourself we all love your
content thank you so much
thank you so sorry for skipping i really
i wonder
yeah i really feel like i use it all
i really feel like i i'm going for each
and every one of them
weird sometimes i even repeat them
why use it
all right didn't we have this before
foreign
[Music]
what are you doing with your money
well my friends we have reached the end
of
well thank everyone for staying until
can i even speak english anymore
thank you everyone for staying until the
end
i love you all so much thank you for
giving me a home
i i really feel like i found
a new passion and um
i really really really enjoy
bringing out content for you guys every
day normally i'm like
really [\h__\h] lazy
so i'm surprised at myself that i'm like
really
like going through with this so much
like
i i originally i was like oh we just
really got it like
luna thank you thank you
we already reached the end but thank you
for coming
right at the end last time i think it
was also like that
[Music]
thank you for coming what was i saying
yeah yeah i was like in the beginning i
was like oh i'll just do this like three
times a week
but now it's so much fun i want to do it
every day and i'm looking forward to
every new day
to
[Music]
next week we'll do a membership stream
sorry for not doing it this week
they might depending on how much time i
have
or kfp trash can donating
how does the trash can have enough money
to fill
out a red super jet
depending on how much time i have next
week i'll do
at least one but maybe two
membership streams we'll see i mean i
guess there's no need to force me to do
two but
yeah i'll see because next week we have
her
some important things coming up
hmm and i need to pee right now
well it's hard to leave you guys i
really feel so comfy here
thank you for celebrating with me
oh yeah collab band lifted tomorrow
i wonder what the other girls planned if
they planned any senpai collaborations
next week already
well i did i didn't really hear anything
from the other girls i wonder i'm gonna
ask them
i want them really curious i went like
right into it
i can't wait it's too exciting
yeah next week super the same fight
collaboration
thank you for joining the membership
thank you thank you everyone for
supporting thank you for believing in me
[Music]
well i gotta end this now
you know you remember that deep talk
about chicken and egg sandwiches
i often have these deep thoughts you
know today i was thinking
humans are so weird the whole eating and
then
you know letting it all out again the
whole
that whole thing is so weird but i'm not
this this deep thought i will keep to
myself
i i was just thinking today humans are
so weird
but this one i'll keep to myself again
because of course idols don't go
to the toilet this is why idols
are in constant need of peeing
what am i saying oh my god please stop
me
please
stop me stop me now goodbye guys i love
you see you
tomorrow what stop me
[Music]
oh
you