foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
not
[\h__\h]
[Music]
that's funny no no I can't get it okay
you didn't see that
[Music]
you didn't see that ah
well something had to go wrong let's
hope it uh it's only that knock knock on
my table knock knock is that even it's
probably not even wood
um welcome
you didn't see anything very good very
good uh well hello everybody
I am nervous
I am very nervous
um
how are you doing guys good morning good
evening good day wherever you're
watching from today is whole life the
start of whole life English
kimono reveal unveiling relay yeah we're
starting with the myth members this week
today and the first one and the top
batter yeah let's go oh
wow
and uh yeah the theme is New Year is
kimonos yeah and if you didn't know
um Japanese people they wear traditional
kimonos or they like to wear them on New
Year's maybe a little bit more often
than on other days but what am I trying
to say yeah wouldn't it be nice to go to
a shrine together bgm doko good question
thank you wouldn't it be nice to go to a
shrine together
right now but ah traveling not really an
option right now huh I I do miss Japan
but it would be so nice to go in a in a
kimono in a Japanese kimono touch run I
did wear a kimono before and I wear I
wore a foodie so there before putting
soda is like a special type of kimono
um that uh you you uh you wear when
you're like coming of age in Japan I
guess as a lady with it has like longer
sleeves than other kimonos but said fine
wait yeah
[Music]
thank you for watching I guess she's
probably still awake not just woken up
it's 6 a.m right now in Japan and as I
know lots of missing but she's she she's
still awake
um
so yeah uh I I don't want to say that um
I am very very grateful and very honored
that whole life English has received the
chance of getting these kimonos and all
of us including Iris Iris won't be a bit
delayed
um but she will get it and yeah I want
to say thank you so much
um for making it possible uh yeah I
think it's so so so so cool I think a
lot of you guys also didn't really
expect that we would be getting a key
model outfits like the Japanese members
I think it was very very unexpected a
big surprise especially because it
didn't it didn't come with together on
the same day as as the Japanese members
this year so you guys are probably like
oh okay well I mean that's that's
probably confirms that they're not
getting it yeah also because we got the
party dresses but the party dresses I
know they were really recent but those
were not supposed to be our New Year's
outfits those are just outfits that were
they were supposed to come out of it
earlier than that quite a bit earlier
um but because they came out like a
month ago people thought that maybe that
would be our New Year's outfit well
you're wrong
yes so I'm really excited to be showing
you guys my kimono and then this will be
a 30 minute stream so maybe I should get
started
although yeah I think I'm fine and then
uh right immediately after me is uh
Ina's reveal that the order and the URLs
are in my description and also one more
thing please uh if you want to tweet
about it if you want to post screenshots
then you're welcome to use the hashtag
Holo en kimono relay that is in my uh in
my title oh oh can I say one more thing
these are not yukatas
it's one of my peeps hearing uh people
say Yukata but not everything is a
Yukata
kimonos okay Yukata is kind of the the
summer version of kimono um it was
something you would wear In Summer with
a more light fabric these are fancy
fancy uh kimonos that we are showing you
yeah so uh please enjoy uh oh
um so anyway yeah oh remember that time
I went to Hokkaido I really missed sad
oh it was so nice I like the snow I must
be so nice there right now oh I ended uh
wouldn't it be so so cool to to go to
the Shrine in the winter I I did hear
about this is reading off my memo
I did hear about this mountain shrine
I'm curious about it I heard about it
it's apparently very magical and Serene
Serene yeah like very calm and and
um
I want to go there if if only it were so
easy to travel right now with all the
[\h__\h] happening
oh
what is this
huh
I'll turn it around so you guys see it
too
[Music]
huh
I am galinas
flights to any destination under 39 what
the [\h__\h] wait what that's [\h__\h] cheap
what
that girl she looks hot looks like me a
little bit weird is that me
uh art by Christina Manzanita
uh yeah wow price down new with free
Wi-Fi for 39 dollars and free Wi-Fi are
you kidding me that must be wrong that
what a thing
maybe we should look up this heirloom
it's probably a [\h__\h] Airline but
maybe we should look it up and maybe
this is our chance to fly to Japan right
now and uh go put on our fancy kimono to
that location you know Kiana always
needs an occasion okay
um
um [\h__\h] game stopper
okay everyone and welcome onboard the
kfp 2300 on our flight to Hokkaido Japan
please listen to these safety
instructions do not [\h__\h] die on my
plane today number one please fasten
your seat belts whenever the seat belt
sign is on connect the metal buckles and
pull the strap tight in order to not Ram
your table into your stomach throw it
away for takeoff and Landing put your
bag under the seat in front of you and
put your seat back into the original
position for your handheld devices I'm
gonna stop bullshiting you here no one
cares what mode you switch it to as it
does not really affect the plane please
do not smoke any kind of cigarettes in
our plane not even in the toilet can't
you hold it back for a few hours come on
all exits on the airplane are marked but
I decide when you get off some doors may
be stuck does someone have some WD-40 in
case of an emergency landing we might
need you to slide off the emergency
floaty boat yay
jumpy jump it's not only for children
okay if the airplane loses pressure
oxygen masks will drop from above put it
on your face and now inhale deeply to
sound like Darth Vader life vests are
under your seat or maybe not we had to
make some Cuts this year due to the
after doing our final cabin check we
will take off and bring you to today's
destination thank you for your attention
have a nice flight
[Music]
that sounds legit
I mean
I've I've
used a lot of different airlines and out
of all the airlines that I've used so
far
that sounds the most legit and that was
the most professional video that I have
ever seen I was we're already flight
instructions yeah yeah so I guess we're
going now Jake Paul I'm putting putting
made this video thanks pudding alrighty
oh God okay here we go okay uh oh God uh
see you see you then on the mount Shrine
I guess uh oh God oh God
oh God oh God oh God
uh
okay
okay I'll I'll go now oh bye bye
foreign
[Music]
it's so cold but it's so beautiful
so cold so cold I'm freezing yo no I'm
not freezing I'm a phoenix it's no
problem no problem okay let's check out
this Shrine shall we please stay until
the end I have some secret uh weapons
that you don't think that that you're
not expecting it okay so we have some
cute black uh uh slippers slipper
thingies and white socks and uh here
starts the beautiful kimono patterns
this is this is the aesthetic that we
want to see don't we beautiful kimono
patterns okay Papa worked on some
gorgeous kimono patterns
yes
yes uh so far it looks very floral huh
pretty and it seems to be
um a bay the base color color seems to
be
what what oh must be to say so idle
takanasikiwawa oh wait that's why my
body ends okay oh
beautiful oh oh
very Floral
[Music]
oh what do you call these flowers again
I'm sure they have a name
[Music]
I love the the golden outlines
very pretty oh and you see a little bit
off my sleeve here in the background
flowing around
Lotus is that a lot no Carnival current
something like a Cornelia I think so too
I think so too
oh okay okay wow I'm actually pretty
fast now
okay okay
it's it's hard to uh
hard to guess how much time I should
take well okay see uh I really like the
color combination so far it has the
turquoise of uh my oh like the a few
elements of my original outfit had that
turquoise color and
yeah but it's mostly white which I
thought is really really pretty yeah
yeah yeah I'm gonna zoom out a little
bit
what is that
does that look like
the tale of a phoenix to you
baby I already spoiled it huh
no is it really a phoenix oh and on the
right sleeve you might see something
that looks like wings as well oh
it does now now that I said it
oh okay
[Music]
okay I'm I'm gonna do it a little bit
differently This Time by the way but
okay so far this is what you see the
bottom part of my kimono
[Music]
um yes that does seem Like a Phoenix I
guess followed by a beautiful butterfly
fly like a butterfly hell yeah okay
um
just zooming out zooming out okay
nice it looks beautiful so far let me
[Music]
oh you need to look at this beautiful
Shrine though I have I have a various
various angles of it actually
but okay oh I see some some ribbonish
things with stars on it but it's it's
pink colored cute
[Music]
another oh I also like the the sheer
patterns in the background that you
don't see so well because they're the
opacity is pretty low but you still see
it
[Music]
all right all right all right oh
here's my hobby
turquoise apparently with some more
pinkish ribbons okay okay okay
oh foreign
[Music]
okay
wait uh
[Music]
I'm out of here
to wait a minute
[Music]
okay it should be safe to go
welcome to the mountain Shrine everybody
[Music]
how much time 10 minutes okay easy
and pink
[Music]
thank you
pink
peek
wow it's beautiful oh
wow it's so cold but
it's too pretty to be freezing
don't enhance no no let me enjoy this
beauty
[Music]
let me walk around the shrine a little
bit okay
oh
wow Japan is so beautiful
wow
gorgeous
hi
[Music]
but wait there's more
are you ready for this
I don't think you are
[Music]
foreign
and this time I have long ass hair again
and the color on this one is kind of mmm
yellow greenish but
um
[Music]
and then properly show you this one yet
twin tails is like so cute oh my God
look at the toy tails
so here we have a lime color towards the
bottom some yellow lime color oh and
earrings okay don't ask me questions
about it I don't know how to explain it
after all the things I've said about my
my feathers
um I I I I I hit them in my hair I I
there are somewhere in there don't don't
ask too many questions I don't know how
to explain
but yay thank you
look Queen Tails I'm so happy the twin
Tails twin Tails yay pretty long bangs
on this one and pretty spiky hair
strands and let me hide myself again
let's go um
let's go
uh
let's go here
[Music]
hello
wait
you can take some nice pictures
everybody cause this beautiful
background I'm so happy with it too I I
got it specifically for this purpose uh
yes my beautiful Monster drawing
tomorrow will be a special stream about
this yeah
where I'm gonna have some girls over let
me bring back this one
gonna have some girls over uh for for
some uh Mountain Shrine visitation and
uh do you guys want to take a close look
at the fan
you need to take a look at this
uh
I guess I didn't show you a close look
at that
okay hello here I am look it's uh
chicken in a uniform if you look closely
but it looks so serious doesn't it
well I need to hide this Den
put you guys put you guys here
[Music]
oh it looks like it looks so much as
it's so traditional doesn't it
um
when he first sent me a draft of this
fan it was way more comical but then I
was like I wanted to be more
um you know Japanese traditional and
then he sent me this updated version and
I'm like dude
okay okay if you don't look too close
for you won't even notice huh
yeah there's also Fried Chicken on this
on on it do you see it
so I hope you like
[Music]
the whole relay is over on my channel
we'll be having a big worms collab with
all the myth girls and and we're gonna
all be wearing our beautiful kimonos so
yeah please come to see that I'm gonna
give you a few more moments uh with my
other hairstyle in case you wanted to
see uh this combination a bit more as
well
[Music]
foreign
I
guess I wanted to show you guys without
the filter as well
[Music]
because because it was so snowy and I
thought it looks better but here here is
uh me and all of my glory uh in the in
the void but shall we make it a
different color
uh okay we have two more minutes Thomas
speedrun
ah I don't even
it's only slightly different I suppose
but still uh noticeable well here you
can cut it out if you want
you can do something with that maybe
[Music]
yay and one more uh
back to this air and here we go thank
you so much thank you hope you liked it
and in German we say
[Music]
stream tomorrow as well into the worms
club and check out all the other kimono
reveals after this yay
[Music]
foreign