[Music]
ah
oh
[Music]
yeah that's cute
hi oh my technical difficulties hi
everybody welcome to my birthday party
it's so nice to see you
how is everybody wow we're crunched for
time now
thank you everything going wrong at the
very last second
hi everybody how are we good good i hope
we're all right
uh uh my brain is a bit scattered i'm
not gonna lie
thanks for um uh you see no matter how
much prep i do beforehand things stories
tend to go bad at the very last second i
would like to take this moment now to
give
you know the biggest thank you uh the
biggest thank you in the entire world
thank you anna thank you so much she
saved my butt big time oh my god
hi guys hello
how are we i'm shaking
i'm so fresh for tires i'm so shaky
because i just
i said i need to calm down for a second
i need to come down for a second
wait why is this not working ah wait a
second
so yeah play it for it
this might not work
who knows who knows who knows who knows
um anyway we're really pressed for time
uh so
[Music]
how is everybody i hope we're all very
good today
very very good thank you everybody for
your support today
[Music]
thank you everybody for all the art
you've made too as well
[Music]
what does anna say her ceiling is
leaking because
ah okay okay
uh anywho let's see thank you everybody
[Music]
ah
i held it together for a while though
we're good
[Music]
anyway i want to say thank you
to
run pc for help setting up my birthday
party thank you
thank you so much um
on let me do something really clear
okay
[Music]
all righty all righty give me a quick
second here
[Music]
oh
uh i don't know why this is it working
guys sorry anyway
time to move on okay so what do we have
planned today well all right let's see
what we can do
um what do we have here
wow it's been i want to say it's been a
year but it really hasn't been here it's
just been well it
was a birthday it's kind of weird we've
almost been a year together it's been a
couple
a couple months a couple months yeah
yeah
well no yeah but it's just a body here
right thank you guys for all your
your support thank you guys um
uh yeah
i got some i got some uh
i don't i don't think i'm gonna i was
gonna okay i was gonna do collins at the
beginning of the stream but we don't
have time for that and i also
i don't think i'd be able to keep myself
okay for those right now so maybe we'll
do them at the end of the stream i don't
really know
um we're just gonna have to see
so yeah that's literally have to say
this thank you guys
[Music]
oh my god what's wrong with me
what are you guys excited for i know
what you've been waiting for i know what
you've been waiting for should we talk
about that now
should we talk about how there's a
hollow live tradition
every birthday what do we do every
birthday
we have fun stuff planned every birthday
so let's start with the fun stuff right
i want to show you guys something that
oh okay
i want to show you guys uh some stuff
that you guys
actually sent to me you guys sent it to
i don't know how you guys got it too but
uh manager son
manager sent me some stuff from you guys
yeah some special stuff from you guys
um
and uh wait hold on i just
oh geez
ah
[Music]
wow okay
um
give me give me a second hold on
i gotta pick something here
[Music]
oh well oh well man
me and this jar here have gone round and
round for the longest time
man anyway look at all this cute fan art
you guys are the best someone made a
cake
honestly this cake looks a lot better
than mine did you guys see this cake
that i made
all right i'm recovered now sorry uh
anyway
oh god all right uh
wow okay let's take a moment let's take
a moment too oh dear god i forgot
something else
let's take a moment to reflect upon
these past few words
ah you think you'd think that
i have stuff under control but a lot of
times i don't
a lot of times i don't i'm still dyed
blue from the food coloring by the way
isn't that something
oh well
why is why well why is this not working
holy cow okay
uh
let's listen to what you guys had sent
me yeah
so these are special things from you
guys i haven't seen them yet i know what
they are
i know what they are but um i haven't
seen them in full
okay um
okay uh
i have an idea of what they are uh
anyway
let's see what is this what is this here
from
from our dear our dear shrimps what is
this
who is this
i understand that your birthday is june
20th
yeah how curious virgil is not so far
from my own
what are you doing here virgil well then
apex
predator from atlantis yeah this is
power what kind of power
huh what's power
what do you mean it's power get back
here stinky
wait a minute where's the rest of it
can't just leave me like that
virgil wait stop the music virgil
what's power i don't know what he was
talking about
holy cow though that was virgil virgil
virgil
get germinated get germinated virgil
holy cow how did you guys get
to do that
he's haunting me in my in my in my he
said my birthday part i didn't
invite virgil wait a minute there's also
this one
i'm feeling uh uh that's this one wait
hey that's my music
[Applause]
oh my god hey there little sharky
so here's your special day you know you
might have what it takes to be a
third-rate
demon hunter third wait what do you mean
second rate if you try hard enough
so gura yeah what you got planned this
special day well i had a lot planned but
cake okay yeah pizza yeah make sure you
hold those olives
well i better get back to work got
demons
sleigh and first flush so
on this very special day just make sure
you enjoy it with all those special
ladies you love so much
and happy special crazy birthday
[Music]
oh
captain i think we're gonna need a
bigger bowl
[Music]
thank you guys
okay i don't know what i did to deserve
people as nice as you
but thank you all so much
[Music]
okay i'm okay thank you guys seriously
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you guys it's really
oh
thank you thank you guys
a lot
wow one day
you guys have any dishes i could borrow
ah i was holding it together so well and
then
i don't know just everything went
everywhere
ah all right i'm okay
i'm okay oh okay oh good
i'm okay i'm okay
all right we're okay wow rachel
and dante and all of you and my birthday
party
never in a million freaking years did i
think this would ever happen
cool we're okay i'm okay
it's all good now it's all good now
thank you guys so much
cool thank you
okay
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna do this now
i'm gonna do this now let me
i'm sorry i had this all planned out
everything was so perfectly planned
apparently
i'm having trouble sinking on my feet
now
uh thank you guys so freaking much and i
sound like a broken record but really
thank you guys so much i'm so
i think i'm overwhelmed that's what it
is i think
i think sharky blew a fuse
i seem to have blown a fuse um
[Music]
uh anyway
um
[Music]
okay i'm recovering now i am fully
recovered now
wait actually i need to not do this hold
on
oh my god i'm all backwards we're gonna
do this first we're gonna do this first
hey guys can i give you a present now
can i give you a present instead i feel
like i you guys all right so
he just cry okay you guys want to talk
about
some fun stuff
i don't know there's only there's only
one way i feel like i can go back to you
guys
and um so let's start with that let's
start with some fun stuff
yeah hello
let's get this party started yeah
birthday celebration time
birthday celebration 2021 what a year it
has been
oh my goodness what a year
we have some fun stuff planned i hope
you guys like
like what we have planned we've worked
really hard on it
because i want to say we worked really
hard on it because
so many people have helped me with these
and i
i i'm so thankful and yeah so
each person involved in this has worked
so very hard on it
so we really hope you enjoy
okay what do we have first
let's make this tiny tiny we'll sit this
in the chum jar
[Music]
is my music too
man i've been streaming i've streamed
already twice today you think i'd have
had i've had this streaming thing down
already but i guess not
yikes
all right oh are you guys excited
are you nervous
just kidding let's see what's behind
door number one
let's see
hello wow is that a mouse pad
it looks like a mouse pad it's a squishy
cheek mouse pad
i told you guys i was gonna do this and
gosh darn it
we're gonna do it so instead of oppai
uh because we have squishy cheek mask
pad so it's kind of like oppai but it
says oppai it's
uh
sticks and a cute squishy
i don't know what millimeters are so
yeah and they're cute
that's designed by ikemuchi thank you
very much
so now you can rest your you can rest
your tired wrists
your tired carpal tunnel wrists on my
my squishy boing boing cheeks right
how exciting is that i'm excited
in a cute
ah how am i gonna put this
i don't know where i'm gonna put this
[Music]
cute boy yeah boy boy
squish squish squish what's your punchy
[\h__\h]
ah all right let's see let's see what
else do we have here
what else do we have here hmm
let me see we have uh-oh
oh boy
[Music]
what could this be next we have
dead on
wait a minute a t-shirt
awesome design by bizarre bite
mochi thank you we have a t-shirt
a t-shirt now my goal with the t-shirt
was i wanted something that was kind of
subtle
right subtle in a way where if somebody
looks at the t-shirt that you're wearing
they're not gonna be like wow okay guru
but like people that know me right
people somebody that's a shrimp is gonna
know you know
it's like our our secret club if you
know you know i guess
i guess yeah
t-shirt it comes in two sizes we got
large and extra large
uh what the cool thing about this
t-shirt uh let me point out a few things
about this there's a custom guru tag on
the inside
and then on the where is that
right right on your chest there there's
a trident you see the trident
that's actually embroidered so it's it's
a raised embroidered part which is
pretty cool
um and then there's a fish bone on the
right sand side on the sleeve right
there you can see it down on the left as
well
and then we have the mouse design like
on my hoodie
and then there's another red tag at the
very bottom for
cohesiveness to pull the three other
parts together the trident and the tag
on the inside
and then you see there's like blue
pieces you see
on the the the sleeves and at the very
bottom this is like a
like a false layer shirt if that makes
any sense so it looks like you're
wearing a layered t-shirt
but in actuality it's just one t-shirt
and i think that adds a really a really
really cool element to the t-shirt
yeah i think it's pretty nice i like it
i like it and i went for a shallow
v-neck
yeah no no deep v-necks just a nice
shallow v-neck
yeah i like it i hope it's subtle enough
i think it's pretty subtle don't you
i think it's pretty subtle how cool is
that though
nice so so i make sure that my shrimps
are stylish
all the chum buddies are stylish yeah
don't worry i got your back
i got your back very nice
[Music]
also with this one i forgot to mention
this we have voice packs yay voice pack
yay
special voice pack everybody likes a
voice pack what's a voice pack a voice
pack is my voice
just my voice in your ear special voice
in my in your ear in my ear in your ear
very nice very nice we have another
uh item item we have a bonus item
if why is it so if
bonus for complete voice and merch set
if you get the entire set you're gonna
get a postcard
a special postcard from me
to you a special guru birthday postcard
right
postcard
how cute i love my my my swimsuit i
asked for something super cute and
frilly
and yuko mochi mochi did it perfectly
and lots of cute cute little stickers
all around like little emojis and stuff
and bloop is there too how nice of bloop
to show up for my birthday stream bloop
thank you
you little jerk
very nice
nice padding would have been padding
yeah and you have a problem with padding
and swimwear
you weren't supposed to call it out so
easily stop it
so what you can take the padding out not
that i'm gonna
[Music]
anyway
oh my god
[Music]
bye girl birthday celebration 2021
we have voice pack we have alarm
collection i know you guys are always
asking for me to do like alarms and
stuff for you
so i did a little collection of alarms
with different types and stuff
uh that are more well done i guess you
could say
so uh yeah i hope you enjoy that we have
the mouse pad the t-shirt
special special bonus postcard as well
yeah special special
i also have another picture cause i
here's are you wondering what the merch
looks like in person
cause boy do i have a very special guest
for you to see
just that let's see who our special
guest
is can i get a drum roll for our special
our our model
oh boy could it be
[Music]
it's yago
wow thank you for modeling
you can see he's got the mouse pad and
he's got the t-shirt he's wearing the
t-shirt
he's wearing a collared shirt he's
actually i like the layer
game nice
[Music]
yeah you can see the double layer of the
t-shirt right and then at the very
bottom and you can see the red tag as
well
and the stripes and you can't really
tell that it's an embroidered trident
but it is it's a raised embroidered i
was really specific about that
i said i want the trident to be erased
like a
raised stitch embroidery i think is what
it's called but yeah
very very nice thank you yoga
thank you so much for modeling my
birthday stuff thank you
yahoo lucky we all go here
should i put yoga in the jar
[Music]
where'd you go
now go in the jar you can't really see
him hey what gives
jungle
[Music]
anyway let's bring up the other images
again so you can see
let's see now you can see
[Music]
wow
this is a lot of stuff on screen i'm
trying to
organize i hope you can see that all
right
maybe
oh no that's not the right one
[Music]
here's the menu
all right it goes it goes live i think
you can order
you can order everything in like five
minutes yeah i think there's gonna be a
tweet about it so if you wanna
if you wanna get on the the pre-order
list i think it's pre-order
you can get on the pre-order list in
about five minutes
five minutes get your goodies
come one come on get your goodies get
your get your goodies
all right stress level is down
considerably let me
let me just tell you that
oh my god
how is everybody i hope i did that in
time and i hope i'm not forgetting
anything
callie what
oh no no no chad was saying callie sorry
[Music]
hey wait wait wait wait wait wait i
can't hear you they can't hear you hold
on
i'm having another technical difficulty
because
uh oh my god
um give me give me one
second
uh brain
not working how do i do this
[Music]
yeah it's not picking up like it's not
stopped
[Music]
no i think i can fix hold on i think i
can
oh geez i don't know how to do this oh
hold on i'm gonna
ah wait a minute why
she's here
[Music]
um
i can i can i
can i can do
wait wait wait i can do this
[Music]
hold on hold on
yeah you learn by doing by
experimenting what is a trial by fire
and boy
boy am i roasty toasty crawled by fire
wow i i guess that that is a thing
however the volume is level but maybe
it's not that low
i could i could scream that's okay
that's okay
it should be better now okay so happy
birthday again
thank you
[Music]
you made me cry because you were crying
i'm i'm uh i'm yeah i'm sorry
that's so sweet i'm so happy for you
those videos like
i didn't play the game but already even
from someone who didn't play the game
that was so exciting
that seemed so so lovely and sweet and
fun
that they made you knows down and the
merge looks so good i was like
the chic mouse pad the first moment i
didn't realize
it was your cheeks so i was like did you
give yourself some boobies
no but i can dream a shark can dream
when you say those are cheeks but if you
if you see it
in a little bit of a different way you
could say that those
might be a butt
shaped jaw of chin
you said i have a button up right yeah a
butt chin
wow gee thanks you can see it as that
um ah those are obvious normal speaks
thank you i won't be able to unsee that
now thank you very much
oh you didn't see it until now okay all
right
i'm sorry but cheek my
i want it anyway those are actually
actually really comfortable
so yeah ah i'm gonna get one hey
uh i don't know if you saw it you were
probably busy before you streamed but i
made
uh an m shark video to wish you happy
birthday
you did yeah i just uploaded it before
you stream it's just me saying
i'm sure you know oh yeah before that
i'm obviously making a shark noise that
we all know
you should know it i know
yeah afterwards it's really short um but
yeah
i i i wish you a super lovely birthday
while i was making that
i'm shark video i burnt my noodles like
a legit burnt i was cooking noodles in
water and then i burnt them
would would you how do you burn water
wait hold on how did you burn water
yeah well i was cooking the noodles and
i was like
losing track of time while i was like
you know making the m shark video
uh i ran over and i noticed all the
water was gone
and i turned the noodles around and they
were like burnt
yeah um i can send them to you
if you would still eat them yes i will
yes i will did you get any of your sweat
in it
sweat i i can't i can add some
okay thank you wow wow okay also that
cake looks looked amazing
i like you take up much more time but
because i have to go to sleep
but but i wish you a lovely birthday and
you are amazing i am so happy that
you're part of halloween
and i hope we can do many more fun
things in the future
and like for example
and i will give you the biggest hug and
kisses ever
once we meet and then i i'll also
take a little bite from you i'm okay
with that
[Music]
um i know i know
life is [\h__\h] stressful just take it
one at a time
and you take it take it easy i know it's
everything's overwhelming but i think
everyone understands that
and we are here for you to support you
if you ever need something i'm always
here to help
okay if you need someone to draw your
ttrpg character
i'm not the best i'm not as good as nina
but i can draw it for you
thank you
[Music]
oh wait you probably already know that
phrase don't you uh
from ina's birthday stream but that's it
all right let's get it out of you
squeeze it out alex
what's up perfect i'll send you
i'll send you something in between one
two five
apples thank you
man she came in here with the butt chin
and now oh hey what's up
watching hahaha funny oh funny
funny watson is here comedian how are
you what's up
stinky hello
thank you your shirt looks so
freaking cool actually you like it
yeah it looks like high fashion like uh
i don't know like i could see it in a
at the mall you know at the moment the
mall is high fashion
no not like that but
i guess people trying to buy it at a
expensive store somewhere that's not a
mall okay
well thank you i i appreciate it
it looks like a designer thing that's
what i'm trying to say yeah you like the
designers oh i get like design
okay that i see that i see maybe it's
the trident emblem um
hi
uh i wanted to say that um
you know i'm really proud of you i don't
know like oh good
sorry no it's
oh you know like since the first time
that i knew you
met you i was gonna do something really
special
and now the whole world knows it too so
uh i'm really proud of you um
happy birthday thank you and also
i have uh this for you
i see that this is me
uh ignore the calls from before i oh
you're calling me
i should have picked up hello
you made this for me my ceiling is
leaking almost a year ago
almost a year ago what the first well
the first ever
wait did you you posted this in the
discord didn't you you sent this to me
like way back
okay yeah it's almost been a year yeah
that's crazy
[Music]
do you have a tissue i can borrow ah
can i use your sleeve yeah you can use
my jacket thank you
is that where i can is there like a drag
and drop way i can do this
i always try drag and drop but it never
ever works i don't know why
yeah uh if you ever launch obs is admin
for some reason drag and drop doesn't
work on there
but uh nah there's no easy way to do it
let me know other people check it out
can you see it on twitter it's on
twitter we'll see what all my boys say
on twitter
it's so cute i've already tweeted that's
what i'm going to do
thank you thank you
omi thank you so much thank you for for
all the help you've
you've always you've always been there
at like the drop of a hat whenever i
need something
for today you were streaming you were
busy
stop it stop it you were busy the
discord discord
the streamer mode stops me from seeing
the notifications
you were streaming i mean i had to
stream up in a tab so i knew i knew
yeah and i were trying to fix it so i'll
thank you thank you so much
no problem all right leave you done uh
good luck on the rest of your stream
thank you thank you
that was that's true it was like a year
ago that she made these
it was like a year ago a year ago
a year ago at this time i think we were
all still
we just met each other i think we all we
were all hanging out
and i remember almighty made this and
she sent it to me
i think i drew some stuff on me too we
were all making like art of each other
ah michael
ah you have no idea how hard i am i'm
holding uh
more tears back oh
okay i got it i got it all out earlier i
got it all out earlier
hi
[Music]
thank you so much you are such a big
help
i'm the uh the uh what's your say
sub sub tech support
strongest tech support team think i
figured it out but
uh we'll talk about it it was what it
did you got it working perfectly and
then it was working perfectly for me and
then
it wasn't the uh actual problem that we
were having but
let's talk about it after we're here to
celebrate
uh okay sharks happy day
me me me yeah yeah yeah
the uh the the recorder gods have uh
oh baby happy birthday
oh god i forgot to do this okay
[Music]
me
one more thing for you give me a second
to find it
oh no uh
i also just want to say while i'm
looking for the file ah
i am so so so proud of you
for everything you're such a strong
strong shark
i forgot to fix my ceiling yesterday
my ceiling is leaking too we can't have
this
[Laughter]
[Music]
you will do so many
amazing things with our uh
with everyone in ian hall alive
i'm so proud of you
[Music]
give me all the headphones for me when
we meet one day
back breaking hug vertebrae or no
vertebrae all right
here's the deal i'm uh
for you i will be a taco and i'll say i
don't have a bones to break i think i
think they don't have bones to break so
it'll be fine it'll be fine
yes thank you
thank you
[Music]
okay
oh my god
sorry guys i tried my best here
so hello
oh god hi can you hear me
hi yes i can what's up i'm hi
i'm sorry i'm i'm just i'm sorry gosh
i'm at a hotel i just i just checked out
of the hotel but i had to make sure i
could call you to say
happy birthday thank you
kelly
sorry you're cutting out a little bit
okay sorry i think it's fine now
i think it's fine now yeah anyway i
wanted to say
um i hope you have the best birthday
ever i wanted to wish
the happiest birthday to the cutest
shark that i know the only shark that i
know
it doesn't change the fact you still be
the cutest that's the truth
so yeah and also i wanted to say uh the
birthday cake that you made
yeah looked really really delicious um
it said
uh it said feet on it so i have a
question oh gosh what is it um
it doesn't actually what does it taste
like uh
please please don't say feet please
don't say feet because every time i look
at that cake
i just imagine that it tastes like feet
you know what feet tastes like
um uh anyway let's maybe forget that i
asked that question
let's really forget that i asked that
question
sorry it looks very delicious though it
looks
it looks very tasty oh thank you thank
you
and i'm really looking forward to
resting um resting my
my hand on your on your cheeks uh huh
yeah there sorry there are a lot of cars
around here gosh
um please have a wonderful birthday girl
i'm really excited for all the stuff
that you're doing and um
i can't wait to keep having more fun
together thank you cali
have you been spending your day nicely i
did i spent it streaming
for the most part i hope
it was really fun i was able to tune in
occasionally but uh
as you know it's kind of morning time
here so i got you
i got it yeah but i can't wait to go
re-watch everything
i'm a little busy yeah well thank you
you made time you're on you're out busy
doing stuff and you still make time to
call me thank you
you're welcome my dude i i love you my
dog please take care of yourself
i love you too
i'll be my dog let's uh let's keep
having fun and
please treat yourself really really well
today
um for the rest of the evening and
tomorrow as well just do whatever you
want dude just do whatever the heck you
want
okay thank you thank you all right my
dog i gotta go
but um happy birthday okay have a great
rest your birthday thank you callie
thank you
bye bye bye peace
wow
uh we're okay we're okay we're not done
here guys we're not done here
oh no i know i'm not done with you yet
i'm not gonna miss you yet
okay i oh my god
they are they are i am so lucky to have
each of them in my life
and i'm so lucky to have all of you in
my life
i've been so emotional this stream it
wasn't supposed to be like this i don't
know why i like this
but i'm sorry um but
i have if i
i have i have something else that is
i hope you will enjoy um
that i think a lot of you have been
looking forward to
god somebody call somebody call a
plumber here i am i am
a leaky leaky leaky leaky
um yeah one more thing for all of you
everybody um it's something that
i think you've all been looking forward
to and um
yeah and i really hope that you will
enjoy it
are you ready everybody i need to be
ready i don't know if i'm ready
i was ready but now i'm not so sure
anymore let me make this smaller can i
hold on can i have a second i just want
to make this a little bit smaller
or not i guess not it's fine as it is
we're just gonna leave it then
okay
[Music]
are you ready everybody
are you ready can we hold hands while we
do this
oh god i'm such an emotional wreck
okay
[Music]
listen to it again sure why not here it
is
what you just listened to is a sneak
preview of my
very first original song that is coming
coming out june 22nd uh
midnight global time wherever you are
midnight
um and it's something that
it's something that i've worked really
hard on and um
and i'm really excited and um
and i hope that you are all looking
forward to it it's gonna be june
june 22nd june 22nd
june 22nd
wherever you are june 22nd at midnight
it will be releasing yes an original
song i know
do you know how long it's taken me not
to accidentally click on on this audio
on stream
i've been so nervous i'm like i'm gonna
miss click sometimes
ah here let me put on if i put on music
again this might be loud i'm sorry wait
a second let me pull this back down here
okay yeah
i don't have a video a video for you
right now
i only have that little snippet but the
song will be coming out very soon in
like a day
a day for some of you two days 42 hours
yes
that's very fast um maybe we can do like
a release party
maybe do you like the drums in it
do you feel the drums in your soul
[Music]
i do have an image for you maybe
let me see if i can get this let's see
if baby can control
obs for a second let me see
let me see here oh wait maybe i can do
this
i can do this wait look at this
[Music]
hold on i do have a picture for you
oh my god why is it so tiny wait a
minute this might not work out very well
wait i have a picture for you i'm just
unprepared as usual
[Music]
is it gonna be small it's absolutely
tiny
why though
hold on i have a picture for you
you have
[Music]
give me a second
there it is all right you ready to see
the jacketed match we got the jacket
image
yay oh dear god
damn
expected maybe i don't know anyway
here's the image
reflect by gargra yes
yes reflect
okay
[Music]
wow
wow you know honestly now
i figured out how to do this i'm gonna
do this too
[Music]
isn't that exciting
yeah yeah reflect
i hope you i hope you're excited for it
because i know i'm excited for it
ah also i wanna i wanna show you
i wanna show you um me do
this
[Music]
this may not work this will probably
change this
now that i figured this out
eena made this this is what i was uh
this is what you know made
look
oh you're making
[Music]
thank you
you want to hear the preview again you
wanna
let's do the preview one more time wow
preview while you can see it
maybe this time i actually have the
audio all set up maybe
unlikely though hey name
[Music]
all right that's all i have for you that
is all i have for you and that is all
she wrote and by she i mean me that is
all i had planned
i think i might be missing something
i'm probably missing something but i
think that's all i had really
oh loud okay audio ha ha
[Music]
so everybody thank you
thank you for today
thank you i'm
sorry i was so emotional but thank you
for having patience with me
and for thank you all
to my to my friends for for coming and
saying hi
to me and making me laugh and cry
i forgot to mention the artist of the
artist of the jacket cover at home
dog you are missing something
thank you thank you thank you
the artist for my jacket cover for my
original song
thank you so much
thank you thank you guys
wow
[Music]
wow what a crazy year it's been
well not even a year what are crazy how
many months are we in now are we
like how many months
uh nine i said didn't i say nine i think
he's nine months ten months
but we're getting up to the ten month
mark that's pretty crazy
that's pretty crazy
[Music]
well thank you guys so much
um i have a lot of i actually have i'm
excited for next week because i have
streams planned
next week but i do think i need i'm
definitely gonna need a day to sleep
for like 24 hours but after that i think
i'll be good to go
we'll see though we're gonna have to see
we're gonna have to see i hope you guys
enjoy
what what we've prepared for you yeah i
wanna say if anybody
that has helped with the merchandise or
the merchandise
or with reflect if you're watching this
i want to say thank you so much
because uh without you it would not have
happened
so thank you so much
no we're not getting emotional again my
god
oh god okay
i wanna again i wanna say thank you to
all of you seriously
thank you all so much because
without you without you
i i i don't know where i would be
without you and i'm so lucky to have
each and every one of you
my voice is turning into tiny voice
i think i need some i think i need some
birthday cakes
give me that sugar rush um
but yeah i wanna i do wanna say thank
you guys thank you so much
um
you guys
you make me make me laugh you make me
cry
i feel like we've shared so many i've
had so many
firsts you know and i've got to share
them with you
and they're in there because of you as
well
so thank you guys thank you so much
[Music]
this is all i have for you today thank
you everybody who used
the the guru art hashtag i really
appreciate
it each and every one of you that has
drawn any art or animations holy cow the
animations
and the arts and the videos
probably more in the hashtag i need to
see it there's so much
i thought i got a lot of it but there's
so much more
it's endless
[Music]
thank you so much thank you so much
oh all right though that's all i have
for you this is all i have
um like i said though i think merch
should be available right now so if you
want to get on that pre-order list for
any of the stuff you see here
then i think you should be good to go
and then reflect
i'll have lots of more information about
reflect and stuff like that
um probably after the stream i don't
know
uh and i'll i'll talk more a bit more
about it i'm so excited to talk about
like
the recording process and stuff like
that
and like the everything about it i just
want to talk all about it
so i don't think it's sold out i don't
think it's sold out i think it's um
no i don't think it's sold out don't
worry i think it might you know the
website's
like oh my god or or maybe
does pre-order stuff say it's sold out
i don't think it's sold out because it's
pre-order so don't worry about it you
can still get it don't worry don't worry
don't worry don't worry
it just went live now
oh it's on sale now okay it's available
now then
i hope you like the voice pack as well i
hope you like it
we can talk about this stuff more later
definitely i want to chat about it
yeah also also all the
super chats that we have to think oh my
goodness we have a we have a we have a
we need to have a sit down all of us
a nice sit down ah look there it
birthday is there's the link
look i tweeted it look ma no hands i
didn't tweet it
what is that can i paint a pink pin that
how do we pin that it's gone now where
did it go pin
[Music]
disappeared into a c pin nice
i think your manager sounds like yo
there you go there's your link if you
want to go and check it out
okay everybody i uh
i don't know what else to say i really
don't
i don't know what else to say other than
thank you that seems to be the only
thing i can say is thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
i think what do i say now
i think i think i'm gonna go i don't
know what else to say
[Music]
thank you everybody i had a very happy
birthday thanks to all of you
i did wait hold on what
am i missing something wait a minute
i think i'm missing something
[Music]
ah i missed something
i missed something hold on manager
assigned to the rescue
again yeah i think we have something
nice
exciting should we take yahoo out of the
jar i feel bad
[Music]
there he is
all right
oh god what is this
[Music]
what is this it's a pdf should i be
nervous
what is this
pdf how to stream your guru
[Music]
we've noticed that
you struggle a lot so here's the pdf guy
that we've assembled
did you i just what is this
am i gonna cry again
i'm gonna oh my god
oh no
[Music]
holy cow there's a hundred and how many
of these are
there polish
[Music]
is 250 oh my god
ah okay
[Music]
is there a way i could show this i don't
i don't know how this i'm scared
[Music]
this is it's a pdf of of of
are these letters from you guys
i think it's letters dear guru
gargumba gargoyle shark g floaty goomba
roomba gar guru from youtube buddy
oh my god
it's a pdf of 200
to 250 letters written by all of you
[Music]
ah
dear guru
this book was made just for you it was
made with the help from your community
of fans of
an artist and it was put together by a
small team of people that's
us this is a i don't know if i can read
this
this is a unique gift for you there will
only ever be one
copy of this book unless you ask for
another copy of course
none of us have any experience in doing
this kind of thing so we apologize if
it's a bit scuffed hey that's all right
the stream is pretty scuffed too even if
there are parts of it that looks strange
or if there are mistakes that we don't
notice we hope you'll love it just the
same
after all it reminds us a little of you
sometimes a little scuffed but still
awesome happy birthday
this is a present from your community
straight to you
this book is not waterproof reading in
the tub is not advised
oh my god
[Music]
we have verizon and we have anonymous
elena unlucky lira
[Music]
oh nice images thank you wait i can show
this
wait i can show this
sorry yoga i have to sacrifice you
hold on i'm waiting i'm waiting
nice all right
[Music]
let me do this
i'm going to show you i'm going to show
you one of them give me a second
sorry she's really unprepared but we
already know this
where is it coco
[Music]
this is from doodle doodle made doodle
made one of the animations
the summit summit summit summit
will cry
hey sharky i hope you have an amazing
birthday you really deserve it thank you
so much for all the fun streams and
making the day so much better
know that i'll be for everything
know that i'll be oh then i'll be
forever thankful to you
huh
[Music]
no i can't
know that i'll be forever thankful to
you for
bringing back my animation passion
now go get yourself some great food
thank you doodle
thank you thank you i do love me
some burger i do
i do i do i do
i do
well this one here
this one here
[Music]
this is from let me scroll so i can see
it
[Music]
is
for being here and making my days
brighter lots of love happy birthday
thank you i'm sorry is it blurry it's
blurry thank you
thank you look at it there's all the
memories
yeah inna and i one to five with keanu
cool glasses like cali rhythm game
fishing christmas
[Music]
oh boy
what does this one say let's see
hi there glitter i have so much to say
about how you've helped me
through to tough times and how you've
made me want to look forward for every
new day ahead
i can't really put everything in the
words but your singings and streams
in general bring me joy i'd like to
thank you for everything that you've
done so far and congratulate you for
everything that you've achieved
here's two more things to look forward
to cheers to you little sharky
nice shorty thank you huh
thank you thank you so much
cool
i should have got tissues before this
hahaha
who is this let me see here
hide thank you happy
nine mystery mister mystery birthday
girl don't eat too much
yeah what if i want to you can't stop me
try
just try try stop me
you can't stop me thank you hi thank you
thank you thank you
lmit hi thank you
[Music]
nothing beats a great smile
look at all the it's like a it's like a
uh uh well a coconut compilation a
collage in the in the background
of my face
[Music]
every moment spent together is a moment
we cherish
be silly be fun and be different be
crazy be you the best track that we love
and cheer for
ah thank you i don't know how many more
of these i can do you guys
i'm going to read them all of course
absolutely
absolutely i will read these all maybe
maybe
maybe the the next dream when we do the
super chats as well we can read all of
these
[Music]
oh my god you guys
so much work within this there's so many
[Music]
horror time you were able to connect so
many people across the world thank you
for your hard work
thank you is that
is that is that this type of cake it's
called is it like the one with
lots of layers of crepes and stuff
it looks like dessert yummy thank you
hard time
thank you we have one more
thank you manager
hi how do we say your name mish
misho thanks oh thank you
artist of this book cover i just wanted
to say
here we go okay we can do this i just
wanted to say that you
and everyone at hall alive have had an
incredible influence on my art journey
as well as numerous other artists
you have fostered an incredible
community of creation and inclusivity
and i want to thank you for that
without hollow life without you my
artistic development would have never
come this far
for that please enjoy the illustration
and book i look forward to what comes
next
thank you thank you so much thank you
everybody so much
[Music]
wow
thank you guys thank you all so much
oh from the phone oh god i didn't have a
headache from like lack of air
[Music]
why has it been such a roller coaster
i've laughed i've cried
up and down i've never had a birthday
like this before
ever in all of my years well i hope it's
a ps5
um what an incredible birthday this has
been nothing ever i've never experienced
something like this before
so before we go i just wanna i just
wanna say
one more one more absolutely humongous
thank you to all of you
seriously thank you so much
i hope you are excited or
reflect to to be in your ears
soon i hope those of you that
are excited for the merchandise
i hope you you get your hands on it soon
[Music]
thank you for this week
it's been a lot of fun um
thank you guys i'm going to go now
and blow my nose because i can't breathe
out of my nose
so one more one more
big huge thank you guys
and with that i am going to say
bye bye bye
thank you again
okay thank you thank you for this
thank you for this day thank you for
everything
have a good one i'll see you i'll see
you guys i'll see you guys soon
okay
[Music]
oh yeah
thank you bye
bye bye bye bye
let's watch these again on the way out
okay bye bye bye
[Music]
summit
yeah that's cute
[Music]
you