[Music]
thank you
thank you foreign
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Laughter]
oh my God wait wait wait wait wait hello
welcome everybody
ah okay
um I am I am very very nervous right now
because uh I mean I'm not really nervous
but oops I was trying to practice this
one Vocaloid song and and it's like so
fast it's like
and uh yeah it ended up with me having
almost a heart attack because my my BPM
uh was going up to high I think my
eyebrows feeling my Doki Doki in my
heart and uh I realized it's okay maybe
maybe I shouldn't be I'm first yes
shouldn't be singing that song after all
I prepared a lot of other songs
um but I've had one vocalized on it I
promised you guys that I would be
singing I can't do it after all look at
the
it's not a Happy New Year to some
countries and not yet Happy New Year to
other countries what do you mean I'm
muted what do you mean I'm muted I'm not
muted
oh God oh God oh okay
oh man first of all one question uh
don't like during my singing there will
be uh a time zone that will be
celebrating New Year's does anyone know
which one like which which countries are
celebrating the New Year's with me
does anybody know that because I was
wondering because most SCA countries are
already there uh my country is not quite
yet there
India
okay I need to brief oh my God
Central Asia UK front strip no no no no
no here right now I am there and it is
currently half past 8 PM so it can't be
us we still have a couple hours to go oh
oh Philippines Malaysia really in 30
minutes you have your Okay who in the
chat has their new year in 30 minutes
that's that's the simple question and
where are you from
me Siberia
don't lie to me
oh everyone who says Germany must not be
in Germany and have no idea what they're
talking about
oh well okay anyway it will be New
Year's for someone for someone ah oh the
Emirates really is that so I don't trust
anything that the chat says anymore at
this point
anyway so um I am the top batter do you
say that in English too I learned it in
Japanese even though it's an English
word
this is this is the homo Ian New Year's
karaoke relay
[Music]
I am the opening act indeed um
and uh here is a if you haven't seen it
yet the time schedule is right next to
me it's starting off of me Kiana and
then Sana crony mume
Iris Kelly AME and ending it with a gura
and then Edgar stream at the very end
there will be some kind of announcement
regarding hello live English perhaps I
don't know uh
so please look forward to that and uh oh
yeah so you can see the there's a
There's the link to the schedule is also
pinned in my uh comments so if you want
to see it bigger but you will notice
that there are 15 minute breaks in
between each slot and that is in order
to you know prepare for delays
beforehand so if anyone wants to go a
little bit longer hi Sana you're here
thank you I will watch yours too if
anyone wants to go a little bit longer I
told everybody that's okay too as long
as you don't overlap with the starting
time of the next member and uh yeah
everybody will be doing 45 to 60 minutes
because of that Hi and then
is
[Music]
yeah and so yeah yeah I don't know what
else to say should I start singing I
don't know oh my God
so last minute and then I was also
practicing songs uh until last minute
until I swear until three minutes before
the stream I was still practicing this
this super fast Vocaloid song and I just
can't get it right I think not yet not
yet I mean it's I can get it right but
not 100 perfect it's like 90 perfect
anyway um now let's get started because
we already have eight minutes behind us
but don't worry I have more than enough
time I have more than enough time I got
this i got this in the bag I got this in
the bag all right
so shall we go to the stage
and calm the [\h__\h] down I have uh by the
way oh yeah one last thing my stream
will be archived but some of the other
girls streams will not be archived
um I know that
uh Bae it will be archived and
you know I think too but besides that I
am not sure most of them will not be
archived so make sure to check them out
okay okay uh Celebration Time come on
let me drink some water right
oh oh one last thing my uh stream
um uh that I was planning today the clip
stream will be happening tomorrow
instead in order so that I can prepare
better for this and I can also prepare
better for the clipstream understanding
yeah yeah
okay
do you notice that I have troubles
breathing right now or taking a freaking
break but what can you do it's exciting
it's [\h__\h]
oh
huh
hello hello see for times like this
these outfits are perfect aren't they
yeah
um okay where shall we start uh
I have an interesting set list I think
you will realize I have some joke songs
and I have some serious songs and then I
have some songs that everybody knows
um I will start by hyping up the crowd
out with this banger
uh what was actually the well the full
title was I only know it is
something else
full title is actually ah
maybe you guys recognize it doki
call you know
let's find this
okay okay
let's go
I recorded a little bit of a background
vocals for this one
um
[Music]
my money
hi hi
hi hi hi
everybody
[Music]
beautiful
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
[Music]
blah
foreign
[Music]
oh
you didn't hear that that was the
spoiler for everybody who knows that
song
[Music]
that wasn't so cool Idol song
did you like that I'm sure a lot of you
guys have heard this song before it's
very famous in the idol world
hi
hi hi hi
yes yes yes yes yes yes thank God what a
nice way to start it off right Perfect
song Perfect song to start it off
yeah uh well
then
oh
let me uh well quickly I forgot to bring
out these lyrics
uh
next song is one of my favorite anime
songs to sing
okay I hope these lyrics are correct
they should be
Michelle
it's
on this
so
raps
yeah rap no wraps sorry I can't type
let's go
there it is
oh yeah
please me
without you
oh yeah
um
[Music]
don't go anymore
communication
[Music]
I don't see them anymore
foreign
[Music]
we are
here
[Music]
clap your effing hands
let's go
[Music]
back
foreign
[Music]
without you
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah Rhapsody
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
oh by the way I feel I feel it would be
nice to have the graphic up here for
everybody
there we go let's put it up here
everybody could see it at any given time
yeah thank you
[Music]
thank you
Happy New Years by the way I
I if you didn't know I had a stream
today on the whole life official Channel
um they had like a long uh stream where
like all kinds of programs were
happening and I was participating in the
one that I also participated in last
year
um
I still have time right I think I still
have time
I still have 40 minutes okay and and and
and and
um uh and that was fun but I barely got
to sleep so I took a nap afterwards and
in my dream of that nap I dreamed that I
would I overslept for this very stream
and I'm panicked because hey I'm the one
kicking it off I can't I can't oversleep
it was horrible I was really um uh
terrified by that dream I woke up and
for a moment I still thought that I
overslept and I looked at the time and
I'm like oh thank God I still have two
hours of nap time
foreign
um
next song which one should we do
which one should we do
well in in the end we will sing all of
them
let's do
let's do this one first
or should I ah
um
let's sing
I think this one okay okay okay okay
got these stupid websites with so much
so many advertisements I should have
copied it and put it into a different
word file anyway time to sing
a famous
very famous
hot it had it you kind and y'all are
welcome to dance behind the scenes
because with this body I cannot dance
myself
um
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
she can't
today
[Music]
that's
um
Loki dancing
foreign
[Music]
when did I turn so big
foreign
[Music]
actually
the song
[Music]
I was trying to dance did you notice
if you know the dance then maybe you
notice the feel of my movements as far
as I can move my body
oh
haha I feel like I I might be wrong but
now that I'm singing it it feels like I
never actually sang this one in my
stream sport did I it almost feels wrong
even if I did then maybe only once I
know I said God knows definitely
this one
might even be the first time I'm seeing
this
I think you did I didn't I don't think I
did yeah I don't think I did how did I
never seen this one
well that's that's good we have a lot of
new songs that I have never properly
sang before and the next one is one of
the
ah
get into the mood
starts with a B
no just kidding that's not it
that's the wrong B song
[Music]
foreign
time
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I know you
foreign
[Music]
what
oh my God
I was so enjoyed I didn't notice what
the hell happened
a bunch of
[Music]
happiness oh that was the wrong song to
sing at that time and God damn it
no no
okay maybe
um maybe we have something more uh
cheerful now uh I have a candy pen
so maybe let's sing it that way every
once in a while
let's go how much more time do I have
okay okay in theory I still have 20 uh
seven minutes but yeah okay okay
was emotional wasn't it I almost cried
let's go
[Music]
jump down
Showtime
[Music]
one two three
fall in love
[Music]
will you see
me
[Music]
one two three
falling
[Music]
[Applause]
one two three
[Music]
music
yeah yeah thank you thank you
enough
[Music]
can you put me up on your songs are so
fun so much fun
I don't know if if I'm like too too
quick or too slow but uh let's
immediately go oopsie oops into the next
song which is one of my uh beloved songs
um that I love very much
you're beautiful
hope the audio is fine
oh let's go
let's attend
tent and airplanes no no no not like
that I don't pretend like that don't we
all love Pretender I especially love
Panda the Pentatonix version
um but we're gonna sing the OG
I haven't seen this in a while song
[Music]
all right
oh sorry it's not fool Fighters
[Music]
I need to drink water
level stories
[Music]
cheetah
my mother said guys
[Music]
[Applause]
Italian
[Music]
foreign
you're beautiful
[Music]
Italian
goodbye tonight
[Music]
I forgot that it was like that oops
goodbye
[Music]
Italian
foreign
[Music]
yeah thank you oh now I'm bringing to
you a song that when I first sang it in
my uh stream wait I just realized what
the hell is this
this song is something that when I sang
and you guys went absolutely crazy for
it but I felt like I could probably sing
it better eventually so yeah I'll give
it another try
by Golden bomber remember that one
remember that one
um
[Music]
I will try to like oh singing them like
two two different voices again though
let's go
[Music]
foreign
memories
[Music]
foreign
give me
something
[Music]
foreign
did you like my choreography it's a
little bit inspired by the original
dance because they kind of they go like
maybe she didn't understand like the
dance actually goes like that
you guys need to watch the OG video this
is my golden bomber there is so good
golden bomber they are they are Divine
one might say how much more time do I
have 10 more minutes okay okay no time
I learned a new beautiful song for you
guys uh a new a new macro song from
Maine from Cheryl
I believe it's called North from Cross
I think we can fit in two more songs
now if I'm quick maybe oh God quick
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I
I I I I I I I I I
I I
[Music]
don't know
foreign
[Music]
which will start right away sorry I
didn't think I would actually take that
long but no worries we're not
overlapping yet she's starting in six
minutes
only virgin is my last song
Michelle
[Music]
I love you guys
Happy New
[Music]
year
my soul is
[Music]
foreign
alligator
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
stream I'll put it up in the in the chat
bye
[Music]
check it out
you'll miss it otherwise
Rachel and here is the link
come on
button Touch button button touch
see you tomorrow