[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
welcome to Among Us with whole life
English and Indonesia
hi hell yeah oh Lordy
we have Gabbert here today to present to
you a new feature that just was updated
in Among Us for the whole life
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
okay yes wow
then you can like get outfits from
selective members from Whole Life en ID
and Japan this these streams are not
sponsored but we just really want to
show you also good look at everything so
oh
[Music]
uh number one detective I'm naked
um
introduction
[Applause]
[Music]
hello everyone I'm shirakamian today
nice to meet you guys
[Music]
Nation hello thanks for having me
hi hi
okay next we have Clio primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even fucking bother why
even bother yeah Mommy I need to get
some whole of Swag as a sheriff let's
party
[Music]
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now we're right
Among Us
[Music]
you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore
I love it oh God sharklings around here
[Music]
[Laughter]
right now oh my God
hello
[Music]
it's a crazy building
oh my God
right now
[Music]
it's suspicious
happy
so part of the people whose outfits you
can get in the game
hi everyone
from Whole Life Indonesia generation one
nice to meet you you're wearing your own
hair oh yeah yeah
I feel like right now I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
I'm I'm doing a touring love in the
Among Us
oh hey
yeah yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy this looks like Felix senpai's
face I am chocolate ice cream today
chocolate ice cream we're working on it
yeah spicy
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah understandable all right
now
today I'm cosplaying as sexy naked money
that Depression was so good that
impression was so good what the heck as
expected from Madison
wow wow and then we have Zetta
hello hello hello
I am I will be the second
today
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God
you've been grinding Lots around okay oh
it sounds fun at least the organizer of
today's event the sponsor of today's
event
let's go
[Music]
of course of course that happened one
second now we'll open a new one that
timing was amazing yeah that time it was
amazing the fact that that happened on
your turn yeah yeah so sad yeah okay a
new code is in the Discord chat please
please go get it and don't make it seem
to the yeah
one second
ah hello oh that looks funny comedy gold
okay I'm gonna I'm gonna and put the
code please wait a moment okay I'm
inside hello and let's let's re
introduce
[Music]
and
um I will now change the world settings
we will have everything included we'll
have scientists
can see the vitals at any time no not
anytime well there's a countdown but you
can see if someone's dead before finding
the body and then we have the engineer
engineer can uh is a crewmate who can
jump into the
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that might be
helpful meeting in the vents oh yeah oh
no that's that would be too spicy for
you too
you're very spicy and now we have the
guardian angel which I thought was
really useful because the guardian angel
is the ghost of the first crewmate that
dies who can then go on to protect
others from Death yeah that sounds loud
that sounds so fun I can't do that yeah
and then we have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is that that
calls for a lot of
fights
[Music]
shapeshifter can be only an imposter but
that imposter can change the looks of
themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her other people will think wow
oh my god well if I was the one who
found you instead there would be two
anions on reception
oh no
to ancient weapons
but just so you know all of these roles
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know what happened to you now
let's okay
[Music]
before another it's something it's
something
oh my God
everybody everybody
says
oh my God
what are you loving like that Milson
because you're not the music I know
oh oh
yeah
hold on
okay oh God I need to do my task
um I don't know this map
um I I I I don't know this map
um
okay
main main hall the contaminate where do
you do that
what the heck
what the heck all right I'm gonna go to
the um Communications instead
I don't know this map guys I'm sorry
this is like
that
was fast um yeah
[Music]
really
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes that's like uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory but like oh but that
was the beginning I was in the guest
room when it was well she got killed
fast
you know
something I have no idea though I didn't
see anyone okay so you can uh if if you
are you were telling me that um I was in
a Armory you can ask a gura because I
saw Guru also in uh nearby there in the
kitchen
um yeah
[Music]
oh the way the way the voice comes that
was that was pretty funny
the way the voice subtly cuts
I want to do a task two I need to do my
task oh damn it
um what
use
oh okay okay okay okay cargo bay oh um
we can unlock safe oh hello
[Music]
unlock seven man away
unlock safe doco
here oh oh here I see it
five
do you do it like this
what
oh four hello is that you're gouda
senpai
right
I saved movie at first how the hell do
you do this
eh
name
bye
all right um anyways um let's go make
some burgers you know that will be
that'll be so spicy I need to go to the
kitchen oh electrical
um yeah I have a task at electrical what
is this
oh PL something I don't know I have no
idea what is it Halloween
Ahoy
use this
hello
don't kill me don't kill me no I don't
want to speak with you what
when I got to do my task please don't
kill me
no I said mermaid at first
but I didn't I I didn't believe myself
and I was like all right I was doing my
test
oh yeah it's lights off okay
oh um God damn it
it's hard oh my God come on man oh my
God
is that is dead kitchen
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical I was going to be here I was
with a roommate and Kelly senpai
I passed by I passed by I think it was
Watson or and
and gura in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw zado they were in
the main hall with Kobo Cobo
so I have no idea
about global because uh she she telling
me on the previous one it was me well I
definitely like far away from the
kitchen and now
um kitchen right around yeah no okay I
saw coldfield but like she left I was
like hi Coco but then she left
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobble yeah
any last words
was like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh see herself like like just
what she said and then after that I go
up
right near the lounge
that was beginning though that was the
very beginning I have no idea after that
I go up
[Music]
I go after killing her you mean
[Laughter]
we have like we have little short time
uh shoes
enough information I have no idea yeah
I'm gonna follow what everyone's doing
okay okay
oh that's a lot of people
that's a lot of votes
okay
rip couple
let's see koble at the at the very
beginning but like
rip clay
I'm on to you Mommy
oh no they didn't uh
I'm going back
let's go to samba's Voice um do I have
something to do here yeah I need to
download datas
um oh it was
um where Kiara Senpai died
I have no idea I was just like following
votes oh hello Raina what the heck
so scary what the heck
really kind of sucks not gonna lie is it
the IDS
I feel like at least one ID is the
Imposter this time
foreign
security
connection poor what
is
hey what's this hello hello
wait how how can I upload
[Music]
that's insane Watson is dead uh I found
them
this time oh yeah ah um okay so I was in
the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like he hates
he and doing things and then I walk out
and Watson's dead body is there
Watson if you were entering the front of
the ship you would have passed Watson
how did you not see her well I don't
know but I did pass I want to say I
passed gura and I would be
people people didn't
I asked him yeah oh okay yeah then you
freaked me out
I'm not gonna point fingers at you
immediately I just want to know what
your Alibi is no no I'm not I just want
to know what your Alibi is because I
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about I don't know do you
remember so much Kelly I'm I'm just
surprised I got a lot to say I don't all
right now listen here's the deal so the
amount of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
oh
[Music]
wait
I don't know I don't think it'll listen
to me I don't know the uh it might be
move me actually I have no idea
I have no idea
oh it was awesome
[Music]
it was moving it was Mommy
okay
[Music]
cool down yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimate
I think Kelly you should go for it
Amelia wants some detective outfits oh
my God
detective Kelly
on the case let's go thanks are you guys
ready for another round yes yes
let's go
bro
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay wait what scientist wait I'm the
scientist now
success finals at any time oh hello oh
hello
don't kill me don't kill me
um
certainly not says
um okay okay I need to do my task oh
yeah holy hell oh cockpit
um
oh here
they're good
huh
okay oh oh those that was so simple
enough
okay there's electric stuff
hello I have to put the rivals away
OMG rifles just like in
I'm not gonna say that
Moana senpai
wait no
more
[Music]
what is this place
um download
okay
download outside I need to go to the
outside world and touch us
OMG
I wanted to I need to touch the closest
can you can you go outside from this way
no oh um I need to go from the kitchen
it seems
need to touch the closest what the hell
there's no kusas here
I have been tricked
it's not the outside at all I've been
treated where
[Music]
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower and then I walked up and I
turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone I don't think I saw Ollie shower
house above the shower
around the way to the archives
I was on the list
I have no idea if you remember well
let's see um Renee was busy doing things
around the shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she did pretty close I think girl was in
the shower as well but she like went
down to the left
[Music]
if it's really if it's raining if she
already killed only probably she cannot
kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like
she was trying to tell me a joke and
then I ran away from her oh yeah
so
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below and I was at the left side
no I'm just like saying uh so probably
saying that you are nearby the the place
I just like thinking oh it's true
but I I don't remember I saw moonassemba
in the middle-ish or on the left side I
don't remember
[Music]
um
yeah I'm gonna skip okay
what's your voted for herself
oh my God
hey Spider-Man actors rotoscoped into
Mario Kart pretty funny oh what
what
all right oh why oh my gosh anyways what
the hell is this we just what wait what
oh you returned
what
eh I'm gonna have around here didn't
have to do records oh how do you do this
what
let's see oh you can see how many people
are in each room
who is sabotaging shit oh oh there you
go
kill me
okay
all right I have to pick up a book
and then
okay
one
this is taking a long time
why is there four of it and why can't I
take like all of them at once that's
gonna BS at least it's simple enough
okay so no one died yet I forgot I'm the
I forgot I I could do that
you know what I'll use
oh um yeah I don't have anything to do
here
um
wow
who is that Zeta
is it is
hello hello
they did something in the toilet
hmm
what
eh
I'm gonna find another cat
hello
was it a drain it no did she shape
did she shape shift
wait hold on
you who are you talking to you
oh my God where no
no no no no oh
[Music]
um
where was she very bottom of the armory
what oh my God
everybody else Kiara and we confirmed
each other as Alibi Yes
[Music]
actually I was on the way to the kitchen
so any any sooner I would have fallen
the body but I'm from the engine what
the heck I saw you I saw you at the
right side of the map going up
because I was doing tests at the cargo
bay you know okay cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then bomb that body oh so you
were pretty close by yeah
I don't like my imagination but training
went past me and it was the last voice
for some reason it was there what it was
like way back
inside it's not me yeah I don't know but
like granny went past me and it was no
training's voice it was zetta's voice
and I was like I went like what
oh
[Music]
I didn't even spot
in time
same
I'm sorry you're too hidden I'm sorry
to voice
my imagination but I I swear to God I
swear to God drainage you went past me
and it was that as voice
foreign
[Music]
goodbye
oh God oh God
um I need to go to the
viewing deck
okay
oh no I need to go from the kitchen wait
what oh you go from the kitchen here
this way oh
hello couple
please let me upload
kill me
don't kill me I have to finish this
I'm struggling with poor connection
right now
okay okay shower I need to go to the
shower
[Music]
mama mama
um no no no no
who's that hello
[Music]
oh
wait what
okay oh here oh here okay okay
please fix
now I'm
okay
um I need to go to the shower
all night uh oh it's closed
bye
to the shower and the engine room right
now
hello wait I need to do this one
hello Mommy
okay um let me go to the engine room
first
oh
um
how the heck do you go oh from this way
okay
and then to the shower hey
hey
the shower I go
[Music]
it can only be
what
whoa whoa
wow
[Music]
what the I clicked the report button but
it didn't work
what the heck
what the heck what the heck
I literally I was like
okay
someone's got it I was just doing yeah
yes
wait it was it was simple and I I keep
thinking
wait Teresa
but rainy white yeah
real quick
yeah guys
[Music]
both the body
and then um protect people oh
no
oh
oh this is we're done four oh
wow well it's over it's over here
wait
please guys catch that Luna Senpai was
like one more what the heck does that
mean that's so sauce right
someone placed the emergency
oh oh you're the guardian angel
wait can only not hear me was that
okay um oh I have to God damn it I have
to go to the meeting
no I'm not dirty
hello hello
fellow dead people how's she doing oh my
God we we both are football keys and
we're both dead
I'm sorry for looking so bye
[Music]
focus on Empire
okay okay
in the shower
God damn it
that's probably not possible one two
three four five six oh oh never mind I
thought anyways
um
okay all right
okay is that it I need to fix lights oh
no no I think that's all for the
individual task right
I thought it was one of those tasks um
like in the scale where you put like one
two three four five six seven eight nine
times
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
it definitely wasn't ready then I
thought it was her maybe but oh my god
of me
so yeah
before that I was in the cupquake with
Google with gura and then and then rainy
come and say she got she's so
doppelganger of me
[Music]
but but she didn't kill me neither yeah
cause both of you are dead
[Music]
they didn't kill each other
I wonder there was no one I wonder why
how is no one noticing the
contradictions of Luna sent by
statements
the kitchen I haven't I haven't got I
haven't go to the Armory can anyone
vouch for Ahmed and say like she's safe
I was with Gouda and I didn't kill her
ah
that's so
it's done oh this is a mess
it's over
no it's over here
someone please do the emergency meeting
freaking God
I swear to God someone please do the
emergency meeting ah
emergency
come on anyone
bye bye bye to hell with your task don't
do your task
don't do your time
so silly it's just a big silly head can
someone do the emergency meeting please
please please
ignore your task
come on
God damn it
laughs
man
amazing that Noah noticed Muna senpai's
contradictions in her statements though
wow
aggressively trying to frame me yeah
[Music]
what I was barely doing nothing easy to
do
okay
[Music]
it's not her
thank you
because I heard you in the selected
screen where you where you just where to
go next I
can't get caught on his senpai's outfit
like you might have been acting was that
what you were doing
um
so you were like aware that we would
hear you and you were on purpose saying
something that only a crewmate would say
[Music]
oh my God
right now
I'm ready
[Music]
a different face
okay let's do this again
thing
doesn't that mean Ollie's The Imposter
though wasn't shape-shifting something
that only the imposer has
I don't know
um
okay so
um oh my God shower you good
shower you good
I love the sound effect
was that Cobble or was that um I'm good
at senpai
um wait what I can't I can't
what the heck
oh yeah I need to pick up all wait what
what
um
okay there you go
and what do I do with this
I think that's all all still some some
of them here
okay
[Music]
I don't know the location of the map oh
you know
um you can you can check them
out I'm so rainy I saw rainy uh yeah uh
going to the Armory and the kitchen when
when I want to go to engine room so I
didn't know I thought you would or she
from cockpit or main hall
[Music]
I saw her I saw her in the shower but
then she went away to the left side I
think
she went to the left side yeah she went
to the left side yeah she was in the
shower I saw her in the shower
Callie do you have an alibi maybe I was
going out to get service I did pass you
Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't
and you probably weren't that worried
since you're outside
but yeah I found Zetta actually right by
the body because uh I was wondering I
was coming up the ladder yeah I couldn't
help because it was really dark and then
oh
you went up I went up no I went I didn't
see you go up um
I'm skipping I'm skipping
so I'm gonna vote for Zeta because I
didn't even see them right that's very
good I keep not seeing the people who
get killed she said
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't yeah I don't want anyone
dying yet I don't think I saw Luna
senpai oh
[Music]
okay
shape shifter
what's with the shape shifter
I don't know it might be anyone because
like
um you know um when I saw Kobo she
wasn't talking so it might be someone
who who was shape-shifting hello
destroy it to me
it might be someone else was
shape-shifting she didn't answer about
um
I saw I said that I suffered at the
shower but I don't think she said
anything regarding that oh hello hi
hello hi just cleaning towels here don't
mind me yeah I finished I finished
cleaning cleaning them
and you be careful zeta's here and she's
gonna pause
okay I gotta go down
are we going down
oh oh God it's so dark it's so dark oh
no is it closed
no okay fine I'm gonna go to the cargo
bay
cargo bay
all right what is this
oh do you like try to oh oh
what
I'm sorry guys this is my first time
okay
okay oh
anyways
now I can go straight to the lounge
instead
oh nice nice wait what
do you do here um do I need to go inside
the toilet
oh use
and then
how do you do this
I know that was about to happen
oh my God
I was yelling at Kobo the entire time
somebody else here okay
where's the where's the body uh anybody
else
Lounge which ones
what are the bathroom stalls are
they wear
um
the last time the last time I went near
the wait who killed you guys main hall
is I saw only guys
I think I was getting some Giggles out
of Kobo though yelling at her the entire
time so haunting people does really work
like psychologically it is
[Music]
so many times
stop he's got it wrong
she's innocent yeah listen to me I'm
always us when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm a nuts
now you're saucing me which means I'm a
crewmate
the reverse psychology I don't think
that's gonna work oh my god
well then I say why the fuck why aren't
you providing an alibi instead of
Defending yourself huh what if it's a
man
[Music]
found a buddy twice I was only this
included room where like she would have
killed me
please
from where she killed me
Ali voted for me
Ben is it Ollie and Kiara instead
she's one of the imposters
all right um
hello oh they can hear me I think
all right
oh here
this is so sad
I will make her go crazy I wanna be a
guardian angel
I want to try being Guardian Angel and
protect people even though that's
usually not what I do because I'm an
ancient weapon but you know oh yeah I
need to do the toilet thing God damn it
how do you do this
what
okay
all right
um are we done here God I died I died at
the toilet that's so sad
that's so sad
okay it's Zetta for sure I'm voting
[Music]
games
yeah because I just happened to be a
detective he's really good at spotting
bodies
but I don't know man Rayna could I have
killed you or would I have some ideas if
I was with you and in that room for like
over 30 seconds
I don't know uh you want me to be honest
um what you said was oh just kidding I
was just waiting for my cool down so
yeah but I was already in the room
uh-huh it's like three times
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jetta
no
but I mean I can give Alabama running
away from the body well because Reina
and I were both up in the room like in
the meeting room and then me and I went
down I was operated the whole time and
then we saw Zayna pass Us in that
hallway
yeah I thought Coco take the little
elevator across yeah
[Music]
wasn't like near the fan if I die
okay
30 seconds 30 seconds
[Music]
[Laughter]
who
nice
nicer
[Music]
goodbye
what about the giant hand what I don't
know yeah
[Music]
records right
oh records are
okay
oh my God so is the other one get a
senpai I'm not sure
I'm gonna find out later though
oh I have so many things to do here
wait what my friend
wow look who's here huh
what oh they're having okay they're
having lights down
um oh yeah I needed to do this four
movies you hear like people
hello
okay I need to do my task at least now
we're going fast we're doing this first
um
and then
um tree one one seven
all right
um I'm gonna go to the cargo bay first
because
what's that
avert crash course
well good luck guys
crash course OMG
um
all right oh
okay they got they got it they got it
nice I need to go to the engine and do
whatever this is
all right we need to download data at
the cockpit
um
oh God
what okay
all right
cool
okay
foreign
guys
um I have one task left
and then um this should be this should
be my last individual going so we can do
this one and nine oh what the heck oh
meeting room
oh wait never mind I have some tasks and
that um I need to go to the outside
oh
all right all right um
[Music]
[Laughter]
probably Kobo to be honest because she
was with rain
she was just following us trying to wait
until one of us was like separated
[Music]
but why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you oh true
I was just being stupid
[Music]
I'm sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place all right
because we want to develop you off yes
let's go everybody
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
wait they've still got chance right yeah
cause only only one in poster left
well now everyone knows it's kyota
Senpai I think
no everyone knows who who is it because
like um
um
they just need to go they just need to
go um and press the emergency button
to fold off
um the other imposer
all right um oh my God oh my God um
um um um wait what
wait that's it right
I finished all my tasks
I finished all my tasks right
okay I'm good I'm good I'm good okay
okay cool where is electrical does
anyone know where electrical is
um um electrical is at the right side
right middle side
oh she's gone
oh this is a security this is electrical
this is electrical okay
foreign
I thought it was but I don't know
I don't know I have no idea too
um why is no one pressing the emergency
button
oh it's not impressing the emergency
who are you going foreign
[Music]
just fixing the lights
wait so was it Kiara senpai
I have no idea is it though
she's not gonna tell me though
it's combo
[Music]
y's task huh what about your Cask right
on all my tasks
all right someone needs to press that
emergency button oh you're dead but
someone needs to press that emergency
button right away right now
come away probably
someone someone needs to trust them
oh
[Applause]
my God it was Kobo it was global
oh yeah
nice hustle
oh my God hello everybody
[Music]
foreign
was so spot on
yeah
the way she kept finding bodies was kind
of funny not gonna lie
but she was so aggressive that's why we
were so scared
that's just her personality it's not
that she's the impossible yeah
it's her and I was like doubting myself
don't you believe me
believe me
[Music]
um
thank you thank you for coming with me
thank you
or
hello there's a lot of people here at
home
hello
[Music]
oh lights the lights it's all
um um use this
what
okay
all right um I need to do my task real
quick
go to the launch
this
oh no
[Music]
that's not it that's not how from
because everybody does it wait not this
one
yeah that was so similar that was such a
good impression
this is so hard what the heck
okay okay
hello everyone
why I am a young girl we should from who
live Indonesia
first generation
oh wait there's there's a task I'm
missing okay
hello hello
don't kill me
don't kill me oh
all right
um cool now what the f what the frick
should we do okay
um all right Emma wait
oh what well we can separate it's fine
oh my God
oh
[Music]
yeah
you watched her die
though
[Music]
I really like
it well she said please
all right we'll give you some more time
to get some kills
you want to be killed or or Kiara Kira
just uh go to Mumbai so if she was this
or maybe we can restart the game
yeah
sure killed I mean you're suffocate oh I
want to watch me get like you know
beheaded or whatever okay then I'll I'll
grab this year when she have my Will to
me all right we'll give you until the
next meeting and then okay
want to talk about it because she
reported so cool yeah sorry true oh yeah
yeah
where did you find the body Cobble
communication
oh I I was uh
I just don't think um left side
bottom left side middle okay that's why
she's writing the last time I saw Cali
was somewhere near me we'll give you
until the next meeting
okay I'm gonna kill as many people as
you can
yeah okay
[Music]
sounds nervous
sleepy
oh yeah because it's like bedtime 1am
I'm in Malaysia right now
kitchen brick main hall
oh and I
um
oh we're doing something oh I love this
wait
um wait Tomatoes right
Tomatoes right okay
oh here no no no no
hello
I'm making I'm cooking right now
you are I'm cooking I was cooking you
can build a burger yeah yeah it's pretty
good
okay I'm just gonna do this real quick
today
[Music]
um oh I need to go to the viewing deck
outside
oh time to touch the cool sauce
oh
two times in a row that's kind of crazy
[Music]
okay so I have good connection when I'm
a ghost
closet
[Music]
yeah and then they didn't kill me at all
wait um
doesn't talk as often she can like she
can blame it on like every school it's
so good yeah
an alibi for for Oli and gura because I
saw them and we were we were near there
just so good and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
um
for a while so
what is also what's uh what is on my
account
um
something usually when when she was the
crew matched she always
cut me off and scream I feel like me and
Kelly Senpai always die early
I mean yeah
yeah focus on tasks yeah
[Music]
really loves to scream whenever I met
anyone
that's because
you're scared
you didn't show that you are scared me
to vote one of the imposters or else
[Music]
oh God
oh God they need to vote
ah
quinoa
oh no though who who's the other one is
it is it Kiara senpai
I'm scared for my life I don't know what
to trust anymore
[Music]
what is this
um oh
um
and hello
I still have tasks wait so it's not it's
not kyota Senpai I guess because she's
doing task
let's go to the assistant hello
oh my God
this is so fun what the heck
here
yeah I can hear you
hello I have a real task left
[Music]
oh okay there you go hello let's go oh
my God
good shit let's go let's go oh my God
language
I mean sometimes I do that too you know
when you find when you find good shit
you say wow good shit
let's go
spicy
wow so ghost can take a shower too
it's not really shower wait is it is it
a shower
it's a shower
all right
all right cool
okay I have two more
do I need to download
oh this
is
a big freaking murderer the killer she's
down there Kobo she's right down there
Coco oh
[Music]
there oh I think it's a good kill
oh I I have I have one more task oh
cockpit cockpit
yeah
I didn't get impulsory though said
I didn't get imposed with the whole
round
you know um some of us
um were playing off stream before before
the actual stream and I got like two
imposters in like in a row and then I
won all of them
the crazy thing is that um the first one
we were playing with like one imposter
one imposter setting and so I was doing
all alone I was doing it all alone
and then of course that stream I don't
get any impossible
wow
just the usual thing God damn it
okay I think I'm done with all my
individual tasks
no what are we doing
oh
what if I hold like an emergency meeting
oh oh we all is right there oh
oh
sure wait where's Coco now
she's here
this is haunted by so many
times
[Music]
oh she's going
it wasn't me yeah I saw I saw Muna
Senpai going towards where Ollie was and
that was the last time I saw her
this is because I wanted the chickens
on your way there or over there
button
no okay yeah
it really went to check if anyone's
bid by pressing one you're the last one
left and you want to try to vote people
out
also not saying anything yeah I didn't
know
what is it called what are they called
imposter what skin consumers
wow
oh grumbles oh goodness
stop the tasks read it I thought it was
over you know what yeah I'm done with my
task anyways so like maybe I can just go
chat with the girls you guys can vote me
out that's what you guys want no
[Music]
um
I really did I've been stuck in
electrical
oh God
oh no it's over
here
[Music]
with Lego Steve
mask anyways no it's impossible I don't
know
[Music]
this is so sad
people right
yeah
[Music]
good afternoon bye
girl please please just go just go just
go to the meeting place just go meeting
yeah someone has to press the emergency
meeting
because yeah yeah it's gonna end ignore
your task
um I wonder if we can win um I wonder if
we can claunch this
I don't think we can cause like
isn't doing her task so it's like
impossible
no
I wish I could
[Music]
what is that weird who is breathing
yourself God damn it you guys are so
good
you guys are so good okay
I don't know
every time Kobo is the Imposter it's
incredibly difficult that should tell
you whenever people are dying really
fast it's definitely Kobo she's so quiet
yeah she's so quiet she saw the crime
scene went goes to the emergency meeting
and then Ahmed Changes Everything by
sussing the innocent gloves yeah yeah
[Music]
it's right with you Kiara salty
I take it out too early
when it's cold
that's something she'll do like staying
quiet so it's incredibly hard
[Music]
okay okay
we're not Bella
you don't know
man this is so sad
[Music]
hello
let's try to live I'm just picking up
all the towels on my knee
oh it's dark oh I have
um
[Music]
oh my God what
oh
what wait wait
what
once again
[Music]
I thought it was your body I thought it
was no Raining Raining is dead so here's
what I found I was picking up all of the
towels and shit in the shower and I said
I hope girl doesn't kill me a girl is
fine I don't think that she did it but
okay Kelly sent by Kelly Senpai and we
were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta
[Music]
from the left of the shower walked up
and in that photo room we're all like
it's like a dark room I guess that's
where I found the body I didn't see that
there was a dead body in there because
the lights were out until it said report
conflict report and I guess Renee was
killed in the dark room so that's all I
have to say about that I literally was
just cleaning up the shower was anybody
down there okay
I was last at electrical
uh
where where I was at electrical I have
my I was at the bottom right of
electricity
did you finish the towel the towel test
no I didn't finish picking them up I
thought I did but it wouldn't let me put
them inside of the hamper thing so I
still have to grab a couple towels
yeah that means I was in the electrical
I saw I was in the electron I was in the
middle I was in the middle bottom and
see that he was in the bottom but I
didn't see anyone it was too fast
that was that was way too fast it might
be that or Kelly Senpai my God is
telling me that
what's that did I not see Rainy after
Zetta
too much
I think I I I think I saw rainy like
going I think I saw Zeta going first and
then drain it but
it wouldn't have been too fast and if it
was still shooting oh hello
it will have been too fast for like for
her to die
and the only the only possibility for
that is that is a it's a self-deport
it might be a self-report
hmm
that is overly quiet
all right
I'll be weird hello
hi
oh hello and then I have to do some
wait or wasn't I'm a senpai
wait what's I'm a simple scholar oh
and then
um what what was strain is called again
it would be really
oh nice guys guys guys guys I I I pass
uh on Ollie's I pass on Ollie's uh in
the in the electrical
and then and then after that she's going
up and then I saw I saw
[Music]
the first time only said that she was an
electrical but I didn't see it and then
the second time you know we we had to
teleport first right and then after that
he said you know I'm an electrical I
find you and after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie pass by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw Carly
died
Bond
[Music]
is it actually Ollie
I don't know
I feel bad what if it's not her
okay
by the process of elimination
so the shower the shower thing so Kelly
Senpai died
which means
I mean by process of elimination or
maybe I mean gurus Senpai was also there
but I didn't hear her anymore so either
she left the shower room early
why are you not fixing it oh I fixed it
I fixed it I was in the middle of fixing
it what the hell
whoa
I literally just came
hello how do you feel about all that and
there we go there we go
and bingo bango bongo
I know it
I I know it sucks
I figured it out like um
so that's nice
from the alarm like as she finished the
alarm and then she walked to the right
side towards oh that's right there you
go
elimination
and then I will protect the body process
of elimination
retails me that this is the result
this is so sad I literally died
immediately like a minute after I
figured it out around the showers dang
it um
[Music]
that's like Kelly Senpai you were in the
shower but
um I was in the shower pretty long I was
picking up the towels and I didn't hear
good assemba anymore so I figured out
she was she left early so it was only me
you and Zetta come on come on we need
and you died and then you died I was
like okay
shifter accessed here
for sure but it could be we don't know
for sure
I don't know but me neither but but
she's like she's like uh you know when
she tried to do her alibiscus
[Music]
she's always crazy
accomplice
[Music]
good job everyone
let's go nice job let's go
I didn't even have like 10 seconds
[Laughter]
you guys figured it out heck yeah yeah
[Music]
good job everyone
oh it was a great job
okay
that was my alarm sorry oh okay
it is
memorial time
yeah
[Music]
we're like too strong so the game has to
contain us
you know this game is like never end I
feel like I want to play it until I
gotta make another imposter
yeah
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know two ways oh
yeah it's fine because I usually
means
yeah I'm good yeah I'm good really good
I'm good yeah
is this like my prime time
okay
yeah okay one more
oh my God oh my God
thank you
thank you so much
yeah oh my God hello goodbye
I know that was gonna happen wait where
am I all viewing deck um I need to go to
the kitchen hello tomato hello hello
let's cook together
you guys want to see a magic trick never
mind please no I'm not that the magic
trick not a magic trick well I'm cooking
now we can all vouch for each I'm
cooking right now here
yeah okay
um
and then this one I need to take down
the trash okay
onion onion okay
hey
I did it
um oh
it's closed
it's closed God damn it
I can go here I have nothing to do on
the viewing that though
oh my God that was so scary
can you open the door please because I
can't wait
good question please
open the door
again
[Music]
come on
it was in the hallways it was in the
main hall actually yeah okay
yeah so uh I was I was I actually uh saw
her through the showers I went to
electrical a little bit then I went back
to the main hall and guess this I
actually met another Ollie so if you
guys said anything like oh my God no
there was actually a doppelganger and I
actually met her she was chasing me down
no no listen she was down and you know
what even if you guys
even if I
like the past the task here I believe
okay you know what she's defending
himself
[Music]
she's desperate when whenever she's like
she's trying to defend herself so much
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah
and vote me off because I'll do the task
easier that way anyways I can just fly
now you stay here
[Music]
I think
yeah maybe
yeah because you guys you guys um
what happened last round
um Ollie always the Imposter and
she didn't even she didn't even try she
was trolling so oh oh I I didn't I
didn't choose okay
ah I'm gonna ignore this soon for now
I'm gonna go to the cockpit always gets
killed off first like hello don't kill
me don't kill me
all right
okay just kidding
or am I I don't know that's what that's
what an innocent would say that's what
an innocent that is pretending to be an
imposter would say you mean you
mean you
all right oh my God
I don't know though I have no idea
I have no idea so far
but if Kelly Senpai died that means it's
gonna be my turn
it's gonna be my turn to die after this
ah
I always die after Kelly's senpai
oh God
holy hell gaming
India gaming
see
I can't I can see the future
I can see the future it's it's my form
of gaming guys
[Music]
it was a double kicker oh I got the
pretty name plate
[Music]
and pause
it yeah
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen Gora
or something
and then there was also or something no
it was like a bunch of people there
so who killed you guys I feel like Yeah
I wanted to show a matchup
just telling what I saw I feel like shit
thing is yeah something that I'm a
senpai
for a long time
[Music]
for like a long time want to save her
yeah but the thing is I don't know Anya
Anya was also there but Anya's also
there but girls also dead
I don't know
um
because everything will be used again
because
[Music]
she always stays quiet when she's
impulsive oh my God
oh my God
yeah combo is always quite the thing is
Coco just stops talking she she doesn't
talk a word
when she's the imposters
always quiet
okay um I gotta do my task
all right
over and we survived
but probably is like really
yeah it might be cobons on second third
one second thought it might be cold
Focus she's awfully quiet
she's overly quiet again and that always
happens whenever she gets the impulse
roll
oh
all right
um oh oh let me do the one at fault
first
what is this what is this how do you do
this
oh he wiped the okay
oh
okay that works
okay let's go to the cockpit
all right I was like man
okay I got one left at the cargo bay
well I'm spit running this
I'm spit running this let's go let's go
um this this and this am I done
yeah let's go
[Music]
Cliff Cobble
because
oh a minute she wasn't doing anything
okay
whoa
nice scary Senpai I trust my wife
stop killing me and cow Senpai oh my God
don't shape-shifting though I feel like
one might be I feel like I'm a simple
definitely make use of any skill that
she has
so if anyone will be so brave to use the
shape-shifting a lot I think it will be
I'm a senpai
but also I think one of them has to be
Kobo as well because she's awfully quiet
this round
correct for some reason
correct the soup how many people died
actually
yeah that's a good question almost like
you should call an emergency meeting
yeah okay let's sleep together I figured
out that it was it's cold
over here magic trick line okay
[Music]
the goddamn
but they're not
[Music]
ready
come on
come on I need to go up on the way for a
desk I'm gonna go there now
come on come on for safety just for
safety
he's going
oh interesting oh smack it
can someone fix that oh
hi okay I was gonna call an emergency
meeting
oh I'm online
okay hello what happened nice
it's cool
she bented I like previously when I was
the Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second yes
doing that thing now but like she was
there I said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gura
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
sort of electrical to
because if she's doing a task but it
takes one second and she waited went
there believe me trust me this is true I
will I don't have any proof of her
that's one way to figure it out
for me suspicious
[Music]
up until like in the discussion at all
do you have a defense for yourself yeah
do you have a defense for yourself like
why are you so cool or you know because
[Music]
I believe
thank you thank you
thank you goodbye
if that was correct I deserve a medal oh
my God
buddy I don't think yeah that was
freaking Bitcoin indeed oh hi holy shock
of course it stopped me
I finished my task right okay
okay
okay so who's the other one
I guess if I'm a sip by Ollie and um who
is it again Zetta are always together
then I guess it's not them because
um an imposter will want to like search
for victims you know I was just like
leaving everything to Cobble
which
um which I think
no I don't think that's effective
together
actually I don't think we can all go
because there's like a little is it Mona
Senpai then yeah yeah I think let's all
go again is it Luna Senpai
right hello
hello okay
Randy can you hear me I fixed it okay
okay I don't think she can hear you yeah
I know can she yeah
bring my dress if I die it's Muna I'm
just kidding then
yeah she didn't say that
um
I'm a senpai and who was it again Ollie
and zit that were staying all the time
and I think if it was I'm a senpai
she'll be more aggressive hey what
so that that only leaves Senpai and
rainy
oh oh come on what you gonna do
let's go
yeah go to the other side please thank
you oh you're you're dead now we can
finally be alone I am
a trick it's not Watson I guess it isn't
playing
tonight
[Music]
oh I don't know what are you looking at
what are you what am I looking at
I'm gonna take my magic trick
it must have been so good
I don't want to go over there because
then we can only go alone
Stay Together
what was that where was it okay okay
where was it she said where was it she
said because she's where was it um
okay I just saw Muna it must be Muna
don't you see that um I was from the Gap
room and I passed by when you are fixing
the electricity and I go to the shower
and then I go to record again okay I
wasn't sure
earlier
I I saw I saw I saw I think it was Kiara
and then Zeta is from the shower too and
we passed right okay
where is where is the location of the
body
um
in the cargo bay between the door of
medical Tokai Reyna and Zeta which way
were you guys going to the showers
I was with you oh sorry sorry
we came from the top to the bottom from
like lounge and we saw Luna going the
other way or you saw her going with you
in that direction I don't saw her I
didn't see her at all which is the
problem what
[Music]
I think there goes some of them going to
the up to go into the record and then
after so after that I saw man I bet he
made public speaks in class this is
actually intimidating
[Music]
she's pretty good ideas bloodthirsty I'm
telling you except for maybe you and
Reina
most of the ideas
yeah we haven't seen their potential yet
Watson
nice job guys
[Music]
nice job guys good win nice
that was fun
[Music]
[Applause]
during the meeting was actually really
scary
videos
[Music]
a great a great round
let's go
I want to hear a goodbye from everyone
if that's okay
real goodbye
[Music]
how was it today oh yeah it was pretty
fun I won an embossed around and then
won all the crewmate rounds or pretty
much all of them so it's you know pretty
good day pretty good game thank you for
inviting me Kiara thank you for setting
it up uh yeah thank you guys for playing
thank you for always sussing me even
though it's me
[Laughter]
put your reflex now but okay I just want
to see your reaction that's how I test
you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsory but it's fine
it's cool thank you so much for
organization right yeah what we need is
we can do something again together thank
you
I'm gonna think it was fun
yeah
and next we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
um I was born to be crewmate I don't
like playing imposter anyway so I had a
good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your boy that's fine just let it be
and then everyone killed you early
afterwards
it's so convinced
us I just gotta work on my longevity in
the game
but I have to do tasks and I love doing
tasks so it was fun thanks for the
invite here doing tasks I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damn this best teammate that I possibly
could
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
I was relieved I I was scared to see
what happens if it's like especially
like shape-shift there killing all of
you
oh my God
I wanted to be shape-shaped
shifter I haven't got yeah
pretty rare
well well if you guys want to look like
good on go get the Cosmic Cube
yeah take over the world
cup
killer killer it was a statement
a lot
wow
that's so rich
these collabs there's always like one
person who gets it off yeah I am yeah I
only got it quite a bit too right yeah
I'll say sorry for
you for uh
are
um being posted together with me because
I cannot
um I don't know why but a playhouse room
like uh there's
maybe are you sure
yeah yeah like yeah so I'm not that like
I felt that you you seem very impressed
yeah
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good excuse or I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia it's so easy but
um I don't know you can always use that
as the excuse me I use that with the JP
no English
Japanese
yeah
you did a good job
a lot of kills good job today
good job
so many times
[Laughter]
it was actually pretty funny because I
thought the reverse psychology would
work it did not
like I thought if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually access and say oh I'm
actually says haha that would make you
guys uh Ali's just messing around but
nah
I feel like
oh oh oh
[Music]
her in
especially because uh organizing be
source of collabs it's like a big hassle
in there and well all the most utmost
respect thank you for accommodating all
of us in this collab yay Kiara thank you
yeah
thank you
that was fun again after a long long
time
for a second and go to oh Muma is not
here anymore let's foreign
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
let's play again and then it's gonna be
time for us to be the imposters
lunch
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few
free uh two or three I don't remember
yeah
[Music]
thank you for those who teamed up with
me and thank you
and I want to apologize because my
stream died six times
how did you survive oh god oh no
oh God
[Music]
oh my God
okay
no that's her and another one
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah
Empire
are you able to talk
we can't hear your voice no voice
somehow
all right
[Music]
okay okay
it's okay you got your full outfit now
Muna you did it
yay congrats thank you and you look good
so I hope you had fun oh I wanna buy you
have fun Luna I have fun uh actually uh
the first time I'm doing uh the to
become an imposter with I mean it's
really fun
because I'm the one that I'm I'm usually
afraid of whenever I become an imposter
everyone
if I make it a list it's probably a me
Kiara and then Kali is the one who can
like talk a lot that make me you know
so that's usually the person that's okay
yeah
I'm the sheriff hey what was that
surprise there oh no well anyway we can
just talk in here yeah yeah yeah we can
talk in here yeah we can talk we're done
anyway I think I got to hear from
everybody I'm glad that we all came
together for another big Enid collab I
think the last one was Mario Karts
[Music]
yeah and I really don't have anything
else to say besides good job everybody
hope you had fun and yeah see you again
soon sometime yeah see you soon everyone
[Music]
absolutely
okay muted
oh my God that was so fun holy heck
hope you guys enjoyed that as much as we
did
yeah and thank you so much for coming
um I will see you guys at the next
stream
um for me um there's gonna be a rust
stream today at like um I think it's
gonna be 7 P.M gym Depot seven there's
no change to the time
it's gonna be a team battle team fight
this season's team fight the one that
coyote coyote is hosting
yeah it's gonna be a team fight and my
team consists of
Meine Zeta and Kayla so that's like a
full ID team wow so that's gonna be like
a full ID team mm-hmm
yeah um yeah I think that's that's it so
I will see you guys at 7pm GMD plus
seven if there's no change to the time
for the team fight that coyote is
hosting
mm-hmm
So yeah thank you so much everyone hope
you guys enjoyed um the E and ID collab
I will be reading Super Shots and
donations
um another time
thank you thank you and see you guys at
the next stream
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]