[Music]
This old, hungry Tato is
still lying on his bed. Is he not in the
best condition? No, he's
serious. This is the number of times I've said that.  If you're
not feeling well inside, please cry,
we can't just say it,
so let God
heal you.
This is a 140-character poem.If the bat is decided, it
will be 2.I'm sure I'm going to get away with it.There
will be more and more losers, but of course I'm on the run.The
only thing I'm good at is Sabo's mouth, and he's quick to prey.
[Applause] I don't want to
go to the dojo, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I've
caught quite a lot of fish. No, when I'm hungry, I'm motivated. I use my smartphone again.
If you're pretending to be dead in bed with a kite you've messed with, why
don't you do it because you're just a fool.Before that
guy got hit again, I'll
be honest.  Beck, I'm rotten. I've been in a
bad mood lately, but I
'm still serious. Shaka
[Music] I'm
doing my best.
That's why I'm doing my best today.
[Music]