[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
yeah little assets that you have as well
it looks good thank you I'm a fancy
sorceress yay
ready a sorceress nice who who's
everybody what is everybody playing as
good question good questions go around
Ring Around the Rosie okay
all right who's this yourself
more episodes of my character's name is
Morp uh Morp is uh she thinks she's a
skeleton she's just really weird she's a
necromancer
um very skinny and strange and talks in
third person more talks like this
four bits more being to aim it more
gloves pretty lady these new pretty lady
let's let's go to
Keandre keonder Deandre
don't I look pretty because I put
um the it used the trends more good
whatever it's called
I know the specific cloves on top of
other cloves that don't look so pretty
so now I look super pretty mmm
looks cute but Callie I'm so glad that
you're joining us a necromancer yeah I
like playing his Necromancer but now I'm
realizing you guys can't see the
skeletons which makes me really really
upset actually morph is sad you can't
see her skeletons really don't they show
up maybe when we leave town maybe I hope
I'm sure they do
okay who else does we have Kyla right
next to me as well let's go I'm a druid
I don't know how to play the drift but
let's just let's go let's go
[Music]
bring just like a brick from your house
on your back yeah what is that a brick
let's go let's just throw some bricks
let's go actually wait you might be
building the house with Cali right
because Cali has a really nice sex on
your back how you do okay
um whoa wait Karen you look like crony
what I changed I changed my outfit oh
very nice that's very nice what's Chrome
are you playing I am playing as a rogue
oh wait Rogue you have
I have like a bow and oh I guess I have
two swords yeah needle
Circle
I'm playing on a controller
oh
sends more plays on PS5 oh wow
oh okay so I'm I'm so serious I chose
the the special thing is the day do you
guys know what I try to reference in my
name
um
Drake
Kinder egg
no no because you know I saw uh I was
first trying to recreate myself but it
didn't work so well and while I was
creating the character I realized oh
she's looking kind of like Game of
Thrones character Miss Andre
so I combined Kiara and Melisandre and
I'm the hot red sorceress yes
pretty lady they look like they're on
fire
tag
called in 4k
but we all kind of have our own colors
here yeah
yeah like I got purple
macaroni has blue
macaroni and then well as red and Kyla
is kind of green I guess it feels like a
hammer but for now brown is also good
you'll literally get greener
and Greener
ogre color
yo I haven't played in a couple days but
uh my current goal is the campaign list
for Littleton the tarnished luster and I
thought we would do that unless you have
any other ideas it's okay I'll just
follow anything
foreign
[Music]
skeletons let's combine
oh wait there should be game audio okay
but you hear the other ones but no uh
game audio one second
[Music]
check everything's fine right
sound check
wow
okay all good all good okay all good all
good nice nice thank you thank you
[Music]
I think we're here
game bgm now I'm a skeleton
is it too loud
take off my helmet so you can see I'm
Scarlet okay ready oh you can go to the
Wardrobe you can go to the Wardrobe to
like hide your cab instead of like just
removing it really yeah come here the
mirror
I want to go to the Wardrobe together
everybody yeah let's go girls gonna
dress up I don't have anything I can
address
yes okay I'll just wait I'm I'm reading
the skills right now it's okay just
ignore me it's okay
is it safe to show
um the the group screen where I invited
everybody it's okay yeah fun you'll be
fine oh my goodness yes we're looking so
cool Kelly looks like she is she needs
sleepy so I can do unequipped look but
I'm still equipped with it right
I drew it yeah
plain draw it you need help can we let's
see I'm trying to so unequipped wow look
but that doesn't mean that it's
unequipped correct
uh yeah it's not it's not an Ends don't
need don't reaching
I forgot how it works crony you help her
uh so you got a wardrobe
and then you can just like uh go to the
Head section and then it just says
unequipped look
oh okay cool yes choose that yeah yeah
cool I'm ready to go okay what did you
change ah the camera yeah
because I want to look like a skeleton
Morp wants to look like skeleton hell
yeah I feel like baldness looks so good
in Diablo I know right I can stick
why is
no cap
Kelly maybe you can reflect light on
your forehead and find like a new skill
to attack with a little nice idea yeah
use my head as a mirror you use morp's
head as a mirror yes okay okay
you must clean it all the time
my shiny cloth good shiny clothes
[Music]
down
down in the east
can I track this okay good
now
we're gonna kill a bunch of guys let's
go love killing love killing me the
murderer with the ladies murder with the
ladies ooh murder sleepover girls night
out yeah there's no accident there hello
damn it we're going in a circle okay
girls night out in the
circle's not accomplishing anything
let's go ladies my favorite time of the
day where are we going
to
uh what's it called actually you can
bend it though
yeah yeah
yeah
just just right click right click on the
map
so we can follow
I did oh yes
[Applause]
do we share items or does like everybody
get their own drops
I think we get our own draws yeah we get
our own yeah that's what Chad told me
yep yep yep
that's true
yeah
I'm not ready yet
I'm already kind of like
struggling to see where everybody is
because now I thought this person
belongs to us
they're just random hey more says you
are not invited to this party
you are not part of our group
where the cool Mean Girls cool like cool
me cool Mean Girls let's go
yeah no no others no Outsiders allowed
sorry we're super quickish
to have in the group yep
damn bossley we're the Mean Girls of
Diablo yeah you can't sit with us
all our characters are all girls yeah
yeah yes we are you cannot go to hell
with us no exactly you can't no you'll
go to heaven and have fun there yeah
Super Evil ladies but also not really
evil but just kind of mean not East mean
is good
oh there's even yeah do you guys want to
go even even let's go let's go let's go
here
[Applause]
something
okay more do skeleton things do
[Applause]
is quite loud
this is not too loud for you
it's always the battle of
volume control I die cast blight
yeah oh you guys don't like that
okay I'll change it in a second a little
bit
I I I feel like I'm taking away
everybody's like item drops but but hold
on
later yep yep yep
[Music]
mental stability
Christmas
[Music]
yay yay
nice gold together Diablo game right
yeah I've never played diabolo before
I liked it so far let's go
yeah I'll probably end up doing a 12
hour stream this week
what let's go
hey
[Music]
once you're in the Diablo
whatever you're not getting out there's
no way back you never go back go low I
try to stop playing the game because I
had to go do a recording and I was like
all right time to stop and then I spent
like five minutes trying to stop the
playing the game and I could
that's what Diablo do to you right yeah
yeah yeah blue
you bolo
are we already inside no that was quick
we're all playing on tier one right yeah
okay I am too
already privately played the other one
right
yes
the whole game
uh the the main campaign yeah
oh I kind of forgot how how long was it
guys I don't know can you help me
asking for help no feeling of time
anymore wait what do you mean by tier
one
three stream three stream they say tree
stream can you not hear me
though yeah tree stream how long
damn I don't think they hear yeah how
long I wanted to I want the game to be
longer than that
50 40 to 50 yeah they say 40 to 50. um
wait can you guys hear me
what the heck
well
you okay
you good all good all good I'm just
speeding up all my need is cleaning
oh cool it's very very low guys
and they're not surprised or explosions
oh my goodness
much
I have to go up here for my quest okay
you don't have to go there too or is it
just me no I think it's
um
[Music]
oh are we going into the mines
let's go
okay yeah I did this one
yeah
I'm gonna steamroll it
can you guys hear me yeah yes uh
okay yes yes the conversation of the NPC
or yes
okay okay that's probably not necessary
oh I think I skipped it
oh no problem okay I marked the location
on the map so yeah ladies let's roll out
I should activate the the Waypoint yes
nice chicken or thank you Amazon
[Music]
um
hello hello hello
it's the Ebola time
we're just playing some diabolas diabolo
[Music]
Diablo
what what is it in Spanish evil devil
yeah oh yeah Diablo
yes just some trivia that everybody well
maybe not everybody knew you didn't know
that did you Kiara I mean I feel like I
heard it before yeah it just makes sense
yeah
he's thinking and
I think there's Diablo Pizza which is
like really spicy
oh
for like Diablo hot sauce yeah I feel
like I've heard of that before oh yeah
yeah it's really really the really hot
hot sauce that sends you literally too
hell wow you could almost die that's
Diablo Hawk sauce right oh that sounds
delicious
get that skeleton Captain skeletons
thank you
so much
I have to pick up all the gold now clean
up clean up okay
skill point maybe this this one it was
medicine right here
okay strangers
can you not use your skin Ranger morph
is no stranger
oh Morp is nice lady
nice skeleton
warp is nice skeleton lady
give more information
[Music]
flame Shields
I'm reading I'm reading
reading skills I don't know
[Music]
um
reading I also don't know what I'm doing
with the skills
I don't know what to do more with the
secret need lady
okay
shut up let's go
what should we do right now
The Necromancer is kind of cool
Necromancer is really nice yeah the
character is kind of cool
but somehow the what is that
the all of the scale is gonna confuse me
no friends
oh you talk already I'm talking now but
us being in the group messed up the the
cutscene
how much of the game have you played uh
as I already played this part so I don't
need to see it I played and the beta I
played like
um
act one
got some work done
this is your first one playing the main
game
uh uh I played uh last week or so one
time
but before me and coroni played Diablo 2
resurrected right yeah that sounds fun I
hear that's fine
say that one's really good like this one
and then at uh that was pretty fun yeah
when I was a child my mom used to play
Diablo one and two I suppose and I was
watching her and sometimes trying to
game uh myself but I was always too
scared of everything oh that's so cute
never get past the first little boss so
I was just like wandering around always
I mentioned this time I'm playing it
properly I mentioned on stream I feel
like I understand why you like it
because it's not too scary for you
because I know you don't like scary
games well even now it's not too scary
but but it definitely was yeah although
I saw something and I think that we're
maybe still gonna see it I don't know
I'm confused what happens when but like
the blood ritual stuff and all that that
is right even now fun
scary
Define scary what is scary like
how much scary is scary everything is
scary no
life is scary life is scary it's true
well life is scary yeah we'll die
oh
it will
sometimes
what's going on
there's just a lot going on that's fine
Warp cleans the battlefield I'm excited
football spots I want to see how yeah
yeah we can kill a boss yeah
I took an arrow to my heart I took an
arrow to the near
where should we go what why why I have
no no mana mana
hello
energy
are you playing like uh what elements oh
fire okay
[Music]
According to some people but you know
I'm a phoenix I gotta be a fire saucerer
yeah I wouldn't believe it if you were
an ice storm
is great
yeah yeah I feel like in most other
games that I played like MMORPGs where
you have the choice between Fire and Ice
major source or whatever usually the ice
one is always like super weak
um
like ice ice is more like for status
effects and that's why people go for it
but fire is just like more physical I
think like well not physical it just
deals more damage in my opinion and I
think about status
if you freeze someone like you can just
they can just get unmelted but if you
burn someone they're like that's like a
piece of their body that's gone
yeah
Diablo balances it's so well that you
can play Ice and still do good damage
I appreciate that maybe I sometimes
some other time
but not this time
I mean you can play both oh
I was considering playing a druid in the
beta but everybody was saying that the
Druid was like super weak yeah everyone
say that everyone say that did they
change anything in the balancing since
kinda kinda yeah kind of
um it's not weak anymore like it's the
build
it depends on the build I think okay
yeah
Kelly you know what's cute you have five
skeletons right yeah when I just stayed
behind a little bit one of your
skeletons stayed behind with me
what a gentleman to be yeah
what a sweetheart
gosh that's that's the dead beats for
you making sure nobody gets left behind
just so that I'm gonna be too young and
scared in the dark
oh except
it's too weak we need stronger opponents
I know we're kind of we are really
steamrolling yeah
cool okay now we're cooking we look
really cool though
oh that was cool wow
yeah we could go to tier royals here too
if we wanted to I think we might need we
probably should at this point
can we do it while we're Chad can we do
it while we're in the middle of the game
maybe we need to finish the quest first
we need to get to the finish some Quest
like complete some quests to go to the
here too yeah but it's not that hard if
like from one to two
I think I'm already on tier two
yeah
[Music]
wait then wouldn't we not be allowed to
play with each other though
that's a thing I'm so confused about
that
IDK
we're gonna no whoa whoa what's that
Skillet dude thing
yeah if we play with others we following
the the host world so if it's like near
one so it's like transport all to tier
one yeah
okay
run away past Chihuahuas is still deep
inside of you saying no too scary
it's okay
the love I don't hate this mommy you
play
all right well I guess I could sell this
yeah oh for here two weeks and just go
back to fill fast chat yeah oh wanna
want to do it now probably we can just
open the portal
finish
we can do that
okay okay whatever you guys want to do
because it's gonna be like uh more XP
too right true enough yeah so we better
do it now how do I get out of the
uh dungeon map
uh do we just teleport out or no we just
need to press t hold T
um
here we go did we leave someone behind
is everybody want to kill the Shad okay
no girls left behind no no ladies all
right now let's let's go to higher
higher level
how to change uh you need to go to the
wait the statue uh
the world tears tattoo oh
wait is the is the green one you yup yup
yup I'm the green one
[Music]
um
isn't he the blacksmith
Kayla why'd you lead us to the
blacksmith yeah
uh statue I I've never visited the
statue
okay
this one
throw this one selfish well okay let's
sell things first I also need to sell
I need to scrap my things anyway yeah
nice World tear statue veteran
wait why can't I I don't know wait this
game anymore
it's not letting me
huh
it will not let me press confirm
what happened with the Discord can you
guys hear me yeah yeah
uh
uh hello we hear you
can you hear us hello
yep we can okay okay
where do they go
only the party leaders
yeah only the host apparently but uh
okay let me let me just restart
sure I guess what statue what's that I
don't see a statue statue go north
okay wait yellow check mark up north
yeah North North is this this way uh
she pinned it oh she penned it okay
yeah I just went up there I couldn't
change anything no so you have to do it
ah okay veteran oh never mind
this will be uh enemies are more
challenging monsters go back to 20
increased experience and they drop 15
more gold money
has all active portals
determinants are reporters we have to
walk back to the
um dungeon
it's fine right
nightmare
I'm not gonna do that no no the
nightmare sounds fun I I don't know you
have to be worse than my real nightmares
I'm trying to click to respond
what are you scared Kelly do you not
want to do it no I do no please vote
again hold this to respond uh let me see
ah I see more prison Necromancer and
she's scared of dying
stop no shut up
no more points to be skeleton that makes
no sense with Mark's lore
no no it has been changed but I guess we
gotta wait for Kyla what's what's
happening internet Maybe
yeah I think restarting
okay all good glass more Bruns in
circles
you know your damage is like real good
but you're gonna die real quickly if you
get attacked
I see so is this
[Music]
speaks a lot but no action
no no no no actually like they deal a
lot of damage but they should not get
attacked or else they're gonna die
almost immediately yeah that's why it's
a glass Cannon because it'll shatter
pretty easily
so think of like a Pokemon that has like
50 health
hell strong at
I think you said Gengar
Gengar for example Shadow Ball
but Gengar gets hit really really hard
I love Gengar though because the speed
is like real good
uh Gengar rules just not in Nuzlocke
and uh
for 10 seconds each head spits fire at
the enemies what the [\h__\h] I can
something
let's go nice that sounds amazing
that's exciting I want to try it I'm
Gonna Leave the city for a moment
okay I can't connect to Discord
okay
yeah
what's going on with what
just give her time I'd say okay
we can kind of stray outside while
waiting a little bit but not not
completely going on a mission
because mean girls don't leave other
Mean Girls behind
exactly is that how it works
is that how I worked in the movie
yes it is
let me see oh cute always yeah that's
how that's how the plot goes right
they they learn the power of friendship
yeah and like we watch very different
movies together forever
That's How It Ends yeah it's very sweet
ending enemies here you go
oh great that is so cool I look after
I'm going to run after Kiwa whoa
okay wow so they just kind of popped out
of the ground
are those your little pets your pet
snakes nice oh my God elsewhere
the silent fish do we need a key for
that I want this silent chest yeah can't
open it sadly but I want to open it can
we buy a king
oh welcome back
I changed back the connection
[Music]
all right okay I think someone need to
invite me back
I got you um
hold on hold on yeah I'm still in the
loading screen okay
so many there was a problem logging in I
cannot login
the ID course
excuse you
let's go qo let's get them
hey
oh I'm going to die no no no no no no
rattle them boys
everyone dead
including your skeletons yeah I'm just
cleaning up the battlefield real quick
hey I brought a friend
freak
48 dude here
that's a strong guy what are you doing
in Noob area
yeah only new people
wants to take a look
pockets
foreign
let us know when you're ready
okay it's okay it's okay you guys want
to check out the cellar while we're at
it oh seller yeah that sounds fun what's
there I have no idea
okay I'm down let's go
pretty sure it's like a mini dungeon
like yeah yes invite me now Kyla or
oh no no no no it's okay I'm I'm still
um trying to fix the battle knife
you guys just have fun first it's fine
[Applause]
true
yeah so it's okay it's okay uh
you've seen it all you've experienced it
all
did I just got bad or wet I don't even
know what's happening
there is a problem logging in oh no yeah
oh goodies this looks nice
these all look super good yeah I guess
that's it now oh nice loot ladies was a
small signed
um
okay leaving the cellar
okay
like a wine cellar right Carrara
I don't drink wine what what's that wine
cellar yeah he said yeah you said you
had to sell her I'm just asking Hey
where's The Cider at wait what is this
where's that where's the cider
that's what I want to know where's the
cider room
there I think
I think I'm in
really okay
yay
oh dude look good damn okay
maybe we can invite possess you're not
in the game yet what I'm in game
maybe it takes a moment oh wait now
invited
okay let's go
[Music]
um try to catch up with us it's okay
it's okay I'll just teleport okay having
a party right now
everywhere Pepsi these guys are nothing
they're chumps
I still feel like we're kind of
steamrolling yeah yeah we're doing
pretty good I'm glad we changed tears
it yeah it's good now it's more like a
little bit more challenging now a little
bit
stronger enemies
it does feel like it yeah but I already
gotta level up so the EXP is flowing
I'm close to leveling up excited for
hard bosses yeah
the act one boss but I I guess we
probably won't get there today
it's okay
[Music]
I tried to look for Monsters I can't
find anything it works just following
you guys
[Music]
um it's okay I'm here I see Kyla I'm
here let's go
[Music]
United again yay yay let's go
also you guys finished the what is that
the the story the first story The the
dungeon one oh no no it's a seller like
a random ah okay okay screen
there is an event below
okay yeah we can go get some new
skeletons
we need to wait for a moment it will
spawn here I think I don't know I'm
gonna change my skirmishers okay into
defense skellies oh
inspect the ancient Obelisk oh here we
go let's go
um Corpses
okay
[Music]
so we have to stand on this place yeah
we need to stand still
you have to keep standing on it until
it's gone it's already it's already done
it's already done oh it's already done
yeah there are like um orange circle
until it's gone
yay
oh okay yay
[Applause]
I want to see some some stats on who
does the most damage me too do we get to
see that no I don't think no
what I want to see more wants to see if
she's actually helping
you have the power of five skeletons I'm
sure you're helping I guess so
Shield skellies toys like the Defenders
lightning storm tornado
[Music]
um
under the bone Zone
which which uh uh classes did you
already play
oh uh I played uh sorceress and
Barbarian before
oh nice
and Magic sounds fun it's still got some
different classes to go maybe yeah sure
true true that's true you can do yep I
wanna try it all
yeah true and using magic seems fun in
this game in particular
um
personally and in games like this I just
always like to keep a distance from the
enemy so I'm usually like some kind of
Mage class yeah or or a Healer and
usually a Healer I feel like you'd do
good with Necromancer too because
Necromancer has a lot of far away stuff
yeah
my
my sorcerer was like a tank sorcerer
I take all of the damage
romancer I would like to be a nickel
mantis
[Applause]
um
they can be big scary cats or they can
be small kitty cats that you can pet
Dude Where's the mug for this that
sounds amazing yeah right yeah I know
right
forget the skeleton deadbeats I want I
want skeleton cats
wolves
or they could just be regular cats
that's fine too
oh Tyler careful
it's fine I'm calling my wolf
yeah
oh okay you're back up
what happened why
why flexor
[Music]
thank you for forgiving me casually
arrives in the Mustang
oh this way
okay okay
now we are going to what oh where do you
have you have wolves now I see the the
yeah the Wolves I'm calling my wolves oh
that's cute
oh cool The Necromancer isn't the only
one that can summon some friends to help
yeah
the trolls are super cute though
you know
I'm thinking about it now when I was um
trying to choose classes for this one
yeah
yeah but like I thought the Wolves were
just for show like in the character
selection because they didn't mention
anything about summoning wolves
just an image but okay
maybe next time there are like 10 slots
yeah I mean that's the reason that you
can keep playing dialogue again and
again right so you just need to complete
the main campaign first and then after
that you can play the Druid after that
yeah let's try different characters
it's true it's true
no left or right left oh and then I
we're back in the mine
I think we'll blast through it again
it's got a good feeling
everything
but we didn't get so far anyone that's
all right it was just
beat them up
preview
yeah
bombs away
okay
spinning around it's almost like a crony
copter
Too Perfect
yeah
I just like spinning
I think we really need more mops
this is like
too little for us no this is planning no
no no no no no
I want the bit rate to suffer
I can only do worlds here too I'm so
sorry nice
it's not your fault
I'm just saying
Thailand is too bored he already played
everything this is boring no no I'm not
playing this is boring nah this is fun
it's not fun for her it's nothing yeah
having the worst time in the world right
now you can tell yeah exactly
we're just pulling your legs
issues hanging with the noobs no no you
guys are not no no no no
you seem a little too uh Pro but I guess
you know we can include you know that
you can hang out in our Noob Squad yes
I'm Noob I'm I'm the part of the noobs
I mean My Level is the lowest I'm the
noob I'm the most Noob so yeah
hold on a full blade
let's go boys
okay yeah I'm so excited I love these
fights I want the floor covered in
viscera for me to clean up
set an evil laugh
yes
okay
look at that guy
[Music]
yeah
okay
I got frozen I could barely use nice
that was you killed the bastard
floor
smile that was only a mini boss now
it's not the big big boss yeah
are you gonna
um uh play with the same character in
your like other streams or are you do
you have separate characters
uh I I have a necromancer
what about you is this your
I was gonna just play with this
character
um and then if if the group ever like
feels like not playing anymore then I'll
just continue playing this character
online
sure
because I cannot see us like finishing
the whole game together I doubt that we
can make time so often and
a lot of times where not everybody is
available so I'll probably beat the game
on my own as well I'll be available
every time by the way of course
I'm just playing just saying we weren't
referring to you we knew
when is he ever not available
yeah I mean
if you want to play anytime just
it's fine
yeah
I will support your addiction even
though wow
yeah I mean I will still going back to
my main character so if like let's say
you guys have already like reached um
tier 3 or maybe I can just play my main
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
sign up with your like potential to play
so many games for so many hours I feel
like
I'm surprised you're not or are you are
you playing Zelda tears
oh that's the reason like I mean I need
to choose between the Zelda and the
Diablo back then yeah yeah because I
know that if I I just cannot uh later
[Music]
I think for some games that I cannot
have the time to play I'll just watch
others to play
okay yeah
I'm almost done though with the game
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
others members playing Zelda too back
then yeah
grinding on it for a while there yeah
like nine hour streams but that's
nothing for Kayla that's nine hour
stream is like a three hour stream oh
silence Kiara silence you're still the
marathon come on now don't give me that
both of you guys are insane people
what are you saying you're also the one
that do like a long streams no no no
what do you mean no you guys all do long
streams
[Music]
they all grind in our own ways I guess
you're all guilty all right well
guilty as charged is that how you yeah
yeah
I don't know streaming it doesn't feel
like a chore to me so I mean I don't
know it's just kind of fun I don't
really notice it
not anymore at least
how do we get down there
we need to go around a ladder
whale ladder
sugoi
consideration
so technology
technologically oh
they should look at Germany and use
Germany technology
oh
put an elevator in this weird ass
dungeon
something happening are we opening the
door no I don't think so I think we just
need to go this way
okay I don't think we're going out
no no
no bring on them
[Music]
complete no reward received you have
completed this Quest already okay well
all righty reward receive
sadness I mean I've already completed
the quest so I guess we are going that's
it no
you got a wrong way oh
to talk to the dude we need to wait for
the NPCs
oh gosh I made the same mistake before I
also did the same mistake right so makes
me a little
yeah
no no no no we just have to go all the
way back
it's like just a shortcut
look for later always talk to them PCS
really we got it I don't need NPCs I got
my girls
oh ah only one person had to talk to
yeah there we go there we go completed
by the crownster
opening the door
okay no
oh everybody's dead sweet and there's
one that's alive money talks a lot
though do you have any money oh yeah
over where this guy talks too much okay
who did this
oh yeah he's dead don't worry I made
sure
yeah he's super dead now
every jump jump oh well not super dead
enough
girls are you coming over
you guys already yeah
I I don't want to skip it but yeah
okay let's go
it's okay I already saw the stair the
story okay to see it it's in my Beta
stream chat if you're curious okay okay
oh yeah let's go Mommy
oh they're all watching I see
yeah we all know Lilith is hot okay we
get it are we watching the cutscene
I mean I skipped it
I'm afraid if I press Skip and then you
guys gonna be skipped oh no no no it's
not it's not oh really yeah there's a
symbol that shows that someone's
watching okay then
next time maybe I'll watch
I was wondering
while I'm watching a cut scene oh LOL no
no no no Mean Girls play together don't
you even worry about that
yeah Mean Girls sleigh
yes
I wanted to ask you something yes
would you maybe consider
um sharing some of that cake with me
wait all of a sudden yeah
she's in desperate need I am in
desperate needs why I mean I think I'm
fixed it
what might but it's still like nothing
compared to your cake and that's just
not fair I want the cake too
I mean it's it's
can't help what you're born with yeah I
mean I can't deny it I can't I was gonna
say it's not that good but you know it
is pretty it is pretty good but the next
question for you to sit on and stream
for long hours
[Applause]
okay okay so so no cake for me is that
what you're saying no I think I think
you should ask again
for them to like Bluff your man buff
your cake
I feel like the buff that I got uh was
the first and the last one there will
not be any more Buffs what
that's not fair
you could probably get another like you
know outfit
where there is more cake butt pads yeah
butt pads and the new outfit but be like
oh I don't want to be able to see the
butt pads or notice that they're butt
pads but there are butt pads in the
skirt or whatever yeah and the shorts
well uh as far as I know they wouldn't
change like you know the butt size just
because there's a new outfit
but but you could still ask for the pads
though yeah
like they can't really say no because
those are real things
I know K-pop Idols use it yeah exactly
so maybe it's a tribute
K-pop Idol butt pad butt pad oh it's
just for it's just for protection you
know when I get down on the floor you
know yeah ma'am I need some buttons
for uh one million dollars but you know
even the insurance it's just not not
enough see it has a use do we need to
climb down I think we need to climb down
have has anyone talked about the talk
with the whatever sign is that like in
the corner of the room because like I
wait now I see now I see a quest mark
thingy oh there it is okay okay okay
yay
thank you more
yeah Morp says no problem place to trap
nope
booty
did you know
that your mommy is next on my list
she's going after all the hollow moms
what do you mean
well you know you know that I'm very
popular with whole moms but the thing is
that your mom is kind of special to me
because she's a hello project otaku just
like me
yeah you told me yeah
so you're going after my mom
yeah
just admits to it
no oh no my mom not my mom
she she will maybe adopt me you know
because she she she's into Idol so I'm
into Idols I'm sure she wants a daughter
like me you can have a sister
is my game glitch
you're just all about in the back what
happened no you guys are Frozen at the
gate oh wait I can't attack enemies
you cannot move
I mean I can move no you're standing
yeah you're just standing still yeah I
think you're having like a
um a network
issue a DC maybe
I don't have to rejoin maybe yeah
if I leave the party and come back do I
do I have to start over or is it okay
good question
I mean it's okay
um there's gonna be like a portal that
you can teleport to us later on
okay yeah no worries okay
progress is based on party leader well
that's good news
okay okay let me get out of here
didn't
didn't no I'm not this disowning my papa
but I mean one can have more than one
parent right
i i i oh
morph is yes
why are you girls dying
what oh no it's because of like if we go
further and it's not in the range it's
gonna be like we're dying
of course why would I
um
where is okay we can't we still at the
door okay
okay we just need to go around I gotta
run all the way back
all the way back yeah we're running all
the way back
kind of far away I'm a little further to
oh no nothing changed
yeah let me see
um let me try again to just leave
okay
did you maybe just restart the game
completely yeah maybe I restarted the
bed on that I restart the game
let's wait here let's not go too far in
case she has to walk all the way no no
it's fine uh the portal can be like
teleport to us okay yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
luck is not good tonight
that's okay
that's what matters that's the fun part
you know about collabing there's gonna
be like each other
now let's morph back into party yeah
I'm in yeah your party campaign state
does not match with the party leaders
you'll be making progress in the party
leaders campaign okay now to teleport to
you guys you need to go to the
um the Waypoint they're like there's
gonna be like four portals just hop into
us
okay teleport to oh crony yep yep okay
macaroni oh okay
morph is on the way okay yes ladies
it seems all here okay let's go
picking up macaroni
last time I was in America I had my
first ever macaroni and cheese
what'd you think how was it
yeah I knew you'd like it yeah it was so
good but the portion was so big I could
I only eat like half of it I I swear it
was cute I tried my best
better to share
American portion
what the [\h__\h] American portion please
they are too big
I feel like it's better to make it a
shared plate yeah so it was so good I
want to try making it at home
yeah it's pretty it's fairly easy to do
is home cooking
I don't really know how mac and cheese
tastes like
no
what
I thought everybody over there eats mac
and cheese all the time
Maybe
maybe not me or maybe not
um
I'm gonna ship you a ton of instant
craft now oh dear are they instant one
that one's good too
yeah
they're decent it's not as good as like
The Gourmet stuff like stuff you might
get at like a restaurant that's for sure
um but what the [\h__\h] still pretty tasty
I mean I think it depends on the person
and not in excess of course oh gosh like
little me
hello
that guy's annoying
um
I got
um Kiara's birthday present it came in
today
I saw something on the Internet and I
thought you'd really like it what yeah
you're getting me just a little bit yes
just a little thing I hope to ship it to
you make it in time for your birthday
but I don't know maybe you'll never use
them but I thought I don't know
in Japan
oh yeah wait wait why Kiara is like
I don't know what the [\h__\h] happened oh
wait yeah yeah she's not here what
happened I was trying to kill an enemy
and went in the same spot where I was
putting my mouse at suddenly something
appeared and I accidentally clicked yet
oh no
what was that anyway here let me maybe
we can invite you back if I the leader
now is crony why invite the party yeah
you're the leader now oh no you're
joining
uh you're about to be transferred to the
party okay transfer now did I miss
something
you're off tonight can I delegate my
host to you just just leave the party
just leave the party
just leave the party yeah just leave
your party uh right click yeah
and now and now it's gonna be me okay
I'm leaving the party okay
with me I don't know I don't want party
leader
[Music]
I'll be the party leader everybody else
come back here I'm inviting you guys
back into okay I'll be the party leader
on my powerful PS5
[Music]
oh yeah I can host
okay I I need to catch up on you girls
oh boy
okay I don't see anyone
you guys gotta teleport to Me Maybe yeah
I don't uh I'm confused Jacob teleport
to town first the [\h__\h]
okay
yeah we just need two together
yeah just go to the portal oh
it's gonna be easier
okay
hold hands all right I'll wait for you
guys
okay coming
what was that thing that popped up on my
screen
okay let's go
yeah
sometimes like the leader will do
something or like
a character will do something and then
if you decline
it's like join in it'll kick you from
the party
um
okay
I almost here
crony dad or is she just not here oh I'm
still here I'm walking I'm gonna say no
way I should have teleported
I couldn't protect her
don't be there for her
yes RIP and tear decomposed The Flash
you can't just kill me off like that
I'm still in the game
let's go
I I can still hear her voice
ouch it's because I am here nope no way
oh my goodness
oh boy I'm not gonna fall for it I
should have teleported what have I done
you can still do it you still have the
choice okay
I'm gonna revive everyone
oh dear oh bother
oh joy
oh you're almost here I am almost here
and I'm gonna die
no don't die you're not gonna die
Pro tips don't die
yeah just drink all the potions
I'll come to pick you up
Mean Girls don't leave each other behind
it's raining yeah it brought a whole
party I thought you guys would like the
experience points
oh hell yeah
hi
okay that wasn't so bad I there were
more I guess they lost interest
oh I see them
are you taking care of them yeah of
course yeah what kind of what kind of
party host would we be
your number is here crony
yeah getting the Uber oh whoa thank you
again and losers we're going shopping
no no
no it's been your imagination
it's okay finishing the dungeon
's crafting me no
how to clean the battlefield gotta clean
the battlefield can't do that oh a
succubus cool tornadoes nice nice nice
those look thick
ER
Google
okay
[Laughter]
super boost
oh boy help I feel years coming off of
my existence
every time you say that
mm-hmm
ouch
well even so many bodies around guys I
have to clean them all up
thank you janitor they've had enough of
me chat already I I guess next time I'll
play alone no no no no no no
oh
no alone
all these terms you know where I'm
learning them where
well chat
whole live and through everything I'm
doing that's connected with whole life
you know
my education is thanks to all of you my
condolences yeah
oh yeah
ouch nope
the more you can leave the corpses
they're useful for other skill abilities
oh like what necromancer advice I don't
really understand
I mean I don't really see another use
for them is the thing but if I if I do
see a use for them then I can understand
I just kind of like to leave a clean
Battlefield oh wait okay I understand
now because I I I know that skill the
corpse explosion skill is absolutely
insane oh that one's pretty handy I like
that one I haven't seen that yet if you
get to it in the skill tree choose it
and then whenever you run around and you
press the scale all the corpses all the
dead enemies around you will like
explode and do AOE damage yeah it'll be
like some fireworks
yeah I love that that sounds amazing Don
I love necromancer
they're so Nifty
yeah
okay
ouch
this dungeon is very very long
we're making good progress though yeah
of course
um
my dragons are so cute I hope I get some
fan art with my dragons
your little Hydra heads
and Cali with the skeletons yeah wolves
and and Kyla as oh Kyla with her wolves
really happy with her chronicopter Souls
Chronicles
it actually wolves might be a better
idea
nah probably doesn't need any companions
no I I think I like companions I I think
I like the ideal companions
I can be your companions though
do you want to be my wolf
wow are you ready for Mom what do you
mean maybe
maybe not like that what do you mean not
like that what do you think I said
I better just kill all of this mob then
think about that
it's okay
okay
yeah they're definitely taking a lot
more time to kill which I appreciate
yeah I think it's a better idea that we
change
I didn't want to do it alone but at the
party
um yeah yeah
I'm not ready yet
it's a [\h__\h] chaos though
it's been amazing
my next we're too strong
the boss might be a bit harder now might
actually kill a couple of you well
looking nice let's go I can't wait
if you die from the boss just so that I
can feel something
nothing here not great question no idea
but hey not knowing is part of the fun
right exactly it raises the steaks but
as the ritual started already here or
what What I Hear Voices dead priest
oh no she's just talking next to me okay
she's just a little freaky
yeah she's just her mind a little bit
she's destroying fan art
I have your back lady
we want to watch this costume this one's
pretty cool oh oopsies I kind of skipped
it already
where is everyone oh look at it there
they are where are you guys moving
hey why aren't you guys moving oh
because you're watching it all right
it's fine I got it
enjoy the casino hold down the fort I've
done this battle before
okay you're fighting someone yes
you fighting a lie
I'm good don't worry about it I got my
skeletons
she awakened me Magpie I saw a magpie
blood ritual the other day on YouTube
can't even oh what okay I thought you
were just gonna say I saw a magpie and I
was gonna say oh I'll make my blood
ritual oh
I'm here
it's a bird right oh yeah it's a
birthday just to collect things I
believe right I thought wait it wasn't
reactions
they were crying when one was like dead
and all the magpies were gathering
around and going like
oh they're mourning oh yeah
who are we fighting eh we are fighting
the mother
ow yeah she's really pissed right now
okay wait I I I'm never gonna watch
blinds again
if I'm missing all the accents no no no
no I wouldn't have skipped it if I had
known that there was gonna be a
difference
should we find the health spawns and all
that over here it's probably a good idea
she's immune right so yeah yeah
gotta kill her her demons
whoopsie
okay get him oh
come on get the hell spawn okay that's
one down
let's go
oh nice
oceans for days let's go yum yum oh
you want someone
you want some let's go not mean to do
that like these oh yeah these are some
big boys
all right it's getting a little tough I
like it yeah this is fun this is fun
Lord
oh God I should focus on our skeletons
where are you at yeah that's usually a
good idea
oh the pit Lord is pretty scary
who is a spicy meatball
come on die okay great
[Music]
do we have to kill enemies in order to
make this fun yeah
close
yeah
Lord really likes me he will not leave
me alone
it can be a distraction you're you're
the chosen one in the chosen one yeah
oh the pit Lord hates it oh I killed him
yeah
nice one team that was pretty cool I
don't know about you girls but my HP was
struggling yeah me too it was fun it was
fine
yes I was protecting you
everything I don't know no idea
I'm not skipping it because I feel bad
that I skipped at the first one
go back to your profit less blood okay
beg if you need to oh we're gonna see
the problem
eat it grab I'm going to finish it
it's me in the Mr Woods
those Australian people say pravar
finding it
[Music]
if not Nar yard
I need time okay I'm done watching just
believe me okay okay I'm done okay me
too
oh it's complete
we need to go back home we can just
teleport right
cannot we need to go back yeah oh okay
we need to go back
Park
let's get going
make sure to walk and leave a one line
or hold your partner's hand
yeah
yes ma'am like some ducks okay like a
conga line
oh hi
more enemies more exp very nice
I'm just gonna take the loop
Christmas
yeah I'm Luke Goblin I can't help but
more physically no I'm a loot Goblin
just just I am in general
I love Gathering Gathering things
I get it we fight it though
okay
um
waste uh this is where we accidentally
left before yeah
where is it
okay we need to go there to find neural
oh
that dead beats down
you go
is this like the I don't know like the
deadbeats that try to sign up for a job
at Cali's place but like fail so they
get mad yeah they Rebel Revenge
anger Beats
where did Kyla go it's okay just come
here
I'm waiting
we must hold hands or walk in the line
you know my hands are just that long
dude are you like Luffy or something
yeah my heads are just flexible and that
long
it's amazing I forgive
Trader beach sounds like a merchant me I
know Trader Joe's or something the
traitor Beats from the Trader Joe's
was in 10 minutes I don't know if we can
join the world's boss
yeah
just getting no need I'm Invincible oh
nice
do you guys want to join the world boss
level 35 Plus
um
we can take them we can take them no no
yeah we can yeah we can you want to try
it's there it's like
the north of the map
um
no it's like level 35 hell yeah let's do
this four of us if you combine our
levels it's way over 35.
um is that how it works
[Music]
we need to just go as fast as possible
to there but actually I can do it you
guys really want to do it I can just
really because I can I can go with my
horse and then you guys can tell it more
there if you want to try no no no no no
one time when we're higher level we'll
do it yeah yeah
okay
then we can do it confidently probably
why are you so enlightened what happened
oh I touched the shrine
oh nice I was enchanted I was blessed
with like a momentary boost
oh I see here's one artillery Shrine
um
you attack faster and summon holy arrows
that sounds fun okay we need to find the
narrow yeah my arrows
check out my arrows I'm sure she's
around somewhere oh
chest
s
[Music]
like Skyrim vibes
what the heck is she
I don't know near real standing
somewhere I
found her before somewhere here but it's
been too long I don't remember
oh there's a chest here nice
so
chest oh I want chesto
oh no the trees
out I want to hurt the trees the trees
are good people
trees aren't people Kiara they're good
people you're not
they're good trees but they're not good
is what I'm saying wake up
they're good people wake up
I know it's been a long time wandering
these woods but you gotta stop mistaking
trees for people
but I mean
the trees that we know it's not moving
so maybe it can be people
oh yeah yeah yeah
right right right right well yeah all
right ladies whatever keeps you sane
okay
oh there we go
it wasn't the person it was a stone
darkened Holt
hello welcome it's snowy
it's very cozy I like it I love snowing
games we're getting closer to Santa
Claus's home yeah
[Music]
I want Christmas to come already this
please let's enjoy the summer a little
bit no hate summer summer sucks Summer
sucks I agree I wholeheartedly agree
it's been Worst season
whoa
I wonder if I've been good or naughty
this year
I'd say good
maybe your chat can answer that well
they don't know me they don't know me
like like who
does someone know you better
I know me I think I've been pretty good
and if Santa's not gonna give me
anything that's fine because I'm just
gonna get my own gift too
a very good way of thinking about it so
very salty no that's not salty what do
you mean
I I couldn't understand it I can
definitely like I don't need Santa's
help to get me what I want I can just
get it myself
it's a real girl boss attitude and I
appreciate it thank you
no problem girl
why are we fighting Phantoms again
It's a Spooky Forest
why why are we going back and forth
but none of us know who it is
I was just looking at my inventory it's
fall I want to sell some stuff yeah my
inventory is full too actually yeah when
I go back
we can teleport yeah yeah we could do
that
okay
let's go
[Music]
kill shed
teleport break at least it's not as bad
as in like Diablo 2 when you had to go
and sell your [\h__\h] after five minutes of
fighting all the time yeah always
inventory full it ah it was so um
it was typical though it was like the
charm Point somehow yeah
diabolo hey bolo okay let's Salvage all
of them
oh I got some really nice view items
actually hey why are you selling them
why are you um salvaging salvaging yeah
okay both
it's probably gonna benefit my main
account so
[Music]
true
okay
all right um junk common
junk junk
oh
can I not just sell these guys because
these like I don't need the the look
something I'm gonna go to my wardrobe
because that's the most important part
I should actually carry that where it is
um
yeah
[Music]
um
why not they sell hot yeah that's what I
was thinking
Hmm this do I have a stash in this game
yet because I have yeah of course of
course yeah okay is it by the Wardrobe
yep okay
let's buy something
drew it
important
fashion is pretty important has to be
honestly important
what's this
oh this one is so cool oh no so
expensive how does somebody have
um
70 000 gold for me 17
000.
no
so kind
I don't need it
my my chat tells me not to buy things
yeah you can just uh pick him up
apply look
you still won the gold no
no
I am done uh doing my things
okay
which which uh what am I which
teleportation thingy am I using
any others yeah
yeah
this is the Winding Way one I guess
Winding Way yeah yeah okay
okay
me too
back to business let's go
no I'm always not streaming my PV today
I figure I figure three is enough I
figure three is enough yeah because it's
not like we have vastly different povs
so yeah yeah
oh heavy scythe
that seems like it could be good oh
brutal heavy sight yes
oh
very nice be beautiful
oh this is a scary Red portal here
oh we should go in
fiery portal oh yeah
who are we in hell
it's a wolf cute big wolf I guess the
big wolf saying actually meow meow meow
I don't know how you guys know about the
lore but it's looks like my Fisto
Mephisto oh
blooded wolf
this wolf saved me in the mountains
why are you helping me I had a horse
are we watching the cutscene I'm
watching oh gear
never do that by following the whole
road trip
oh this seems kind of like I anti
anti-hero character
yeah he's cute
wait can you pet the dog
that is the important question with
games I'd like to know it is
if no petting then [\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay I have a question Kiara did did I
ever actually ask you to step on my back
or to just crack my back because I don't
remember asking you to step on my back
no no you you did you did remember in
the studio you laid down with your face
on the ground when we did the pretty uh
the collab yeah yeah yeah yeah okay on
the ground and you were like
can you step on my back and crack it the
way that I ask people to crack my back
is I breathe in and then I ask you to
push down as I breathe out but you're
supposed to use both your hands oh yeah
I was I was too weak oh didn't I crack
your back before Kelly yeah yeah we've
cracked each other's backs yeah
did it successfully damn yeah
what the [\h__\h] I guess why is it just me
and Chihuahua now because we are still
outside
yeah let's go is it back cracking time
sorry I was just so absorbed in the back
cracking conversation
I would also like to get my back cracked
but that that the way you do it Kelly
just scares me I don't want to hurt you
oh that's okay I mean whenever people
give me massages they kind of do a
similar thing so yeah but they know how
to do it and I I could possibly kill you
and when I do it guys no no as long as
you don't like you know crack the neck
I think it should be fine unless you
want them to rest forever then you can
do that
remembered that because whenever I go to
get massages they say can I step on your
back and I say no you can't
oh really they're awesome
yeah oh
but I'm like no you cannot do that
you wanted me to crack you back though
you were on the ground I remember that
you definitely sure
you don't know how it feels like no I've
never gone any massage
that I will get addicted to that because
what I know it people say that you know
like once you try it and then you're
gonna get
it
we always want to get get a massage once
you did it once that's good for you
especially if you stream a lot you know
yeah
but probably like massage you and be
like holy heck your back is so stiff
what is wrong with you
okay don't you feel that pain Heather
Kyla not really not really not really
wow what kind of chair do you have oh
yeah very nice chair right
must be a good one which one can we like
yeah
I'm a Herman Miller too
oh really nice just like um normal
gaming chair though
[\h__\h]
yeah I mean people say like the office
chair is better for like long hours
right yeah
if you stream like 10 hours do you sit
straight like properly the whole time
not really not really most of the time I
need to lay down
later yeah I lay down yeah I mean you
lay down my Spears know about that like
I I really lay down
and then like usually my voice
somehow change a bit into like very very
calm one that's the time when I lay down
yeah I can lay down and play game oh
yeah in the chair yeah that's one good
thing about gaming chairs is that you
can completely lie down
I've fallen asleep while doing that
Amazon
it was like a bed like a gaming chair
bed and like it's like a desk set up so
that it's like a desk on top of a bed if
you wake up game and go to sleep
I know about that
uh-huh yeah I think I've seen that one
no that doesn't sound amazing you'll be
bedridden for the rest of your life
think about the bed sores Chad it was
starting what for you
oh okay
I think I'm frozen again oh really no
yeah everybody's we're jogging in place
skeletons included
oh maybe it's because of the Cross play
you know oh maybe
which is really too bad but let's see
I'll just leave
it's okay
oh Kiara's the host again oh yay oh it's
back it's made of Full Circle
it's gonna like tell me who's the
prettiest of them all yeah we all know
the answer
I mean
I mean this is true
but yeah okay the game do you want to
say no what what where are you saying I
didn't say anything
who is the prettiest of them all crony I
don't know I don't know I just think
it's a no-brainer
why are you chroni it's me wow what a
surprise wow
you you flatter me too much
you would never anger Mia
you're too pretty for that
kylo what you doing
wow you're like Chopper
yeah oh no I'm not ready yet
no wow
how many wolves can you summon
or no
what's the max
I don't know
I think Floyd is the max though I'm
pretty sure oh really okay
do rose only have the Shadow Ball
floating around you anything else
nothing nothing cool
they just reduce damage
uh that's
getting received
okay I'm sure you have something better
maybe in the future
you know okay I kind of doubt that let
me take a quick look
is that question towards me or towards
Chrome
set your first enchantment so why am I
stuck at this dark screen it's okay okay
I have nothing I only set up traps I
have no companion
what is this screen I've been I've done
it before press yes
what do I do with this
to unlock complete sorcerer let's Legacy
what
you have to do quests to unlock
enchantments
you need to finish your priority Quest
oh oh the projects
[Music]
let's see I restart my PS5 oh
it's the eventually
from level 15.
huh oh oh a quest that came in when I
turned number 15 well that was within
two days so I couldn't have done it
which questo
where do I see my quest
[Music]
press J
Jay why is it not Q
because Q is potion right ah right yeah
so it is
ah priority Quest
sorcerer the legacy of the Maggie this
one you guys snitch off collab I really
want to do off collab but yeah I do
[Applause]
[Music]
that's a good idea oh my God