[Music]
Please give
me a new one. I'm asking
for a new one.
Chiara-chan, tell me, please.
What's real? My
senior is real.
That's what I'm talking about right now. All 1.
Who's the cutest one?
Peko in real life is cute too, but she
's a cat, right? Tiara-chan also greets her. Yaro
Peko. Oh, that's right. After all, all I have is a key,
so why don't you make me something cute?
Pikola-senpai is a genius, so Tenten is a genius.
Yana-chan's
Greetings
Kiriki-no
, please put it on. You're being so reckless all of a sudden.
Your senior is that celebrity entertainer, so you'll
be able to do it.
Since you're also affiliated with Hololive, you won't come here
in a hurry right now. You
don't have the experience like your senior.  I got it,
so I just tried it out and it's 321, which is super
cute, super strong, and the strongest phoenix.It's
not a copy.It's a
copy of that one.Thank
you very much.Well,
before we start today, there's one more thing.  It's
also important to make the song stand out.It's an important tweet.The
last time we
collaborated was 9 months ago, but it seems like the two of us didn't
meet up before.Seriously, it was
quite a long time ago.The
songs were separated by a lot of time.  Time passes quickly, but at times like that,
Pecora Senta
was writing that poem with me, and today we'll
write it together. It
started the same way as it did nine months ago. Once upon a time, it
started with these words.  I don't understand that,
OK
Mix
Phoenix
[Music] It's
unnecessary to say that Japan was built. I
went to the Japan Tower, OK
[Music]
Art
Yes
OK OK
[Laughs] I
don't really understand what it means, but
what does this mean?  What does it mean? Yeah,
um,
new
, um, I feel like it's going to
make it feel a lot better than before.
Good words are kids. Good words, good words. That's
right, okok, ah,
pekona.  That's
fine.Finally,
let's enjoin it.
[Music]
When my senior collaborated with me that time, I was
still really bad at Minecraft, but
since then,
I've gotten really good at it, and now I'm in this mackerel.  And
Ina-chan and I are the best of the two.Top We are the
top two, and I and Torina-chan are the best.That's
right, today we get to see Chiara-chan's
growth.
[Music]
Pecole is here right now.  By the way, I
wonder if Tiara-chan made this. It would be even more amazing if it was made by a character. That makes sense. It's night here. Oh, I see. Well, I don't
have a bed right now, but
for now,
please take the mine cart out of here.
It's okay.  There are already some zombies, but I'm
fine. Please
help me so I don't die. I'm
going to get into this. The title is
already dead. I was
surprised, but she was
also equipped with diamonds. She also had elytra. I
thought, ``Eh, seriously.''  Senpai, I was the first person to
get Elytra at the Minecraft Sour around here.
[Music]
Wow, that's Pico! It's
amazing. I'm
getting chilly, and I want that little Elytra. It's
getting cold.  The
first thing you see is Amelia's body. Her
big breasts are normal. It's a
roller coaster here. It
might be dangerous. Not at all. Don't look at her panties.
Well then, the next one is Una-
chan, that Mona-chan, and this
is a memory of when her mother came to this mackerel.
Yeah, yeah, what's this? It
's a ritual like passing under everyone's feet, but
there's something dangerous about an enemy.  Oh no, this is dangerous. It's
going to break. It's
not Pico, it's going to break. Eh,
wait, it's a normal place with enemies, but it's
okay, it's okay. This mackerel is very
springy, and it's easy to crush it.
Eh, here's the
hero, Oni-chan, on this mackerel.  Last time I visited,
it
was a very dangerous place, so I cleaned it up and
gave me a rainbow, and there were
lots of beds, so I prepared a lot of beds for you,
so
please take one.What's
your favorite?
[Music]
[Music] It
's Peko's first time here, but she didn't
expect a sudden welcome to pass under her feet.
Pekora-senpai's one also made it on the 5th, so please let me take over there.
Okay? That's
amazing.
Let's go through the Rainbow Bridge. It's a
rainbow road. It
's beautiful here.
Tiara-chan and Gura-chan are so
cute. They
worked so hard to make this. They fell down over and over again for hours and
hours
.  This is
what it took to do this.
We're beginners, so it
works even for beginners. It's not fast. We can do this.
This is an event. It
's the only pixel art. That's
you. That's
not terrible.
That's not 3D.
[Laughs]  ]
[Music]
[Music] It's
amazing. Peko looks so cute in the forest. So when you go here, the first thing you'll see is to the left. Well, it's a little broken in half, but here it is. Also, there's an eyed sex scene,
really.  Mike's
No. 1 in the house is no lie, really.
This is
what I did.
[Music]
It's a battle owarina that I made for that purpose when I invited that polka-senpai to this mackerel a while back,
but it's
scary.  It
seems like Cure became the center of attention because the computer and minecraft crashed over and over again, and we couldn't collaborate at all, so
here it was revealed that she was a toddler, but
yeah, it was like that, but it's
nothing.  This is also a management page that I
made a long time ago, very early on.
[Music] It's
like a crazy store with a lot of employees.
That's right, it's a store employee and a customer. Both of them are chickens. Also, these
guys
cannibalize the customers.
Well, it's a joke, cannibalism. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. I wasn't that human, but I was still a beginner at the time, so it
's not really that amazing, but that house is
one of the buildings that really stands out.
Normal
Crispy Chicken, please, OK,
please wait a minute.
Eh, Chocochi,
Chococho, Pochapocha. If you don't do it,
how are you going to kill them? Why do
n't you just kill them one by one? Yes, it's crude
oil.
I made it.
Awesome Pika-chan map. That's
great.  Well, I
don't mean that everything is written here, but I don't
understand, wait a minute, it's a
little bit good,
but I don't think Peko House makes any Pecolas.
[Music]
Gather all those
rabbits that don't have anything to do with it, but I want to go to a scam cafe later,
okay, okay, okay.
I'm the store manager.
Yeah, yeah, that's nice. You're a rich man, Tiara-
chan. Then everything around here is mine. You
need food first, right?
Ciara-chan, you're seriously winning the bird.
That's why I
made something amazing for the first time under here with Amelia-chan, but there were already
too many eggs and so I stopped. I
see. The
bird saw the eggs and collected them
automatically.  That
makes sense.I'd love to have a store nearby that
could produce eggs.Yeah,
yeah, yeah, that's
amazing.It's
amazing.This isn't particularly amazing.But it's
amazing.This
has a lot of history.When I first
started.  I went with Kari-chan and curry
Opera-
chan Well, first of all, I thought, let's build a house together, so I worked
hard on my tiara, and this is the house I built for Kari-chan.The
rented girl slept with me for one night, but after that...  I
went somewhere else, yeah,
well, a lot of things have happened since then, and that
roommate came in and left,
but it's a
dance spot, and that's where Chiara's dandruff.
Made by Synthetic Leather Meat Room It
's a story that doesn't exist in Minecraft Saba, but I said it only for one night, but in the end, I end up living alone again and again.I
see, no one gives everything to me.
But I've been living in this humid house for a long time, and
as a result, I felt like I needed to make a more beautiful house, so I
made this one.
That's right, it's a bird house, and it's
really stylish. I
tried my best to make it look like a kitchen,
and here it is in the living room.
That's the TV. That's the
TV. Is it the TV? The refrigerator. Oh, yeah, that's
it. Nice. What is this? What is this? Um.
Eh, sorry, yeah, yeah.
The lighting.  I'm
sure I'm stylish with this door I'm always fighting with this door It's
difficult
Thank you, thank you, are you okay? Eh, I wo
n't let it fly, but I'm
going to die. I can't help it. I
tried my best to make it, but
in the end I have
n't used it, and this bed is a bed that can't be used.  Well, I
can't buy that, I thought it was just for looks,
but I just acknowledged this house.
No, Chiara-chan's home base is not here right now. That means it
's Pyoko. No, it's true. It's
true in the documents, but she
doesn't actually use it.
But I didn't look at anything and just made this.Awesome, good
night.It's
like Christmas right now.It
's Pico.Yes, there are already many of them.The
area around this cat is hidden here.
It's the main place where everyone gathers, like
Merry Story, and Ina-chan is so
good at it. It's amazing
. It keeps evolving.
On top of that, she even made her own handmade
key.
Ina-chan's bonsai is a big hit.  He
loves animals and collects a lot of them. He
has
friends like Fubuki-senpai. He's so
amazing.
[Music] It's
so authentic. Ina-chan's authentic style. It's nice to have a tree in the house like this.  It
's Peko.
I think you can go upstairs.
Okay.
Senpai is
eating something. It's Pico. He's eating something.
He's adding it to his mouth. It's the first time I've ever heard of him being able to do something like that. Hey, he's
cute. It's
not food, is it?
Everyone, there's cheese here.  Well, that
means she's on top of things. There's an axolotl.
Pekojana, oh yes, this is also recent.
Lately, that's
right, she's
beautiful and beautiful. I'm so
jealous that Ina-chan has this kind of taste.
Hey, she's
doing almost everything here. It's terrible.
Let's just say, I know what I'm going to show you from here.
And this is the most important part of that house, Rain
's,
uh,
Nether Portal. I
see. I might
show you a little bit about what's inside. It's
Pyoko that's doing it. Yeah, I'm
doing a little bit of it.
Ina-chan's various things.  Hey, here,
for example, it's wool. It's
amazing.
There's a lot of things behind it too. There
's a guy who makes stones. I didn't know about this. Infinity stone. This might be the first time I've ever seen people like stone making. I think that's Ume-chan, right? Ina-
chan.  I do
n't understand this. It's a
new hand warmer.
That's how the mackerel at home
keeps evolving. It's so nice.
[Music]
Chan,
Muna-chan, and
Reina-chan's
grave. They
died. It
hurts. I wonder
what it is.
[Music]
Something like a grave.  It's a little scary that there
's a Pyoko, but yeah, it's a little scary,
but
here, Neina-chan is making something.  I
haven't done it
yet. Box donot open. Please teach me how to make it.
Yes, this is terrible. How did you make it? Pekura-senpai,
bazaar,
etc. You have a lot of skills. It's
easy to go home.  I
can't make it.
[Music] I wonder
if she could teach me if I asked her to help me with the construction.
If Gura-chan gets involved, but
if Pecola's cunning comes in, there will be
trouble near my house.  It's
okay, it's already too late, it's too late, it's too late I wonder
if this is a bit like that.What do you think of
Gura-chan?
Yes, I had the impression that Pico would
n't fit in. I guess she got in somehow
[Music]  ]
This
is a cake to commemorate that six-month anniversary.
On the top is the ender dragon egg.
But we
defeated it together recently. You mentioned that. It seems like we
should all do it together.
Yes, yes, we finally
defeated it recently, and everyone is amazing.
That's what I did poorly.
[Music]
If you look to your left, you'll
always see something like that
Gura-chan house.
Here, Gura-chan is
trying to put all the axolotls in that
Gura-patterned glass. She's
trying to make it here,
but there's still a lot to be done.  So,
this is what Goya's house looks like. Yay,
that's amazing. It's the ocean in his mouth.
What is it? This is where it says ``kids''. It says ``kiss.'' That's right. That's why it says ``kiss.'' I didn't chew. What is this place?
Hey,
it's a riddle Senpai What? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's Noah's DJ boost. I don't know how to use it, but I don't know how to use it, but there's an item called a record in Pico, so if I
put it in, I wonder if it'll make a sound.
No, no, this place is broken
[Music]
I'm currently making something amazing in a place far away,
so I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Everyone is so cute.
Thank you for making things like this.
Beginners. Also a collection of beginners.  Yes,
all of us. It's been a year now since we've
been building this Saban with just the five of us, so there
's still a long way to go, but here are some
memories of the Minecraft collaboration we
had at Christmas. It's nice to have some fond
memories of that kind of collaboration that we made together.
Japan Seven
I want to make a lot of things like this, but I really want you to make them,
and I want you to come and see all kinds of things
. Let's get
down from here carefully. It's
Chan's house. It
's in a nice place, right?
Wow, it's covered in water, Pyoko.
All around me. There
's a lot of stuff in here. It
's Amelia. There's a garden here too.
Tiara-chan, where did she go?
[Music] I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oops, I can go
upstairs. I've never been upstairs. It's an
amazing dog. Today, Meiya-chan
had a dog with her, and she also brought two dogs and a cat.
Go back to this different, different job.
Ah, she
's dead. You
killed her.  Noha,
Miya-chan, Nea-chan, the
dog always says wan-wan-wan,
wan-wan during the broadcast, so that's amazing. That Ban-chan is
famous.
Today, it
's cute. I'm going to put it on top of this cute one. No, it's cute when there's a mascot on top of the house.
Well, let's go back here once.
Eh, Kari-chan's
house is here. The
Holo family's
Holomis.
Of all the people I trained, I haven't played that Minecraft the most. I have
n't done it, so I'm just wondering
why it's in this remote place.  I've moved
here from the house I worked so hard to build. It's like I
'm inside a rock.
Hmm, there's nothing around this big place.
[Music]
Darukakoko is Tai-chan's house. To
the left.  That
A really looks like Kali-chan,
right? Hey, Skull.
Chan loves red wine, so he
probably likes this color, too. I see.
This is it.
Well, it's my first time at home. Well, it's my
first time at the
Minecraft collaboration. It's a
great first.  It's a book that was
distributed only on Gura-chan's channel. We
collaborated on building a tunnel to Atlantis.
But I wonder how many hours it
took to dig. For now,
the five of us dug, dug, dug,
dug,
dug.  It
took 4 hours and 3 hours to dig. It was
n't really that big,
but in the end we decided to dig all the way to Atlantis,
but the most important thing was that Gura-
chan was running that place. There was
also a clerk in the back there.  That's where I live.
Ah,
that place is a bit dangerous, but
there are a lot of zombies, and they all
have eggs. When I screened them, I saw
Zombies, and
there were chickens everywhere.
That's right, Atlantis, after all,
Gura-chan wasn't created there.
But
there are other important things at the end, so
let's go. I
have a cart, right? I have it. I don't have it. Oh,
what should I do? It's not here. It's not here. I
don't have anything like iron.  So please wait here for a moment.
Give it there and wait. It's
okay. I'll
go back outside.
[Music]
Iron. Was it just
iron? Iron, right? 5 irons, okok. I'll
go back. It's
really spacious.
The five of us made it.  - Um, all five of us were
so
sleepy.
Gura-chan, how long do we have to dig this
? It's a memory that keeps on going.
[Music]
On the way, there
were so many things, ah, so many things. Hmm, so many things.
Stop
digging.  It's a subway that the guy who stopped after the train did his
best to make. It
was happening early in the
morning on Japan time,
and I thought it was a Minecraft game, but when I saw it, the railroad tracks were
just pulling out and I saw something like
1-2-3-4.5678
I made this to give the impression that it's a cute Peko doing something while counting.As
a result, that Mamilia-chan
becomes a subway person.This
is a very long subway person.
Please understand that Opera Club-senpai,
it's not quite that big.
It's Marching. I
think I was surprised when I dug it. I
'm digging a lot of things here. It's
long. It
's Atlan after all.
There's a lot of songs in there. I
was on my way, uh, I just passed by.  However, along
the way there was my town called Phoenix Sen, which should have been
written about in the small print, and I
'll introduce you to it later.I now
have a way to
get there.It's faster than the subway.  The
way to go by ice cream
Pierre car by boat
Shortcut
Short It's so cute, it's so hard on the subway
It's
okay because there's a reason There's a reason It's
okay There's a ghost
This is mine at the end  Oh, I've
arrived at your request Um, there's coffee made by Amelia-chan here as well. PP It's picola pekola pekola. What do you mean? It's over here on the left. Wow, you've worked really hard, so please climb up. I'm
waiting for your name, and now I'm joking.  Pecola
said, but apparently that PP is
called Preview Three Pecolas.
Until recently, it
was Pecola
's, but now it's not Pecola's.
Pico is probably copying something made by a senior.  So,
yeah, that's right, probably this and that.tkt
Yeah, yeah, that's right, I use it a lot.Push
here, press here.It's
going to come down, so you can go up even higher,
but you can go higher.  And it
feels like the seats are growing more and more.
[Music] There's a
bed on top, and I
sleep on it once. It feels like it's getting bigger and bigger. Wow, there's
already a lot of Iriyata
[Music] It
's a big building that's really important.
This is
here [Music]  It's different, right? Which
one is more interesting? I
wonder if it's more effective. No, I don't know, Pyoko, but this is
amazing. It's
interesting. This is the kind of Peko that accumulates. Is it
different from the senior's one? It's
just a completely different flow of Pecola.  It's not like I'm involved
because it's just a normal tsun tsun peko falling down. It's
funny. The
best senpai. I'm
glad it wasn't a complete rip-off. That's
amazing. This senpai is the inspiration for Emuya. I
like this.  Is it still this button? Do I
press it every time? If I press it once, it's
gone forever. I press it every time. It stops coming. When I
think there aren't enough of them, I go up one more time and go
to sleep one more time.  When I go back down one more time, a
lot of things come up.Eh, it's
about 1 person for every pico I made.It
must have been a lot of work.Amazing!
Well, how
do you make it sound?
Hado
[Music]
Also, it might
be a little different.
[Music]
Hmm, I'll have to fix it. Apparently
Iris-chan
broke it. Also, there's a very popular fishing spot over
there on the left.
[Music]
Over there.  Stop it
Your ears aren't here.
Fishing.
Fishing both above, here, and below.
That fishing is popular. That's
not to say there's no one out there that's dangerous. If
that's the case, then there are plenty of them. For some reason, it's from the top,
from the very top.
Waiting for the enemy to spawn If you do
n't have the equipment, the diamond sword is dangerous, so let's
do something about it.
[Music] You
can't cut people anymore. Give
Pekoara the diamond sword,
please. Give Pekoara the tire sword.  I'm in the mood. All
I have to do is the diamond commotion. Besides, I've prepared some presents, so I
wonder if I'll go over there. I want a gift that makes me really
happy.
Give me a present.
[Music] It's a
subway
car. I
have my daily allowance.  I have
n't brought it back many times, because it means I'm not connected to JP yet, so I can't bring it. I just came to the subway. You got on the train first. This, this, that, my senior, I'm going now, I'm going now. Okay,
use something amazing 2  In many ways, it
's a useful Pyoko.Well, recently there
have been fewer people using it, but that
's right.I do
n't really ride it anymore.I guess it's something
like a train.I guess it's
something like this.I'm still a beginner
at home.  There's a lot left in Sabah.The whole life span is
Beginning, and it
's all about Elytra.It's
not too much to grow.How are you
doing with 350,000 people in 9 months?I
wonder how many presents they'll give me.What, what, what,
what, what kind of My
Craft?  If there is a God of the en server, I
wonder if I'll get some kind of gift. Please stop
it. Are you looking forward to it?
Please don't expect it.
Hey, what do you mean?
Chiara is the only person in my house who collaborated with me, and I'm sure my
senior is as good as I am. You know,
her English is so bad. Well,
like Tiara-chan, she must speak a lot of Japanese. If she was
n't that good, she'd probably be a nuisance to the other person.  I don't
think Tiara-chan is going to hang out with her
, but Inu-chan and Kari-chan
can speak Japanese pretty well.It's
true.I wonder if they're going to cause trouble from here on out.That's something I'm
worried about.Japan's
face is always like that.  You're
holding back, aren't you? You
shouldn't be holding back. No, it's difficult. Minecraft ran away, after all.  I
wonder if I'll be able to get all the equipment for Nether Rise while I'm at it? So far, all I've got is that ice ax, and I'm still collecting them. Well, of course, when I'm done collecting them, that's what I was planning to
do from the beginning.  That's
good
[Music]
I can't stand it. I
look like a girl, so I'm going to show you a present.
[Music]
Kahlo is this. Ah, this is it. I
want you to look at it from the other side. It's the
other way around.
Pecola settled me down.
It's in the Bunny House and Diamond Sword, but it's serious.  Okay, I've had to
wait a bit.
[Music]
Eh, thank you
Pico.
[Music]
Yeah, I'll give you the Eternal Car Box as well. Hey,
but I haven't enchanted the window
yet, so maybe it's better not to use that yet. It'll
break easily. That's true.
But since I left that book behind, I
also have totems to keep me from dying,
diamonds, fireworks, and carrots
to help me fly. I do
n't have 64 diamonds, but I
don't have enough here.
Please give me a break on that, seriously.  Okay,
please live here. I tried to make it a little more stylish. It
looks like a fight. It
's a photo.
[Music] No,
wait a second. First of all, why are
Muna and Tiara fighting
here? That Sakura-senpai is amazing.  I
thought you
liked it. Yes, the video. Please watch this while thinking that you are loved.
Stop cleaning up your nightmares. We
won't fight. We'll
protect you. It's a song that will protect you, right? There
may not be any left, but
which one?  I'm afraid it won't work, but
thank you
[Music] It
's close to everyone, so I can go see you anytime.
Thank you, Human Pico. I've found a home. There's a little more
on my home server that hasn't finished yet. Well, I haven't been
there lately.  The
new member's
house is a bit humid, but I'll
show it to you just in case. I'm
wearing it a little, but I'm sure he's an idiot who just started doing it recently. I'm
not sure, but TV Koala
thinks any house would be amazing.
As a senior, when am I being too harsh? It's like I'm sorry for being too harsh. I'm
just acknowledging the reality. Piss fans are like that.
Those
left and right
are scary seniors, Pyoko. I have to give them a little praise.
Where are the juniors? Yes, I took a
little
detour. I'm disappointed.
Why are you so
disappointed in Pico? Do you
want me to explain a little bit? Well, this place actually
looks like there's nothing here,
but it's a historical place.
Many
Hollow Live viewers are watching Hollow Live
English.  viewers are trying to solve the mystery about this.
[Music]
Don't fall in. I
hope you fall in.
[Laughter]
What's this hole? There's
something very mysterious about this
hole. Well,
it's not suspicious.  Immediately after that, I
wonder what that thing is, it's amazing,
it's in a strange place, and Chiara
fell there twice and died, so she got
really angry and asked who made this Anna.
Good luck to the winners as well.  Well, I
looked it up, but I've
asked all the members of Hololive Image,
and no one has made this image.I made a
mistake.I'm seriously asking who made this.Stop
it, because
Tiara-chan isn't moving forward.  I
thought I couldn't let it go, because I
know my seniors very well.
[Music]
This is the
new member's house. It's the place where we
all live together,
but it seems like he's been building his own house lately.
It's amazing.  Helmet
is all messed up, but I'll sleep with him once. Have you
seen the new members? I
saw his house. I'm curious.
I thought everyone was cute, but
Pecola-san, a while ago,
Hakosu-chan, that mouse, that mouse, that
squirrel with the ID.  I thought it was interesting that Pecola and Hakushon were
saying something about Pean and something like that at one time or another,
and I was a little concerned about
it.
Yes, I want to join the group. It's okay. I want to
join. No, it's okay. I don't know how it will turn out. But everything is fine.
Pekoira's English and other things are getting better, so I
'd like to try to communicate with her. But then, then,
Holtori is also really fun.
Follow Lauren Yes, Pekoa-senpai,
please be
friends with me. I've been
wanting to study English, but I have
n't been able to do so, so I'd
like to try my best at this, but this is a book that Chiara and
Chiara's real mother made together.  Even though she was
playing Minecraft with her real mother, has she appeared recently? Or is it about the way she
flies? Oh yeah, my
mother also appeared in the video for the 1st anniversary commemoration,
but that real mother,
Mike.  I'm an addict, so my
mom has been helping me out a lot lately,
so I have to show her here as well.
Well, this is
Iris's
house. It's full of
amazing flowers blooming. It's cute, isn't it
? Esprecure,
Precure Saul Spy's
friend.  It's normal. I'm
really looking at it.
Everyone, why are you
putting these things up? I
don't know who came up with this, but it's a nickname called Fukipu.
[Music]
It's a prank by Furi-chan. That thing that has Santa Clauses everywhere.  Ice-chan
is famous for hating Santa Claus. She's a
killer, so she's
scared of wide sheets and wide ceiling games because she doesn't like them. Oh, I see.
Also, I didn't get that all my life, so I guess it's a
memory from when I was little.
Someday, I'll talk to Iris-chan.
If you have a chance, please try playing around with Santa Claus.It's
like talking about someone you don't like when you feel sorry for them.This
is that new member of the 2nd generation who recently made it.It's Japanese in Japan.So how
many people are there?
Let me tell you something interesting.It
may not be particularly interesting, but their
names are Sana-chan and Sona-chan,
but if you
combine the names of Sara-chan and Former in the announcement, it becomes a sauna.Ah, it's
really boring.That's
why I don't like this rod.  These
two people are making
this.
Who
is Pico? Who made this? What
cat is nearby? I don't need a cat. They made something like this oven. Yes,
that's right.  I
see, the sauna is nice. It's just the two of us. I'm sorry, but the difference is really
small, but it's just a little bit more. Just a little
more.
This is
my forward
pride. It's what I'm most proud of.  I'll
show you this. Please get up from here.
Let's GO
Senpai, my
sister hasn't won yet, so run away. It's
okay. Maybe you can
run away. It's okay to
ride with two people. Well, let's ride with two people. I'll tell you,
riding with two people is the
worst.
[Laughs]
This is the cat that was tested. This is the
boat. There's
nothing there
. There was a Pico that didn't serve as a door.
Wait a minute, it's okay. You
worked so hard to make it. Come along and
ride with us. It's
amazing, but it's a little short.
There's a bit of history, but when I
first
went out to play, I
passed through this wasteland, and
all the people in the village died in a tortoise.I felt
sorry for that, so I
made a plan to rebuild it.Look,
that's Ina-chan and Chiara.  When Gari-
chan and I first
passed through this village in the early days, some kind of enemy came and all of us
died. That villager was
really killed.  I'm
so sorry, Chiara. I
want to help you get back on your feet. I'm a
phoenix, so I'll do my best to assist you. Quietly, shift shift,
shift shift. If no
one explains this too much, I'll die. That's where I
often die. Starting
from 0 from various reasons.  I
started over from 0 without any villagers, but lately I've
become a mother, and there
are a lot of villagers, so it's a mess.
But now, I'm in the
process of redoing all of those pictures,
houses, etc.  I looked around once and saw that my
mom and I have been making these recently.We're making them
for the villagers who can really use them,
so we're going to
get rid of everything else.Okay,
everyone's going to have a house like this, so
this and that.  If you go to the other side, you'll see the
big pores created by the pores.I'm
sorry, Tial-chan, because I made them recently.You
can ask me once.Here, go ahead.I'm a
villager, so why are they multiplying like this?It's so
messed up.It's originally like this.This place is a
slave.  I'm sure these people
who are trying to do this are
not trying to
create something dangerous, but that's not what you're trying to do
here.  You
know, Kirara worked hard to build that amazing village just like Pecola-senpai, and Pepper-senpai is that amazing person who can only use one block.
At that time, before the
war, there was no living space, right?
I thought, ``That's really terrible,''
and I thought, ``It's too cruel.'' It's
not a reset. About the president
[Music]  ]
Even the senior makeup artist, Juice, I
made it so that everyone could go safely and enjoyably in that large space.But I'm still making this far here, I'm
still making it,
and this is what I'm doing.
I'm currently working on it, but lately I've been trying to make it look even more beautiful,
so here's the
one-piece base that Tiara has worked so hard to bring up:
Megumi,
Eh, for example, this person, you
can see her name, Eric, Jah,
Click
[Music],
etc.  There are a lot of people who are very important to me in various ways. I'm
proud of this place.
Everyone is taking photos from here, including diamond equipment.
Only talented people are given names. What's that? Oh
yeah,
where are my seniors?  Are
you pyoko pyoko dakocchi?
[Music]
Hey, if you go a little further, you'll
find us here too. The
most famous person here is that iron guy.
Somewhere along with boss Face, why did the
enemy come in there?  I'd like to show it to you.
Well, for now, this is
dust from the characters. They
want you to keep a pet, or something.
This means that all the villagers probably haven't been
able to sleep. Well, there have been too many of them lately,
so I'll
clean it up next time.
Don't you have to say that in a shocking voice? No, you can't
put people away. You're
doing something scary like that.
[Applause] You
're acting like an angel.  Are
you saying that you wouldn't do such a terrible thing
?
Yes, Peco Rise Angel,
please come out.The
last thing I'll show you is the
carnival that Kani-chan recently started making, to welcome the second season of this house.  It's
been about 12 hours, but I haven't finished making it yet.For
example, here, you can
get a
fortune teller.How do you use a
fortune teller?Don't just push the handle here and there.Hey, go ahead, here it is.It says,
oh, it's here.
How do you say this in Japanese? The Shareef Bless You And Share Four Sheriff Cherie Sherif How do you say this in Japanese? A
person named Lee. What does a person named Hallory from Texas
mean?
What does Texas [Music] say to you?  It's a
good thing that you won't get arrested, umm. The
main building
will give you its blessing. It doesn't mean that you'll be indebted to the police.
That's right, the handwriting is different. Ah, that's
okay too. I don't think it can be helped if it was Pecola-senpai.
Yeah, that's still a
good thing. It's not a care. I
received something that was made for something that I absolutely hate. There's a
pun in English, and the
word ``e'' is the word ``awesome'' in Japanese.  It
's a station, so what's great about
it is how I write it, but when you put those two things together, you get something like
this:
Excellent Oh yes, that's right, before that, you can
see the eggs, the pores are like chickens, even though you're immortal.
Make puns and
eat fire very well That's it. There should be a lot in
it.
This is funny. This place isn't finished yet. It
's a Ferris wheel, but it's still
being built. This place is
cute. It's nice
. There's still a long way to go. Horses and pigs are still
being collected.  So, this
is P.He's on a business trip.This is where he's having dinner.Here's the guy who
shoots the arrows.Someone can
easily come in, and I don't
think the person will fall without seeing the video.Maybe not
yet.  I don't
think it's moving. I do
n't think it's running. Maybe Mr. S. It's something you
often see on game shows. If you're here
and hit it, bang.
Try it, it's scary
. It's so scary. Please don't die.  Bekula-senpai, I
can sleep. This
is an interesting place, but
here it seems like something like that
wants to explode, but it's okay.
Please put your own things here. Maybe not
yet over there.
[Music]
One more thing.
There's a place to hit the shine.
Nothing happens anymore.
Not really. Maybe it's in the
middle. It's okay, it's not in the middle. It's
good. It's really good. This kind of thing gives it a bit of a festival
feel.
Maybe Kari-chan is from Japan.
After seeing the festival in Saba, we thought, ``We want to make one too.''
Yeah, that's great,
because it's really amazing, so I'm going to
say it here. I'm going to
close it. I'm sure
our Saba will be connected
soon.
Pecola-senpai,
lend me your help.  I want you to
make EM mackerel even more beautiful.I
want them to call Peco La Peco La Dish Construction.It's
nice and I want to make something for Sarbari.That's possible.I
don't know if it's pretty.
[Music]I feel
like everyone is black at the end.  I'm
asking you to show me your house.Edoko
Glass Camp Irondad
CoordinationAh but ah But I'm
sorry I forgot something
Oh, I see, I can't fly, Senpai I see, I'm
sorry I have about 15 minutes left.  Please
[Music] I
started using it Nine months ago, I was just
walking around, but I
guess I've changed.
Well, well, well, here,
Gura-chan
won the championship. Another one made by Kwa-chan.
Well, I haven't finished it yet, but
at the finish line, it
looks like a sacred place. It's
like a temple. Yes, it's a temple. It's amazing.
&conder
What is this? When will you
say this in Japanese
? It's a place where you can breathe.  That's right, that's
nice.
Please come with me once.
Um, you
came by our side a few times a while back, but for
some reason he stopped coming, so I made a
heart tower for this Togo at the end.
Then I jumped off,
so that's where it ended. I was thinking in my head that it might have been destroyed. I
see. Even if I said that and jumped off, I still wonder if it will come back. It's definitely going to come back, right?  I
love this shrine that my favorite girl built.
Aira-chan set off Happy's fireworks here. It
's so, so beautiful. If you look at it at night, it'll be crazy. It's so beautiful. It's
there, so it's here too.  If I could just show it
to you, Kura-chan probably
has a trident. Is
that a trident? It's something that's that wide. It's amazing. It's okay to tell me what's amazing. I don't need it. It's a lie. Chan has a trident as a weapon. Yes, so well.  It's natural to get the Trident in Minecraft,
right? But even after chasing after that Trident over and over again, I
couldn't get it, so I
created a Trident Farm, and
from there I started doing this.  Elpico
seems to be able to get it, but it still took hours and hours and
hours, and it
was really hard.
[Music] If you
go out to play somewhere, you'll be attacked by enemies,
and if you defeat just one enemy, they'll
make you hate you.  Well, I was lucky,
but in the end, the purpose of the stream was different,
but then I
thought, ``I'm fine with Triant RTA'', so I
returned the title and gave it back to the
shark. That's terrible. It's also my first time trying Trident.  It
took me about 13 hours to watch it. I
watched it. I watched other people's streams. It
was so much fun. I spent hours on it.
Now that I've turned him into an enemy,
I
can't do that. That's not what happened.  You can't use it there
.
By the way, that staircase
is the path to the end of Endo. The
path to the Endo portal.
Eh, yeah, follow that path for a while on Twitter, and you'll reach the end. Eh, that's
right.  End Portal End Portal
Rain Sky Temple This is the Sky Temple made by Ame-chan. It's
amazing. If you do the subway, you can also do the sky. Is it
Pico?
Well,
there are some smaller ones here and there, but I
think this one is probably good.  By the way,
could you please change something?
To Pecola-senpai: It
's nothing.
Impressions:
Wait a minute, make something, make something,
press it, but it's
amazing.
[Music] You can
write it. Eh, if
that mackerel connects from here,
could you make something?  I don't know
what I'd like to create first, but it's too peaceful.Shadow
server.It
's really beautiful and has a lot of cute buildings.It
's Peko, but isn't it a little too peaceful?The
standard
is a rabbit that hates peace.Yes,
Simon.Natural.  There might be something like screaming or splashing or falling into a hole,
but it's a bit too peaceful, so I wonder
if it's going to cause fear.I'm
scared.As
expected, that Pecola-senpai
came up with a good idea, but Pecola-senpai.  is prohibited on this server
[Music] I'm looking
forward to seeing your senior's successes. That
means you should be active, Kirara-chan.
Still, I
received it, so I
'd like you to mix up the characters.
Ok, so maybe it's the one that Peccola made
and who is it?  But now that it's turned into a bone, it's
all Chiara-chan's fault.
No, it's a little different.
Thank you very much. Where should I do it? I wonder
if it's
above. What should I do? It's a
play.
Where should I play?  Well, for
now, I'll
leave my impressions here.
[Laughs]
Just here, not there. Eh, that's
okay. Poimono Bridge [Music] [Music] [Music] What should I do? The
waist,
etc. Ishigaki Nene Chiara-chan.
How do you say "wait in fear" in English?
Today
[Music]
[Music] Should I
do this?
Even if you say that in such a cute voice, I'm not scared at all. I'll send
your screams to the cat's en server.
It means I'm going to make some noise, so I'll be waiting for you.  Hey, Pico,
if I could use it, it would be fun,
no, it would be scary, right? [Music] What should I do, what should I do, but I can't say I'm having fun, jp, but it's connected. Pig-chan, you're wasting so much fireworks. It's not like fireworks,
so it's Peko.
Well,
Peko-senpai, get out of here.  I'm
looking forward to seeing that
Potara.Please come and
visit us anytime.Prince Kamueni
Time 2
Create
By the way, when he comes, I think he'll probably be able to bring some materials from that Japanese mackerel,
but if
there's anything, I don't have much here.  It's
okay to have everything you want freely.
Thank you,
nice 19. It's okay for Ina-chan's rules, too. It's
okay to take all the iron things from the test. You
can't help me with this or
that. That's right. Isn't that why people are being killed?
No, I like it.  Well, that's a sad sacrifice,
but it can't be helped.
[Music]
-
Chan
Yes, I have a Peko at home, so that's right. I'm
sorry for letting you use it without losing it. Thank you, thank
you. It
was fun. The
next collaboration will be in 9 months.  After
that, we'll finally
take a picture somewhere, and we'll take a photo at Pecora-senpai's house late at night.It's so
nice to be able to get along
so well.  Let's set it up.
[Music]
OK, it's okay, OK, thank you
Bye
[Music]