[music]
ya
oh
[music]
[music] mio [music]
ya
[music] oh [music] oh [music]
miomi
[music]
oh
mi
[music]
oh
Oh
[Music]
Miya
[Music
] Oh [Music]
Oh
[Music] Miya
[Music]
Ojio [Music] Ji [Music] Oh [Music] Miomi [
Music]
Ya
[Music]
Oh
O
[Music
] Miomi [Music]
O
[Music]
Miji
Oya
[Music] O [Music] O [Music] Mio [Music] Miomi [Music] Oya
[Music] Oya
[Music]
Mi Ato Eyo Eyo yoshi
yoshi yoshi
yoshi
daui Hello everyone Hello, I
didn't open it, I was surprised.
Sometimes, when I go to that loading screen, I
always start streaming after I go to that loading screen.
It's so dark, it's so dark, it's so dark. It's
okay, it's okay. Are you okay?  It's
okay, I'm all set. Umi is all set. Nami is all set.
Today, that squirrel
will explain the rules and guide us around.
Today, those 3 teams that will be practicing will be Ifi.
And Rane-san and that Chiara and that Lele, I'll
do it without Taunra and Pabu.
Oh, actually, wait a minute,
something went wrong. What's going on? I can't move. I can't move. Yes, it's true. That's a
bug.
One more reboot.
Yeah, it's Japanese,
so it's set to Japanese.
Yeah, wait, everyone's volume is adjusted here.
Yeah, that's the setting. And that escape button.  When I
press it, something comes out. It's just me.
Yeah, I set the level of the voice to 300%. Why is it so messed up? It's quite loud. I
thought, but only one person said +300. I
just don't understand why. I'm like a demon.  That's what I
kept
thinking, ``That's terrible!'' That voice was so
loud, it was 300. That voice
chat was the same one I used in the Holodoro series the other day. It
might have been the body at that time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, at that time I
added 300. Yeah, yeah,
I don't participate in hodo, so I do
n't know. No, yeah, did I do that at that time? Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm going to sleep, or maybe I'm going to sleep.
Probably, the sound will be doubled.  Maybe I don't like it, but it's
perfect for my frame.It's chat side 2.I do
n't have a bed, so I'm okay.
[Music]
Now we are in the middle of nowhere.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Music] I
made it all myself.
Oh no, I
put it in.
Nice
and then
Dada
Kura
[Music]
Doul, where should I start explaining?
Where,
here, here, I'm going
Okay, yeah, yeah
[Music] I'll
just leave it here for now.
Yes, one more time, um, Borore.
[Music] There are
5 games.
Yes, I haven't finished the pre-games yet,
but I'll explain the rules. Yes, I'll explain the rules. Yes, I'll explain the rules.
Race to find emeralds
Yes, Rad collect and exchange them for final game essentials
Yes, yes Events include
challenging gimmicks
Platforms
Yes, brain damage and require teamwork  The
task is included. Yes, it
's inside. I need to
search for Chisto. It's
inside blocks and other things, so all I have to do is
look for it. It looks like it's
treasure, but I want that location to be a surprise right now,
so I've set the rules.  I guess it's just an
explanation I want to be sorry, I want you to want to
explain the next game if you are
regrettable [
Music]
MONMON I made this for about 2 months. It's been a
long time.
Nae is working. It's working.
Over there, that maze thing, oh maize. It's
working. I don't know either, but Nuna
was doing
it. Yeah, I don't know about Redstone.
[Laughter]
[Music] It's
safe and secure.
[Music] I'll
introduce you to you.
[Music]
This is the only platform where you can say it.
Yes, yes, yes, and Saimsez,
everyone is doing well, but let me explain a little bit.beexplalittle
BOh, each Hua will stand on stage and
follow the instructions of Kinkai.Yes, Oishi will
be held on the Indonesian ship, so all the
talents will be there.  You need to learn some simple Indonesian words beforehand.
Yes, you're
good at India. You're good at Ido. You're
still a little better at time. I
don't remember it yet either. No, it's okay, it's okay.
Okay,
teams get emeralds based on how much they want to give to C
BASIC
yoube
Swillalsobekindof
MEMbecausebegivguys
instructions in
indonesianbythe
wayanditwill
beuwillbe
ordersandhas
Yeah wait, where have you been, uh, this? Oh
yeah
[music]
That's it, everyone remember the
words  I'll teach you Kiri Kiri Kiri Kiri
left and yeah Kanan
Kanaka
right
Majima
Yeah, it's behind me, yeah
[music]
from the door, it's
12345, that's it,
Tiga,
Empa,
Emma,
Marima, and
ter. I
can do it with my heart, somehow, I can do it with my heart. Is
this a clan?
When someone says "Kiri", turn to the left, that's
right.  Is it
possible to go? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, if you say Hap, it's almost
like you can go.  It's an
easy win.Ajiko
squats, Jinko squats.What else is there?  You can
throw whatever you want, but it's a real game, or something.The button that says throw is
from here to here.  It
seems like there will be a wall later on here. The wall won't be built. Yeah, yeah, yeah, Kiri is Left Kari, Times, yeah, Ka is something like times or twice. If it's Doaka, it's like twice.
This is the number
[Music] Yeah, the
second floor on the right, the cut door, and the Mera are
probably the same.
Red Yoisho Rima I want to do it while watching this. If you
say Rima, you'll say something like 5 Karin Rima.
That's right, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, let's memorize it while doing it. Well, yeah, I think it's easier to remember that way.
Well, now you know what I'm talking about. I'm
going to come out anyway. Well, I
'm here. And
I'm here. It's so
bad that it stinks.
[Music] I
'm here. I
don't know who I'm talking about.  No, there's this one here,
so I'm going to give you some instructions, and the last thing I'm going to do is
make sure that you can stand in the impression spot.
Yes, both of them are going to the left or right.
What is this? Yes, I
understand. It means that they are in two pairs.
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, I understand.
Well, it's okay. In my heart, I'm ready.
Let's start, let's
go with Oris-chan OKexample
willwillhave
Will There
are three of those
stages Let's
start from the first stage
and
aftercommIwillSay32
1 Ah, there's a countdown for 3 seconds after the instructions are given,
so when the countdown is
over, it's like moving.
[Music]
Where should I turn?
Hey, look at the squirrel, I wonder if it's the squirrel on the other side of the squirrel.  I
hit the squirrel, and I turned towards the squirrel. Yes, the
otaku is on stage.
Hey, Waronpa, I like the Ronpao. I
see, I see. If it's the
same, I feel like there's a bell.
Oh oh ooooooooooooo, it's the
next
Magica, I'll
do my best.  So next time, I
want to see Rene and Chiara, so let's go over here. Oh
yeah, Go Rene
[Music]
Kio, it's okay.  It's so-and-so's
time, so don't worry about it.
[Music]
Time oh, I see. It's
so red, it's so red.
[Music]
Oh SL
slok
slok Stay 1
Hanan 3
[Music]
2TRUSTTRUST
uporafter
BACK
BACK I see,
Oste
2 Wow
[Music]  [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
want to go like this for now.
[Music]
[Music] Naru: There will
be about 10 stages.  Well,
there are about 10 stages, right? Earlier, it was the
stun stage. Yes, it
was the stun stage, but then there's about 10 stages. I see
. At first, it was
just jumps. It was jumps. It was jumps. It was jumps. It was jumps. It was jumps. It was jumps. It was
run. It was a jump. It was a jump. It was a jump. It was a jump. It was a jump. It was a jump.  Now jump,
run left, go back left, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
think it's going to get more and more difficult. Are you okay? Are you
okay? There are
about 10 stages, so do your best.
Please do your best, do your best, if you guess at least half of the time, you'll
be able to do something. Yeah, let's
move on to the next mini-game.
Well, next time, uh,
Rango. My poor memory will come out. It's
okay that I don't remember anything. It's fine. It's okay,
go ahead and have fun.  That's okay, that's
right, that's
right, that's right, that's right.  The
outer layer is made of colorful wool, and the outer layer is cut off from the top in the moon realm.
By destroying the upper floor, you
can also drop the opponent's foreman to the lower floor.I
see, if the foreman remains on the top and the
color of the chimu is the one that
wins, the chimu will take the wool.
[Music]
Well, there's one person at the bottom,
and there's also a lower level here, right?
This is the upper level and the lower
level. Well, it's easier to memorize while doing it. Yeah, yeah, there's another level below.  There's a little bit of it, let's take
it down, and it's divided, and there's a person below,
and a person above, and the
person on top can pick up the wool, and the person below can
cut that wool.
Take it off from under the  It's
fine if I can take it off.For
example, I'm going to cut it, and my
sister is on top.She's going to lay it on the wool of her own team's color.Yes, I'm
going to paint it.I'm going to give birth to it.Later, it's
going to be empty.Sister.  But if you change your team's
color, the team with the most colors will
win. There's wool in that color
somewhere, too.
Afterwards, it's given to you by your sister.  If
Mr. is against that team, for example, Chiara,
and Chan is on top, and Nee-san
hears that Chiara is over there on the left, I'll make a cut,
then that Chiara will drop it, and if
Chiara drops it below, we'll win.  I see, I
see. Yes, I see. Yes, I
see.
[Music]
Let me go. Let's
take a look. From
here, it's okay to look from above. From above, it's okay. From above,
it's ukaru, so the squirrel is hum.
become
Oh yeah,
that's right, I cut it from the bottom,
but I wonder if the one on the top is going to be a squirrel. Hey,
simple, simple,
simple. What's that in Japanese? That
's right. For example, I see, it's on top
[Music]  [
Music]
That's right, that's right. That's the thing. It's
like cutting cards so you can open it quickly.
If you press green, the game is already over.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, if there are that many cards.  The more
you have, the more you win.
Oh
my goodness, let's do our best for now, sister.
Which is better, the top or the bottom? It's the bottom, so just cut off the top and
put it in. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. You
can also cut the top,
but whichever you want,
it's white.  I
can destroy the wool myself, but I can't destroy the opponent's colors.But the
team below me is below me.Members can
also destroy the colors of other teams.
Ah, I see, so if I'm on top, I
can't do anything but put it in.
That's right, I can do white wool,
but it also destroys the other team's wool.It's
easier to understand on the top, so I ca
n't do it to the bottom.  Hmm, I
want to do that.
Oh, I'm going to
take the wool under the wool. Is that a
cutter?
Well, what should I do? Well, what
should I do? The
person below is that wool
.  Ah, that's right,
only those below me can
destroy it, but that's how I can
destroy it. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, okay, wait, I understand.
[Music]
I know, I'm a specialist. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
see. That's right, my seniors are older. So
cute.  It seemed difficult, so I chose the upper
one.O Yeah, yeah, I guess either one is fine,
but
yeah, you can do it without thinking about it.If it's the upper one, that's right.
harusfirstperson
person
Fmenuilang
[Music]
BL
Kiara is orange here
If you have 1 stack or stack of oranges, I think 1 um, 2 Stacks is fine.
Wait a minute, it's okay. It's okay.
A
[Music]
ADIASAMASkiriuoh
Ijangandiah
Bbisa
AMAtidakADADI
okekiriKIKANkalau
salahjatsalahikiri
kirikiriKANKAN
[Music]
Kana people
Kanao people are too cute, huh?
Cute people are seriously too cute, aren't they? They're cute, seriously, the
threads on the top are too cute
,
huh? Cute. [
Music]
Kanao is too cute.  Kamajide
[Music]
L
oet
[Music]
Thank you very much for your support
B
[Music]
Meg
ITU
F
FPleasePRfok
[Music] I ca
n't find the right position right now. Where's the left? [Music] Why can't I do it on the left? I'm here. I
don't know. I don't know. Look, I see.
Where, where, where? It's dangerous to put it in.  Danger, danger,
danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger, danger.
[Music]
Ooo and
Ooooo
Ooooo,
who will be on the top, so that
[Music]
If there are three teams that have been spinning, it will be more possible.  It's okay if you
don't have to go with that.
[Music]
So,
would you want to switch it up? Let's try it out. Let's
do that. That kill
in the jump and the jump. It's
okay if we don't have to jump.
I just
did that, so I'm going to go down there.The person under there is pressing F1.I can't remember my partner's name.I have to press F1.  I'm
sorry that I don't know where your sister is. Yeah,
yeah, if I do that first, maybe that's it. If you
put that color, I might be able to find it. Yeah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
That's what I'm
going to do when I'm off
. Oh STS
[Music] I
see.
[Music] I see.
HaveSTS
[Music]
Te
PeoplePeople
[Laughter]
Oh, I get it, I get it, I get it, that's
what it says, that kind of thing.
Please, it feels like this.
[Music]
If there's a hole, you can push the other team's people. You
can hit them, you can hit them.
[Music] I'm ready. [Music]
[Music] I'm
ready.
[Music]
Da4
3 Where Daa
BL
Danger, Danger,
Danger, I wonder if it's here. It feels
good, it feels good, it feels
good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels good, it feels
good, it feels good, it feels good
[  [Applause]
[Music] It was left
over
[Music]
have I
got it
Oh, there's more left over, white, well, well
[Music]
Man
4Um, how was it? Do you want to do it again? It's
okay.
Sister, are you on top or on the bottom?
The difference is that it's difficult. I'm going to be on the bottom.
Thank you. There will be 4 teams later, so we'll have a lot of fun. Is that so
? There will
be 44 people at once instead of 22. It'll
be quite a bit of trouble.
It looks like it's dangerous.
If you open it up a lot, you
can hit someone else so that they fall.  It's
okay to hit me, it's okay to hit me, it's okay to fall down, it's
okay to fall down, it's okay to attack me It's going to be a battle,
yeah, it's going to be a battle, it's going to be amazing, I'm going to do my best, I'm going
to do my best, but
each
willMA
ROUNDGOAgainsteach
in the final Ah, there are three of us now,
six teams.  So it's going to be 3 vs 3, 3 people, 3 people,
3 people at the same time, 3 people at the same time, so that Yu will later
win
that final land. Ah 3
teams, 3 teams, 33, final final.
Yeah, that's right, the tournament
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was 6, but it was 6.
[Laughs]
Nada, it's pretty bad. It's all going to turn out to be bad. [Music] [Music] There were
also 6
people. In the end, it was
the third round, not the final.  That 3rd
round, 6 people, ok, ok, 3 We're
playing a game,
right?
Everyone's gonna fall, I'm sure we'll be panicking later.If we can
get to that green color, we'll know we're
here, alright, alright, we'll
do our best.If that's the case, then that
white one, even if it's not white oil, there will be
teams of other colors too.  That's it, you should break it.
Well, you don't have a partner yet,
so you can just hit her. Don't
leave her alone, just punch her. That's
right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's
right.
That's right, it's not the number one left, it's that there's
only one left, that's right, that's right, that's important, that's important. At first, the more I looked, the more I thought it
was a win. I thought the same way, but I was
wrong.  The one who stays on top wins, so the one who
stays on top
waits
[Music]
ClearMayhelp
lookatmonitWetell
others have
problembrighten
screens
or I
see, yeah, yeah, no,
senpai, 6 teams are participating at the same time.
So why don't you try one more round now
and do it with everyone? I
want to see that chaos. I want to see it a little bit. I want to experience it.
6 Yeah up and down
6 Yeah
BL
[Music] [
Music]
makes
HORN
[Music] I
can hear the sound
again
[
Music] Let's do it [Music]
[Music] There
's something wrong with that.  It's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous
[applause] It's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous.
I see, I own a house.
I'll just come in here as usual.
[Music]
Sorry, that's what it is. Hit me, hit me,
hit me.
Hit me,
viornever
VIVI
[Music]
[Music] It seems like
it's a smartphone. It's
vibrating
[Music] [
Music] That's it. [
Laughs]
Mao, are you okay?
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sorry.  Ngongon,
okay, okay, okay, you can hit me,
yo, 35 seconds,
30 seconds, I'll put you in a strange place, okay, okay,
onji,
onji orange, won't you forgive me, orange?  It's orange-
green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, green, surface, and a strange place.
I see, I see. It
's counting.
[Music] I
made a mistake when I stroked it, but Gane-san immediately fell asleep.
[Music] It's
delicious, it's delicious, it's delicious.
Let's go upstairs.  It's
not a good idea to keep criticizing it. You can stay.
Yeah, yeah, that's it. Fusu is delicious. I've
tried both, but it's pretty good. The one with
more people might fill up quickly, so there
might not be any holes left to fill. Yeah, yeah,
that's right.  I'll give priority to the person who fills that hole.
Well, maybe that's better. I'll put more
people in. Right away, there will be people who can't
fill that hole, so yeah, yeah, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Then I'll hit you
hard. Oh yeah, I
got it.
It's the first treasure. Treasure. The
sky makes the same movement as before, this one, and two
more.
[Music]
Oh, it's okay. Where are the predictions?  It's so
hot, let's play the next game. [Music] Well, we don't have much time, so let's play the last game.
[Applause] I
guess I should put everything in there.
Moa, rice is fine. I feel
like I need food other than rice.
What's your meal?
Chicken, uh, let's just have the same rice for now.
No,
senpai, please use this.
Potato, potato, potato, okay.
Potatoes Potatoes
Potatoes,
but I don't know how to
eat them. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. But I don't know. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes. Potatoes.
That's right, willbeUStheVC.
After this, we'll be using the Momo VC group, so
just for group practice, do we need a group
voice chat? There's no need for
that Burgchat. For
now, let's practice the settings.
Even though Nisun's group chat is a
group,
it's a group, right? It's a
group, so it's a create group.  I'm going to
make it, so I'll wait and let you know when it's
done. It's done tomorrow. It probably won't come in.
So what's the point?
[Laughs] Yeah,
put it in.
[Laughs] I
want it. It's
Ruru. It says, ``Hey, password.''  I do
n't know what it is, I don't know who it is.
Yeah, it's about 1111. Yeah, it's about
11. Maybe I'll
change my password later,
so I guess I'll just use 1 for
now. Yeah, I'm using that voice, that chat, so...  I
can't hear the voice of the team, right,
right, right, right, so we can have a conversation in chat.
Oh, I'm going to go with Lady, Lady.  I
wonder if that's what it is, and I
can't hear it. It's just a normal group chat. I'm
thinking of leaving the group chat.
[Music] I wonder
if the user has returned.
Hey.
Ern is
already playing the next game. Well, I'd like to explain the next game.
Yes, well, this is the last game.
But, yes,
the team is made up of a fighter and a navigator. I
see, the navigator is
Guide the fighter through a maze that changes body to one on top.Yeah yeah
yeah yeah The navigator's mission
is to help the fighter defeat the other fighter.Yeah yeah
And the team the fighter is on will be the final  Let's
move on to the round.
Look,
I was the one who moved over there,
so I'm fine with the older sister. I don't know
what to do, but I thought it would be better for one of us to move properly.  The
beds are probably going to die, so I'm going to
die. I was just about to die. Well then, um, here we are.
[Music]
That person is Mel.
[Music]  It's the
best game to enter, so I'm
going to turn that Emera that I've been able to get really
well into into that weapon.Oh yeah, so there are a lot of them.If you
win the game, you can get a good weapon.Yeah
yeah yeah yeah.  Yeah, yeah, the
weapon changes depending on the number of emeralds, right? That's right, if you don't wait, it's
bare. So,
bare and bare are bad fighters. You
can do something with your spirit, somehow, you
can do something.  In
the world, here and there, here's the upper sister, this way,
yes, this is where I'm going above here.
Hey, there's no weapon. There's no weapon here. Yes, we're all using the same weapon for the time being. Yes, this is practice, so the weapon is that one.
Weapon.  No, I'm
sorry. The yellow one. The yellow one. The yellow one. The yellow one. The weapon I finished is here.
Did I explain the navigator? Noaun
Bao, uh, the navigator is also a bit weird. Boaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa navigator
has a
boaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaas yyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy of the navigator uh
uh my navigator is a
fighter and other navigators.
Oh, I
see. Well, if that's the case,
poop, that one, and those two, here and there, and the
bed is up
[Music]
emeral
PIN
uuu My
sister navigates us with WEAPON.
That's right, that Kira is there.If
Demaki is on another team, then her sister will
be too.That's why she's on
her side.For now, what I can see right now is yes.So, umm,
Yuffie is going to be this purple as much as possible.  I'm going to make
sure it doesn't come out, so I'm
not going to
get on top of this, so here's the recipe.  Noisy
That's what I see, that's what I see.In the group
chat, Yofu says, uhm, I
'm in the pink meji, but I
feel like someone is there, so Unnie ignores me and says that
there's an enemy over there or that there's another team.
Yes, yes, it was warm.
Maybe my sister can hit that and that, so I'll try to
stay in this purple, pink, gold, and this range as much as possible.
Okay, I did my best. There's a device there.
But I see, standing here makes it easier for people to target me. That's right, yes, that's
right.
That's why, please. That's right, that's why, please.
When I dropped it, here's the stairs.
So I'm going to go into the group chat, and I'm going to come back.
In the group, my
password is 5555,
okay, so I'm going to change it to 555.
[Laughs]
Oh, I changed it.
Oh, you've changed, you've changed. What's that? That's it,
Gogo
, I'm going down to Oja, which is about to start. That's where I'm going.
Oh,
hey, my position. Oh,
but I can see it properly. Oh, I
see. I can see your name.  Do you understand? Oh, it's
okay to start, okay, maybe it's a start. I wonder
if it's a countdown.  I ca
n't see anyone right now, so I'm
going to go to the place where
Yuppi is a little pink.I'm not in pink, but I'm not in pink.Ai, I
can see one person on the pink side.  Wait, I can't see who it is. I
can't see Reine here either. I can
see where I am so far. I can see
the name. I can see the name. I can
see it. It's in the back.  Taja
First of all, I've
been shot a lot. Wait a minute. Oh no, I've been shot a lot. Well, I
'm in a bit of a purple color right now. Don't let
the base get too much on me. I can
hear it. Pa is getting shot a lot.
Go.  It's over there, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, I'm going to get shot too.If
I'm over there, I
hear someone saying, uh, I'm downstairs.Wait a minute, it's pink right now.
My power
will be shot at me. If it
hits pink, I'll get hit hard. Pink, I'll hit you after I aim for it. I
can't go anywhere, I can't go, I
can't go anywhere. It's better to
come back to the purple that's in the bag.  It
might be good, maybe the pink side will
fly.What is this?  I'm
chasing you, uh, hey, there's no way.
Why are you so close? You're right next to me. You're right
next to me. You can shoot. You can
shoot. You're shooting. You
're shooting. You're shooting. You're shooting. You're shooting. You're shooting.  Okay,
oh, I guess you forgot to eat. If you
don't eat regularly, you'll get killed. Yeah, I
forgot to eat.
Well, the road is often blocked, right? That's
right. That's amazing. I was being chased from behind. Yes, I was being chased around. It
was like I couldn't even get to the other side for a long time. There was something wrong.  Kasokaaaaaah,
um, normal, out of the voice chat,
uh, group live, ah, all,
it seems like there's a group chat all, all open, uh, all, ta-ta-ta, ah, are you going to go to all? Yeah, I see.  I see
Okay, but the punch hurt, the sword, the sword. I
'm sorry Mavro, Senpai, I'm sorry
. I couldn't see where you were at all.
Seriously, where was it? Where was it coming from? It was
in a red place. Yes, it's red. That's right, isn't
it?  That's what I thought,
but I
thought, oh, I can't see it, and I
can't see it.It's
quite small, to be honest.
When Ioffi and Unu were fighting, they both
had white hair and were so far away
from me that I couldn't tell which one was Ioffi and which was Una, so
I did
n't know at all.  I
can't read it, so I can only judge by the color,
right? And you
play, but do you want to switch it up like this
? Do you want to do it again? Yeah.  Yes, I understand. Is it
okay?
Content: I understand. Generally, I
understand. I totally understand. Yeah, okay, rules, okay,
rules
, oh. Do you want to switch? Questions with Fighter.
Yeah, my question. Oh, by the way,
people down there.  As for the person below, do I
have to press that F1? No,
thank you. I do
n't know because Chiara hasn't been hit by anything, but if she gets hit by something like this, will she
die someday?
DIHknow Ah, navigator, navigator, I
'm going
to die, I'm going to die. I'm going to die, so I need Bedo and the others. Is
that senior dead? He's barely okay.
But it was dangerous. That's the last thing he did.
Ah, if he gets shot, he'll probably die.  It feels
like there's no second time. There's
no second time. If the navigator comes back to life, you
can be the navigator again. That
's fine. Not at all, but there's no time. That's all there is to
resp
figh.  I
could go on and on, but if Fighter
dies, then that's it.
Then the Navigator will come back to life. That's
right, the Navigator is
Phoenix. That's
right.
Way
isthatalsolikewhere
ATeamwouldbe
orthat
knowOL
Sorrycommunicating
with theSTwhatwasthe
likeWhereIstandIfI
LooktomyrightThere
islikeBIGHOUSElike
mergingwithAnother
EnemyAREAbutlikeis
thatwhere
HowthereTOWERSeach
Side
Going3
think6 not thinkhave
ah
janda try your best not to die
then
let's try our
best not to let them die
then ah nah ne ne ni ni ni ni ni ni ni ni ni na ni ni ni na willbe
3andoneone ah
ba nice
ah
ONEisthereyousay
ThereisFOURTOWERSI
guessoneachSidein
themiddlelikemyview
totherightTOWERfrom
mysideisblockedby
theisthewoolgameNo
ThewoolGame  Shall we
do it one more time?
Oo and Risu will be joining us. Let's
try our best.
Nieto Group
[Music]
Smile, Gogogo Okay, okay then we're not Chiara. So let's
try our best not to get angry. Let's do our best.
Well, I'm going to go down there, and I'm getting really pissed off, so I
have to eat some bread or some potatoes right away. It's going to
be dangerous. I can't have any fries. No, no.  I
left it somewhere like that, so I left it there, and I didn't know where it was, but it
disappeared. So, well, it's okay, it's practice
, so it's okay, it's practice, it's okay, it's
practice, it's okay. Oh, that's fine.
Where is everyone?  I don't know if
it's there. I can't see it. I
can't go back. It's not gone. Yeah, even if I jump, there's no one there.
If there's no one there, then I can't see anything.
Yeah, this is me, so I shouldn't go here.  I'm
being targeted so much, I'm
being targeted. I was targeted just now. Okay, so where are you
now
? Pipi isn't in Pink. Pink, pink. That's right, Pink. Oh,
then, uh, right now, I
can see you,
Chiara. I can't see you at all.  That's it, it's
moving so tiny It's
moving so tiny I can't reach it I can't reach this?
I want a telescope.I want a telescope.I wonder if I can do that.I wonder if
I can do that.What about a telescope?I'm sure I can't do that while I'm using the telescope.It looks like I won't be able to do that
.
[Music]
Anyway,
where are we going? I'm
shooting Naome, Wow, I
hit the mark, and for now, I'm still in purple. Oh, that's right,
isn't it?
Oh, that's right, that's Yuhu, there's
someone out there. There's someone in the pink, so I'll
invite you to the purple side. There's also yellow.
There's yellow, too.
Oh, then I'll just invite you to this purple one, nee-san.  It's
hitting the person under there. It's
shooting right now. Thank you, thank you, yellow. It's a
big hit on the side. There's a squirrel, but the
road was closed off.
Uh, uh, everyone's in yellow. It's in yellow.  If
everyone's yellow, should I go yellow too? Or
where? I heard there's a squirrel on the left right now, right
? They're all there. Maybe they're there. But I'm
going there, but I don't know where to go. I
don't know where to go.  There it is, it's
there, it's there, it's fine, it's fine, it's
fine, it's fine, it's
fine, it
's in the middle, it's over.  I
know, I know, it's scary, it's scary, it's so funny, it's so funny, the
squirrel is laughing so much, it's so scary.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know if it's me, but I
thought the squirrel was trying to catch me,
but it kept going up and up.
But what should I do? It's true, it's on top.
Just get off, get off, get off, get off, go to purple,
go to purple. Oh, I
wonder if it's right?
Inside, there's warm potatoes.
But wait, just eat them.  Eat it, but right now,
it's going to break soon, so what
should I do?
This is purple,
oh, let's give it a little. It's purple, it's purple. It's purple, it's
purple.
Go
The wall is in the way. I have to climb up here at this time. I
see. Well, I don't like
this, but yeah, no,
no,
the sword is broken quite a bit.  Well, that's a lot.
When you get money, do you change your sword a lot? Well, I
think you'll change it as much as you have emeralds, so for example, do you
want to have one strong sword or multiple weak swords?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.  That's right, I'll see later  I'm going to
ask you a little bit about it. Yes, it's
fine. It's because it fell apart a little while ago, but you can quickly get that item from the person you defeated earlier, so yeah, yeah.  I ca
n't tell you where I want to go, after all, yeah,
everyone, where is everyone, uh, Voice? Is it still
in Gluor? I guess it's like a group, huh?  Let's
go, Kana-san isn't here. I
heard Peko just now. I want to hear it, Peko. Are
there any seniors?
What's that? Ah, there are some of them. They look
pretty similar.
Thank you, E. and Question.
Question.  What,
that, that, that, uh, you know, you can
buy many swords, or you can only buy one sword.
That sword has fallen into disrepair, and I
can't use it anymore. Well,
if I had a lot of money, I'd be able to buy many, many swords.
Or maybe just one. That's probably not the case. [
Laughs]
DYiber
[Music]
[Music]  ]
duanybertikitabeliA
SWORDrusak
lagi
mennyaini
APABIMnantiKANini
emeral
akanemalakanDIPUN
jadinantidiis
aja I have to pay already.
Well, the rules have changed again, and
if the navigator dies, he
comes back to life, but he can't navigate anymore.
But the game doesn't end.  I
don't want to navigate, I'm just looking
at it. I'm just looking at it, so don't
use it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Is the time okay?  Are you okay
My time is not okay
Yes, I see
Nesoka
Well, it's okay, but it's okay, Naru
[Music]
Eman is
really chasing after me
Who is Enderman?
[Music]
[Music] This
is Medoko.
I don't have anything to pick up, so now
[Music]
is
How
[Music]
Oh
[Music]  Okay,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, next game, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, they
set that stage within a part of Momo 1,
and the players try to guess what it is, and the
pairs have to answer.  Next, emerald
is in demand.Yes, it
's okay.Ah
, it
can come in any color.Well
, I'll use yellow.And
who will make the building?I wonder who will make it.
Where should I start? I'll
make a little bit earlier, then I'll go ahead and write it.
[Music]
Yes, Mio, please do your best.
21 Hmm, I feel
like it was like this, hmmm, seriously.
Wait, wait, wait, this is seriously too much. Ok,
uh, hey, uh, that's it, that's that, uh,
uh,
that's it.
This is this. This is
this.
No question mark, uh,
[Music]
Hey,
oh, grape, that's not it, no, no,
uh, that's it, the color doesn't
matter.  A
certain color has
something to do with it.For me, the color has something to do
with it.It's not like a snake or something,
it's like a pondering.
Oh, I shouldn't read the chat during the actual performance.It's
probably something like this.If it was the moon, I would
n't be able to tell
because it was just a round shape.So, yeah, I imagined all kinds of things when it was round.I
like balls and
things like that.  Hey, oh, let's
try it with Senpai and Chiara-senpai
[Music] Let's
do
it, oh Okay then, then
[Music]
What is it? It's good and
difficult. I
like it.
This is
difficult. I think it's difficult, but it's difficult. Yes, I'm ready.
[Music]
Yes,
it's 321, what is it,
what is it, what is it? I
guessed it right now Who said it was a dead tree?  I
thought it was a bit expensive because it was on top of the bamboo shoots
with just one tree, but I thought it was a genius tree.I
see.I see.Oh, I see.Okay, then, ask questions.Let's
do it one more time.Let's do it one more time.  The
people who are always drinking beer are
always changing
[Music]
SIKmanglebih
baiksemuaKATAdilar
aja
[Music]
Maybe they're talking to management about something like bener
Yeah, I don't understand this, I do
n't understand.  I'm wondering if it's going to be a round or that
change, which is it?
Yeah, I just heard that Rhys was
talking to the management.
It seems like they don't do it no matter how many times they do it.If
it's three or four times, we'll take turns, and that's it.Yes, it
's okay, it's more fun if we take turns.It
's more fun, though.  If we were to take turns, it would
be 2 rounds or 4 rounds. Yeah,
yeah, that's fine. It doesn't matter if one of us
writes twice and one of us answers twice.
Okay, you guessed it right away.
Somehow, somehow, I was told to
come. It turned out to be true, but with just one surisa, it popped on top of the
crest, so I said, "Yes, pop.  I was
thinking of adding it to Marutsu. Yeah, I see.
So please answer before that.
[Laughs]
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good
, it's nice.
[Laughs] Your
voice is soothing.
What happened earlier was that
bond in the sky, telepathy,
telepathy, yay. I wonder
if someday we'll climb a tree together. Will we climb up? Will we climb up? Will we climb up? Will we
climb up that tree?
At that time, I'll go help you. Yes, I'll fly away.  I
can climb
up the tree, but I
can't get down. I can't get down, I guess.
That's why I'm going to help you. I'm going to help you.
Burn that tree Don't burn it,
burn it Hey, we're being burned, right? No, do
n't burn it, then let's burn it.
Use the stairs and stuff like that. Stairs and stairs are
a little difficult.  I
hit the tree with my bonds.Telepathy.What is
telepathy?Telepathy
is telepathy.Telepathy.Thank you
very much.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.
Yes, no matter how you look at it, she's a girl, but
[Music] She's
been wearing her same face since two months ago. I
always thought that Anya, the voice of Rene,
was there.
[Music]
[Music] Hey, she
looks like Anya [Music]  [
Music]
De
Mao
Pa Yeah, I'll change the details later. I'm
talking about how many rounds there will be. Yeah, I do
n't know yet, so maybe by the end of today or tomorrow.  I
think I'll get a notification saying at that disco.
[Music]
But if you still want to practice, just say hi. I
'll practice. Yes, I'll practice one more time. I
don't need it. I'll try it one more time. I'll try it one more time. So
who knows?  Who's building? I
guess I got it right in one shot,
so I guess I'll try again. Oopekora peko. It's too much. Let me ask you the question.
think
haveang
think. Oh, it's
over.
[Music]  I
was
wondering if it would be okay if I built a building on top of it, or if I used a floor covering.I
think both are fine.I
mean, you can use the floor, and the floor seems
easier.  When I was on the floor, I was also looking at it from above and
thinking, ``Okay, this is it.'' I think it's probably
easier to do it horizontally than vertically.
For now, okay,
okay, are you ready? Yes, yes
[Music] Let
's go.
Yes, it's 321. What's going on?
[Music] I
'm Ida Hana Ahana.
Our
bond is so strong. It
doesn't seem too strong. No, no, no, no.  This is it. I was
thinking about making this shape. It looks like a
plus, so I wanted to make it. Wow, I'm really bad at it, so I
guess I'll
start from here.  I
think it
might be a good idea to separate the locations,
but I'm afraid we'll bump into each other. But if you want to do it on the floor, that's fine. But it's a
squirrel, so I see. I'll
leave it to Una, so maybe Way should be on the floor.  I
probably won't do it. I'll do it one more time.
So let's do it one more time. Please, please.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Yes, it's a nose, it's a nose. Hey, yes, sorry
Pron-o, yes, I'm ready. Kako-
kouchi Color doesn't matter, but it does, it doesn't
matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it's
starting, it doesn't.  [
Music]
Time
Kokou Um, ne chiken chiken, uh,
no, no, 30 seconds, right?
Fireworks, oh, nice, I don't think it's that bad.  It's
not bad, what is this, what is this?  Yeah,
okay, what a banana, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
this is a banana, yeah,
yeah, this is a banana,
right?
[Music]
Yeah, yeah.
That's good, that's good, let's do it again I
thought it was Gura-chan's favorite mark That's
Mark Mamark
Well, this time the older sister guesses a little, let's
see
if it's a hit.  [
Music]
[Music]
Have you?
Oh, I don't understand what they said in Indonesian. I guess there
's no need to turn it off. I wonder if it's
something like that.
There's a building next to me. It's better to look at it from the floor on the floor.
Oh, yeah, lady, yeah, lady. Radio
[Music]
321 Um, tree, no, no, no, no, no, no,
ah,
what should I do with the spoon
? The spoon did it.  I
thought it was a tennis racket or a tennis spoon,
but when I saw both of them, even though they were doing it diagonally, I
thought, oh, that makes sense.  Is it better to
hit it right away?  I
think it's a
little bit possible that the rules will change in the actual performance.
There's a possibility that I'll play it, so hey
[Music] Yeah, yeah, I wonder if I played all the games. I wonder if I did it. Nice [Music]
than Yeah, it's Groups
[Music]
Outside,
outside, outside, outside, outside, outside, outside, outside, outside,
Apa Piand, ah, that's good, that's good.
Excuse me,
someone? Tomorrow is the actual day, isn't it? It's true, it's tomorrow.
So I thought I'd use today's practice session's spectacle for tomorrow's thumbnail.
Ah, I'll use it, okay? Let's climb here.
[Music]
Oh, let's climb, how do we climb on top? This,
this, this, this, this, this, this, this,
where do we climb from here?
[Music]
Oh, it's night, zombies [
Music]
Where do I want to take a picture
?
Where do
I go?
Even here. It's the entrance. I
think it's okay here.
This is the top, so is this the right place?
This is the top. The
chair is good. Okay, wow.
No, I want you to send me a photo. Is that what
all the seniors want to take?  I'm
fit but I want to take that one too Really Okay
Cheese Cheese Can we get closer? There
's no close and us. We're also practicing Kamenkan. You
can use the thumbnails of the 6 members of the group. Let's
use the thumbnails. Wow
cheese. Let's take a screenshot too.
You can't get too close to the things you put down.When you get
close, they all get huge.It's
time to take them.
Thank you for being nice. Send it to me. Cue Yayada desu.
[Music] Waniwa Wani Wani Wani Wani Ni Ni [Music] Wani Ni Wani Wa [Music] he fuwa [Music] Wawa Wawa