[Music]
[Applause]
been a while since we started don't to
think what have felt by now a certain
feeling stinking in but yet we we're
grow stronger as time goes on and I can
think of ever ever letting
go every night I dream of you and smile
got you tied up in my heart I remember
it's so worth a while so now from the
start besides you I'm free and I'm home
finally
wherever you want to go no I will
follow I'm a laugh La I feel it every
every day hold you TI I'll never let go
got a la la la you're in my heart you'll
always St right here won't fade
away give me laugh but fli Fire Fly Away
higher right up to you even in the dark
times I hold my hand up I do the light I
see you and you see
me it's all la la brush
[Music]
every moment I'm waiting patiently for a
new surprise The Perfect Memory will
keep it making us Bolder though we're
getting older these times will live
forever on and on
every night I dream of you and small got
you tied up in my heart I remember it's
a wor wide so now from the start beside
you I'm free and I'm home finally
wherever you want to go no I will
follow oh my last last R I feel it every
every day hold you tight I never let go
la la la Bu you're in my heart you'll
always stay right here don't fade
away give
me SP up F fly fly away higher right up
to
you even in the dark times I hold my
hand up back to the light I see you and
you see
me
eternally
we without you i' be done you gave me
what I
dream my love rush I can't give up ah
ooh get set
[Music]
ready my la la la brush feel it every
every day hold you tight I'll never let
go got a l love F you're in my heart you
always St right here won't fade
away oh my right you're with me each and
every day promise don't say
goodbye even in the dark times I hold my
hand up right to the light it's you and
you see
me it's all la la r
is
[Music]