[Music]
go
one two say no
[Music]
oh you're so me
one two say no
[Music]
Dre
turn
[Music]
one two say no
oh
[Music]
so one two say no
you
[Music]
why are we in the void okay we're not in
the void anymore
B I
am sparkling J English and
today we
[Music]
zombie
up hello hello
guys afternoon morning good
day how are you guys hello p boys it's
beo oh we
got 19 we got like two or three days
until the next hord appears we got a
prepare of 69 it nice let's see who's on
right oh me and kiaha are on so
far okay okay well well wait for other
people to get on let's see what we have
I got
bullet
[Music]
um I don't really need money do
I being made of paper I guess we can
just keep the old tach
for fire purposes Maybe
uh oh far is here far far follow of me
I'll join
them and then I will unmute it unde and
then I will wait
maybe we should make
F
uh oh
did people are starting to Lo
in do we have a water collector out here
oh
oh my gosh there are so many trees
hello hi
hi hello oh hello hello traveler hello
fellow Travelers hello
welcome we're Trader Jen's oh you're
Trad going to grab a Quest from her
right away oh yeah so we start with
questing right away since we I guess
have a couple days to do stuff before
that might be a good idea happen okay
I'll head to Traer J uh I'm going to put
you all in my party okay everybody get
in my
party gets in your party oh you invited
me to our party oh
shy yeah everybody get in my
party we can we can change going to be
inside your
party you're welcome inside my party
anytime I give you permission that you
have consent
you have my complete consent to be
inside my party I don't know what I
would have done without it your consent
that is not be in your party I suppose
inside Mor's
party jeez are we 12 Gigi my God slap
you with this roll slap you with this
this big bandage we're in an apocalypse
okay we have to humor how we yeah it's
how we cope in these dark dark times you
know okay I appr appreciate the honesty
do you like my bat I like it is it
cool over the head with this try it no I
won't do that if you didn't I would eat
this
egg do you like how I ah my armor is
getting oh you got you got a B baseball
bat right I found another baseball bat I
put it in the um weapons test if you
happen to need a second baseball bat
your baseball bat is crazy that's for
you
oh thank you a first
bandage there's a big chunk of HP
gone strong about your armor hope you
can get it fixed I hope so too it's fine
it's no longer getting shredded that's
good yeah I need to keep that armor safe
check your inventory my
girl no problem o Furious Fists B would
like that she's the Fister in this
universe yes the fist are yeah
yeah so I wonder what we're going to do
today for
um what's it the the the raid the raid
I'm wondering what we're going to do
because we could use the spikes or we
could try funneling the zombies the
spikes worked really really well last
time I think able to hold them back I
think it depends on how many of us there
are as well
true I'm heading over to traiter traitor
lady I'll be waiting for you yeah you
know I feel like um how' you
say uh let's just use the same method
until it doesn't work anymore okay I
mean if if it ain't broke don't fix it
exactly exactly that is something they
say that is a saying I wish I could
figure out how to repair my preacher hat
so is it going to be like two times more
difficult because we miss the other one
or does it Scale based on our level I
thought it Scale based on level but I
wouldn't be surprised if it didn't oh
well it's okay hello I I have unmuted
well hello have a nice day everybody
W the Wawa armor Shop is open for
business yay we need armor K my hat yeah
armor kits that those can be crafted too
you can check out like uh what you need
for it okay craft an armor kit uh yeah
armor crafting kit needs okay my cat
knocked over something uh armor parts
steing kid and duct tape yeah I have all
this stuff awesome okay I'll go get it
and I'll have you make me a nerd hat
yeah okay let me see what level after
today's after today's
uh Quest currently the nerd hat that I
can make is at level three so it won't
give you the best XP buff yet but like
pretty well any buff is a good
ex agreed oh yeah my do you see the
quest that I just took on your screen by
chance yes it's highlighted just meet me
there okay anyone who wants to join me
on the quest that's in my party GG
you're in my party oh I have a quest
near there too oh wait let me join your
party yeah get my party I sent you an
invite there you go thanks
yeah not sure where you are but I'm
going to see if we can go do the
quest are you
guys yeah clear that's a clear Quest
okay I'm
here I'm pretty far it might take me a
while to join you guys can maybe do one
Quest without me first oh that's okay
I'm just like looting the area and
killing
baddies okay how's that going for oh my
Lord zombies so much wood I'll come a
little bit later I'm a beaver oh just
kidding it's you Gigi I thought you
were
uhoh okie
dokie turns out I do need the Tactical
Warfare magazines that say improves
assault rifle crafting skill because
that apparently also includes Ma I put
so many in the in the magazine chest so
you should check either old house or new
house I put like seven of them in there
ooh thank you awesome nice hey Gigi and
and uh bio if you want to if you want to
do a quest with me I'm right in between
you guys okay
hi yeah just meet me in the middle I am
here nice nice welcome bab I saw over
there welcome welcome I have lots of
magazines any shotgun mags I have a
rifle world is that different I think
Kiara needs that one I have a batter B
up one I have handy
land oo an explos magazine if you want
to do Quest we're starting and you're
right next to us wait yes where are you
add it to the party yeah we're in the
town that we were last
time good
luck going to do some other stuff right
now in the beginning sure do your thing
youa I'm on my way thank you for your
services
yeah very excited well you're really
looting and shooting everything
huh do you want some wood
don't yeah I'll take your wood okay come
here and take my wood
here swear to God
3,000
3,000 I'll get some more don't worry he
full of wood I have so much
wood
cool it is kind of cool thank you
Grandpa's awesome sauce what heck I'm
here y they got Grandpa's awesome sauce
oh my Lord that's awesome sace yeah all
right ladies let's go wait wait wait
take this book oh oh is the basball one
yes GG you cool books which books Andy
land
um yeah this
one oh and it's a lumberjack one too
I've been reading these ones and then
the ones that improve the club or axe bi
aren't you reading harvesting rifle
world oh no I a hand gun oh you know
rifle World I'll hold on to it since it
seems like you really want to give it to
me and I appreciate a
present what what does rifle world do
it's
umit I don't know what does it do it's
um I'll just hold on to fora ah sniper
rifles no no I don't need sniper rifles
that's fine just the assault rifle
magazine cuz those are for machine guns
too apparently yeah get them ladies yeah
good
idea bik up here I'm going to destroy
him I hear in the closet oh he's got
yellow eyes oh he does that's a tough
one
hey when can this how these spikes go
away okay cool I didn't stab you did
I no I don't think so
okay oh
hello maybe going up this way is
better hello the spikes are popping off
hello Spike
house all
[Music]
head oink
nice good job
ladies what are you doing
zombie that was awesome oh no I have
something for you to read right here
that was stupid strong thank you there
is a lot indeed stupid
strong kind of awesome this bat's broken
I agree my sledgehammer is broken too oh
nice you can we're experiencing the same
things even though in different
places
crazy there's a lot of medical stuff in
here oo someone should take one of these
Med
kits oh oh the barb wire oh yeah good
idea I wonder who would be a good
choice well he's on fire
wa yeah make him pay the zombies on
fire oh charge zombies now huh
okay it's fine bye-bye zombies
enough how many more left I wonder oh
there's a safe
here ooh is found a safe yeah it's lock
picking I don't I have a lock pick oh do
you yeah can I see it you sure I dropped
it on the ground ah they're all
upstairs okay it will take me 15 seconds
to unlock this please defend me I'll
defend you thank you with my life with
my life B boo I got your back oh dang
all
right nice
punching thank you nice punches up
[Music]
Mis okay I got it it only had one
molotov in it amazing oh that's the
saddest thing I've heard all day and
we're just getting
started pretty sad day do you use 9 mm
ammo I do I have some do you craft
bullets too yes I I have bullet casings
also I I can hold on to those wait did
it did someone pick it up or did it
despawn plant fibers wait what are you
talking about what thing there was 9 mm
ammo it despawned what it Desa it was
only it was only on the ground for like
a second I thought it takes 20
minutes it's messed up game yo fun pimps
why why is that how it works fun pimps
where did it
go wow so much fun world not very
fun we completed the quest working on
like medicine and stuff I have a book of
how to make
bandages okay I'll give that yeah I
think a couple of us are so maybe give
to I think it would be
good yeah I think everybody having a
little medical skill is probably for the
better just to make decent
bandages okay oh yeah I think I can
craft for
fun who is that how are you going to use
sledgehammers in the future probably yes
right cuz it's a big um I don't really
think sledgehammers are in my build I'm
pretty sure it's just bats and shotguns
It's Just Bats okay I have a
sledgehammer I think is doing Hammer oh
okay I'll save that for you yeah kiar is
getting hammered oh nice oh nice idea
yeah now they're going to break it
down watch out before he vomits on you
are police they police zombies be
careful I got guns oh wow he so strong
This Bat is so
broken but I'm also very high level with
the skill so you going to move I think
the server is lagging oh yeah
maybe I'm better already help help
everybody's moonwalking in place help uh
oh god oh I'll take it that was silly oh
fun oh here you go play moonwalking um
what's here pipes just pipes oh there's
ammo on the top of here there's an ammo
pile I got it uh shotgun and Crossbow
parts but I don't really think we need
those everyone so
guys want to go uh turn in the quest
maybe get another one okay well actually
there's there's uh tier two clear for
Gigi and fauna here
there's nearby Quest yeah G's is really
nearby lead the
way I think it's over
here we lead the way and then both
parties split completely oh
no I think it's the same house first
really quick and
then can we even do it though right now
there might be a cool down so maybe we
should do the one Gigi wants to do ew I
ate a bad sandwich and now I have the
poop pe oh no I have I would like some
tea that would help a lot I'm on my way
oh thank
you do you want any more sandwiches
before you drink the tea oh God I don't
want I didn't like it it made me
sick you can min max your sandwich
intake oh gosh yeah eat another sandwich
no I already drank your no no more
sandwiches more sandwiches I've been in
the condition to hate sandwiches now
because they gave me diarrhea that one
time so now I hate sandwiches I've been
traumatized better than raw
meat all I have is raw me yeah this
Quest isn't available until 1413 okay
let's go to fa's one then yeah fa's got
a quest
is it over here wait no it's not it's
somewhere bye-bye
diara that guy's freaking me out over
there yeah why he look like that let him
let him
see just straight Savage eating the raw
meat I've eaten raw meat before in
Japan oh that's because D oh yeah
Okie
doie
newspapers Jacob's
residence R crazy there's books here oh
really help book arery book where arery
I have it for you yay oh here take I
have a bunch of Arrow stuff please take
it rattle them girls let's do it here's
Archer
yummy yummy his Bat is so
strong oh do I push it yes I think so it
is your quest I've never done my own
Quest
before first time for everything another
people's Quest yeah time to kill them
all and sometimes it's forgetting Quest
hello oh
hello ow please don't smack me oh I
died no no way no way did my bat really
hurt you yeah I think you smacked me too
hard oh
no maybe I should perish too as you know
no no no no no keep your class keep your
class no I think you should we demand a
fair trial tells it how it is it's okay
I needed to be punished for all the
times I've killed everyone anyway so
this is just my own retribution yeah you
have killed a lot of people asked them
to turn off friendly fire from here on
now we we
could oh know with this little
H you don't think so because sometimes
people want to be killed like when FAA
killed Cecilia because Cecilia wanted it
true oh there there are flaming men
upstairs be careful flaming
men
Hallelujah there's flaming man I'm glad
I wasn't with you girls cuz my internet
just died and kicked me out you
can you know is fa behind me right
now oh no don't worry I make sure to not
hit you you see how strong that bat is
one hit one hit dead if you hit them in
the
[Music]
head upstairs yeah it is part of the
experience did you girls hear why CeCe
can't join us today because he's drunk
she's too drunk it's so funny I yeah she
she took 100 sips more than 100
sips yeah
130 130 sips
of of her cocktail we need to hang out a
little
more incredible Jin
Jin sips of isn't Jin really strong not
not I wouldn't really I think that
whiskey would be a little oh
whiskey would probably be a little more
intense but I have a CLE with the
poopies cuz I need a sandwich oh
no tea I don't have te need tea do I
have anything that
helps here you go that'll help you oh
thank you eat some more sandwiches first
okay okay let me sand sandwiches and
then take
it you have to m ex your hunger yeah
yeah all right time to take my tea
shells is anybody working on Salvage
tools
I um let me
check Salvage tools I have 12 on Salvage
tools oh okay I'll give it to you um can
I you use heavy
armor oh I use heavy armor she will here
you go I have heavy armor for
you oh which one is it a helmet oh oh I
think I already have a helmet that one
yeah it's you can hold on to it h
shotgun shells need a helmet take the
shotgun
shells I probably should oh thank you I
probably should get rid of my preure hat
not going to
lie but it's so dang
cool I kind of can't like an old rock
star
I know I have that did you guys already
finish that first Quest yes yeah
oh well we have we have more there's a
there's a GG clear nearby oh yeah you
could do that really quick I'm just
going to quickly build myself a new
machine gun I think and then I'll come
over
[Music]
okay going to be a bodybuilder you think
we can start your quest now or do we
have to wait some more we can start it
it should be there
now oh she's Speedy
I what you can't pick up a bike if it
has stuff in the storage yeah you can
it's okay you can just ride it ride it
and park it um no one's going to pick it
up really what if someone does steal it
I'll take it don't worry a zombie
apocal I'll make you a new one if
someone takes it yeah I'll give you mine
don't worry oh we can we can share a b
the wives can share a bicycle I think
you can block your bicycle you can you
can lock your bicycle and enter a code
for it I don't think people can steal
your bike if you lock the bike yeah
there's a locking function that's
amazing tell me your bik code now no
it's one
one1 what a good bik code the typical
whole life password you can get into all
of our social media accounts if you just
type in one one1 one one one one it's
very secure mhm oh yeah come on give it
a try hack
us 111 is the
password they're going to get us locked
out of our iPads for a
year oh no not the iPads no my iPad code
is different though it's very funny that
you guys think we're joking stinky sorry
oh my
God he's going to bomb it in the head
with my
bat oh have I already finished my Quests
for today how can that be can I give you
my um a bandage if I hit you in the head
please maybe as an ingame today so then
maybe yeah cuz it was 6:00 a.m. when we
ended last
night oh God there's a lot of big popos
here are you kidding
me there's no way that I one shot him oh
my gosh you're a menace
it had to be a critical hit wait isn't
there someone in The Walking Dead with
like a terrifying baseball bat like that
there is who was it oh yeah Negan yeah
and he kills a bunch of characters that
I love Yeah Yeah spoilers just kidding
well you don't know what characters I
love B silly trees oh okay what
characteres yeah I'm going to call this
bat Lucille in negan's
honor yeah his Bat name is Lucille
gy yeah the trees you planted in front
of our house conceal our house so much
it's it's hard to find the house now and
it's hard to find an exit and an
entrance it's don't worry I'll chop them
down once I come back please
do let you take care of it I don't want
to kill you I also don't want to stab
you to death you will bleed out oh you
found the fake wall oh yeah
nice smart has got better eyes has a
tummy ache I hear it you hear my
growlin hear anything do it again I hear
them do it again this might be a fake
wall too actually hold
up please this could be a fake wall need
that Golden Rod tea I'm okay oh
hello hello oh this isn't a fake W is it
oh ow the still hurt it was
huh what's that noise oh oh someone's
using the
defibrator yeah after the spikes I
really you need a bandage FAA oh I had a
pit okay so you're good I'm good for
now I can craft one I'm level 14 nice
well
well let's
see we did it now get
body
Yay good job team now we can return Yes
get those there's some farmer boots in
here if anybody wants farmer
boots any Farmers that need
boots boots and Cat one of those and
cats o and cats and boots Boot and cats
boots and Cat boots and cats and boots
and cats and boots and cats boots and
cats we're in a zombie apocalypse um
wait until I suck on your lips what yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah swag swag swag on
you she's a r chilling by a fire while
we sipping
fondue lyc have never been sip
sip are you a toilet sitter you can't be
on our team if you
are toilet sitters my favorite all right
there's some loot up here I have no more
room though so if anybody wants it feel
free to take it no worries I'm heading
back to the trader you have to go home I
have so much stuff in my pockets I need
to go home too I have like a bunch of
Band-Aids which I would like to share
ooh we will need those are you just
offloading them on us no I'm worried I'm
worried about People's Health ouch are
you really sharing
them I'm worried about everyone's Health
you know how
kind I reached the quest limit for today
too
oh who's the
Duke all of these kind of suck J
Jennifer I'm sorry but it's kind of bad
yeah but look at her chest that's the
only reward we need
didn't didn't you want her to like be
into and now you're like dissing
her no she's just she gave me some silly
items and I don't really know how I feel
about
them uh let's see structural brace mod I
don't really need I don't really care
about decoration
though
Wonder coal
oh weighted head Mod's pretty
good what does that do um it says it
adds a chance to stun and slow victims
oh I I already have that I'll grab it
for somebody else then if that's the
case okay we got some more
things
oo this is good actually weapon
flashlight
mod can you put it on your bat The
Shining bad of Justice I
wish well maybe on the next shotgun I
can
do this seems pretty
good I'm hungry
actually I know I need to go home to
cook stuff
yeah big
hunger
starving oh she's got grilled meat
though and Cornbread wait I'm full on
oops I bought it
inventory on
inventory I'm full on
inventory I love the taste of
inventory for it
despawns I feel like if we do another 10
quests with her or do all of her quests
will she give us a
motorcycle
maybe that's why I kind of really want
to do a bunch of quests I don't know
she'll give us something good
though something
good is a cooling mesh mod good um not
really because it'll take you your your
uh your armor only has like a limited
amount of slots
so I see like Bigger Pockets mod and
stuff is better I
think wait am I not done with quests I
think I
am I don't know if there's anything I
can really give
her not really farming these days I
really need these oh I have ammo for you
don't spend it all in one place but if
you do just make sure it's
here there's really no reason to even
sell her things if you can't just take
all the
inventory what's wrong with you
woman my God I hate her just kidding no
I would never say that about my
wife smell give me a
sec I got to make some of those armor
kits now soon for G would you like a mod
for melee weapons that lower degradation
by
25% I'm okay I'm not too worried about
degradation thank you very much I
appreci I'll put on my axe or something
then yeah yeah go for it you can
definitely make good use of it and then
this I'm going to put maybe on my
current shotgun even though it kind of
sucks I am sorry you right in front of
me I tabed back in are you drinking
again
I'm sorry dear I didn't mean to punch
you don't tell anyone okay okay I won't
you want to you want to ride home
together are you coming home we're
coming home yes yipp what are you coming
home for I to offload stuff and cook I
guess okay so many things I will do
Quest I need to go home too though cuz I
have too much stuff yeah
what is the best way to get home a quick
trip home might be a good idea
um where even is
home so North well there's this main
road we could
take well we could take the main road
and then go west and then go
north okay where'd you go I went into
the
okay let's go this way aren't you so
curious what's in here yeah I guess so
I'm working hard working our legs yeah
getting swoll ever skipping leg day
going to follow you guys
gosh well when you girls come home and
offload and you're done with everything
then I'm ready to do quests any
time sounds
good is there this way probably up oh oh
maybe this way if the bike can even go
up path it just takes a while you know
cuz it's really it's rough but at that
point why not just
no but then how will you increase your
biking skill oh you guys are going the
up pathway okay I'll come too those
Cales yo can Trader Jen get us a
mountain bike please yeah oh gosh
jeez my gosh I'm just going to run
goodness great
[Music]
me this is just like yoi
pedal what is what is yoi pedal yeah
it's exactly what you imagine it it's I
don't know what to imagine can you
please explain in great detail so I can
visualize it in my head um bunch of
yahoi and they're pedaling on bikes oh
it's not really what it is but I guess
well how would you explain it what it's
called yoa Mushi petal uhhuh and but how
would you know that it's yahi petal if
that wasn't a good description of how
would you know that's what she's talking
about I
really I know how you think so is there
y on pedals
yes ah yeah well no but but yes kind of
I mean if you really if you look at it
that way I guess I can I drink from this
Lake really quick yeah do you need any I
will watch you um are you
thirsty I don't think I am but I would
like a second what what is it called I
would like to share your hat
indirect she's
drown just don't worry about it does
anybody need
water okay okay actually I would like to
sip sip so that way I don't waste the
water that's in my inventory okay here
you go an indirect kiss
oo okay I speaking of yoi I need a
freehand take my corn
seed delicious
Mikes are so silly in this game they
really aren't that much faster but it
saves your
stamina true my stamina is still like
zero but it's it's fine all right bi boo
take this hat for drinking water I will
go to the exact same spot that you drank
at so it would be more of an indirect
kissy kissy
yeah it's more intimate yes she's going
out of her way see I think she sip like
right
here I can still I can still see the
water is still warm it's still I don't
know why it's
warm oh delicious sip sip they actually
started growing yummy my eyes hint of
hint of G this is
GG it's like it's like G water it's like
flavored water where it's like you run a
run a fruit over a faucet and then
that's what it tastes like that's that's
it ran over
yes a fruit in a
faucet I'm eating here you go thank you
thank
[Music]
you oh an a bay potato yum yum don't
tell them I'm in their fridge in their
fridge eating things right
now you can we get some Cooks Maybe
cooking some more of this meat cuz we
have a ton of raw meat we have 52 raw
meat I will cook some more Cooks in the
kitchen great do we have do we have eggs
cuz oh there's a bird what the heck I'm
out of
there oh my God there's a lot of
birds is it really Birds nice wait I
hear I hear more there so oh my gosh
shooting them out of the
sky get them around they're going to
give me a bad
[Music]
reputation we need better representation
of birds in this
game we good
you yeah I'm just taking out my
anger wait I'll your party invite
mailbox oh thank you you're welcome yeah
I got kicked out twice already out of
this game and out of the internet wait
do you read Magnum enforcer I
do here you go thank
you what was that I love how you ask as
though it's like we're subscribed to
certain magazines like that
I no have a
few let's let's get out of here before
more birds show up okay
on the
mailbox and I can't pick my bike
up oh no who built this
Forest maybe maybe we can we can we can
smack the mailbox to death yes okay
let's smack the mailbox today wait wait
I got it I got it okay oh yeah mailbox
magin H hold on hold on I'll set you
free I think I'm free I'm
free thank
you oh no
oh shoot I am
pretty I got water I'm
fine just open your mouth collect the
water yourself with your mouth why is
that not possible I'm very mad about
that I know know right I wish we could
turn snowballs into
water right I'm going to go get armor
plates so that I can make those armor
kits so I can get a nerd hat from Kiara
that ner oh yeah we have to prepare for
the The Raid yeah it's on the 21st have
the old house is pretty reinforced still
I think yeah it's going to be a tier
three raid oh
God
yeah yeah I think the old base is still
pretty well reinforced you know if it
ain't broke don't fix it but I still
want to go get a little up close and
personal with some of the zombies yeah
get some me
yeah we should try to craft as many nerd
hats as we can yeah definitely
everybody don't Tex and ride I was watch
to you and then I also hit the
car so far this traitor
I have one armor parts I think that you
just need
one uh for what for the nerd hat yeah um
let's see we need for the nerd hat in
order for me to make it on level three
it's free our crafting kits if you just
want it on level one I can make it for
you for one crafting kit like apparently
it really correlates
yeah I think it would be better to make
it on a higher level if you can get more
armor crafting kits okay I could have
sworn we had
more you can make them with pretty
simple ingredients but we're currently
always lacking duct tape why you
have jeez
why I'm still duct tape and I'm putting
a bag later I see you biking with two
birds overhead another
one sound
yesh we just brought the desert back
with us
yeah oh wait is this the house really
loudly oh it's our house oh it is get
rid of those
trees for God's sake free duct tape from
the old house or from at
home I don't want to see these trees
anymore o it is night time can you still
make glue from Bones and duct tape
actually
I'll make her some new ones right
now
better just
kiding I have sworn I had
glue my iron sled was C
why what I'll take you with
me all right time for a very frightening
bike ride back to the new house
what is that does anyone have
eggs yeah that's what I was thinking we
can make bacon and eggs with all them I
think we have a lot of eggs at the old
house
oh well the spikes did not really affect
him huh where I look for
eggs ah shiny eyed
zombie finally the moat with spikes came
in handy if I can find the entrance to
our house I will direct him to it
SC ladies uhoh I fell in some spikes I
think he's here he's here oh God he's
fast he's coming into our house he's
chasing me he's chasing
me easy I feel like I'm breaking our
house there we go so
scary nothing to be scared
about a spike attack
like big moment thisiss
all my character's so hungry I hope you
guys are grilling some meat um oh I have
some food for you hey
chefs where are you I'll go looking I'm
on the way to the new house okay I guess
we can make regular grilled meat but is
it worth it I don't think it's worth it
we have so many eggs at the old house
that bacon and egg would be so much
better can we get an an egg delivery oh
God all right I'm turning around thank
you I'm turning
around what happened to my armor it his
crit does that mean it's critically
damaged we have some baked potatoes and
grilled corn in here that's good I might
eat some of that tied you over H
yeah well we're waiting for the good
stuff right
yeah hey Chef all right I'll be
waiting we have one bacon and
eggs yum
yum I guess I shouldn't have been just
fisting those eggs in my mouth I gu are
you still eating raw
eggs I I was doing it to prove a
point I asked her if she wanted to see
me eat these six raw eggs and then I
did did that's three bacon and
eggs think of how much breakfast we
could have had we could have had so much
breakfast Gigi sorry I'll St forgive you
stop eating those you have a
problem I can't help so much protein
you've made your point don't worry Gigi
okay I'll stop eating the raw eggs
please no more this isn't Japan you
can't just do that I have a tummy
egg I'm not surprised I have 13 13 eggs
here we got 13 I'm going to go put you
can you should check the cooking pot uh
at the house or the one of the cooking
pots cuz I think I was cooking a bunch
of bacon and eggs before so you might
want check if it's in oh you were
there's five water go you can go ahead
and take it and bring it over if You'
like okay I'm going to eat one of these
bacon and eggs okay there for anybody
keep myself alive okay and then I'll
bring the rest of everything over to put
how many armor parts do I need for the
Hat uh if you want it on level three
then free I have sadly oh nice what else
do you need uh the rest I can take care
okay I'll give it to you go about to get
the ner I'm I'm in the house in the
kitchen the real kitchen where there's
no cooking to be
done where no cooking is happening
whatsoever yeah okay and then I'll take
my forged iron and the leather nerd hat
is wait did I pick it up you gave me
free armor kits I did
where did they
go oh was it oh maybe I gave you armor
part oops oh yeah I I think that's
different you can have them back okay
let's see how do you make armor kits you
need sewing and duck tape I actually
have some duct tape for you bio I just
need to get some GL oh no I have I I
have the other things too I'll make them
quickly okay okay okay okay wow wow
armor shop well I stole your duct tape
in the old house just know so I owe you
three duct
tape we need duct tape more duct tape oh
I can craft duct tape oh have a bunch of
cloth and we just need glue I do need oh
wait I can just make duct tape too I
think yeah I'm a simple
ingredients y never have
enough true
enough I like how this game brings you
to like even later in the game you keep
on needing simple ingredients that you
get early in the game yeah even the
simplest things like claw fragments and
stuff like that it all has a
purpose yeah which is nice I prefer that
to always learning about new items and
never needing the old ones
yeah for sure okay I'm almost there I've
got a delivery of eggs okay I have the
kit for you m okay I'll go back to the
kitchen
you have to make my nerd hat too
kiaha okay we'll all be nerds nerds
we'll be so cute go to oh no I made a
mistake I put away my
letter where did my leather
go quick there it is okay there are
zombies
here
crafting and finish you're going to look
so cute yay Y where are you rid of my
preacher
hat put this on oops that's fine oh
getting some hair do I look
cute oh wow I didn't know you had such a
beard you do I look
cute oh my gosh you guys match look at
you I am I cute do you think I'm cute
very cute those
glasses perfect
hey they're having a fashion show
without
me we're matching we're matching want to
show you guys my mustache wait I have
cool facial hair too please well I
already know your mustache it's very
sick it's very cool you know it well
don't you it's so in style yes it's very
scratchy for smooches you're such a
fashionist all the ladies I want the
person who dug this hole in front of the
trader
[Applause]
dead no it's funny
oh I I want to meet them I would love to
meet them and shake their hand and give
them a smile and tell them how good it
is the hole Yeah the hole ah yes it's a
good hole it is the best hole Yeah holes
are nice you can hide in
them what are you doing now giggy oh I'm
hitting trees enjoying life
the
beaver can never have too much
wood oh somebody's screaming oh oh yeah
there's a screamer oh I heard that too
actually oh whoopsies that's me ow here
they come oh oh yeah there's a couple
coming towards our
house I will help defend the new
home help
get help I'm out outside I'm out of
stamina
thank you oh my God that's
spner need more
stamina oh there's a lot
jeez let's go oh there really are aren't
they oh my go we can take him we can
take them oh my
God
OU ouch
o I'm infected too a little bit me too
little bit a little bit yeah
0.4% not that bad not
bad nothing a little honey c
f whoa see we're a great team I like
this action I wanted some exp bring me
more oh there's more I hear more you
asked for more you shall receive Kiara
where's it there's still someone
alive sounds so
close he's on the ground he's over here
just having a snack
so hard to see yeah he's chilling in the
gror I see you down there hey gaha I
have the materials for the nerd hat you
do nerd hat so popular all right yay
yeah your special Kiara brand nerd hat
here's will'll get to it right away
thank you so that you can show off your
nerdiness proudly so excited do we have
I've been preacher for too
long let's see I also have the eggs I
don't know we have
ingredients that's okay I will just
zombie it up don't don't become a zombie
ner had finished but then your your
current hat what's going to happen to
that it's almost broken so it's fine oh
okay well well this will be hopefully of
good use to you ooh and I can put my mod
my intelligence mod on it to make it
extra nerdy ooh intelligence mod what
does that
your hat I don't really know what it
does I don't really know if it's even
helpful but I'll take it
[Music]
okay byebye preacher hat let's see why
am I fatigued maybe I will make this P
this is so silly
[Music]
oil hey guys why am I
fatigued you you SW you swung too hard
now you need a little nap the bullet is
eepy
dang I guess you need vitamins maybe
maybe vitamins will
help oh yeah we have some I'll eat a
couple oh uh K I have this for you parts
for later since I think you're using
hammers oh thank you thank you are there
steel steel
steel I get so many Steels let my parts
I eat this if anybody finds machine gun
parts please let me know I just need one
more I'll let you know okay I wonder if
there are any at the old house I'm
pretty sure I saw somewhere check I
checked no there was
um uh not enough not enough dang it dang
it yeah some
glue um is coffee good um it gives you a
buff I forget what buff it gives you but
it gives you
something coffee yeah coffee you you
stamina regen 20% oh that's good stamina
regen is good does it fill your water or
does it make you dehydrate no it makes
you it feels your thirst it
does and pipe shotgun is maybe maybe we
should be making drinks with the with
the empty water than just drinking
straight water maybe yeah I feel like we
need glue maybe yeah glue is what cuz I
have a ton of cloth there's like 91
cloth that's I have more glue I have
couple couple more
glues oh nice cuz that can duct tape GL
glue is water too wow everything needs
water huh yeah
oh see I might make some
glue
yeah
oh good
idea I have fdy glue oh you can get all
the skills one level earlier with the
intelligence mod so it's very nice
mod
cool I'm going to make my sledgehammer
cause some sick Burns today cuz it's
going to light zombies on fire yeah I
want to see it in action I want to see
it too I can actually show it off
earlier probably making it right now I'm
going to take some bandages wo it's
constantly on fire
ammo thank
[Music]
you look look f look my sledgehammer
it's on fire oh it is you put it in the
fire yeah I I honestly don't know why
it's how it does that but it's fun hey
kiaha you're making armor right I don't
really know if this will be useful to
you but I feel like you should you
should take
it dramatic oh yeah I mean anybody can
put that on their armor to make their
armor stronger I think yeah oh
yeah well you can have it oh oh but ah
this is the schematic too I see never
mind I'll I'll learn that yeah yeah I
shall Lear could be
helpful
okay I want to do
Quest okay I'll do a quest with you I'm
ready for quest really
yipp I just I don't come home drop stuff
off and um we can go to the new Traer
okay I don't have any uh quests
personally but I'll just do whatever you
girls have I think there is an active
Quest but I don't know who activated it
it's 88 M away I have I have a tier 2
infestation and then Gigi also has a
tier 2 infestation up oh nice well let's
go do those perfect 400 a.m. ah if does
anybody use clubs yes here I think I
have a mod that you could juice ooh uh I
dropped it in the right here
than metal chain ooh the chains yeah
people have been wanting me to use the
chains so thank you I brought home
eggs I have five five eggs and 20
meat good job oh thank you our bread
winner providing for the family that's
why I accidentally put who he is
everything into my inventory on
accident
hello
welcome we W up on our bunk bed
yeah we're going to help but we are uh
babies and it doesn't look like
anybody's at our house uh we have a new
house right now what I figed uh do you
want me to come pick you
up it's night time no it's 4:00 a.m.
you're fine yeah
yeah and you guys can be on our team and
get the EXP if you dogs we're going to
go and find you if you if you look at
the map and zoom out like really far you
can see a bunch of our names on the map
and that's that's new house
location okay we'll go on a
quest okay that's not that far it should
be that going to
do I'm going to go towards the the tier
two quests the okay in the
desert is anyone learning how to
lockpick no oh I think I would like to
okay here you go thank you but why
lockpick when we can just Brute Force
open everything apparently apparently
there are saves that that won't work
with I had to lockpick one oh wait I
need food so it might be nice to
have we're going to go on our journey
and once we everybody oh is it okay I
see at the old home here there's a bunch
of magazines and animals and stuff yeah
you can use whatever are they can I take
everything at Old
home um we're going to we're going to go
back there for the raid um so maybe
leave some resources but whatever you
need you can
take okay yeah just stop the you
need we'll go on our journey then okay
and then come have a
question sure make sure to take lots of
quests at the if you want to get a
bicycle
okay okay
Willow do we have any honey Now by any
chance no I'm still infected
too a you can buy it from the Traer
actually ah he just charges too much no
the lady she charges less I think oh
really she's so nice
yeah she's a nice lady she wants us I
could she wants us so
bad yeah I'll just get some tree
stumps on the way to the desert or
whatever that place is yeah I'm sure
you'll find some honey have better RNG
luck than me have you been looking for
it
too no I'm good now but whenever I do
need it it just doesn't pop out of the
stumps yeah it's a little bit rare yeah
okay so I'm going to go there whenever
you girls are ready we're going to do
Quest ready
I'm yeah I'm on the way some food and
water yes yes yes so we can stay strong
for as long as possible yes and some
bandaids are there tree stumps in the
burnt area as well or should I check in
the think I did see
some but I'm not exactly sure but
there's a lot of trees
maybe like generally surrounding the
area if I see any I'll try and break
them
okay I wonder how much percentage until
you die from
the from
the sickness 100 I wonder One okay well
then I got a lot of time where a I I
found a couple stumps I'll crack them
open for you okay see find any
honey is that where honey is in
stump yeah I need a stronger
axe I'm still on quality one heading
toward the infestation
Quest I have quality
[Music]
5x quality five wow man you're a beaver
huh I am a beaver I can make iron tools
now too but I haven't touched the bench
you're the tool Master yeah for my
Beaver activities now you need to truly
RP and bite them with your teeth and
that's how you yeah yeah yeah just like
that ah
infection is everyone
infected not you mean you're going to
get infected yeah once I bite
them I'm sorry Kiara my luck is just so
bad I opened up the stumps but there was
nothing in it's
okay I anyway I think after a certain
percentage uh honey doesn't work work
anymore and then you need antibiotics as
well oh okay oh can we craft that well
maybe
someday maybe
someday so after
5% honey doesn't work anymore what oh oh
well then I kind of want to find honey
right now oh tree
stump I would like to find some honey
too
I found one a tree stump
please oh no my character's hungry and I
didn't bring any meat dang it got food
oh really oh Chef yes really thank
you oh no it does work it just removes
5% at a time I got honey I see Yay good
job gu also I have two Hammer magazines
for you crafting y you can take
thank you did you put it in like a box
or so no I'm just waiting for you at the
location oh yeah I'm coming now Quest
now that I have my honey I will
hurry decided to get rid of these
magazines oh my gosh us training
magazines is so fun yeah it's nice
everybody has like a different specialty
yeah that's why I kind of appreciate
that we're not like 20 people or so in
this collab because then I feel like I
would lose oversight of who needs one
and now we have such clear rolls and
it's really
comfy yeah I like this
group me too me too yeah usually I don't
play like a killer in games like the the
really physically strong ones so this is
new for me but I'm having fun I love
what do you normally do food cooking or
something like that yes thank you how
about some bacon and eggs Rando stuff oh
my gosh my chef a blueberry pie yes Chef
thank you Chef that sounds so good you
have a Band-Aid here have a Band-Aid
just in case I'm visualizing it right
now in my brain I'll take your
Band-Aids I'll take your Band-Aids off
your snake a snake there's a snake it's
just an angry zombie I'm going to punch
it I'm thirsty oh it is a snake let's
stab the
snake what is that chhat why why am I
laughing at my ligma
like M yeah like I have an icon that's
laughing at
the
radiation I guess because I'm laughing
because it's going
away yeah of course that's definitely
the only reason that it's it's laughing
okay it is a little
weird okay I'm kind of in the area now
what's Lima oh you're what is Lima stop
you all it's a very serious
illness that cannot be cured
normally how do you cure legma yeah how
do you kill you know it you know it gy I
don't think I
do
jobs who's that oh huh oh wait how do we
get huh Zoomers these days don't even
know like my balls I said it someone had
to say it Lima balls lima lima balls
almost worse than coblin D oh this time
it's you sacrificing yourself bi boo
thank you you're welcome bi boo do you
have any bandaids I do okay there's a
bird watch out je
whoa so right click for the
too that there roof I'm getting chased
by a
hog I help
don't wait stop
running I don't wanted to bite me where
are they you guys are down the road huh
yay Yum Yum Yum wait are you guys going
to infestation or bi boo
infestation we are any of them we are at
bioo infestation oh wait that's your
there an infestation of bi Boos yes yeah
bi boo infest of get infested
yeah we can this real quick and then
we'll do GG's okay and then I want to I
really want to go check on the Twins and
make sure that they're ready for the the
apocalypse so I'm going to go talk to
them after this we can we can also start
preparing uh the old house for yes we
need to prepare cuz tomorrow is the
chosen day The Chosen day the dawn of
the final day this is so
strong I'm looting a real quick okay
you're looting a pig yeah so much
meat okay you don't like that I'm
looting this Pig please don't Lo the
Pig please don't do my
best just get the meat just get the
meat I'll keep my thoughts to myself why
you thinking about the pig no no no
they're funny share
them thought thought you didn't want me
to
I only pretend like I don't want you to
it's really I speak in opposite speak
which is really annoying okay so you
want me to lose the P I love it oh yeah
I'll get your bone and meat you guys got
some water all right yes yeah I have
some water and some tea sorry I'm going
the wrong way just
water from the to is fine I don't want
to pay extra for water just give me tap
water thank you what does this look like
oh it's
chained all right you guys ready so
ready are you done looting the
pig yeah but now I'm lost I'm almost
there okay I think I'm almost there
you're here I'm here let's get started
yippe final
quest yippe kill them all
yipp we could break it or H we find an
open door a different
door ah dang it dang it they really
tried to board up this house huh a why
do they need us to clear out these
infestations because like no one's there
anymore what's the point the houses
don't have a yeah we want to make it
livable again oh maybe
aspirational ow did I oh gu we're
breaking down the door does the beer
want to break down a door oh I would
love to break down a door
we're so in oh they're in the way cash
there's actually still they're alive
they're here oh they're very much
alive and on
fire my hammer takes so much to
SC keep up the good work everyone help
help okay almost died you are you okay
oh no I'm not okay you have a Band-Aid
I'll try and lure them
outside I'll need a bandaid later here's
a bandaid oh thank
you best nice see we get work
done bio looks so funny with the hat and
the
beard zombies fear me right I'll oh
there's an AK machine gun oh I picked it
up get someone else I have
no it's bleeding it's you it's you it's
you it's you it's
me I just opened the door and you
stabbed me I didn't know ladies noty
leing
out okay you need a bandage instincts
take this forgive her I have thank you I
will use this bandage too empty here and
also yeah your health is low so use a
regular bandage too hold
up let me see I'm sorry I drew blood
from my friend thank you no problem
heal
yourself is someone up there oh people
okay me and F are up here I don't know
if there's any more bad guys
maybe the closed door is always a bad
sign still some more yeah probably okay
W I have ammo for you oh wow okay thank
you I'll get shooting
then no mercy oh there's there's an
upstairs o cat picture new cat cat I'm
not sure we've seen they love the cat
pictures uhoh I've seen that one orange
cat behavior oh maybe we did see
it it's a good cat yes every cat is good
cat there are no such things as demon
cats I agree
agreed they're all perfect angels yes we
are the ones that are out worthy of the
cats there's a hole hello where's the
last zombie
H probably down the hole come on
jumpy who's a good jumpie who's a good
jumpie yes you
are oh maybe it's down
no do you guys see an orange dot I do
see an orange dot I think oh it's
upstairs somewhere cuz it poed up second
floor ceiling
zomie oh no it's second floor second is
this second floor what yes is the dot
really going to a zombie it like
pointing
outside yeah that's a little strange
maybe the zombie is outside oh I think
it's a bird outside oh oh yeah on top of
the
other I didn't see a bird's nest oh
there's a bird
outo yay
y okay this Quest is complete complete
nice job ladies
a bit thirsty okay are we going to go
straight to the next Quest yeah uh yeah
it's right below
us okay below I'll follow you also is it
possible for uh Kiara to repair my bat
at a workbench possibly uh I think with
a repair I you just need your repair kit
mhm okay just do and you can do let me
let me give it give you one try oh you
have a repair kit bi boo thank you
appreciate it
prepared okay and I used it at a
workbench right no no you just
unequipped your weapon and this to be op
to repair it repair I see thank you bi
you're Lifesaver yeah thank you so
much nice that's huge uh which Quest are
we going to uh T it's over here tier two
infestation gigy yeah yeah it's just
down the road
on my almost
there I'm almost there too I'm getting
wood no she
loves in case we need it
yeah
there serious wood addiction a this
bat's so
cool I'm I'm I'm there a tree house how
sweet not when I'm done with it
she's of the
children you're going to watch me do
this dismantle it you're going to watch
me do
this I like this treeh
house you actually hurt me at
the oh look at that oh you try again God
is gracious do it again do it again do
it again you kidding me how many times
do you need to F The Treehouse to be
satisfied Gigi they cannot have a
treehouse not when I'm around not when
the beaver no
no the children can't believe you're
doing this in front of fa messed up oh
it gets so messy around 7,000 okay
there's a lot coming uh there's a lot
coming watch out are they
mad they me I'm shooting me I'm
sorry I was I wanted to help oh crazy
melee is
suffering it is feel that I've got N9 HP
no all
right I can blow on it and kiss it I I
have two thank
you oh my god blowing on it does that
help it should it should thank you I
hear it helps helps me kind of house is
this what are they doing in
here what have I done they are super
angry I've lost
myself not the same person anymore this
zombie stuff is getting to
me I'm becoming one of them it's okay I
beat FAA earlier too I why would you
beat your wife I didn't know to I just
lost myself I found a couple there a lot
of punching bag take the shotgun ammo
there's there's a ton of bi boo ammo and
Kiara ammo in this infested catch that's
yellow up here thank you shotgun M oh
God he's
big why did I miss so hard there's also
a really
good shotgun shells I'll take them
you GG do you also use a shotgun oh my
God though okay it's so noisy it
is okay I'll make sure they
it
oh what a big
family a pipe machine gun yes where's be
there's there's a ton of 9 mm ammo in
this yellow crate up here I'm upstairs
I'll come down
after you know I'll grab it for
you there's a lot of there's a lot of
things in the house right now I'm kind
of occupied get into the house I I broke
the
door Ah that's the best way are getting
more
intricate oh yeah what is this for are
they protecting themselves from US ah
couldn't be the floor is they the family
that turned into zombies
wow the heck is going on I want to get
rid of this oh oh oh are you guys
destroying more
floors no no I'm not trying to it's
doing it on its own really is there an
upstairs
okay I was thinking is there an upstairs
it must be we're not done yet
does anybody have any dirty water I can
drink leg I have noral water dirty
water I'll dirty water I checked the
toilet
already okay outside the
[Music]
house here some dirty water upstairs
thank you leg H you have to be able to
get upstairs maybe yeah where's the last
maybe it's a bird again if I want to get
somewhere I'm going to get there so I'm
going to make a little make shift
stairwell mhm outside and
good did you grab all the ammo where was
the ammo did you
say I am holding on to it now
okay I don't see an orange dot
anywhere where at the zombie
behind ah
why am I picking up so many
things let's eat okay I am on the second
floor if you want to join me I made a
little stairwell out oh here here you
are sir ah I see I
see oh wow he's quick and he's on
fire that zombie is on
fire oh is this a
[Laughter]
finally be useful I can't jump that high
I took I'll let you girls check it out
we can here like a whole lot of dudes
and they're very strong oh really so
many yeah send them down them down we
did oh that was it huh good job team
yeah yay more more more more more Quest
more Quest here are you guys' ammo by
the way and Kiara thank you you guys
want a ton of ammo a butt ton I got a
butt ton this is for bi boo okay
and this is for Kiara where is she where
is this beautiful pink-haired woman Oh
you mean pinkhair pink mustache
lad are you on the roof still not not
there oh oh oh are you down there Kiara
yeah all right I'll bring it to you if
you're down if you're on the bottom
floor I'm down for it yes so I guess the
only way to get up here is by making a
stairwell outside now leave it to
me y all right let's
see where was Kia you destroying the car
yeah what for do we get parts or
something yeah here you go to KCK
Cham that's for you thank you a lot of
bullets ammo I'm swimming in
ammo all right I need to make a new axe
new stone
axe
wow and just satisfying oh we don't get
to pick it up a no I have an armor book
for
you I take I
take I have a cooking book for you nice
exchange thank you thank
[Music]
you pumpkin cheesec
cake
cake the world is
saved let's go I'm so happy
cheesecake will be our savior anybody
find any baseball magazines I do no I
have seed and
medical okay well if you find a baseball
one you know who to
call who
Ghostbusters you no
Ghostbusters hey o Raiden the cafe I
think somebody's been here
does well let's see what time is it um
why so broken we can go back to the tra
and then yeah we got to turn in this
quest after preparing for the thing
maybe there's a safe in here already oh
I have lock PS maybe we can get another
Quest when we turn it in yes more quests
more
quests okay oh I'm in the wrong house
okay I'm coming
come to me there's a
safe I do feel
safe what do you mean ask for the AK-47
does somebody have an AK-47 I do yeah I
was going to give it as a present here
waa here's a it's a AK47 machine gun
where did you get that found it in box
o thank you cuz mine was just about to
break my my shitty machine gun oh allall
enjoy yippee brother you're in the
middle of day 20 upstairs or downstairs
it's down
okay I just want to get the
T I am going to turn in a quest where
are you I'm in the basement I thought
you went downstairs base but no no it's
wrong house H you're in the wrong
house come to me
I'm coming I'm just a little
[Music]
silly make sure they got their weapons
and
such are you two just riding houses over
there still there's a safe I did ask
them what they want to okay uh special
they said
shotguns everybody wants to use shot I
why are you doing this on
purpose look at your I would like to
have my back
okay I'm here a little embarrassed but I
here be right back you guys I got to run
I got to run real quick I'll be right
back
okay ready to
go
um Barrel extender
mod
nice okay okay it is unlocked you can
take a look
okay there's a wooden
bow a singular wooden bow it's so worth
it what is this reward well it's not a
primitive bow at least I have a lot of
books for you
kiawa cool thank
you I will take a look at
it what why do I use rewards I don't
need any of this
[Music]
are you serious
now are you
serious I'll just take the ammo for
other
people okay
um oh I was hoping you could run over
zombies yeah it's I think you can but
only the car
not with bicycles were you trying it
with bicycles yeah yeah that that won't
work unless you have spikes on your
bicycle or so now that's an
idea oh yeah can we like tie a spear to
the bicycle so it's like
pointed just very
[Music]
creative it said gg gg yes I have
something for you I don't know if it's
good for you or
not I am waiting with anticipation
here a beautiful
bow here maybe it's so beautiful maybe
You' like this because you are obsessed
with trees as
well oh wow look at that southern
farming there's the difference
yeah oh well what a beautiful be thank
thank you for the seed magazine in the
you're welome you're welome please
please read it somewhere
private I will read it in front of
you fun are you Village Place oh you're
coming here I have
magazine thank you I just got a
notification that Cece's playing Seven
Days to Die oh she said she was too
drunk she
so did she sober up
just for the zombie horde I
guess maybe she can have the real
drunken fist
yeah ah there you are yeah they didn't
have any good Quest rewards so I just
took a magazine for you thank you I knew
you had it in you also who uses 9mm
again I do oh I have I took a lot of 9
mm ammo to give to others as
well wait where is bi boo I'm by the
booby lady
the booby lady
okay that could be any of us almost the
quest booby
lady here I dropped 9 mm ammo on the
floor what oh thank you
yeah rare zombies like policeman oh damn
I should have chosen that Quest
huh when is the we still have time until
the race let's do this
I'm here we should do Quest oh here's
assault rifle crafting for you oh thank
you you the
best the rest conratulations I can make
my pay to
the yay oh you have unlocked machine
guns AK-47 machine gun Quality 4
yo if only I had machine gun parts what
the nail gun do we need a nail gun for
things I don't know wait bio have you
read nightstalker volume 3 um I've been
reading nightstalker different
volumes have you read three already
which one is
three uh bladed weapons do 10% more
damage at nine I think I have
[Music]
okay reloading is so slow I'm going to
take that skill kiss you my leg Yeah my
leg why is it broken again or still what
happened oh do you need a
splint h i mean it's just two minutes I
I I'll just
wait people you should get the nail gun
it's the best building upgrade tool oh I
did I did get a nail gun or a jump okay
ladies I'm going to go help out the
twins but feel free to continue your
journey okay
okay all right I'll see you later see
see you
byee we do more level two Quest right
over here we do the heavy stuff okay
let's um wait do you like all of
these
yeah reading for
you are you doing medicine rewards I am
we oh thank
you that's a lot I'm going to get really
smart yeah become the smartest there
ever was how full is your inventory F
it's pretty full
okay all right I'm ready to move okay
are we going to the the the bunch
there's a bunch actually
by a gigy is already at one right yeah
okay we
go see how honey can I ride a bicycle is
that okay when I'm have I have a broken
leg it
acceptable I hope so where are we
going just don't Sprint okay if you
don't use shift okay I'll be careful
Sprint no it's 37 seconds oh okay soon I
will be healed which
way over there
wait where are we going uh back to where
we came from I guess giggy's already
there
no I am hungry and thirsty let me bring
you stuff
yay
okay 9 8 7 6 5 what are we counting down
for B going
toy no de happy birthday happy
anniversary happy 2025 everyone thank
indeed happy birthday happy New Year
happy Christmas Happy
Everything no my photo of a family do
you think this is a de family or a stock
photo
family stock photo I thought you said
dead family not dead
family family it could be both it could
be dead and a St family stock photo
family that's true if it's taken long
ago that would be sad it would be
sad but in a way they will live on in
Theo in this G someone makes an
advertisement and purchases the rights
to use their photo yeah wait I'm here
which Quest are we doing first the gy
one okay I don't know yeah I'm at the
house okay look at the with me all of
these quests okay I'm coming you know
that's a that's a great idea when I move
I'm going to just put a bunch of stock
photo family pictures around my place so
that way when someone robs me they think
there's more people living in the house
and just me they perfect idea I don't
know if that works because if nobody's
home somebody's got to be home for that
to work
go after the after the eggs and bacon
yeah does someone have um
food uh or we running out oh you we're
running
low it's not the best food but oh no
corn is the
best oh I can cook it
uptime
okay did you know corn is so
nutritiously bad that the corn we use
today is chemically altered and
processed to make it nutritional before
we eat
it
yummer I love
superfood oh we have the gun okay I'm
here let's go with new gun I'll open
itome oh oh thank you that amazing do
you see the family right here that not
that family not that
one something's on me oh there is
something on
you don't jump on me don't jump on
me
no ah a
concussion have you guys ever had a
concussion that's kind of crazy feels
weird
C makes your screen kind of blurry for a
moment but I'm good family wait 1 hour
minutes
bro I almost punched be
boo it's okay I probably deserve it
no here's armor crafting thanks
frame while you guys are fighting for
foro frame pretty which family do you
think that is a typical
American family so you a stock
photo
yes don't think it's one of the devs
no hopefully
not hope that
oh what is this zombie
doing yeah I saw the C message do we
need armor parts I mean generally um
eventually
hello oh if we have
oh people no people you're going to get
hit from the side careful my
[Music]
hero oh did I hit you with the shot no
I'm
good
okay
me meow
[Music]
toilet
water and with your hat you can drink
that too or yeah I
can what do we have wiring a somebody
wanted electrical crafting
right somebody I saw it like in the
Discord ity was Cali
ohon's online oh and is
online everyone's ready for the hord
Now where's the last zombie I I think
outside because someone crawling
there
crawling upstairs
upstairs another
upstairs there's a there's there's a
there's a there's a rope R Gun a rope a
rope how to get up are you f are you
okay I think I'm okay is no I'm not okay
actually I'm oh I see the Rope okay I
see I see I see I see
there's yellow
eyes aim do what's that growling noise
is that your
gun watch out watch out
okay it's really scary oh oh the dog oh
a dog ah it's biting me okay we're fine
we're fine it's cleared it's that was
crazy damn they hid the dog in the Attic
huh good place for pet wasn't there a
dog house outside that would have been a
nicer place to keep him the
foreshadowing mhm yeah guess so I think
every house that has a dog house might
have a dog Enemy
Inside take care take
caution
ooh shipping
crate o Thomas
Harris William
Dillinger John Smith AKA to Fresh
there's some wanted people with
some realistic
looking pictures as if they took them
from
Facebook yeah right Facebook did they
take them from well they're own
Facebook those really look like they
could be from
devs yeah oh you looked at them too mhm
it's the working Theory
uh well if I was developing a game I
would want to be included somewhere too
I have bu for
[Music]
you hey thank you does anybody here
read
books I love reading no I'm a literate
wait I need to look uh do I use
this maybe I do I'm at the next Quest
does anybody have food outside of stinky
sandwiches no maybe we should go home
we're all full I'll eat the stiny
sandwich potato wait wait wait eat this
potato it's only one yay it's better
than the stinky
sandwiches how to get out of
[Music]
here without hurting
myself ah there yeah I'm so full I'm so
cucumber
yeah and hungry and thirsty oh very oh
my God I'm so thirsty uhoh maybe I
should drink my Yuka juice okay I'm
going to see if I can make it to the
trader in time before she closes oh yeah
okay let do that when did she close
though nine
in an hour I'll make
it let's go zoom zoom zoom let's go and
then we are speed I don't know should we
still do more quests after that or
H um I guess it's not tonight the zombie
ra tomorrow night the 21 we can do them
and turn them in in the morning and then
get ready for the is it good hoorde
fully
um do you need a bandaid your health is
um I might but let's let's go to the
Traer first so we can get before it
closes
okay I'll survive for now do we want to
go home once to unload or do we just
want to keep on going I don't know maybe
we should try to do more quests if we if
we can cuz we're going to have to go
home for the raid
yeah find some food and live I still
also have one more quest in that
area let's clear
it
ooh wait where am I going is this the
right
place oh
yeah oh yeah I have a oh yeah we have a
few uh quests still okay me too me
too well aren't you a sight for S well
that didn't take long man stamina why
always so
low
ammo pipe bomb also sounds
fun need some relief Trader Jen's got
what you need your health my
[Music]
priority doesn't really have any
what what wait
what she doesn't want to show me her
yeah she doesn't want to show me her
stuff either sorry it's cuz I'm working
oh is it like one at a time I thought
you can only do one at a time I thought
it was I thought it
wasn't it
before okay lady you can try now it's
just realistic I
guess yeah works
[Music]
now sorry
her I don't know what do I even
want does she
[Music]
have does she
again well I'll sell some stuff m
what can I
sell
uh
egg it sucks that certain things you can
only sell in a specific amount of
stacks so if you don't have the exact
amount of that stack you you can't get
rid of it oh that is that is
weird oh the traps electrical traps you
need a lot to build
[Music]
anything electrical traps you want to
make electrical traps yeah I don't think
anyone else was reading it or collecting
it so I started reading some but okay
but you need
25 to build
anything I you're the one who wanted
wiring electrical yeah I got one for you
no one else was reading it but I guess I
can start specking into it well cuz I
don't think anyone else is doing here
take it take it thank
you are you
moving no okay I thought my game was
like dying okay thank
you oh wait I have ammo for you of
course you do you always have ammo for
me how much do you have in harvesting
tools I think GG is learning that oh
yeah I have harvesting tools how much do
you have um I have let me
see well okay
then where did I put it where is it I
have 18 into harvesting tools o I'll
give you one then when I see you are you
already heading back here's your dirty
water I know how much you love it the
quest area I love my dirty water I'm
going to drink this right now yeah
[Music]
I eat this old
sandwich I'm going to eat the old
sandwich please uhoh don't hurt
me scared
me if you're still inside while she
closes does it kick you out yeah it
kicks you out
oh
okay where's my bike
a what do you mean on thirsty I just
drank three cups of water
waa this house do you guys want to see
pictures come here there's so many cute
pictures oh inside is she going to
close there's like there's dog she has
dog pictures and bird pictures and what
she's selling machine gun wait are you
still in there can you buy machine gun
parts before she closes is she Clos I'll
try I don't know I'm going to make it oh
no
she she Clos 10 minutes early what the
heck why would she do
that I can't find my bicycle has anyone
seen a bicycle lying around uh there's a
there's a bicycle icon if you look
around to to your bicycle oh found it
okay okay I'm going to for a bad review
cling
ear okay but good to know she has
machine gun parts I'll go get them later
um so let's go back can make some quests
even though we're all kind of thirsty
and hungry and cucumbers think we'll be
fine'll surv right yeah we have no do we
not not have any more food at all on any
of us I have one
sandwich some raw corn and potato M raw
corn surely in the house there'll be
food yeah maybe we'll get lucky and find
something she restocks tonight so they
might not be D no
but it's okay for right now I I have a a
better gun than before uh like five
minutes ago
so oh it's not too bad we already got an
upgrade maybe for the next H
night we get him next time I'm not
coping it's it's the
reality yeah Calli gave me the
AK 4070 whatever we're doing this one
AK47 the bio one
[Music]
coming w a tree has been F who did that
by who I wonder I just don't
know okay which one are we doing um I
guess we'll do this one this
one this is fetch
clear Okay we okay stuff this is an oat
Farm there should be food um magazine
here
yummy oh so you have to do you have to
clear and find supplies I see no problem
we're multitasking easy oh oh sham
sandwich please don't give me diarrhea
please don't give me
diarrhea it didn't give me
diarrhea the diarrhea gotcha
Still
Standing I thought they were dead this
guy's
strong
oh oh they were hiding medical supplies
here
what found a medical journal who learned
learned it again I learn it good okay
well they have lots of medical journals
and I found food already like a sham
sandwich and PE
pears
[Music]
wonderful oh I feel like they hide the
CER Satchel so well I got to look
everywhere oh yeah I forgot F
that mine was hidden inside a wall ouch
where am I are you going upstairs yes
I'm on
fire oh
no that's not good run really fast run
really really fast and then make it go
out like that I brought more
owie I once I once uh made a kitchen go
out in my k a fire go out in my kitchen
by just blowing really strong believe
you I totally did I remember a fire in
your kitchen was it the same one yeah
yeah I think pretty
sure fire run run run run run
run it works I'm so
hot blow really
hard has it anybody found their supplies
yet I found mine cool still looking for
mine if there's a down arrow does that
mean
down oh I should look at that too
yeah or does it just always have a down
arrow oh no I don't trust it oh I think
it does have a down arrow armor crafting
in
here please pick it up I'm somewhere
else I think or wait I'm here where you
are now iCal crafting in here ooh where
upstair oh it's a scary zombie he's
spinning oh he kind of hurts I'm I'm
[Music]
scared help
huh help
help oh help I'm coming my
are you coming you're standing there I'm
standing here but I'll be
there why you looking at that leev trunk
so long run keep running keep running
keep running I have so much random
garbage in my inventory okay it's dead
are you putting it in thank you I'm
dropping them maybe I should drop my
2,000
wood I dropped 2,000 wood if anyone
would like 2,000
wood where's you had a
book medicine there's a medical book up
there I'm not sure if someone Pi I I I
picked it up for you I have two now
okay still need to find my Satchel me
too it's really R is what is
it oh oh that's the normal way to get
[Music]
there uh I don't like hiding here
oh oh the
fire
dodged where are these
Satchel they might be in the
walls um no use your
radar I found mine in a
wall okay I mean that's kind of
sus I got it do you want a dirtty water
FAA yeah
dirty water thank
[Music]
you maybe downstairs yummy maybe here
wait is there a medical book somewhere
did you say I got two I got two oh oh I
found my Satchel
yippe
yipp everyone find their
thingy yeah
okay yeah
shall we go to the next Quest oh yeah I
am here oh do we have the same Quest
over there there's two people who have a
quest there I
think is it the same oh the day reset I
had the quest limit but now 21 we're
being so
efficient wait I'm almost there almost
there and let me give you the medical
journal so I have it off of my hands t
thank
you let's
go get my gun out what is this clearing
okay fists
out
oo zombies where are you everybody oh
there's one watch out for the fire oh is
they're on fire it's digging a
hole die
he's back
up get down he so
strong it
hurt
okay watch out watch out I forgot my
bike oh I'll pick it up when we're done
with this Quest run run run if you're
burning just run I walked right into it
my depth
perception can we walk under it no we
can't no we can't a wait I'm going to
burn to death I'm going to burn to death
I'm
dead
eliminated oh no don't play with fire
girls when you're on
HP Fire H fire ow cannot blow on it too
a oh my god wow whatever I will break
this
wall okay I'm really dehydrated
H we could go to a
pond why
how I know
why huh oh there's a button go around
it why does it s us on
fire I don't don't touch it anymore oh
hey it
open oh go around there ah help help
zombies
where out
[Music]
outside watch
out they're still
alive K you use arrows right I have some
arrows yeah I use arrows I'll give you
in the moment oh in the window oh my God
oh my God there ow ow did you get shot
here let me give you I don't
know doesn't matter what kind of arrows
you use any I use them all
okay oh I feel like I shouldn't be here
I feel like I shouldn't be here by
myself where did you go oh upstairs okay
let's go careful coming
down almost
again ah teamwork so Tity oh I
leveled oh there more zombies oh there's
definitely more up here I
believe
oh oh yeah
[Music]
hello oh he's so
green is this the effective
Quest if they're
green what that wow he's glowing ah he's
glowing whoa oh this is
new
oops o what's going on here
what where where where you have to do
some you have to do some Parkour but
there's
a there's some around you can there's
another floor
upstairs
uhhuh what is
this what is this
chamber
what secret tank
this is all a little scary yeah watch
your
step
ow zombie
bird but I do see a zombie there he
wants to be uh
released can I shoot
[Music]
for I think we have to do something
about
him eh
oh there's
a another
level there's one like behind the locked
door in the middle
level I don't want
to oh
my
scary
y okay
the roof zombies are dead oh not quite
the roof roof but there's like several
roofs there's another level
upward this place is gigantic yeah oh
there's a roof roof I'll try to get up
there hello down
there okay I'll try to do something
about the door
but yeah it's still there can you not
just open the door from there Z why do I
have to do
it I wonder if there's a key for this
place oh
go oh my gosh oh this oh help help help
help oh okay well this
works are you up there yeah they're on
the roof roof there's a I'm
[Music]
coming I've got no stamina
so many
uhoh yeah after this Quest maybe I'm
done for we're done
yay wa I want to explore over there and
still need to open one more door to
Tactical Warfare uh yeah I think I do I
do is that the assault rifle one oh
don't know yes it is okay that's mine I
have one for it shall be mine wait I'm I
need to break this door otherwise I'm
not
satisfied
ooh anyone's hungry I got Cal
food can I use your hat to drink water
yes is there a water source out there I
found murky water oh and here you
go I have another quest in the exact
same location but we don't have to do it
now
as this one yeah the same house I think
there's a cool down yeah yeah oh
okay my
bicycle I don't
know where anyone super
starving uh getting there and I have an
old
sandwich I'm mer water you could drink
the the water in combination of the Hat
might work yeah
yeah I just I can't find you
girls there's uh there's some stairs but
you have to parkour for
it now they're all the way up there
oh we got to check these there's books
in here where newspaper dispens
ERS of them there's books in every
single one of
them except that
one oh I found like six books got to
take a look at them where where is every
cat
food actually I might need to eat the
cat food I'm going to eat the sandwich
you'd rather eat the sandwich that gives
you poooo I have I have good stomach I
see strong stomach
are you in the
house I'm trying to leave H I'll look
for my
bicycle
bicycle and let's
[Music]
see
um I went in a tank
400 a.m. Traer open
yay can give back Quest
now first find bicycle I think I think I
found your
bicycle do coyotes attack people um the
dog they meat
yes but it looks so nice
oh it was so cute and pretty
oh I'm
bleeding damn hit you right in the eye
huh my
eye sorry you have any of those
bandies I don't have any I have a
regular bandage it'll stop your bleeding
inde my bleeding stopped I'm just dying
oh
no maybe Trader Jen can help
you are you still lost in the building I
finally made
it okay I'm going to the trader giving
back my coins
[Music]
and I got a couple of books but there I
don't know if anybody wants these I'll
put them in the book chest at home
later
okay boom see if she has gun PS yes very
important of utmost
importance then I can already make a
level four gun
right come
on I feel like I'm not learning these
roads at all
I'm we're still new here it's okay map
Reading is an important
skill I wish I could drink this rain I
Wasing the same thing Lally opened my
mouth and looked up the moment you said
that why can't we put like buckets down
and stuff I know we have a du collector
yeah yeah but we could we should just be
able to you know have buckets or like
use our hat it's
true I learned the crazy trick if you're
ever um on a deserted island uh what you
can do um to filter water uh you you
take some you you try to find some
container maybe nowadays you know with
how dirty the ocean is you can probably
find a plastic bottle somewhere up the
shore take the plastic bottle cut it in
half uh take some um
uh water ocean
water place it in the sand and then the
second half of the cut plastic bottle
you fold it uh on the bottom it will
make some kind of like catchy container
and then you put it on top of it's hard
to explain but but but but over time
this will filter the the sea uh water
the the salt out of it and then you get
clean water only a few drops per day but
if you get a lot of these you can have a
lot of water eventually
survival skills
babyes filtration camping I want to
drink that water hope we don't need to
use this when we're camping but I will I
will if if if we get dessert one day
we'll remember this just for
[Music]
fun yeah I'll take this oh did you guys
get the next Trader Trader
bombie oh yes I did get Trader bomb I
would love to give you you can always
quit a
wait does that mean she didn't give us
anything special she didn't give us a
motorcycle she gave a nail gun right oh
yeah she gave me mini bark mini bark
mini bike
parts oh that's a motorcycle bike
no yes I think so kiaha I have stuff for
you thank you thank you thank you I
wonder anybody is investing into
explosives crafting does anybody know I
kind of want to I like
explosives I have I have some Molotov
and pipe bombs okay I'll start I'll
start learning explosives then yeah
yeah
then mining tools is anybody fighting
with mining
tools I have the art of mining Volume
7 don't know who to give to just
[Music]
two well I'll just put these into the
chest I can't think right now maybe
G which one mining yeah mining
okay um what was I looking for machine
gun parts
yes bye bye all of
them okay what magazines they have
explosive s farming I
see I like I've never seen you with your
hat
off I have cool glasses now yeah you
do I don't know it's kind of giving
scary Vibes though the you don't like
how I
look my glasses I don't know I'm just
getting scary vibes
what kind of Vibes maybe it's the angle
what about this from the profile view
from the
profile
maybe just little the the mustache and
the bald head and the
[Music]
glasses well my bartering is plus 2%
with these so maybe it's threatening 2%
that's going to do a big
difference we all start small got to
start
somewhere you got to start from the
bottom now we from the bottom now we
here are we going back or like home yeah
it's it's the
21st it's almost time we must probably
go home bike bike wait did I ever find
my
bike
where all right then
it was uh a fine time questing with you
ladies it seems I'm not ready for tier
three yet though so maybe soon
but I do have one more Quest over there
maybe after the
raid
oh all of the girls are currently at our
new home are there by any chance trying
to fortify our new home I wonder well
let's go find out let's go
yeah she had automatic magazines
what I didn't see them I'm
blind I'll check it out before I
go just me the open road and 10,000
zombies this is just like mad ma what a
life witness
me this one you mean for the first time
and I didn't think I would be into it
because like I don't know I don't
usually watch stuff like that but it was
so good was it yes just like seven days
to die I I started watching I fell
asleep I fell asleep so much is
happening yeah it's like the most action
packed movie like everything is
happening maybe I was really tired that
day I don't
know maybe why am I going the wrong
way how much does she pay
for8 it seems like my type of movie
though so maybe I'll give it a second
chance it's it's fun it's a fun movie it
is
fun the world is cool
and
bald and bald cool and
[Music]
bald she sells it's so much more
expensive I sell her something and she
she you can't even eat the raw
corn or wait is it just cuz I'm on the
bike yeah I think so you can normally
eat it I'm pretty sure I have to eat the
raw corn cuz I'm starving
in no flana it doesn't have any
nutritional
value super corn I have no choice I
can't guys I can't buy
it wait is this a shortcut this
road this curving
Road let's find out I think it is goes
right
[Music]
home I want to at
home could we have a Lakeside date so I
can drink your water yes I also use
water wait I want to go where you girls
are oh yes I would like a sip too just
in case so we don't waste
resources true but you're so
far just catch up to us whenever you
whenever you're ready I'm going to the
lake to the north I feel like that's the
best water source for good sip
sip I also have tons of meat and five
eggs for you to cook oh
good me too I got some meat as well meat
too meat meat too me
too nice to meet you nice to meet you
too thank
you as we are all made of meat and Flesh
and Bones may be nice to meet you isn't
so far
off we don't have to resort to
cannibalism just yet I know we're all
starving but but you look so yummy F no
you're
[Music]
F people always tell me I look tasty
they say I look like fried chicken to
them in their eyes
they're just
projecting yes they are they're the
tasty
ones they are you hear that kfp
okay here you
go she's running into the lake
wait did you get like being used I got
it okay okay I got so
[Laughter]
scared it's the most PR precious hat of
all time I'm trying to find oh here we
go
go yeah your hat has been passed around
so much at this point everybody's
wearing it you're probably getting lice
no none of us have lies I have no hair
on my head there is no way will not
touch anyone for having
lies I have PTSD from lies so no
judgment I
have drink a gallon of Lake water I am
ready to stop drinking ooh tummy
egg maybe by the time you're all done
drinking I'll be there almost there yeah
yeah yeah go go go
go I mean sip sip sip
sip but I'm really
chilling you are really drinking it
all oh it's so tasty
almost there almost there almost there o
day 21 it says right I think I drank
enough to give myself
water a and this is only our second okay
I don't want to roll down the hill night
okay here you go oh I'm I'm I'm I'm
almost there I'm almost there I'm
literally there I see you I see
you fauna awaiting me I'm waiting
it's like you have to babysit people for
drinking like it's a dangerous thing or
something it's very dangerous don't
overd drink
water ah there it is thank
you I wonder if we can make more of the
water purifier where did you get it did
you find it I just found it I don't even
remember where I found it maybe maybe
they'll sell the mod for it cuz like the
rotate their mods and stuff so maybe
hope we got to learn the schematic for
it
yeah okay do you think that's
enough I think if it's at 90 it's enough
90 oh
okay there you go thank you so much
let's go home I miss home I hope I hope
it doesn't look too
different never know what to expect
after a long
outing I know suddenly there might be
five rows of spikes in front of our home
or more trees more trees yeah but the
trees would be probably there for a
different reason for giggy's addiction
oh gosh what did you I have to plant
more
trees trees are natural defense right
yeah a little bit but we also won't be
able to see clearly anymore okay I only
see spikes good good question mark is it
good it's been a long time we're finally
home let's alloy
Queen wait alloy cream is already the ah
finished thing okay potato seed oh I
hear I hear
[Music]
something they inside I think they're in
on the back of our house or so
oh knocking on our door what would you
want we don't buy anything we don't want
to buy anything please go away
okay all right all right they're getting
a little bit too
rowdy oh yeah they're knocking on our
back door I didn't know we had a back
door oh she dropped some
loot what did they
drop oh night vision mod see in the dark
of this high-tech night vision head
armor
mod and oh weighted head mod schematic
interesting knives and
machetes oh I can use that I have knives
and
machetes uh wait what does this say
knives and machetes do not have a head
that can be weighted oh I don't think
you can use this yeah never mind uh but
it's for all melee weapons except knives
and machetes
well I'll put
it maybe in
here should I make my new gun now
chat or it's the time right yeah but I
just got the
AK-47 if you got the
materials
H I don't want to replace already
but maybe maybe I should I think we
might have to just make grilled
meat instead that's fine yeah that's
okay cuz if we don't have enough eggs
carnivore diet I guess yeah it
[Music]
is things just disappear when I click
that button
I wonder where they
go ooh vehicle
crafting do I have to keep the crafting
window open to
craft no I don't think so it goes
passively oh okay
cool I think I'm learning that um
potassium nitrate where to put that
making gun
powder
spicy ah do they H nerd hat nerd hat uh
okay okay okay okay did they were they
going to give me anything uh like armor
kits for
it wait let me go down to the
SE what do you need to make duct
tape uh glue glue
[Music]
and quick faster faster cloth cloth
fragment I totally knew
that
oh I
need take some of this
stuff in
here W oh she left she went to their
thing to ask her something I think you
should just just take it yeah yeah yeah
it's for everybody can I wait it might
not that might be for full
m oh that might be their nerd hat
ingredients how do you make Forge
iron clay and
iron yeah you need to put them in a
smelter I have some smelting right
now can I have some how many do you
need um the of
okay almost
done here's
12 thank you right here
tape how do you make the nerd hat um you
need for level three you need three
armor
fragments and then leather I
believe uh and something El do you need
the armor crafting kits oh yeah you need
three armor crafting kits and leather
for level three uh it depends cuz you
can make like level one level two level
three so the amount of armor crafting
kits is correlated to the level so if
you want three then you need three
I'm getting lost in the crafting
sauce crafting
sauce what does it taste like
tastes like leather and
metal oh there's a there's an armor part
up here if you want it I don't know I
have a few
okay but thank you let
take o
oh grilled meat only gives 10
Health I'll try and find some eggs thank
you wish we could like have a chicken
farm I know maybe you can
though supply
drop o
oh how far is
that
oh oh it's pretty far down south I'm
going oh yeah it is good luck good luck
I'll find some eggs on the way thank you
please thank you
I need
iron I found a pig a pig kill
it 30 more meat take his eggs yeah his
egg I'm putting him open to take his
[Music]
eggs get right you want to cut right
into the underbelly right here that's
where it opens up into his egg egg
sack it's egg
sack it's just like a
fish yeah they never specified the type
of eggs we can have sa cavard that
sounds fancy that sounds too
fancy we have to it's our
only little remnant of civilization in
the C
y maybe we can build a casino
oo yeah gambling
gambling did you have any more duct tape
T anywhere no I can make two more you
can uh cook bones or maybe I can cook
bones to make glue I like
that's
awesome how much duct tape do you need I
need
five duct
tape okay I
have
some how much how many bones become glue
I think one bone but you need
water a the expensive
part do we have any
iron oh maybe I think I put them all on
the it's in all in the Forge right now
it's melted okay can I use some yeah
okay thank you
the nerd armor is heavy armor it's heavy
armor appar
taxing
yeah so I need three armor crafting kits
leather and that's it oh that's it okay
you need like at least 10 leather
though okay I
have what the hell I just ran over a
mine oh yeah they're
mes land
mine are you okay I'm
okay just
scared I'm at a public school right now
oh that's the most terrifying place ever
yeah it's really scary
here
um I have two duck
tape I'll take it
um what there's just medical journals in
here use
that I'm going
to oh I need water for bow or for glue
that
sucks yeah that's what makes it hard
there's mutated zombies here uhoh be
careful oh no be
careful I'm taking everything and I'm
leaving I don't want to be here anymore
good
luck I'm bringing I'm bringing a bird
with me back
home I think we have plants
outside but I'm not a farmer so I don't
know if I should Harvest them
when I don't think our Farmers online
yeah maybe it's okay to harvest the pl
yeah as long as you plant them again it
should be okay
yeah I'm getting some stuff
I'm just so
hungry so hungry all the time we
need I do I have two egg and one bird
following me that is to say
oh help can you kill it where are you
where are you outside the house oh I got
it I got you I got you okay dead
iy time to find out what I
got did you get the supply drop yeah I
got a four time scope and a bunch
of other mods I can use the four time
scope if you're not using put in the gun
chest okay
and all the other parts I
found I think I could use okay it's in
there I wonder does this work with a
handgun no it doesn't ah I guess not
[Music]
corn I'm I'm the farmer now I'm just not
very good at it you're learning just
like how you learned how to mend
everyone's wounds now you're learning
how to
farm renaissance man
ow what fine What's
happen KY just smacked
me uh-oh
sham
chowder Cham chowder you make that bio
Cham chowder I did not sham CH who made
sham
chowder Tam chowder
oops I'm punching we just beating each
other in here it's chaos it's day 21
chaos it hurts it
[Music]
hurts
umum I need a little bit
more a pumpkin trees Che
cake I need beer
beer oh no my alcohol problem wait you
need you need beer to pumpkin cheesecake
yeah wow oh no I used our last eggs
though to make eggs in bacon I put two
eggs in here I used them to make eggs in
b no no there's two new eggs oh there's
two new eggs two new eggs
oh thank
you I could make can I even make
beer I don't know if I know how to make
beer you have to learn so much in the
apocalypse I know I thought we were just
becoming a chef you have to make beer
too I'm going to make two pumpkin
pies and
that's it I
guess did anyone take the Bunches of
cloth fragments in
the test oh I have cloth
fragments here go thank you oh that's a
lot oh here's duct tape too oh thank
you one two three
oh I can modify my
knuckles I don't know what I can put in
there though more Knuckles a stack of
them more Knuckles knuckle SE more more
spikes put a sandwich in
there give them the good old classic
knuckle sandwich sham sandwich
[Music]
I don't know if these modifiers work
that's all right a silencer on my
Knuckles on your
knuckles wait is it almost time do we
need to leave do we need to go to the
other house uh I mean everybody's still
here so I think we have a little bit of
I think it's like at night time like 10
p.m. I believe yeah but it's already 4:
and it takes a while to walk over
there I don't know oh is it cuz my time
my silly timer ran out my fake timer on
my stream
hold on can I restart my
timer wait I have to click it like 100
times P yes hello hello I'll make it for
you but I need to wait for a little bit
more iron um oh do you need more iron
yeah I'm forging it right now I'm also
needing a lot of iron for myself too I
need one I need like five I need seven
more iron for myself as well oh okay a
lot of iron a workbench can you make is
it expensive to make another one uh I'll
check but the the iron is being made in
the Forge that's separate oh
um but wait
I I need for your nerd head wait how
many armor kits did you give me three
okay I can already actually make a level
four nerd hat for that I need four but I
have an extra one that I can give you
for yeah for free a discount for my
for how do you call someone who's only
related to you by being someone else's
wife who's who you're also their wife
sister
sister I guess something like that we're
also wives so we're not really Sister
Wives wait no I ran out of Leever no
wait I have a bit more lever oh yeah
okay okay okay okay okay I'm always hat
with the
forge does anybody have some more like
iron for me to like smelt there's
there's 100 already in
yeah that's not enough we need that's
not enough okay I'll look I'll go out
and look for
more I'll also look for iron please
please me
too oh wait maybe if I undo this Springs
I need Springs I thought I I have I have
Springs in my inventory you can have I
have one spring I'll take that one spr I
have nine Springs I'll take Seven
Springs here just take take all all of
my Springs
amazing thank you are we are we
fortifying this house
what's okay okay Callie's going to the
the main
house oh it's time soon soon wait did I
give you your hat oh wait F fun I have
your hat oh my hat
yay level four nerd
hat now I can match everyone else yay y
we look so cute gosh I look
crazy wow it suits wait you know wait
do with the green hair and now even more
so with the hat and the goggles have
alien glasses you look like the lady you
know from that photo from the chocolate
FB um Charlie and the
Chocolate that's Charlie look like lady
from the picture yeah
oh uh here here's some Springs I'm going
to drop it by your feet oh I'm actually
I I have enough now oh okay I'll you can
play I'll put them into this chest
[Music]
yeah okay Ooa
Loa
cute what am I
doing I need so much iron
so much iron I'm looking for more thank
you that's so sweet but oh wait with
this 10 + 4 oh
yeah more I'll probably get there do we
need to head over we might yeah
soon soon
soon the sooner the better probably get
mentally prepared
okay what the blast furnace speed up
foring yeah but I don't have time to
make that right
now I'm going to make it after the
hoorde found a little iron deposit oh
nice oh you right you are
our
uh what are you again yeah minor 69er
Beaver yeah
scary okay one
more it's getting
scary why is the thund wor come into my
arms and my iron
hole we'll be safe down I'm ironing
straight
down I now have 1,000 iron oh my
gosh soent you can just thr it into the
forge okay
okay I made my machine gun there's a lot
of hammer books Hammer books I use
Hammer books sled Hammer books in the in
the book one
okay I wanted to keep digging but it
looks like time will be soon now I'm
hungry can I eat this pie I'm going to
yes
okay I will save
it 2,000 IR I'm
running okay I'm going to I'm going to
head over also okay all right I'm going
to bring some so maybe we can click over
there yeah okay good idea let us
converge wait do I even remember where
the other house
is um oh wait is it it's all the way
over there yeah
oh will we make it what time does night
start
21 oh boy something like that not yet I
got to drop everything off we have bikes
yeah we have we have bikes it's fine
move quickly it seems like is nobody
there yet I think everyone is making
their way they're almost there okay
maybe they just
arrived this sky is starting to
darken
[Music]
yeah okay I am heading over we must ride
so many trees I have to go
through leave through
them like the forest creature you are
this snow area I don't I don't wait
don't you don't need to go through the
sow snow area for yeah but there might
be a road there oh I think it's okay
it's not too bad if your your bike is
faster than the zombies
yeah I
guess I can go this way we need to build
a bridge yeah yeah this darn
Lake
mhm can you ride your bike through a
lake um I I rolled through a pond and I
seemed okay I was kind of suffocating in
butt oh it works actually it's
fine you can just go straight
through can you make it without drowning
yeah across a river at least maybe not a
lake if you have if you have a stamina
for it I think you should be
okay oh my bike is taking a
beating am I bike is a
24%
quality I'm forting through the river oh
no you should you should heal your bike
she needs Band-Aids but I don't know
where to get bandaids for her oh it's
just repair kit so you can repair it
with those there's some in the the chest
in the new house
okayy come almost there we can make it
we so
far it is really far I don't know how we
how we made it so far from each
other maybe we should start up like
multiple residences near other Traders
too cuz we're it's like going more and
more south especially with this third
one we might need a new resid
is come on bike you can do
they reinforced
it they did I feel like it's going to be
hard to to jump through
now if you want to run in and out
you go through the water so slowly
yeah but it's it's a faster
shortcut I was drowning they have the
faster shortcut to
death
[Music]
cornmeal oh they did
reinforce
yeah oh they have no fuel Fu
here you know who has
fuel us you
specifically I
hope
oo yeah let me just let me take a U-turn
real
quick let me take a pit stop I'll find
some
fuel wait do you no longer have 8,000
wood in your inventory no I only have
7,000 wa wow enough that's
enough I'm
worthless you're worthless you don't
have
8,000 I know I only have 7,000 oh my
go I can make a bunch of pumpkin bread
when we have fuel I can't find any wood
around I'm almost there I have all the
wood
oh there's some there's some repair kits
in the old house too for your bike
[Music]
yay where am
I oh my God I was routing to our old
house I made a urn somewhere along the
way I I think you should come to the old
house now you have about an hour before
they start
arriving I was I was biking to the old
house and then I got lost and then I
started following the arrow to our our
new home and then I was like where am
I don't forget to set a new
bed okay
I'm taking matters into my own
hands I'm getting my own
wood oh they set up a nice pew pew
spot
oh okay I'm going to hop
over okay see you guys there we will be
there
[Music]
hello um I need them for a pipe shotgun
I'm making for crony actually I'm
stealing them from bio sorry bi I owe
six pipes no you don't owe me anything
just take it it's fine are you sure get
to the base hurry I'm trying but I went
the wrong way drive faster run go theong
way use your bike go through the river
you don't have to go through the path go
through the river
I'm try harder don't shoot me when I get
there please I'll try really hard not to
no promises with the zombies oh oh oh
then we might have to I prom don't shoot
me don't shoot me I'm almost
there food we have 60 B
let's make them count
okay yeah you guys will be fine I'm
going to show you I made a little that
you guys can I'm take itan
accent and ammo oh my God this shooty
platform is so good thank you thank you
you're welcome you're
welcome oh you made it y I was going to
shoot you no shoot her shoot her no
late it's dangerous place dangerous does
anybody else have any pipes any amount
of pipes at
all not sorry okay it's okay man I can
make you a level three I can make you a
level three shotgun when the zombies are
here I recommend the clock they'll be
here in 20 seconds oh the so beautiful I
want to sing it's going to be
fun okay okay 65 ammo as well to help
you out crony all right oh thank you
where are you I am
outside I see waiting for everybody's
facing that way face the other way see
okay here you go here is your gun and
here is your ammo oh my God have to what
the heck that's a lot oh my God use them
well but remember it only sh it only
shoots one at a time yeah yeah so just
be ready for that
I'll make them
count oh boy here we go oh here we go uh
oh good luck
everyone oh
gosh we got this it's easy
[Applause]
easy kinky can you put one more block
here for me wait a minute
okay can't jump so high
yet a party coming
shotguns are not the best to have at
this thank you really a lot of them yeah
thank
you they are okay no one out no one's
out on the field right I'm going to
throw Molotov please do not go on the
okay what be
careful oh oh they spit all the vomits
now oh they're spitting
pretty
far okay seems like no one's attacking
the house from the other side it's only
the the other side okay
[Music]
nice okay don't do that maybe just use a
gun maybe just use a gun maybe just use
a
[Music]
gun okay all right all right this might
be prettying time for put my bed roll in
here I'm oh my God it's boming like
crazy I'm
scared it's a bit laggy too oh that
moment is
like uhoh are you
okay I need to get almost you don't hurt
me
uh-oh uh-oh they're going to break
inside in the food chest and also F
anyone needs
a they're going to break for the spikes
soon over here where where can can
somebody build more spikes I have I'll
more I have some
spes you're doing it you're
doing on the left side of the house okay
okay okay I'm building right now all
right all right
I don't know where I'm looking I'll cut
this tree down too while we're at it for
more wood are you sure but what about
the natural uh uh you
know on the hill on the hill uhoh zom on
the hill the brides on the hill the hill
they're they're coming from the front of
the house now again from the Hill from
the hill and then from the h going up
the stairs you yeah they are coming from
the hill
CeCe right click to activate it and then
throw it with left
click oh go behind C DOD Dodge backwards
okay
okay I thought the B kid
you oh there was a bomb I didn't even
know
that yeah but it was very very little
ham time
baby bird all the birds are onir spes
don't
those are bir are not that strong it's
okay yeah the birds are like okay I'm
putting spikes on the front thank you
right now it's kind of calm over here
there there there dog there dog watch
out watch out watch
out watch out for the
dog oh it's
okay I think taking am I taking them
down okay dog is dead it's alive oh no
that's not that's a big
dog oh dear the dog hurts yeah the do
broke it side am I helping I think so
just keep on shooting am I helping I
think
so someone's naked out there it's
me my arm is
spr okay I'm going to try putting down
more spikes oh
I'm C more spes I killed the
bird he's in he's in wait is that the
person he's in oh did they get in okay
we can filter them in a certain way like
choke them through let's try to re
forticate when there's
time we need to heal we need to heal it
okay where the chill time right now now
down time healing and food inside in the
food chest yeah there's down time so
let's eat oh they're coming they're
coming from the left side left
side killing oh I'm going to throw a
Molotov so don't go in the field on the
left side yet okay should have brought
my
[Music]
mol this is definitely different from
the first night yeah yeah yeah it's
getting a little harder nice fire
okay oh God so many of them are
broken you do it you it all right I'm
going to throw pipe bombs also on the
left side so don't don't go out oh watch
out watch out watch out watch out watch
out make it go boom I saw right in front
of me there's a lot going on on the left
side left yeah there is a lot
oh nice make him go boom yeah make him
go
boom I the
bridge okay don't worry don't worry
we'll be fine they're starting to come a
little bit from the left be a
bit okay it's a lot on the left back
there they are don't mind me he SP oh my
God he's having a contion over there
down yeah reloading reloading get him
get him I'm going to set the field on
fire
[Music]
again nice ni weo I hope he doesn't set
the spikes on fire by himself burning oh
nice get him I think we got him
uhoh anybody over here down below
much better
shotgun I'm out of ammo soon there he is
there he is where are the repair kit do
we have any here inside I'm pretty sure
they're coming from the southwest
South get him there a
big throw it yeah I'm I'm helping I'm
helping get him get him get
him yeah
nice job
team oh no don't break his is fa out
there using her fist she always does the
no fears jealous yeah I'm getting I'm
getting bonuses oh my gosh I'm super
jealous of f right now I'm going to out
fight she's so
brave I'm brave too they up did they up
I'm too scared to go out there yet but
I'm out of ammo soon so I'll probably go
out and die watch
out do not shoot shoot the okay watch
out behind you there's a big
guy yeah
that's
officer oh oh oh back back there yeah
yeah he in the I don't know if we hit
him a lot of stuff so
weird we need to be I don't know maybe I
should go outside and it's so laggy
I it's Prett
laggy I tried to hit them like face
through me oh my God
reloading oh wow terrible swings for
me should we go backwards
oh back off okay get him get him I'm
trying oh that one's really strong
down the orange eye ones are very strong
I need to get out of here we
could I'm going to start throwing pipe
bombs watch out people on the
field I'm out of
ammo I think we're almost out of ammo
too
I'm
scared who's who's outside right now
besides fauna or fa just went in I'm
in I'm coming oh oh jeez okay I see we
miss going so that I can go back out and
fight again damage me I don't know what
it's almost over no God bit this bad not
too bad it's not bad
I'll make some more
spikes get
get go back go back go
back it's the big one oh there's there's
there's a there's a lot Southwest
Southwest uh-oh it won't let you oh it's
lagging out here there a zombie is do it
okay okay hit with fire yeah okay oh
stamina
nice oh no I'm going
to yeah they are
camping
nice love dying oh joyous day to die
yeah Seven Days to Die Seven Days to
Die oh crazy are
shocked face oh
boy I do
it theyed the house the
door just
two so close not D we're let them
[Music]
in no there's just one it's fine it's
fine
are they is it
done did we do itary music stop suddenly
didn't until three I thought I thought
four it seems quiet now it's they're
preparing for the next wave recoup
everybody last second oh it's over for
real oh man why did oh it's it's quiet
too quiet it's too quiet
I don't think it's over ladies a happy
song or
something I thought we were
leaving how many bullets do we have left
if we don't have any 79 is it over
there's the music's 79 there's no way
it's over I don't know it feels over it
feels over I think so but the but the
the the the the the the the the sky is
still
red and the Happy song isn't
playing was there a happy song
can't touch this okay you got it nice I
got
it okay I'm going to put stuff in the in
the
stor well too quiet wonderful we' done
we've done it once again but I think
next time maybe one more row of spikes
because they do seem to be breaking
through now just one small row yeah I
worry if we're going to I I wonder if
we're going to have more like flying
type enemies as well if that's a thing
oh CRA there was only a few Birds yeah
and more ammo also there's iron spikes
that you can build
now better it's not over over it's
not where are
they me yeah did I scare you guys a
little bit it's just me oh you're such a
troll ha silly I get a little silly
sometimes get
better I think it's not
over yeah I heard a we it's over there
was a
lightning yeah it's over yeah apparently
you can you can uh get fredom all before
4:00 a.m. we were just back yeah we were
just that
good okay free waves that makes sense
okay yay we did it we did
it felt more intense than the first time
yeah yeah the first time was a bit anti
yeah we just got so much
stronger nice
nice together everyone we didn't die we
help maybe good job helping you did you
did you did it did it you guys are doing
great how do I fix the spikes oh God oh
not with our body not with our
body die I'm stuck on a oh no am
can we heal now we're going to die M
let's maybe maybe
fixing oh let's heal let's heal M
let's this kind of a weird noise mhm I
hope it's over cuz I already left and
we're far away oh God yeah it's over
it's over yeah it should be done I think
speaking of uh how long may we be online
today 4 hours total again or um I would
I would be very happy if if we could if
people could not play past uh 45 minutes
from now okay okay sounds good okay okay
of course we'll play again tomorrow of
course you know just to make sure that
everybody's got enough time to level up
and such and do a bunch of quests
together and such yeah yeah there's
shotgun ammo and uh 762 ammo in the old
house so take that before you leave the
old house is it in the ammo
box we need to end here for today but if
anybody wants our our our what's it
equipment we have a good good right oh
yeah you can borrow to someone else I
guess yeah oops I'll drop it for now
okay uh thanks
ah I I was going to drop the other ammo
in the new house let's check the current
stage the game
stage uh Faun is the one that's furthest
in game stage
50 what did I do how did I get what's a
game state tting so
good punching things
punching not been leveling very much I
wonder if I have the EXP debuff or
something maybe I'm just not doing
enough Quest more quests huh if you want
to go the N goggles again oh yeah I'll
bring it into the new house okay
okay I hope it gave you some
levels
nice everybody looks so nerdy look
atch of nerd
NDS should we put our levels into
strength again what weapon are you
enjoying using the shot shotgun or what
are you using strength is probably best
for that okay strength for shotguns and
clubs I want to take some of these
materials like iron and stuff from the
old house to the new house since we have
a forge over there good
idea
yeah we'll see everybody tomorrow
bye thank you byebye bye bye will also
head out for now I have a different
stream I'm doing um but I will see you
guys tomorrow
don't overdo it
Callie by bye all righty bye I'll see
you guys later take care take see you
tomorrow peace
u o
O2 uh yeah let's do quests I need to get
rid of my exp debbed
okay yuming yuming yuming I love yum in
here we
loveing
weing around we oing we yapping we
yapping it takes so much
stamina stamina contest let's start I
already zero I'm
[Laughter]
out I love yuming y what you yuming
about cool I think I'm like I have like
a radioactive sign are you sober
now yeah I I Dr a sound
disappointed sad about
it no I'm happy cuz I was then I could
join I didn't want to be the weird drunk
uncle at point no I think I would I
think that would have been great you
would have been the life of the party
yeah um wait where where did Cory go
where did you go me yes where are you oh
there do you want to do you want to do
Quest
too uh sure I'll do one yeah can we guys
join you even though we don't have
bicycles
yeah bicycle L pointing and
laughing imagine not having a b try
hard yeah we don't need we like being
healthy and moving our legs properly and
you move your legs on Bic are you
jealous of the of the ding ding huh
watch this ding ding
is low impact
exerc uh I'm going to the house back
first the new house I need to drop
stu okay oh you can the bik too yeah you
can repair with repair kit so it's
actually pretty nice also you can dye it
whatever color you want yeah I was going
to say what a coincidence you'll all
have your colors but then I
realized I wish I could take you guys
with me but it doesn't unless you like
move with
me it's kind of working it's it'sing a
little bit it's kind of working kind
of he so if you girls join us should we
still be doing tier two
quests yeah we did that with CIA too I
think they they get
exia CIA
[Laughter]
yeah that's a good
password better than 1111 at least
111111 no no one would use that as a
password ever
nope a we're totally joking by the way
for legal reasons that we never use
1111 of course not yeah no
way I feel like we slower this way
people than if we just walk all right
bye BS really are pretty fast
yeah I wish I had Bic don't tell them
that don't tell them that 10 quests or
so we don't need bicycles cardio is good
for
you what do you think Bing is it's also
cardio but it's less it's less cardio
it's not less cardio it's like longer
cardio cuz you can bike for longer then
you can where iron yeah but we're going
the same way wait where did you go I
lost her it's over I lost her too it's
okay I I went across the
river you can cross the river with a B
over here
hello what I always get off of it you
can go straight through yeah if you have
stamina you can just n through
it crazy that's strong you have some you
go underwater like on the ground
physically
yeah this hold your breath for S my
Common Sense has prevented me from
greatness it
seems but now you can achieve greatness
yeah but I'm always low on stamina guess
I can't do it
then just get more stamina going oh I oh
okay it's this way I was waiting for
crony oh I'm I'm ahead of you
it's
okay okay we're going this
way are we going that way yes we are
going I'm just going to where Kiara is
oh I'm going towards the house but I'm
taking weird paths I think oh okay and
Mining a little bit in the in
between I'm not getting what I want
here that's iron help
no let's
see where's the iron I can't find iron
oh I
have um I am
bringing
1300 on what 13 what 1300 not
13,000 still that's a
lot yeah that's a lot that looks like
iron oh you call it iron too I'm so
happy you do what what wait who who what
you say that to do you wait you call it
iron yeah you call it iron yeah but your
first language is
English oh you're getting
owned no I love I was trying to relate
to
you are you kidding me right
now I thought it wasn't normal I thought
only wait what do you call said wrong
it's iron iron iron iron iron iron iron
iron iron oh I feel so kind I kind of
like character from it's like the
character from Avatar iru Uncle iru you
don't I I right I literally can't find
my house most of the time look for the
trees look for the trees no but like get
rid of them I'm sick of them they
concealed it's like like it's just like
Twilight where they live in I be finding
my house the vampires live in this house
yeah vampires live in this house the
Clementine
family I thought they were called the
cullins that's we can't yeah it's a
reboot we can't take it for copyright
reasons it's a spin-off
okay okay I put a bunch of iron in the
iron in the Forge uh
check the book chest where are they
going electric and food cooking thank
you I love reading we made it yay
[Music]
yayas
doas
what I can make a robotic Sledge oh I
don't know what that is wait Raider
Sledge like a the trees are growing into
the house hey
chill likes it what are you wearing on
your top oh what what is it
called what are you wearing right
now
Commando oh I think I have something of
interest for a set bonus oh Raider top
perhaps or your Raider hat although you
are wearing a nerd hat
now uh I think it does this wait good
outfit yeah thank you I found it
somewhere
scary my hat
doesn't you look
hardcore this is WTF what the fauna oh
want the
fauna I was thinking of something else
but I guess that's what it's supposed to
mean in
reality I got some
L but I'll I'll put some Rogue boots
into the uh armor chest whoever wants
this wants it can take
it thank
you oh I have fist stuff on a here floor
ow I'm sorry I don't know what came over
me
you I don't mean to hit my wife so often
what what was that you're a wife pater I
can't help
it can't help don't cry my
sweet don't let them know you have to
change can't keep going on I I stopped
drinking is that not enough isn't the
gambling
then it is the gambling I dream of it
yeah oh no take
this oh thank you think you might like
it if I put this on my weapon
yeah do we have like electrical parts of
mechanical parts that kind of stuff
somewhere uhwhere in the chest I think
we should in the uh the miscellaneous
crates we have a lot of parts parts in
these two chests um might be able to
find it there oh yeah there's robotic
Parts in these wood stor these unlabeled
wooden storage crates right here next to
fin there's some there oh okay nice
thank you
oo
okay I got so much stuff oh my God
careful
I didn't know you could very cramped as
you may have
noticed careful
man is there any leather oh I have 12
how much do you
need I
need um I need 12 oh okay here's 12
thank
you okay um
seeds H oh I'm
hungry are
you yeah oh tummy rumbles o I have a
banana
bread I love banana bread they have
bananas in this game pumpin bread pumpin
I was disappointed pumpkin bread is nice
too I like banana bread better too it's
behind
you floor I just put it on the floor
thank you I'm going to eat
[Music]
it so it was nice and moist thank you I
almost punched you in your face were you
scared did I frighten you a little
bit what WR maybe I'll do it
anyway ah
just because I'm wearing glasses the way
you don't like it it wasn't your glasses
it was your what was it it was your your
the the the worm under your nose the
hairy worm come closer and get a better
look not a worm oh let me doing some
renovation you're scared of me I see I
have good reason to be
scared
you scared wait you look like Eggman
from from Sonic oh thank you that's a
compliment
better I want to move this too IDE oh
that looks pretty it's pretty yeah was
in the
way okay if I burns my eyes five fored
steel I'm burning again ah there's some
oh fored steel why do you love burning
yourself man oh do you
need do you need for steel have some I
have 15 yeah I need oh nice I just need
four okay and then I can make my item
thingy that I've been wanting I'm at the
forge Workshop
thingy here you
go I dropped
it thank you so
much okay the windows are patched up
which is
good nice nice okay oh you're fixing our
windows
oh yeah the exterior oh G she's the
fixer yes do you have something a mod on
your head
item
um
um no do you want
this oh thank you welcome my sunglasses
are just going to have light shining out
of it I don't think it would be
visually visible but uh damn I wish it
was
that would be
amazing okay we only have like 30
minutes left until CI kicks us off okay
so maybe questing time oh I can make
dynamite now
oo yeah I'm done to do Quest I'm ready
yeah I'm
[Music]
ready where should I put this there's a
chicken give me your
eggs oh does anyone have food I
hungry aren't you the one that
cooks eggs in the
output I guess I guess I'll just use a
little bit of meat without the eggs just
cook the meat yeah oh I have three eggs
wait oh
okay here I put it in here thank you
Eggman does anyone happen to have a
baton a baton a bon baton
Bon um yeah there's some in the weapons
chest nice thank
you um
H what was I going to
do ow
no everyone's on fire it's so crap we
need to renovate the house make it more
Spacey I think what we should do is we
should have a third house near the next
Trader yeah because we're we're on like
the third Trader now or some of us are
so we're all going to be over there
later so may we should have a house
there I will make the house more
spacious are you breaking our house I
was breaking some
renovating that's a that's a wall right
there here we go I got rid of the mod
bearing wall take take these arrows
please off of my hands it's just a few
so much more space
yeah it's getting somewhere why is this
trash can here in the middle I'll get
rid of the wall to the bathroom too we
don't need privacy we don't need privacy
we do not need privacy in this household
oh we don't need washroom yeah we're
family no you can still use it just in
front of
us I love that agreen the wide open
Toilet
yeah Smash It smash it
yeah smashing together giggy look at
this wow perfect I would love to see
someone use the toilet with the Cece's
box over
it it's okay we're Idols we don't use
toilets yeah we just
[Music]
go we just have so many meetings all
there's a wild boar over here let's kill
it let's take his eggs kill it eggs oh I
killed him in one punch she's one punch
girl I feel can you guys to cron and I
oh I think I think I'm going to head out
so okay
okay good
night good
night thanks for fixing byee byebye
how much time do we have repair kid oh
20 minutes maybe uh
24 okay we can
do CL
Quest run run run run shall we go to the
tier two yeah place oh yeah Sicilia
needs an invite though I think yeah Cy
Cy
bcle
bicycle bicycle
there are I so quiet
hello hello hello
[Music]
hello we need eggs is there can you make
a chicken
farm I think we might be able to but I
don't know how I wish got to do some
research uh okay I'll make my way to I
have a quest over there so I'll make my
way there oh I see your quest okay I'll
head over there
too all right I haven't I haven't gotten
the wait who's the party leader you me
oh you is it you me is it me K I don't
think so I think it's K is it me oh it
was me I see a chicken all along
chicken be nice to it oh uh H I was very
nice to it really I will be did you trat
it to uh to some food did you give it
some
corn um they like corn
oh they
do can you put the chicken that is with
you on the phone so I can hear
it has a lot to say that's
cute oh it seems like the chicken is
fine yeah yeah
yeah okay I'm relieved to hear that I I
let I let the chicken go on its merry
way it went to cross the road oh that's
you can cross the road huh oh no I'm
glad I did raw
[Music]
potatoes going on here meat stew oo meat
stew
yummy and vegetable
stew where probably better
right uh
I'm just doing it's funny to hear that
from you f yeah I
know between meat stew and vegetabl
[Music]
stew honestly like iralo there's so many
times where I just prefer having
something without meat just because it's
just
uh sometimes I just want like a bowl
full of
vegetables yeah yeah often when I get
like a curry or so I'll just order a
vegetable curry because they put so much
meat in there I don't even need that
much oh some days I just eat a bowl of
boiled broccoli and that's
it bowl of broccoli but it season I
season it good so it's tasty no that's
good yeah is it grilled or cooked or raw
it's like steamed broccoli and know like
the yeah and then and then you put like
seasoning like SES oil and like peppers
in it and stuff M okay I hope I don't
get lost to you guys oh I hear a have
someone on foot like a noob we can eat
the SN hey now I'm I'm alone now you
can't do
that you what you can't you can't you
can't say that can't call you a noob oh
because I'm T hanging up on
you oh level up you would do that where
was my exp de I don't think you have exp
de um what yeah you don't I don't there
there is no consequence to dying well
then
awesome uh yeah I've been I've been past
level 65 for a while and I have not
gotten any exp de from dying so I don't
think it exists in This Server
anyway I am fine with
that wait where did the playing on easy
mode baby server baby
server b car
I can finally jump two blocks
[Music]
hik this zombie is on
fire wow he had a lot of loot what's
with him why is he carrying so much
stuff for what what are you
hiding wooo snake
are we ready to Quest I'm ready but I
don't think everybody's here I am wait
you're
there no us two are here we are waiting
yeah me and B you've been waiting we've
been waiting this entire time oh just a
little bit we weren't here that long I I
was at the house and I was like I I kept
I was like oh are we going and then I
looked at the map and
sudden
here how could you keep us waiting the
Ser is going to close
soon it's because
okay we're
chilling we're just looking around yeah
I'm just killing
things casually all the things you do
yeah yeah just ending some people's
lives some zombies suffering
casual releasing them from their
suffering some casual violence you know
as one does during a zombie
apocalypse yeah relatable is it
cathartic yes that's nice I like the
sounds when my knife pierces their flesh
oh like the yeah exactly I actually
don't like
it it's disgusting
yeah are you okay I was peacefully
hitting a tree and there's a
dog and a bunch of other
zombies I do be like that sometimes is
yes I found my
way I'm pedaling as fast as I can oh
biker oh you're over there okay wait I
think this is a real life dog no live
it's getting killed by the
zombies doly dog oh there's so many
okay you guys are here I'm trying to
save the dog h on the back of don't Hur
the dog save the dog I'll save you save
the dog save the dog okay the zombies
are dead dog
I'm okay okay don't hurt me don't hurt
me ow don't hurt me don't no please here
I have a bone do you want a bone
no me me me no
need meat to eat but he's so
cute it hurts me too you know you are
you're cutting it apart meat
meat meat Meats me tears it
off oh
man he's going to Doggy
Heaven
okay in heaven now I'm ready everybody
here so sorry I died I'm in heaven now
don't worry so sorry I died
begin let's let the chaos
begin oh GG you're in already what are
you hitting why are you hitting
that log she's she's she's she's hung up
above the dog ow why why do you keep why
stop running in front of me I'm hitting
lck stop hitting us I'm hitting the
lock is there a way
up a it's the fireplace again
oh watch out for fire oh
God you're going to leech XP off of you
guys okay
yeah you're wearing you're wearing a
nerd hat right yeah yeah okay good the
good one even I'm going to cheer you on
go
oh oh I'm bleeding oh God I'm going to
die the hammer is so fun I have one
bandage are you
dead owie can I have a bandage
powerful wait that's not you where is bi
boo I'm behind you I'll get the zombie
first okay hello
button I'm sorry a regular
bandaid fire is off yay has been
found oh but be careful with the Cal on
the ground doesn't that make you go on
fire too no oh
okay
zombies is this a really meing Place
yeah this is the parkour this
is parkour civilization this is parkour
civilization yeah watch out for the be
fin
[Applause]
ah ah I'm
dying
fun when you turn them on fire no that's
not how you burn them on fire you know
what I mean and my my sledgehammer has
fire on it ooh that's so really cool
that is very cool oh I have another wait
no I don't never mind anti that would
probably be really
effective uh type of weapon in like a
zombie apocalypse just burn them yeah oh
sense yeah burn the stinky corpses oh
that must smell bad actually
e
e f are you up there no I'm
down I'm going Up's up here I'm up here
the door is
locked hold on I'll just smack yeah
Brute Force
woohoo i' have help but then yeah I'll
get hit probably have a better axe oh
the window might be easier oh but
there's no at the window
no oh maybe that one I have brought a
bird maybe a
bird oh I guess it's outside still I'm
contributing me too me
too what's the HP
at
660 fine here I have a ow I have
I'm hitting you hting people I'm trying
not
to trying to get the perfect
angle bro 40 HP you owe me a bandage
once I find when I'll bandage you
up almost there almost there almost
there why isow bird making the noise
crazy oh what oh what uh oh we can still
we can still get up
oh
there hello help help help help help I
am all help help help help take your
time Tak take your
time
fall yes
bir he went all the way down oh no he
got back up what where what all the way
down oh I can kill him from here
sniper machine gun
sniper oh was that a lady in a
dress I think there was a man
really I saw Red Clothing it reminded me
of the beautiful dress
water now it's empty was it murky yeah
it has mky water this bird used to
chill where is the
bird no why is so
loud where should I
go a bunch of some
stuff oh oh there you are okay
are you going are you
up where are they there's there's one in
the door in the door yeah but it's
locked too I
think I don't even know if I can make a
[Applause]
jump on the roof SL is it oh
man oh
no wait where did they
go I don't
know I will avenge you thank
you what what happened were you
overwhelmed I I was at like 5
HP oh there's a bird oh he already
opened it up a really loud Bird Okay the
bird is dead oh thank
God it's been screaming this entire
time
oh what who is that right behind that
monster it's me how you make it how did
you make it there I went down the
elevator I believe
genius where's okay still not finished
yeah where's the last one
been here
forever one might have fallen all the
way down I'm not sure the music stopped
yeah they were like oh you girls are
taking too
long we didn't pay for such a long music
track I hear it I yeah I hear something
yeah I can't tell where it is
though I hear
hello sounds like
crying I found
it oh you're
downstairs oh wait did you we did it did
finish
[Applause]
y okay uh if we have one more nearby
already we could go
otherwise does anybody have mine's kind
of far let's
see H we could go to T gen and see if we
can accept another Quest that's close
by um mine's kind of close to her but
not really I think it's over the
mountain yeah we could go straight there
finish it off shall we go to gig's Quest
okay and then to Traer and then ended
okay okay oh wait bicycle
do
bicycle oh I'm so hungry though I'm so
firsty I especially hungry I don't have
any sham sandwich I have some raw steaks
and a sham
sandwich that's at least something oh
you can't get sick eating raw meat
right not an
apocalypse maybe I'll eat the raw egg
it's t
steak
tartar with a little raw egg on top of
[Music]
it well I hope we make it like after
this geigy Quest I hope we make it in
time for the Traer before she closes
hopefully we're going to have to
speedrun RTA
style
yeah are we going the right way yes I
feel like it might take that long just
to drive there
yeah should I drink the yoka juice drink
it yeah get off yeah after the bicycle
right almost almost there what is it is
a fetch Quest oh Fetch and clear I think
I'm not going to be in time because I'm
slow walking I'm go to the I'm going to
go to the trail all good okay keep her
open keep her occupied I I'll try
stalling as much as I can tell her not
to close or else oh can we take a quick
sip SI water okay I
also me too if only we had more hats I
know wait actually I don't know where
your traiter is yet so I'm going Traer
do you see like from yeah go straight go
straight basically I know it much what
direction you're looking at it's the
Green Field I guess you don't see the
map yet but if you go straight over the
mountain thank you just try to keep on
going south okay okay South
okay and it's like a talk to her we the
we the people that come into the store 2
minutes before closing and then we take
a long
time long time do you think you have a
size in the back
sorry oh you know the people who come in
at like 9 9:00 p.m. be like do you have
the size in the
back oh never mind of the St of the
store back of the store can you look at
the oh do you have this in a different
size oh yeah it's always it's always I I
worked in retail a lot and then it was
always like please look check in the
back and then you just go into the back
and come back and you're like there's no
we don't have that does anyone have
antibiotics or honey no uh but Trader
dad J Jo George Sells it yeah it's fine
does anyone have any emergency food no I
have raw meat oh yeah raw meat or raw
eggs maybe I'll eat this raw corn
meat
H oh wow Traer Jen
o I am met her I met her she has a flow
in her hair that's cute is she a doctor
why does she have a I'm wearing it
really quickly okay take this
g o the art of
mining or your
iron iron what do you mean four minutes
uh oh she has cream maybe I don't know
in four minutes we should my mean it's
not that exact I would
think but minute 4 minutes and and plus
like 5 Seconds it'll be okay
right yeah yeah
yeah she's not just did a little
grinding off stream just a little just a
tiny
bit it's fine it'll be fine she'll
forgive
us okay uh we can begin I'm here
okay okay oh what is this
person
okay I met the Traer I'm happy um I'm
going to go see you guys
[Music]
tomorrow bye-bye byebye or good
morning
true why are we doing this to a
graveyard oh no I my knee again not the
knee what this guy's kind
of I'm leaving no back into the grave of
you oh
god oh now my knee is
sprained oh
no are we looking he's getting back up
he's getting back
up satchels
yeah I think we're looking for the
satchels he dead now no he's not okay
now he's
dead I already looked in that casket
there's nothing in there I thought this
was a barbecue grill and I was like out
a graveyard oh wa in here
maybe oh yeah oh oh there's a whole
dungeon down here probably be careful I
found mine there's a lot of scary things
down here
wao watch out for the spikes there are
spikes
spikes oh there
okay this is cool this is different
mhm maybe we got to get rid of these
things here and there to see what we
need
no
oh I'm star
ing what's
that oh watch out behind
you what is
that oh I found mine it seems good maybe
it's the same for someone else watch out
watch
out oh he's falling he's green so easy
to
see oh scar
H oh oh that's
me you're both
GRE get out of my
swamp it's her
swamp
swamp I have 30 HP oh there's a oh
there's like a hidden thing over here
is that oh
nice a book crate I love
books
books there's honey here you still need
honey oh I need honey wa you can have it
you should you should you yeah you can
eat
it oh
D I'll buy mine from
Jane Senai Tex is strong as
ever it works it just works
ha books have been read we standing four
generations here oh we
are a good mix
mhm graveyard who's missing their
statue or do we all have it I have mine
oh we're done okay we're done run
where's exit
TW please please don't close
please the exit oh it's here it's
here baby please don't
[Music]
close it was it 900 p.m. then she when
she closes I think it 950 yeah somewhere
around there 950 okay we'll be fine
maybe how do you get there though
there's a little there's a there's a
windy path there's a windy path behind
the house if you see the
map I see
it I'll follow
for yeah she closed early on us last
time like 10
minutes but I think we're
fine I hope 9:45 oh we're 2 minutes
over we're going to get banned oh no
we're going to get reported don't report
us please
come I'm stuck me
too I looked away for a
moment are we going up a mountain is
that the right way yeah go up the
mountain and then slide down the cliff
you won't take fall damage if you just
slide down
okay I changed the controls or something
something's
weird oh I don't like there's birds up
here I really want to check The Nest but
I'm
not I see
it I'm going to slide down with my oh my
gosh it's a little
steep a thank you Mouse button is it
really okay it's so
steep wait did you go left
or I think I went right I'm going to
slide down on my
butt maybe oh yeah this is work
especially now with my parkour SK have
this do I
yes run run
run another successful day in seven days
to die yeah
slowly I walk into the
church oh that's a lot of
ammo that I don't
use maybe
these oh tier three stuff now yeah I
still don't have
it oh there's a night only
[Music]
Quest suar suar
butts whose Sugar Butt are you talking
about could be anyone's could be yours
that could be a cute nickname hey sugar
buts what's up sugar
butt she gave me mats to craft a mini
bike
[Music]
oo shotgun ground oh
oh there's batter up
magazines but I don't should I should I
buy this for CI Cali wanted uh B up yeah
see what se's BL weapon baseball bat yes
yes
yes uh with the volume does it matter
like if she already read volume three
can she read it again I don't know what
volume can't read it again ah cuz it's a
book I'll keep it in there maybe she
read it
already Okay farewell I am so
hungry
farewell goodbye see you
tomorrow
byee sleep
well just going to eat this stew Quest
failed oh that always shocks me I know
right
what I'm getting so strong yes be the
one punch profal boxer
now do you still have you still have
that perk for drunken fist we need to
get you lots of beer I don't does it do
anything does it help me I don't know we
got to find out yes books books
wait come outside in case she closes
come I'm afraid the stuff is going to
get stuck in there and will be forever
separated armor for you not armor sorry
ammo ammo ammo a here's book for you as
well thank you so sweet such sweet
exchanges who here uses shotgun uh call
do okay I'll keep it for now I forgot to
sell
the woman let me me sell my money for
more money you have 20
seconds
easy
JMA thank
you did you just call
herma yeah is she JMA I imagine her to
be jenma in a different different
Universe yeah oh I oh that scares
me
purch well I'll think about that skill
point next time all right I I guess I'll
end it here me
tooe good job today had a good
timee
byebye I should L off and make sure I
don't
I don't AFK for 7 hours quit the game
the game is quit the game is closed the
close is
[Music]
game okay
hello on today's episode of how long you
can keep me here until I have to go what
are we going to do together
huh on today's episode of how long are
you going to keep me here
today I'm your host
Co
welcome more L more parkour more explain
didn't I ever explain
civilization to CC earlier
[Music]
today okay where is the super we got to
get
those
[Music]
done have you watched the full movie of
of Parkour civilization yet and parkour
civilization you never go for the
beef or else you'll go to parkour jail
you need to you need to ascend the
parkour Temple to become a parkour Pro
not a parkour Noob I'm still a parkour
Noob want to watch along for
it maybe if I can get someone to watch
along with me
[Music]
all let me take a sip of d w yeah D wood
for
sure but Iris
and CeCe seem to have to
have sparked some interest so maybe
CC seemed quite interested in
it okay today super
CH Panda thank you for super rock rock
hi B hi as a member of so many B watch
to watch Club I have like 16 hours of
the 70 die to watch so far including
adding tonight's stream on good note the
pebble ke r I'm happy to wear it oh
Pebble Pebble kit that's
cute it was really
fun I sniped so many zombies I feel like
I was a I was a great great asset to the
company of the of the streamer house
Defense Force I shot some I set things
on fire people Wick I covered F of
six oh yeah I didn't get to see how how
many kills I had for for
um the the game oh well I'll check next
time I have over like 300
nice I have the most zombie kills
cool I have 300 F has 200 yeah I covered
her
six I shot so many during the the zombie
raid
hey I didn't I didn't really kill too
many people today more people I think
friendly fired me than I friendly fired
them today so
yeah my goal was
successful
achievement
mhm
terar development
St thank you for the super rock rock
yeah you thank you for the super rock
rock
um I'm thinking never mind I'm not
thinking anymore I don't know what to
think about uh good luck t b we'll hope
you get more kills on the other Ms I
mean on the hord of zombies yes on the
horde of zombies right of
zombie cool I at 300 kills nice I'm a
killer James Ro thank you for the super
rock rock skellum thank you for the
super rock rock hi beu since um you are
moving to Japan I know you won't have
any pets have you considered adopting ra
so you can have a house cat I actually
want to move somewhere where I can get a
pet so I won't be lonely well I don't
think I'll be lonely anyway cuz there's
so many
Hollow members and friends around but it
would be nice to have a have a kitty to
have a kitty
cat yeah lots of friends my my main
reason why I don't have a a pet now is
because I knew when you know doing the
the the streaming stuff that I would
have to travel eventually and travel
back and forth and don't really have you
know anybody who could take care of a
pet in my stad um and like I wouldn't
want to leave my pet alone
so that's why I never got a pet yet um
but I I want I want a cat so bad or a
pigeon a cat or a pigeon yeah cuz I
don't want I don't want to you know
having having pets is like you know
they're your family they're your family
and stuff so like I wouldn't want to
leave them alone unless it's somebody I
really trusted but the good thing is you
know there's a lot of there's a lot of
like other Hollow members in Japan so if
I did get a like
uh I did get a cat I'm sure somebody
would love to
like um watch if I ever had to like go
anywhere and stuff so yes I want a cat I
want a cat or a pigeon why a pigeon
because pigeons are super smart and
adorable and their story is super sad
and if you have a sad backstory then I
um feel sympathy for you and want to
make sure you are in a Place full of
love so so yes the pigeons pigeons have
a sad back story so yeah want a I want a
pigeon and plus pigeons are super cute
they can wear pants they have pigeon
pants and um yeah they lost their JS M
and they're super smart and they're
super cuddly and they're in terms of
birds they're not super loud cuz I know
some birds are like super
like you know
so I want a p then um or a cat or
both I want a rag doll cat that's my
favorite cat breed I want a rag doll rag
dolls are
so they
[Music]
so yeah Pig can be super clean as
well a Dev gone wild thank you for a
super Rock orange cats are also cute
orange cat behavior is so funny I they
they can be so brain empty and I'm also
brain empty
so
yeah orange cat Menace
but I kind of want to I want a chill cat
I want a cat who I can like who will
while I am gaming come up and sleep on
my lap and then I'm stuck in that
position for like 5 hours that's the
kind of cat I want yeah the kind of cat
who will like huddle up and eat with
me yes
[Music]
and then and then if I get a cat you can
hear like cute cat noises on stream
that'd be
[Music]
cute
uh I don't want to adopt Raa I want R to
adopt me
can't be here pet
rock well I'm already multiple people's
Pet Rocks I'm like sh's pet rock and M's
pet
rock there has to be like some sort of
time share going
[Music]
on um SK thank you for the oh wait I
read the L Dev gone well thank you for
the super rock rock but you thank you
for the super rock rock yes I think you
are very very cute wow thank you
he B cute y BT thank you for the super
rock
rockon thank you for a super rock rock
Mar thank you for a super rock
rock she thank you for the super Rock Ro
another hor survived yay thanks to the
stream thank thank
you um D4 thank you for the super rock
rock hi people all the 70 to die
gameplay really makes me want to see you
guys play project zom boy oh I've never
heard of I've heard of that one I
haven't seen gameplay for that one
though um it's similar to 7 days to die
but it's top down and more challenging
also the zombies are terrifying as beep
terrifying I oh I requested perms for
Silent Hill too by the way so I
requested to play that so we'll see if I
get the okay
[Music]
never played a silent hill game before
so I don't know anything about
it poopy
season
uh Jo thank you for the super rock rock
good job being the MVP against the HD
people a you think I was the MVP well
everyone did their part but I like to
think that I did my
part as a part of the
part I really was kicking
[Music]
butt yeah we f f with the fish and then
me covering her sticks and then Callie
with the baseball bat and then I we had
like GG reinforcing the house and and
everybody was like backing up and Pew
peing we were a big Squad good teamwork
everybody Cod training really paying off
yeah the FPS training who knew it would
it would roll over to to here
um yay thank you for super rock rock
here in Pebble civilization no one
chooses to jump for the candy feet at
the top is where all the jetpack Pros
live but us Pebbles are jetpack noobs at
the bottom of
society now at the top are the pebble
Pros who have
limbs
but you guys are Pebble
noobs who have no
limbs yes what you have to master you
have to master the do they exist I don't
know you have to get get to the top of
you have to get the top of candy feet
Temple um and to find out find to find
out what's up there you have to find out
what's up there right but right now all
of you all of you are Pebble Noobs
yeah how do we do that you have to get a
pass to take on the trial of the candy
feet Temple and only when you ascend can
you can you become a pebble
Pro you're going to have to find out
yourself how we the pass
uh by jumping for the beef
nean thank you for the super rock
rock um wow another episode of how long
can we keep COI bizu before she leaves
it's one of my favorite shows alongside
24 hours of prism naho and brain Rod
explained featuring people Wow Let's see
am I in a yapping mood
today if you can if you can Peak my
interest in something to Yap about I'll
Yap um
oh but is Mo mate anniversary still
happening well okay let's let's read
through and sleep then wait is it still
happening okay okay okay okay
okay thank you for the super rock rock
bab there's definitely there's a horror
game that you'll definitely do it's
called carryon it's a reverse horror
game and with your regular streaming
time you can finish it in one sitting
please look into it okay I'll look into
it Go verse thank you for the super rock
rock
um you're not changing your streaming
schedule in Japan got it but what about
daylight savings time will you just
along with DST or maintain your hours
perh a mix of both no it would it will
always
be 400 p.m. PST so it will be always 400
p.m. PST 700 p.m. EST so what that is in
jst will adjust so but it is always 400
p.m.
PS yes always mhm yeah yeah yeah no no
change to that like I've never changed
from daylight saving time um so far I
will not change it again
so plus it's better for me anyway cuz
it's like 9:00 a.m. jst then and 9:00
a.m. jst is easier than 8:00 a.m. so
it's like it's fine for me if I
do p thank you for super rock rock
people are there any benefits to being
vertically challenged what about being
horizontally challenge I'm glad you are
proud of it to be honest seems such a
good role model for others in the
situation I've always liked being short
then well I only know the world from
short but I I prefer it that
way um I don't take a lot of space I can
hide in the shadows I'm really good at
hiding places um I can you
know you know I can sit and if it sits
if it fits I sit wherever I want and
that's that's kind of great
um I can if I if I fall I can just get
back up again uh I can get things from
like small spaces where people need help
with plus if I if I am vertically
challenged oh yeah I can shop at the
kids section and not pay as much money
but I think uh my fashion now is too
advanc for the kid section anymore I've
growing up a little bit now it's fancy
fashion but used to
be kids kids sizes I can fit
um has two evance I've leveled
up I leveled up you see there there's
there's definitely some disadvantages
like if there's like a crowd or
something or there's a lot of people
I'll get swept away
wee wee Blown Away In The Wind or
something like that
but yeah like
[Music]
we um that's why I will never go to
things like Black Friday or something
like that I would probably not survive
it I don't need feels that bad that it
would cost me my life
[Music]
yeah I
gu the
the not
benefit is no one takes me
seriously is that is the biggest disad
advantage of height and stuff like that
is no one no one takes
me seriously or thinks that you know I
can make my own decisions or you know I
have
competency
but it's it's
okay I've had I've had to deal with that
so I'm kind of used to it by now
[Music]
I like it it's nice I like it when you
know people are looking out for me cuz
I'm like a they care enough about about
like you know wanting wanting to make
sure I'm okay and they like they like me
enough that they want to like make sure
I'm okay but there is a cut off line
where like if you would try to do like
everything for
me I don't I'm a strong need depend of
be I'm
fine I I'm okay I yeah you
know I have a I have a limit to being
babies I guess like I appreciate it and
you know I like I like it to an extent
like I like being babied especially by
Advent because like they're just you
know trying to look at for me and like
oh cute so like that's totally fine but
just like when like I can't do anything
at all that's the cut off you know
because I can do things to myself
[Music]
mhm I'm a
person like like the the cooking thing
here's here's here's an example so many
people think I can't cook because based
on my personality and and my like you
know childish Aura people never believe
that I can like cook for
myself but I'm actually a pretty good
cook though like it's a it's a very
interesting connect the dots too I I
never thought that like people would
like assume that you know someone is bad
at cooking because they have a childish
Ora around
them yeah
[Music]
anyway I'm rambling too much
oops gar Griz thank you for the super
rock rock hey B dubs B dogs I finally
got prison Maho on Spotify on repeat
playlist number one can't wait to see my
Spotify rap to tell me how many hours
I've been listening to it keeping swag
swag thanks bro I appreciate
it thanks
thanks
bro stay
frosty are you a fan T thank you for the
super Rock block all uh I'm going to
go so that way you guys can catch M
anniversary and
maybe I
can yeah I'm going I'm going to say
anniversary to M okay bye wait oh bye
bye bye we
we bye we bye we
[Music]
to