[Music]
ah balloons would be a little tacky huh
look what you have now is fine Callie
don't overthink it okay okay but what if
it's all too much I tend to over
decorate you know the skull vases are a
little morbid but at least the roses are
uh
fragrant cookies are not extra chocolate
chip anyone want to try
oh Mimi
ah that usual Ina sweetness
cookies with the foreign recipe book the
measurements are all off
no time to fix them counts is gonna be
here soon
[Music]
timing huh
what's up counselors in the house
everyone looks super cute today as usual
and you guys remember the extra snacks
and drinks
a valentine for you and a valentine for
you
homemade cards for all of us
oh Kiara you shouldn't have mine even
has little flower petals peeking out of
it oh lucky mine was just a can of
sardines
I'm sure they'll taste good with the
drink
hey bae you didn't forget the drinks you
made right the super spiky ones oh
button
are you talking about the
spiked once
oh so that's what they're called wait
but there's nothing spiky about them why
are they called that does it matter wait
I'm rambling you're not making any sense
dude oh and thanks for setting up the
party you guys did a really good job
with the decorations
uh
who's that over there huh
wait a minute Callie did you invite a
total stranger into the party oh the one
in the corner they're not hurting anyone
and I figured a little outside company
might make for a livelier get-together
you know
I've seen you a caffeine yeah
Duncan what are you doing here what
should we do with them guys they seem a
little uncomfortable now that we've
noticed them
I say the party goes on
[Music]
do you want a drink or something maybe
we should get outside and do something
more active since the party's almost
over
going outside
[Music]
come on there's a super nice cafe I
found recently we could take them there
oh yeah I remember we found it with Bay
in Japan they had the best hot chocolate
The Vibes are really chill and naturey
plants hanging from the ceiling and cute
flower arrangements
sounds pungent
okay I'll go
wanna come with us Bae ah actually we're
about to hit the theme park iris is
doing this big Valentine's Day concert
at kuji who tonight so sorry I'm gonna
have to sit out this one I'm back DJ so
my hands are tied too laters
hey if cafes aren't your thing do you
want to come hang out with us at the
show
[Music]
hey Detective still up for shopping and
Ginza later today oh sure I'm in gotta
take bubble for a walk first though we
could go to the park if you want would
be way better to have a friend come with
to make walking past all those smooching
couples a little less awkward
good point hey Corner person you look a
little lost
also like you could touch some grass
come with us to the park if you'd like
oh yeah hope you're good with dogs
you guys are gonna leave Ina and I to
clean all the dishes seriously watch
movies afterwards
hmm that does sound kind of fun
I told you I was gonna make your watch
guilds more guys with me eventually oh
yeah the one that Kelly's convinced was
made into jrpg oh that's the golden guys
oh well I'm down for either
yeah but where's this one gonna go what
are you gonna pick I would recommend
following your instinct and don't worry
no one's gonna be offended
an extra hand in the kitchen would
really help leftover cookies for whoever
stays to help yeah
[Music]
foreign