[Music]
[Applause]
oh hello hello we are back again day
four of seven days to die does that mean
we're on day four of seven I don't know
wait what day is it in game is it
normal
19 I think that's the normal I was
trying to get my timer right I don't
know I'm not I'm not
sure we'll just we roll with it it's
close
enough 3 days left to die oh
boy let me eat my snack I almost titled
the
stream was I going to title
it just a pumpkin bread girl in a bacon
and eggs
world I I don't
know I did make my pumpkin bread by the
way I didn't take a picture of it though
cuz it wasn't very
aesthetic but it was it was yummy it was
yummy I think I can improve on it though
I'm always nitpicking my baked
goods and snail licked a piece this
morning and you know what I still ate it
after he licked it I wasn't going to let
the slice go to
waste sourdough retry
maybe maybe I also made some caboa
Curry which I love I'm kind of on a
squash kick as you can see with this
pumpkin bread and squash Curry it's all
it's all squash all the way down not
Kucha Ka kab
Kucha kab
Kucha kaboa squash what did I call it
not
kombucha
kaboa yeah it's like a Japanese pumpkin
it's a yummy delicious squash oh my gosh
it's
GG said it right the first
time
kaboa
squash it's so good it's delicious I'm
in a very Fall
moon the hardest Nails pumpkin it was
really hard I had to put it in the oven
before I could chop it up into pieces
and scoop out its guts good practice for
today if you ask me I've got these
Knuckles wait this is for this is for
cie this book I should turn in my quests
hold on I'm going to join the the
VC
momentarily dissected the pumpkin I want
to carve a pumpkin you're look kind of
rough what did she say you didn't get
bit did you
no hold on um her eyes are up here
congratulations I actually make my
payment to the Duke now rewards bi
boo is
that am I logged into bio's
account what
happened rewards bioo is she the
reward oh it was bio's
Quest that's a big reward yeah what is
urban combat oh
it's it's the sexual tyranosaurus
one um I don't know if I need that I I
feel like nothing else here is that
good I don't know what this means and I
don't think I want to know these are Big
rewards are
they I'm not going to be smoking cigars
so reference I need
it okay
fine
o and cash and say I want to learn to
lockpick but this this is volume three I
need other volumes
right cigar is a helmet mod is it
they it it's hard without the perk Point
invested okay I'll get the bundle
then any jobs wait really is it cuz I
didn't do my
quest I'm not I don't have a quest limit
anymore
right okay sexual
tyrannosaurus
fists rifle World handy land
okay I've got too much stuff what level
is
my0 I can make level three
already level 36 to get the steel
Knuckles these are so expensive
though I miss level two they're so
expensive now maybe they're not they
seem expensive
okay let's see what what everybody else
is up
to nice nice welome hello I saw G over
there she was
hell welcome welcome I have lots of
magazines for people any shotgun mags I
have a rifle world is that different I
think Kara needs that one I have a
batter batter up yeah yeah yeah all you
want I have handy
[Music]
land an
explosive any you want do Quest we're
starting and you're right next to us
wait yes where are
you wait can
I yeah we're in the town that we were at
last
time
[Music]
where I'm going to do some other stuff
right now in the beginning do your thing
I'm on my way ready for quest later
thank you for your
services
yeah very excited well you're really
looting and shooting everything
huh do you want some wood
don't yeah I'll take your wood okay come
here and take my wood dear right here
for you swear to God
3,000 that was half my you want to make
one I'll get some more don't worry she's
full of wood I have so much
wood
cool cool it is kind of cool thank you
awesome
sauce they
got oh that's awesome sauce yeah let's
go wait wait wait take this
book oh is the baseball yes GG aren't
you reading tool books which books
handyland
um yeah this
one oh and it's a lumberjack one too
I've been reading these ones and then
the ones that improve the club or axe bi
aren't you reading harvesting rle
world oh no I'm a handgun oh you don't
want to read rifle world
I'll hold on to it since it seems like
you really want to give it to me and I
appreciate a
present what does rifle will do oh
wait I don't know what does it do I
don't know it's rifle crafting um I'll
just hold on to F you sniper rifles no
no I don't need sniper rifles that's
fine just the assault rifle
[Music]
magazine cuz those are for machine guns
too apparently yeah get them ladies yeah
good idea
[Music]
the closet oh he's got yellow eyes oh
[Applause]
he away okay cool I didn't stab you did
I no I don't think so
okay oh
hello think going up this way is better
the spikes are popping
off is this the deadly Spike
house nice good job
ladies what are you doing
zombie that was awesome I had something
for to read right here that was stupid
strong thank you there is a l stupid
strong kind of awesome this bat's broken
I agree my sledgehammer is broken too oh
nice feel like we're experiencing the
same things even though we were in
different
places
easy there's a lot of medical stuff in
here someone should take one of these
Med
kits oh oh barb wire oh yeah good idea I
wonder who would be a good choice
who's our everyone oh he's on
fire there zombies on fire oh charge
zombies now
huh okay it's fine I think we get byebye
zombies how many more left I wonder oh
there's a safe
here ooh you found a safe yeah
it I don't pick oh do you yeah can I see
it can you sure here I dropped it on the
ground ah they're all upstairs oh Yik
okay it will take me 15 seconds to
unlock this please defend me I'll defend
you thank you my life take my life B I
got your back oh dang all
right nice punching thank you nice
punches
[Music]
F oh boy okay I got it what's in there
it only had one molotov in it amazing
that's the saddest thing I've heard all
day and we're just getting
started pretty sad day bio do you use 9
mm ammo I do I have some do you craft
bullets too I am yes I do I have bullet
casings also I cuz I can hold on did
someone pick it up or did it
despawn plant flers wait what are you
talking about what thing there was 9 mm
ammo it
despawned it was it was only on the
ground for like a second I thought it
takes 20
minutes it's messed up game yo fun pimps
why why is that how it works fun pimps
where did it
go wow so much fun hey
not very fun from the fun
anyone working on like medicine and
stuff I have a book of how to make
bandages and stuff okay I'll give a
couple of us are so maybe give it to
fauna I think it would be
good yeah I think everybody having a
little medical skills probably for the
better just to make decent
bandages okay yeah I think I can CRA the
fun pimp for hide in the
fun who is that
Callie are you going to use
sledgehammers in the future probably yes
right cuz it's big I don't really think
sledgehammers are in my build I'm pretty
sure it's just bats and shotgun oh it's
just bats okay I have a
sledge hammers right okay I'll save that
for you yeah Kar is getting hammered oh
nice oh nice idea yeah now they're going
to break it
down watch out before he vomits on they
are police they're police the vomit oh
oh wow you're so strong This Bat is so
broken but I'm also very high level with
the skill so you going to
move I think the server is lagging oh
yeah maybe I'm help help everybody's
Moon walking in place help oh
God I'll take it that was silly oh fun
oh here you go walking
um what's here pipes just pipes oh
there's ammo on the top of here there's
an ammo pile I got it uh shotgun and
Crossbow parts but I don't really think
we need those everyone's so
noisy guys want to go uh turn in the
quest maybe get another okay well
actually there's there's uh clear for
Gigi and Fa here there's oh sure both
nearby Quest yeah g is really nearby
lead the
way I think it's over
here lead the way and then both parties
split completely oh
no I think it's the same house first
really quick and
then can we even do it though right now
there might be a cool down so maybe we
should do the one Gigi wants to do ew I
ate a bad sandwich and now I have the
poopies oh no I have
te would like some tea that would help a
lot I'm on my way oh thank you do you
want any more sandwiches before you
drink the tea oh God I don't want I
didn't like it it made me sick you can
min max your sandwich
intake oh gosh yeah eat another sandwich
no I
always no no more sand sandwiches I I've
been in the condition to hate sandwiches
now because they gave me diarrhea that
way time so now I hate sandwiches I raw
meat have is raw meat yeah this Quest
isn't available until 1413 oh okay let's
go to fa's one then okay F's got a
quest is it over here wait no it's not
it's
somewhere byebye
diarrhea that guy's freaking me out over
there yeah why he look like that let him
let him see
just straight Savage me I've eaten raw
meat before in
Japan
IA DC oh
yeah dokey just don't
newspapers wait crazy there's books
here really archery
book where archery
for you
yay oh here take I have a bunch of Arrow
stuff please take it thank
you rattle them girls let's do it here's
archery
yummy yummy This Bat is so
strong oh do I push HP do I st I think
so is your quest I've never done my own
Quest before
first time another people's Quest yeah
time to kill them all and sometimes it's
forgetting
quest for
hello ow sorry please don't Smack me oh
I am di no no way no way did my bat
really hurt you yeah I think you smacked
me too hard oh
no maybe I should perish too as no no no
no no no keep your class keep your class
no I think you should we demand a fair
trial tells it how it is it's okay I
needed to be punished for all the times
I've killed everyone anyway so this is
just my own retribution a lot of people
maybe we have to turn off friendly fire
from
here we we
could oh we know we shouldn't we should
n you don't think so because sometimes
people want to be killed like when fauna
killed Cecilia because Cecilia wanted
that's true oh there are there are
flaming men upstairs be careful flaming
men
[Music]
Hallelujah I'm glad I wasn't with you
girls cuz my internet just died and
kicked me out
no it's fall behind no no I said oh no
oh
no I hit you I see how strong that bat
is one hit one hit dead if you hit them
in the head
be more upstairs yeah it is part of the
experience did you girls hear why CeCe
can't join us today because he's drunk
she's too drunk that's so funny oh yeah
she's playing she she took 100 sips more
than 100 100 SI I heard3 yeah 130 130
sips of what I I wonder of of a cocktail
we need to hang out
more incredible Jin
Jin sip isn't Jin really strong not not
I wouldn't really I think that whiskey
would be a little more
oh whiskey would probably be a little
more intense but I have a tummy egg with
the poopies cuz I ate a sandwich oh no I
don't have do you need tea I don't have
te I don't need tea do I have anything
that help the stomach ache here you go
that'll help you oh thank you wait eat
some more sandwiches first okay okay let
me sandwiches and then take
it some you have to min max your hunger
yeah yeah all right time to take my tea
shell M yummy is anybody working on
Salvage tools at all um let me
check Salvage tools I have 12 on Salvage
tools oh oh okay I'll give it to you um
can you use heavy
armor oh I use heavy armor or I she will
she will here you go I have heavy armor
for you oh which one is it a helmet oh I
think I already have a helmet I that one
yeah it's you can hold on to ites anyone
else a
helmet take a helmet I probably should
oh thank you I probably should preure
hat not going to
lie but it's so dang
cool you kind of can't like an old rock
star oh I know have that did you guys
already finish that first Quest yes yeah
oh prob we have we have more there's a
there's a Gigi clear nearby oh yeah you
could do that really I'm just going to
quickly build myself a new machine gun I
think and then I'll come over
[Music]
okay going to be
bodybuilder do you think we can start
your quest now or we have to wait we can
start
it it should be there
now oh she's Speedy I want SL my ear
what you can't pick up a bike if it has
stuff in the storage yeah you can't it's
okay you can just ride it ride it in
part
no one's going to pick it up really what
if someone does steal it I'll take it
don't
worry that's what
I I'll make you a new one if someone
takes it I'll give you
mine oh we can we can share a b the
wives can share a bicycle we need you
can lock your bicycle you can you can
lock your bicycle and enter a code for
it and I don't think people can steal
your bike your bike yeah there's a lot
function that's amazing tell me your
bike code now no it's 11 one1 what a
good bike code the typical whole Live
password you can get into all of our
social media accounts if you just type
in 1111 one one11 is very secure mhm oh
yeah come on give it a try hack
us 111 is the
password they're going to get us locked
out of our iPad for a year
oh no not the iPads no my iPad code is
different though it's very funny that
you guys stiny man oh my
God he's going to vomit head with my B
how I I already finished my Quests for
today how that mean can I give you my um
a bandage if I hit you pleas maybe as an
ing game today so then maybe yeah cuz it
was 6:00 a.m. when we ended last night
oh God there's a lot of big pop here are
you kidding
me way that I one shot him oh my gosh
you're a
menace what it had to be a critical hit
wait is there's someone in The Walking
Dead with like a terrifying baseball bat
like that like a villain there is uh who
was it oh yeah Negan yeah yeah and he
kills a bunch of characters that I love
yeah yeah yeah spoilers just kidding
well you don't know what characters I
love B trees oh okay what I'm call
Lucille in negan's
honor yeah cuz his bat's name is
Lucille yeah the trees you planted in
front of our house conceal our house so
much it's it's hard to find the house
now and it's hard to find an exit and an
entrance it's don't worry I'll chop them
down once I come back please
do I let you take care of it I don't
want to kill
you I also don't want to stab you to
death you will you found a fake wall oh
yeah
machine smart fa's got better eyes who
has a tummy ache I hear it you hear my
T I didn't hear anything do it again I
hear them do it again this be actually
hold
up please
this could be a fake wall need that
Golden Rod tea I'm okay oh
hello oh this isn't a fake is it oh ow
the spikes do
[Music]
hurt huh what's that noise oh oh
someone's using the
defibrator after the spikes I really
hurt you need a bandage fa oh I had a
kit okay so you're good I'm good for
[Applause]
now I'm level
well let's
see we did it now I can get y
Yay good job team now we can return yeah
get those tasty oh there's some farmer
boots in here if anybody wants farmer
boots any Farmers that need
boots oh sure cat and boots and
cats boots and cats and boots and cats
and boots and cats and boots and cats
boots and cats we're in a zombie
apocalypse um until I suck on your lips
yeah yeah yeah yeah swag swag swag on
you she's aing by a fire while we sing
fond lyrics that have never been
TP are you a toilet sitter you can't be
on our team if you
are toilet sitters my favorite all
there's some loot up here I have no more
room though so if anybody wants it feel
free to take it no worries I'm heading
back to the trader you have to go home I
have so much stuff in my pockets I need
to go home too I have like a bunch of
Band-Aids which I would like to
share Oo we will need those are you just
offloading them on us no I'm worried I'm
worried about People's Health ouch are
you really sharing
them I'm worrying about everyone's
Health you
know how
kind I reached a quest limit for today
too
who's the
Duke all of these kind of suck Jenifer
I'm sorry but it's kind of bad yeah but
look at her chest that's the only reward
we need didn't didn't you want her to
like be into and now you're like dissing
her no she's just she gave me some silly
items and I don't really know how I feel
about
him uh let's see structural brace mod I
don't really need I don't really care
about decoration
though
Wonder
hole
n oh waited head Mod's pretty good what
does that
do um it says it adds a chance to stun
and slow victims oh am I already have
that I'll grab it for somebody else then
if that's the case okay we got some more
things
[Music]
oo this is good actually weapon
flashlight
mod can you put it on your bat The
Shining bat of Justice I
wish well maybe on the next shotgun I
can
do this see seems pretty
good I'm hungry
actually I know I need to go home to
cook
stuff yeah big
hunger staring I've got the best well
that was fast she's got grilled meat
though and corn wait I'm full on oops I
bought it
inventory on inventory
I'm full on
inventory I love the taste of
inventory for these
spawns I feel like if we do another 10
quests with her or do all of her quests
will she give us a motorcycle
maybe that's why I kind of really want
to do a bunch of quests I don't know
she'll give us something good
though something good
is a cooling mesh mod
good um not really because it'll take
you your your uh your armor only has
like a limited amount of slots so I see
like Bigger Pockets mod and stuff is
better I
think am I not done with Quest I think I
am I don't know if there's I can really
give her feeling a bit
days I have ammo for you
oh than you
iron there's really no reason to even
sell her things if she can't just take
all the
inventory what's wrong with you woman
looking for a little pain relief my God
I hate her you ha
no I would never say that about my
life SM give me a
sec I got to make some of those armor
kits now soon for gaha would you like a
mod for melee weapons that lower
degradation by
25% I'm okay I'm not too worried about
degradation thank you very much though I
appreciate it I'll put it on my axe or
something then yeah yeah go for it you
can definitely make good use of it and
then this I'm going to put maybe on my
current shotgun even though it kind of
sucks I am sorry you right in front of
me I tabed back in are you drinking
again I'm sorry dear I didn't mean to
punch you don't tell anyone okay okay I
won't you want to you want to ride home
together okay are you coming home we're
coming home yes yepe what are you coming
home for I had to offload stuff and cook
I guess okay so many things I will do
quests I need to go home too though cuz
I have too much stuff yeah okay what is
the best way to get home a quick trip
home might be a good idea
um where even is
home so North well there's this main
road we could
take well we could take the main
and then go west and then go
north okay where'd you go come back I
went into
the okay let's go this
way aren't you so curious what's in here
yeah I guess so I'm working our working
our legs
yeah getting swoll ever skipping leg day
to fall
well when your girls come home and
offload and you're done with everything
then I'm ready to do quests anytime
okay I don't know which way this way
probably up oh maybe this way if the
bike can even go up it it just takes a
while you know cuz it's really it's
rough oh my God I mean but at that point
why not just no
no but then how will you increase your
Viking skill
oh you guys are going the up pathway
okay I'll come too I'm almost there guys
CES yo can Trader Jen get us a mountain
bike please yeah oh
gosh jeez my gosh I'm just going to run
goodness gracious
me this is just like yoi
pedal what is what is yoi pedal yo
it's exactly what you imagine it it's I
don't know what to imagine can you
please explain in great detail so I can
visualize it in my head um bunch of yahi
and they're pedaling on bikes oh it's
not
really I guess what how would you
explain it what it's called yoa Mushi
petal ahuh wait but how would you know
that it's yoi petal if that wasn't a
good description of it
how would you know that's what she's
talking
about I think it's a really
good I know how you think so is there
yoi on pedals
yes well no but but yes kind of I mean
if you really if you look at it that way
I guess wait can I drink from this Lake
really quick yeah do you need any I will
watch you are you thirsty
I don't think I am but I would like a
second what what is it called I would
like to share your
hat she's
drowning don't worry about it does
anybody need
water okay okay bought a couple actually
I would like to sip sip so that way I
don't waste the water that's in my
inventory okay here you go an indirect
kiss oo
okay I speaking of yoi I need a
freehand take my corn
seed
delicious Mikes are so silly in this
game they really aren't that much faster
but they are F but it saves your stamina
true my stamina is still like zero but
it's it's fine all right bi boo take
this hat for drinking water thank you I
will go to the exact same spot that you
drank at so it would be more of an
indirect Kissy Kissy yeah it's more
intimate yes she's going out of her way
see I think she sip sip like right
here I can still I can still see the
water is still warm I don't know why
it's
warm oh delicious
SI yummy my eyes PE hint of hint of G
this is
gigg it's like water it's like flavored
water where it's like you run a run a
fruit over a faucet and then that's what
it tastes like that's that's it ran over
yes a fruit and a
faucet I'm eating blueberry here you go
thank you thank you
anab
potato in the fridge in the fridge
eating things right
now yo can get some cooking some more of
this meat cuz we have a ton of raw meat
we have 52 ra I will
cook some more Cooks in the kitchen
great I'm going to eat do we have do we
have eggs cuz oh there's a bird what the
heck I'm out of there
oh my God there's a lot of
birds getting out of
here is it really
Birds nice zombes wait I hear I hear
more there's more oh my gosh you're
shooting them out of the
sky get them Ratt okay they're going to
give me a bad
[Music]
reputation we need better representation
of birds in this
game what was I you okay yeah I'm just
taking out my
anger wait I want to I'll get you your
party invite mailbox oh thank you you're
welcome yeah I got kicked out twice
already out of this game and out of the
internet wait do you read Magnum
enforcer I do here you go thank you what
was that I love how you ask as though
it's like we're subscribed to certain me
that we are right oh
Noe no
you zombie bird let's let's get out of
here before more birds CH I'm stuck on
the
mailbox and I can't pick my bike up cuz
it's little
stuff oh no who built this
Forest yeah who bu maybe maybe we can we
can we can smack the mailbox to death
yes okay let's smack the wait I got it I
got it okay oh yeah Ma magazines huh
hold on hold on I'll I'm free I'm free
okay okay thank
you oh
no oh shoot I am pretty I don't have for
this water I'm
fine just open your mouth collect the
water yourself with your mouth why is
that not possible I'm very mad about
that I know I know right
I wish we could turn snowballs into
water right I'm going to go get armor
plates so that I can make those armor
kits so I can get a nerd hat from
Kiara oh yeah we have to prepare for the
The Raid wait do it's on the 21st so we
have the the old house is pretty
reinforced still I think yeah it's going
to be a tier three
raid yeah
yeah I think the old base is still
pretty well reinforced you know if it
a't broke don't fix it but M I still
want to go get a little up close and
personal with some of the zombies yeah
get some
XP yeah we should try to craft as many
nerd hats as we can yeah
definitely I was not watching the
road don't don't text and ride everybody
I was watching you then I also hit the
car so far this
traitor I have one armor parts I think
that you just need
one uh for what for the nerd hat yeah um
let's see we need need for the nerd hat
in order for me to make it on level
three it's free our crafting kits if you
just want it on level one I can make it
for you for one crafting kit like
apparently it really
correlates yeah I think it would be
better to make it on a higher level if
you can get more armor crafting kits
okay I could have sworn we had
more you can make them but pretty simple
ingredients but we're currently always
lacking duct tape why are the birds
still fall
why duct tape and I'm putting it back
there I see you biking with two birds
overhead another
one what this
sound we just brought the desert back
with
us they're knocking oh wait is this the
house really loudly oh yeah it's our
house oh get rid of those
trees for God's sake duct tape from the
old house
tree I don't want to see these trees
anymore o it is night time can you still
make glue from Bones and duct tape
actually I'll make her some new ones
right
now better just
kidding could have sworn I had
glue my iron sled was cancel
why what I'll take it with
me all right time for a very frightening
bike ride back to the new
house what is that does anyone have
[Music]
eggs yeah that's what I was thinking we
can make bacon and eggs with all of them
I think we have a lot of eggs at the old
house oh the spikes did not really
affect him huh I will look for eggs
ah shiny eyed
zombie where punch him the moat with
spikes came in handy I will if I can
find the entrance to our house I will
direct him to
it I'm on the road ladies uhoh I found
some spikes
I he's here he's here oh God he's fast
he's coming into our house he's chasing
me he's chasing me
easy I feel like I'm breaking our
house there we go so
scary nothing to be scared
about
a moment thisiss get rid of the
[Music]
trees my character's so hungry I hope
you guys are grilling some meat um oh I
have for you hey chefs
we need eggs where are you looking I'm
on the way to the new house I guess we
could make regular grilled meat but is
it worth it I don't think it's worth it
we have so many eggs at the old house
that bacon and eggs would be so much
better can we get an an egg delivery oh
God I'm turning
around EG you I'm turning
around what happened to my armor is is
crazy
does that mean it's critically
damaged we have some baked potatoes and
grilled corn in here that's good I might
eat some of that hide you
over
yeah well we're waiting for the good
stuff
right hey Chef all right I'll be
waiting we have one bacon and eggs
I guess I shouldn't have been just
fisting those eggs in my mouth I guess
are you still eating raw
eggs I I was doing it to prove a
point I asked her if she wanted to see
me eat these six raw eggs and then I
did that's three bacon and eggs
think of how much breakfast we could
have had could have had so much
breakfast Gigi sorry I'll stop forgive
you stop eating those eggs raw see how
you have a problem I can't help so much
protein you've made your point don't
worry G okay I'll stop eating the raw
eggs please no more this isn't Japan you
can't just do that I have a tummy
egg I'm not surprised 13 13 eggs here
we got 13 I'm going go put some of this
oh you can you should check the cooking
pot uh at the house or the one of the
cooking pots cuz I think I was cooking a
bunch of bacon and eggs before oh yeah
so you might want to check if you were
there's five and there's there you go
you can go ahead and take it and bring
it over if You' like okay I'm going to
eat one of these bacon and eggs okay
there myself alive okay and then I'll
bring the rest of everything over oh how
many any armor parts do I need for the
Hat kiaha uh if you wanted on level
threee then free exctly I have three oh
nice what else do you need uh the rest I
can take care of myself okay I'll give
it to you don't go get I'm I'm in the
house in the
kitchen in the real kitchen where
there's no cooking should be done
he no cooking is happening whatsoever
yeah
okay and then I'll take
my forged iron and the leather nerd hat
is wait did I pick it up you gave me
free armor kits I
did where did they
go oh was it oh maybe I gave you armor
parts oops oh yeah I guess so oh I think
that's you can have them back okay let's
see how you make armor kits you need
sewing and duct tape I actually have
some duct tape for you bi boo I just
need to get some glue oh no I have I I
have the other things too I'll make them
quickly okay okay okay wow W armor shop
I stole your duct in the old house just
so you know so I owe you free duct
tap we need duct tape more duct tape oh
I can craft duct tape I have a bun ofo
and we just need glue I do need oh wait
I can just make duct tape too I
think yeah I'm simple ingredient
y can never have
enough true
enough I like how this game brings you
to like even later in the game you keep
on needing simple ingredients that you
get early in the game yeah even the
simplest things like claw fragments and
stuff like that it all has a
purpose yeah which is nice I prefer that
to always learning about new items and
never need eting the old ones
yeah for sure okay I'm almost there I've
got a delivery of eggs and okay I have
the kits for you okay I'll go back to
the kitchen I'm here I'm here you my had
two
k okay we'll all be nerds nerds we'll be
so cute oh no I made a mistake and put
away my
letter where did my letter go
quick there it is okay zombies
here
crafting and finish you're going to look
so cute
yay where are you rid of my preacher
here put this on
oops oh from there do I look cute oh wow
I didn't know you had such a beard you
don't I look cute cute oh my gosh you
guys match look at you look at you am I
cute do you cute cute those
glasses
perfect hey they're having a fashion
show without
me we're matching we're matching
mustache wait I have cool facial hair
too please well I already know your
mustache it's very thick it's very cool
you know it well don't you it's so in
style yes it's very scratchy for
smooches you're such a fashionist all
the ladies I want the person who dug
this hole in front of the Traer
[Applause]
dead no it's
funny I I want to meet them I would love
to meet them and shake their hand and
give them a smile and tell them how good
it
is the hole Yeah the hole ah yes it's a
good hole it is the best hole Yeah ni
you can hide in that what are you doing
now giggy oh I'm hitting trees enjoying
life
beer you never have I'm looking for a
nest oh somebody's screaming oh oh yeah
there's a screamer I heard that too
actually oh whoopsies that's me ow here
they come
oh yeah coming towards our
[Music]
house I will help defend the new
home help are they help I'm out outside
I'm out I'm here to help you thank you
oh my God
it's need more
stamina oh there's a lot jeez let's go
oh they really are oh my God oh my
God
ow
ouch
ooh I'm infected too a little bit little
bit just a little bit
0.4% not that
bad nothing a little honey
C wa see we're a great team I like this
action I wanted some exp bring me more
oh there's more I hear more you ask for
more you shall receive Kiara where's it
coming from
alive sounds so
close on the ground he's over here I'm
just having a snack break really quick
so hard to see yeah he's chilling in the
grass sorry didn't see you down there
hey gaha I have the materials for the
nerd hat you do nerd hat so popular all
right yay yeah your special Kiara brand
nerd hat here's I will get to it right
away thank you so that you can show off
your nerdiness
proudly for too
long let's see I also have the
eggs
ingredients that's okay I got you I will
just zombie it up don't don't become a
zombie not had finished but then your
your current hat what's going to happen
to that it's almost broken so it's fine
a
okay well well this will be hopefully of
good use to you ooh and I can put my mod
my intelligence mod on it to make it
extra nerdy ooh intelligence mod what
does that on my preure hat I don't
really know what it does I don't really
know if it's even helpful but I'll take
it byebye preacher hat let's see why am
I fatigued maybe I will make this for
this is so silly
oil hey guys why am I
fatigued are you tired SW you swung too
hard now you need a little nap the
bullet is
eepy I guess you need vitamins maybe
maybe vitamins will
help oh yeah we have some I'll eat a
couple oh uh K I have this for you parts
for later since I think you're using
hammers oh thank you thank you are there
steel steel
steel I get so many steel Sledgehammer
Parts I eat this if anybody finds
machine gun parts please let me know I
just need one more okay I wonder if
there are any at the old house I'm
pretty sure I saw I checked I checked no
there was
um uh not enough not enough that's rough
dang it yeah some glue
um is coffee
good um it gives you a buff I forget
what buff it gives you but it gives you
something coffee yeah coffee gives you
stamina regen 20% oh that's good s is
good does it fill your water or does it
make you dehydrated no it makes you it
feels your thirst it
does and pipe shotgun is not even so
maybe maybe we should be making drinks
with the with the empty water than just
drinking straight water glue maybe yeah
glue is what cuz I have a ton of cloth
there's like 91 cloth I have more glue I
have a couple more
glues oh nice cuz that oh glue glue is
water too wow everything needs water huh
oh I might make some glue
oh good
idea I have 30 glue oh you can get all
the skills one level earlier with the
intelligence mod so it's very nice mod o
co I'm going to make my sledgehammer
cause some sick Burns today cuz it's
going to light on fire yeah I want to
see it in action I want to see it too I
can actually show it off earlier
probably making it right
nowes constantly on
fire ammo thank
you look look fa look my sledgehammer
it's on fire oh it is did you put it in
the fire yeah I I honestly don't know
why it's how it does that but it's fun
hey kiaha you're making armor right I
don't really know if this will be useful
to you but I feel like you should you
should take it
and oh yeah I mean anybody can put that
on their armor to make their armor
stronger I think yeah oh yeah matter
hold well you can have it oh oh but ah
this is the schematic too I see never
mind I'll I'll learn that yeah yeah I
shall
learn okay
I want to do
Quest okay I'll do a quest with you I'm
ready I'm ready for quest really
yipp I going to come home drop stuff off
and um we can go to the new Trader
okay I don't have any uh quests
personally but I'll just do whatever you
girls have I think there is an active
Quest but I don't know who activated it
it's 88 M away I have I have a tier 2
infestation and then Gigi also has a
tier 2 infestation up oh nice well let's
go do those perfect 4 a.m. okay does
anybody use clubs
yes here I think I have a mod that you
could use ooh uh I dropped it in the
right
here metal Chain O the chains yeah
people have been wanting me to use the
chains so thank you I brought home eggs
I have five five eggs and 20
eat good job oh thank you our bread
winner providing for the
family that's I accidentally put who he
is everything into my inventory on
accident
[Music]
bye
welcome I woke up on our buk
bed we're going to help but we are uh
baby that it doesn't look like the house
is clean uh we have a new
house I figured baby uh do you want me
to come pick you
up it's night time no it's 4:00 a.m.
you're fine yeah yeah and you guys can
on our team and get the dogs we're going
to go and find you if you if you look at
the map and zoom out like really far you
can see a bunch of our names on the map
and that's that's new house location
okay we'll go on a
quest that's not that far it should be
that
do I'm going to go towards the the tier
2 quests the in the
desert is anyone learning how to lock
pick no oh I think I would like to okay
here you go thank you but why lockpick
when we can just Brute Force open
everything by just apparently there are
saves that that won't work with I had to
lock food so it might be nice to have
going to go on a
journey everybody oh is it okay I see at
the old home here there's a bunch of
magazines and animals and stuff yeah you
can use whatever can I take everything
at Old home or is it still um we're
going to we're going to go back there
for the raid um so maybe leave some
resources but whatever you need you can
take okay yeah just stopped
the we'll go on our joury then okay and
then come by we have a
question sure make sure to take of the
Traer if you
want good okay
[Music]
we do we have any honey Now by any
chance no I'm still infected too
a you can buy it from the trader
actually he just charges too much lady
she charges less I think oh
really she's so
nice yeah she's a nice lady she wants us
I could get used to she wants it so
bad yeah I'll just get some tree
stumps on the way to the desert or
whatever that place is yeah I'm sure
you'll find some honey have better r
left than me have you been looking for
it
to for theone I'm good now but whenever
I do need it it just doesn't pop out of
the stops M yeah it's a little bit rare
yeah okay so I'm going to go there
whenever you girls are ready we're going
to do Quest there right ready all right
I'm on the
way water yes yes yes so we can stay
strong for as long as possible yes and
some bandaids are there tree stumps in
the burnt area as well or should I check
in the I think I did see
some but I'm not exactly sure but
there's a lot of
trees maybe a barely surrounding the
area if I see any I'll try and break
them
okay I wonder how much percentage until
you die from
the from
the sickness illness 100 okay well then
I got a lot of time I I found a couple
stumps I'll crack them open for you okay
see find any
honey was that where honey is in stumps
yes yeah I need a stronger
axe wait where are you I'm still on
quality one ax we're heading for the
infation quest I have quality 5
a quality 5 wow
man you're a beaver huh I am a beaver I
can make iron tools now too but I
haven't touched the bench you're the
tool
Master yeah for my Beaver activities now
you need to like truly RP and bite them
with your
teeth yeah yeah yeah just like that ah
infection is everyone
infected you mean you're going to get
infected yeah once I bite them
I'm sorry Kiara my luck is just so bad I
opened up the stumps but there was
nothing in it's
okay I'll probably die anyway after I
think after a certain percentage uh
honey doesn't work anymore and then you
need antibiotics as oh okay oh can we
craft that well maybe
someday maybe someday feel like we
crafted that before so after
5% honey doesn't work anymore what oh oh
well then I kind of want to find honey
right now oh tree
stump I think I would like to find some
honey
too I found one a tree stump
please oh no my character's hungry and I
didn't bring any meat dang it oh I've
got dang
it oh really oh Chef really thank
you oh no it's does work it just removes
5% I got honey okay I see hey good job
gu also I have two Hammer magazines for
you Hammer crafting y you can take them
thank you did you put it in like a box
or so no I'm just waiting for you at the
location oh I'm coming now Quest now
that I have my honey I will
hurry decided to get rid of these
magazines oh my gosh that's trading
magazin is so fun yeah it's everybody
has like a different specialty yeah
that's why I kind of appreciate that
we're not like 20 people or so in this
collab because then I feel like I would
lose oversight of who needs what and now
we have such clear roles and it's really
comfy yeah I like this
group me too me too yeah usually I don't
play like a killer in games like the the
really physically strong ones so this is
new for me but have F what do you
normally do
food cooking or something like that yes
thank you how about some bacon and eggs
Rando stuff oh my gosh my chef a
blueberry
pie yes chef thank you Chef you have a
bandaid here have a Band-Aid just in
case I'm visualizing it right now in my
brain I'll take your bandaids
for I'll take your band
snake a snake there's a snake
I'm going to punch
it I'm
thirsty
snake what is that Chad why why am I
laughing at my
ligma ligma yeah I have an icon that's
laughing at
the
radiation I guess because I'm laughing
because it's going
away yeah of course that's definitely
the only reason that it's it's laughing
okay
weird okay I'm kind of in the area now
what's
Lima what is Lima stop you it's a very
serious
illness that cannot be cured
normally how do you cure
ligma yeah how do you you know it you
know
it I don't think I do I've never heard
of it before
[Music]
jobs who's that oh huh oh wait how do we
get huh Zoomers these days don't even
know okay I said it someone had to say
it Lima balls lima lima
balls oh this time it's you sacrificing
yourself thank you you're welcome boo do
you have any
Band-Aids I do okay there's a bird Watch
Out w please wa so right click works for
the sledgehammers
too who is that over there I'm getting
chased by a hog killing I
help don't
miss wait stop
running I don't want it to bite me it's
dead one hit down the road H
yay Yum Yum Yum are you guys going
infestation or bio infestation get
chased by a pig of them we are at B boo
infestation wait that's your arrow
infestation of bi Boos yes yeah so many
of her s good get
infested and then we'll do GG's okay and
then I want to I really want to go check
on the Twins and make sure that they're
ready for the the apocalypse so I'm
going to go talk to them after okay okay
we can start preparing in the old house
for yes we need to prepare as well cuz
tomorrow is the chosen day chosen day
the dawn of the final day this is so
strong I'm looting a pig real quick okay
looting a pig yeah so much
meat okay you don't like that I'm
looting this Pig please don't leave
the please don't do my best
just get the meat just get the
meat I'll keep my thoughts to myself
what are you thinking about the pig no
no no they're funny share
them thought thought you didn't want me
to I only pretend like I don't want you
to it's really I speak in opposite speak
which is really annoying okay so you
want me to lose the
pig oh yeah I'll get your bone and meat
you guys got some water all right
yes yeah I have some
water sorry I'm going the wrong way just
water do from the tap is fine I don't
want to pay extra for water just give me
tap
water thank you what does this look like
oh it's
chain all right you guys ready so ready
are you done looting the pig yeah but
now I'm lost I'm almost there okay I
think I'm almost there you're here I'm
here let's get started yippe finally
Quest yippe kill them all yipp oh we
could break it
or find the open door different
door ah dang
it they tried to board up this house huh
H why do they need us to clear out these
infestations because like no one's there
anymore what's the point the houses
don't have a point yeah want to make
livable
again ow did I oh down the
door down a door oh I would love to
break down a door we're so in oh they're
in the way cash there's actually so many
they're alive they're here they're very
much
alive and on
fire my hammer takes so much to swing
keep up the good work everyone help
help okay almost died are you okay oh no
you have a
bandaid I'll need a bandaid later here's
a Band-Aid oh thank
you a best ni best girl work
done bio looks so funny with the hat and
the beard H zombies fear me oh there's
an AK machine gun oh P
sound a l
of I just opened the door and you
stabbed me I didn't know I'm bleeding
you Instinct take this forgive her I
have thank you I will use this bandage
to empty here and also yeah your health
is low so use a regular bandage too hold
up let me see I'm sorry I drew blood
from my friends thank you no problem
heal
yourself is someone up there oh be okay
me and F are up here I don't know if
there's any more bad guys maybe the
closed door is always a bad sign more
yeah I have ammo for you oh wow okay
thank you I'll get shooting
then no mercy is this a new cat picture
there's an
upstairs o cat picture new cat I'm not
sure if we've seen this they love the
cat
pictures uhoh I've seen that one orange
cat behavior oh maybe we did see
it it's a good cat yes every cat is good
cat there are no such things as demon
cats I agree
agreed they're all perfect angels yes we
the ones that are not worthy of the cats
there's a hole where's the last
zomie H probably down the hole come on
jumie who's a good jumie who's a good
jumie yes you
are oh maybe it's down
no do you guys see an orange dot I do
see an orange Dot
that might be where it is it's upstairs
somewhere cuz it's pointing up second
floor ceiling
zombie oh no it's second floor second is
this second floor I don't is the do
really going to a zombie it seems like
it's pointing
outside that's a little strange maybe
the zombie is outside oh I think it's a
bird outside oh yeah on top of the other
I didn't see a bird oh there's a bird
out there hello
yay okay this Quest is complete complete
nice job
ladies bit thirsty okay are we going to
go straight to the next Quest yeah uh
yeah it's right below us okay below
below also is it possible for uh Kiara
to repair my bat at a workbench possibly
uh I think with a repair I think you
just need your repair kit mhm okay just
do and you can do it yourself here let
me let me give it give you one o you
have a repair kit bioo thank you yeah
app okay and I use it at a workbench
right no no you just uned your weapon
and there option to repair it repair I
see thank you B your Lifesaver yeah than
you so much
nice that's huge uh which Quest are we
going to uh tier two infestation gigy
yeah yeah it's just down the
road almost
there I'm almost there too I'm getting
wood oh no she wood in case we need it
you have a wood you know
serious wood addiction this bat's so
cool I'm I'm I'm there Tree House how
sweet not when I'm done with
it she's going to no think of the
children you're going to watch me do
this are you going to dismantle it
you're going to watch me do
this no I like this treeh house
no you actually hurt me look at the
ground
can't at
that try again God is
gracious again do it again do it
again how many times do you need to F
the tree house to be satisfied Gigi they
cannot have a tree house not when I'm
around want to
be no the sh
it
get
coming shooting me stop shooting
me I I wanted to help oh no God being
melee is
suffering it is feel that I've got N9 HP
all right I have a I can it it I have
thank
you God blowing on it does that help it
help it should it
should I hear it helps helps me kind of
house is this what were they doing here
so much
kissing what have I done super I've lost
myself
not the same person anymore this zombiie
stuff is getting to
me I'm becoming one of them it's okay I
beat FAA earlier too I why would you
beat your wife I didn't mean to I just
lost myself found a couple there
punching
bag take the shotgun ammo there's
there's a ton of B boo ammo and Kiara
ammo in this ined Cas that's yellow up
here thank you shotgun Messiah oh God he
oh why did I miss so hard he's also a
really good are the shotgun
shells I'll take
them also GG do you also use a shot oh
my
God okay it's so noisy it is
oh what a big family a pipe machine
gun yes where's beo there's a ton of 9mm
ammo in this yellow crate here I'm
upstairs I'll come down after you know
I'll grab it for
you there's a lot of there's a lot of
things in the house right now kind of
occupied the house I I broke the door
that's the are getting more intricate
oh
yeah what is this for are they
protecting themselves from
us could be floor is unless the family
that turned into
Z oh
wow the heck is going on I want to get
rid of this oh oh oh are you guys
destroying more
floors no no I'm not trying to it's
doing it on its own really upstairs
okay I was thinking is there an upstairs
it must be there has we're not done yet
does anybody have any dirty water I can
drink oh my leg have
water I'll drink might be some toilet I
checked the toilet
already okay inside the
house here's some dirty water
upstairs leg H you have to be able to
get upstairs maybe yeah where's the last
zombie maybe it's a bird again if I want
to get somewhere I'm going to get there
so I'm going to make a little makeshift
stairwell mhm outside sounds
good did you grab all the ammo where was
the ammo did you say
I am holding on to it now okay
okay I don't see an orange dot
anywhere where could this zombie be
hiding actually why am I picking up so
many
things let's eat okay I am on the second
floor if you want to join me I made a
little stairwell out oh here here you
are sir oh I see I
see oh wow quit and he's on
fire that zombie on
fire oh is this a stair who are good at
[Laughter]
jumping I can't jump that high I tooki
I'll let you girls check it out we can
stay down here there's a whole lot of
dudes and they're very strong oh really
so many yeah send them down push them
down oh that was it huh good job team
yeah yay more more more more more Quest
more Quest here are you guys' ammo by
the way B Kiara thank you you guys want
a ton of ammo a butt ton I got a butt
ton this is for Bio okay and this is for
KI where is she where is this beautiful
pink-haired woman Oh you mean pinkhair
pink mustache
lad are you on the roof still not not
you there oh oh oh are you down there
mariara yeah all right I'll bring it to
you if you're down you're the bottom
floor I'm down for it yes so I guess the
only way to get up here is by making a
stairwell outside now leave it to
me yay all right let's
see where was are you destroying the car
yeah what for do we get parts or so yeah
cocky
Chum that's for you
thank you so ammo I'm swimming in
ammo all right I need to make a new axe
new stone
axe
wow it's just satisfying oh we don't get
to pick it up no I have an armor book
for
you I take I
take I have a cooking book for you nice
exchange thank you thank
you
cheesecake have a cake the world is
saved let's go I'm so happy cheesecake
will be our savior anybody find any
baseball magazines I do love no I have
seed and
medical okay well if you find a baseball
one you know who to call
who
Ghostbusters you no
Ghostbusters hey o raid in the cafe I
think somebody's been
here it
do well let's see what time is it why so
broken we can go back to the Traders and
then turn in this quest after all start
preparing for the thing oh there's a
safe in here
already oh I have lock picks maybe we
can get another Quest when we turn it in
yes more quests more
Quest okay oh I'm in the wrong house
okay I'm
coming there's a
safe I do feel
safe what do you mean ask for the AK-47
does somebody have an AK what I do yeah
I was going to give it as a present here
wa here here's a it's a AK-47 machine
where did you get that found it in
box
oh thank you sick cuz mine was just
about to break my my shitty machine gun
oh enjoy yippee in the middle of day 20
is it upstairs or downstairs it's down
okay I just want to get there is
up going to
turn I'm in the basement I thought you
went downstairs basement but no no it's
wrong
house you're in the wrong
house come to
me I'm coming I'm just a little
silly make sure they got their weapons
and
such are you two just raiding houses
over there still there's a safe o I did
ask them what they wanted okay um SP
they said shotguns but everybody wants
to use shotgun the wrong house you doing
this on purpose look at your map look at
your map I would like to have my
map okay I'm
here a little embarrassed but I'm here
be right back you guys I got to run I
got to run real quick I'll be right okay
okay
ready to
go
um Barrel extender
mod
nice okay it is unlocked you can take a
look
okay there's a wooden
bow a singular wooden bow so worth it
what is this well it's not a primitive
bow at least I have a lot of books for
you
kiawa cool thank
you I will take a look at it oh look
like what why I use rewards I don't need
any of
this are you serious
now are you serious
I'll just take the ammo for other
people okay
um I hoping you could run over
zombies yeah yeah I think you can but
only with cars not with bicycles were
you trying it with bicycles
yeah yeah that that won't work unless
you have spikes on your bicycle or so
now that's an
idea maybe I should oh yeah can we like
tie a spear to the bicycle so it's like
point
did very
[Music]
creative is that Gigi Gigi yes I have
something for you I don't know if it's
good for you or
not I am waiting with anticipation
here a beautiful
bow beautiful maybe you'd like this
because you are obsessed with trees as
well oh wow look at that southern fire
me where's the difference
yeah oh well what a beautiful be thank
you for the seed magazine and the ball
welcome you're welcome please please
read it somewhere
private I will read it in front of
you fun are you Village Place oh you're
coming here I have magazine
[Music]
thank you I just
got that Cece's playing s Days to Die oh
she said she was wrong did she so up did
she sober
up just for the zombie horde I
guess maybe she can have the real
drunken fist
yeah ah there you are yeah they didn't
have any good Quest rewards so I just
took a magazine for you thank you
also who uses 9mm again I do oh I have I
took a lot of 9o to give to
others Adventurer good job where is bi
boo I'm by the booby lady the booby lady
okay that could be any of us almost the
quest booby lady here I dropped 9 mm
ammo on the
floor oh thank you yeah
yeah rare zombies like police oh damn I
should have chosen that Quest
huh when is the we still have time until
the race yeah let's do the quest we
should do Quest I assult rifle crafting
for you oh thank you someone who's
willing to get you the best I knew you
wouldn't let me down the
rest use real yay oh you have unlocked
machine guns AK-47 machine gun Quality 4
yo if only I had machine gun parts
what's a nail gun do we need a nail gun
for
things I don't know wait B have you read
nightstalker volume
three um I've been reading Night Stalker
different volumes have you read three
already which one is three uh bladed
weapons do 10% more damage at right I
think I have
okay reloading is so slow I'm going to
take that
[Music]
skill my leg Yeah my leg why is it
broken again or still what happened oh
do you need a
splint uh I mean it's just 2 minutes I I
I'll just wait I hope you come back and
see me
sometime people you should get the nail
gun it's the best building upgrade tool
oh I did I did get a nail gun a jump
okay no jumping I'm going to go help out
the twins feel free to continue your
journey okay all right I'll see you
later see you see you byebye we do more
level two quests right over here we do
the heavy stuff one okay let's
um do you like all
a reading for
you did you are you doing medic I
am oh thank you that's a lot I'm going
to get really smart yeah become the
smartest there ever was how full is your
inventory FIA it's pretty full
okay all right I'm ready to move okay
are we going to the the the bunch
there's a bunch actually fine a gig is
already at one right I think
go see how can I ride a bicycle is that
okay when I'm have I have a broken
leg is it
acceptable I hope so where are we
going just don't Sprint okay if you're
don't use shift okay I'll be careful no
it's 37 seconds oh okay soon I will be
healed which
way over there wait where are we going
uh back to where we came from I guess
giggy's already there no I am hungry and
let me bring you stuff
yay okay
9 8 7 6 5 what are we counting down for
something bad going to
happen happy New Year happy
year happy happy 2025 everyone indeed
happy birthday happy New Year happy
Christmas Happy Everything no my photo
of a family do you think this is a Dev
family or a stock photo family
family stock photo I thought you said
dead family not de
family family it could be both dead and
a stock family stock photo family if
it's taken long
ago that would be sad it would be
sad but in a way they will live on in
the stof every time someone makes an
advertisement and purchases the rights
to use their
photo yeah wa I'm here which Quest are
we doing first the G okay I don't know
yeah I'm at the house okay look at the
with me all of these quests okay I'm
coming you know that's a that's a great
idea when I move I'm going to just put a
bunch of stock photo family pictures
around my place so that way when someone
robs me they think there's more people
living in the house and just me they
perfect I don't know if that works
because if nobody's
home somebody's got to be home for that
to work in case you have to go after the
after the eggs and
bacon yeah does someone have um
food uh yes or we running out oh we're
running it's not the best food but oh no
corn is
best oh I can cook it up
sometime
okay did you know corn is so
nutritiously bad that the corn we use
today is chemically altered and
processed to make it nutritional before
we eat
it
yies I love
superfood oh we have the gun okay okay
I'm here let's go with new gun I'll open
it oh that aming thank you do you see
the family right there not that family
not that
one many something's on me there is
something on you
don't jump on me don't jump on
me
no a concussion Wow have you guys ever
had a concussion that's kind of crazy
feels weird a
concussion makes your screen kind of
blurry for a
moment but I'm
family 1 hour 40
minutes
bro I almost
puncho it's okay I probably deserve it
no here's armor
crafting and here's the phot frame while
you guys are fighting for foro frame
pretty which family do you think that is
a typical
American family so photo W yes
think it's one of the devs
no hopefully
not
hopefully
oh what is this zombie
doing yeah I saw the Cali message do we
need ammo parts I mean generally um
eventually
so oh
no oh if we
have oh people no people going to get
hit from the side careful my
hero oh did I hit you with the shot no
I'm good okay
meow toilet
water and with your hat you can drink
that too yeah I
can what do we have wiring a somebody
wanted electrical crafting right
somebody I saw it like in the Discord
maybe it was
Cali oh cronies on
night's
online everyone's ready for the hoorde
now the
hord where's the last zombie why are
they always hiding I think outside
because I saw someone
[Music]
oh there's people upstairs
upstairs they upstairs there's a there's
a there's a there's a there's a rope oh
God a rope a
rope how to get up are you f are you
okay I think I'm okay is no I'm not okay
actually I'm running wait run run I see
the r okay I see I see I see I see
there's two zombies so yellow
eyes what's that growling noise that
you okay that growling it's really scary
oh oh the
dog
dog okay we're fine we're fine it's been
cleared that was C
damn they hid the dog in the Attic
huh not
a pet wasn't there a dog house outside
that would have been a nicer place to
keep him
foreshadowing mhm yeah guess I think
every house that has a dog house might
have a dog Enemy
Inside take care take
caution
oo shipping crate
Thomas
Harris William
billinger John Smith AKA too
fresh there's some wanted people with
some realistic looking pictures as if
they took them from
Facebook yeah right whose Facebook did
they take them
from their own
Facebook those really look like they
could be from
devs yeah oh you looked at them too M
it's the working
Theory well if I was developing a game I
would want to be included somewhere too
yeah right I have bullets for
you m yes
you
oh hey thank you does anybody here
read
books yes I love reading no I'm aill
literate wait I need to look uh do I use
this uh maybe I do I'm at the next
Quest does anybody have food outside of
stinky
sandwiches no maybe we should go home
we're all full I have one baked potato
wait wait wait is this potato it's only
one but yay it's better than the stinky
sandwiches have to get out of
here without hurting
myself ah
there yeah I'm so full I'm so
cucumber
yeah and hungry and thirsty oh very oh
my God I'm so thirsty
uh-oh maybe I should drink my Yuka juice
okay I'm going to see if I can make it
to the trader in time before she closes
oh yeah okay let's do that when did she
close though
9 in an hour oh I'll make
it let's go zoom zoom zoom let's go and
then we are speed I don't know should we
still do more quests after that or h um
could we I guess it's not tonight the
zombie raid right it's tomorrow night no
it's the 2 can do them and turn them in
in the morning and then get ready for
the is good
hoorde do you need a bandaid your health
is low
um but let's let's go to the trailer
first so we can get before it closes
I'll survive for do we want to go home
once to unload or do we just want to
keep on going I don't know maybe we
should try to do more quests if we if we
can cuz we're going to have to go home
for the
raid if we can find some food and live
okay I still also have one more quest in
that
area let clear it wow I didn't think you
had it in you good job why where am I
going is this the right
place oh
yeah oh yeah I have a oh yeah we have a
few uh quests still okay me too me
too man stamina why always so
low
ammo pipe bomb also sounds fun your
health my
[Music]
priority she doesn't really have any
food what what wa what she doesn't want
to show me her yeah she doesn't want to
show me her stuff either cuz I'm
looking oh is like one at a time I
thought one at a time I thought it
wasn't Oh I thought it wasn't
before I hope you feeling better okay
lady you can try now it's just realistic
I
guess it works
now her other
wear I don't know what do I even want
does she
have does she
sellor well I'll sell some
stuff what can I
sell
uh
egg it sucks that certain things you can
only sell in a specific amount of
stacks so if you don't have the exact
amount of that stack you you can't get
rid of it that is that is
[Music]
weird the traps electrical traps you
need a lot to build
anything electrical traps you want to
make electrical traps yeah I don't think
anyone else was reading it or collecting
it so I started reading some but okay
but you need
25 to build
anything oh yeah you're the one who
wanted wiring
electrical I got one it's just cuz no
one else was reading it but I guess I
can start specking into it what cuz I
don't think anyone else is doing it here
take it take it thank
[Music]
you are you
moving no okay I thought my game was
like dying thank you oh wait I have ammo
for
you of course you do you always have
ammo for me how much do you have in
harvesting
tools I think Gigi is learning that oh
yeah I have harvesting tools how much do
you have um I have let me
see where did I put it where is it I
have 18 into harvesting tools o I'll
give you one then when I see you are you
already heading back here's your dirty
water I know how much you love thank you
I love my dirty water I'm going to drink
this right now
yeah might eat this old
sandwich I'm going to eat the old
sandwich please don't will be closing in
a few
minutes
scared if you still inside while she
closes does it kick you out yeah yeah it
kicks you out
oh
okay where's my bike a what do you mean
on firstday I just drank three cups of
water I don't this house do you guys
want to see pictures come here there's
so many cute
pictures oh inside is she going to
close there's like there's dog she has
dog pictures and bird pictures and what
she's selling machine gun wait are you
still in there can you buy machine gun
parts before she closes is she Clos I'll
try oh gosh I don't know if I'm going to
make oh no she closed early how dare she
she closed 10 minutes early what the
heck where's my bicycle why would she do
that wait I can't find my bicycle has
anyone seen a bicycle lying around
there's a there's a bicycle icon if you
look around
to your bicycle oh found it okay okay
I'm going to leave for a bad review for
closing okay but good to know she has
machine gun parts I'll go get them later
um so let's go back and make some quests
even though we're all kind of thirsty
and hungry and cucumber we'll be fine
we'll probably find right we have do we
not not have any more food at all on any
of us I have one sandwich some raw corn
and potato M raw corn surely in the
house there'll be food maybe we'll get
lucky and find
something she restocks tonight so they
might not be there sh
no but it's okay for right now I I have
a a better gun than before uh like 5
minutes ago
so it's not too bad we already got an
upgrade maybe for the next H night
look at him next time I'm not coping
it's it's
the yeah Calli gave me the
AK 407 or whatever we're doing this one
AK47 the bio one
[Music]
coming wa a tree has been found who did
that by who I wonder I just don't oh
no okay which one we doing I guess we'll
do this one this
one this is fetch clear okay so we need
stuff this is an Oat Bar there should be
food uh magazine here
yummy you have to you have to clear and
find supplies I see no problem where
multitaskers easy oh oh a sham sandwich
please don't give me diarrhea please
don't give me
diarrhea it didn't give me
diarrhea the diarrhea
[Applause]
got he still
standing I thought they were dead that's
wrong
oh oh they were hiding medical suppli
here
what found a medical journal who learns
that again I learn it good okay well
they have lots of medical journal and I
found food already like a sham sandwich
and PE
pears wonderful
I feel like they hide the CER Satchel so
well I got to look everywhere oh yeah I
forgot mine was hidden inside the wall
where am I are youone upstairs I'm on
fire oh
no that's not good run really fast run
really really fast and then make it go
out like that I brought more
owie I once I once uh made a kitchen go
out in my a fire go out in my kitchen by
just blowing really
strong I totally did I remember a fire
in your kitchen was it the same
one yeah yeah I think pretty sure now
fire run run run run
run it
works I so
hot
[Laughter]
blow has anybody found their supplies
yet I found mine oh still looking for
wait if there's a down arrow does that
mean
down oh I should look at that
too why does it just always have a down
arrow oh no I don't trust it oh I think
it does have a down arrow armor crafting
in here I found please pick it up I'm
somewhere else I think oh wait I'm here
where you are now medical crafting in
here ooh where
upstair scary zombie he's
spinning oh he kind of hurts I'm I'm
scared
help huh help
help oh help I'm coming my are you
coming you're just standing there I'm
standing here but I'll be
there why you looking at that L trunk so
long help Run keep running keep running
keep running I have so much Rand of
garbage in my inventory okay in thank
you I'm dropping them maybe I should
drop my 2,000
wood I dropped 2,000 wood if anyone
would like 2,000
wood where's you had a
book medicine there a medical book up
there I'm not sure if someone picked I I
I picked it up for you I have two now
okay still need to find my Satchel me
too it's really Rel where is it
oh oh oh that's a normal way to get
there
uh uh I don't like being hiding
here oh oh the
fire
dodged where are these
Satchel they might be in the
walls um no way radar
I found mine in a
wall okay I mean that's kind of
sus I got it do you want a dirty water
FAA yeah I do dirty water thank
you maybe downstairs yummy maybe here
wait is there a medical book somewhere
did you say I got two I got two oh oh I
found my satchel yppe
yppe did everyone find their
thingy yes okay
yeah shall we go to the next Quest yeah
I am here ah do we have the same Quest
over there there's two people who have a
quest there I
think is it the same oh the day reset I
had the quest limit but now it's yeah
day
21 we're being so
efficient wait I'm almost there I'm
almost there and let me give you the
medical journal so I have it off of my
hands Tada thank
[Music]
you let's
go got to get my gun out what is this
clearing okay fists
Out
ooh zombies where I you where is
everybody oh there's one watch out for
the fire oh is it on fire diing a
hole die he's back
up get down so
strong didn't
hurt okay ow ow out I forgot my bike oh
I'll pick it up when we're done with
this Quest run run run if you're burning
just run I walked right into it my depth
perception can we walk under it no we
can't no we
can't I'm going to burn to death I'm
going to burn to
death oh
no elimin
eliminated oh no don't play with fire
girls when you're low on HP fire fire
fire ow cannot blow on it too a oh my
god wow what I will break this
wall okay I'm really
dehydrated we could go to a
[Music]
pond why
how I know
why h a oh there's a button go around
it why does it s is on
fire I don't want to T it anymore oh hey
it
open oh go around there ah help help
zombies
where out outside
why do they
break KY you use arrows right I have
some arrows yeah I use arrows I'll give
you in a moment oh in the window oh my
God oh my
God
owow did you get I don't
know doesn't matter what kind of arrows
you use any I use them all okay
oh I feel like I shouldn't be here I
feel like I shouldn't be here by
myself upstairs where' you go upstairs
let's go be careful there's zombies
coming
down
again ah teamwork so TI oh I
leveled oh there more zombies H there's
definitely more more up here I believe
oh oh yeah
[Music]
hello oh he's so
green is this the infected
Quest if they're
green what does that mean wow he's
glowing yeah he's glowing oh this is
new oops
oh what's going on
here
what where where where you have to do
some you have to do some Parkour but
there's
a there's some around you can there's
another floor upstairs uhhuh
what is
[Music]
this what is this
chamber
what secret
tank this is all a little scary yeah
watch your
step ow zombie
bird H but I do see a zombie there he
wants to be uh released
can I
[Music]
shoot I think we have to do something
about
him oh there's
a another
level there's one like behind the locked
door in the middle
level I don't want
to oh
my
scary
y
okay the roof zombies are dead oh not
quite the roof roof but there's like
several
roofs there's another level upwards this
place is gigantic yeah oh there's a roof
roof I'll try try to get up there
hello okay I'll try to do something
about the door
but yeah it's still there can you not
just open the door from there zombie why
do I have to do it I wonder if there's a
key in this
place oh gosh loud SC loud here all the
help help help
help oh okay where this
works are you up there yeah they're on
the roof roof there's like I'm
coming I've got no
stamina so many
uhoh yeah after this Quest maybe I'm
done for we're done
yay but I I explore over there and still
need to open one more door to tactical
Warfare uh yeah I think I do I do is
that the assault rifle one I don't know
yes it is okay that's mine have one for
you it shall be mine wait I'm I need to
break this door otherwise I'm not
satisfied
o anyone's hungry I got half food can I
use your hat to drink water yes is there
a water source out there I found murky
water oh and here you
go
f I have another quest in the exact same
location but we don't have to do it
now as this one yeah the same house I
think there's a cool down yeah oh
okay
bicycle I don't know is anyone super
starving uh getting there and I have an
old
sandwich I have a mky water you could
drink the the water in combination of
the Hat might work yeah
yeah I just I can't find you
girls there's a there's some stairs but
you have to parkour for
it they're all the way up there okay
we got to check these there's books in
here where newspaper
dispensers more of them there's books in
every single one of
them except that
one oh I found like six books got to
take a look at them but where where is
cat
food actually I might need to eat the
cat food I'm going to eat the
sandwich you'd rather eat the sandwich
that gives
you I have good stomach strong
stomach are you in the
house I'm trying to leave H I'll look
for my
bicycle
bcle and let's see um
ah
um I went in a
tank 4:00 a.m. Traer open
yay can't give back Quest
now first find
bicycle I think I think I find a bicycle
do coyotes attack people um yes yes
yes I'm so it look so nice
why oh
no it was so cute and pretty
oh I'm
[Music]
bleeding damn hit you right in the eye
huh my eye oh
sorry bo boo I'll be your eyes you have
any of those
bandies I don't have any I have a
regular bandage it'll stop your bleeding
indeed my beding stopped I'm just dying
oh
no maybe Trader Jen can help
you are you still lost in the building I
finally made it out
okay I'm going to the trader giving back
my quest and
okay I got a couple of books but there I
don't know if anybody wants these I'll
put them in the book chest at home
later
okay see if she has gun parts yes very
important of utmost importance
then I can already make a level four gun
right come
on I feel like I'm not learning these
roads at all I'm
still we're still new here it's okay
it's okay map Reading is an important
skill I wish I could drink this rain I
was just the same Lally opened my mouth
and looked up the moment you said
that why can't we put like buckets down
and stuff I know we have a du collector
yeah that's like we we should just be
able to you know have buckets or like
use our hats
true I learned the crazy trick if you're
ever um on a deserted island uh what you
can do um to filter water
uh you you take some you you try to find
some container maybe nowadays you know
with how dirty the ocean is you can
probably find a plastic bottle somewhere
up the shore take the plastic bottle cut
it in half H take some um SP it all one
place water ocean water it's here place
it in the sand and then the second half
of the cut plastic bottle you fold it uh
on the bottom it will make some kind of
like catchy container and then you put
it on top of it's hard to explain but
but but over time this will filter the
the sea uh water the the salt out of it
and then you get clean water only a few
drops per day but if you get a lot of
these you can have a lot of water
eventually survival skills
baby filtration cing I want Dr that
water well I hope we don't need to use
this when we're
camping I will I will if if if we get D
Zer one day we'll remember this just for
fun
[Music]
yeah I'll take this P now did you guys
get the next Trader Trader bom someone
like you hurry back soon and I'll have a
nice oh yes I did get Trader
Bob wait does that mean she didn't give
us anything special she didn't give us a
motorcycle she gave a nail gun right oh
yeah she gave me mini bark mini bark
mini bike
parts oh that's aot mcycle bikee
no yes I think so hia I have stuff for
you thank you thank you thank you I
wonder if anybody is investing into
explosives crafting does anybody know I
kind of want to I like
explosives I have I have some Molotov
and pipe bombs okay I'll start I'll
start learning explosives yeah let's go
yeah
then mining tools is anybody fighting
with mining
tools I have the art of mining Volume
7 don't know who to give this
[Music]
to well I'll just put these into the
chest I can't think right now maybe
G which one mining yeah mining
okay um what was I looking for machine
gun parts
yes bye bye all of
them okay what magazines they have
explosive s farming I
see feel like I've never seen you with
your hat
off I have cool glasses now yeah you too
I don't know it's kind of giving scary
Vibes though the you don't like how
ites what's with my glasses I don't know
I'm just getting scary
vibes from what kind of Vibes maybe it's
the angle what about this from the
profile view from the
profile
maybe just little villainous you know
like the mustache and the bald head and
the glasses
well my bartering is plus 2% with these
so maybe it's threatening 2% that's
going to do a big difference feeling a
little rough around the edges we all
start
small got to start somewhere you got to
start from the bottom now we start from
the bottom now we here are we going back
or like home yeah pocket it's it's the
21st got to prepare there it's almost
time we must probably go home bike bike
wait did I ever find my
bike where's my
[Applause]
bike all right then it was uh a fine
time questing with you ladies it seems
I'm not ready for tier three yet though
so maybe that a good deal trust me I'm a
doctor I do have one more Quest over
there maybe after to the
raid
oh all of the girls are currently at our
new home other by any chance trying to
fortify our new home I wonder oh let's
go find out let's go
yeah she had automatic magazines
what I didn't see them I'm
blind I'll check it out before I go
[Music]
just me the open road and 10,000 zombies
this is just like Mad Max
literally witness
me I watched mad ma for the first time
and I didn't think I would be into it
because like I don't know I don't
usually watch stuff like that but it was
so
good yeah it's just like seven days to
die I I started watching I fell asleep
you fell as how do you fall asleep in
mad I fell asleep so much is happening
yeah it's like the most action-packed
movie like everything is happening every
second maybe I was really tired that day
I don't
know maybe why am I going the wrong
way how much does she pay
for it seems like my type of movie
though so maybe I'll give it a second
chance it's it's fun it's a fun movie it
is
fun the world is
cool and
bald yeah and bald cool and
bald she sells it so much more expensive
I sell her something and she
I can't even eat the raw
horn wait is it just cuz I'm on the bike
yeah I think so okay you can normally
eat it I'm pretty sure eat the raw corn
cuz I'm
starving no fana it doesn't have any
nutritional value super cor I have no
choice I can't guys I can't buy it wait
is this a shortcut this
road this curving
Road let's find out I think it is goes
right
home I hope there's food at
home could we have a Lakeside date so I
can drink your water yes I could also
use
water wait I want to go where you girls
[Music]
are I would like a sip too just in case
so we don't waste
resources true oh but you're so
far just catch up to us whenever you
whenever you're ready I'll try I'm going
to the lake to the north I feel like
that's the best water source for good
sip
sip I also have tons of meat and five
eggs for you to cook oh
good me too I got some meat as well meet
too meet meet to meet
too nice to meet you nice to meet you
too thank
you as well we are are all made of meat
and Flesh and
Bones nice to meet you isn't so far
off we don't have to resort to
cannibalism just yet I know we're all
starving but but you look so so yummy B
no
you're people always tell me I look
tasty they say I look like fried chicken
to them in their eyes they're just
projecting I don't know what they
mean yes they are they are the tasty
ones M they are you hear that kfp
okay here
go she's running into the blade
did you get it doesn't like being used I
got it okay I got so
[Laughter]
scared it's the most PR precious hat of
all time I'm trying to find oh here we
go no your hat has been passed around so
much at this point everybody's wearing
it you're probably getting lies no none
of us have lies right I have no hair on
my head there is no I will not judge
anyone for having
lies I have PTSD from lies so no
judgment I
have drank a gallon of Lake water I am
ready to stop drinking ooh tummy a thank
you maybe by the time you're all done
drinking I'll be there almost there yeah
yeah yeah go go go go
my num num num num n n I'm sip SI sip
sip sip sip
sip W I'm really
Ching you are really drinking it
allll oh it's so
tasty almost there almost there almost
there o day 21 it says it in now I think
I
to a and this is only our second okay I
don't want to go down the hill okay oh
I'm I'm I'm I'm almost there I'm almost
there I'm literally there I see you I
see
you fauna awaiting me I'm
waiting it's like you have to babysit
people for drinking like it's a
dangerous thing or something it's very
dangerous don't over drink
water ah there it is thank
[Music]
you m
I wonder if we can make more of the
water purifier hats what did you get it
you find it I just found it I don't even
remember where I found it maybe maybe
they'll sell the mod for it cuz like the
rotators rotate their mods and stuff so
maybe we got to learn the schematic for
it
yeah okay do you think that's
enough I think if it's at 90 it's enough
90 oh okay
[Music]
there you go thank you so
much let's go home I miss home I hope I
hope it doesn't look too
different never known what to expect
after a long outing I know suddenly
there might be five rows of spikes in
front of our home there might be more
trees more trees yeah but the trees
would be probably there for different
reason for giggy's
addiction what I have to plant more
trees trees are a natural defense right
yeah yeah a little bit but we also won't
be able to see clearly anymore okay I
only see spikes
good good question mark is it good
it's been a long
time we finally home allo
[Music]
Queen wait alloy cream is already the ah
finished thing okay potato seeds oh I
hear I hear
something are they inside I think
they're in on the back of our house or
so knocking on our door what would you
want we don't buy anything we don't want
to buy anything please go
away okay all right all right they're
getting a little bit too
rowdy oh yeah they're knocking on our
back door I didn't know we had a back
door
[Applause]
oh she dropped some
loot what did they
drop oh night vision mod see in the dark
with this high-tech night vision head
armor
mod and oh weighted head mod schematic
interesting knives and
machetes I can use that I have knives
and machetes
uh wait what does this say knives and
machetes do not have a head that can be
weighted oh I don't think you can do
yeah never mind uh but it's for all
melee weapons except knives and
[Music]
machetes oh not well I'll put
it maybe in
here should I make my new gun now chat
time right yeah but I just got the
AK-47 if you got some
materials
ah I don't want to replace it already
but maybe maybe I should I think we
might have to just make grilled
meat instead of that's fine yeah that's
okay we don't have enough
carnivore diet I guess yeah it
is things just disappear when I click
that
button I wonder where they
go ooh vehicle
crafting I think I'm do I have to keep
the crafting window open to
craft I don't so it goes
passively oh okay
cool I think I'm learning that um
potassium nitrate where to put
that making
gunpowder
spicy ah do they H ner hat ner uh okay
okay okay okay did they were they going
to give me anything uh like armor kits
for it
all right let me go down to
NC what do you need to make duct
tap uh
glue
[Music]
and quick faster faster cloth cloth
fragment I totally knew that
a I
need can I
of this
stuff in
here
Chihuahua oh she left she went to their
thing to ask something I think you
should just take it yeah yeah okay yeah
it's for every can I wait it might not
that might be for f
m that might be their nerd hat
ingredients how do you make orange iron
clay and
iron yeah you need to put them in a
smelter I have some smelting right now
can I have
some how many do you need Under
okay almost
done here's 12
thank you right here
how do you make the nerd
hat um you need for level three you need
three
armor fragments and then leather I
believe uh and something else do you
need the armor crafting kits oh yeah you
need three armor crafting kits and
leather
for level three uh it depends cuz you
can make like level one level two level
three so the amount of armor crafting
kits is correlated to the level okay so
if you want three then you need three
I'm getting lost in the crafting
sauce crafting sauce
M what it tastes like tastes like
leather and
metal oh there's a there's an armor part
up here if you want it I have a few
okay but thank
you going to take these
time grilled meat only gives 10
Health I'll try and find some eggs thank
you wish we could like have a chicken
farm I know maybe you can though
[Music]
supply
drop
oh how far is
that
[Music]
oh oh it's pretty far down down south
I'm going oh yeah it is good luck good
luck I'll find some eggs on the way
thank you thank
you I need
iron I found a pig a pig kill it 30 more
meat take his
eggs C open to take his
eggs get right you want to cut right
into the underbelly right here that's
where it opens up into his egg egg
sack it's egg
sack it's just like a fish yeah they
never specified the type of eggs we can
have sing cavard that sounds fancy
that sounds too
fancy we have to it's our
only little remnant of civilization in
the
caviar maybe we can build a
casino o I would love a
casino gambling
gambling did you have any more duct tape
t anywhere no I can make two more you
can uh cook bones or maybe I can cook
bones to make glue
oh gun that's
awesome how much duct tape do you need I
need
five duct
tape okay I have
some how much how many bones become glue
I think one bone you need
water um this is the expensive
part do we have any
iron I think maybe I put them on the
it's in all in the Forge right now me
melted okay can I use some yeah okay
thank
[Music]
you the nerd armor is heavy
armor it's heavy
armor apparently nerd is
taxing yeah
wa so I need three armor crafting kids
leather
and that's it oh that's it okay yeah you
need like at least 10 leather though
okay I
[Music]
have what the hell I just ran over a
mine are you okay God they mines land
mine
are you okay
okay just
scared I'm at a public school right now
oh that's the most terrifying place ever
yeah it's really scary here
[Music]
um I have two duct
tape I'll take
it um well there's just medical journals
in
here use out I'm going to
oh I need water for ball or for glue
that sucks yeah that's what makes it
hard there's mutated zombies
here be care no be careful
I'm taking everything and I'm leaving I
don't want to be here anymore good
luck I'm bringing I'm bringing a bird
with me back home
I think we have plants
outside but I'm not a farmer so I don't
know if I should Harvest
them but I don't think our farm is
online yeah maybe it's okay to harvest
the plant
yeah as you plant them again it should
be okay yeah
I'm getting some
stuff I'm just so
hungry so hungry all the time our
eggs I do I have two egg and one bird
following me that is to say oh
help can you kill it help where are you
where are you outside the house oh I got
it I got you I got you
okay hey I'm to find out what I
got did you get the supply drop yeah I
got a four time scope scope and a bunch
of other mods I can use the four time
scope I'll put it in the gun
chest
okay and all the other parts I
found I think I can okay in
there I wonder does this work with a
hand
gun no it doesn't ah I guess not
[Music]
corn I'm I'm the farmer now I'm just not
very good at
it you're learning just like how you
learned how to mend everyone's wounds
now you're learning how to
farm Renaissance Man a
no who fighting what's
happening kie just smacked
me
uh-oh sham
chowder sham Chow make
thato sham Chow I did not sham CH who
made sham
powder to tow
sh oops I'm punching we're just beating
each other in here it's chaos it's day
chaos it hurts it hurts
[Music]
pumpkin I need a little bit more pumpkin
cheesecake I need beer beer to make pump
my alcohol problems wait you need you
need beer to make pumpkin chees yeah wow
oh no I used our last eggs though to
make eggs in
bacon I put two eggs in here I used them
to make eggs in bacon no no there's two
new eggs oh there's two new eggs two new
eggs oh thank
you I could make can I even make
beer I don't know if I know how to make
beer you have to learn so much in the
apocalypse I know
I thought we were just becoming a chef
you have to make beer
too I'm going to make two pumpkin
pies
and that's it I
guess did anyone take the Bunches of
cloth fragments in
the oh I have cloth fragments
here you
go thank you oh that's a oh here's dug
tap too oh thank
you one two
three oh I can modify my
knuckles I don't know what I can put in
there though more Knuckles a stack
knuckle setion more more
spikes put a sandwich in there
there give them the good old classic
knuckle sandwich sham
[Music]
sandwich I don't know if these modifiers
work that's a silencer on my
Knuckles are your
knuckles wait is it almost time do we
need to leave do we need to go to the
other house uh I mean everybody's still
here so I think we have a little bit I
think it's like night time like 10:00
p.m. I believe yeah but it's already 4:
and it takes a while to walk over
there I don't know oh is it cuz my time
my silly timer ran out my fake timer
timer on my
stream hold on can I restart my
timer wait I have to click it like 100
[Music]
times F yes hello hello I'll make it for
you but I need to wait for a little bit
more iron um oh do you need more iron
yeah I'm forging it right now I'm also
needing a lot of iron for myself too uh
I one I need like five I need seven more
iron for myself as well oh
okay maybe I should have taken the
workbench can you make is it expensive
to make another one uh I'll check but
the the iron is being made in the Forge
that's separate
oh um but wait
I I need for you nerd wait how many
armor kits do you give me three okay I
can I already actually make a level four
nerd hat for that I need four but I have
an extra one that I can give you for
free and then yeah for free a discount
for my
for how do you call someone who's only
related to you by being someone else's
wife who's who you're also their wife
sister wife wife
sister I guess something like that we're
also wives so we're not really Sister
Wives now I ran out of Lea no wait I
have a bit more lever oh yeah okay okay
okay okay uh done with the
forge does anybody have some more like
iron for me to like smelt there's
there's 100 already in the yeah that's
not enough we need more oh there's not
enough okay I'll look I'll go out and
look for more I'll also look for iron
please please me
too maybe if I Springs I need Springs I
thought I had spr I I have Springs in my
inventory I have one spring I'll take
that one I have nine Springs I'll take
Seven Springs here just take take all of
my Springs
amazing oh are we are we fortifying this
house what's the point
no okay Callie is going to the the main
house oh it's time soon soon wait did I
give you your hat oh wait f f I have
your hat oh my hat
yay level four nerd
hat now I can match everyone
else yay look so my gosh I look
crazy wow it suits wait you know
wait with the green hair and now even
more so with the hat and the goggles why
have alien glasses you look like like
the lady you know from that photo from
that chocolate f um Charlie and
chocolate oh my gosh charie you look
like that lady from the picture yeah the
sad
OAA trying her best Springs I'm going to
drop it by oh I'm actually I I have
enough now oh okay I'll I'll put them
into this chest
yeah oh okay OA
loopa
cute what am I
doing oh I need so much
iron so much iron I'm looking for more
thank you that's so sweet but oh wait
with this 10 + 4 oh
yeah more I'll probably get there do we
need to head
over yeah
soon soon
soon the sooner the better probably get
mentally
prepared
okay what the blast furnace speed up
foring yeah but I don't have time to
make that right
now I'm going to make it after the
hoorde now found a little iron deposit
oh
[Music]
nice oh yeah right you are
our
uh what are you yeah Min 69er Beaver
yeah
scary okay have oh one
more it's getting
scary why is the thund wor come into my
arms in my iron
hole IR be safe down
ironing straight
down I now have 1,000 iron oh my gosh
you're so efficient you can just thr it
into the forge
[Music]
okay okay I made my machine gun there's
a lot of hammer books Hammer books I use
Hammer books Sledgehammer books in the
book one
okay I wanted to keep digging but it
looks like time will will be soon I'll
I'm hungry can I eat this pie I'm going
to go down
okay I will save
it 2,000 iron I'm
running okay I'm going to I'm going to
head over also okay all I'm going to
bring some ingredients so maybe we can
cook over
there let us converge
wait do I even remember where the other
house
is um is it it's all the way over there
yeah
oh will we make it what time does night
start
21 oh boy something like that not yet I
got to drop everything off we have bikes
yeah we have bikes it's fine move
quickly it seems like is nobody there
yet I think everyone is making their way
they're almost there okay maybe they
just
arrived this sky is starting to darken
[Music]
yeah okay I am heading over we must R
many trees I have to go
through weave through them is it a bad
idea to go snow
area I don't I don't wait you don't need
to go through the snow snow area for
yeah but there might be a road there oh
connect I think it's okay it's not too
bad if your your bike is faster than the
[Music]
zombies I
guess I can go this way we need to build
a
bridge yeah yeah this darn
Lake
mhm can you ride your bike through a
lake um a river I I rolled through a
pond and I seemed okay I was kind of
suffocating but oh it works actually
it's
fine you can just go straight
through can you make it without drowning
yeah across a river at least maybe not a
lake if you have if you have the stamina
for it I think should be
okay oh my bike is taking a
beating and my bike is a
24%
quality I'm
4 you should you should steal your
bike she needs Band-Aids but I don't
know where to get Band-Aids for her oh
it's just repair kits so you can repair
it with those there's some in the the
chest in the new house okayy
I'm almost
there we can make it we can so
[Music]
far it is really far I don't know how we
how we made it so far from each
other maybe we should start up like
multip
residences near other Traders too cuz
it's like going more and more south
especially with this third one we might
need a new
resid come on bike you can do
it they reinforced
it they did I feel like it's going to be
hard to to jump through now
H if you want to run in and
out you go through the water so
slowly
yeah but it's it's a faster
shortcut I was drowning they have the
faster shortcut to death
cornmeal oh they did
reinforce
yeah oh they have no fuel
here you know who has
fuel I you
specifically I
hope
ooh yeah let me just let me take a
U-turn real quick
let me take a pit stop I'll find some
fuel wait do you no longer have 8,000
wood in your inventory no I only have
7,000 W that's enough that's
enough I'm
worthless you're worthless you don't
have 8,000 I know I only have
7,000 oh my
gosh I can make a bunch of pumpkin bread
when we have fuel I can't find any wood
around I'm almost there I have all the
wood oh there's some there's some repair
kits in the old house too for your yay
where am
I oh my God I was routing to our old
house I made a uturn somewhere along the
way I I think you should come to the old
house now you have about an hour before
they start arriving I was I was biking
to the old house and then I got lost and
then I started following the arrow to
our our new home and then I was like
where am
I don't forget to set a new
bed
Mony I'm taking matters into my own
hands I'm getting my own
wood oh they set up a nice pew pew what
o okay I'm going to hop over okay me too
see you guys there
there somebody
has
[Music]
hello um I need him for a pipe shotgun
and make for cron actually I'm stealing
them from bi sorry B I owe you girl you
don't owe me anything just take it it's
fine are you sure get to the Bas hurry
I'm trying but I went the wrong way can
I
Foster the wrong way use your go through
the river you don't have to go through
the path go through the river I'm trying
I'm drowning try harder don't shoot me
when I get there please I'll try really
hard not to I might enter with the
zombies
oh oh oh then we might have to shoot
don't shoot me don't shoot me I'm almost
there F we have 60 bullets let's make
them count
okay yeah you guys will be fine I'm
going to show you
I you guys I'm
Ania ammo oh my God this shooting
platform is so good thank you thank you
yeah you're welcome you're
welcome made you made it y I'm going to
shoot you no shoot her shoot her no it's
not too
late it's dangerous place it's dangerous
does anybody else have any pipes any
amount of pipes at all don't I do
not it's okay man I can make you a level
three I can make you a level three
shotgun we know when the zombies are
here I recommend the club they'll be
here in 20 seconds oh the is that true
beautiful it makes me want to sing it's
going to be
fun okay 65 ammo as well to help you out
crony all right oh thank you g where are
you I am
outside oh I see waiting for everybody's
facing that way face the other way let
see okay here you go here here's your
gun and here is your ammo oh my God you
didn't have to what the heck that's a
lot oh my God use them well but remember
it only it only shoots one at a time
yeah yeah so just be ready for that I'll
make them
count oh boy here we go oh God here we
go uhoh good luck
everyone
gosh we got this easy easy easy
kinky can you put one more block here
for meit a minute
okay I can't jump so high
yet
[Music]
partyers are not the best to have at
this let me make it for you
quick thank you oh yeah thank
[Music]
you okay no not on the right I'm going
to throw
M the okay what be careful okay
the oh oh they spit all the vomit now
spitting
ew pretty
far okay seems like no one's attacking
the house from the other side it's
only I okay don't do that
oh
[Music]
God okay all right all right this might
be pretty bye this time I forgot to put
my bed roll in here oh my God it's Ving
like crazy oh I'm
[Music]
scared it's a bit laggy too vomit is
like vomit so
uhoh are you
okay I need to
get you don't Hur
me uhoh at uhoh they're going to break
for the spikes soon there are bands
inside in the food chest and also food
if anyone needs a
break they're going to break for the
spike soon over here are
they can somebody build more spikes I
have
uh on the left side of the house okay
okay okay I'm right now all right all
right us I don't know where I'm looking
I'll cut this tree down too while we're
at it for more
wood what about the natural
uh
[Music]
ow uhoh oh go on the hill the zombies on
the hill H they they're coming from the
front of the house now again from the
Hill from the
hill yeah they are coming from the
hill right cck to activate it and then
throw it with left
C okay
okay thought the ball K you
oh there was a bomb I didn't even know
that bird all the birds are on
there not that strong it's
okay yeah
the okay I'm putting spikes
on kind calm over here
thank the
out for the
dog I think you're taking oh wow taking
him down okay dog is dead
it's that's a big
dog oh dear the dog
hurts on this can I helping I think so
just keep on
shooting am I helping I think so someone
naked out there it's
[Music]
me okay I'm going to try putting down
more spikes oh God you scared
me I'm more spes I killed the bird with
[Music]
my in's in wait is that the person oh
get
in filter them in in a c
them through let's try to reate when
there's
time
heal okay there's a little bit chill
time right now down time there's healing
and food inside in the food chest a
little
bit oh they're coming they're coming
from the left side left side
healing oh I'm going to throw a Molotov
so don't go in the field on the left
side yet okay should have brought my
mol this is definitely different from
the first nights yeah yeah it's getting
a little hard oh nice
fire oh God so many of them are
[Music]
broken I want to all right I'm going to
throw pipe bombs also on the left side
so don't don't go out oh watch out watch
out watch out watch
out make it go bom right in front of me
there's a lot going on on the left
side make him go boom yeah make him go
boom don't worry we'll be
fine starting to come over from the left
kind of
bit it's a lot on the left
back don't
me oh my God
he's reloading reloading get him get him
get him right all I'm going to set on
fire
again
nice wait look I hope he doesn't send
the spikes on fire by himself no oh nice
get him not I think we got
him anybody over here down
below I'm out of ammo
soon where are the repair kit do we have
any here inside I'm pretty
sure they're coming from the southwest
I'll get take the
down throw
it I'm helping get him get
get don't is spawn out there using her
fist she has no fears
yeah I'm getting I'm getting
bonuses she's so
brave I'm too scared to go up there I'm
out of ammo soon so I'll probably go out
and die watch
out not shoot shoot okay I want out
behind the big
yeah
what
officer I don't want be here there are a
lot of stuff so
weird we need to be L I don't know maybe
I should go outside and fix so
laggy it's pretty laggy
War oh wow terrible swings from
me we go
backwards get
trying oh that was really
strong the are very strong I need to get
out of here
[Music]
I'm going to start throwing pipe bombs
watch out people on the
field I'm out of
ammo I we almost out of ammo
too I'm
scared who's who's outside right now
besides fauna oh fa just went in I'm
in I'm coming back oh jeez I see why we
miss I'm so scared
so that I can go back out and fight
again damage to me I don't know what
it's almost
[Music]
over bad not too bad it's not bad yeah
I'll make some more
go back go back
back it's a big one oh there there's
awest Southwest
uh-oh it won't let you it's lag out here
it's a
zombie
[Music]
okay
stamina
stamina know I'm
going they are camping
dying oh joyous day to die yes s seven
days to die oh oh
crazy
emoi shocked
face
nice
get the doors are open the doors are
open
so close
[Music]
nothing are they is it
done suddenly didn't until three I
thought I F four it seems it seems quiet
now it's we preparing for next very
quiet recoup everybody okay we
could get your second oh it's over for
real oh man why last second oh it's over
it's quiet too quiet it's too quiet too
quiet I don't think it's over time to
lose Happy song or
something how many bullets do we have
left and we don't
have9 really is it over music
gone I don't it feels over it feels over
but the but the the the the the the the
the sky is still
red the Happy song is it playing
what's you going for
this can't touch this okay you got
it okay I'm going to put stuff in the in
the
[Music]
storage well it's too quiet wonderful
we've done we've done it I think next
time maybe one more row of spikes
because they do seem to be breaking
through now yeah just one small row yeah
I worry if we're going to I I wonder if
we're going to have more like flying
type enemies as well if that's a thing
oh yeah get craer there was only a few
but yeah more ammo also there's iron
spikes that you can build
now better spikes
not not over it's
not the one you was me yeah did I scare
you guys a little bit it's just me oh
you're such a
troll a little silly sometimes she it's
getting
better I think it's not
over yeah I heard it's
over there was a
lightning yeah it's over yeah apparently
you can you can
get through them all before 400 a.m. we
were
just okay free waves that makes sense
thank you yay we did
[Applause]
[Music]
it it felt more intense than the first
time yeah yeah the first time was a bit
an we just got so much stronger we did
nice nice nice
yeah everyone we didn't die we help
maybe good job helping you did you did
you
did you guys are doing great how do I
fix the spikes oh God not with our body
not with our
body going to die I'm stuck on a Spike
oh
no heal now we're going to die M let
maybe maybe
fix let's heal let's heal M let's heal
that's kind of a
weird mm I hope it's over cuz I already
left and went far away oh God yeah it's
over it's over yeah it should be done I
think speaking of uh how long may we be
online today 4 hours total again or um I
would I would be very happy if if we
could if people could not play past uh
45 minutes from now
okay good okay we'll play again tomorrow
of
course you know just to make sure that
everybody's got enough time to level up
and such and do a bunch of quests
together and such yeah there's shotgun
ammo and uh 762 ammo in the old house so
take that before you leave the old house
is it in the ammo
box we to end here for today but if
anybody wants our our our what's it
equipment
we have a good good right oh you can
borrow to someone else I guess oh yeah
I'll drop it for now okay uh
thanks ah I I want I was going to drop
the other ammo in the new house let's
check the current stage the game stage
how do IOP it oh fa is the one that's
furthest in game stage
50 what did I do how did I
what's a game stage you're just pting so
good punching things punching game stage
much I wonder if I have the debuff or
something maybe I'm just not
doing Quest huh you want to the N
goggles again oh yeah I'll bring it into
the new house okay
okay I hope it gave you some levels
thank
you nice
bu everybody looks so nerdy
look
nerds should we put our levels into
strength again what weapon are you
enjoying using the shotgun or what you
strength is probably best for that okay
strength for shotguns and clubes I want
to take some of these materials like
iron stuff from the old house to the new
house since we have a forge over there
good
idea yeah
we'll see you everybody byee byebye okay
thank you byebye bye
bye also head out for now I have a
different stream um but I will see you
guys
tomorrow don't overdo it cie by
byebye all righty bye bye lat take care
bye take care see you tomorrow PE
u u u
uh yeah let's do quests I need to get
rid of my exp Deb
[Music]
okaying yuming yuming we love yumping
here we love juming yuming yuming yuming
we
yuming we yumping we oping we Ying we
Ying it takes so much
stamina stamina contest let's
I already have zero I'm
out I love yuming what you yuming about
cool I think I'm like I have like a
radioactive sign are you sober now
yeah sound sad about it yeah sound sad
about
it no I'm happy cuz I was then I could
join I didn't want to be the weird drunk
uncle at the party no I think I would
prefer I think that would have been
great you would have been the life of
the party
yeah um wait where where did Cory go
where did you go me yes where are you oh
there do you want to do you want to do
quests
too uh sure I'll do one yeah can we get
Jo you even though we don't have
bicycles yeah yeah have bicycle list
pointing and laughing no imagine not
having a b should try
hard yeah we just we like being healthy
and moving our legs properly and
walking the of the ding ding huh watch
this ding
ding I low impact exercise different
colors uh I'm going to the house back
first the new house I need to drop
stu okay oh you can repair the bike too
yeah you can repair with repair kit so
it's pretty nice also you can dye it
whatever color you want yeah I was going
to say you'll all have your colors but
then I realized
[Laughter]
well wish I could take you guys with me
but it doesn't unless you like move with
me this kind of works it's a little a
little bit it's kind of working kind
of you
sh he so if you girls join us should we
still be doing tier 2 quests yo we did
that with CIA too yeah I think they they
get exp
CIA
CIA that's a good
password better than 1111 at least
111111 no use that as a password right
no ever
no a we're totally joking by the way for
legal reasons that we never use
1111 of course not yeah no
way I feel like we slower this way
people than if we just
walk B really are pretty fast
yeah I wish I had don't tell them that
don't tell them 10 quests or so we don't
need bicycles cardio was good for
you what do you think biking is it's
also
cardio but it's less it's less cardio if
you it's not less cardio it's like
longer cardio cuz you can bike for
longer
than yeah but we going the same way wait
where did you go I lost her it's over I
lost her it's okay I I went across the
river you can cross the river with a
bike over here hello
what I always get off of it you can go
straight through yeah if you have
stamina you can just through
it crazy that's strong you have some do
you go underwater like on the ground
basically
yeah Common Sense seconds my Common
Sense has prevented me from greatness it
seems but now you can achieve greatness
yeah but I'm always low on stamina guess
I can't do it
then wait just get more
stamina oh I oh okay is this way I was
waiting for
crony oh I'm I'm ahead of you it's
okay follow we're going this way are we
going that way okay I'm just going to
where Kiara is oh I'm going towards the
house but I'm taking weird paths I think
oh okay
and Mining a little bit in the in
between I'm not getting what I
want that's
help no let's
sleep where's the iron I can't find iron
oh I
have uh I am
bringing 1300 what 13 what 1300 not
13,000
still that's a lot good yeah that's a
lot that looks like iron oh you call it
iron too I'm so happy you what what wait
who who what you
call do you you wait you call it iron
yeah you call it iron yeah but your
first language is
English oh you're getting owned
I'm not I was trying to relate to
you are you kidding me right
now I thought it wasn't normal I thought
only people like me would say it
wrong iron iron iron iron iron iron iron
oh I feel so see I kind of I kind of
like IR it's like the character from
Avatar I roll Uncle I roll you don't
call I IR I literally can't find my
house most of the time look for the tree
look for the trees no but like get rid
of them I'm sick of them they concealed
it's like it's just like
Twilight be finding my
house the vampires live in this house
yeah vampires live in this house the
Clementine
family I thought they were called the
cins
we can't yeah it's a reboot we can't
take it for copyright reason it's a
spinoff
okay okay I put a bunch of iron in the
iron in the Forge uh check the book
chest where are they going electric and
food thank
you I love reading we made it yay
yay m e do e
doas
what I can make a robotic
Sledge oh I don't know what that is wait
Raider Sledge yeah the trees are growing
into the house hey
chill likes it what are you wearing on
your
top what what is it called
um what are you wearing right now
Commando oh I think I have something of
interest for a set bonus oh Raider top
perhaps oh for your Raider hat although
you are wearing a nerd hat
now uh I think it does this wait this is
good outfit yeah thank you I found it
somewhere scary
my hat doesn't
matter you look hardcore yeah this is
WTF what the f yeah I want the
fauna I was thinking of something else
but I guess that's what it's supposed to
mean in
reality and I got some Rog Bo i
l but I I'll put some Rogue boots into
the uh armor chest whoever wants this
wants it can take it
thank
you oh I have fist stuff on here
for I'm sorry I don't know what came
over me oh thank you thank you I don't
mean to hit my wife so often what what
was that you're a wife Peter I can't
help
it help don't cry my
sweet don't let them know have change
this can't keep going on I I stopped
drinking is that not enough this is the
gambling
then it is the gambling I dream of it
yeah know take
this oh thank you I think you might like
it do I put this on my weapon
yeah oo like electrical parts and
mechanical parts that kind of stuff
somewhere somewhere I think we should in
the uh the miscellaneous
crates we have a lot of parts parts in
these two chests um might be able to
find it there oh yeah there's robotic
Parts in these wood storage these
unlabeled wooden storage crates right
here next to fa there's some in there
nice thank you oo
[Music]
okay I got so much stuff oh my God
careful I didn't know you very cramped
as you may have
noticed careful
man is there any
leather oh I have 12 how much do you
need I need um um I need 12 oh okay
here's 12 oh thank
you okay
um
seeds H oh I'm
hungry are
you yeah oh tummy rumbles ooh I have a
banana
bread I love banana
bread I me pump no sorry a pumpkin bread
I was disappointed pumpkin bread is nice
too I like
banana it's behind you on the floor I
just put it on the floor than thank you
I'm going to eat
it it's not actually good it's so good
was nice and moist thank you I almost
punched you in your face were you scared
did I frighten you a little
bit what's wrong maybe I'll do it
anyway just because I'm wearing glasses
the way you don't like it it wasn't your
glasses it was your what was it it was
your the the the worm under your nose
little hairy worm come closer and get a
better look she not a worm she does look
like
renovation you're scared of me I see I
have good reason to be
scared don't be scared wait you look
like Eggman from from Sonic oh thank you
that's a
compliment
better I want to move this
too oh that looks pretty it's pretty
yeah was in the
way okay if I get my eyes five fored
steel I'm burning again ah there's some
oh with fored steel I do you love
burning yourself man
the do you need for steel I have some I
have 15 oh nice I just need four okay
and then I can make my item thingy that
I've been wanting I'm at the forge
Workshop
thingy here you
go I Dro it
thank you so
much windows are pached up which is
good nice nice okay oh you fixing our
Windows oh yeah the exterior oh gig
she's the fixer yes do you have
something a mod on your head
item
um um no do you want this
oh thank you my sunglasses are just
going to have light shining out of it I
don't think it would be
visually visible but uh damn I wish it
was that would be
amazing okay we only have like 30
minutes left until Cali kicks us off
okay so maybe questing time soon oh I
can make dynamite now ooh
yeah I'm done to do Quest I'm ready yeah
I'm
ready where should I put this there's a
chicken give me your
eggs oh does anyone have food I
hungry aren't you
aren't you the one that cooks there's
bacon and egg in the
output I guess I guess I'll just use a
little bit of meat without the egg just
cook the meat yeah oh I have three eggs
wait oh okay here I put it in here thank
you
Eggman does anyone have
have a baton a bon baton baton
um yeah there's some in the weapons
chest nice thank
you
um
uh what was I going to
do everyone's on fire it's so crap we
need to renovate the house make it more
Spacey
I think what we should do is we should
have a third house near the next Traer
because we're we're on like the third
Trader now or some of us are so we're
all going to be over there later so
maybe we should have a house
there I will make the house more
spacious are you breaking our house I
was breaking
renovating here that's a structural wall
right there here we go I got rid of the
loadbearing
wall take take these arrows please off
of my hand thank it's just a few so much
more spacious yeah it's getting
somewhere why is this trash can here in
the middle I'll get rid of the wall to
the bathroom too we don't need privacy
we don't need privacy we do not need
privacy in this household oh we don't
need washroom yeah we're family no you
can still use it just in front of
us I love that agreen the wide open
Toilet
yeah Smash It smash
it yeah we smashing together giggy look
at this wow perfect I would love to see
someone use the toilet with the Cece's
box over it your
head it's okay we're Idols we don't use
toilets yeah
the Sham
[Music]
sandwiches we just have so many meetings
all there's a wild boar over here let's
kill it let's take his eggs kill
it oh I killed him in one
punch she's one punch
girl I feel you guys how to rep thison
and I oh I think think I'm going to head
out so okay okay okay okay take
care byee
byebye how much time do we have repair
kid 20 minutes maybe uh
24 okay let's go make a quest Quest
Quest run run run run shall we go to the
tier two yeah place oh yeah CIA needs an
invite though I think yeah CE CE bicycle
bicycle bicycle
there it's so quiet hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
hello oh we need eggs is there can you
make a chicken
farm I think we might be able to but I
don't know how
got to do some
research uh okay I'll make my way to I
have a quest over there so I'll make my
way there oh I see your quest okay I'll
head over there too all right can I
haven't I haven't gotten the wa who's
the party leader you me oh you is it you
me is k k I think I don't think so I
think it's K is it me oh it was me TW me
all along chicken again be nice to
it oh
uh I was very nice to it really I will
be did you TR it to uh to some food did
you give it some
corn um they like corn
oh they
do can you put the chicken that is with
you on the phone so I can hear it
lot to
say oh it seems like the chicken is
fine okay I'm relieved to hear
that I I let I let the chicken go on its
merry way it went across the road a
that's chicken cross the road huh I'm
glad it did
potatoes oh I can make meat
stew ooh meew M M M
yummy and vegetable
stew meat stew is probably eat
right
uh I'm just it's funny to hear that from
you I
know between meat stew and vegetabl stew
M honestly like IRL though there's so
many times where I just prefer having
something without meat just because it's
just soing yeah sometimes I just want
like a bowl full of vegetables yeah yeah
often when I get like a curry or so I'll
just order a vegetable curry because
they put so much meat in there I don't
even need that much meat oh some days I
just eat a bowl of boiled broccoli and
that's it bowl of broccoli but it season
I season it good so it's tasty that's
good yeah is it grilled or cooked or
raw it's like steamed B you
know yeah and then and then you put like
seasoning like s oil and like peppers in
it and
stuff I hope I don't get lost to you
guys oh you have someone on foot like a
noob we can eat the snake hey now I'm
I'm alone now you can't do
that do what you can't you can't you
can't say that can I call you a noob oh
because I'm T hanging up on you
oh level up do that where was my exp
dipped I don't think you have exp that
um what yeah you don't I don't there
there is no consequence to
dying
awesome uh yeah I've been I've been past
level 65 for a while and I have not
gotten any exp dep from dying so I don't
think it
exists server anyway I am fine with that
wait where did easy baby
server y baby
[Music]
server I can finally jump two blocks
high this zombie is on fire
[Music]
wow he had a lot of loot what's with him
why is he carrying so much stuff for
what what are you
hiding wo snake are we ready to Quest
I'm ready but I don't think everybody's
here wait you're there yeah so far no us
two are here we are wa yeah you've been
waiting we've been waiting this entire
time oh just a little bit we were into
your that long I I was at the house and
I was like I I kept I was like oh are we
going and then I looked at the map and
suddenly
I how could you keep us waiting the
server is going to it is going to close
it's
okay we're
chilling we're just looking around yeah
I'm just killing
things Okay C things you do yeah
yeah just ending some people's lives
some zombies
suffering releasing them from their
suffering just some casual violence you
know as one does during the zombie
apocalypse yeah relatable is it
cathartic yes that's nice I like the
sounds when my knife pierces their flesh
oh like
the yeah I actually don't like
it it's disgusting yeah it's little
gross are you okay I was peacefully
hitting a tree and there's a
dog and a bunch of other
zombies I do be like that
sometimes
my I'm pedaling as fast as I can oh
biker oh you're over there okay wait I
think this is a real life dog no live
it's getting killed by the zombie noit
it's like a friendly dog it's a
friendly oh you guys are here I'm trying
to save the dog hop on the back of my
bik don't hurt the dog save the dog I'll
save you save the dog save the dog
okay oh okay okay
don't Hur
me please here I have a bone do you want
a
bone meat meat
meat need meat to eat but he's so
cute it hurts me too you know while
you're cutting it apart
[Music]
me me tears It Off
oh he's going to Doggy
Heaven okay it's a nice I'm in heaven
now I'm ready everybody here so sorry I
died I'm in now don't worry so sorry I
died
begin let's let the chaos
begin oh you're in already what are you
hitting why are you hitting
that vog she's she's she's she's hung up
about the do ow why why do you keep why
stop running in front of me I'm hitting
logs stop hitting us I'm hitting the
log is there a way up a it's the
fireplace again no watch out for fire oh
God think we just going to leech XP off
of you guys
okay ow you're wearing you're wearing a
nerd hat right yeah yeah okay good the
blue one I want to cheer go
go
oh oh I'm bleeding oh God I'm going to
die the hammer is so die I have one
bandage are you
dead owie I have
a wait that's not you where beo I'm
behind you I'll get the zombie first
okay
hello I'm sorry this is a regular
Band-Aid a delay fire is off yay has
found oh but be careful with the coal on
the ground doesn't that make you go on
fire too no
oh
zombies is this the like to meet you
place yeah is
par parkour civilization hardkour
civilization yeah watch out for the
[Applause]
be I'm
dying
fun I turn them on fire no that's not
how burn them on and my mymer has fire
on it ooh that's so cool it's really
cool cool that is very cool oh I
have wait no antibiotic probably you
really
effective yellow eyes just burn them
yeah Mak sense yeah burn the stinky
corpses oh that must smell bad actually
[Music]
e f are you up there no I'm down down oh
I'm going up people is up here I'm up
here the door is
locked hold I'll just yeah Brute Force
woohoo I'd help but then yeah I'll get
hit probably have a better oh the window
might be
easier at the window no there's
no oh maybe that one I have b a bird
maybe bird guess it's outside still I'm
contributing me too me
too what's the
HPS
660 fine yeah I have
I you stop hitting people I'm trying not
to I'm trying to get the perfect
angle bro 40 HP you owe me a bandage
once I find one I'll band did you
want almost there almost there almost
there the bird that's making the noise
crazy what oh what uh oh we can we can
still hello help help help help help I
am help help help take your time
take your
time uhoh
they're go he went all the way down oh
no he got back
up what okay where what all the way down
oh I can kill him from here
sniper machine gun sniper
oh was that a lady in the
dress I think there was a man
really I saw Red Clothing it reminded me
of the beautiful
dress
water no it's
empty is ity one water yeah it has murky
water this bird is a
chill where is the
bird no
why is so
loud where should I
go where it coming from
the oh oh there you are
[Applause]
okay are you going are you
up where are they there there's one in
the door in the door yeah but it's
locked too I think
I don't even know if I can make the
jum on the roof sled is it
fast man oh
no wait where did they
go I don't know
oh I will avenge you forgot to jump than
you what what happened were you
overwhelmed I I was at like 5
HP oh there's a bird oh he already
opened it up I see it's a really loud
Bird Okay the bird is dead oh thank
God been screaming this entire
time
oh what who is that right behind that
monster it's me how did you make it how
did you make it there I went down the
elevator I believe
genius where's okay still not finished
yeah where's the last
monster been there forever one might
have fallen all the way down I'm not
sure the music stopped yeah they were
like oh you girls are taking too
long we didn't pay for such a long music
track
think I hear it I I hear something yeah
I can't tell where it is
though I
hear
Hello sounds like
crying I found
it oh you're downstairs
all right we did it did it finish
[Applause]
oh okay uh if we have one more nearby
already we could go otherwise does
anybody have mine's kind of far Let's
see we could go to T genen and see if we
can accept another Quest that's close by
um mine's kind of close to her but not
really I think it's over the mountain
yeah we could go straight there finish
it off shall we go to gig's Quest okay
and then to Trader and then ended okay
okay oh wait bicycle
do
ble oh I'm so hungry though I'm so
thirsty I know especially hungry I don't
have any food sham sandwich I have some
raw steaks and a sham sandwich
that's at least something you you can't
get sick eating raw meat
right not
apocalypse maybe I'll eat the raw egg
it's tartar steak
tartar with a little raw egg on top of
[Music]
it well I hope we make it like after
this geigy Quest I hope we make it in
time for the
she closes yeah we're going to have to
speedrun RTA style
yeah are we going the right way yes I
feel like it might take that long just
to drive there
yeah should I drink the Yuka Juice drink
[Music]
it yeah drink it once I get off yeah
after the bicycle
right almost almost there what is it is
a fetch Quest oh Fetch and clear I think
I'm not in time because I'm slow walking
running to the I'm going to go to the
trail it's all good okay okay keep her
open keep her occupied I'll try stalling
as much as I can tell not to close or
else an angry m is going to show up can
we take a
quick yeah okay I
also me too
if only we had more hats I know wait
actually I don't know where your Trader
is yet so I'm going Traer do you see
like from yeah go straight go straight
basically I know in which what direction
you're looking at it's the Green Field I
guess you don't see the map yet but if
you go straight over the mountain thank
you just try to keep on going south okay
okay South
okay and it's like a talk to her we the
the people that come into the store 2
minutes before closing and then we like
take a long time oh but she'll us do you
think you have a size in the
back sorry oh you know the people who
come in at like 9 9:00 p.m. be like do
you have the size in the
back
oh the door of the door back of the door
oh do you have this in a different size
oh yeah it's it's always it's always I I
worked in retail a lot and then it was
always like please look chick in the
back and then you just go into the back
and come back and you're like there's no
we don't have that does anyone have
antibiotics or honey no uh but Trader
Trader dad J Jo GE sells it yeah it's
fine does anyone have any emergency
food no I have raw meat ra me or raw EG
maybe I'll eat this raw corn meal
H oh wow it Traer
J I am met I met her she has a flower in
her
head cute is she a doctor why does she
have I'm wearing it really quickly take
this ooh the art of
mining oh your
iron my IR for minutes uh
oh maybe I don't know in 4 minutes we
should I mean it's not that exact I
would
think but minut four minutes and and
plus like 5 Seconds it'll be okay
right yeah
yeah she we just did a little grinding
off stream just a little this a Time
B it's fine I'll be fine she'll forgive
us okay uh we can begin I'm
here
okay okay what is this
person
okay I'm at the tra I'm happy um see you
guys
tomorrow good night byebye
byebye or good
morning
true why are we doing this to a
graveyard oh no I sprained my knee again
you spr
me guy is kind of
strong I'm
leaving no back into the grave of you oh
God
oh now my knee is
sped oh
no are we looking for he's getting back
up he's getting what I thought he
satchels yeah I think we're looking for
the Satchel he dead now no he's not okay
now he's
dead I already looked in that casket
there's nothing in there I thought this
was a barbecue grill and I was likeing
out of graveyard oh wa in here
maybe oh yeah oh oh there's a whole
dungeon down here
probably careful oh yeah I found my
scary things down here
[Music]
wa watch out for the spikes there are
spikes
spikes oh there
okay this is cool this is different mhm
maybe we got to get rid of these things
here and there to see what we need
no
oh I'm
starving oh watch out behind
you
that a I found mine it seems good maybe
for else out watch
out oh he's falling green so easy to
see oh
scary oh that's
me you're both green
green get out of my
swamp it's her swamp get out
[Music]
of I have 30
HP oh there's a oh there's like a hidden
thing over here oh car who is that oh
nice oh book crate I love
books
books there's honey here you still need
honey oh I need
honey you should you should read this
you can yeah you can eat it
oh
D I'll buy mine from
Jane okay Senai Tex is strong as
ever it works it just
works have been sping four generations
here
oh a good
mix uh graveyard I missing their
satel do we all have I have mine I have
mine oh we're we're
done where is
Exit please don't close please where is
the exit oh it's here it's
here baby please don't
[Music]
close was it 900 p.m. then she when she
closes
I think
950 yeah somewhere around 950 okay we'll
be fine maybe how do you get there
though the there's a there's a windy
path there's a windy path behind the
house if you see the map I see
it I'll follow
fora yeah she closed early on us last
time like 10
minutes but I think we're
fine I hope
9:45 we're 2 minutes
over we're going to get banned oh no
we're going to get reported don't report
us
please come I'm stck me
too I looked away for a
moment are we going up a mountain is
that the right way I don't know yeah go
up the mountain and then slide down the
cliff you won't take fall damage if you
just slide down okay oh I changed the
controls or something something's
weird
oh I don't there's birds up here I
really want to check the nest but I'm
not
going I see
it I'm going to slide down with my oh my
gosh it's a little
steep ah thank you Mouse button is it
really okay it's so
steep run wait did you go left
or I think I went right I'm going to
slide down on my
butt well good job I knew oh yeah this
this will work especially now with my
parkour skill
this do I yes
run run
run another successful day in seven days
to die
yeah slowly I walk into the
church oh that's a lot of
ammo that I don't
use maybe
this oh tier three stuff
now someone I still don't have their
hands dirty oh I would oh there's a
night only Quest apocalypse hygiene and
all sugar
butts whose Sugar Butt are you talking
about could be anyone's could be yours
that could be a cute nickname hey Sugar
Butt what's up hey Sugar Butt
she gave me mats to craft a mini bike
[Music]
yeah
shotgun oh there's battle up
magazines but I
don't should I should I buy this for
Cali CI wanted uh batter up right yeah
see what she's blun weapon baseball bat
yes yes
yes uh with the volume does it matter
like if she already read volume 3 can
she read it again I don't know what
don't you can't read it again ah cuz
it's a book I'll keep it in there maybe
she read it
already Okay farewell I am so
[Applause]
hungry goodbye see you tomorrow bye byee
by sleep
well just going to eat this stew Quest
failed oh that always shocks me I know
right sell it sell
what I'm getting so
strong yes I'm a professional boxer now
do you still have you still have that
perk for drunken fist we need to get you
lots of beer doesn't do anything does it
help me I don't know we got to find out
yes books books books books wait come
outside in case she closes come I'm
afraid the stuff is going to get stuck
in there and we'll be forever separated
armor for you not armor sorry ammo ammo
ammo oh here's book for you as well
thank you so sweet such sweet exchanges
who here uses shotgun uh Callie does
okay I'll keep it for now I forgot to
sell
the woman let me sell my money for more
money you have 20
seconds
easy
JMA thank
[Music]
you watch her JMA yeah is she
JMA I imagine her to be JMA in a
different timeline different Universe
yeah
sces out
there well I'll think about that skill
point next time all right I'll I'll I
guess I'll end it here to me too
for had a good time
bye
[Music]
byebye oh oh we're failing again let me
leave thank you again for watching today
we're playing all week
long we're addicted I need to reset the
timer that was good I'm getting really
strong
with my
punches very that's too big very
strong it was intense I and I just got
another upgrade I want to punch
something I want to punch
zombies okay I'm going to go as well and
I'll read all the super chats I'll do a
big catch up catch up on
everything cuz we're just we're just no
lifing this game this week also in case
you're worried I saved the members super
chats in a spreadsheet so that I can
read them they're not going to get
lost I have them so don't don't worry if
you were worried about those old ones I
haven't forgotten about them and I've
saved them so they will not be lost to
time but thank you very much for hanging
out I'm going to go get some
rest byebye FW bye
[Music]
a