[Music]
always keep your on the line of the
Horizon come on climb on the
brighter W will knock you down and Cur
pull you
out life with the trying to make a
splash but every stream has crashed on
but still we keep on
[Music]
swimming give me 000 youing neck with a
home we not
[Music]
Al fun Hang
On Come Sail Away with
Me my f beond us see the sun shine on
our Liv's no dream we can reach so no
matter how we
go
I'm the
same keep your on the line of horizon
come
[Music]
brigh
hello what's up hello YouTube
the am one looks very
blurry she's perfect she's cute just
like my flash games
do it works it
works she's
dancing yeah there it is there it is
there it is there it is there it
is oh nice moves and I'm slapping G's
head
B hi guys today we're going to play
paranormal par paranormal cleanup which
is phasmophobia I guess mixed with
viscer Cleanup Detail have you guys ever
played that oh yeah I've SE I haven't
played it but I've seen I've seen it V
clean up goo yeah body parts and aliens
that explode it's a lot of fun and this
is the same but also we're going to be
hunted by spooky ghost
doesn't that sound
exciting I want I want to know what was
your motivation to invite me to a horror
game collab that you know I hate horror
games because because you're very
entertaining I think to watch to play
horror games content AKA content I'll
try to be useful but normally with these
games I'm not very useful also honestly
I wasn't expecting either of you to say
yes I was I didn't know I don't know if
you would have the energy or if the hour
would would be weird or if the game type
wouldn't be what you wanted to play so
thank you both of you for saying yes it
was surprising hell yeah we're going to
clean up those
pizzas oh yeah The Moldy Pizza the
pizzas that good I left
over I Gathering your lunch I am the
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle we're going
to wait that trash piles trash bag we
have to pick up the trash we have to
take it to the dumpster and we have to
dispose of moldy pizzas
16 all oh it's all 16 okay so what's 16
uh split by
three uh 369 eight no not eight that's
two uh 369 e 36 36 12 15 that's
5.3 uh 6 point 5.3 okay chat says 5.3
everybody has to clean up at least five
things 5 5.3 item
s or what or what or you're punished
yeah you're fired we fired you're fired
you're never you're never going to club
I'm the session host I I own this
company oh god
[Laughter]
oh wait should we what a what an
unfortunate company to own what's the
name of our
company oh
ooh oh ooh okay company we CLE for you
oh o oh ooh oh ooh spooky cleaner oh
spooky cleaner oh
[Music]
ooh radio it's a it's a ghost when he
notices there's people in the house he's
like
oh
oh oh starting so clean oh yeah uh job
starting in 45 seconds I'm so excited
guys our first job hire do you think
we'll do well will we impress will we be
asked no idea how to even play it I
don't even care I just want to get paid
are you good to can we how's your
cleaning
skills I'm pretty good pretty good yeah
me too me too okay no decent what about
you g okay if we have two two that are
pretty good that'll cancel out the one
that is not good at cleaning so this is
this is perfect this will work out you
mean your room was your room was always
pretty clean when I saw it oh thank you
cuz it had to be cuz I was scared that
somebody was going to come
in I didn't be like like stand outside
stand
outside don't come in back me
in oh oh that was kind of
spooky yeah well the transition very
spooky what's going on why am I facing a
read it GA 22 whe a duplex has fallen
into to repair one side just renovated I
didn't read fast enough I can't do
it paranormal level one dumped on the
word
disre
okay
hello let's seeing of
Ctrl oh our are here crouching crouching
oh okay
craft maybe we will who knows how do you
pick this up
good
oh oh okay God why do we walk like Mario
and
Luigi what
you this walk cycle is so
poopy so we're bringing the dust pan and
the flashlight anything else I don't
think there's anything else right now
maybe we have to unlock it we need a
power washer where's oh yeah dumpster
where's the entrance I think well
there's a door oh a bone what outside
there's stuff
too or is that wait that's one of the 20
so that feels like
extra oh I see there's like piles with
with
flies okay okay yeah can you guys Shine
the Light over here I can't really see I
don't turn on my
flashlight is the flashlight
Duty you're closer to my
house and what's up oh the lights go on
okay um taking out the
trash open oh you can go inside with e
inside the closet this shift is going to
be easy when I have you guys by my side
carrying everything
CLE all right flashlight flashlight Duty
I'm cleaning but nothing's getting clean
why maybe there is you have to crouch a
light switch here though yeah it's these
piles of flies wherever they are breaks
yeah wait who is who who are you I'm I'm
Bruce it doesn't say your name who used
to live here oh why does that door sound
like that sweep sweep I found note wait
I've discovered hidden passengers within
the house leading me to believe that
there is more to this place it meets the
eye I must explore further to oh God why
are you so big
what what you're
h oh
bone fre bone tasty
snack that's quite the
animation Watson shaped like a tank
Watson you're the first line of defense
won oops sorry I turned it up oh sorry
I'm so sorry I found a not a not a out a
note too says lately I've been having
Vivid Visions oh did you just read this
no different of the victims as if
they're trying to communicate with me
they appear tormented Des for their
stories to be
heard you go in the closet how do I get
out of this message cool
torment they breathe so loud how do you
put the message
down do I have
to
oh we're new on the job um all right all
the lights are mostly on unless
someone's turning them off but I think
they're mostly on for now wait where's K
uh I don't know
there's a dead
dog what or exit there's a picture of a
dead dog it's not it's just
sleeping are we paid by the
hour uh I hope so St turnning off the
light wait how do I switch to how do I
switch to the dust pin L you're a
horse oh my godse
hello have s s sweep ladies
number two number two we got a trash
pile the lights are turning off wait
where's the dumpster it's it's this
house has been condemned it's just bad
electrical I
think our boss would never put us In
Harm's Way right the pizza did you eat
that I disposed of it I didn't eat it I
would never do such a thing that is
disgusting can you guys come with me
back to the house I'm scared I got to
throw away the trash Oh you can go in
this way I think so we are in a part of
the
house it's quite nice here is this the
same place I don't
know looks so clean oh there's there's
another pile here is this get this
sweeping where's that pile there it is
help me sweep sweep sweep
sweep
I sweep sweep sweep is it is this bait
sweep sweep sweep also I can't switch to
the dust pen how how do you do it hit
number two press one F huh what two yeah
just hit the number two on your on your
keyboard I'm pressing it doesn't work
it's funny so I'm only going to
be showing the flashlights for you guys
right it's a useful
wait where's the front door we need to
get out of here to throw away the trash
number
lock wait can we all pick up a oh this
the B
you can only take one trash bag at a
time that's the
bathroom spooky ghost hello is there
anyone here what the
who they just broke the window wait
really did you see it and hear it that
looks like a front door you walked by it
guys this is the basement we need to
find a
[Music]
key ke's got to be in like a drawer or
something right I saw I
saw oh
[Music]
don't die girl I'm trying oh she's
coming I found the
closet I think the the window breaking
was the first sign of a ghost coming oh
good chasing
you are you in the in the closet
now that ghost was really scary guys I
don't think I can go back out there good
I don't hear you are you
dead she's you muted she's
m oh she really
died playing
realistically you guys like it wasn't
that scary it wasn't that scary cuz you
didn't just H okay whatever I'm going to
be I'm what are you are you why are you
crawling around like that are you okay
I'm dead do are dead can you still clean
and make yourself
useful it's still here oh
my I don't think it goes away I don't
know what we're supposed to do we feed
The Moldy pizza so dead good luck Kiara
what we only cleaned
12% what why does it not go away how do
you make it go
away
G you missed a spot shut
up you're still carrying the dust pen
yeah are you alive oh hey who is that
who's it I'm in the I'm in the kitchen
car get out of the I'm no no you say
they're still around I'm not going to
get out get out and help
me
how oh hey where me how do I do that can
you
res clean me up put me I to get out of
the closet and it would it I think the
game is bucked cuz every time I press it
will only re relive the scene of me
entering the closet oh I see is my way
you're out now I don't know how to help
you are we supposed to have a medit oh
maybe there were Med kits in the loading
screen I need a mini map how do we get
out of
here well this way the door is this way
but so is the the ghost the ghost lady
is this
way can I open doors I hear
her are you
sure she she's on that side I'm pretty
sure what's that side this is she like
around the corner IRL P point of view oh
I think she's gone for
now actual girl
P all right I see the front door I think
is that the front door front door
spotted wait I think
this ah my inventory slot one is on five
not the front door they're just
completely wrong this the front
door why is this
confusing clean faster where is
everybody I'm looking for the front door
ooh looking for a
medkit are there Med kits
okay this is the
garage why are the doors opening so loud
I found the front
door where bra
me is there a trash can there yes oh
might have dropped off a trash bag nice
I'm getting work done they're going to
get a
raise can the boss give themselves a
raise or is that illegal yeah
no oh the front door is this way oh God
don't crawl over around my feet like
[Laughter]
that I'm going to get some more
trash okay how do I stand up
again if we die we die together yeah
good at that angle isn't that your
normal angle anyway that you live with
day by
day
yes
wait where where is GAA over here I mean
down here wait there's an upstairs up
here let's maybe we should clean
upstairs first cuz it's right by the
front door okay where's the pizza you
think it'd be in the kitchen I got one
pizza so far it was like randomly
somewhere woof woof oh there's the
stairs hope I can climb them oh yeah oh
there's even an
attic spooky attic is no no big no no no
pizza box did you go up to the attic no
I'm I'm next to the stairs kind
of did I just eat that
yummy wait I found a note things are
getting worse objects move on their own
doors slam shut Shadows Dart through
hallways Emma's nightmares are getting
more intense I'm hearing
things o what is that oh is that
you there's something crawling around on
the floor it's G kill it step on it wait
where is the exit I want to thr this oh
yeah it's downstairs I think to the left
okay found okay
nice Drop It Like It's
Hot GE I
wish I wish I had normal height leg no I
dropped my I dropped all
my I Dro my cleaning supplies and
everything
else pick it back up I I threw it into
the garbage disposal and I can't get it
out can you jump in this game how do you
get inside my God you look terrible
going down the stairs this is Lally
Co it spawns new ones
okay oh okay can it spot me some new
legs my
God I think you have to be like this
forever it's your handicap now man we
need a med kit maybe maybe can find one
somewhere but I haven't seen anything
that we can pick
up oh Pizza do I dare to enter this room
can I use it as new legs you baby
modeo all right we got to look for more
trash yeah come with me please I don't
want to be alone locked locked we need
to look for a key but I haven't seen
anything like that did this ghost just
leave after she killed me she's like
okay job
done yes well it is easy mode so maybe
that's why are you absolutely incapable
of doing anything good or can you clean
still I can't do anything I swear I
swear yeah I want to say emotional
support we need
that I'll be the find the pizza sniff it
out sniff sniff sniff sniff sniff Sni
sniff W it's in here it's in here Sni
sniff s there's no pizza wait can I
through the doors wait close this
door okay a close through the door Clos
got oh the lights are turning off and I
think she's haing I think she's
hating I'm going to
hide I found trash woof woof woof woof
sniff really no you're messing with me
no I did it's it's in the bathroom
across the hallway I
swear okay I see her she's coming for
you guys I'm hiding in the closet
bye-bye okay I'm hiding to
the grow
grow B her bite her
ankles into the apartment she's walking
into the house W lick her toes W oh I
hear
her oh I see
her she's over here so
red she's coming bright she's
coming what you call
me
you're going to leave her over
here what would Man's Best Friend do
that to you would I really do that wo w
w w woof here woof woof carpet shark a w
carpet shark
what cleaner uh yeah there's another
one oh no now she just walked out okay
ah I see you g you did good job getting
rid of her are you in here yeah this one
this one no oh no it's the other one
there's another
one what really why why did she come for
me man what are we supposed to do do we
just like does she just go away yeah I
guess so she walked out
again okay I'm I'm I'm I'm going to R
I'm going to come out too oh I hear her
to clean I'm going to go up you hear her
still yeah the lights won't turn on so
she's still out
there well she's pretty
slow but when I went in the closet she
wasn't anywhere near me though that's
the
thing did she grab you from the closet
or she just I don't know how to describe
it but I screamed it was very
scary I love bunny pets
everywhere bark bark bark look trash
here I swear I swear right be look
out oh good there's a closet in here and
you can't use it so it's
mine where's K I'm on the second floor
I'm
I'm are we on the second floor you guys
on the first on the first floor oh lead
me to the exit G
you know where it is cuz I'm lost I know
follow
me you're just leading me to her or
something huh no see front door is still
open
nice safety safety this is a massive
house it's like a duplex it's a duplex
yeah okay I just got scared by G's
stream that I have open in on the
window W wol are you upstairs yes come
get you are you in attic no I have to
work um don't get me I want to
work
hello
away can you warn
me
open where see other where's the keys
where's the oh I have the basement key
by the way uh I don't remember where it
is
though was it
in B in the
bathtub we don't even need the
bones we
need proper trash found the basement all
right come on let's go to the basement
basement time okay wait woof
woof uh W all I see is the top of my
[Music]
hair to get strong floor shark uh you
can't be down here cuz I just unlocked
it oh okay o I found a
bone yeah
that there's nothing here oh
trash Pizza you pizza oh I
take I hear her I hear her
uhoh uh-oh do you see her no I think
you're fine no I don't see anything I
found another closet though I guess I'll
get in it has to look out don't worry
the Roomba has a camera on
it she's definitely somewhere close by
dark down here did you guys turn a light
on did you leave any I tried to turn a
light on ah then I'm coming
out um I think the power is still
out yeah she's haunting don't you see
her oh you see her no I hear her but I
don't see you
she there she is yeah cuz I hear the
footsteps there she hide but don't hide
in my
closet unless you can is that possible
to people in one he's
coming doie doie I wonder if we had
trash bag we could like throw it at her
maybe got a try give it a try I found
pizza but I can't reach
it this is so just one bite
please
is pizza all that these people
eat yeah Left Behind balanced meal oh I
found more trash meat W
cheese pizza she gone I think she's
upstairs she still here I maybe she's
going up I heard some creaking sounds
lead me to the pizza wolf wolf where are
you uh
okay this way this way oh there's K
hi over here over here over here behind
you behind you this way no this way yeah
yeah yeah this way this way this way H
this way you this way this way why are
you
running where I can't see you are you
dead I'm on the floor I see you okay
down oh wait not this way not this this
way this way this way wait this way what
you don't even know I do look it all
looks the same there's one there there's
some
here why do they have such a huge oh
okay
uh there's Pizza there's Pizza I swear
there's Pizza there's Pizza over here
it's gone you lied to us SC there's
pizza here no see there's pizza pizza
pizza pizza ah okay nice oo see youash
you can find all of this stuff o I'll
take it and there's pizza here where'
you guys go still on the same floor just
walking
around
oh wait come get this
pizza piz P piz piz piz is it with
pineapples what the was that oh
okay oh okay thought somebody like broke
my neck but no oh no I'm me picking up
the pizza let's throw this away let's
throw this away oh okay there's stairs
over here but I don't know if it's the
entrance I don't know I don't
remember pushing
me don't step on the
room go I don't think this is the way we
came in well let's find the other stairs
wait what if it's a shortcut it could be
a shortcut out uh well okay the way we
came in was like the shortcut oh okay
there we go my trash
open the door thank you your trch fell
down
again dud hold on
sorry
okay get a lookout yeah look
out I don't know where we oh there's
trash over here so this is what I think
we're pretty far I think we're in the
other duplex we probably have to find
the exit and then get to the other
building okay map is huge oh I yeah bark
you hear
her morning bark
bark I found Pizza I don't hear her
anymore Pizza Pizza I will we'll come
back for the pizza pizza pizza pizza not
the way
Pizza where pizza pizza pizza this
way pizza pizza pizza this
way piz pizza oh oh I see it the pizza
will lead us this
door exit nice is this the exit though
we oh yeah uhoh I'm out I'm out
[Music]
okay why am I so short this is such a
good is true to true to your real
size I
want
okay all right pizza shark
Pizza shark should we go down again or
was there more stuff down there I feel
like we saw most of below there was a
bag here that we can take with us
wherever that is I don't remember
somewhere over
here later guys I got to go I'm in the
closet right now okay me too me too I'm
in the
closet good alarm GAA good one protect
following you guys or
something I'm I'm in the closet I don't
even see her I haven't seen her at all
all I see is geta dragging her legs
around like little slug why did why did
I die what
is streaming the
game
so wait if I like a slug do I leave a
slime
Trail uh I didn't see one good what is
it with you recently in slime huh do you
blame me have you seen a slime girl
before um yes I yes I blame you have you
not wanted to to play with slime before
just in a general sense slime as a child
yeah as a so you're telling me what
about you Watson you want to play with
slime have you made slime yeah uh no
wait yes as a kid I made
slime I'm I see recently you haven't
made neither of you have made slime
recently recently no is it like borax
and glue
yeah I think maybe I'll go
upstairs okay I
will also where's
upstairs I'm in the first duplex right
[Music]
now I don't know where I'm following
Kara I'm still in the one that we just
came back from outside wait Med
kit oh
nice
a
please Med kid please give me legs take
it I take it please give me my legs
please I can use this to heal myself
when hurt it a no please wait what
oh what the was
that I feel is is it using it on you I
feel like they're forgetting to sprout
I'm healing
I'm a
priest welcome back to live let's go I'm
alive now you can
clean
no sweep sweep sweep let's go upstairs
oh I'll follow you upstairs and a note
but I hear her I don't care you hear her
oh there's stuff there nice you take it
I'm going to die again this is what's oh
how do I turn my flashlight
I everything's fine did you turn your
flashlight no you didn't okay you should
be
[Music]
fine I got spooked if she finds me the
game is right and I don't want to play
anymore if she finds me this is such how
do I turn off the
light do you have to do I have to I
always kept it on I
think just bring out your dust
pan dustan back
her no but I don't hear her anymore do
you hear her she was outside I'm I'm
like at the entrance to the outside
backyard thing okay
okay sweep sweep sweep okay she's
sleeping then
I I'm out as
well what's in new B oh the what was
that they got to sweep sweep sweep are
you guys in the basement by second
floor Pizza I found the
key the bedroom key think that's for one
of the upstairs rooms oh and I found
another Med kit just in case something
happens oh
nice I have trash but I don't remember
where the exit is
always how about that race boss can I
get can I get a race hey what do you
want to advance yes all right I have a
contract for
you better check it with your lawyer
beforehand you never know oh she's
right here oh am I first floor yeah
right below the
stairs tell us when she's coming up if
you can see it no I can't see it wait do
you she's coming up she's coming up car
right behind you you lying he's coming
up okay master bedroom is
unlocked know nice
Pizza no pizza
pizza oh my game lagged or something I
teleported where am
I okay I my job I'm just doing my jum
what the I found a lot of trash where
in the master bedroom on the second
floor all
right where's the master
bedroom um the room that I will be
coming out of hi oh
[Music]
hello I can't
see I will try to throw this away oh I
get a lot of like teleportation lag just
got to sweep sweep
sweep is it safe right now yeah
yeah awesome dropping this off hey we
have 62% already ow you got a
medit the door is
locked
oh the door it's closed oh where's the
trash front door yeah the front door
closed the front door is right to the
left of the staircase so if it's closed
that means I guess she's doing her thing
yeah but I don't hear her I went back
inside wait I'm not scared I hear trash
but I don't see
any wait when the trash is so bad you
can hear
it where am I hearing things what was
that wait can can Kiara only open a
master bedroom key or with yeah I open
this door too now to open each one I
guess
okay oh okay this is just another
entrance sweep sweep
sweep well I guess the rest of the trash
is probably in the other duplex or
there's also a garage we need to find a
garage key mhm true
okay keep your eyes open my eyes are
open my eyes are
peeled I hate that saying I'm so peeled
and ready it's it's terrifying peel open
just for
you peel like an orange
E I found trash I I found the trash
uhoh
uhoh is she around she's right by night
oh she's in our room uhoh I think I'm
dead okay I better the
hide this
trash she's right in front of my closet
I think she's going to open
it she can't she can't she doesn't have
to Rite to closets are supposed to be
safe spaces I know she's like breathing
in I'm got s a kitty she's breathing her
air inside my
closet what does it smell like musty myy
Pizza I'm scared she's going to jump
scare
me are you girls on the on the first
floor right next to me is she still
there yes she's right in front of me
still hasn't she scared you
yet uh no not yet why she's about to
she's like getting
louder
did you do it
no and you go on on the first floor
second floor I
think should I run as a
distraction uh I guess you could if you
want no but you have a med kit now at
least what can happen actually I'm going
to come out too he just disappeared so I
think we're safe oh why didn't she kill
you what
the I was waiting to here you go a I
guess I'm not as tasty as a
shark where was that trash I here okay I
got a
bag check if we see the garage key in
here do you see any type of
key I threw the trash out the window oh
my God it's good it's good yeah it's
right in front of the dumpster can I
jump out the window no no
I got a
note all
right doing our
jobs
8%
andit oh here we go the other
duplex and 72 oh you put in my bag okay
cuz you put in a bag of mine before I
wonder oh no we came up through the
basement here so I guess the last place
is probably the garage we need to find a
key
what about the attic we didn't really
check the attic did we oh the attic of
this this floor no we checked it the
other just in case there's a pizza
there's two um floors and two duplex so
we didn't check this attic a there's
still an attic key too the door can't be
opened oh
yeah where do we find
that think key I don't know we guys keep
keys in the kitchen or something like
that's where I would you can't open a
look for a key kitchen I'll look in the
kitchen for a key okay okay kitchen pry
key you guys have a drawer in your
kitchen that's filled with like just
junk mail and a junk
drawer dedicated to junk yeah I keep it
out in the open so that at least
sometimes it might remind me that I have
something that's all the wired
headphones
go do you know like when you go like
when you fly to Japan and they give you
the wired headphones oh you're not
supposed to keep those what do you mean
you're supposed to give that back oh no
no can you even use that on your own
because don't they usually have like two
plugs on them yeah they're kind of
scummy now they they changed it so it
has to be like stereo headphones you
can't just have the one plugs you know
people keep it I
guess I found my Twi
bag I think it depends
yay understandable go are getting better
I've seen like they they have some
soundproofing headphones now quite nice
oh yeah putting in some bu okay I think
some I hear her the second floor I think
is
[Laughter]
pretty okay I'm not scared I'm not
scared I'm not scared I'm not scared I'm
not scared I'm not scared that was so
close that was so
close where are
you the the around the master bedro but
she's she's still close by to me did she
one duplex
two I don't know I can't tell them
apart it must be duplex
one oh my God to be duplex two loud I
hear her to my right that
one I don't know why my cream so hard
it's not even that scary
did she get you no I'm I'm safe it was
like 1 cm off or whatever that is in
foot
language uh oh she's right here a
toenail clipping where is she a toenail
C she's here no she's she's at my closet
again she's going to the attic she's
going to the attic all right we're good
on okay we're on the yeah we're on the
first floor this this is duplex number
two this is duplex ad Doo Oh outside
hello damn I'm shaking like crazy I got
to go not scary by the
way not
scary n do
you not like this experience some
troubles not doing so well yeah for me
it's safe now who's opening
doors I'm going to leave the
uh I'm on the first floor and I'm
hiding where did I go are we
good up where are you I'm in the second
house first floor I
think she did she mute herself again
hello you hear me yeah yes okay
hi I didn't m i I get
scared I get scared of shaking my little
Shar you got so scared you you became
quiet I did cuz I don't want to get CED
again don't you play like way more worse
horror games than this
yes we played
Outlast yeah who hasn't played out
though out no you didn't did you I
played the first one
when really long time ago
how long ago like I don't know four or
five years ago whenever it came out oh
would you be willing to Play It
Again perhaps uh yeah I thought it was
pretty fun I liked it I thought it was a
good
[Music]
game nice PC setup these guys have
here wait is this the second house I'm
in or the first house
found I'm in duplex number two this must
be duplex one how do you know cuz a
duplex number one was to the left that
was the first duplex that we went into
and then we went number two that's the
second you good orientation senses yeah
yeah I can't find a key she's got good
map neither I'm going to go to different
building oh where is
this basement key basementy key oh wait
maybe there's a key in the
basement uh oh yeah probably all right
I'm going down to the basement I'm
coming except I don't know how to get
there hello you know there a kitchen
right where's
everybody we're trying to find the
basement this way dlex number
two in the dup to and we're going down
to the basement which is in the kitchen
I'll try to find you oh wow you're right
I guess it's pretty normal for the
basement to be like in the kitchen we're
in the basement now so that connects to
the first two PLS if you go into the
basement there smells like
basement what is the key look
[Music]
like I'm so
alone it's going to turn into musical
closets down here come come oh wait
hello
oh uh you found the
electricity move L get out of the way
damn it she stole my was that you guys
that sound just she stole my God dang
closet is she haunting push you out the
way I just let you have it you're the
streamer today okay streamer
privileges
I guess I'm in an advantage cuz she
would prefer to haunt uh at two people
cuz there's higher chances that she gets
someone oh yeah I don't know how to turn
the flashlight off
okay don't turn the flashlight off in
this game what did you say what she's
gone I think so you want to get up uh
you first no no no after you be my guest
boss you are the CEO of course uh
streamer first oh no no no no this is
this CEO boss this is hi hi hi hi you
need
the I
come
content no I still hear her I can't find
anything is it getting louder now that
I've done that no I feel like uh she's
upstairs probably on my floor I'm I'm on
the first floor right now you're on the
first floor yeah cuz I had to run you
took like the only closet down
there all doors are closed I can't get
out chat do you guys know where we can
get the garage key yeah guys where's the
garage key look up the guy quick get the
wiki
open oh maybe she's mad that I keep
turning the power back
on yeah I think it triggers her okay I'm
going downstairs again lights on
stinky oh it's so it's got to be here in
the basement oh I hear Gage the garage I
hear
trash I hear therefore I
am can you kick down this
door okay yeah
baby
help me help I'm in the torture room
help okay torture room where are you
how'd you get in there there's a torture
room the the garage key must be in
there there's a bloody
bone the light turned
off what
the now why would they do
that did I do that
do I hear your footsteps or
mine uh I'm not walking around I was uh
now I'm walking
[Music]
around I think you're hearing your own
footsteps so no garage key
huh hello I can't get into the house the
house I'm stuck outside oh she trapped
you yeah I'm trying to find maybe it's
better this
way hey
ghosty oh
nice all right bless you I want to can
someone pick me up I'm scared I'll try
find I'm at the trash
can just want to go where you guys are I
don't have a basement
key hello hi hi am
hiair back oh God I was walking around
here the whole time but I couldn't find
the way to the below oh it's in the
kitchen oh it's a paintbrush I thought I
found a key to paintbrush where is the
key is this stupid
key where haven't we checked yet we
checked the
basement check the up
St is the key in the garage who put the
key to the garage is in the garage it
logs out check the kitchen in the Attic
or the master
bedroom
uh wait that would make sense if the key
to the next room is in the one that you
need a key to open does that make sense
yeah oh wait
uh
what why do I scream so much why do I
scream so much why do I scream there's
nobody here I heard her very clearly you
were right next to me so you should have
heard her please no please no please no
please no please
no oh gooda was almost caught or
what you think you're safe huh is I yeah
I
do come at me
Stinky I'm also in a closet right now so
I can't I'm going to get to your closet
first ha wait actually she shaking she's
shaking ooh I see her passing by on your
on your stream hey
stinky oh you found the voice
feature I did but I don't think she
hears voices so we're good oh
okay all right time to come out again
okay are you sure about
that uh no I going back in yeah I'm
going back
is
money where are chickens big big
chickens I wonder if the key could be
like outside in the backyard or
something I'm going to look around in
there are you in the house still I am in
the house still I'm pretty close to you
I think you behind me is is you and me
in here then Kiara is where k k was
right next to me yeah oh we're all
together as an
exit oh you're right right by the exit
yeah the whole way is this like
heartbeating thing ever going to go away
or is she suppos I don't know I mean I
still hear her so okay that's probably
why oh good I saw her again I saw her
there she
goes there she's Bey she goes again she
needs to freak okay I think she's
gone you think so as the boss says
she's G all right get back to work okay
back to work stinkies let's look around
on the
floor what hi there's a med kit here
there we
go where are we
going uh I'm just going to check around
wait look up do you see me where in the
[Music]
window watch out behind
you all right I was hoping there'd be
like a patio table or something maybe
the key on the table or I don't know
anybody got the key for the hot
tub only have the bedroom key we're hot
tubing
oh
oh oh another Med
kit we're finding medkits but we're not
finding the
key yeah we should uh maybe we should do
a sweep of each master bedroom cuz I
think I think we only went into the
master bedroom of one duplex did we oh
the door just closed right in front of
me one
door why we can check the other the
other
one
okay are the keys easy to find
door yeah they highlight
yellow I guess when you highlight when
you like cover over them you can tell
it's like a yeah it stands out okay but
from far away it just looks like a
little blob I'm checking the attic
again not the attic the
basement
okay
[Music]
hello hello hear someone oh my okay I
found the torture
rooms what the why what why would you
have something like
that maybe it's a old house
um that's why from the medieval times or
what yeah I guess so they're history
buff they really like um that
stuff she's
haunting once again she's
coming the usual roomit where is
she I don't know but the front door is
locked I can't get
out key
we key hello
key all right chat stop playing around
tell us where the key
is or or the Roomba gets it no not the
Roomba
please the key where de there the key
locations are completely randomized in
the game they're always on flat surfaces
but there are just too hard to see uhhuh
ah they're
randomized I feel like we have maybe
yeah it's like in the upstairs of the
hello one of
the
houses I'm on the floor too
somewhere did you see her
no I thought I did but it was the carpet
I hear her though oh she's coming she's
coming she's coming she's coming she's
coming oh yeah you're shaking okay
that's that means it's safe for
me
a
bone
key I don't think
so
okay in the
[Music]
basement I'm in
the basement flat
surfaces all right there's a lot of
those
loud loud loud lady is loud lady is
looking I think it's gone okay I heard
it like disappear and the lights came
back okay
[Music]
down
well all right I'm going back to the
other duplex cuz I think I've checked
this one pretty
thoroughly what was that well the lights
went out again hello yeah the lights
went out again what the
can she
[Music]
stop you scared me
hello wait I didn't see it in that
Master
bedroom yeah I think we only checked one
master bedroom
oh but the duplexes say they share Keys
that's kind of weird they must be really
close to each
other wait we missing attic and garage
key both of
them yes wow how come we haven't found
anything it's hard to see
it's
dark someone should be on light
duty light doesn't
work car are you on the second floor
yes but
um I heard
that but uh I don't I don't need to be
there I can go anywhere cuz there's
nothing here anyway no I'm on the first
floor uh where freaking key also don't
see any key
anywhere I am coming to the other
side oh the birds are chirping they're
happy uhoh oh she back she
is okay don't scream don't scream don't
scream my froat hurts can she can she's
at me she's at
me oh my God you died
[Music]
[Applause]
scary are you
okay it's okay J you want take both of
us right is it she's still standing in
front of me is it even worth Reviving
myself when she's in front of me no
wait it said press each of why is she
waiting yourself can you crawl are you
RBA mode we have
[Music]
no she's going to make
it you can bark I'm so
[Music]
scary I screamed so loud I scary though
isn't it thank you for your
sacrifice I want to stay you know what
I'll just stay on the low for a little
bit I found another Med kit so when you
use yours you can pick one up
oh she's she's still
[Music]
outside
where is a key it's this freaking
key maybe somewhere in the
bathroom scary not scary oh hi oh the
door opened oh she's gone she's gone
maybe saf she's not gone no but she's
still chilling outside in the same spot
oh would like the backyard I see her
yeah next to the garbage truck oh you
see her oh she's on oh so she can go
outside there too wow she yeah she's uh
in the entrance right at the door she's
right outside we should just call the
police or something now she's gone now
she's going
to I'm turning on the
lights thank
[Music]
you I'm Reviving
myself
y
I don't want that to ever happen again
that was
terrifying wait we should close the do
careful maybe turning on some lights
we'll be able to see the small key tiny
key I checked this room I checked
everywhere down here there's no key down
here I'm going to where's the
stairs I've checked this room
come here there's a another Med kit in
here oh oh wait where is it here in this
room here I'm closing the doors to rooms
that I've checked
thoroughly okay good
idea I also have a med kit in case you
need it I got one thank you okay is it
in the
toilet I've closed these doors cuz we
we've already
checked uh it has to be in the upstairs
at least it's not down here where where
are the stairs
anyways
MH are there two different basement or
they're connected right they're
connected so not worth checking again
turn off the lights
again ever since I revived myself my
game is stuttering like crazy oh bug
that's the5
wonder it was pretty cheap so I forgive
[Music]
it it's freaking
key two keys two freaking
keys I'm thinking it's in the basement
or there's like a door in the basement
yeah there there are hidden passages
wasn't the Tor room hidden passage or no
oh was
it
I very slightly hear her
oh oh you br you you broke down that
door so maybe there's more that you can
break down did it show like in yellow
that you can break something down it was
it was wooden there's like wood baring
it and then I went up to and it kicked
it down okay oh all right M I'll keep an
eye open for that where's the basement
the chat just saying we missed the door
in the basement yeah okay uh the it's in
the dining
room oh
wait no oh I think I know what door that
is oh yeah yeah
yeah you girls are going down again
yes we can if we find
it sorry sorry sorry we in other wa
garage key who has the garage key yeah
the garage why what the heck where the B
wait who has the garage key nobody oh
that's what we're looking for
oh and the attic key wait I have it what
I'm just
kidding
you
I I'm
lost oh my God found Watson it's over
here wait wait wait okay where wait uh
can you hear me running around go to the
the front door the what the front door
of the
house okay uh I'm lost
okay okay you goody where are you uh she
was very close to me but I think it
ended just
now I think
in the basement though okay we're also
going to the
basement hello basement not alone you
turn the lights on or no the lights are
on oh
okay now they're off see you
girls all right so we're looking for uh
chat say there's a door we
[Music]
missed could we miss
how blind are
we well this place is
confusing place is
huge H hi hello
yay so nice to see
you yeah where is GA here hi
[Music]
hello it's a hidden passage somewhere
maybe got to kick down another door what
if it's in one of the closets like
Narnia
what I don't think
so
oo I think my character is like lowkey
crying very
traumatized have trouble sleeping at
night
mhm oh another Med kit if we can't find
a
uh um what
the imagine if it's actually bugged it
uh would it be potentially nah nah they
can't bug it so that we can't find the
door can they we can't find a key what
if the key spawns like uh on a Surface
we can't reach or underneath the
house
oh no I hear her hear
her a
shovel like it's just know mean
I'll be my guest after
you are you hiding CU I'm scared you're
still everybody's still in the basement
yes
yeah I I don't think there's anything in
the basement
honestly I ran around in circles a
million times
H I'm going back
up no as long as the lights are still on
does that mean that she's not
around does she always turn them off
middle stairs is the basement someone
has the basement key to open the middle
I have the I have the basement key
middle stair middle stair we'll go after
she leaves okay okay middle stairs it's
just
confusing it is this is
massive
stairs H you think you found the what
some secret the chat has gathered Clues
they determined that there are three
stairs in the basement and we've only
opened two of them because there's two
duplexes right so we've gone in and out
we just haven't gone to the third one
which I guess is probably the secret one
yes
okay when are you hiding from GAA
lady no she's breathing funny yeah me
too I'm like right around the corner and
I still feel it e that's weird I don't
feel
it can I get
out can we be haunted separately is that
possible I'm shaking crying and shaking
no man I want to keep hi
hi all right GAA is out of the
closet what about these stairs middle
stairs where I came from all right where
are the middle stairs I've run up to
them a couple
times Well find the one that has a
closed door did you just turn those off
maybe why would you do
that okay so stair
one this one St
one I'll try to stay with you ghost
that's better so this one's open so
we'll go go to the next
[Music]
stairs come
on you can't go through that yeah too
wide okay
whatever middle I lost you again oh I
found another
staircase okay I found the closed one I
found the closed one follow the sound of
the flashlight
uhing I hear
it where did you go are you in the
basement
still
hello uh I'm I'm on the first floor I
hear very loud clicking but you're on
the first floor yeah and I hear very
loud clicking notm open the key you
unlocked the
basement yeah it just leads into the
middle of the backyard wait this is a
sign I already checked the backyard
there's nothing over here there's a key
here here I even checked in the grass
and stuff I didn't see
anything uh what in the world is
this wait so if I go back down to the
basement I should be able to find
whatever you opened or what and we're
out of the basement now it's just a in
the backyard yeah it's just a shortcut
to the m
okay a shortcut to the
basement from the back here uh yeah
[Music]
okay well huh that's well not going so
well all in favor of starting a new oh
just kidding I found a
bone
bone should we just find should we just
do another
map okay maybe we can is it even
possible to like maybe go to the car and
end it early and just go away with 80%
okay yeah let's do that oh we
try I think that that should be a thing
right oh
just get a bed score medoc where's
outside where's
outside you locked us in right now I
think
H oh no all right I'm getting in the
van take me with you you might want to
hurry she's coming open the van
Watson
from from where is she coming no she
right there no what she's right there
uhoh oh she is actually SC her oh we can
get into the van can we no we can't get
into the van okay why are you why are
you talking me why would you do
that why can we only walk so
[Music]
slowly she's chasing me in circles right
now is she yeah cute
don't worry guys it's safe oh chasing
again
CH that is very loud that is
terrifying no no please so a good Sharky
[Music]
please oh she broke another window oh we
don't have to pay for that right
no maybe it's a maybe she's giving us a
hint okay maybe breaking the window is
supposed to open another path no I don't
think
so I think she's gone
though
maybe
probably she just closed the
door and said goodbye you you girls are
I'm not going to be able to finish this
anyway I still hear her yeah dle number
two oh she's outside
again the game says that we hid the keys
so well you're never going to find it
she disappeared for real this time in
front of my eyes so it's safe now you
guys come out I'm going to open the
doors
again and check again and close them
again maybe we threw it away by accident
we got to dig through the trash bags no
way I don't think you can do that
because the key just goes to like for me
it just went it's not in the inventory
you know it's like on a side menu I
don't think you can throw it
away was it a j
a yeah was joke okay I think we should
restart okay Chad what Chad
restart yeah what saying
yes restart restart restart okay we
checked thoroughly we did a million
times
okay all right wait was notes tell us
where it
is no they were so vague yeah it didn't
seem to give a Hint it was like a lore
but it was like I don't know weird
more what if we did
[Music]
what if we did like a harder level well
the hiding places the I mean the hiding
places can't be much harder than they
already are
right uh oh new I I will accept level
two level
two I think I can handle it oh there's
yeah there's only two options right now
level one level two or level
five what's that Spike and difficulty
I can refresh the contracts okay so this
one is level two but it says take seven
trash bags to the dumpster that's it
okay wait can you invite me again
somehow it didn't work for me me me too
me too please thank you where's 34
I I can refresh the contracts
oh I can't
the join isn't working anymore it
doesn't work for me
either I can't join the game I press it
and nothing
happens I'm just going to close the game
and then I'll make another Lobby then it
reopens the game don't accept just
ignore this game is
haunted apparently the missing key issue
is somewhat common says some I put a
curse on my
PC your PC is now haunted by the ghost
okay you
guys oh send another
invite nope it's not
[Music]
work maybe it's me maybe I need to
restart my my uh
game what if I host it are you guys I
don't know if I have all of you as
friends
though I think you have us as friends
I
don't it's been 3
years I think I have somebody's old
account like I got changed up or
something K has yeah um let me should I
create a I can try okay and totally make
sure that we do a level two and not a
level five
yeah she's going to lie to us we have
the stream open
Kaa N I only have what oh you don't have
me
is it possible maybe I can invite her
okay can
you is Steam down send
meite oh I got
it clean up 10 trash pths take 10 okay
it's actually less but I guess it's more
difficult oops my hand slipped no no no
good
[Music]
no you got do is pizza disposal you
don't even have to bring the trash bags
to the
trash
dispose uh 13 trash bags to the
dumpster want to do dumpstered it but
nothing happens one more time please
restart your game yeah I did but I
closed it again now can you send it
again I'll try again uh launch your game
first and then
okay wait
uh so whenever you get into main
menu
yes game is buggy but that's what makes
it kind of fun I like buggy games me too
no that's
fine buggy games need some love too also
it's early access still it just said
even in the beginning Please be aware
that this game is still in Early Access
and still undergoing development so many
games are Early Access feels free money
what you say
what okay please invite okay I sent
it I'm going to be Bruce too now ra
boost nothing happens when I press play
game oh wait now it's happen happening
oh oh nice I'm in yeah all we're already
then not okay 19 mold no the other one
was better what do you mean the other
one was
15 no yeah why would you choose a five
difficulty MTH girl it does it does it
that's what okay okay
okay eeny meenie no we won't
ah ah four disos of five moldy pizzas
that's easy oh
yeah okay there must be a cat but okay
right are are there different I hope
it's a different
ghost a duplex that's fallen into repair
that's the same what we did last time
wait always the same map wait no we need
a on of
charming one a
Charming
yeah
ready okay I'm going to change no change
your avatar so I know who I'm seeing in
the game cuz otherwise I don't know if
is it am or is it GAA stor okay how
about this one we have to we have to we
should all be
Bruce okay I'm Bruce you yeah Bruce
team triple Bruce the Triple B
big bald and Bruce
beautiful yeah big bald and Bruce oh I
have to ready
oopsy why is what what what the whatd
I'm a level two already cuz I'm good at
this game picking up all the Dr we
didn't even finish
it Master trash pick her up she gets the
CEO bonus yeah
paid myself a little
extra 18 trash bags that's
fine 18 trash 18 lot me my God the other
one was you said it was only five pieces
of pizza it was situation here not
situation but we're on a
tight we must be in New York at least
it's a different house and get out of
there as fast as you can let's speed run
B Watch Your Voice Sounds different over
there radio I got a toy ready pickle
pickle pickle enter a haunted house
achievement was the previous one not
haunted what monkey mode I found a
rabbit oh with like monkey mode I took
it loot Goblin okay garage key maybe
this map is smaller which could be
better for the keys as
well ble
ble
it's like it's
Easter the sliding glass door opens ooh
what is this sound this next level gamep
play we need the key who's making these
sounds me wait not me you were you
making like sounds what does that
mean no oh
key
o what
key already a key we're doing good the
garage key was in the bathroom key
confirmed I'm hearing noises and I don't
like
it the house is like I think I can tell
the difference this one's really haunted
compared to the other one this one's
like constantly
moving what the house yeah and there's
washa sound again and I hear the goh
[Applause]
is it attacking
yet I'm in the closet and my my heart is
like yeah yep yeah me too maybe it's
invisible ghost this
time I think she's faster I saw it in
good on stream she's not in She's Not
Invisible oh was the same lady the same
lady she's just faster
[Music]
now
this will be
difficult keep an eye out for
medkits yeah she might be gone I'm
coming
out I still
here he coming up he's coming well well
well
I have a feeling this is not we're not
going to finish this one
either think she's done guys no she's
not no don't trust her I still hear her
may we just like
avoid yeah she might just be like
haunting
24/7 wait I think I'm
dead I can you not notice that the
moment you die it's a jump scare oh no
it's just like the model of the cabinet
is gone or something and I'm like
in uhoh she's in the void I think I'm
possessed
guys okay don't come close to
us in the bathroom that we're all Bruce
so I don't know if you or I think my
game is bugged Big Fish choose a big
key oh hello
[Music]
buny help me what where are you what do
you want I'm trapped trapped second
floor first floor I don't
remember o a m i I opened that door wait
come back you did that okay you scared
me well how am I supposed to help you
okay do I look okay oh my God he you
look okay oh
closet you were like kind of BL
on I'm trapped take get out the
trash yeah you're like turning in front
of the
closet I think I got bugged in the
door you are making the vasha vasha
sound if you enter the closet again like
I can't turn around can you press e and
nothing happen I already I already
spammed
everything our CEO is stuck can you get
in the closet I got to go I got to get
into a closet maybe it's better if she
gets you then she can kill you and then
you you're going to maybe be reset in
movement
sacrifice oh
God lady bad this is bad is she taking
you to a better place I don't see her
H oh she sniffing me down at my
cleavage what about your cleavage I'm
looking down at
it I'm going to risk it I'm going to
throw this trash
away oh my God hi
where is the exit oh no oh no oh no oh
no oh no hello oh no bye-bye that's my
closet oh you
too a
shield shield oh wait that's what I can
do hey
lady okay I found her
she left
what hey
lady I can't even use my
flashlight do we
restart we just started
anyway maybe this will help you have
killed me don't trust her Kiara wait I'm
still stuck I'm still stuck
he maybe if GA heals you with the med
kit then maybe it resets you oh
wait but
you she's like constantly
haunting it's cuz she wants
me you are a desirable
woman going there girls are
you we should restart them we can we can
we can
K you got to come check out this new
Beyblade I got you're not going to
believe how big it
is what's a what's a beblade
saying go play beblade go go
go well playing Beyblade all alone
doesn't seem very
fun let it
rip oh oh my God okay my arm
hurts is it the trash is that why I was
stuck maybe are you unstuck
no Yahoo here's lies here lies
Bruce oh still alive you have a medkit I
saw it on you
you should I drop it no you have to left
click
her while you're on the med kit
oh yes give me your med kit come
here that worked for me before I
think a healing touch and you're groin
I'm still
stuck you're
stuck stop being stuck all right well uh
good luck guys I'll I'll I'll be a
lookout I'll let you know she comes by
this bathroom she's here she's here
she's here
sacrifice I'm going to die
again what the
see this just uh not going
anywhere we have one team down though
one teamate down hey we're up to 2% yo
can you just end it I'm I'm on the floor
again oh we want to
restart yes Now or Never
charm oh she's stuck now wait going is
she stuck she's stuck you're safe you're
safe can we exploit this bug for
our for our game personal game
oh I'm keeping her traps in the corner
is she really stck oh my God
I are you stuck
now I think she likes me very much M are
you stuck no oh man she ran from me keep
her occupied guys keep her occupied I
got another trash just don't worry lead
her to me and I'll take care of her okay
I'll get her
stuck could it be that these the trash
in this house is already all in the
trash bags we don't have to like
actually clean it cuz I've only found
trash bag so
far that could potentially be it cuz
I've also only found trash bags not
all we can
restart okay
just we should we should
restart
okay it's fine who make the room I can
make
Del oark shark one more try yes this
this will be the one no bugs maybe maybe
level two and not level three GA
maybe
maybe CU she was like always
[Music]
there but that's what makes I mean yeah
okay level I wonder what level five is
like I mean we're only going to do one
more
right oh level four
it's only 12 moldy pizzas so we can hear
it too okay and we can eat it at the
spot all right okay that's not that bad
sounds easy sounds easy there's a lot of
closets around so it's yeah it's
probably not that bad yeah wait did I
join your I might have to relaunch or
something cuz I I accepted your invite
but it didn't do anything okay
oh
loveby
I predict you won't clear this one
either Ah that's okay that that sounds
realistic sounds about
right different characters might be
because of oh like Bruce is so big they
get stuck you think
oh all right I'll be a small
character okay come
on I'm not able to enter I'm uh hold on
restarting the
game poor Bruce Bruce is just too big
too much of unit too too wide I'm
joining right now joining it's
working now we just need wah a Bruce
might get stuck that might be the thing
maybe
okay Cho M oh yeah okay
invited yay where's our final member
Bruce is bugged the be stands for
bugged okay it's not doing anything for
me to let me reopen the game oh my word
what we should report all these
bugs dear
developers write your game is fun but a
but write them a feather P feather quill
message but Bruce is bugged Bruce
bugged possibly where key
um
yeah versus the man the invite please oh
okay did the other one not work oh you
had to relaunch mhm
okay uh noted to the
developer have to restart the game after
every Lobby yeah seems
like Okay small people
gang but this dude was fine too right
pretty much yeah I think's okay okay
gaura
is dead almost dead
eventually
no wait why would I be dead I was saying
that like take that oh what just trying
to remember what you look like so that I
can react
appropriately memory
Dead one side just renovated the other
still abandon both haunted by by the
past yay level
four
[Music]
y right
listen this place again I guess so the
big one
no okay but at least we're
[Music]
little upstairs wait I don't think we
need this cuz we're just doing pizza oh
yeah right but at least the
flashlight
uhoh pizza pizza pizza I'll go upstairs
he's
[Music]
hunting got nothing better I want a kit
yay oh I see her she's here her she's
here you're right I think she might kill
me ooh spicy lady ah she killed me okay
okay I thought she killed me she she
came into the
closet no maybe we were just too late or
I'm not here I was in the closet I'm not
here I'm not here I'm not here I'm here
here I'm not here I'm not
here I'm not here I'm not here I'm not
here if I find your body I can heal
you I'm uh dragging myself around on the
floor by the
stairs okay I'm upstairs how do I get
out of
this I
have why do I have oh oh my God I'm I
don't remember what my name is I just
saw a a hanged uh a piece of shirt uh
shirt clothing and it looked like a
person to me so I screamed because of
wait there's a pizza in here there's a
pizza in here wait you leave me in this
form I'll just go around and look for
pizzas pizza pizza okay there's one in
this room where's this room but it's
locked oh okay there's one in this
room
yum okay I guess that's all in this room
I'll go up to the Attic we got no time
to
waste is locked
probably can you use that I don't want I
can only have one at the time I think
I'll heal you girl I'll heal you wait
where are you you don't want to be
healed okay you the door the doors
question why would you put a plant on a
bench in your bathtub is that normal oh
to drain
it on a piece of
furniture uh on a uh okay there's
nothing up here unless we get some keys
uh wait
parkk this one oh
okay
coming good how many pizzas have you
found so far one this is a
race yes there's one
up ke no keys ooh
pizza pizza
yeah nothing in that room it seems like
okay I'm already downstairs this room is
check already
33% let's go see we got it she's
downstairs right now currently I I'm
downstairs R I hear her where I know can
you open this door I'm in I just looked
in there scratch scratch I'm going to
scratch up
okay I'm going to I'm going to piss on
the floor if you don't let me in yeah
I've already I already in there okay do
anybody find a key K maybe KY can you
leave all the doors open for me not yet
not yet I'm going to find
it
maybe the house is
shaking she's downstairs right
now she on the first floor I think or is
she yeah she's by us we got the key oh
she's right across from
get oh she's so
fast she's like okay she runs now holy
cow a busy business lady oh oh
W she's so fast think she's on my
side where is she what where is she can
you see me no oh I see someone on the
floor me yeah probably you only like a
shadow of you is she gone I think she's
gone yeah she's gone the door's open
again not in this house wait you found
the basement key that's huge you can
open this door yes where's the basement
entrance again wa can you let me in
where where are you uh I where just
where you turned around oh hi Kiara's
letting me in you didn't bark though
open I'm Kiara no I'm wait who am I
you're Ki no I'm I'm
go I don't know who's who me it's me
switched models no yeah I'm the guy oh
wait the basement okay where's the
basement I can't find it it's over here
somewhere I just saw it is this
it oh no no this is not it that's not
no it's uh over
here I hear her here it is here it is I
found it okay
okay stuff bark
bark hey it's
open nice oh we can turn the electricity
on down here huh somebody I hear pizza
right here over here y oh she's in down
here though oh there's another over here
too
[Music]
y around there's one right here oh no
k's in it I'm not in it I'm not in a
closet I want to be in a
closet bye I
mean I LoveIt I'm okay no it's fine it's
fine it's fine it's fine she's not I
think they're gone hey guys just a Pizza
come here pizza right here Pizza she's
gone she's gone Pizza don't go you take
us the pizza pizza over
here I want to be Raphael no she here
run run run run run don't scream don't
scream don't scream there's no reason to
scream you I'm holding her back I'm
holding her back get
Heron okay now she's going after good
this is not good on my Thro this game oh
shoot I think she went
upstairs yeah seems Seems
safe I'm out of
the we have five pie that's progress
we've actually done
stuff 41% we can do this I think we can
we just have to get the
keys true but every time I enter when I
think it's safe it's oh she's passing
by she's checking out my
closet o I found a door that's closed
out oh never mind I opened it oh she
left she
left get lost
lady she's so excited to finally have
visitors why is she chasing us out then
she wants to say
hi she's uh running around in the
basement right now
I'm about
upstairs I think she just went upstairs
no no
way she went up the stairs but then she
disappeared this door is
locked oh yeah bye oh I found a pizza in
the basement Pizza a I'm looking for the
key wait what room did you find the key
in
no master bedroom um Master bed bom well
it was in one of the bedrooms is where I
found the basement key not the locked
bedrooms just one of the open ones
okay I'm so dead I'm so
dead W where' she go from where did you
go where did you go from where were you
when it
happened sh up lady it's not you oh she
showing me under her dress why come down
to the basement come down to the
basement good while crawling and then
heal yourself and there's another medkit
right here Pizza okay but she's in the
basement
now I I just saw her run by and she's
running away again she's like really
zooming I thr
hurts yeah me too oh here she is she is
in the basement checking on me hello G
you're our last hope you're the best
can heal but yeah she can heal I can
also still heal myself don't come over
here run wow ising H hello hello fellow
slug
hello we're we're uh we're like Army
crawling around instead of SEAL Team Six
we're slug Team
Six not again not again there's another
Med kit and go go okay okay
okay I am now growing my own legs she
whispered I miss you you want to heal as
well safer like
this can look through doors it's like a
I'm a different class just think of me
like
that I get out of the basement but she
always like Cuts me
off okay we are halfway there she's
she's
gone no she's coming back no she's gone
oh good when you get out can you open
this door over here there's a another uh
you have you have the basement key right
no I have basement key wait who's in
this closet
is
okay car if you come down to the
basement uh there's another closet uh
really comfy waiting down here for you I
just came from there why you didn't open
this there's a door over here you didn't
open oh she's she's down here right now
hold on
oh I almost got
you why you say that so
joyfully she got
you nice nice lady I
[Music]
I she's going to get many empty
rooms nothing down
here yeah nothing
[Music]
haaa wa for you e for me yeah seems
pretty dangerous yeah I'm looking for
the path again but I always it's so hard
to keep myself orientated
here I can't find what is where where is
what yeah especially this map is so
big so I guess the idea would be the
pick of the pizzas on or maybe not cuz
we still have to do the key 50%
50% yeah that's pretty
good all right lady i r out I I can't
I'm can't find think wait what it Where
Are You where's the room uh I'm still
down here where's the Roomba oh she's
smashing Windows hello hello is she down
here I don't know where you are oh uh no
she's not here right now
he's up above us I think
my
okay there's another I found I found the
basement again okay okay I'm in a
position where I can lead you get us
down here open two doors keep going keep
going
what ooh the guy is also too big to go
through these little oh here this way
let me
this way where you see me no a I see you
now hi okay we got to open this door
hello this is the through the backyard
oh
uhhm and this one now come back and then
there's another door over here we can
open there's also two closets here in
case she comes where where where where
where uh there's one closet right over
here to
the
door oh the other door where are you
guys guys I ran I thought I heard
something
scary I
follow I got start I think it's okay
though but I think she's on her way to
um there's a closet in the corner over
there too wait where open this
door where where uh where you were going
to oh okay
okay run okay oh my God oh my God oh my
God
okay at least Med kit right yeah leave
me alone lady leave me alone at least I
opened the door yeah
I I can
escape stealing the
van wait she's going to stand there
though she still with you oh yeah she's
still up there
yeah right where I opened the
door
[Music]
stop turn it off the
electricity all right so we got to
search through the bedrooms that's
probably where the next key will be
bedrooms wait where did you find the
garage key in the last
map um in the bathroom it was one of the
first doors I went into okay can you
heal
me where are you
oh hi you'll lose your heal though
that's okay then you'll die wait do you
hear her
no
okay welcome back thank
you guessing you already checked in here
o I found a
pizza no key no key you did you find any
Keys any more keys just the basement key
this a basement key did you
rest yeah I'm back alive and I got like
the the laggy stuttering thing again
yeah
same bedrooms so somebody said bedrooms
yeah I'm at the bedrooms but would be
good to find the master bedroom
key
oo man it sure it's easy to find these
bones they're throwing you a
[Music]
bone English J oh Nan did you die
again uh
maybe yeah I
did double I was in the closet already
safe and she still takes you
out like she ran past my closet like
several times maybe she only does it
when she sees you going
in uh yeah
maybe she just like came out of the wall
though out of nowhere have time has a
personal Vendetta against
you you're haunted I found a pizza guys
I found a pizza but she's right here wa
for her to
floor um I'm in Lex number
one I see her she's with
me what I see her over here though oh
nice Med kit Med kit
get I'm doomed to be a Roomba this this
Mission doomed to the Roomba
live what the hell
man can't find I found a pizza
though which means we haven't been in
this floor I'm in the I'm duplex number
one so on the left duplex go back to
theor still standing there floor what's
on the fridge I'm it I mean the pizza is
on the second floor but I'm right at the
staircase the entrance to the
staircase okay so I'm probably in a
different duplex than you just go
outside to where the van is if you can
find the exit okay I see her she's right
in front of me still so I think you guys
are safe oh There She Goes she's gone
front door un hello up here look Pizza
Pizza I See the Light Pizza Key oh
nice is there a master bedroom in here
let's do that first was that the master
bedroom guess not I just came from the
other duplex and there was master
bedrooms there maybe they're on both oh
yeah probably a bone there's a bone
bone pick it up I can't get
itone I can't
leave I thought you closed that door no
oh do you girls close the doors after
you went through o Med kit yeah need
extra Med kit no not yet I need
one here run run
[Music]
run
hello I have a
kid are you okay she still up here oh no
wait okay
[Music]
okay my arm hurts I was so shocked that
my arm hurts
uhoh oh I hate that lady I
hate don't worry we'll get
revenge
we'll get all those
pizzas
66% no not like this not like this
please not like this no not like this no
not like this you we're all down you
have to open the
doors wait you guys don't want to get
rest you want to you want want to get up
um Cara has a med kit she can K herself
I think she's just waiting for the lady
to leave yeah
yeah is she gone are these like master
bedroom doors no right it might be one
of these this one this one oh she's here
no run run run
run
cor where is she any oh she's she just
came from the attic well she's in the
other room you were in it's so dark oh
she's coming down the hallway here she
comes we went into the master
bedroom it's not fair she doesn't have
to open the door she just walks through
she just phases through
all right I think she's kind of out of
the area for right now coming
out tried to open this door yeah then we
can explore and you can go hide oh
nice run go oh slug team oh wait there's
still a door here we need to open this
there's a closet right
here
I oh you scared me this a
zombie
75 we can do
it hide hide hide uhoh uhoh no no no no
he going to get you no I don't that was
so
close that was she even fter now any
announcement of her arrival
okay surpris you survived that yeah okay
there's another check in here for
Pizza Pizza the pizza hear the is this
this
room there it is pizza pizza pizza I
hear I he I hear
her after every
time after every time you guys pick up
an item yeah she's going to come so you
got to hide as soon as you get
an I'll block her I'll block
[Music]
her fight fight I'll TR her attack we
can do this we may have not been able to
clear level one but we'll we'll clear
this level four of course we'll clear
Lev level one was just too easy I think
there's nothing left in the basement
right probably and first floor checked
most of it we're not quite done with the
master bedroom we got to check the
master bedroom and the other duplex and
the garage maybe yeah okay attic wait
there's there's still one more room here
that needs to be unlocked though yeah
there one over here
I think it just leads back out into the
hallway as you can thank
you is this in the other duplex or is
this in the same might be cuz I already
opened all the doors here it might
be okay yeah they're connected too then
so no other key huh wait uh maybe up
here if you oh wait never mind hide hide
hide yeah there's a closet up here too
but I'm guessing you guys already
searched up here this where in the uh
attic on the attic I think I checked but
maybe not
both oh she's coming mm she's shaking
she's gone she's gone she's disappeared
okay all right check this attic look at
there's a closet up here I think I was
up here before okay we need the key key
oh
okay this will be better hide there uh
she's probably going to come like right
now cuz we got the key possibly no pizza
there's no all right we got to use it in
the other house uh yeah can you pick up
a an medkit when you're already dead
probably not right wait there's also
another door here but oh run she's in
this room hide hide hide she's in this
room she's coming it's all other
side go go
go my really yes yes okay she left this
other locked
room
there's another closet over here so I'm
coming out is it
safe it seems like it but you know it
changes
quickly and now oh yeah oh b
b open open
yes yeah there's a
pizza o nice
91% we have one pizza one more it's
probably in the garage so look for a
garage key
maybe and the bone so is this the
other uh yeah that must be okay wait
here oh hide hide there's another
unlocked room in here
though wait maybe I hear her but I
didn't she didn't she didn't do anything
I don't see her I think she's probably
on the second floor or something first
okay okay okay okay okay we're almost
there open this one there's a closet in
here one pizza left
oh I'm coming oh GAA has the
key go GAA go gaura I'm scared she's not
in here she's not in
[Music]
here no pizza I don't think there might
be a key oh oh oh oh she's coming don't
worry she's not coming she walked past
me I was in the other room
still she's going down y y okay bye-bye
lady please don't kill us now we have
one left please ma'am pleas do we have
to like get out
afterwards uh I don't know we haven't
gotten that far yet no
key oh she's here run
run I'm going to die I'm going to
you go away go away go away
[Music]
what okay maybe we should all be room
look at her what's wrong with
her she's like bending over
backwards she's having
seizures
I I I have a med
kit is that room a dead end yeah but the
in
here she's just sitting here marking her
territory away
away also
still okay healing myself back up again
and hiding in the Clos your skirt oh
look up your skirt what do you see
actually I can't see anything all I can
see is my own forehead oh is that
big
yeah
spawn
camping oh is that
allowed you have a med kit right you
just you should just go somewhere else
and then maybe no I already used it
yeah I'm hiding okay okay I I can I can
maybe go look for uh for key okay oh she
disappeared she's probably just
teleporting behind you
no wait did you guys thoroughly check
this room for key yet
yeah do we need it check again we need a
garage key I think
oh that must be where the last pizza is
I'm going to go uh search the garage
like try to look through the doors in
the garage and each duplex okay you find
the
exit oh my
God I'll follow you we would have seen
it upstairs right as we walk through it
yeah we check this room right this one's
closed door is closed I don't
know it's the PC room right yeah yeah
I'm pretty sure check it beener done
that hello
hello I'm going back down hello hello
where are you where is she a
boon I think I hear the pizza in the
[Music]
garage okay no we will finish
it but can you smell the pizza wait
she's somewhere hide
hide I actually don't see her down
here
[Music]
yeah okay can we go down to the basement
again maybe I don't know maybe I feel
like we already searched all of
that oh God it's
loud I'll stay behind you and let you
know if I see
her I think she's upstairs right
now yeah wait I've been in
here did we check these floors with the
doors
closed uh I don't know is this the other
side of the
house I think that's the other side of
the house so we haven't been here
yet uh possibly you can break those I
think the wood
things did you just see the
[Music]
lady okay that means that down here is
safe for now Mimi she's so
angry well
maybe she was
murdered
[Music]
must angry I would be angry
too
yo I can't
find still haven't turned on the I'm so
dead I'm so dead I'm so dead I'm sorry
sorry sorry it instantly spawns
there
you
uhoh
now we each only have one life left well
you unless there's still some first a
kids but I haven't seen any yeah I
haven't seen any either I have one she
Clos me in that stinky old EG
wow
wow when she's gone I want to exit cuz
there were some medkits in like the
lower level one
outside in the
backyard maybe I can find one there yeah
I'll meet you in the backyard going to
the backyard right
now oh she's downstairs and D number two
and I can't open the door so I have to
wait I think WF okay I'm waiting right
outside your
closet oh you in front of my closet
yes
oh she's gone the doors have unlocked
you should be able to open it now let's
go I'm using my last life gone but for
how long oh there's another Med kit okay
Kar found an extra Med kit we are fine
for a little while longer and I found a
bone maybe could there be a key outside
I really wonder cuz it does spawn items
outside well I think the bone no way not
really no freaking way
she found her again she's already
spawned oh the electricity is
here better run and
hide I guess it's safe it's safe yeah I
check for the wait can you check for the
garage key over here on this long dining
room table oh wait I hear doie doie
again doie doie do med kit oh nice M
okay okay we're in we're in we are so in
where is the
key could could it be
outside I checked the part up outside
but not that's like the pretty much what
you checked cuz it would only spawn on
like a flat surface so I can look I'm
sniffing in the grass right now I don't
see I don't want it to be in the
basement that's scary it could be in the
basement I guess but I feel like we
would have seen
it please
no please no please no please there's
nowhere to hide
outside everybody knows that ghosts stop
haunting you once you leave the house
that's just the way it is they don't
yeah that's how it should be the
monsters they stay under the bed they
don't leave the bed oh hi am I see you
hi we should all go into the basement
when we do go and then we'll tackle it
all at once we can basement I don't know
where the basement is so don't follow me
I'm looking for for it though oh she's
right I feel it she's right
there gooda you're safe right now you
should be safe I'm outside the
garage open
it uh knock the the hello uh on
TR oh she's walking by again I'm scared
to take these bones cuz I don't want to
make her
man is it going to make B the bones
don't even do anything
bounds all right let's go where are
youit What are you in the basement cuz I
I don't know where it
is
uh no I am oh wait okay I'm in the
basement so I'll meet you guys there I'm
coming if I ever find it to the basement
the basement in the house you were in
Kara is was by the front door like by
the
entrance I see you
hello I found the garage it was just
right there on the table close to the
entrance she's coming she's
coming uh uh let's go Cur oh god let's
go okay I'll find the garage door hell
yeah oh I found the garage door oh okay
do you know where I am yeah I'll lead
you there you're going to lead me let's
wait a little bit uh we're in duplex
number
one she's with me so if you want to do
it oh okay uh there's a I think there's
a closet right by this door anyways
she's with me she's busy she's occupied
okay okay okay okay okie doie yeah here
it is but you should open it and then
hide because there's a closet right
outside right outside I'll go I'll go in
here right right here oh she's with me I
see Pizza 100% let's get out wait I'm
going to wait a actually it's no danger
I guess cuz I have the medkit but I hear
her pretty loudly oh that's right we
have a a
revive wait does everybody have to be
alive though to get out Watson there's
another Med kit in the
garage can I just pick it up while I'm
down no I guess not but I can heal you
in front of the car or so if we go there
wait for wa for me wait for me no please
woman not like I'm going to follow you
well not
coming
out okay guys occupied
where
a
exit teammates be like
I'm
I'm she are are you locked just stay in
the closet until it's ready yeah okay we
finished
it are you by the well let's see if good
I can make it out
help ver are you
whereabouts I'm in the house to the
right if you're standing and your back
against the van I'm in the house to the
ride okay pretty close to theit number
two number the door's unlocked the
door's oh now is the time uh
okay I'm
coming maybe only one of us has to get
in SL team oh no it
oh nice contct
completed y only one had to be there y
finally holy beat the game you know I
just got an achievement to like beat the
game without being chased once complete
the job without being ched once telling
me I wasn't chased really MVP I died
though maybe it's different maybe being
chased is a little early access please
understand three achievements
nice level four too do we have to click
leave the session yeah think a home
Lobby oh do I do I get a level up for
this
better
[Music]
huh I don't know what my level is now
I'm click single player I clicked single
player too I'm level seven
seven hey I think I'm better at this
than phasmophobia cuz I can't guess
anything any guest in fast guest ghost
in
fast yeah you don't have to like guess
yeah maybe if some bugs get uh ironed
out we can try this again iron yes iron
and there's room for one more too we
have one more slot for an extra
employee oh yeah is it four maximum
again why why is every game four maximum
uh why not five they have to consider
the YouTuber Generations that are always
made up of
people I agree I wonder why it's always
four maybe they think most people have
uh like a uh an average of three friends
so exactly three friends three or less
an average
never well I'm happy to finished one
yeah and the difficult one at thatle
Gamers couple Gamers couple late night
ghostbusting Gamers Ghostbusters the o
no o o o
oh thank you guys a lot for agreeing to
play this game no thank you for
inviting yeah thank you I don't think
there's many chances for me to accept a
2 a.m. uh play along session uh this was
an exception but very good one say thank
you who knows if we had ever found the
garage key without you so thank you true
yeah I guess so it wasn't such a like
obvious simple place right at the
entrance sometimes you got to go back to
your roots baby retrace the
steps all right are you are you going to
just end it or are you going to talk to
your your people I'm I'm just going to
end it I'm going of TI my throat hurts I
did a lot of
screaming AR rest I'm so sorry for your
ears if you were listening I'm so sorry
sorry the chies are blessed the blessed
and de was slightly but I don't know if
Discord picked it up but if yes then I'm
sorry about my screams too it did it's
great Waton have you ever screamed on
stream
like like scream she screams out of
anger when she plays like Mario games I
want like no I want to hear like a cute
[Music]
girlly I don't think I I think if I got
honestly scared i' just be like oh the
silent the
silent I'd be like a grunt
like what's it like a really
scary
Outlast out but she's already played
Outlast oh has she not gotten scared
with Outlast somebody said she did in
outer Wilds did you get scared in outer
wild yeah that game is actually scary
really yeah I love that game isn't it
like the spaceship one yeah it is but
it's not like it's like super
atmospheric so you get really into it
and the yeah it's just the atmosphere it
really pulled you in it's it's spooky
it's super
spooky another game that I will never
play because it's too spooky unless
someone forces me like you girls cuz I
will say yes to anything Halloween is
coming up I mean what Discord cut you
off Halloween's
coming paladins his the paladins
paladins what's of paladins that's not a
horror game paladins is a horror game
no no no no a free to play the true
horror all
along is it free to play yes fre to play
today not
sponsored spored I have the Amelia
Watson okay all right all right
you tell
you can you tell us a voice Slim do the
voice uh I don't remember what I don't
remember do the Paladin's
voice say
something spawn starting in three two
[Music]
one that's just how oh baby and triple
oh
baby Penta
kill but are you on the wait are you on
the switch version then as well like is
it across all oh actually I'm not sure
that's that's a good question
Amia you're also on the switch cuz you
have you're in the group coaster I'm not
in too right or was it Kelly uh mine I
have a character in there but no voice
lines I think oh and a hinotori song is
on there too oh yeah that's right hot
but when I tried playing it the graphics
are making me feel really dizzy it's
it's really fun in the arcade you guys
have to play Arcade version the buttons
are so like satisfying like
oh well unfortunately we don't have such
cool arcades here in Austria with like
games we'll find it next time we're in
Japan back to Japan we go for the arcan
arcades what we got to go back where the
arcades although I really like the
arcades in
America yeah they're those arcades
there's arcades oh there are arcades I
just remember wa
wa one yeah I just remember it I just
remember it they have group coaster
round one I guess round one is is it
Japanese yeah right but somehow I really
liked the one in America I don't know
why they have more like classic arcade
games like ski ball and throwing
basketball hoops and stuff they don't
really have that in the Japan arcades
that we went to
right yeah I guess there is a difference
there they have a dve Busters in Japan
we have round one we give them dve
Busters cultural exchange or Boomers
there's also I don't know if you guys
know Boomers but there's that's also an
arcade chain he who what yeah there
there's one there's an arcade chain
called Boomers but I guess it might be
like a regional thing I don't know oh
it's called Boomers yeah we should give
them
Chuck-E-Cheese oh yeah they can take
Chuck-E-Cheese you give us Tio we give
give you
chuckecheese thank God we don't have
Chucky Chuck-E-Cheese here either
chunkin cheese you guys have any
animatronics there in uh Austria what's
animatronics like a 5 Nights of
Freddy what is that Faz whoa FR
Faz what do you I don't
understand Five Nights of
Freddy's that's where you want to be I
just don't get it is it is it not a
movie or so I heard of this before but
have you never played Five Nights at
Freddy's oh no
no challenge time what do you mean with
animatronics if we have animatronics
yeah so it's like a it's like a robot
that's it's like a character but it
moves MH so it's kind of like a big
mascot but it's a robot inside and it's
like stuck in one place but it it's on a
track and like yeah
and that's in a in an arcade or what
yeah they got it Chuy
cheese
oh famous Austrian animatronic
characters o I don't know if we have
maybe the
Terminator he seems pretty animatronic I
don't know that's actually kind of fits
yeah ew but he's like an animatronic
with no skin and no fun he's just the
the the the
internals be
back I'm sorry I don't I don't know if
we have anything else like that I mean
we have theme parks but like okay a lame
lame theme park but there's probably
animatronic there I bet I mean is is a
is a roller coaster and
animatronic no I still don't get it it's
just a robot what I'm going to send you
a picture okay okay we're busting out
the we're busting out the all the
images I'm surprised we've never played
Five Nights at
Freddy's girl I don't play any horror
games unless I'm forced
to this is a really
small that is terrifying what the hell
do children like this I feel like it's
nightmare inducing um it's scary
yeah oh God look at his
eyes and then you can see the ones with
that I hate that
one why are the eyes so deep
inside they should be more like on the
outside
e ew
nightmares it's just chuckecheese is
this like lowbudget Mickey Mouse or what
uh it's well it's just like an arcade
that's it's an arcade that's known for
like kids parties so like if you had a
birthday party at Chuck-E-Cheese you
were like the cool kid cuz then
everybody would get pizza you could go
play at the arcade for us it was like if
you have a birthday party at McDonald's
then you're the cool kid oh yeah I never
got that animatronic no skin let's go
why is there no animatronic uh Ronald
McDonald is is at at at third Fest
Fourth Fest Etc is the small am and
animatronic we should make an small am
animatronic what the let's play a
game called guess the
animatronic no that is no no can
you guess what lovable character this is
you're going to spare your chat that is
not lovable any sh us here you
go there you go is that what you want to
chat okay wa
here's gace that's not even what AM
showed me showed me mice or whatever tuy
cheese is he a rat yes tri's
entertainment
cheese can you guess what this character
is
Chad what lovable character that looks
like Avatar that looks like Avatar bing
bing bing bing Y and I haven't even bled
it wait you use animatronics for that no
probably on like the rides or something
oh oh there's a
ride
yeah okay so which Avatar do you girls
prefer the last air bender animated oh
okay we have a split
here God this is the worst
one oh he sees you when you're sleeping
that looks like a home project it knows
when you're awake EG no it's apparently
there's a 16t tall sabot
Godzilla oh okay that makes sense but
that's a Godzilla
apparently the internals it looks like a
human just imagine it with
skin then is even more human oh my God I
don't want to see a human like
that I guess the teeth give it
away
yeah stuff I mean it's a horror game
stream we can continue the Fe nightmare
nightmare nightmare don't make it on
don't put it
on Hello hello my chummies did you miss
me oh the teeth mhm that could be good
get rid of it
gone all right cursed
vanished okay I'll die ga next time you
invite me to the game maybe a bit more
of a happy one would be appreciated
thank you happy one five nights at
Friday is
happyer Happy Wheels Happy Wheels how
about Sonic racing oh that'd be fun uh
sure okay is like can't you play with
like 16 people on that one I think so 16
full Sonic where are we going to get all
well almost we have 15 right oh yeah
kind of more like 14 cuz fuok plays with
only one person
oh that's true yeah turns mhm they have
to count as two cuz then we have 16 oh
no 14 uh
15 surely they have to play as two I
mean one as
each wait when we can fill the last spot
with aan
perfect Anan is H life English true
member official she's been doing so much
like mcing for us so
her English is so good now it's so cool
yeah she keeps all
improving all righty though y are we
ready to wind
down down tummy hurts for bed time
for well thank you guys for
playing thank
you absolutely absolutely thank you guys
for
watching you everybody have a nice day
bye we will see you any
nightmares nightmare nightmare
nightmare byebye
bye-bye Al indeed you
remember
bye-bye CH
Chum
[Music]