foreign
[Music]
assistant
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[\h__\h]
yeah
[Music]
hello
uh how's how's Wawa I mean where is Wawa
mama here
welcome to the stream thank you for not
going to sleep
uh but the ones who did go to sleep
that's okay
I do not blame you it's okay
sleep is important
not looping you got a loop
[Music]
um yeah but how is Wawa is actually a
good question right now
um
the inside of my mouth feels a bit weird
since
yesterday
[Music]
it does
I think it has something to do with
being sick
I don't know how to describe it though
I don't know how
why DVR on oh
oops well
TBR on huh I didn't realize because like
every time when I make a new stream but
I don't just copy paste the settings of
the previous stream
um it'll go to default settings which is
DVR on
yeah
wait did I
is a chat on
[\h__\h]
chat is on normal latency
[Music]
well I'll be busy telling stories today
anyway
uh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] normally I always switch it to the
correct settings but I forgot because I
was rushing
I was rushing
as quite long
but just sickness leaving your body I
hope so too it's weird it feels weird
hmm
it feels I don't I really don't know how
to describe it but besides that I have
barely barely been coughing
um
last night for the first time in a while
I did not wake myself up with some
coughs I went I got through the whole
night
without coughing so that's really good
[\h__\h] delay I'm so sorry yeah
[Music]
I don't know
yeah I did stick to my get healthy
schedule
um I slept
ah man so I was tweeting about it so you
maybe know but I slept over at Kelly's
place and slept on uh her couch and
um
even though the cats are tiny they took
up quite some space on the couch
um ghost cat was like sleeping
like at first they were like playing
endlessly and I thought oh
I don't think they're ever gonna cuddle
up to me but they did
um and ghost cat was like around my legs
and like taking up spice but it's okay I
like it
and then
she like started
hurrying it'd be like really needy and
and she um
she first I was like kind of like in a
sit-up position
um so for a while I was just leaning my
head against the sofa because she was on
my she was like lying in a nice position
laying in a nice position on my on my
lap
uh and I was just you know
petting her endlessly and eventually I
was like sorry to I gotta lay down
you're probably gonna leave when I
change position that's okay but I
changed position and she stayed and you
know I was like lying sideways with one
of my arm kind of like under my uh head
um
so there was kind of like a
like a 60 degrees or 90 90 degrees angle
where a cat could make itself
comfortable
yeah
and she did
ah she she went went to that spot and
she was like and then she like flopped
over in a really cute way and she did
that several times though because she I
think she was just really happy
and she flopped around
almost like a dog like she would like go
in a circle a turd and flop down
it's so cute uh and she was purring and
it was I was petting her endlessly and
like
slowly but surely I know that the
petting made her so happy that even
though she was like in the sleeping
position she was like Restless
she just wanted to experience the
cuddles just like I wanted to experience
the the massage
yeah
it was so sweet and then
um so we were ghost cat was by my legs
and tutu was by my my head
and we were falling asleep I was falling
asleep it took me a while but I was
falling asleep
and then goals cat gets a little jelly
and comes over
to lie down where tutu was lying because
tutu was getting all the action
so he lies down right next to her
and he also tries to like
groom
lick
tutu which was so cute but tutu didn't
quite like it
and then I think tutu was like
stretching and ghost cat took that as a
challenge
do you want to fight and then
they started like fighting even though
we were about to fall asleep
and then
eventually they ran down
it ran away and then they were making so
much noise
so I
even though it was going so well I
eventually like just closed the door on
them
because they were for some reason active
again
finally I could fall asleep but it took
me another while
and in the morning I opened the door
and then tutu came in the morning it
wasn't even the morning yet it was like
10 30 or so but I only slept like seven
hours okay
and then
she comes again and she's like and then
she's like needing everything that gets
no way like I'm chilling on the couch
yeah and she like walks over me walks
around me and while walking she's
literally with every step she's taking
she's kneading it's so cute
eating everything she was needing even
my skin she was trying to knead my my
arm and so on
please stop spamming
um
and then she was like lying down again
to cuddle him but like she was so
Restless again because she was just so
happily needing ah so she went under my
blanket and she was like her whiskers
were tickling me everywhere and you you
you you you she was trying to like suck
or eat I'm not sure which one my fingers
and my nose
every single second with her was cute
hmm
she's so small
yeah so I had a nice nice wakey wakey
with tutu
so cute
so cute and eventually
can we woke up and she looked into my
room and I'm like okay we
put you on the blanket
and then tutu looks out of the blanket
and she sees Kelly and in that moment
she stops purring
and her focus is immediately on can we
and then it's it was over
once you realize her real mommy was up
it was over for me
but then you know we slowly got up and
then uh uh we were like ordering some
breakfast
and then stream started so we were
watching that on the TV
um and eating breakfast while watching
and then tutu especially tutu would just
not leave me alone she was always like
climbed up on me like I'm a mountain
trying so hard to get something from the
breakfast
she would just not give up
it was ridiculous ridiculous
tutu needs to learn
some manners yeah
[Music]
yeah and yesterday I had a collapse room
on Cali did you guys see that on Kelly
on Kelly's Channel
and that was that was fun
because we did a hand cam stream and uh
before that we had a long spa day
which was really good really fancy
uh and then we had some extremely good
Yakiniku holy [\h__\h]
but that place was so extra so over the
top every like thing that came out
from the kitchen served at our table
everything was so extra
they did not not like other Yakiniku
places where they just served the pretty
looking raw meat
on on a on a planner no
they serve it like on animal statues and
in
like shiny RGB disco stairs
stuff like that
it's crazy I took some pictures and
videos
how much did it cost that might have
been the most expensive Yakiniku I've
been to maybe
but it was really really good yeah
really liked it
yeah it opened my eyes to something
because they had
um they had
like
avasa bee
um
thing you know we had like a course
thingy and one of the courses was like
basically they brought out a huge like
glass that's like shaped like it's for a
buffet
and it was completely green so it looked
like the whole it was bigger than my
head okay and the whole thing was filled
with Wasabi only wasabias all I could
see but then they pulled out pieces of
meat so these were like dunked in wasabi
and I thought [\h__\h]
I'm not good with wasabi
but Kelly said this one's fine because
when they grill it
the Wasabi flavor
like melts into the meat
and the spiciness goes away
and she was right
it was so good I mean first of all the
meat was so [\h__\h] juicy and soft
and the Wasabi gave it an interesting
flavor because normally I don't eat Vasa
because it's spicy but in this case I
could enjoy it actually so that's that
was incredible
I know
foreign
[Music]
yeah I wanna try that at home
I think it would be pretty interesting
to like try cooking that
using Vasa be like that I didn't know
that the spiciness goes away like that
how is that magic maybe they use the um
a more
non-spicy wasabi
I don't know is
still kind of a little bit sick
but mostly recovered but right now I
feel a little bit stuffy and the inside
of my mouth
and in my jaw feels weird
is this a thing that happens at the end
of a cold
tell me in 20 seconds
real genuine recipes
yeah I figured maybe there is some kind
of like
less spicy recipe
that you can use for that purpose
um it can
huh foreign
[Music]
so I can do that too
the left side of my
jaw
hurts I think
you sound better than the last days yeah
uh surprisingly I did stream every day
of the week so far
because
the members and me we did a Lord of the
Rings watch along didn't we
um
extended version
all free movies one per day
was really fun
it was really good it was it was
actually like
um I'm glad I watched it all back to
back
it was kind of a spontaneous thing but
I'm glad I did it so back to back
because uh
not just that the fact that it was
extended even if it wasn't the extended
version I feel like by watching it back
to back like this
certain things just felt
different they felt more connected and
more
um I know
I don't know it made more sense some
things made more sense
especially the connection between the
end of the second movie and the
beginning of the third movie
was like a big ah moment
hey
it feels more fluid yeah yeah
it really feels like I watched one long
long long long long long long long long
long
journey but it was very cohesive yeah
they said we should watch them all in
one day
[Music]
haven't watched along now I did before
um watch a hobbit marathon in the cinema
when the third one came out
and not I did not go out even during the
breaks I stayed seated in my seat
from the beginning to the very end
[Music]
yeah don't tempt us yeah don't tempt me
I think for now we're good we had enough
moving once alongs for now
um
[Music]
I still feel a little bit weird so
especially now that I have to use my
full power uh unlike the members streams
where I was watching a movie
um
as soon as I really feel
like exhausted
I will end the stream okay but my goal
is to
um
read some super chats then tangent and
then read some super chats and then
tangent like we did it before
I don't have a wheel prepared though
because there's too many things to put
on the wheel anyway I'm just gonna ask
you guys what story you wanna hear first
and then I'll tell you that story
foreign
[Music]
sounds like a good formula it is the
kiwawa tangent formula hmm
oh yeah I don't mind still watching it
again it's good I ever wants to watch it
um
got any stories about Kelly oh my God
wait I think like the most important one
to tell now is the Indonesia story
though
I think that's the most important I need
to get that out of my system the other
girls have already been telling it too
and I also want to tell
um deniji Sanji Ian story
so those are two one the two ones that I
really want to get out now because
others have already been telling their
side
um
okay
every time I drink
my
the bottom left back of my jaw
like
it's like appalling pain
yesterday I've been feeling that too
though
what is it what is it what could it be
not just back there kind of also in
other places
I'm feeling weird
glance
his privilege isn't a cold thing right
glance glands let me
[Music]
no it's not and it's not like in the
tooth it's not a cavity I don't think so
plants
pain cold let me Google that swollen
glands are usually caused by relatively
minor viral or particular infection
including a cold
what's glands in German lands German
huh
that's something that sounds really
scary but um that's not what it is
exclusive well at a glance
where are glands
oh wow
eh why is it showing me facial lymph
nodes
is lymph nodes and glands the same thing
yeah but it's definitely a cold thing
that's what it feels like
tonsils or plants
yeah like this
whole bottom half of my head is feeling
weird
oh yeah when I touch that part
where my lymph glands should be
apparently yeah yeah well I don't know
whatever I feel weird
it's like weird my cold changes the the
every freaking day I have something else
but we're definitely like pretty much
recovered
um
yesterday I was like using a sauna and a
steam room
um steaming that [\h__\h] out of my body I
told I told Cali that I um I didn't tell
you guys that because it was on Twitter
uh
uh that I
I
oh
I know I know that
um
uh like my sister used to do this yes I
have a sister
um but I know that you know one thing
you should do when your sinuses are like
stuffed and [\h__\h] is do the inhaling
thing inhale some steam
um
no no that was not really a cough it was
literally me just coughing up
some flag but it's not really a cough
this is just clearing it up you know
so anyway I wanted to do that because
I've never done it before but I thought
if anything now is the time to do it
because I want to get healthy quickly
and the amount of snot that has come out
of my
sorry that's really loud huh it has come
out of my nose
and sinuses over the past days
is
out of this world
it's out of this world
no that's not the
no no no there's coughs where you just
cough because you cough
and and mine was a productive
oh wait that was that actually has like
uh there's really a differentiation
there though
there really is a differentiation though
um
anyway shut up
it's got this
like a couple days ago I was coughing a
lot
but now it's different it's different
okay
it's the last couple of
um leftovers
of spicy it's not in my sentences anyway
so I wanted to do the steaming thing and
I wanted to do it but I don't like this
place doesn't have a single like
container like
like a like a bowl or anything like that
so I didn't know what to do it but I
looked around the apartment the only
thing that I could find that was
fitting
was the plastic trash can in the room
but it's clean
and I even like cleaned it again
anyway just in case I
put it in the shower
and then I cleaned it and then I filled
it up with boiled water
it's a small one though it's really
small actually it's just kind of
tall huh
if I see brown snot come out you closer
I've never ever seen brown it's not ever
coming out of my body ever in my whole
life what the [\h__\h]
that would be very concerning to me
hahaha
hmm
so I tried it I put a towel on top of my
head
um and like wrapped myself around the
trash can I was holding it but the
problem is like I had to like look down
my neck was hurting real bad but I
couldn't quite get in any other position
um
well doing that I was listening to kfp
podcast
nice podcast
hearing you guys oh
[Laughter]
what was I saying
oh yeah hearing you guys
like actually say out loud
what do you like about me and so on
has
definitely a bigger effect than just
reading it over and over again I mean I
still appreciate it being written of
course
but very rarely do I hear it out loud so
that that feels really special it has
like one person saying it out loud
has
a hundred times the effect
no has the effect of hundred comments
that I read
saying the same thing you know what I
mean
not
like you know it's I can't do that often
right I can't hear you guys say that
often
it's like really you know meet and
greets and stuff like that
um
so it's nice yeah
it makes it more real it really does
no as a YouTuber being in in the virtual
business where everything's virtual
we're never like really interact
so
yeah it's nice when it comes from an
actual real voice and all that
ow
I can't drink
maybe a straw would be helpful in that
case
I don't know
hmm oh well I'll survive
ah so I did that but obviously
I don't know I felt like there was
definitely some stuff going on when I
was under the towel
it felt like it was like happening but I
don't think it really helped with my
sinuses but I also didn't add anything
to the steaming hot water
like no salt or so
but then you know I used the steam room
yesterday
[\h__\h] that was hot
holy [\h__\h] try to stay in as long as
possible but
um
yes I'm up to date on my vaccinations I
don't have Corona
I don't have Corona
just have a shitty ass cold
I want to go to meet and greet too well
actually you know for the people who
can't come to all those conventions that
we do
um I do
think I will in the future again do a
meet and greet for like Zoom calls where
anyone anywhere can participate
um
what does that say
what was that
go to that comical steam usually what
steam usually
team usually is what
that was I scrolled back to
find the rest of the sentence and it was
just is
what steam usually is
what
I thought that would be like something
of interest there
helps me maybe it was that that one
Siemens really helps me after doing it a
few times yeah
um foreign
maybe I should have added something to
it but you know
I couldn't really find
um I wanted to add eucalyptus oil but I
couldn't find anything
like you know nearby so
um
I won one of the zoom meet and greets it
was great highly recommended hey
yay yeah
I'll do those again
you know my birthday is not even that
far away
so maybe for my birthday I can do it
again
that's a really weird way to sit I don't
know how to say in English I know in
Japanese they call it yukari
like a name
and in German we sayptos
so if English if Japanese is yukari
which obviously comes from the English
pronunciation and I thought it would be
like you eucalypt eucalyptus Maybe
mm-hmm
how
you guys got baited
[\h__\h] I want to talk forever
I'll try the tag as much as I can and
then tomorrow we'll play Fire Emblem
where I will also talk
as much as I can
uh
Hey listen to the right
it's all right
wow
ah okay let's let's bring out a tangent
as if all of this until now was not
attention of course everything is
attention
oh
[Music]
yes I'm still getting logo
um
I commissioned a logo for the show that
I want to do
still getting some ideas and I like this
one
I don't know if you're watching Spirit
snare but I'm liking this one
that's my favorite until now
which one though there's two choices and
they're both really good
I guess I'll go with the color
color one
yeah
nice
I will take it
the right one
hey
good
let's go
20 piece Cafe bucket here um sir this is
indeed a kfp
but
you can't order now
you're not quite at the wrong place but
so the argument does not work
but
but we're not here to order food okay
um
this is literally a kfp
it is
[\h__\h]
sorry this is
yeah hmm
okay let's start with the ID tangent
foreign
eucalyptus
thank you watching the Vlog later okay
I'm very chill today I'm glad to see you
back to streaming I was never gone
I was never really gone I was never
really on a break
let me pull up my notes the problem is
you know I've been trying to keep my
notes but
um
I will have you know that the past two
weeks or three weeks I have not been
really writing down things
cause
uh
I thought okay [\h__\h] this
I've been writing down so much stuff
I'm just gonna rely on my brain now and
you guys will have to remember what
happened
unless it's something where you were not
there and you don't know anything about
it well then let's just hope that I
remember
um
okay
so
uh let me see
my brain
does only partially remember the ID trip
it was so short I I kind of was planning
it for
a while already
uh it was not as spontaneous as it
looked like to you guys
uh I just wanted I thought you know
for some reason I thought ID would be
relatively close to Japan because
there's only a two hour time difference
so it would be easy to go from Japan to
ID turns out well it wasn't
it was still a seven to eight hour
flight
um
which
you know to get to Japan if there were
direct flights it would take me 11 hours
so
if you compare that
it's not that close
yeah
but I still I met everybody except so I
would say that's a pretty good quota
foreign
so if it was going to be uh free night
stay
I think it was free nights
and there was a lot of
[Music]
Panic going on right before that
it seems like Indonesia is one of the
few countries
where
you still have to like set up and
register
beforehand all your vaccinations
with proper certificates Etc through and
application
at least that's what you're being told
that you have to do
and it sounded very serious because they
told me at the airport that I cannot
check in otherwise
and that's what they do there
um the internet also
all said the same thing in the internet
when I was panicly looking up everything
um
so you know
problem like you know the lady at the
check-in counter at the airport in Japan
because I was flying from Japan to
Indonesia
uh she was like okay Mrs kiwawa so what
about your vaccination I say well yeah
I'm actually gonna have this PDF on my
phone sorry I don't have it printed out
so show it to her and basically
it's an international certificate it has
English on it but
I I do have to agree it's a little bit
like written in a stupid way that makes
it look like it's only one vaccination
even though it's like
I mean at this point we can all talk
about this stuff right in the beginning
it was still like um should we talk
about this or not and then Japanese
members started talking about it and it
was like okay I guess it's fine so I my
first vaccination I got was Johnson
Johnson which kind of counts as two
vaccinations right it was the only one
that was available to me at the time and
then
I don't know the difference between Miss
and Mrs [\h__\h] it
and then uh I think I got another
Johnson no no but no I didn't after that
I got Pfizer and then they got Pfizer
again so it's free but it's kind of four
I would have already in theory I guess
been fully vaccinated after the first
Pfizer because then that would make free
but just in case that people would like
get confused about it I just in case
because I was like I guess whatever
um got a second Pfizer too
so uh Then I then I was you know good to
go because also in the beginning I think
when I got to Johnson Johnson I think
you know
um we were always like on standby trying
to be ready whenever to go to Japan in
case they open up and at that time they
it I think it was like Japan did not
recognize the Johnson Johnson
vaccination yet
but that was the only one they would
give me
so
um when I got my first Pfizer
I was worried that they only recognized
the Pfizer in that case so I have to get
more prizes even though I'm already
fully vaccinated at that point
I wasn't sure because they weren't being
very clear about it by now Japan accepts
Johnson Johnson too but back then they
didn't so I was just trying to get all
my bases covered you know
um
anyway
so I got all those vaccinations okay and
my certificate says
free slash one
I think
uh on the column that says
something like
uh
series
of vaccinations numbers or the other way
around and the lady was like
the lady was like wow you only have one
vaccination though that's not enough and
I said no no no
I have free and she's like okay where
are the other certificates and I say
well this is the latest certificate
which should like be valid for all of
them
but it also only says the date of the
latest one but it is it should work for
all of I don't know man it was stupid
and I kind of agree kind of agree it's
stupid
um foreign
eventually she was like okay well
whatever you have to download this
application this Indonesian application
that I can delete by now
uh and then sign up and upload on your
all your certifications and I started
panicking because
I did not have any PDFs of my order so
this older certificates but they would
not let me upload the same certificate
for all three of them
and blue blah blue it was this whole
shitty process and I was panicking my
flight was getting closer and closer and
I was being really worried if I would
have any issues when I arrived
and I was trying to read up on similar
cases but I didn't really find much at
all
but it's the one thing I could find is
that everybody like made it really
important looking that you really really
need it
yeah
so I arrived actually like right before
my flight you know thankfully you know I
couldn't tell I I wish I could have just
tweeted it out and asked people for
their experiences but I couldn't because
I needed to keep my
um arrival a secret
for safety it's not only me doing like
saying now but also
um management
uh wants me to be safe of course
um
yeah and
I was panicking though and I didn't know
who to talk to
me and there's some some whole live
English stuff were sharing their
experiences with me and and and calming
me down a little bit they said you will
be fine you will be that jobu
um so I
I eventually calmed down tried my best
to sleep on the plane and I arrived I
got my visa on arrival
and I was like the whole time I was like
okay I'm going through this session I'm
going through this section there's many
sections in this airport until I get to
my lounge but where
where
are they checking my
Kobe stuff though hmm I did however
right before for the flight I ended up
you know uploading my latest certificate
for the food vaccination and for the
other two I uploaded
a cut out from my scanned vaccination
path which is not an official
like document to use for such a
occasion but I was like what else am I
supposed to do it did say the date and
it had like a stamp and all that and
what it was it said on that too
so I just use that and I I crossed my
fingers and hoped it would work and
right before my flight it said uh that
it needs to be checked it needs to be
processed and when I arrived the first
thing I did as I logged into the airport
Wi-Fi and it said it did say that it was
approved
so I was relieved
I'm like okay I'm good but then nowhere
and this kind of makes me angry because
it put me for so much panic and stress
nowhere on this [\h__\h] airport did they
ask me
or check anything
about the covet stuff
nowhere
I swear to God
weren't you gonna like check up on that
ah nowhere
also waited ages for my visa on arrival
man
ow
used to enter public places
yeah
well
why not say so
panicked
um
foreign
but then yeah I went
um to check into my hotel and then I
went to Elena's place
and I met her cats for the first time
and I was at her place for the first
time she has a cool place
[Music]
um
and yeah I didn't see all of her place I
only saw like like her room in some
other rooms and I saw I saw the cats yes
cats have a cat room very nice cute cats
big cats
damn
and very calm very calm
the calmest
cats ever
out
sorry my jaw hurts
um
yeah and they know it's so sweet and I
borrowed a t-shirt from her I gave this
one back to her I gave it back but I
borrowed a t-shirt from her and uh oh
she gave me food like she ordered food
for us and it was really good I got to
try like all kinds of different things
I don't remember the names of all these
things anymore but I kind of mentioned
some of them before
uh on Lane's stream because we did uh an
archived kind of okay so in case you
missed it guys
there's a off collab archived on Dana's
channel so check it out it was a lot of
fun
and I played with lato lato which is
still like a like two wooden balls that
clack clack clack clack clack
um
she enjoyed you wearing it
um so yeah it's really sweet
[Music]
um and then
oh yeah that was like the on the day I
arrived so you know there wasn't much
time because I arrived pretty late we
went straight to her place and stream
and all that
and then I went back to my hotel and
then I went to sleep
holy [\h__\h]
even though that bed was like a million
times more high quality than the bed I
have here where I'm staying in Japan
I could just not sleep in that one I
don't know I woke up a million times
I don't know what it is
I just couldn't sleep well it was really
comfy but I just couldn't sleep
it was really bad I woke up so many
times always
um so that kind of sucked but it's okay
and in the morning
I I got like breakfast at the breakfast
buffet that's one of the biggest
breakfast buffets I've ever seen
um
but like
I barely
I barely ate the things from the
breakfast buffet because
the culture in some countries is very
different in terms of breakfast where
they eat much more like Savory stuff
so many things I saw on the breakfast
buffet to me looked like lunch or dinner
food
you know and I was like
[Music]
I want to eat more breakfasty stuff
it's so different even more Savory than
Japanese breakfast buffets you know
um
yeah so they did have like waffles and
pancakes and so so I got some of those
and then I asked them for a [\h__\h] ton of
Nutella
and I took some fruit from the
fruit section which wasn't that big
surprisingly I thought they would have a
[\h__\h] ton of fruit because kind kind of a
tropical country right
not that much
yeah just put it on my pancakes and try
to make a DIY
a nice kiwawa style breakfast
excuse me
although
interestingly enough
recently in Japan
I've been eating
of savory breakfast more often hmm
so I do understand
wanting to eat Savory food for breakfast
but most of the time I'm more on the
sweet side usually in Austria at least I
wish
they had Nazi going and stuff like that
yeah
typical classical stuff to have on
Indonesian breakfast I guess but you
don't only eat it for breakfast right
you eat it any time of the day right
um
company
eggs and bacon are good
the problem with eggs is that in most
hotels even in more expensive ones
the scrambled eggs that they have on the
buffet is [\h__\h]
I don't know how people keep
accepting this and don't dry it and
demand proper eggs because you know all
of that [\h__\h] comes from some liquid
that is not eggs I can tell you because
I've worked in a hotel kitchen also
before
I can tell you how they make those and
it's disgusting I mean no okay the
process is not disgusting it's just the
texture the flavor none of that is egg
disgusting
it's really bad and I don't know how
people keep on eating that I guess it
doesn't even look like eggs but if you
don't go to many hotels we don't eat
many Hotel breakfast then
um
you may be not that aware of it that
it's like literally everywhere every
[\h__\h] hotel is that are you for real
the same hotels you can like order from
the kitchen fresh omelettes and stuff
like that you can also order fresh
scrambled eggs if you want to usually
yeah so if anything that would be the
thing to do in my opinion
it's so disappointing and also like
bacon from the buffet usually is like
so chewy
yeah
but the potatoes are like black
everything's like blood
breakfast buffets are so disappointing
always
just speaking in general now
um
I don't I don't even remember no I did
see no that hotel
so this hotel scrambled eggs were a bit
different they were a bit more
almost like real scrambled eggs
so I ate some of it
has a sausage and stuff so a little bit
Savory I didn't eat some Savory stuff a
little bit
um
so and then I started my day
I don't know anymore what I did in what
order
but uh
what one I think this
I think this was on that day
let me see my notes
I think didn't I
didn't I arrive on on a Friday right and
then I had Saturday Sunday and then
Monday Monday I left right
what what did I say almost
so on Saturday
I hung out mostly with um
[Music]
that's when the collab was so I hung out
only a little bit
not everyone was there the whole time
because Ollie had to leave at some point
and then she came back and this and that
um
yeah it was on and off but ah
uh
yeah I did go to
you know I asked the girls like you know
what should I see
what should I look at in this city what
is there to see
there must be some sites
and
I don't I don't know if I know it's true
and I kind of doubt it's true
but they did tell me
that
there is not anything to see
that can't possibly be right that can't
be true right
they said all there is is shopping malls
uh
uh is that true
so
because there were apparently no proper
sites to see we did go to some Aquarium
but yeah so I've been to like you know
big aquariums before so that was that
was cool that was that
sounds about right that's what usually
what happens
for real though like what
why
is there no like like historic
historical things you know like
I don't know
it must be like some historical things
right
and then I guess
we did not enter the ocean but we walked
a little bit by the beach
that was like pretty much it but I did
have a lot of fun I'm just like a little
bit like perplexed
that there's not really much to see
the freaking traffic though oh my God
uh
uh probably a note or besides but I
don't know them
capital is mostly filled with malls if
you want to visit somewhere in Indonesia
prepared to go for the provinces in more
rural areas
I guess interesting
I did see like some advertisements
for some cool stuff like on the
countryside but I obviously I didn't
have time to do stuff like that
um
I did see like some of the really really
big
Grand looking
modern looking uh
uh like shopping malls from outside I
saw
yeah and those really stand out
huge
there's historical stuff in Jakarta but
not really in terms of natural sites
that's weird because I feel like in
every like country except the Maldives
no even Maldives that sort of stuff the
main island
the main island
had some stuff but pretty much every
country I've been to and every like
every like capital of the country had a
[\h__\h] ton of sights
um
I guess it's all that's that's so
interesting I've never noticed that
before like what am I trying to say
I've never seen that before where
the capital doesn't have all the
interesting [\h__\h] it's all outside of the
capital
you gotta go a long way to find
something
um
but what they do have is good food a lot
of good food while I was there
and which was a really short time and
during the collaboration
um Muna cooked that those noodles for me
I think they're called holomia
apparently
with some egg and stuff that kind of
reminded me of how they eat
um instant noodles in Korea in South
Korea because you know when I went to
South Korea Nabi Mama
um showed me the whole instant noodles
culture they have there which they don't
do it like that in Japan so it was
really fascinating basically you go to a
convenience store you pick up the type
of noodles that you want so until this
point
it's just like buying instant noodles
but you also then go a indomie
you didn't get a lot to buy like an egg
or cheese or everything and then you go
to the counter
um I also get like a like a container
like a bowl uh like a paper bowl and
then you go to the counter and and then
you pay for it and you can get some
extra stuff there
um there's like specifically stuff four
the purpose of having those instant
noodles outside in the park you know
then you then outside of the convenience
stores
they would have a station with a lot of
like hot boiling stations and they have
like timers and all that it's not just
like a boiling water dispenser no they
have like timers and it's like a cooking
station they put your stuff there
and then you put the other stuff inside
and this and that
and then you eat your instant Ramen by
the by the park or the river or so on so
that reminded me uh
the Indonesian instant noodles reminded
me of the Korean ones as in how you
prepare them how you add so many things
to them
especially egg
yeah extra toppings
yeah but
Muna
even though at that point we were only
free left she put four packages of
noodles in and all kinds of extra stuff
too right so it was a huge like mukbang
portion and I think it's partially also
because whenever I eat when I'm
streaming
because I'm like I guess tense
I can't eat that much I feel too not
really nervous but just tense can't eat
much
so I tried though because it was really
yummy it was a little bit spicy but it
was really yummy
yeah so we could definitely not finish
those noodles
but then yesterday or so I watched
muna's stream and she said
she's eating indomie
alone but
she said she made four packages
but then she finished it
how come we didn't get anywhere near
finishing it with Free People
and then Muna eats it alone
makes herself four people serving huh
I don't understand
well we tried we tried so that I ate
that and then they had like you know
some durian stuff
and
I found it so funny how late it
completely misunderstood
how much durian I actually consumed
so I was like Hey I'm going to Indonesia
you have this like durian thing going on
you guys like durian so I guess even
though I've heard really bad things
about it how stinky and it is and I
doubt that I will like it for the sake
of entertainment just this once I will
challenge myself
so they prepared durian for me they they
said that the pancakes are probably more
bearable for me so they got in Frozen
packages they got durian pancakes
and durian
and we started with the pancakes we did
all of this on muna's stream so you can
watch it if you have missed it it was
really fun it was cool that was a crazy
stream
uh it's a crazy strip
that was
the most intense Mario Party I've ever
played and it's cool damn it was so
funny it was just too funny
but yeah when it came to the eating
section I tried the pancake and both of
these things were still kind of like
not so much anymore but they were kind
of Frozen
but when I
when I tried the pancake oh God it
immediately gave me a gag reflex
I'm so sorry
I only took the tiniest bite and I
immediately got a guy reflex
so I spit it out but I felt bad I wanted
to try it again I felt like in the
aftertaste I felt like you know this
can't be so bad I should be able to
manage this so I tried again
but I just got another gag reflex
I wouldn't say it's that bad but somehow
like this wasn't that stinky
I mean it was but not that stinky I
expected more
so I wanted to try again but then I took
another small bite
I was just what
the texture too I think
pancake durian is a No-No for me I
wonder why because they told me that
if anything I should be able to handle
the pancakes but no I didn't
um
so then we try it the actual durian
which was in a plastic container Frozen
so
like
pulled off a tiny really tiny small as
small as the tip of my pinky
piece
and fed me but
it was still like pretty Frozen
so it did not smell
it barely had a taste
and the texture wasn't mushy or so it
was uh you know it was just fine like an
orange texture
so I was okay
I was okay
but I didn't really desire more
was enjoying it though I think Koba was
enjoying no maybe Cooper wasn't Coco got
me like some other stuff like street
food style stuff I forgot what it was It
was kind of spicy but it was kind of
good it was actually pretty good and I
said I wanted to try the sweet version
of this
if that was really cute I'm so it was so
sweet that they like prepared so much so
much extra food for me man
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the spicy one
kept making me cough but I kept eating
more because also I wanted I didn't want
it to go the waste
it was actually decent food yeah
chilor yeah chilor
and so anyway then Reedy hears about
this yeah Dana who apparently has always
been staying away from Dorian because
she doesn't like it
understandably
um
and she takes it as a challenge
by her own words
she said
as uh as you know since it's like kind
of I guess kind of her country's
fruit I guess
she cannot let stand like that
she she if I am you know a tourist
but if a tourist like me
can eat a durian with no problem
then she must step up her game that was
kind of like her stance
it triggered her yeah she got so
competitive
and
so she did a handcap stream
after it is
where you can see it in her archive she
did the head cap stream where she takes
apart this mushy
but Dorian and really does not enjoy it
but she did quite well I would say
anyway
when she was screaming it was really
Dramatical
dramatic yeah she took it personal
[Laughter]
and then afterwards I write to her like
I'm so sorry you didn't have to eat that
much I literally only ate like the
tiniest amount that's as Tiny as the tip
of my pinky and she's
like what
I ate way more
clip Watchers
just kidding
[Music]
you suffered just because
of a misunderstanding
really unnecessary
yeah
okay
so that was Dad
[Music]
um
and then
yeah so we streamed on Saturday right
yeah yeah
or did we stream on Sunday
I don't even know anymore but all I know
is that on Sunday at uh
like evening time
I I kind of asked this last minute so it
was kind of like not everyone was there
at the same time like for example Anya
came really late and I didn't see much
of Anya
but uh we had like a karaoke
party
we went to karaoke place
they have like
not like a bar they do have like rooms
kind of like Japan and they have
Japanese songs and so on too
yeah
and basically everyone was there
everyone
every one of them
only Annie was kind of like late
elusive Anya Tony
yeah but yeah I got to meet like so many
of them and was so much fun like I met
Kaela I I met eovi
yeah everybody
it was so much fun Carla I was
I was the most shocked by Kyla I think
because my image of her
was so different
like I don't know because she has like a
really low voice right and it feels like
to me like she speaks kind of slow at
least in English
and it's very chill right
she she has gives me this really chill
image
um
yeah oh but then well first of all
I didn't recognize her at all
hahaha
I was I was so confused
I thought
the reason I thought she must have been
she must be like one of the girls
managers
not that they even tried to pull that
kind of prank on me they didn't even try
but it took me a while to understand who
she was
because she was so cute
so freaking cute oh
yeah and I got along so well like I
immediately clicked with her and you
like sat next to each other for quite a
lot of the day of the night
um
um now we talked so much also with Elfie
like eufi I also sat a lot next to eofy
and she she was so sweet I think I even
I do this thing a lot apparently
um I don't know why I do it but I tend
to
lock my arms with
other girls's arms a lot recently
um
was so cute everybody was so freaking
cute though holy [\h__\h] why are they all
so cute huh
why are they all so cute
if it was so cute [\h__\h] hell
I'm cute Oh no I got along so well with
them like even the memories who I
thought maybe I wouldn't like Vibe so
well with them I vibed so well with
everybody I feel like they were so fun
and so friendly everybody was so excited
everybody was so loud
they had so much fun together hmm
uh actually you know when I uh first met
um only
um you know I went to I went to Munoz
place right and uh they they come down
to pick me up because
I wasn't being let in
and the thing is you know since it was
just a short trip I thought okay I'll
probably be fine to just
um
uh
uh like organize no like internet thingy
for me because I'll always I think I'll
always be with someone
uh and I think I'll be fine it's just a
short trip
so I didn't organize anything
um
but on this occasion
I had a problem
Muna gave me her address
so I jumped into a taxi
I I downloaded this app
like uber
where you can put in the address and it
brings you there
and I uh realized
right before getting into the taxi that
once I am in the taxi
I don't have internet anymore
how am I gonna tell Muna that I arrived
but I also don't have her phone number
and also not
the exact room number like apartment
number or so
so
right before I jump into the cab I
panicly type on my phone stumbling over
my fingers
I don't know how we're gonna do this
once I arrive I'm gonna probably I'm
gonna arrive in so in so many minutes
but like I don't know I I don't have
your number maybe write me a number but
that would have only worked if she would
have answered me immediately which she
didn't
um so I can call you or or or
uh or um come down and wait for me I
guess in so in so many minutes
okay which
she didn't so I arrived and I'm like
uh what do I do I
I'm just I didn't even you know calling
someone
overseas with like you know my Austrian
phone contract
is more expensive definitely than doing
it inside of Europe but it's probably
still cheaper than turning on my
internet without a proper contract
thingy
um
so I was really hesitant to do it
but I don't know how else to like let
her know
and they wouldn't let me in and so
um
I ended up being forced to turn it on so
I turned on my
my overseas roaming thing on my phone
which I don't even want to know how much
it costs but I used it for as short as
possible and I was like well I'm here
please
so finally
Muna came down with only
and Muna was just walking you know but
then Ollie the moment she sees me she
screams and runs
towards me and I'm like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
because she ran towards me with such
huge energy and like
say Force vigor
and then she jumps at me
and hugs me like really strong I'm like
losing my breath
so excited I was excited too but oh my
God I was like wow
yeah that's Ollie
[Music]
I felt
so welcome
[Music]
um
that sounds like Ollie all right yeah
for real it was so sweet
huh
I felt so desired
not in a weird way okay I'm just like
happy that people are happy to see me
all of them all of them were so sweet to
me
yeah but all it was
I thought maybe if I met her IRL maybe
she's gonna be more calm than on stream
no she was she was very hyped
yeah
he was very hyped very excited very
friendly
she was wearing
a sweater
that shocked me
because she was wearing a sweater
even though it was like really humid and
warm outside
and Muna wasn't wearing like
like you know Breezy close either
I was like how the [\h__\h] are you wearing
so much fabric girls
and they're like oh that's totally fine
I was wearing the breeziest clothes I
could find
in Japan than I bought last minute
because I realized oh yeah right wait
Indonesia
is hot right now
30 plus degrees Celsius oh I didn't
bring any summer clothes and all they
were selling was winter clothes in Japan
hmm
so I found one like blouse that I really
like it's so cute
that saved me
it was also a little bit a little bit on
the warmer side but it worked but
they talk about it being cool which is
amusing to me I could never I was kind
of heat stroke if I wore the same
clothes as they did
[Laughter]
that was pretty it was pretty humid but
it was nice to get out of the cold
weather for a few days
hmm
so oh yeah
see I wrote down some notes so first of
all
um
Kobo
for the first time she was super shy
she was like always looking down she
couldn't look me in the eye
and she was so small holy [\h__\h] so small
and like fragile
[Music]
from the first moment I saw her even
though she was being so shy I couldn't
stop like like squeaking over her
because like she was so small and so
cute and I was like
[Applause]
and she was like no no no and she was so
embarrassed and flattered and shy
Shinji on a nice show
s
mom energy I wouldn't say I had mom
energy
yeah yeah
I'm at Kubo
oh see oh the collab must have been on
Sunday yeah because I met Cobo the day
before too
um
yeah but to say she was really like shy
the first time we met and she would like
eventually like really she warmed up
pretty quickly
um she was very nervous in the beginning
but she warmed up pretty fast to me and
then
uh she had she just paid so much
attention to me it was so sweet
and she would like force me to eat food
she was like eat this it is
like a demanding angry face
mommy you have to eat this I have to eat
this don't eat it eat it
it's so funny her facial expressions are
so
vibrant
she has crazy facial expressions
they're so over the top
like I don't know she's like constantly
in streaming mode which means that she's
just herself on the streams and that's
just how she is but
um it's so funny
she pouts a lot like jokingly and gives
you like angry face jokingly a lot and
but then she gets she finally breaks
and he just laughs cutely ah she's so
cute [\h__\h] up
is she crap she cracked me up so much
man
hmm
and Oli Ollie was so funny though like
she would like randomly but
spontaneously like dance and twerk
because we were like vibing a lot like
out of nowhere we would just
when we would say like oh my God
suddenly all all of us at the spot would
go like oh my oh my God
[Music]
come through stuff like that
immediately break out in singing and the
whole time we had this whole new jeans
thing going on
and a day
they all like new jeans so they all
actually know some of the dances was
impressed I was like what the [\h__\h] you
guys no new jeans and then what the [\h__\h]
you guys go to dance a little bit
oh I was so hype
it was so hype because I'm also like
deep in the new jeans rabbit hole which
is ironic because their fans are like
bunnies apparently
um
yeah I found my people
ah good night though
and uh oh oh all he has
incredibly warm hands for a dead person
I wrote that down
I don't remember it anymore but
apparently they were really warm hmm
yeah she was she was like touching my
hands she was like okay well why you
have so cold hands when we were in in
muna's place
I think and she would like touched him
and I was like yo you have such Romance
he would warm my hands hmm
also
I don't know why
a lot of this I lost the context but uh
all they like kissed my hand
you know like like a lady's hand
she kissed my like the back of my hand
and then I don't know
I touched her hand back
and we
I don't even know how to describe this I
can only do this in the hand camps
during my thing for you guys to
understand but we did a weird thing with
our hands
interlocking weirdly and everybody else
in the room was like
but it was like screaming and panicking
and
I was like
don't misunderstand it was just this has
no meaning okay what the [\h__\h] we're just
we're just fooling around okay accident
accident
just an accident
oopsie
yeah everyone was like yeah bye-bye
one thing I need to say about Muna
you know she
she's like you know calm right she's
calm
and reserved
so most of the time she's like
just like
chill
and her facial facial expression also
but then sometimes
she would smile and I told her
your smile is so cute so pretty you need
to smile more
and I think
I think I think she was um flat
flattered embarrassed when I said that
but I think she was happy I think she
was happy
but like really she has a really pretty
smile
a really charming smile
yeah
and uh Munda already kind of mentioned
this
but like you know after the stream we
were like chilling and we were listening
to new jeans and all that
and then I know I my hair was like
messed up because I didn't bring any
like hair iron or anything on my flight
I didn't have any hair products and just
[\h__\h] and I didn't like how it looked it
was like from the humidity it was also
[\h__\h] so
I asked if Muna could
do my hair
I thought it would be a cute thing to do
yeah you know girls time so
it was so cute because
Cobble on the side was
um trying her best to do her makeup but
was really bad at it so Muna was telling
Kobo the steps on how to do her makeup
and she was using muna's products too
while
uh I was showing
like Muna video of like you know hair
stuff and then she was trying to copy
that yeah whole time buddy I was like oh
I'm not good at this she was like not
confident but I was like have confidence
you're doing great
yeah so she did my hair and then she
finished kobo's makeup because Kobo was
like
she was struggling so hard
um
we had this girl's time it was really
cute
hey
it was so cute
yeah and she did great
I thought it felt like we were having
like a sister time
helping each other out with like makeup
and hair and stuff
it was like sisters so cute
[Music]
yeah and the whole time we were
listening to new jeans
[\h__\h] love new jeans man
it's a K-Pop group just in case you
don't know
um
[Music]
okay I just saw something in my notes
that
makes me my blood boil
excuse me
anyway sorry it's all like messed up in
the order of the things I'm telling are
messed up
but
uh what was I well so yeah and then
at night we kind of went
okay with everybody which was a good get
together so I could get to know
everybody it was really really great I
want to say thank you to all the ID
members who took their time
uh
of their busy days
especially people like Kaela who have to
stream all day
because they have to because they're
addicted and you sacrificed some hours
in your day for me that was a really
really magical special time and yeah I
feel like we bonded so much it was nice
a nice girls night out
so
thing is my flight
was
I think something like at 6 00 am
or seven or something like that but I
had to leave
at 3am in hindsight I'm so glad that I
did because
um it was in the end really really
last minute close a close call
because
so
uh I check out
I give I I opened this taxi app right
and I type in uh the airport name
and I know that I need to go to I think
terminal free I think it was
so maybe people who live there and use
that app and have tried to type that in
know what I'm talking about
but there's something really confusing
at least from my point of view it was
really confusing there's I think there's
free terminals
and
one I think it's the first one the first
terminal I think is mostly for
uh domestic flights but it does
have
some international flights
on
a section of the terminal that's called
gate free so they have like gate one
gate two gate free get four and so on
until five I think but that doesn't mean
that it's not the gates that are inside
you know that go from like one to 60 70
or whatever you know those are different
Gates
for some reason they call that gate one
two three and so on outside where the
taxis would stop and drop you off and
depending on the gate you know gate one
to two would be domestic flights and
then free was apparently International
and that's the thing they had for all
the terminals
following me so far okay good now here
is the problem
I typed in the airport name and then it
gave me several suggestions
I swear it did not show me Terminal 3
suggestion for some reason
what it did show me was terminal
1 international flights gate free
so
since I didn't see anything else that
said international flights and the
number three I was like um I guess
that's it
I I guess that's it
so I choose that
and yeah it was the wrong terminal but
he dropped me off the taxi driver and I
was like wandering around the terminal I
was like
I immediately knew this wasn't it but I
was looking for
you know maybe I'm wrong but I when I
looked at the flight schedule I
immediately saw there's these are all
not going anywhere outside of this
continent
so I was like okay time wise I'm still
probably fine but how am I gonna get to
the other terminal so I I I I've tried
to find
this was so stupid because there were
there was a an Ebro that said terminal
two and three and I followed that but
eventually the era would always
disappear at some point
and it made no sense I was like
wandering back and forth between gate
one to gate four whatever a million
times the whole terminal one I've walked
through
five times
yeah
in the beginning I was still going
slowly because I thought oh time is fine
but more and more time was passing I
just didn't find my way there and
eventually
I went outside the terminal
there's some kind of like
um like train Sky Train or whatever
that transports you to uh the like yeah
gate now on my way there I passed by
some taxi drivers who were like hey I
want to go somewhere and I'm like no no
I'm good I'll take the train
so I I finally find the this train
trying to get on the shuttle train to go
to the other terminal
and of course I'm too early
it said that it's opening at whatever
seven no nine eight a.m I don't know but
it was definitely not that time yet for
a while for at least an hour or so
so
I'm like [\h__\h] now now I'm getting
nervous because I can't find my waiter I
guess I'll take a taxi
so I walk back to the taxis
I I turned some of them down already but
it's okay at that point I just said
no no big deal yet so I walk over there
there's like a million taxes standing
there right
and
I go to the very front
and there's one guy who's like you know
offering me a taxi and I'm like can you
speak English though and he's like yeah
yeah so we we
[\h__\h] and I say I need to go to terminal
free and he says okay
so in so much money and I forgot what it
was I think it was probably like
um
wait
okay yeah he said one hundred thousand
rupees
and at this point I already knew right
that the Indonesian currency has a lot
of zeros
but I thought
I don't know why but it sounded like so
much to me
and
somehow I I thought it was one more zero
I thought it was more like you know 100
000 real base is like seven bucks or ten
bucks yeah
but I thought it was more like 1 million
rupees which would be like 70 bucks and
I thought he was scaring me because I
know that if I don't order it for I've
been warned I've been warned that I
should only order taxis through
um that's a scam well that's all I mean
it's still like plenty cheap plenty
cheap okay it's fine
but I I indeed thought I was being
scammed but not I was I thought I was
being way more scammed that I was
actually being scammed
um
um so because yeah I was born so many
times by other ID members that I should
only order taxes for the app where it
already says the price before you ride
it so I was being very careful you know
and I think in theory that's a good idea
to have to be careful you know in a
country where our scamming tourists uh
is a very common thing
you guys I'm surprised you guys say
that's expensive because
okay I guess it's inexpensive for
Indonesia but it's fine I don't
I wait that no problem
terminal
so but I then
I guess now you guys make me feel a
little bit relieved because what I did
after that
I thought was ridiculous and so
embarrassing I wanted to
like disappear but apparently it wasn't
that unreasonable apparently
according to you guys so I thought he
was scamming me like big deal I thought
he was asking for a million rupees and I
said no no that makes no sense I paid
half of that
uh to get to the airport from the city
center
so I'm not gonna pay double just to get
to a different terminal
that's that's the reasoning I gave him I
said that it makes no sense that's too
expensive
but all the oh in my mind he was asking
for like a hundred bucks not for 10.
and then he's like yeah no that's that's
the price it has to be this price
because this and that yes and he was not
like changing his mind and I said no
I'm still hoping that he would go down
with the price you know that yeah I was
haggling
um
because I really thought he was asking
for 100 bucks I thought that was really
unreasonable so I was like this is
really unreasonable that's way too much
way too much
hahaha
he insisted so
I said okay that's all right I'll take
uh the shuttle
no okay wait this happened before I went
to the shuttle and then realized oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah this was before I
went to the show I thought at this point
that I still had the option of the
shuttle
so it's like ah it's fine okay I'll go
over the shuttle then that one's free
so I turn around
and I thought I was still gonna be fine
so I walk over to the shuttle where I'm
wasting another like 10 minutes because
the walk is pretty far
for some reason and like oh [\h__\h] and I
walk back
so I wasted another 10 minutes on this
I'm like [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
I don't want to go to the same people
and be like I guess I'm taking the taxi
after all
but I was hoping that it would already
be different people but it was really
early in the morning like four or five
a.m so there was no way that so many
people would be taking taxes so I walk
back it's like literally a walk of shame
for me
and I'm like I I get I guess I'm taking
the taxi because the shuttle is not
operating yet yeah I came crawling back
but at that point I already realized
that I made a mistake anyway I realized
at that point that he's not charging me
hundred bucks he's charging me 10 bucks
I was like that's totally fine I just
feel really
really embarrassed about coming back
after
um haggling and after declining them
so confidently
[Laughter]
and and what pissed me off for real was
because I was literally the only tourist
walking around there it was there was no
one else there so all the taxi drivers
were looking at me there were like 20
taxi drivers you know
and they all gave me that stupid smug
grin
like how she came crawling back that
stupid tourist
[\h__\h] pissed me off so much
but I am really glad to see the comments
thank you
apparently my haggling was reasonable
even though I was thinking I was
haggling a completely different price
ha
it was so old and I wasted so much time
with this whole thing I wasted an hour
I went to the airport two hours before
the flight I think
oh yeah so it must have been six no I
don't know but I know that I went six
hours ahead of time
um like arrival at the airport six hours
ahead of the flight
so then I I I finally reached Terminal 3
one hour before my flight I was trying
to freak out
very confusing even for locals I suggest
got a friend to help navigate yeah when
I was like with all that was happening I
wrote to Muna
I got really close with Muna again
like every time we interact properly we
Bond very much I feel like
last time was that that sports festival
where we bonded for the first time and
now I feel like we bonded really a lot
so she was like my go-to I was like I'm
kind of like stuck in the airport and
this and that and this and that I can't
get to the word and she was like worried
about me it was really sweet
hmm
yeah then I arrived finally and man
I was it was on time all is okay it was
totally fine I could I was even able to
once I was inside right at the gate I
was able to
grab a bite of a piece of cake at a cafe
ow
imagine the Indonesia
um
foreign
I think so but you know I had to leave
at 3am I would never ask them to get up
at 3am for me
nah I thought that was gonna be fine
because all I had to do was jump into
the taxi
if the
if the like application gave me the
terminal free option properly then I
think I would have been fine but do you
understand like why I chose the wrong
terminal in the first place don't you
agree that it's confusing
why does the supposedly domestic
terminal have
an international
section too that's so confused
yeah I was so [\h__\h] stressed why I'm
both at my
um departure
to Indonesia and then back to Austria uh
Japan at both occasions it was just a
big [\h__\h] mess normally I'm better at
traveling alone
done the same thing in Detroit ended up
at the Roman terminal happened to me a
couple times
thank God not only me I buy they divided
by flight company
that's why it's mixed sometimes yeah I
noticed that too um
we're going to check anyway it must be
the third grade of that section
eh
I'm sure you know terminal for option
yeah yeah I really didn't get that
option in the app
oh well that was my Indonesia trip and
even though that was the overall like
stressful trip I had so much fun and I
made great memories and I got to know
the ID members better
um I love them so much
yeah and it really one thing I I I
watched a lot of like videos because I
got nervous about using my left hand in
Indonesia
because when they told me that I was
like oh [\h__\h] what else are they not
telling me that I shouldn't be doing
that's like a given to them so they're
not telling me
um because it's just too too default for
them to normal
so I've watched videos of what not to do
in Indonesia and then you know people
were saying oh Indonesia you know the
culture is so welcoming and everybody's
like so
I guess they have like this omotenashi
like Japan has
where
I know
what was it
they have a very I forgot the word
yeah well welcoming culture hmm
you're behind on the stream well in this
one you can catch up and you can go back
again and catch up again
just show e-ticket of your flight most
will turn the driver now yeah I'm
surprised the driver didn't even ask me
like which terminal I wanted to go but I
guess because I already put it in but it
would have been nice to
yeah you know make sure that this
tourist isn't getting lost
because I swear
I I did not even fit into this terminal
one at all
and I feel like the taxi driver should
have
maybe worried about me because I was
I was the only I was the only white
person in the whole terminals
there was definitely I was definitely
not supposed to be there
um
I mean I immediately knew oh
nothing's wrong
what's wrong here
sadly they don't care
when I in Austria when I uh take a cab
to the airport
um I guess because in the app you can
just type in the airport without using
choosing a terminal they always ask
which terminal
I want to go to hmm oh well
[Music]
did you test your office German no we
didn't talk about that at all
maybe they just thought you're traveling
the country yeah I guess so maybe they
thought I'm flying to Bali that's what I
was thinking they probably all thought
I'm going to Bali well I wish I was
going to Bali in that moment but I was
not
yeah the taxi drivers don't speak at all
I've I've taken a couple taxes while I
was there and I don't talk at all
hmm
gold white girl go
what is this some kind of meme y'all act
like you've never seen a white person
before
oh yeah two people in a row saying that
Bali is for landing I'm saving that
will be a bali trip eventually
when you talk about the ninja Meetup you
know what I will but I should read some
super chats at least
why did I not turn off the super chats
am I stupid
um
did you get to hear Kyla's love
I think so like it didn't stand out to
me like in a weird way
I think it was normal
ah Eminem song
a few taxes still in America and our
older folk and they're all really chill
that's nice
so you can impress Cal if you go to
Jakarta on your ballet trip I wonder if
there's any direct flights to Bali
denies you over love I've heard about
that but
maybe it didn't stand out to me because
I didn't hear anything
but
I also didn't feel like she was not
laughing
I don't know
hmm
[Laughter]
that's funny
ah
thanks for sharing your experience of
visiting Eddie yeah I want to go again
and I want to meet the girls again
are Lisa and Zetta already back
in ID
they're gone right probably by now
I thought if I I thought maybe when I'm
back in Japan I could like still somehow
set up something with them
but
you know it was kind of like
stressful once I got back everything was
very stressful because I got sick
I had some off collapse immediately and
then I got sick then I had to get
healthy really quick and then I had my
showcase and then I was sick even more
and I watched some Lord of the Rings and
now we're here
um
so this one maybe still in Japan
is back don't know about issue
let me Lisa back they're back okay
okay
wow it's so close to collecting them all
so close
that's okay
yeah I did a lot in that short time
didn't I
um and I wanted to do more in a short
time originally
hey
okay let me turn off the super chats
actually thank you for reminding me
I guess they'll have to stay off for at
least a couple days
um
play some super chat now I'm kind of
slow I'm slow I'm slow please don't
please don't please don't
but even if I don't catch up anytime
soon we'll just you know
we'll take it easy we'll take it slow I
mean we just recently got out of a an
endless Super Chat reading
thing because I was sick and couldn't
read it it's like it's history is
repeating that itself
back then I couldn't catch up because I
was sick and now I can't catch up
because I was sick
this one looks more endless well yeah
[\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
no thank God I can tell you even more
stories tomorrow
um I will tell I will try to tell
another story today
but first
let me try to read some super chats so
what was the most recent
no the oldest one that I have to read
sector it is
I'll go back to talking after reading
some super chats because I I've been um
tensing for two hours Fire Emblem part
five okay Coolio
I read Final in part five where I didn't
assume I did that or did I yeah
during ah
what
did I read them
okay
Fire Emblem it is
I want to play more problems I talked a
little bit about flambling with Cali to
the ah
talks a little bit with caliber she told
me she's been playing in hardcore
when she's planning on streaming it
eventually
um
but by that time she will already know
the whole story because like she's
almost done with the game
[Music]
can I take a bite from my katsu sandwich
is that okay for you guys I don't know
if I can
really only do one bite but
I have a cartoon sandwich
I'm gonna take it as a yes
in 20 seconds
go for it yeah that wasn't even 20
seconds
um
[Music]
wow that's a big Katsu
and some salad in there some cabbage
ah oh
[Music]
um
my [\h__\h] job
[\h__\h]
ow
why does it hurt
maybe somebody has to relocate my job
should have put an Apple Air tag on it
huh
oh
my God
[Music]
yeah
um
if I had
a nickel for every whole life English
girl
who's been having issues with their jaw
I would have two which is weird
what
[Laughter]
I tried
something was wrong there I said it
wrong
um
I might be clenching it in my sleep yeah
that is very possible
ah which isn't a lot but the Stranger in
heaven tries thank you
hmm
[Music]
I mean it was a proper sentence at least
um
[Music]
it's so good holy [\h__\h]
some things you know you know Katsu
is one of my favorite foods in Japan
um
but normally you know it's like served
with like rice or soup
which is like the katsu and the rice and
everything separate
um very classic
which is like in a rice bowl with egg
and so on there's many ways to serve
katsu but this is a katsu sandwich and
it's kind of like similar to how
you can have yakisoba you know those
noodles
Japanese fried noodles
uh as its own but then there's also
yakisoba bread super sandwich
genius and both are like
really good in different ways
[Music]
oh
quizzle
I'm eating the whole thing guys I'm so
sorry
it's not that big though it will not
take too long I'm almost done
um
[Music]
next week
on Sunday night
I'm doing something
that I
initiated yesterday
[Music]
um
that I was really nervous about
please remind me to tell you about it
once it happened because I can't tell
you now
it's not a stream
but it's the continuation of an arc and
a story
it made me freak out so bad yesterday
[Music]
next weekend
mysterious
[Music]
mm-hmm
Natural Life related I'm sorry
for me
it's crazy
okay I'm not that crazy but I got really
hyped um
yummy
um
[Music]
foreign
that was a huge bite
[Music]
okay
to be continued indeed
is it music related
um I guess in suddenly yeah
I've never never
um
never happening
sadly I'm not big enough for something
like that
um
so
it's kind of like a like a private life
thing it's not even stream related guys
but I think
everybody who's been watching me for a
while
will
um
be very excited for me
I will see that we'll see we'll see how
it goes
all right all right all right
gotta Read Super chats a little a little
bit a little bit but let me have a fruit
candy
broken candy
[Music]
and then we'll read these stupid chats
tomorrow by the way we're continuing
Fire Emblem
right after Amish stream
is my plan
immediately after work like half an hour
after our show
um
okay very well
him go
Mickey Mouse
Mountain eight thank you for the pinky
so attention by the metro primary Master
choking aside to GB and GBA uh being on
NSO
and this oh
[Music]
Nintendo switch online Nintendo switch
online open up a lot of possibilities
the Zelda Oracle games are pretty great
oh
hoping for that Mario Kart Advance 64 of
collab since it does have local multi oh
do those games I I want to know which of
those um games on Nintendo switch online
have online multiplayer and which have
local because I know some of them at
least have more um online
does the Mario Kart Advance
uh only have local
because then that actually helps me
because I was looking for
something to do
for an off collab with a Japanese member
Mario
party has online Mario Kart is online
too oh
are there any specific ones that have
local only
but you know us
we feel like Mario Kart one would be
would make a lot of sense
don't think so what happened they should
all be online I guess that makes sense
because it's called Nintendo switch
online you would hope that they're
multiplayable online huh
but you never know with Nintendo
you never know
okay actually that's really good that's
really good
[Music]
um
hmm okay
let me put something in my schedule
and then here
okay so that I don't forget
let's go all right
uh uh
thank you mention for letting me know
about that and
um maybe when I get back to Austria
we can play Metroid Prime on the side
how about that while playing Fire Emblem
I think
I mean that would be fine
I'm not that far
from finishing Farmland either like at
least I'm in the middle of the game I
would say right maybe
yeah
and have a side project how about that
yeah let's go
Pinky
[Music]
Hey You Pepsi Wawa
what
what peps you are
reminds me of Google because
she's been you know very very particular
about
her cloaks having to be Pepsi she goes
out of her way to get Pepsi which is a
bit difficult in Japan
oh because of the hip
ah
today was time for my yearly level up
and now I'm now that I'm 21. I think
it's time for a class change oh have any
ideas on what class I could promote into
or
anyway thanks a bunch for making this
past you're super engaging much love
engaging wait is that another Fire
Emblem joke
I guess it is it didn't really mean it
huh
laughs
yeah I mean I opposed to
um she doesn't want Coca-Cola she wants
Pepsi
[\h__\h] my jaw hurts
you're welcome doesn't she seem like a
Pepsi person huh I think she seems like
a Pepsi person
um
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] my job
I hope it will fix itself
ow
maybe and if if I'm basically if we tell
okay okay okay Fred
um
you will be the kfp ring
protector
which almost sounds if as if you like
Frodo because we also watch Lord of the
Rings recently so it has like a double
meaning oh my God isn't that incredible
that's such a cool title for you
have you gotten the check my job thing
no that's like it started a little bit
yesterday but it's been really strong
today
block jaw is that a thing like did I do
that is that what I did did I lock my
job
how do you fix a lock jaw
applying a warm compress by using a hot
water bag or hot towel several times a
day so that it loosens the block jaw
muscles using cold packs as this will
relieve of the pain associated with
lockjaw rectifying your posture is
crucial to prevent long jaw condition
from worsening
hmm
what causes a lock jaw
tennis
inflammation of the soft tissue
other causes
fevers oral diseases illnesses
[Music]
oh yeah maybe I'm
what's the word when you feel empathetic
Maybe
I'm pathetic no empathy
I'm also pathetic but I also have
empathy
what a what a trap to run into as a nun
mother tongue English speaker
[Laughter]
we'll see if it goes away tomorrow if it
doesn't if it doesn't then I don't know
we'll see well thank you rat I hope you
like your title did you change it
already where's Red
I'm sorry in the chat a moment ago and
you still didn't have the title but how
about now
[Music]
where did I live utmost honor yes you
will
yay yay how do you know I don't have
that
yeah it's a child does that work forever
if you uh if you get the thingy as a
child
are those vaccinations like forever
well then I guess I'll be fine
I'm probably fine
okay I should hurry the [\h__\h] up um
[Music]
laughs
really substitute
is that true
it's every 10 years oh then I don't
think I am vaccinated anymore
[Laughter]
maybe I should like update my
vaccinations
where substitute I saw you
where are you hmm
do you know do you remember what you
wrote in this Super Chat hmm
is this your your real true feelings
where are you
this is really how you feel ah
that was a much better reaction than I
anticipated better
my heart is broken is that really better
so I'm guessing that was
not how you truly feel right I hope so
because I I think right now you're also
pulling that all neither aren't you
you are an immediate danger every time
you suffer a cut oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I couldn't have asked for a better
Mentor because then I feel like homework
you need to get vaccinated against
tsundere because apparently it's
spreading
like a wildfire
yeah yeah I think in Austria it's not a
big deal that's why no no doctor ever
told me to update my vaccinations there
foreign
rusty metal
dirt
Etc and blood is drawn
[Music]
interesting
hope you recovered from your vaccination
I don't have energy to beat soon it do
be taking energy don't it
hmm
yes it's under the vaccination
it's not like I like you or anything hey
go to the doctor now
take your meds
soon
the first things first I hope you feel
better soon angel
what
didn't the Super Chat come in before I
got sick what what was I hoping to feel
better from back then
foreign
second in the entirety of the two years
over two years I have been in kfp my
icon has been Hector from Fire Emblem
the Blazing blade so
with the new DLC I hope to appreciate
the glory of Hector and Soren and
Camilla
I don't think I've seen Hector before
ah after the dance lesson I was tired oh
yeah I guess my body was like
um kind of sore huh
suffering from memory loss I still am
I think I was just tired well thank you
for worrying about me Jose hero your
Super Chat is now very even more
fitting because I'm
I'm sick but I'm getting there
Hector best boy Hector from The Iliad he
was in the DLC your brain and residency
because he is the cute girl
yeah yep probably
[Music]
that could very well be
it did I already get the ring for him
I don't think so I would have remembered
the name at least maybe not what he
looks like but the name
oh
not yet it's from DLC he's a bracelet ah
well
you know what I mean
isn't he just one of those like rings
that like the bronze ones that you get
for example the bronze silver and so on
what do I have to unlock him see I am
not really actively using him yet right
so well well well just a hero maybe that
time will come the next stream maybe I
don't know
um
but then I can hopefully make you smile
just by the presence of Hector because
apparently my presence is not enough
hmm
but thank you for the rest of the chat
I think it's spreading to me too I think
I'm turning to the help help help
science the Doncaster for the pinky Ohio
[Music]
hmm
um
[Music]
is it terminal
um well it was not terminal free where I
wanted to go
hey
good one kiwawa thank you kiwawa
um
[Music]
foreign
Iris a drama thanks for the pinky I can
finally catch a stream no way let's go
oh well that probably means we can catch
them one tomorrow too because it's gonna
be around no I guess I started
That Fire Emblem streamed like two hours
earlier than I will start tomorrow
possibly
but I hope you can still catch it thank
you Iris a drama I hope you enjoyed it
as long as you could thank you for
coming to my Fire Emblem streams I
really appreciate it yeah
yeah
thank you
soon
hi up papaya
open the waiting room on my PC while I
went to super access my alarm definitely
oh did it work would I do stuff like
that I'm worried that my PC will just
shut itself down
yo
so I don't really rely on that
okay
that means
[Music]
hmm
please accept my germs
and hopefully you don't get sick from
them hopefully you'll have a strong
immune system taiji
thank you for your support how you doing
huh
how's it going Thai team
hope you're doing well
you didn't even sign up for my germs at
that time I wasn't even sick and you
didn't know
that the kiss you would receive would
have bacteria on it that would make you
sick
you didn't sign up for it but I'm sure
you would still appreciate it
if it comes from me right
cougars48 Skylanders
an ex-general Give Her Sacred engraved
Killer X plus Ike
let her murder whatever she comes across
ringed her totally nothing to do with
the orange hair in them
I don't know if I'll remember that until
tomorrow
the current acts General isn't she
already I don't know at this point
sacred engraved killer ax I'll try to
remember that one
sacred engraved
you're welcome to remind me tomorrow can
vouch for that oh
she is
you know kind of a edgy wannabe Gothic
version of me
I'd make her a warrior instead to be
honest
if you have the strongest immune system
considering you live next
[Music]
to me no I didn't want to be like that
um not quite no
I made her into a Vibe and write it what
that was a character joke excuse me
was so only yours are funny yes they are
nah I've laughed at your jokes guys
plenty
that was bad
fixes her death stops use the sword
users from breaking
well remind me tomorrow please when I if
I ever get to the point where I have to
um like change her class or so
thank you for the red super chat what is
this about
you're just yes
[Music]
yes
that's oh great news wait what was that
about apparently I announced something
because the other one says great news
what was this about
[Music]
it will take a while until I get the
answer ah when I say I want to play
Metroid Prime
[Music]
already knew that at the beginning of
the stream didn't he
I know I guess you didn't you were just
hoping for it there
aren't you two so happy
chickens huh
those Metroid Prime
or she's
yeah my throat is
okay-ish but now my jaw is [\h__\h]
no you only joked about it yeah yeah
yeah
no I didn't re-watch my Vlogs ever
of Fire Emblem
but I did watch some videos about Fire
Emblem engage some tips and tricks
anyway I'm glad I can make you happy
with Metroid Prime I'm gonna start maybe
when I go back as I said before today
hmm
how long is that game huh let's look at
a Metroid Prime remaster
game length here there we go
what
it's so short
well I thought it would be maybe at
least like I don't know 25 or 30 hours
but it says 13 and a half hours
well done all right hell yeah yeah let's
do it let's do it why is it so short
took me 12 hours yeah I mean I heard
also that it sounds so difficult because
it locks
it might be FPS but it locks there it's
like there's like a lock function so
it's not difficult to hit
so I might not struggle that much with
it right
interesting
maybe I can finish it in free streams
would be nice
okay okay yeah I'm looking forward to it
then nice too thank you named
um
thank you for listening to my streams
and covers I appreciate it
I have no idea what's going on right now
but I love it
hmm I also have no idea what was going
on there
yeah I thought that after that day
this kind of stuff would happen all the
time
somehow it didn't
I'm sorry for getting your hopes up guys
well I wasn't like streaming much after
that I guess like I was not doing many
streams where that could happen and the
other girls also didn't do many streams
where that could happen
and yeah I would definitely not want to
intrude on like good as member stream
that she did I think that was one thing
yeah I mean there were at least some
planned off collapse like the Mario
party that Emma did with some girls
and I did ID stuff and so on and I'm
still planning more off collapse
uh next week but we also have uh on
Sunday we have the free day
I want you guys to watch that one okay
now on the next you know public stream
right in when is her next public stream
when is it what will it be
and will she even let me in is the
question because if she doesn't expect
it then she probably also didn't clean
her room
so I don't know if she will let me in we
can apply pressure
on her
[Music]
oh also she probably within this week
she probably wouldn't want to see me
anyway because I'm still considered to
be sick I think
the cans on her dancing
[Music]
thank you
all are really enjoying that huh crew
thank you soon
endless thank you for the pinky thanks
for the stream Kiana glad to have had
the opportunity to catch it live
I am very glad too
maybe tomorrow too because you're in a
similar time zone right now supposedly
right similar time zone is me I think
show maybe generally right now you're
having a better time with catching my
streams than normally even normally I
I'm probably streaming in the middle of
the night for you yeah so cherish this
time cherish this moment
as I do
thank you for watching
Australian kids be living like it's 20
20.
it's so true
yeah don't get used to it
thanks for the pinky I think this is the
first time I beat a game before Kiana
cleared it
really I mean
it well of course I take longer with
those games because I stream them and I
have time in between to where I can't
play it
how how have you not done that until now
I still want this time bad joke aside
it's been a lot of fun watching play
fine bloom again I gotta pass out soon I
hope you keep having fun
well thank you
what what else have you do you even
start at the same time as I do like do
you start after I'm already finished
because then of course you don't finish
it before me
how how is this possible
JK H is a really busy guy
well
still that that's that's fascinating
because I also play like some
shorter games and still take a lot of
time with it
hmm
does that mean that I am a gamer
am I a gamer
oh
um
foreign
[Music]
is definitely a new experience I hope
everything is going well in Japan for
your boss
thank you
thank you thank you thank you wait uh oh
waking up
you're in European time zone right
yeah I hope you can
handle this current
schedule somehow I'm sorry that you know
there's always someone losing and
there's someone winning
but I think you'll understand
it and you'll still support me right
so thank you very much for your patience
I'll be back soon
and be closer to you again
and I'll stream a decent times for you
so please wait for me okay
[Music]
friends ah
nice
I'll be back soon okay
[Music]
thank you
a little pic of your girl so I can make
over section would could be fun if
technology
um yeah but still makeup just
it doesn't quite work on anime
characters it looks weird
like do you ever see it's really rare
really rare do you ever see like
a lipstick
and anime characters it's really really
really rare normally it just doesn't
really look good
unless you have a very specific anime
style
lipstick and like you know eyeshadow and
this particular eyelashes and stuff I
don't know I don't know it's difficult
to like
get that across the same way and do like
the same things like eyeliner
hmm I mean it's possible but it just
doesn't have the same kind of like
impact
and effect as on a human face
but maybe maybe we'll still give it a
try on a PNG
and then yeah draw makeup on top of it
the thing is we can't even use the real
makeup project product still because
we're doing it like in Photoshop or
whatever right so
um
difficult
oh you know what would be cute though
getting elfi as a guest
and having her for the special occasion
Give us new hairstyles
but prepare it beforehand but you know
as if
as if she's doing it right there
[Music]
meet the ball the Europeans
yeah it was still not my turn
I wonder when
when's it gonna be my turn
foreign
[Music]
oh the next one actually has much less
super chats the hollow backs one
I could get that one done really quickly
now if I wanted to
let me do that one
okay
yeah you're gonna use my new connection
with her we'll tell her that you want to
be her customer oh yeah do it please
I think I told her before though
um
what next not small Super Chat is actual
showcase okay okay
foreign
okay okay
yeah but it's good to get these out of
the way first too
uh possibly only these smaller ones
today who knows
and okay let me do this and then we do a
tangent
Patsy that is
thanks for the pinky today I felt a
specially awoken yolk day I realized I
finally got my orange wings yay two
years with you and kfb have been a
blessing for even my rap days and you've
inspired me to move forward with my life
even further so I plan to go back to
school oh I take up a graduate degree
again someday
I'll spread These Wings you gave me and
make you proud love you Kiara and I'll
Follow You Until the End
[Music]
sounds amazing
good for you you say someday though so I
guess it's still gonna be a little while
and you have still
plenty of time hopefully for your kfp
job right
hopefully
don't leave me so soon okay
still need you
still need you here but I wish you the
best of luck and I know you can do it
you'll do great and it will be so worth
it I'm sure
I personally I can't imagine myself like
going to the university or anything like
that now
I definitely don't have the brain
capacity for something like that
or the patients but I'm I'm so like
proud of you I respect that you want to
do it and that you're motivated for it
um
so good luck might be tough sometimes
but it will be so worth it going through
with it so yeah
also thank you for being a member for
such a long time too
yeah
for the pinky a year old or another
birthday with kfp oh you forgot forgot
me forgot to get me a present no worries
while I was seeing you on the screen
while hanging out with KFC already is
the greatest gift I could receive my
only birthday wishes that I get to meet
even more kfp this year
oh that's so sweet
what kind of sounds like you want to see
Kofi more than me
just kidding but
it's nice to see you guys get along it's
very sweet makes me a proud kiwawa proud
boss
to have raised everyone so well
um
oh and should I sing Happy Birthday to
you oh happy birthday to beats happy
birthday to beets
happy birthday celebrates
happy birthday to you yeah
how was your birthday it's already ooh
how many days ago oh that's that's oh my
God that was last month
well okay February was pretty short
as it's just the beginning of March now
so it sounds like it's ages ago
I mean it's still kind of is ages ago
it's like two weeks ago
[Laughter]
oopsie well
time passes by really fast doesn't it so
what does that tell us huh
treasure and cherish every day you have
in kfp with me
um
thank you for supporting me
and supporting kfb too
um
black people thank you for the rest of
the chat thank you so much for bringing
Hollow bags back then so it's even one
of the few streams I can watch live this
month I so fondly remember the first
Hollow backs maybe there will even be
some input from other girls either way a
big thank you showing to you boss yeah I
wish I could do this series endlessly
but there's only you know like a certain
amount of members who I can introduce
the bags from and yeah
yeah eventually it will also get
predictable depending on who
who have already showed
foreign
ID she was still using the same bag
ow
oh
[Music]
well well I wish I wish I could do this
one forever
so it's definitely a very limited time
stream
but hopefully I'll come up with more
interesting uh I actually
I actually did come up with a genius
stream idea yesterday
I don't know if I should spoil it
I didn't even talk about it with Elena
yet because it's something I want to do
as a collab with Dana
it's so genius I mean to me it's genius
I don't know how you guys react to it I
came for the secret for a little while
longer than okay okay
I'll do it sometime in the next couple
months
yeah
it's it's something that definitely
takes some preparation
for one stream but um
I think it will be
legendary
write that down and then quote me on it
later
yes Maldives season two
no but I do want to go to the Maldives
again this year
I don't think I can resist the Maldives
or maybe maybe the Seychelles
are fine too because I should go to
other places too
and there the Seychelles are very
similar as far as I know
no no food review ill I don't want to be
involved in such things
uh
why is my jaw hurt so much
bird making answers just the other day I
re-watched that um YouTube short on Kana
ubu's Channel
from me and Elena you know the word
mating dance it's so funny I wish that
could have been on my channel oh have
you been enjoying my my YouTube shorts
and stuff and the clip and so on
recently guys
um
you know in order to get those YouTube
stuff shorts uh material
I
I begged
every time when I was like one one time
after a rehearsal
and one
[Music]
one after the actual thing I think the
cat one I recorded after immediately
after the
um showcase
even though I was sick and all that but
I was I wanted to use a chance I was
like can I please
if there's still time can could I please
possibly maybe record something you guys
only have to push the record button
please thank you
um I feel bad about taking up too much
time so I always try to make it as short
as possible
yeah
um but it's nice to have something
something small
to upload hmm
yeah yeah the cat thing was still very
fresh
I was kind of originally do the
voiceover myself but then I had no voice
so
you know I thought who else could I get
wait wouldn't it be perfect to get
couple because
she can surely recite it better than
anyone else with such passion and she's
the one who taught me in the first place
fine then keep your secrets
hmm
okay yeah
[Music]
yeah it made sense will you try for your
own cats no because it's [\h__\h] and I
know it's [\h__\h] I've known since the
first moment she told me about it that
this is not even German
laughs
it does not work on cats
the one in the short wasn't even a cat
it was a phoenix
don't know why she was walking on all
four but
she's still a phoenix
always works
cool will be like yeah boy
German always works
if I rewatched it a million times
because I didn't need to they were
always
occupied with me
works on feet well
I wouldn't say it works on me
but I guess the video showed that it
works on me
[Music]
would it help if I massaged my jaw
probably right because it's something to
do with the muscles right
making really funny faces right now
wow wow
wow wow wow
[Music]
why is it so stiff why is everything so
stiff in my face why are there so many
bones why can I not like to shake my jaw
[Music]
Crystal stiff I don't know if I'm making
it better
best to leave it alone really
okay well whatever I tried I I tried
where was I a kiss from Flappy boy
afterwards prime numbers
[Music]
a proud Norse vikings
black Richard nuggets
shrimp
thank you nakashun what is this for the
pinky
wow thank you for all you do also my
birthday was on the 10th and I wanted to
ask for a single favor can I get the
employee number one one one eight it
would mean a lot to me but any number
you give
I'll accept graciously why do you want
this particular number
is there a meaning to it it must be
it must have some meaning
BS I'm always bought genco's work
so you're not here now um
it can't be your birthday
to avoid just me giving the date I would
never do such a thing
but okay you can have that number I hope
you watch this Vlad
I hope this message gets to you and
happy belated birthday too
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday codename Ian shrimp
happy birthday to you
I hope it's not taken yeah I hope so
the chat will tell me if it is
watching me at work thank you what's up
what's up what's up
is it like helping number
well if you want it I guess you can have
it
huh
well it seems no one has a so I'm going
to say oh okay
I'm a chicken
[Music]
thank you Patrick there we go
yep
you didn't notice anything that what you
didn't notice
nothing happened
everything's normal
not taken okay
oh oh
that was for some reason on the right
side of my jaw hmm
maybe I by moving everything moved it
over to the right side
[Music]
anyway tangent time I said I would talk
about the ninja Sandy and meeting right
you may have heard about it
from other girlsies did I write down
notes somewhere I think I did
oh
[Music]
um
what
I wrote something down somewhere
[Music]
laughs
I can't find it
maybe here
okay I can't find it now I guess I have
to go by my memory completely
oof
even though it's already like ages ago I
feel like that's really ages ago
I talked a bit about it on the
membership yeah I guess I did okay okay
so uh basically for members this will be
a little bit repetition
basically
uh so
um
yeah the girls I I'm I've only really
been in contact with Pomo
um and then with some others here and
there you know I would reply to their
tweets and they would reply to my tweets
sometimes that's really about it but I
was always open to like getting to know
them
what do you mean my mother is really
terrible that's [\h__\h] because I do so
many things yeah yeah unless I remember
the fact that I did it but who the [\h__\h]
remembers all the details about it uh
weeks later like every single detail the
way I want to ideally tell you the
details about that's what I mean that's
why I write things down ideally I will
tell you like that but you know I would
say my memory is terrible but if you
consider all the things that I have to
remember
huh okay so
um
yeah and you'll see just how fine my
memory is now eh let me blast you with
my memory
tell him tell me
listen here your little [\h__\h]
so where was I
yeah okay so suddenly Nina messages me
and she's like hi
I'm in Japan too
but not for much longer would you like
to meet
me
and I
first of all I scrambled because I knew
I think she was like only there for
like two more days or so
and I my schedule was full with like
dance practice
and other stuff
so I said well I can squeeze it in
because I don't want to lose this
opportunity
um but I won't have much time and it
will just be like a dinner
and I also asked if you know as far as I
know
Petra is here too and I we talked before
that eventually while I'm here it would
be nice to meet up
so I said how about we combine it into
one thing because I am so busy and they
said yeah sure
so then it was supposed to be us free me
Nina and Petra
and suddenly well very close to the
actual day and time
Nina messages me and she's like is it
okay if some more girls come because
they want to meet you too
and I'm like
yes of course
so turns out
yeah turns out
we were and watch me
they wanted to see me they were also
there and they wanted to see me oh
so it was uh four
yeah four ninja girls and one me
versus
so thank God
they didn't beat me up or anything
because I would have not won I think
even as a phoenix
um
so we're planning to go to some uh like
Izakaya Izakaya is like a place where
you go mostly for like drinking but they
have so much yummy food and so much
variation I didn't drink but you know we
feasted on some yummy food
um
and and I was first I was very early
I was
maybe 20 minutes early
um
because I went after dance lesson and I
had like quite a bit time to spare
actually more than I expected even
though I did my makeup and all that
after the dance lesson
still had so much extra time
um and my problem was I couldn't even
contact them
cause I forgot on that day I forgot my
pocket Wi-Fi
in the apartment
so
yeah I was a bit scared about getting
lost and I kind of did almost
I gave the address to the taxi driver
the exact address
normally taxi drivers you know Tokyo has
a lot of really narrow streets
Street stable go through no problem
so I've never been dropped off that far
from the actual location before
but this dude dropped me off so far
and I did not have internet
and I did not really know where it was
because it was the first time I went to
that place and it wasn't an area where
there were like a million restaurants in
each building on every floor
so it was really hard to find and the
dude the taxi guy was like oh you just
walk down there and then right but it
was more than just that
it wasn't that easy
I looked around and looked around
and then it took me a while to find it
but I thankfully found it and it wasn't
late and I went in early and I'm
actually glad that I
arrived early and alone because then I
could like kind of like gather myself
and calm down
um
and yeah so they started arriving some
of them later than others but oh I think
Nina came first with a weaver
I think yeah yeah
so I started talking with them and they
were from the first moment they were so
friendly and so hyped and like so open
and so welcome and so engaged
you would think they're playing Fire
Emblem
yeah then we started ordering some
drinks I don't think we ordered food
right away I think we waited a bit
until the others would come
um
yeah hey I was so shy I was nervous
um but my shyness quickly I think flew
away because they were so open to me
um
they were so sweet yeah I had so much
fun talking to them and then soon after
came uh worse than me and she sat next
to me
yeah and then the last one to come was
petochan
Petra
the three of them were sitting across me
and we had like a kind of like a private
room because all these izakayas they
kind of have private rooms
um
yeah some of them you sit on on the
floor some of them you sit on chairs we
kind of sat in like an in-between where
you kind of
in some something that's like built into
the ground
but there's something to put down your
feet downwards sometimes there's not
even that and you have to sit like on
your feet or so
um
mm-hmm I don't know how to describe it
but yeah
hey was wasn't me cute yes she was very
wearing very girly cute clothes yeah
she's she was like
I think the the girliest in terms of
like kind of like fashion choice
very
Japanese girly Style
hmm I don't want to give anything away
that I'm not supposed to give away I
think it's okay the station was girly
uh is
it was funny because like she came from
a shopping trip apparently on that day
she was doing a bunch of stuff and then
she went shopping alone she had to like
get rid of all her
um how to say
she she had
attachments that she could get rid of no
matter how hard she tried she said again
and again I wanna go shopping without
saying I have to go underwear shopping
don't want to be like you know that's
embarrassing okay
hahaha
yeah but she went underwear shopping so
she really proudly showed off her
underwear to us she was like I bought
some underwear today do you want to see
that everybody's like yeah yeah show us
it was really cute I feel like the
underwear that they sell in Japan
is very different in terms of design
then underwear that they sell in like
America or Europe
because like Japanese designs they're
very frilly and
very Lacy and very cutesy and the colors
are almost all of them are pastel or
white very bright colors
um I used to love those I would
particularly buy a lot of
underwear in Japan and then bring it
back to Austria nowadays
not so much my thing anymore
um
anyway
yeah but they definitely have really
cute underwear so we were looking at the
stuff that she bought it was really
brilliant
and she had to chase away the
Tunisian boys because they were hanging
out and they were like oh we'll go with
you she's like no but that's her story
sounds very cute but zero percent sexy
yeah yeah yeah I mean I mean they look
for it they also have some like
mature looking
oh underwear yeah they do they do they
do but like the the most like standard
one is always the cutesy stuff
um
[Music]
I guess she did
um
oh well well well yeah um we just talked
so much holy [\h__\h] it was like never
ending waterfall conversations
uh yeah and like it was very sweet I
felt I felt very
um like understood
and it was interesting to hear their
point of views
um but in the end you know
we have different
things but we also have similar things
like you know in the end we're like
YouTubers from
you know two big corporate companies
um but you know
I think there's maybe a
like
rivalry thinking uh from the outside
point of view
and maybe also from the inside for some
people
um
but I definitely with this even more
felt that I just want to be friends with
them
at least the girls
um
I only care about the girls I'm so sorry
about the girl characters
yeah I mean I mean the guys are surely
fine too but girls are cute and I like
girls uh Girls Girls Girls Girls Girls
Girls Girls
um
so yeah I just want to be you know on
good terms with them I'm gonna be
friends and maybe do some collabs here
and there every now and then if possible
I'm so glad that you know nowadays we or
we can do that
um now we can collab uh so yeah I I
think I'm gonna do another collab with
some of them
hmm
either one-on-one or something bigger
would be nice too gonna do something
sometime soon yeah
so
we had a good foof thingy going on
talks talked a lot about a lot of things
uh but then I had to go because
because
before
um I went to that
management told us myth girls that
you know a certain deadline has already
passed please do it within today girls a
video we had to record a short video
within today
no matter what and I was like okay okay
okay
don't worry management we're going to do
it
rely on us it will be fine we'll we'll
make it happen and I was very very set
in my mind to do it today because we
were already late but it was something
where we all had to get together so you
know it was difficult
um
so I said okay I'll be back
uh at 11 PM roughly so wait for me and
then we'll record it okay and I said
okay and I also told them I don't have
internet with me today
so I can't really say anything until
then but I'll see you then I'll let you
guys know when I'm home
so uh even though I was having the time
of my life I had to leave a bit um early
and eliwa forced
Hermione on me
I said no no
that was no sense she gives me like
ichimayan which is like like 90 bucks
I'm like what the [\h__\h] everyone no that
makes no sense first of all the taxi is
not gonna cost this much
second of all it makes no sense you're
from a different company why would you
be paying for my taxi it makes no sense
the very thing even if we were in the
same company then that would be a senpai
so if anything I should be paying for
your taxi
but like she she was like so insisting
on it like no no take it it was so nice
that you came to see us like you came
for us and all that
yeah
um I could literally not turn it down
but I said well
oh I did I think I did like um yeah when
she was like she was paying for the food
too that's right she paid for the food
too and I was like no no no no no no no
wait what the [\h__\h] this is too much so I
I even though she was also then turning
it down I um pushed some a little little
amount of money for the food
in her pocket
when she she was in the middle of paying
so she couldn't like multitask and like
turn me down at the same time as she was
dealing with the payment
for the food at the cashier so I took
that moment and I
put some money into a pocket she
couldn't give it back to me
yeah
the reverse pickpocket yeah yeah
um
uh
yeah and then we went outside and then
you know they called a taxi for me
because I had no internet so I couldn't
call a taxi
um but yeah so I told you we want that I
will eventually invite her to something
if we meet again
so that it will it would even out
because that was way too much money
um
put pocketer
[Laughter]
pickpocket 100 stealth sneaky I mean it
wasn't really sneaky I think she noticed
but she just couldn't react to it
was um not possible to multitask
yeah
so and so I I came back
around 11 pm
I opened my door and the first thing I
did was log into my Wi-Fi on my phone to
be like hey I'm back
and then I see five minutes or so before
I arrived
they were talking
writing on Discord in our group
saying
huh I'm kind of tired can we do it
tomorrow and someone else is like oh
yeah I think we can do it just tomorrow
oh yeah okay well I mean
Kiara won't see this message until later
but yeah all right let's let's sleep
okay bye
laughs
no comment
hahaha
um
yeah
so we recorded it the following day
and they didn't even tell management I
was the one to go to management and say
sorry
um I'm home now but I think they
partially some of them went to sleep so
I'm really sorry I know the deadline is
already over but is it okay if we do it
tomorrow first thing tomorrow
I was the one to go to management who
apologize and say sorry we have to delay
into one more day but oh the word I
promise I promise I promise
[Laughter]
yeah with these kind of bangs
um
yeah I I I I I I I think they they have
a hard time updating management about
the status
well so well I was home
I was still very like excited from the
meeting I just had you know that was
nice it was nice it's nice to get to
know like other people you know
make more friends
the more the merrier yeah
yeah
I hope we can meet again I mean
generally the chances are really low
because
um
uh I don't know I don't think our plans
are gonna line up like this again so
easily I don't really plan
I'm going to America
this year
I don't think so
uh
yeah and I don't I don't think they have
European members like living in Europe
girls
and we're going to Japan again well I
think I think Petra I can meet again
yeah like whoever lives lives in Japan I
can meet again but like in terms of like
members who don't live in Japan will be
difficult to time that because
yeah I don't know when they go to Japan
again and
I have one plan you know for my birthday
concert I want to be in Japan again
in June
maybe end of June
for maybe like two or three weeks
yeah
so if that lines up with someone that's
great
well I don't know
whatever there's a way you'll get
another chance
I mean Nina told me that she likes to
travel
and that she wants to travel to Europe
you're a rope you're what you're up
so that that seems like an opportunity a
possibility maybe she'll take someone
with her
oh yeah yeah she told me she has friends
in Austria yeah
that reminds me of it I talk with with
Kelly yesterday
as she told me
about a an Austrian friend she has
from
you know
an area that I very well know and I'm
like wait
what's their name and she tells me their
name and I'm like well what the [\h__\h] I
know that person why why did we never
talk about this
apparently her friend said a told Callie
that she knows me but that I would
probably not remember her
yeah but I remember her
clearly
I know I remember very very well
yeah you know not me someone else
yeah I was shocked
you know Austria is small most people
don't know anyone from Austria
personally so that shocked me like what
what small world
we live in a small world now
Three Degrees of Separation no that's
not what it's called
something about seven
I watched some videos on that though
some YouTubers trying to find Elon Musk
one YouTuber trying to find Elon Musk
through the Seven Something somethings
of something something
or is it six
maybe it's six
it's not free
apparently it was free in that case but
hmm
we live in a small Society
yeah we really live in a small Society
yeah
foreign
[Music]
a cloud of happiness
thanks for being so nice to me those
sweeties
hmm
no
whatever happened to the same but I was
going to visit you oh oh that was
supposed to be Martin
have you guys not realized until now
haven't we talked about it
yeah
it was supposed to be in Spring
I guess it got moved but we talked about
it again
but she wants to go
It's relatively serious about it I just
have to push her and and remind her
laughs
um
[Music]
still no passport yeah I think she has
she probably has still no password
never said her name yeah but I think in
the collab that we did her off collab I
think we mentioned it we talked about it
then
until then I kept it ambiguous yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
it raining coming to Europe I don't
think that's gonna happen anytime soon I
mean I don't know
I don't really think she's actively
planning it right now no
in fact
yeah
so far
the only one who's been who's visited me
is Cali and Nabi mama
Nami Mama isn't even a whole life member
[Music]
I wouldn't mind someone dropping by
I mean it doesn't even have to be
Austria we can go to another country if
you don't wanna I mean I understand
there's cooler places in Europe than
Austria
hope nabi's doing all right no I haven't
heard from her in a while either but
she's doing fine
hmm
Navi was already near you yeah yeah
you know I feel it feels so surreal
right now to be doing that again why am
I feeling like um having an outer body
experience or something like that
feels so weird right now
she's okay she's busy with school yeah
she did announce that she's coming back
as a streamer I'm like what the [\h__\h]
this is the thing with like
I think you guys know it you see it with
a lot of artists a lot of artists have
this thing where
they have these phases where they delete
absolutely everything on their Twitter
and
and as a fan
like
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] warn us before you do that
because like
huh why do so many artists have this
problem suddenly they're like I don't
like anything I've ever drawn and
anything I've ever tweeted in my whole
life so I'm gonna delete everything
push one button I don't even know how
you blast your whole Twitter like that
don't you have to go for every single
two is there one button that deletes
your whole all the tweets
is it is there something like that I
don't even know about that
but her
like telling us you know no they're
never gonna stream again yeah
that's even worse because sorry
for screaming but on the YouTube is even
worse
because they were like song covers that
people enjoyed listening to
yeah you hear that Nabi mama
I told her in person
or not in person
when it happened right after
I'm confused I don't know anymore but I
did tell her mama why don't you at least
keep up the song covers can delete the
streams I guess whatever
the song covers people like One you
uploaded relatively recently also didn't
you invest quite a bit of money probably
into like the creation of those songs
and then videos huh
why would you just delete that
my God
actually the one with Amy
and Ina
yeah she scared everyone too right
everybody thought she was hacked I told
her dad
that's so frustrating
when artists do that
it's not only Navi I'm talking generally
like there's so many artists to do that
um
and once you delete it it's gone like
twit tweets and stuff oh God all those
memories
hmm
I mean I want to back up now though
thank God anyway so she's going back to
streaming which I didn't think was gonna
happen because I remember you know when
when I was in uh Korea
I offered her
because I knew you guys would enjoy it I
offered her you know just don't want to
do it like a little stream together and
she really didn't want to do it because
she just didn't really
feel like you know streaming was a thing
that she wanted to do that she felt like
like mentally capable of in the moment
and I was like okay no problem
no problem
that's okay
and that continued for a long time
because in in Austria she didn't want to
do it either
well now she says she's gonna stream
again so I'm really happy about that I
hope she doesn't like forced herself or
push herself too much
she did say she's got a stream and
in in in Korean though so I will not
understand a thing
but I'm sure there's many people who are
happy about her coming back
he's so sweet
I miss her I miss her
what time is it almost 7 PM huh
Nabi Mama fighting yeah
[Music]
I guess that the fact that she's gonna
start streaming in Korean again
is good motivation for me to
um be real serious about learning
Korean actually I got like a call back
from you know I signed up for private
classes
and then they didn't reply for a long
time and then I got a call back a few
days ago and I couldn't answer
because they're [\h__\h] calling from
Austria and I'm not gonna pick that up
um I have to get back to them though
I have to set up that whole
thing
for my I have I have a private
one-on-one course and I told you about
it I want to do to focus on getting the
basics hammered into my head
then I think it will go better
anyone
[Music]
he's a bad guy oh
what
what we don't talk about my German sub
channel here
have you asked babe about learning
Koreans you could probably give you
advice no happened
it's okay
I've I've learned languages in my life
before and done pretty well at them I
just need to have consistency
I need to be consistent in learning
hmm
that's my problem
so I'll try my best at that
um
I I still
it's recently I keep on getting
duolingual notifications
keeps on reminding me I think I do still
have that like special premium
subscription
even though I don't use it for moms I
have that subscription going on for moms
how much is it per month how much money
am I wasting
ah
danger owl it's taking all my [\h__\h]
money
help
[Music]
ah 90 euro per year I will never paid
per year
oh yeah well that's all right
that's okay but if all the subscriptions
add up
from other services to
um
the Green Owl demands attention
I don't want to give you attention
you'll just want
my money you don't want my heart
I can't even
learn to grammar properly with you
you just want attention
you don't want my heart
first fix your
desktop app
so it works
like the phone one or was it the other
way around I don't know
okay I'm gonna read
super chats uh
[Music]
foreign
okay okay oh this one has a bit more
the holoca one
but this is the second one right the
the one after the
Showcase of the hollow Curie new update
um
about it this one
Prime Time curing
when you came down
ah you mean that
okay
it's okay okay no problem at all
that's long long ago
yeah I don't think about that anymore
okay here we go Patsy dance
it was hard Challenger anniversary or
hmm Skye thank you for the word super
chat this year I will be brave and ask
again thank you will you be my Valentine
stream High Challenger hmm
[Music]
I can't because Valentine's Day is over
too bad that I read your super chat so
late huh
too bad
who knows what I would have said on the
actual day Skye
I might have said yes
but I guess we'll never know
what you still get the kisses
I'm sorry Skye you should have
anticipated
which Super chats I would read on the
14th or if I would read them at all and
then
Super Chat ahead of time
find out my Super Chat reading cycle
rhythm
yeah well
you didn't
it's it's we're right between
Valentine's Day and white day
um
too bad too bad nothing special going on
today yeah
gotta ask two weeks early sometimes even
earlier
yeah you just have to predict the future
that's it
sorry Skye have a happy Valentine's Day
[Music]
Ultimo MK 203 thank you for two pinkies
which makes one red one
Happy Valentine's Day my one and only
Aussie you know I really learned my
lesson last year and have been working
out working hard on my flirting skills
I think he will be happy with the
results all right are you ready here
goes
are you C12
h22011
because you're really sweet
do you perform nuclear fusion
because you are super hot
are you made of uranium
argon copper and tellurium
you are cute
okay that one was good that one was good
are you a snow white real node
I don't know what the [\h__\h] that means
because you make my heart go Doki Doki
I'll take one of those the other ones
you can have bank I don't need the other
ones I'll take the cute one
well you could try I guess it makes you
seem very smart
you may have not made
my heart go Doki Doki that much but you
definitely improved your image here you
seem very smart to me
the cute one I like that one
even though I don't know like which ones
like if I just read like copper I don't
know which letters go for that one
why is it cu
if all the other ones are accurate
because tellurium t e
argon is AR uranium is you but copper Co
is cu is that y see why why
hmm
is there another CEO already taken oh
wait I guess there maybe there is
Latin maybe ah see always Cobalt a hat
that's why
[Music]
well well thank you Altima
I'll be delayed Valentine's Day
yay thank you
Happy Valentine's Day oh jerroduction
for the pinky Happy Valentine's Day
Kiara thanks for making my heart feel
fuller today I hope you spent the days
surrounded by love and affection
drowning in more chocolate gifts entity
than you could handle use this to buy
some some chocolate love gyro thank you
thank you I actually I brought some
emergency chocolate
from Austria with me and I am surprised
I haven't even eaten half of it and it's
getting
closer and closer to the end now
quite proud I must say
hmm
yeah I haven't snacked so much on my
sweets because I don't I'm not snacking
on anything like else either
well I just brought some Austrian
chocolate in case I have some craving
um
no but I haven't had much of a craving
wow
wow wow wow
[Music]
I'll go to retire what do you mean
maybe you're just going to sleep and
that was translated as retiring because
that happens sometimes but I hope you're
not actually retiring
welcome
[Music]
um
anyway thank you I don't need to drown
in chocolate because as I said I have
still enough and it's really not much
but it's enough yeah
and we did give each other some gifts
that was sweet
cute gifts
thank you thank you hope you had a good
Valentine's day too
thank you
happy heart challenge anniversary
[\h__\h] Valentine's Day it's heart
challenge adversary
I think it's pretty cool that your
dancing Phoenix Idol powers are stronger
than any laptop battery handheld game
console or cell phone on the market
today you tweet about dancing for eight
hours before yeah and that's even though
I am not like actively
like consistently
taking dance lessons or anything like
that anymore
I used to back in the day right but
since I
joined Polo it's just very like
spariously occasionally right
so I obviously don't have the stamina
but this is another occasion of where I
am just willing my stamina into
existence and I really like using this
this phrase recently because it's just
so true
I make the impossible possible
again and again and again and again
although I have to say
the Showcase
uh and the things I I you know some
things were live some things were
pre-recorded but in any case it was very
[\h__\h] exhausting
it was so
exhausting partially because
um
on a very long rehearsal day
I wore the wrong shoes
I chose a size too small and in the
beginning it didn't bother me too much I
was like I guess that's a bit tight but
it will give me grip so that's okay
but after dancing
a lot
more and more
it felt more and more painful
um
but when I asked if I could change shoes
they said ideally not because then maybe
we have some you know calibration issues
this and that
so you're already calibrated with this
blue
and then eventually I was really
suffering that much after holding back
I insisted on it and it was fine it was
fine no problem with calibration but
yeah I would have room shoes but it got
my feet into so much pain I didn't get
blisters no but it was so painful
those shoes
cursed beetles shoes
that reminds me
um
um you know for the upcoming like a
collab showcase
um we had a rehearsal too a while ago
and
I was the first one to change into my
um
outfit yes
we all changed
one after another which is an
interesting culture difference I wanted
to mention anyway
because so far I've noticed every time
I've been there with Japanese members
they just it's not even a big changing
world it's a pretty tiny changing room
but they all got in there together and
change at the same time you know
um and I always like waited
until they're all done but they all get
in together like they don't mind they
mingle in there
but myth so far
I wasn't the only one on that day it was
interesting because I was like
um I was the first one to say like ah uh
so I'm gonna change first or last if
that's okay or wherever because I kind
of I'm shy and everybody was also like
yeah yeah um me too I I would prefer to
change alone and all that
yeah they all it's such a big difference
myth versus all the Japan members
Japan members are like whatever they go
in there they throw off the clothes they
put the others on
they don't give a [\h__\h]
yeah yeah I think it's the whole Onsen
culture and all that
is
foreign
hmm
yeah I mean if I had the choice you know
I think they're also like that we would
prefer to change on our own
actually because
um those clothes are a bit difficult to
put on
I'm not gonna go into details
I would say it's difficult
it's difficult
um
um so anyway
yeah me and Callie yeah yeah I mean
Callie would probably not care I guess
but everybody else cares so we just
change
solo low low low low low solo
[Music]
well what was I saying oh yeah oh yeah
so I changed
um first on that day I think and so I
had there's like
um all kinds of shoes in different sizes
uh and you can like choose whatever is
your size they're not like
um
like assigned to a certain member
they're just they have the sizes and
then you just choose one of those that's
your size and I chose one that's like
supposedly my size
um
but yeah so I put them on
and so I I I I was the first to leave
the changing one more time okay next
question Google
and then I go to the staff and they like
do the rest of like preparation you know
this and that and then
while I'm doing that I hear a
conversation
from Ina with the other girls over there
in the changing room you know it's like
I wonder where the shoes I always use
are um
where are the shoes I should be using
not like they're assigned to her
but I guess you couldn't find the right
ones
yeah
so I'm like uh
hmm
[Music]
my shoes right now are
a little bit too big but I mean they're
like they're still a size that I could
dance in
or they might be a little bit big I may
have may have taken
may have taken the ones that Ina usually
uses as well I'm thinking to myself in
my head but the staff are busy with me
right now so I can't really like
immediately go there but I'm like hmm
should I should I give
should I go there and give her my shoes
eventually they were done with me and I
I go there and I'm like
I
know you're looking for
food she's like you're safe and I'm like
no what they're um there are several
shoes of each size and that was just you
know and then
I I wore the ones that were one size
smaller
and I was like oh well I guess this
actually does fit much better right now
hey well at least I I heard the
conversation and then even though the
ones that I was wearing at that moment I
could dance and I still you know I went
back to give them to her
because apparently there were no others
they should have at least two of each
size though
some some sizes they have more than two
because they're more common
first time here hello
I was technically touching feet with Ina
[Music]
um
sure
sure I was
hmm
another thing I did during the rehearsal
I barely remember it but I think I did
it
I kind of no I think that was during
dance practice I got really excited
um about us dancing together
and and I think I was maybe at the end
of a dance practice or so maybe maybe I
don't remember but
um I was just so so happy with how
everybody was doing
um that I was like you know to me this
feels like right now that we're an idol
group and you know
the idol group said I I know and
followed and so on
um they always had like you know before
before they go into a concert or so they
always do like an Iggy ikigomy like a
motivation call thingy between
themselves
so I know this is maybe cringe but would
you want to do this with me right now
so I gathered them in a circle
small circle and I put out my hand and I
said you just put your hands on top of
me one after another and you say your
name when you do that and before that
no after after everybody has their hands
on on top of each other
one of us as a representative person
says like
the like usually the leader of the idol
group would like say some like
motivational thing for the day
and then just you go like
for example Betty's global
would be like
Betty Zoo
someone the leader says and then
together they say
they scream it really loudly to get like
hyped
and motivated and get like you know
bonded you know
yeah so I was like let's do this okay so
I put my hand out first I'm like and
then next one goes I mean what's it and
they all did it okay and then I said
something like
two days
and then I don't know what I said
anymore but maybe
something like let's go myth something
like that
hey and then you know when you say the
myth you like push your hands together
down and then you go up with your arm
like whoosh in the air can you imagine
I hope I don't forget I want to do that
again
on on Sunday before the stream starts
gotta do it again
have to do it again yeah
that's so tasty hey
yeah I know I felt
I felt I felt Unified
yeah uh what I call yeah yeah
war cry huh
something like that
more cry
yeah okay great way to get a pump before
show exactly
yeah
there's another thing I observed
with um Japanese Idols I don't know if
they do this anywhere else
um
but
I saw Idols
um
slapping
really strongly like more like smacking
really strongly
uh
the other members back
upper back
they would ask for it like can you like
smack my back
when they're nervous
really strong I know I don't I don't
know
I saw a couple times before
but I know it looks really painful but
they some of them do it no not a massage
no no like at least smack
really strongly oh you're doing the
football
another path of encouragement no it's
more like a punch but with your palm of
your hand
apparently I don't really think it works
but it's for getting rid of the
nervousness or so I don't know
distracts the Mind from the nerves oh
why the back though because I feel like
other
mmm
[Music]
like
pinching
some
like meat on your upper arm or cell for
example
maybe that would be more effective I
don't know
not rare to see it but you don't usually
ask for it
oh
that's what my baseball coach did it
leaves a stick to awake yourself
MMA fight and sometimes get slapped in
the face again
if it doesn't leave a mark it doesn't
count
well yeah I'm not gonna do that one that
will not be myth culture but I want to
do the other one again
the motivational war cry
yeah because normally when we do
collapse we can't do that because we're
not there physically
but now we're there physically so we can
do it and I want to do it
yay okay back to Super chats
[Music]
that was a long tangent holy [\h__\h] Chase
workbook thank you for the red super
chat
for the red super chat Happy Valentine's
Day for my Aussie I'm not good with love
messages but I'll be playing heart
challenge or more than usual thank you
that's so sweet
yeah hi Challenger Perfect song for that
day you can hear you can listen to it
again ideally on white day it's coming
up next I would say it fits for white
day too
go for it go for it
yeah
Happy Valentine's Day to you too
cheating
I can't add the words of unrequited love
so I will hide them in a rhyme my
beautiful attractive potential please
have a happy valentine
did you make that up yourself
that's really sweet first I thought you
just translated my heart Challenger
lyrics to English
but no
it's so sweet I like it thank you happy
Valentine's Day to you too mwah even
though it's super late
stream love conqueror yay that's right
hey hope you had a nice Valentine's Day
or maybe a normal one because I feel
like
Valentine's Day
you shouldn't like feel bad about it
even if you don't have like a
relationship going on or something I
really don't give a [\h__\h] about it
don't give a [\h__\h] about it at all
the only thing I I care about is doing
like maybe a like it's a good
opportunity to do a themed stream
the stuff like this is always
interesting for streams because you can
make something out of it
that's more special than usual
generally I don't give a [\h__\h]
but also I mean if you are in a
relationship it's kind of cute because
then you can like give presents to each
other yeah why not nice
especially in Japanese culture
it's cute because the girls tend to make
chocolate themselves
on Valentine's Day
for the Crush
it's kind of cute like doing it Hand by
yourself by your own hand is more common
than buying it when some buy it too but
most I would say make it themselves
and even though it's really simple I
just feel like it's a nice gesture
hmm
yes yes
it's cute isn't it
gives you rifle Vibes
um
wow handmade yeah did you never see it
like in animes or so
right around
um Valentine's Day every single
supermarket
or similar shop that sells stuff like
chocolate or so
they will have huge section
for chocolate to melt and make chocolate
out of
with like little extras like forms
that's very German
[Music]
shapes and stuff decorations Etc and
plastic bags with cute ribbons and stuff
um
so true so true
it's painful to drink right now
ah
ah why let me see I think I may have one
straw
no no straw
I have no straw I'm normally not a straw
person
and I have no straw
I'll get a straw
later when I have to go to do the thing
my back hurts already again spent
I guess I didn't spend money because
Kelly paid for it but
had a really expensive massage yesterday
my back already hurts like [\h__\h] again
oh well
person what
eh
what what's up my whole little twins
what did I do like did that I I have no
I have no idea if they would do
something with that did they just like
do something with it
today
what
did they just do something
what did they do
Holo 27.
[\h__\h] I can't find it
where is that
hey tweeted
oh but they didn't like upload any audio
did they
oh yeah yeah okay well now it's like
really official I guess
I'm doing ghost rule with ume
they have assigned me
to do a ghost roll with mume
um
which is a really cool song
hmm
definitely a song that showcases vocals
uh so I hope you guys will like it
[Music]
um
difficult song
is that one that goes like
[Music]
foreign
that's such a good song I'm really happy
about the song choice
and I also really looked forward to
doing something with mumei
so look forward to seeing
I mean this is just a logical conclusion
so seeing me in Mumbai
performing on the hollow 27 stage
together
oh
did I sing it before
I feel like I didn't but you say I did
[Music]
oh I know it suits Mama's voice very
well
I know
amazing preview but there is no actual
preview right is there
oh there is no there isn't
well ah in two days
it looks like a preview is coming up
like a
short version of every song there's like
this this video
on the whole live Channel
with the premiere oh
the art is really edgy too
the kiwawa all right
it's very edgy yeah
there's no actual career at uh not yet
right
um
well a little bit longer you gotta wait
a little bit longer we're almost there
I mean it's just a cover
I was not chosen to do an original but
but I think the cover is really nice too
um
I'm honored to be included in the
project either way
[Music]
do this
preview of the preview well I mean
that's an already existing song So
Nothing Stops me from humming it a
little bit
yeah
it's not in the face okay let me go back
to Super chattels where was I
um
for the pinky this is the other half of
the Valentine's wish uses to buy
chocolates for the girls or something
thank you for always brightening our
days you and the girls mean so much to
me and happy two year anniversary to
Heart Challenger thank you
two years huh
this time I couldn't you know do
anything for her challenge or like I did
for hinotori I was wondering because
it's my second song if I should do
something if I should do make this a
thing
um
I know
I didn't maybe next year maybe we can
have something going on next year
for a high Challenger love conqueror
yeah
oh oh you know how honey Works has these
like
like answer songs I really like honey
Works songs and
um some of my favorite songs they have
like answer versions right and
and this could be cute for her
Challenger Maybe
it's like a continuation of the story
with a very similar instrumental and
theme and all that
sound very very similar
it's kind of like an answer to it hmm
yeah
sir 956
thank you for the pinky Happy
Valentine's Day Kiara Happy Valentine's
Day to YouTube
[Music]
cute little fox
so cute what does the fox say Happy
Valentine's Day Chihuahua that's exactly
what the fox said Thank you and to you
too
spunkenheim thank you for the recipe
chat I found the foolproof phone locator
my phone is always underneath 20 pounds
of proof yeah
does your cat always like lie on your
phone
I don't really do that
I would say that's your fault
you're placing it under your cat
no believe it
you're ruining your cat's reputation
phone can be warm yeah but it's so like
a small surface
I can like see them trying to lie on on
like
laptops and stuff mine did that
sometimes
mine does really
do that on your phone
really
mine don't do that at all
yeah mine also like to sit right in
front of the my my PC monitor for
example
um
that's a big warm surface too
but they have you know their favorite
spots um they're already decided but
yeah I guess I guess it's cute then
you'll always know where your phone is I
guess
there yeah there are like
phone locators that's fun you know like
a metal detector
your cat is a basically a metal detector
but only for phones
give your cat some kisses please please
please please please please please
please
you must
have mercy with me
let me drink water
soon thank you
thank you what a sweet sweet words
oh now I was able to
sip normally nice
Joey e thank you for the pinky hello
from broad gang I used to wake up early
every morning to watch your life but
since then my workout was flipped I'm so
happy for you that you're back in Japan
and practicing hard for forfeits keep
working hard and reach for the stars
oh wait at this point
where our showcase is not announced yet
right
it was so hard not to like say something
because
you know the only excuse we really had
for being busy and for being in Japan
for so much was the four Fest
um but more than that it was really the
Showcase
mostly the Showcase
so we couldn't say for such a long time
it felt so awkward
I really wanted to say because
especially I you know I stream so much
and then
I I lack the time and then I I I want
you guys to understand why because I'm
always open with you guys I'm always
honest with you guys I always want to
tell you I want to keep you up to date
about what's happening and when I can't
that just breaks my heart
hmm
it was obvious really
I I think I saw a lot of people being
like nah it can't be like 3DW they're
not doing that with Biff because
I don't know it's too late or like they
already like did this and that so
like a lot I saw quite a bunch of people
saying something like that they really
thought we were not gonna do it ever
hmm
which I found interesting that you would
think that when recently just recently
ID did their showcases
after ages of waiting
so of course we were gonna do ours too
surely surely
um this was also uh some opinions I've
seen that
okay cool but I'm not hyped at all like
I saw a lot of people being like Oh
let's see I don't care because I'm not
hyped because you've already been
showing your freely understand yeah okay
but would you prefer us to not do it at
all
cute
what
of course we're gonna do it once we get
the chance
and I understand that you know some of
the hype is dead I would have loved to
do it way earlier two years ago when I
was still in Japan
would have loved to do it then
um
but it wasn't possible but that doesn't
mean that we're like completely giving
up on it and I still think it's still
hype
it was hype wasn't it
it's nice to have a high quality big
showcase where you know we can do
whatever the hell we want with it but do
it in high quality
especially for me who I really want to
do like stuff with 3D but I just don't
have the access to it most of the time
so you know
yeah
and we we've been planning this for a
long time I remember
first putting out like
like an idea of what I want
um like a whole plan and what I want for
the background this and that like we had
meetings I remember doing this like oh
ages ago two years ago maybe one and a
half or so I don't know we did that ages
ago
preparing already because I guess we're
also
still hoping that the country would open
up faster that we could do it anytime
soon or that we would find other
Solutions like you know we were looking
into like home 3D options and this and
that with Ahmed
oh it was like a huge
huge pain hmm and then when it finally
came to the point they said all right
Girls It's Time
you get this one chance to revise your
old plans
um I stayed pretty much almost the same
like
overall I just had this image of a
classic
um Freddy reveal that I wanted to do
and my idea really didn't change much
um I don't think I had Subaru and that
she planned from the get-go
so that might have been something I
added when they asked me what I want to
change
I wish I could Super Chat sorry
um
oh yeah the hatching the Egg of course
that was also something that was in my
plan since the beginning two years ago
the Disco stage no
the Disco stage was also something I
planned back then interestingly
interestingly because I haven't even had
no I don't think I had no there's no way
I had fever Night Out by that point huh
nice coincidence oh
I just wanted to have my
um
stage because we could we can only have
one stage
for ourselves
uh that they would make for us
unless I mean I just found out about
this today so I'm just gonna correct
myself because no we don't want
misunderstandings but in the case like
gouda apparently it was okay to have two
because uh one of them was simple both
of them were apparently simple enough to
have two
um but I as far as I know I could only
have two at one so I I wanted it to be
somewhat versatile
so I wanted it to have a function where
it could be used as a performance stage
I don't think I'll use it again in the
future but if I if I do
um
I mean but it's almost a waste no use
this game but I most of the time I don't
really see these kind of stages not
stages like rooms being reused a lot
most of them are not that's like
reusable
most of them don't seem that reusable
stuff like that on an energy stage for
example is super reusable for anybody
by the way the place I performed Sparks
in was
Matsuri Senpai stage
that I have
not seen being used in a long long time
I think
yeah
but like for example for my birthday I I
I don't know if I would use it again
um
but as far as I know
uh for birthday concerts I think they
like from what I've seen in Japanese
birthday concerts
they arrange
the stage
uh once per year for these kind of
occasions they arrange it uh like the
general use stage they arrange it for
you
according to the theme that you want
yeah
so maybe that's what will happen with
the Eon stage because it didn't happen
this time it was not
arranged according to
us it was just like left the way it is
I used the dedicated em stage
the whole live English stage the new one
I used it
and
you know used it that Kelly used it
kelly didn't use it did she
hold it
good I also didn't use it
this is kfb you can have skits yeah but
like most of these things they're like
you make them for the Showcase and then
you don't really
use it again which seems really wasteful
especially when I don't have access to
3D I asked if they will let me use the
kfb background in home 3D because there
are some backgrounds right like the
Christmasy background and the beach
background and so on
and I was told no
maybe in the Far Far Future but
no
I guess it's like something like with
importing it is difficult
so I can't even like that would I would
use it as a stream background
and then I could like change it every
time because there's so many angles I
could use
um
I would totally love to use that stage
on my stream
maybe they'll change their mind who
knows
great loading screens all right those
were all my idea
I was messing around with those I like
them so much
[Music]
I mean maybe if they don't
maybe I can
if they send me the file and I get some
like 3D program maybe I can at least
even if I can't use it within our
program you know and move it around live
maybe I can just render some
like basically screenshots
you know what I mean
and use them as backgrounds
I won't be able to like move around in
them
but
just take some screens I guess
hmm
oh maybe oh it could probably be
converted to vrj yeah probably don't
know if that's allowed though
I don't know things always complicated
hmm
yeah
yeah yeah poke poke poke
ah you want to sleep that's okay I mean
I won't do much longer anyway so don't
feel bad about it good night
um so anyway thank you Joey e for the
pinky
and I will continue working hard thank
you from the board gang I hope you can
watch live again sometime soon bye for
now
hope work goes well
and thank you for supporting me even
though you can't watch live thank you
I want to tell you that I've been a
member here for a year as of a month ago
well it feels like you were a member for
a longer time
Mark the occasion I wanted to give you
something special my first rainbow
I actually wanted to do this last month
but uh couldn't at the time so I'm doing
it today thank you oh you were
interrupted many times
let me try to find the rest
I wanted to tell you how much fun I've
had with you the past year and I'm
looking forward to more from you your
Majestic Phoenix or I could even say a
lovely yeah you're such a cute and funny
person I always get a big smile when I
see you
to such a kind and thoughtful girl who I
love with all my heart challenges have
tried
to take me away but I stay loyal to
Kiana and KFC I feel Sparks of joy a
different YouTuber whatever what I know
you're trying to reference Sparks but
this is an Irish song Sparks of Joy I'm
always excited to see what you will play
wait there's more probably right is
there
um
did you finish your rainbow
the stream just ended there wait did you
did I end it before you could finish it
it was super happy thank you oh yeah
yeah Indiana just wanted to say I mean
understand that the hype definitely
wasn't as big as it could have been like
two years ago but it is what it is and I
felt super high but not proud of my
showcase and I'm I really liked it
um
and I think you know this is tradition
and it has to happen and I'm glad it
finally happened it's [\h__\h] Justice
um better than it not happening
so anyway
I don't see you anywhere in the chat are
you here
and I'll see you
yeah I think every fan base you know
it's like just should be happy I think
you are happy about it because you know
it was a long long journey until this
point along
journey to lead up to this
hmm
and I do think
if I did this showcase
in a timely manner
two years ago
it might have not been this good
it might have been received with more
hype
but obviously I've improved in two years
so it might have not been this good
hmm
even though I was sick
thank you I loved my showcase too
[Music]
oh
now
what's next is
in in order of like Senpai right
is next
id2 or Iris I think Irish right
who was first I did two Iris
Iris right
that was first
[Music]
but
sheesh
oh
[Music]
I guess
they did take like a year or so until
they debuted Iris right before like I
mean like after us
foreign
so the correct order
would be id2 Iris
counsel
ID free
oh I'm excited I want to see all of them
I want to see raining 3D and I want to
see Kobe
I want to see all of them yeah
oh are we pretty gonna be so energetic
[Music]
um
so hype
yeah Council Council also very curious
about Council
I can't imagine
a fauna thought I can imagine fauna's
showcase
and bales
Bales I can imagine will be in an
energetic and chaotic and and be alive
dancing and probably she's gonna she
would call a lot of Japanese senpais too
I can see her doing that
it's very predictable
fauna will be chill and ooh
and more
I can see what kind of background she
would go for but she's probably gonna
prove me wrong though
hmm
you know what it would be nice maybe
it's not really
a fauna thing but I feel like what
aesthetically would fit is a nice
Greenhouse
with a nice beautiful like Forest
that you can see through the greenhouse
and then there's like like a nice tea
table and chairs
for drinking tea and I don't know like
cute stuff and in the greenhouse maybe
some some more plants that she's like
growing
oh
yeah
oh well who knows what they go for
Anything is Possible
it's a lovely idea thank you
imagine if she goes full email I doubt
it I think if she makes the stage to
represent herself for a 3D showcase she
would want it to be something that just
clicks for everybody you know
the college card would be so cute
Lucy Hobbit has
oh yeah I want to live in a cozy Hobbit
house
anyway thank you super snake Mario for
the um rainbow
I don't know if that was really the the
end of it because it wasn't quite a full
rainbow but
you know sorry if it was me who
interrupted you thank you though for the
support
and all the references really smart but
there's one that's very sassy to me we
have an imposter reference amongus
um
[Music]
I hope you had a lovely Valentine's Day
thanks for supporting me with the
membership for a year
[Music]
who knows if that ever continued
this is why you number your rainbows
yeah yeah that would be smart
bran no wait no no no no Blackfish and
negot private location
for the pinky thank you so much for
streaming at this time I am
did you fall asleep while typing the
Super Chat
with your head just falling on top of
your keyboard
are you okay
I think currently my
Korean fans are
um
possibly happy because the times are
much better than usually
what I do think
they've become quite quiet in general
also I need to wake them up
maybe gotta do a Korean Duolingo stream
to remind them
I'm still here
I wanna see some of you
um
Ida
I forgot everything that I learned last
year but as I promised I'm gonna do
those lessons
and I'm freaking serious about it
yeah same time zone yeah yay
[Music]
um
I know what you like boy
[Music]
take it to the sky
Blue Boy
[Music]
stay in the middle
thank you
[Music]
I'll just say it back
foreign
[Music]
because that's the only part I ever am
able to sing
[Music]
you were five minutes behind behind oh
because you paused and normally I don't
have DVR on oopsie
[Music]
I've requested by the way I've requested
so many times
um to use certain
Korean like K-pop instrumental
channels YouTube channels who have like
a lot of self-made K-pop instrumentals
on there because we need permissions for
song for like instrumentals even if we
do
not archive streams so I've been
struggling I've been asking several
several times I've never hear anything
back I don't know what is going on
because the channels even all say in
their description you can use this for
free on your channel no problem but
that's not enough for us we have to
contact them directly and get like um
um
and that really happened like trying
this for like a year because I really
want to do a Kpop focused
uh karaoke stream yeah but like three
days ago I found like two more channels
so I
requested them again
maybe this time we'll get an answer I'm
going crazy
I want to sing new jeans on a
non-archived karaoke stream endlessly
and twice well I'm going to going to go
crazy I'm gonna go crazy
I need to let this out
[Music]
yeah maybe they don't answer because uh
maybe it goes into the spam folder
or because they think well why should we
answer if it's already in our Channel
description they must have not even read
our Channel description
because they mailed us asking for
permission when we have it so obviously
in our Channel description no no that's
not it please answer
well honestly sometimes I I'm not sure
if they are even being contacted but
that is never around
foreign
because I never get updates
I don't know maybe this time maybe this
time I will continue to hope
they don't believe the real takanasikara
is contacting them yeah because it's not
the real takanasi kiwawa is management
that's contacting
It Ain't Me Maybe it should be me
maybe you will get a reply
have you tried contacting on Twitter uh
so far look I have not really seen these
channels on Twitter
but yeah right I know JJ first yeah yeah
I mean I think I've had a situation like
that myself in the past where I was like
this person is asking me for something
and it didn't even bother to read my
freaking description so I'm not gonna
bother to answer them
yeah yeah right don't waste my time
but I would hope that they would make an
exception when they get an email from a
big company like that hmm
because it's not like they're being like
ignorance they're just trying to get
oh
an extra special written permission
I don't know there was something going
wrong there either our emails are going
into a spam folder to every person or
dare I say
the email hasn't been sent
I don't know
I don't have access to their emails
entered to say it but um I'm losing my
mind over it
look guys
[Music]
meant to CC me hmm
um
I don't want to be annoying like that
also that's not how they do stuff okay
please don't get bonked yes okay I'm
sorry I apologize for what I've said
I'm sorry for assuming that the email
hasn't been sent out in the first place
I'm very sorry I apologize I'm gonna
Doge's apology
that's what I I would love to see it
proof
I would love to see proof
yeah bye I'm sweating I'm reading
General after this
kidding I'm not sweating I'm
scared I'm scared mommy if you don't
hear from me
um
in a couple hours then
you know what happened
I'm scared
handstand together
you think so chicken nugget
I wonder
if people
who give explicit permission in their
Channel description if they just really
don't
care about answering or they just don't
check their emails I don't know if I
don't know
pathology and accusation had the really
different times
but what was it that I was apologizing
to Gemma the other day uh well one thing
was a swimsuit
wait was there another thing there might
have been another thing
when was it
when was that
General confession wait I forgot about
what was that
ah oh I mean she didn't block me because
I didn't like properly stream
until I was really fine
it's okay I can judge myself I'm I'm
an adult
[Music]
no no no I know they didn't abandon the
channel because they've been actively
posting
oh well
let me finish this one
um
Happy Valentine's and happy second
anniversary
oh wait no no no no no wait wait oopsie
to uh no there was a continuation of
ibane and Super Chat I just saw now
the cat interrupted Super Chat
the cat's name is come on
please say something to the damn cat
are you for real
I don't believe it because why would you
name your cat come on
are you here
you're blaming it on an imaginary cat
that poor poor imaginary cat
maybe the translation the Korean word
for come on maybe
where are you about it
are you not here why are you not at your
shift huh
[Music]
I need explanation
I'm gonna scold your imaginary cat
for ending your super 10 I don't think
she's that skilled
my cats have done interesting things
before but they have never really done
something like that
on a keyboard with a mouse
[Laughter]
okay if it turns out your cat was really
cold come on that will be so funny like
hey who names are cats come on
cat probably is thinking the whole time
I have a name
or I should have a name I should have a
proper name don't call me come on
yeah right I would think so I don't send
super chats often unless Thomas Super
Chat was ages ago but I think there's
more than just like enter
you have to do more than that probably
right right
about it I've seen through you
so clearly
like you're transparent
um
like a window
it doesn't sound so bad in Korean
what is it
what was it
I probably heard it before wasn't it
something like I heard it before
[Music]
foreign
right
I put it before
did I say it right
actually that does sound kind of kind of
like a name
not itoha no no
where where am I
where are my Korean Bros answering me
eat it
it's come here right
um
sorry 20 second delay today
I remember
I remember because in that kids show
Superman blah blah blah
that I used to always watch the dads
would always say to the children
uh
wait
The Return of Superman
ah
it was a really cute girl that I really
liked her name was
[Music]
so cute
cute cute
[Music]
she was so cute I love Sarah she's so oh
my God there's like a recent is that a
recent picture of her
oh she's grown some they grow so fast
yeah I guess her name is love that's
cute
[Music]
I think she was half Japanese half
Korean
some family there was half Japanese half
Superman yes
[Music]
wow she's like a teenager now almost
oh my God she was so cute as a child
guys you need to look up Sarang and
Superman I think that it will come up
yeah if you look that up you will see
what I'm talking about
you
she
is making my brain react
or my uterus
probably my uterus
she's so cute yeah
oh yeah the dad was Japanese and the mom
was Korean I guess
what
it's natural
my instincts
what why are you guys being so shocked
what I'm having a
mother instinct reaction
huh
why are you guys so shocked it's a
natural thing
huh
hey you guys that shocked as if I said
like something like I
I eat babies
[Music]
that was the other way around dad Korean
Mama's job that's what I thought but
somebody who said something different in
the chat confused me
yeah
charging yeah
my motherly instincts yeah
why don't you get it
you missed the context well maybe you
should have been listening
um
okay let me carry on
all I eat is baby carrots if anything
anyway
you make me feel so weird when
how can I help
it's a cute cute really cute baby
I know
oh yeah the one that's half uh half
German half Korean I love that one
down down she's oh
it was so funny because sometimes she
would speak German and I just felt like
I know I felt like
I was describe this
I felt represented
because the mom like normally it's only
the dads was really rarely they would
show the mom a little bit and they would
show her speak German to her child
and I'm like I understand
noun Superman
oh
my God
literally the cutest child to ever exist
so cute
okay calm down
[Music]
should you strike your heart yes
did you see my eye my ears twitching
when I do that
they go crazy
motherly instinct
Kobo cute too yeah that's I guess that's
how I feel about Kobe
do not let her cook excuse me
I'm in a kitchen what else am I supposed
to do
although at the beginning of the stream
I said this is exactly what we're not
doing today
giving you mixed
mixtures
signals am I not
[Music]
okay okay okay
uh
okay after doubting ibane we can now
continue
I know thank you for the rate to pretend
Happy Valentine's Day and the happy
second anniversary
I want you to know that you're really
amazing and I love you so much you're
the best my Oshi even after two years
I'm still streaming heart Challenger
almost every day I'll never stop
streaming it
hey I'm glad people are appreciating our
challenge yeah
and remembering it on this day you know
I think some people say and I kind of
agree that releasing a song for like a
special occasion
really really make it relevant only for
a short time really just one day or two
but then people will go back
on it the year later
and remember it on that day
I don't think you can lose some heart
Challenger any any time anyway
I don't think the lyrics even say
anything about no no they do no it's all
about Valentine's Day [\h__\h] it what am I
saying but I don't think I don't think
they say specifically
Valentine do they say
it's about making chocolate and all that
it's obviously implying Valentine's Day
but did they actually ever say
Valentine's Day
mmm
I'm onshore now
[Music]
no the lyrics are all
Valentine's in there
it worked for Mariah Carey exactly
exactly
hmm
that argument really only works if you
have hyper focused on the lyrics
and that really bothers you that much I
don't think it would bother me that much
[Music]
oh
hello Rock Mal sarala
maybe I should release next time we're
getting close to the heart Challenger I
should release a video like Mariah Carey
but you know I've already done this
before but this one with Valentine's Day
and I'll be like
and then a heart Challenger intro starts
playing
it may feel out of place but it's still
worth listening to it because it's
[\h__\h] cute
it's a fun cool Apple
anyway thank you unknown I'm glad you're
enjoying it so much
see you you're one of the people who
don't hyper focus on the lyrics and you
listen to it every day thank you thank
you thank you
motion Super Snake Mario again Brandon
for the pinky great job on the stage
love stream and Happy Valentine's to you
oh yeah the whole cure yeah I think I
was doing well right I was doing pretty
well thank you happy Valentine's Day to
you too thank you
[Music]
really where's my certificate huh
I have not received it yet
doesn't seem real yet
oh that's okay luluca I'm actually
planning on ending it now to
after this after like five more Super
chats
thank you for coming
um Caillou is supposed to send it to me
[Music]
I'm gonna continue to wait for it then
I'll check my post box every day okay
I'm waiting for a cup episode
for the pinky good job Happy Valentines
thank you to you too thanks for watching
Sky donkey soon Moon doc thanks for the
pinky too good job on defeating airtime
you've definitely have been doing good
at home look here happy Valentine's day
as well
why thank you
I appreciate it yeah I haven't been
playing recently but
hmm every now and then when they release
something new I'll get back into it yeah
it's a fun game thank you Moondog for
watching
I appreciate it Happy Valentine's Day to
you too I'm a chick dancing
and that's it for those super chats
[Music]
so hmm
the ones there's like three more after
that before the Showcase and they all
don't have that many super chats so I
think
it's okay but I want to take a little
break before I do the thing that I have
to do and I actually also have to take a
small short video really quickly for
anime what was it Boston
yeah
so I'll do that
and in the end you didn't get that many
tangents huh well if you want more you
must come tomorrow I'll stream fire and
blend tomorrow after
I miss showcase
I know
attorneys
[Music]
quality of a quantity
um
indeed
[Music]
I've been playing this after a long time
looking forward to it
yum
enjoy dinner thank you I don't know what
to eat but thank you
I hope my jaw fixes what's up
someone is knocking on my door
why
foreign
[Music]
Nina brought me cake
strawberry cake
with many
strawberries and they look good
she didn't come in though
she knows I'm streaming apparently
oh they smell good
very short okay
but normally they don't have that many
strawberries on top so this is a good
one
cake
[Music]
nice dinner nice dinner
what I want for dinner
how does she know
yeah
thank you
I miss Cena it's like I haven't seen her
for 50 years
same for Army
and goopy Depot
um
let's eat now
okay
so um
thanks for spending time with me
and I'll see you tomorrow for five blend
and in German we say
laughs
I timed it with you guys
I waited for you
[Music]
okay okay
starting wouldn't happen but no that's
not German
bye bye see you tomorrow yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]