[Music]
yeah
y
Yi yeah
having
hallucinations
yes no I okay Kiara was like who's
making that sound and Kiara was like
Moon walking in place then are moon
walking in place it's you guys it's you
I was standing still she was standing
still I was also standing still my my my
stream be on my side I believe it but
the stream is never on your side you're
alone you're
[Laughter]
alone you you you be on my side
right who me no
Dam hell what's going on here what's
going
on stop it and introduce
yourself this game has toggle Crouch I
thought it was old this whole
time p
p yeah introduce
yourself
okay oh can't see face
everybody yeah it's a little
intimidating right it's kind of
creepy hello yeah
yeah no you're
Wu I'm W oh of the worldwide what was it
what were we worldwide wife web we are
the worldwide wife
web I'm I'm Wu of the worldwide
Wide Web thank you it's not that hard to
say why are you having so many trouble
saying
that I just woke up
okay oh oh yeah can you give them like
uh the story of your your your current
issues that maybe issues arise because
of your current location oh yes I might
stop pointing at me I feel wait who's
who's making that noise
what wait who's making that noise nobody
no noise there's no noise there's no
sound
[Laughter]
my chat hears
it okay curently s I'm currently in a
hotel in Japan so I might poof out of
existence maybe a sound from the hotel
room oh
[Music]
kind wooo
spooky um all right anyway all right
heard enough of that wife yeah next next
one
who oh this live the we we I'm
Wu what no she's Moon
walking he's not I'm
Wu from the worldwide
[Laughter]
wi I thought we were all Wu no only
she's Wu oh then I'm
po hi I'm wewa from the world
wide
okay I'm WEA from the worldwide wife
[Music]
webing I'm I'm
so I'm so happy we're finally collabing
cuz we even met IRL before but we so
happy
finally didn't you wait when we met IRL
didn't you like pay for like my whole
dinner no yes you did yes you did stop
pointing don't dance at
me no
[Music]
no that was so that was pretty cool and
handsome of you oh then yes I did
nice thank you so much maybe this time
maybe today I can thank you for all of
that maybe I can I'm looking forward to
it wow what do you what do you know
about this wife
there she got some great assets oh yeah
oh
yeah I'm embarrassed stop what's
happening
there I
mean I Gotan art of myself drawn in A's
outfit it looks pretty sexy I saw it it
looks so good yeah I saw
it I love the POR one more saw I saw it
yeah okay
Lisa Go on the stage the wife stage
yeah hi Darlings I'm Lisa of the
worldwide Wu web
[Music]
yay Beau life this is this is my wife
because I'm literally going on a
honeymoon with her that's so
[Music]
funing Ki for
myself I don't really know if that's
really applicable because I invited you
I don't know how you're stealing me you
don't need tell them that Kata damn
I'll have her on
Tuesdays every other
Tuesday yeah yeah we just switch
off yeah okay okay I guess oh my gosh
she's
moonwalking nobody's Moon
[Music]
walking Me Maybe maybe we don't know
about our moon
not
I know what you're talking about do it
do it again do it
again
[Music]
yeah that's
not
[Laughter]
walking I me guess wait that's so smooth
oh my God she's actually so smooth with
it she's she's a smooth
criminal can get so excited over the
most scuffed and simple features of a
game wow so easy
TOA hello I am The Mastermind behind the
worldwide wife web I am the wife of
everybody if they make me a wife I will
be everybody's wife let me wife you uh
today I came here to go to the wife
convention this is the wife convention
right yeah yeah yeah of course we just
need to pick up a few things first oh
okay then your wife let's go my
wife my
[Music]
wife you guys have a lethal company
wife uh no you you girls maybe yeah I
think I like the I would pick the
Bracken oh the Bracken like The
Nutcracker I don't think I played since
the Nutcracker existed oh is it a
Monster yeah yeah yeah oh okay okay I
don't know them yet well shall we set up
and start our first mission then we
should wait we have to explain to how to
play okay okay we pick
up yeah okay have you ever played
phasmophobia yes and I do not like it oh
well it's like the exact same thing
except different yeah yeah point at me
point at me okay so basically kiaha
we're going to be going to moons okay
and on these moons it is our
responsibility to go into these uh long
abandoned buildings and collect
materials that at the end of 3 days we
are going to be selling um There Are
Rules so you're going to actually want
to come over here since it's your first
time and go ahead and read this manual
uh that's on this table there's a manual
no way it's so hard to read though
yeah dominated by a few species is
dominated by a few
species
she that's what I thought the first time
I saw that too I was
like okay can I manual I thought I
thought I'm reading the
manual is
sorry it's kind
of so we could also just explain as we
go but basically we're just looking for
things to pick up bring back to the ship
if all of us wipe we lose all of our
items um so if everyone's dead it's best
to just
leave there will be monsters chasing us
to place on the counter and buck d d
ding ding the Bell until the company
answers the door and what what what is
this about what when selling crap to the
company yeah so Day Day Zero technically
or the last day we go to the company to
sell all the stuff that we found um and
we have to place it on a desk and then
ring a bell for them to come get it how
do I oh there oh oh
uh I can't I can't read and dance I
can't you what did you do did you do
something can you oh did you just answer
the question was it so dark oh there we
go yeah I answered question but I also
don't know how to use the terminal I
don't think we have to use teral for the
first one I think we
just the
G in order to R risk of damage that
autopilot pilot ship will not stay on
the moon surface mid please don't worry
you'll get it
keep get keep a crew at home can I stay
at home no no no
no no you can't just type the code how
do I know the broadcast code whatever
you'll tell me right you'll tell me all
of this um yeah of
course yeah yeah oh that's a lot okay
let's go let's go okay
the how do I punch someone you can't
well you can if you get if you pick up
like there's like stop signs inside if
you pick it up you can hit people yeah
yeah you can hit people or you can hit
monsters team kill yeah so when a
monster attacks me I I should try to
attack them back um well some of them
you can and some of them you can't
Walker okay walk some of them if you if
they see you it's
over that's a crab B I feel like oh
we're moving we started let's
go let's
go k just like Valerie guys just run
yeah I will run I will run wait did it
start you better run no one started I
thought the game started Why didn't it
start I thought so too I'm going to
press Start okay it sound it sounded
like it yeah I'm going to
start oh here we
go
down okay please hold my hand
all we have to do is go into the
building and pick up
EOS okay threatens other life forms okay
okay I see good morning this
way uh I don't know they've left me the
moon are we on the yeah we're on the
moon there's no we didn't leave you come
here did you buy I ordered one
flashlight
okay can I run we don't need a
flashlight it's
fine but I have nothing you girls have
it no this way now we don't have
anything yet we got to make some money
honey oh my God it's Christmas theme w
w
what I haven't played since before
Christmas so I'm like where we where is
it okay um I should be where the [\h__\h] is
she
going
ice ice
cream following you I'm trying to find
the
building this oh my
God where's the
building why we already separating where
are the others it's okay they'll find us
eventually hopefully what where the [\h__\h]
did they go new
creat
not that creep don't okay don't go in
the water or you will
die okay here's the
bridge new creature what creature am I
seeing there's like one in there's like
little birds that fly but they're not
harmful oh okay down oh don't go in the
water no there's no water there's a fire
exit yeah we're upstairs I think the ex
where's the entrance oh it's right
beside me so we go in from here
here the way she run hey that's the way
you run
too so you just hold e and go
inside
[Music]
y hi
hi this just me who finds the Acoustics
so so
upsetting find the
what the acoustics are so
upsetting hey it's just one here one
little Dev who made this game all
alone yeah the
toilet it's so awesome it's like 2010
Xbox
mic yeah nothing here love the Xbox
nothing here okay there's
nothing so far everything's still normal
but I'm like I'm getting nervous when is
the r happening don't
I'm Fring oh my God I'm Fring
Fring holy
sh
oh my
wife are you
okay stay with me come here is he gone
come
upstairs okay okay okay let's go
out [\h__\h]
man my wife he heard me because there's
a
bragon pomu oh pomu is bringing stuff
back to the ship oh my God what a
queen she just dropped something off um
down here and go in the fire exit we can
try to scale the mountain
okay it's so weird I don't understand
anything there's like a monster in this
game that I think if you look at it for
too long then it can like start chasing
you and then it kills you oh yeah he
gets mad and then I looked at him and
then he was not happy oh
okay
who oh oh I like the I like the audio in
here it's better the bracket's over
there the bracket
yeah where no way I saw something move
for a second
too the hall you can go see him if you
want okay yeah go go ahead K the Bracken
is my choice of waifu for in-game
characters I don't see I'm too
scared I don't see it oh do I have to
scan
no you'll you'll know when you see
it
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] that's not the
bra that's not the
braet I don't know what that was I don't
know it was a really big guy
yeah guy where's Pom she's at the ship I
think or that's her
[Music]
hi why are you
laughing
where you guys going um well there's a
thumper I think and a
braen oh right inside well when we were
going through the main entrance the
Bracken was there and then we went
through the fire exit just now and then
there was a
thumer and the braen yeah you wouldn't
believe watch check this [\h__\h]
out check it
out holy [\h__\h] he just the right paast
oh oh he was just it's just chilling I
saw him come here
[\h__\h] you wouldn't
bumper we're going to lose day
one are you stuck no I got a find glass
do something are you going to burn him
with the
sun leave the
way I stay I think he's he's
[Music]
not jop good jop wait did we all live um
I think he found us oh we're all good
well I think we should go back yeah it's
5:00
pm.
um you're joking
[Music]
me hey is he chasing me
why me I'm just a girl oh
bye there's
no he can see you well he can see three
other beautiful women
too but no he chose me he's mad that I
said that I like the
Bracken he want the force whatever
wanted to be my
no
way
Marissa where where did she go uhoh
oh oh she's crazy what's happening oh is
he like following
them
uhoh what is that the
Bracken n is
dead I think she got
bored there's no spec of her on the
screen green not even not even a green I
mean blue sphere nor her vision to even
give a
slight a slight reminder that she
existed be funny if we left now no the
autopilot will go at midnight
so I should give them as much time as
they can to get back here yeah I'll
close the door
I'll close the door until they come
back are they lost no I don't think so
because pomu came here and dropped a
bunch of stuff off
[Laughter]
one
oh I forgot that it auto
opened they got this it's
fine
uhoh oh
yeah
yeah see my
God
see it's not like a dog is going to show
up and eat me alive or
anything a ship we leave at Mid hi hi hi
I made it is that a dog I made it wait
sh is there a
dog no dog dog I'm I'm a kill yes
there's a dog yes there's a dog I'm
starting I'm I'm I'm starting I'm
starting I'm
starting was there actually a
dog I think so I saw something running
oh it was a word there was a word oh I
couldn't tell if that sound was a dog
the she's like I baed she's I'm like
uhoh no my wife is dead who will go to
the m with me most paranoid the yeah I
mean yeah the most still going to the
males with you do
mean a it's okay back live it's worth 57
no one no one got anything else we
couldn't cuz the Bracken tried to kill
me the second we walked in is this the
only thing we've got got to do is yeah I
grabb that I haven't played this game
since we last played
it oh yeah it's been a while thank you
for 20
memberships thank you for 20 memberships
thank
[Laughter]
you nice W nice so was that that was
Prett bad wasn't it we didn't really I
that was a pretty bad situation that was
a pretty bad we did pretty good I mean
yeah we did good you got one thing we
just got
unlucky is our zero out of 130
nice yeah yeah yeah
yeah pretty good oh oh let's go let's
Go's
go who whoa who it's the same map three
times in a row so you won't get lost if
you remember it okay yeah yeah there's
aive Don't Go Near The be run
run oh there's two we hives
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh-oh it's but you got tricky about it
and
basically close they're both close
though I think we'll be good yeah we
could try to get them at the end and
then just have everyone else on the ship
so let's go there's the
entrance oh it's not the same map every
time yeah I thought it was we're on
March cute no it's December uh no the
Moon is called March honey
[Music]
wow um why are the lights
off sometimes they are um what was that
sound is there one
way is there a oh Kiara I forgot to tell
you so when you right click you scan and
that's how you can find items and stuff
okay nothing down always
okay okay ABS always be scanning always
be scanning okay like this okay okay
there's nothing
[Music]
here oh it's a
key oh your key look like a
gun oh careful for turrets I thought I
heard something oh there a turret
I think I heard a chunky
wony chunky wonky has come to
assassinate my sock B
but you thank you why am I alone and why
is it dark don't leave me alone who's
squash
squeaking oh
[Laughter]
nice thank you D oh my God you scared me
so
bad there really nothing down there I
scared you yeah I turned around and
you're standing on the stairs I'm just
there I but it's so dark get scared of
me okay there's nothing downstairs
anymore
[Music]
okay I think we got to find oh I can't
see where the jump is should I just
should I do it no no no no no no it's
you can walk around
literally you don't have to moon walk
your way over right we why we gone again
she did again no I think she was she had
something I think we got to go to the
other entrance yeah I think we got to
find
it
yeah was let's go do a flip I would
have I would have Chad I really would
have this
way
oh where did she
go what I don't know moment though oh
you don't think she you don't think she
died to the bees right there's no way
that she died again where is the other
entrance out of the
coll I'll take these I'll take these to
the
ship I I'll go back with
you you
okay yeah the graphics scared me they're
so
bad the be be the be no those are little
flies the bees are like in a circle
they're like if you scan it'll come up
with their little name it's like the
something Hive I don't remember Don't Go
Near
them
um red red
redit what are we
doing I'm I'm kind of dead but I think I
got scra Nur is fine but I don't know
where she is she's
walking where are you guys I'm in the
ship
oh oh wait that was my
stamina that was just my
stamina
this welcome back you guys heading back
yeah because they'll follow they'll
follow us into the ship that's why okay
do you want me to we have to do it at
the end though
oh I was looking for an an entrance in
fire exit trying to find the ecy find
one don't be such a loner stay with us
I'm
sorry so
[Laughter]
cute where I don't know where wait isn't
this the way we just came from orle a
door oh there's over here
is this where we came in
before any chick who want to be eaten by
me oh it's here it's here oh there's
bees
oh me
baby want window oh we can just go
inside but very
slowly
slowly what if we just go very fast
let's
go let's go hi
yay oh where are you guys I we went in
through the
emergency oh where is it it's on the
floor it's like a
little my game just lagged is there a
mob it's a little what sorry the second
I was saying something my game lagged
and I'm like uh is that a mob spawning
in it's like a little down a hill I
don't know what else to call
it okay I I'll go look for
it but
how just iy full stamina how good are
you run and then drop it do a loop
around watch out for Doos oh yeah you're
right it's getting really
late two out of
two she
crazy
what she did it solo
okay that's the first
[Music]
one why don't they come to rescue
me
think
I I might swim again nobody is
it did you say
that
wait
how I feel so
bad
the okay let's
see what if Buu goes
on oh are you okay
no no
oh hi
we sorry you left
me this mom showed up behind me it's not
my
neck I even found a teapot I know I was
watching you I felt so bad
[Music]
oh entr y y I saw a cockroach and then I
think what killed me was a was a
different mob though was it really dark
we need to go home now I'm not
somewhat hanging out and chilling
here she scared she's not moving so I'm
inclined to think that she is dead a
Bracken okay with a Bracken oh yeah
that's what got me
too I'm
here
oh Bo get in
here I think I saw a dog oh yeah quiet
that wasn't like a doll dog though um I
think the other two are dead I think
it's just us no way can you see that in
there yeah
so assumtion is correct um I a little
creature by yeah yeah um well those I
think are the beads so what I'm going to
do is I need you when I say so to hit
the start I'm going to grab the bees
okay and then I'm going to bring them
back in
Nissa you're so brave she's so brave you
ready yep the I'm ready ma'am
y be get
theive get the should I hit the
button died so fast
Isa oh
oh not the
Discord H the
button oh was that the right order the
Beehive yeah yeah yeah yeah okay The
Beehive I'm
running I think I did
it hell
yeah where'd she
go the LA if we what lazy is I I'm sorry
I got my neck
snap hey got some stuff this time stop I
the is in love with me or
something mine is 60% oh [\h__\h] where's
our beehive
gone where's the Beehive I I brought it
in I brought it in oh they knew that we
did it for Discord so they don't count
it oh my
god oh we were recorded or the the the
game developers are watching the stream
right now and they're like all these
[\h__\h] everybody died for no reason of
stuff
scar scared
me you cheating aloud no you know you
know one good thing about living alone I
just realized is that nobody can like
turn off the lights in the room I'm in
randomly by accident does anyone ever no
that's so annoying do people do that to
you that's so mean do people do that
when I when I used to live in my family
I mean it just happens doesn't it like
when you're in the toilet ID don't
meeting and then
what what no I mean not on purpose just
by
accident this is a k only exclusive
experience maybe maybe Americans have
the light switches on the other side of
the room yeah the light switches on the
inside yeah yeah usually on the inside
on the inside your bathroom light switch
is on the inside in the bathroom yeah
yeah oh wait is this a cultural thing
yeah probably maybe I think so oh
interesting I have some light switches
uh uh for example my guest room has a
light switch on the inside but my
bathroom has a light switch on the
outside wow I see him
why now I know what to do when you're on
the toilet and I see you no wait now Rea
knows now rea's going to turn the light
off you're right no you're right the
opportunity you will not
there did you die to the bra mon there a
monster or an animal he kissed me what
is that he kissed you I'm not sure I'm
scal
zooming where oh the bird a bird that's
a huge [\h__\h] bird why is it on the
ground he's walking around yeah it's
just a
bird what that's not how birds
move why are they on the ground
Zoom where is the entr oh I see a
beehive but I don't think we'll be able
to get this one I'm going to get it oh
my
God you are you're going to get it okay
oh what the [\h__\h] I need to make up for
my failure run leave me
do it at the very
end I need to get it
closer failed construction it is okay
why don't they fly anymore why are they
only what the
[\h__\h] where is the entrance
they oh over there I found the
entrance
oh oh my God oh my God who are you you
scared me so why you scared me scared
I'm just a
girl a girl I'm just a
girl let's
follow Jesus this wire is scared the
[\h__\h] out me toy
Cube plastic
fish I need anything else
nope why does it say
total
[Music]
oh thank
God okay I'll get
it yeah oh my God I haven't played this
game in a while I'm so
[Music]
scared the game is lagging know what
that
means mob Spa oh [\h__\h] I have a
key actually don't know what that
means that's just what I assume it
means why is pomu
yelling
what the [\h__\h] rubber ducky
you're you make that time so much oh my
God what's up here
anything damn I can never find
anything this game is so
scary
okay okay I got everything out of here
pH no need to ever go back over here
right guys right there's something else
right yeah
yay nothing at
all
[Music]
pH this [\h__\h] is going to
break
I'm going to
die might as well go back
once drop things off so we make
quota and then go back in sound of the
duck in a track
monsters wish I could make it quack
more I'm on the wrong
side wish I could make a quack on
command damn the laser pointer is so
expensive the fairy
crashed what the fairy
doing
is she
[Laughter]
dead
I think I
disconnected because I lost internet um
you can keep playing until I'll I'll
join at when next game okay okay we were
ki's going to die
so
should I just start the
ship is it a coil
head
I think there's a
dog
it's not a coil head if she's looking
away and it's not
moving
oh let's
go
uh
oh there's something at
the
oh I think she
fell was that a scream or was that a
mob
wait
yay y yay this someone want to reinvite
pomu yeah yeah can you can you reinvite
in this game chat or does it have to
remake REM so when you when you hit um I
think we might need to drop off the
items real quick have days left to meet
theit I think I have to remake the lobby
because you can't inv
people that's okay yeah but I I think
what I'm saying is I think we can drop
off the items get the money and then try
to read okay oh okay let's try that real
quick I don't know how to go to the comp
someone please reinvite me whenever you
have the chance thank
you we're selling stuff and then we're
going to save the file and then we're
going to reinvite
you thank you I miss
you I think to go to the company we just
press here right no use the terminal to
rout to the
company okay on our
way y I have no idea how to play this
game aren't you proud of me that I
actually did kind of escape the Bracken
first yeah so good I was watching you
thank you Somebody's Watching Me helping
me hey I can't help you I don't we don't
have a teleporter yet you should have
come back you should have come back oh
you were dead okay right no I was alive
R what she what she doing with it just
drop everything off here oh okay can we
be killed during this process no no of
course not of course not she sayle so
confidently okay I don't believe her
after we drop all these items off uh can
you come hit the Bell until the guy
shows up we don't have to sell
everything right the Bell oh
yeah just hit the B show up so you can
just sit
there oh we got
it
yay oh
okay I feel like I heard some noises
from Monsters out there so we work for
Monsters okay so now let's start the
ship and see if we can reinvite pomu
otherwise we'll remake the lobby okay
okay oh wait ringing the bell would
would that do something like
no I would never I would never
K be careful or I'll turn off the light
when you're pooping yeah mhm not when
you're pooping
[Laughter]
bye yes yes that's exactly when I'll do
it have reached yeah really what no way
yeah we had like 250
no okay here I can reinvite
now will you no okay uh would you mind
making a new room at we okay I'll do I
just quit I think wait
confirm
post
confirm it's the same save right oh it
is it is
right
F I can't
read God I just have so many friends on
my friends list
like oh everybody here I go again
P she's
[Music]
alive yo we were together and suddenly
you were gone and I was like what the
[\h__\h] yeah um my internet decided to just
I know it poia yeah but now you're
back yeah can can you tell it to not do
that again please yeah I think it maybe
got really flustered it was like so
nervous around you like I mean just by
ourselves so oh you're if your
connection is so unstable then I think
I'll I'd rather stay with one of the
other girls the
next holy [\h__\h] I can't rely on you I
can't rely on
holy [\h__\h] God damn call an ambulance but
not for me for me
people we we damn I just got thrown away
so she looks so serious on the compter I
love you
pomu I can't
he what you say you doing what is WEA
doing on the
terminal wait what did you say
my my headphones came
[Laughter]
out only stream will
know it's over for me guys what are you
doing me
S how do we start the game Oh I thought
you you knew you what you were doing you
looked like you knew I picked the moon
and I ordered some stuff but the now
just eat on this like the thing on the
here if you hold e then it'll be
like wait no it's not giving the prompt
though yeah I didn't get the prompt for
start game oh it's because I'm the host
du yeah you have to be
the
sorry
Y is this new map I almost jumped yeah
yeah it's a new map
pumpkins yum yum I like the pumpkins how
there
I stay with you Lisa don't die okay I
heard a flashlight so I'm going to watch
for
themer I why is it why is it echoing
we're not in a
room we will what did you
[Laughter]
say it's okay you can tell me they're
gone
now
I was this is really
funny yeah it was so
funny is this the right
way it was
hilarious oh God where is the
entrance I think it's down
here where's oh over
here
oh I see it yeah main entrance yeah
yeah wait how do we get up
there oh this is how we get up there
yeah the
ladder well all right here we go here we
go oh God it's dark it is dark I hate
when it's dark in this game I got a big
thing
is that a mob or is that
P
okay is this a fuse
box
[Music]
yeah did it
work oh a big
thing
I found a big thing
[Music]
too
yeah I think I hear something uh-oh I
found a big
thing oh okay I'll stay with you
hi hi wait do you have another big item
mhm K wait for me oh wow wants to by
myself are you going to try this you
yeah it's me
there scrap gotcha in this game
where where are you I'm on the other
side oh there's a turret oh maybe I'm
near
you
gun sticking out your turret I'm closing
that
door um there's a turret in that
room sorry yeah yeah I let's go the
other way is it down here no no no yeah
it's right there yeah down there okay
yeah other way it is did you go down
yet uh no I haven't gone
downstairs oh it's a bug it's a bug but
it's nice
right no it's so feel
what oh like the one that goes on your
face no it's the one that takes your
stuff oh God they're everywhere ew e
what is
that oh
God it looks
even the loot
bug
maybe but they don't kill you unless
you're holding something right that they
like I think so did you know there's a
mod where you can make it say yippe
what yeah someone in my chat just said
the yippe
bug yes the yipp bug oh I found him he's
on top of a key oh don't take it what do
you want
it what if I
do what's happening why he man did you
take
it did you take it
no I just walked up to
him wait a sec you provoked
him oh [\h__\h] what do I
hear I don't know what was that my
screen is still like
woo was that what
happened I don't know you're Moon
walking
Annie are you okay are you okay are you
okay Annie is that her
name yeah yeah
yeah um turn
around
nor
way I saw two of them yeah me
too I think one just finished
consuming no
way that means we have to get back but I
don't know where the ship
[Music]
is
oh my God where's the
shoe
right okay I'm
going
what
you hear
me no oh they're alive did
missing
wow no no it calls pom lazy don't do her
dirty like that oh my God I was so
scared I'm lost um disconnected again I
know she disconnected right beside
me
a maybe she should be alone maybe being
next to somebody like does something to
her
con so should I remake again does it
save yeah well she didn't she didn't
seem to I don't think she's back cuz she
didn't write anything after I wa let me
see is that
yes
are you okay you want to come back it
saves when you're I want to come back
yeah orbit stream so I'm going to just
play okay less pressure on the web wait
someone said it Autos saves when you go
into orbit so are you guys saying if we
pick a moon and then restart the room it
will let's do it a try I just don't know
if they mean like
now
or yeah now it's fine right because it
save it probably saves after it shows
the report of all the players right yeah
right I don't
know um you are in orbit it's already
saved it said and saved okay now it's
save to leave all right we will make a
new room save the progress thank you sh
okay
reming
nice that was so funny I oh come
back that was so funny I can't believe
she
[\h__\h] and we will turn around I turn
around
disappears me P raided me she loves me
the
most darn it I'm back did you hear
backed me so she loves me the most wow
the worst she can do is say
no can you hear me yeah yeah yeah we can
okay I was like be you're like I don't
know where to go I'm like it's okay
follow
me a that was so hopefully you survive
this time a little bit
longer let's go let's go let's not waste
time we yes go um you guys see there's
some there's some flashlights on the
ground for you guys so please pick them
up than you
yeah L
[Music]
it oh yes I will start the
game
yippe Yi
oh my God yeah take
it h remember the charge is here you
Nissa are you sure about
that uh a WEA did you grab yours I'm
grabbing it thank you I okay yep I'm
going to buy some more stuff did you
guys die to dogs or no they didn't I
didn't
die Pro Gamer wait is this the
first is this way yeah it's the first
one tangle
wood tangle
yeah this one's easy to
remember I was seeing flashlight guys
did you not
notice go up wait for
me
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello hello open
[Music]
Isa sugar Mommy
okay what are we getting pick up this
walkie
talkie talkie time how many are there um
only two so if we travel in cars I got
one um I'm dropping the other one right
here okay so I
said I won't go with p anymore um
so flashlight bot who wants the walkie
you we oh okay someone take how do I use
this okay
onward we should we should do let's just
do a little um exchange wife exchange I
go with we pomu goes with wi okay okay
okay oh my God Wife
Swap God do you
there's a TV show maybe maybe America
has it too where they swap
wives it's so
stupid I didn't think you're going to
say it's so
stupid okay we go this
way
down no The Backs what's
a the back rooms there's a bracket on
the map
what when they when the game oh Jesus
there's a slime at the entrance oh you
guys are
here oh no slime coming towards us
slowly slowly no the Slime is no
joke but it's so slow yeah we can walk
around it ow ow ow ow ow
ow um guys I think the Slime is in love
with me
oh there
and guys slime is in love with me oh
it's gone this is the fun you can say
stuff like that but so far it's not
doing [\h__\h] yeah not impr
yeah okay bye y wait where's we I'm here
she already went oh okay I checked that
room there's nothing in
there here
so what do you like to do in your free
[Music]
time I
know I like to so bad I know right I
like to look up random facts about you
on the internet
[Music]
what a smoke
Smokey where what the [\h__\h] this the
spash is not helping that's because
there a steam Le yeah I can't find the
valve you got to find the valve oh my
go
that's dang
oh oh it's
you I think I'm alone no yeah we're
here we're in the guys my flashlight is
dead oh my
God
I did it
yay
yum hello oh oh hello hi okay we're all
here together awesome yay we're all here
together together steering
wheel yes take it I can finally have
Direction in my
[Music]
life where did everybody go my
flashlight
died are you guys wait where' they go
guys
nowh I'm
scared too everyone's
gone what if I walk in here and I
die I'm going to turn around the valve
I'm going to turn around and there's
going to be a Jack In The Box or
whatever it's
called and not the hurg there over yes
I'm here
over I hear
you I can't find a single
thing
[Applause]
we I might die to my death here why
would you be dying
over I'm going to jump to the other side
you are a crazy G
overa [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I
don't know what that
was what was it I don't know it was a
little shaky sound like a little sh sh
sh maybe a bug maybe I can't see
anything who oh but I can see you hello
hi we're the ones with the
walk I know why are we together here a
I'm going to jump here no why I'm going
try and get to the other side because
there's no other way to the other side
okay
[Music]
any
loot I found a fire exit oh wait I'm
going to jump over
[Music]
too and a fish I don't think I'll make
it though to be honest you'll make it
you'll make it you'll make it where are
you I made it Yi
where's the fire exit it's this way that
way
yep
oh
wait where you go did you find
anything yeah I found some stuff it's 6
o00 let's
go yay God I hate going down on here cuz
it's
so if you got motion sickness Look Away
guys look go
away oh that's you yeah it's dark
outside we got to be careful we'll be
fine this is tangle
wood
I don't know if you can hear me still
pomu but I believe there is a
worm a
worm a worm uhoh um oh yes hello okay
let's go everybody Kiara where's
Kiara
dead did she
fall I don't know what
happened but uh let's just get out of
here on the grave
cuz the dogs are coming
out the dogs get back in the sh get back
in here she'll automatically get thrown
in I think okay good unless be really
funny didn't I
am
o o
nice wh suain the most injuries it's not
my fa slime was in love with me hello
welcome
back you all notic I don't know about
the Hest but pom you just said it in the
ship why did you notice so late what the
hell that was dead took you a while
um it's a pretty big place
okay wait is it just me or was it really
laggy when you
[Laughter]
some sometimes because the game is like
a indie game like the microphone gets
really like pixelated and when you were
explaining it just got
[Music]
really but did you understand I
basically just walked off and fell and
died really not not an exciting death it
was funny
though that happens that's like the
lethal company experience not going to
lie it really is M now did I lose the
the flashlight yeah oh
[\h__\h] can buy another one Mommy it's okay
did you order something again yeah for
me this
time I'm going in yeah you and P leave
leave a walkie-talkie for KI here you go
oh yeah here you go
thank you oh okay I'll pick it
[Music]
up I feel like every time I play this
game I don't use a
flashlight this is hen's
influence
when she was like flash like we don't
need those and she just kept running in
I was like oh okay is this
evil my butt is on the Hollywood
sidewalk whatever as it should be mhm oh
hi
guys how are
you we are the light oh where are you
where are you I'm at the start I picked
two things up so I'm going to put them
outside okay I'm
back welcome back which way you want to
go I was going this way oh I guess we we
can go we'll go this
way if you're happy there's clap your
butt
cheeks clap your butt cheeks if you Happ
know then you really want to show
it clap your butt cheek yeah clench them
[Music]
okaying oh
[Applause]
Jesus
door the door on
me I'm still coming please
okay
well
she was just
[Music]
there that was
freaky yeah still
there I don't
know if you're scared then Clans your
but butt Che you could go through the
fire exit yeah let's go get the fire
exit about this
yeah go of
fire I think we clapped our butt cheeks
a little too loud
spider sum a spider spider spider was
jealous because the spider has no bud
cheeks yeah just a hole
Dariel just has one
hole
cheap wait tell me more about that one
hole what do you mean the spider's butt
has one
hole bring that back to the ship yeah
girl
wait what did she pick up a giant uh
engine thing oh good I thought it was a
mask a Bo
box I haven't played don't where the
[\h__\h] uh the spider's up here I haven't
played since the mask up wait is the
mask a mod or is it actually a part of
the
game what I part of the game because I
think someone used it
yesterday rainbow put on a mask it's
actually oh God yeah that's
scary okay I'm leaving what
Chien I am a
chicken I'm literally kfp what do you
mean only work 22 the
engine
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
it's only
3:00 they bring my fish oh I see one of
them fish they're gone
okay they only hostile if you take their
stuff
so do
they
do
they like sit on the item that they like
or do they just know in their like
little bug soul that you took it when
when someone really strong like a
bodybuilder flexes their muscles and
then their their shirts just like wow
you
know you know so like that I did that
with my jeans I guess well what we got
everyone have you ever ripped a pants
with your butt
no no likely
story but I mean okay now I am now I am
probably flexing as if it was my butt
but before I actually said it's the
moths and I still believe it's the moths
okay so before you told everybody it was
moths but now you're you're taking that
story back well yeah I'm taking credit
now because my butt could do it if I
butt wanted to but it was the mobs yeah
oh like the mths like yeah chew through
it I think so how dare they Ry should
that's so rude should have been
you why does it look like we're
incriminating each other I don't know
likeor you're the one who killed kiar uh
what did it say
objection objection
objection all right who's getting Eed
off the ship
me wait we got so much l what happens if
you jump off um oh
oh [\h__\h] idiots those [\h__\h]
idiots [\h__\h] IDI I jum you jump girl
you [\h__\h] donkeys eat sandwiches hey I
you donys did I drop the
walkie-talkie
look everything you were
holding oh no it's okay we
made
yay oh my God I thought maybe if I had
jumped it would have like be back into
the
ship no what I mean I thought it would
happen I thought we would be safe guess
it was it was for science
yeah all right let's go drop everything
off shall we oh okay we have
enough we'll find out real
quick I think we have more than enough I
think
[Music]
good did you learn about
this what about the
what K you have to after we drop off the
last
yeah no all right click the button
anything
else which button the Bell that just
went off just keep clicking it till it
shows up which one
okay oh
um yo she's played this game so many
times you wanted that to happen to me
yeah cuz I love you I can't tell if it's
open or not you know the M be and
there's sharks and stuff you know sharks
don't really like to eat humans though
well I have a good relationship with
sharks so I will tell them to do that
why would you do that they won't like me
not tasty do we have enough oh 4 I tasty
400 let's get P
back oh man why why did that
happen for what what was the purpose I
didn't think it would happen so fast
pomu did pom know did she know yeah she
knew it was going to happen I think she
didn't think it was G to happen I didn't
think it was going to happen so
fast
$92 we got fin for your death the heck
I'm sorry where is okay let's see so pom
died unnecessarily
twice
yeah it's okay cuz every time that you
connected it didn't count as a dead so
we didn't get charged so it's just
making up for
it true up logic
okay girl math it's girl math for real
if you died if you died two times for
free and then you had to pay two times
for death it's
free yeah it's just evened out now okay
okay okay okay I won't die anymore on
purpose I didn't die on purpose before
but you know I won't really really die
on purpose okay um where are you taking
us this time mommy somewhere is
fine I wish we could go to our Navigator
yeah thank you thank God yeah don't want
to touch that keyboard
okay we can't we can't afford to go
to yeah we're
poor
Titan we're too poor to go to
all right there's more wait before you
guys jump there's going to be more
flashlights coming for
you thank
youmy what was that wish you Merry
Christmas I've I've never had a sugar
mommy before I'm so excited and happy
yeah now don't let the plane land on you
or you will die oh don't worry pomu
knows all about
that yeah I knew that happen
where is it the sun where is it is it
because we didn't put out milk and
cookies
maybe
okay thank
you oh strong Flash oh my eyes big
flashlight all right don't lose them
this
time or whoever the other walk if you
want to leave it in the the thing since
we don't have one so that way if you die
just a
walkie-talkie okay I'll come with
[Music]
youart I want I I'm happy being the
bread winner I'm happy to find loot and
provide for this family yes I will
continue to just buy stuff I didn't
think you guys could hear that from that
distance oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's so
dark holy
[\h__\h] it's so dark what the hell I've
never had like the smoke be
here what smoke do what is this it's the
it's just the the
smoke how do you find okay watch out
because you can't fall and die here how
do you find the
valve oh hello hello hi
hi I found a big
loot
yeah there oh
there's can't
see follow the
sound
oh where it's the
[Music]
loudest
is there like a
time when enemies spawn more in this
game oh that was so
embarrassing like do enemies only start
spawning after 3:00 for
real 5:00 p.m. 5:00 p.m.
oh should have charged my flashlight I
was thinking about that like while I was
bringing the back I was like yo I should
just charge my flashlight when I get
back so smart I forgot 300 p.m. is the
earliest oh
okay so we're still
good that's only outside though right
like inside they can spawn at any time
while the Bracken spawned literally the
second I walked in that room
so
hello
I heard someone call my name say my
name
seriously
loot have we seen a little girl uh last
time when I played pomu was like talking
about her but I haven't seen her
personally
wait where did I come
from am I stupid what the [\h__\h] was
that oh from
here
yes
stop hi
guys
[\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] scared me so
bad that scared me that scared me
too I'm here to be the bread
winner I'm doing my
part can I hello
you are the definition of girl
failure
what I feel like I'm girl
capable
[Music]
sometimes
[Laughter]
opum oh that means that they took the
thing right yay they found the
light anyone turn the steam off if not
I'm going to use this as a learning
experience
oh they
did oh was
right what's happening I'm I'm really
injured why am I
injured sa
day loot bug out of nowhere but there
was a sign
hello if you had hello don't go back in
oh I did I almost
[Laughter]
died well you didn't I have to walk
around I didn't no you can jump down oh
okay nice all four surviving and
bringing back no
way a circle of life save the game I
didn't bring anything but I was here for
support yeah oh yeah also I brought a
key but I I didn't use it again like I
never used key save M yeah we can save
it for next time yay we have so much
stuff adopting the ID wife sharing
system yes we have a wife sharing system
yes yes CH all right should we depart
yeah yeah you in I guess so
access fig from Fire
Emblem what's this posted
girls what's this posted it I think you
can type it into the oh yeah the
computer it just tells you I think it's
lore post it m
[Music]
it's oh my
God I'm the CEO I'm not the
[Laughter]
intern okay um you know someone has
everybody starts somewhere Kiara okay is
this real
no what's real someone in my chat said
type boobies on the
computer
what did you do it what
happen I don't think you need to type in
on the computer they're on the screen AR
they happen
[Laughter]
they're they're
trolling what no no no no it's a it's
oh code it's a code gamer talk
80085 oh I don't know about that one oh
is it not boo bees so should there be be
88 uh 1 three five for boobies
oh nothing
happened yeah
135 type
135 nothing happened but when I typed
boobies it asked if I wanted to buy the
boom
box
oh wait maybe you bought a Bo box no I
didn't it said do you want to spend and
I just Ted out that is what I call
customer
service boom box is 60 box yeah but if
you type on the menu it'll just
automatically or we could save up for
the jetpack no I think we or we could
save up go to
Titan Titan okay let's go save up the
Titan okay so we need uh about I think
it was about 400 to pass So currently
our stuff is worth about uh uh
157 so we still need to get quite a bit
of stuff we got it okay yeah we got it
we got
this when we didn't even
die
sh do you guys want to try going toch
sure again okay anywhere that's not
eclipsed or
well I'm not I'm not I'm not going to
chance
it
okay I'm going to switch WIP we're going
to wipe just no Just
For Boobies switching W can you I'm
going to
switch I
choose wait wait wait een Meen Eeny mo
catch the tiger by his toey Mo I don't
know how it continues go we
okay didn't even consider
me no because I I was with you last last
run m
okay I think we're witnessing a lover's
[Music]
quarrel the
birds birds and the be and the
bees wait is that why there's birds and
bees oh you make a good point the dev is
a little
sneak he a little
spicy spy
spy oh huge
yay we can go this way let's go this way
okay I right you my for this R okay I
hope I will not be a burden to you never
I have a key by the way oh awesome let's
find out lock door God I hate the
smoke smoke
smoke no I don't know I could oh I can
hear a land mine though watch out yeah I
think I saw it oh yeah that thing there
yeah wouldn't it be funny if um you
know don't let the intrusive thoughts
win oh there's a key would be kind of
funny it would be funny if I stumbled
into it accidentally oh another
key there oh there's a turret there's a
turret that's a turret that's a turret
oh portal
oh what the [\h__\h] there's so many
landmines and turrets and stuff oh my
god there are there's so
many oh I don't think the landmines will
kill us I think it will be
that this place is kind of there's so
many
Landes well as long as we don't step on
them oh oh um let's go back the way we
came help we we got this don't worry
I'll protect
you
um maybe oh come this way does it react
to us
talking um I honestly I I don't know
what it reacts
to guys what does the Bracken react to
chat lethal company players I think
that's a door lethal company players in
the chat
Oh wrong
door it was a
door exit
doco exit Doo I don't know oh a bolt oh
interesting room oh there's a bottle
here hello wait is there another someone
hello where someone
hello yeah there's a
bracket
I wonder if we can find another
exit I can hear a landmine
though oh what the [\h__\h] that sound is a
land
mine
oh there's so much happening I'm
scared why is this game so scary oh wait
there's something there oh there's a
door here we can
leave oh yeah pick it up
oh
exit yay I found the most important item
in the game where are we I don't know
how to get back from
here feel like we're in the back side of
the whole
thing that's what my women's intuition
tells me all right lead us the
way me okay yeah you got it okay
maybe I shouldn't be tooting the horn
maybe that will call the dog
over no W oh you scan to find your ship
oh how do I know where it is you have to
be in like a specific oh is this water
okay don't go in the water
[Music]
okay
I oh I hear
bees yeah what about this path this is a
nice path
okay what why are we so lost or maybe
what
[Music]
about you still here sorry yeah I have
no
stamina oh got to work out girl uhoh oh
that just means they took the
core but even outside radiation y I
don't know
I think it's just inside the building
where is the ship oh it's right here
right
here right
here hello
hi you found the way back oh oh my God
you're so good at this game yeah we only
found landmines that's all we found and
we found some stuff hu is on her way
back too oh oh no there's a monster guys
guys guys guys stop there might be
[Laughter]
dogs okay
[Music]
pomu I don't I'm not sure where she
is yeah
but people people oh no no no pom no no
I have to save her where is that can we
zoom out no no uhoh oh oh she went
inside
oh okay she's at the entrance anyone
want to attempt to meet her there save
her and we want save your real wife I'm
on my
way oh it's like one of those jumping
things you're crazy
hello oh my God I was trying to those
things I was going to go over there and
try to distract them but you're
gaming oh my God I'm almost dead she's a
gamer she when I went over there she was
already running you made
[Music]
it you [\h__\h] made it wait those guys
aren't bad
right oh there's one near the ship watch
out but here hurry and get on and let's
run
[Music]
yay ready I almost died to the braen too
that guy came up on me and I turned
around at the last second we kind of saw
we saw him so many times he was so cute
we are we are ladies of competence holy
moly he was so cute and like let's go
look at all that I think we're pretty
pretty close to our quota I think we
need 399 we're at like 368 so if we just
get a few more it doesn't count
everything sometimes like the game
glitches a little yeah I think it's not
that I think the the buying prus is
different like it's not based off of how
much like I think
uh6 if you stand over here it scans them
all better yeah yeah is that how it
works in the game like the company buys
items at different rates every time I
I'm not sure don't forget to charge your
flashlights oh thank
you okay is that enough is one charge
enough oh yeah it is yeah just one left
scanner only scans a set
Limit Oh you're trying to scan kind of
random it's percent based on what day
you go different rates based off of days
left oh I
see oh okay I don't
[Music]
know deping
on
oh go let's
go I'm going to take one key is this is
this the last one yeah yeah this is the
last day so we just need to not wi so if
everyone's dying just whoever is left
leave
okay I go with pomu now okay me yes and
that's probably going to result in you
the
seeing let's do this yeah let's go
how are you so
fast I used all my stamina okay the ship
is underneath okay this yeah we just
keep basically hugging this
way yeah you got to like yeah I can
never remember where the ship is on this
map yeah this one's more
tricky here we
are Yow all righty show
Girls
show let's go this
[Music]
way I'm
scared don't be scared we got this oh my
God she's so
confiding um nothing else okay metal
sheet let's
go oh I wonder if there's anything in
here oh there's a lot of stuff in here
oh it's just a
robot he's so loud there's a cookie tin
too uh maybe we should drop this off so
it doesn't attract stuff yeah we can go
back okay my hands are full I can't even
walk
upstairs yeah rest that you know you
know they make pble rangs
what what the [\h__\h] is going on uhoh that
was the
robot little guy he's just a guy it's
just a robot it sound yeah he's just
loud oh that's the they want us to take
the robot to the ship right away
apparently so I'll be back so you three
travel together maybe he brings a lot of
points maybe wait the remote
is yeah the remote's good I can turn off
can I leave it here
turrets it can no way no I don't know
somebody said nice or remote that can
turn off a turret no way for
real oh my God she went it on her own
she's so
brave brave she's a new Phoenix one
guide [\h__\h] you
guys over there oh it's coming what oh I
see him the
spider oh it's a mod so it can do it
we're not playing modded though we're
playing vanilla you're not scared of the
the
speed I believed it for a second you you
have a problem with this game
[Music]
Shino you have a problem with this game
you're Min maxing
scrap I'm scared I'm going to take this
back I'm going to leave the
key hey playing solo is kind of
fun has a prop okay this is going to be
my arc where I finally remember on this
map where the ship
is so I go this way wait where are you I
don't
[Laughter]
know I'm I'm I'm I'm in front of the
entrance come back up here I'll help you
yay I'll help you I'll show you how to
get back oh hell yeah okay so yeah go
where p is going so you always go under
this thing can we leave you going to get
any no I'm not anything under this thing
get
under and then go straight through and
then you hug right basically so you go
right and then you go right again and
then the ship is right over by these
these basically anything that pomu
collects means I like it
too why you laughing also I got the
remote control
so got his right I mean I found it but
she grabbed it oh my God I went the
other
[Music]
way this map confuses me so
bad mhm I know this one's
weird
yay okay we have so much stuff I know is
crowded the keys we definitely make the
quota so do we want to keep looking for
a little bit or do we want to go why is
it
scan 12 objects outside the ship
totaling at approximate value of
1,65
1200 I want to go back in
okay be quiet be
quiet is there a dog oh yeah yes God
yo I was we were closing the door right
when I was about to leave again
dangerous oh did you just start yeah
there's a dog right
outside I could take
him you could take him that's not a dog
that is not a dog I could take open it
up so you can see it
okay damn it oh he's gone damn
damn yeah really motivated I want to go
back inside gets eaten by dog yeah n i
win i' win so loudly I was like shut up
shut
up oh it's
over damn it no okay okay we can go to
the next map no we got to go to the
company oh after we sell everything do
not unal life yourself at the ping pong
machine again
okay pink
pink okay let's see how much money did
we make a
lot what guys we're going to Titan baby
what does it chat just because I did a
little ping pong doesn't
mean
anything what do you
mean like Ping
[Applause]
I think we should sell
first what are you doing going to sell
is it going to f we got to we can sell
multiple
times oh I sold something I don't think
I can't tell if it's open oh it's open
it's open it's open it's open open
why oh the ping pong is
selling yeah take it guy oh so if you
stand there when you're selling it it
will eat you yeah
500 wait do we want to sell everything
or do we want to keep it for yeah we
want to sell it all let's just sell
everything we're not sweaty almost had
me that's true yeah we need to go to
Titan yeah some some people who play
this game are sweaty and like save
things for later quot
do yeah be careful be
[Laughter]
careful stand back hey hey get back here
he's not opening the door okay we're
good maybe he has no more money to buy
it just opened it wasn't
opening okay now we wait Mr man you got
it got it
okay chica
woo
Yi
okay how much money how much did we make
who how much money
much
see Ru don't watch the
stream oh oh I'm inside okay well that
scared me go to Titan or the other one
first
we need to go into orbit first
pom yeah sh you're outside no she's
right here no I'm right
here oh oh oh okay I thought maybe I
thought you were just some hanging suit
like this
one oh I'm just like I'm a mannequin
yeah yeah I don't know that was
weird did you guys see her I don't see
her should we go to the house one or
should we go to Titan going I'm sorry
said it this yeah I like Titan what's
Titan the difficult map it's a difficult
map you're a professional now yeah we're
going to die now because it's foggy on
Titan we haven't died in a while yeah
maybe I should do a a DI for
ENT yeah I don't want
okay wait I'm going to buy some items
before we leave
[Music]
okay wait come down okay here we go plus
there's
snow snow oh wow the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh this is is this
Titan it's foggy so here yeah you go why
is it why why is it why why is it doing
this cuz it's like extra foggy holy cow
no why my my I think I have a bug what's
wrong do you see my
hand what about it what's happening why
is your hand doing that I don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
know guys where is it on top fixed I
don't know it fixed
uhoh is this way it's right here no I
found it hey hit it hit
it I it it's like like there's shovels
on the ground
now come to the
music I'm right here yeah there shovels
on the
ground okay I can't oh my
voice
start guys I have my light on I'm
yelling yay hi okay where here circles I
think oh I got the
ship where are the rest of the shovels
on the
ground where wait did you not pick one
up no oh we can hit things with this now
yeah oh let's go our our weapon wait
there was three on the ground and now
they're I've got two of them where are
you for
po did she just go in okay it's time to
go but where the [\h__\h] are we going poo
where are you I have no idea I think I'm
just going to go up wait I'm right
behind
you hell are you near the chip she's at
the entrance yeah I'm at the entrance
now I couldn't find you guys I never
finding the
entrance it's right
here no behind you behind you
behind me yeah here here and then we go
up here oh my God okay where's P Mo I
think she's climbing yeah they're
climbing there's a about you a shovel
yeah oh oh it's not foggy you have it
yeah yeah she's bringing it to
you
oh okay oh my God my
12:00 maybe we should just leave no the
qu we have to do it for the company yeah
we got to do it for the
company we have to meet our quota
there's a
key we must meet our
quota yes we
must
why is pomu
screaming I'm so ready I've never killed
anything in this game before everybody
but today might be the
day can you drop the ladder on
mobs we bring back because I'm already
full inventory yeah we and this is
really rare this is expensive yeah bring
it
back w w w w
w why you got close to me I'm just a
girl they're so I'm dead I'm so dead a
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you I'll kill you stop it
you
bug where are
you I can't help first Blood
I did it guys I
killed
guys that's right where are you I'm here
I killed the
bug good
[Music]
job I I'm
scared where's the exit Make Me Home
Country
Road I don't know where I am sounds like
you're really close to me and I'm by the
exit Okay I'm going to follow your voice
okay but I just have no
idea oh I think I'm
far I don't
know I'm following your voice I
think I'm not going the right
way
hello oh it's over goodbye
everyone everyone is over for me yes you
still hear me yes I can okay I'm by the
exit you can just get to me okay if I
die I just want you to know I love your
cover of i t by Kiko is one of my
favorite producers I'm
so me
too oh [\h__\h] it worked
y okay let's get out of here okay I am
sustaining critical injuries okay um I
can't carry them because I have too many
things not the mask like this mask oh no
ohu are you coming up yeah I'm coming up
we have a heavy item could you carry it
back yeah I'll carry it thank you no not
the oh yeah you can take that one oh
okay I'll drop the other
one someone should stay behind no we
should all leave it's
almost did get it I only I was inside
for like 2 seconds found five items and
then left I saw like an one square meter
of the inside I killed a bug and then I
killed another bug and you killed a bug
yeah it was really scary
damn it I didn't use the shovel at all I
that was my first time killing anything
in this game
damn how will I ever become
KN somewhere this is the ship like right
okay yeah this
way what does that even mean over here
over here what does over here mean I'm
lost yeah right right right you're
yeah we're
safe oh okay don't do
it I think we should leave okay I heard
you
screaming okay scared
me who screen you I don't know maybe
just mask screen uh we have
$466 worth of things you have the mask
oh my god oh don't let pomu pick no no
no put it down P put it down why what
does this do it'll turn you into evil
monster it'll kill you yo I saw that
clip of when when Milly teleported you
into the ship with the mask on I I saw
what happened I know what you are
capable of doing I've changed my
ways
[Music]
no interesting I didn't do [\h__\h]
just but I'm like way more productive in
this game than in uh what's it called
cosmophobia yeah this is cosmophobia
it's fun right [\h__\h] the only yeah this
is just like phasmophobia um control
wise everything else is very
different it's just
fine this time this time I'll go inside
and do something
yeah didn't you pick stuff up though
that is doing stuff I did but it was
like immediately after we entered I
didn't see anything from inside yeah oh
my dentures yeah do you like my dentures
I do I love them my dentur I picked
those up are we going yeah let's
go yeah okay what was
that what was that sound effect W when
you pulled the Le
P the
L she did a little W back beaches is
this is this not the Titan no that we
can we now that we bought it we have it
permanently so we can go or I think AO
will on the save until we die die I
thought you had to pay for it every time
nope oh there he
goes nice it's not permanent you have to
pay
is that what they said I think it's only
you can you don't have to pay for the
three times but every yeah maybe every
round you have to pay for or or it's
[Laughter]
okay it's
pay-per-view no worries oh a
bolt
my favorite
anime okay today I
learn not again you [\h__\h] I swear
to
God
it's get down no
we that was a real get
down get
down
yeah oh my
God hit me don't hit me oh I my
flashlight Friendly
Fire why did it do that when I killed
it that was so
nasty so gross [\h__\h]
youu cool
[Music]
here oh I don't want to fall down again
yeah don't tell be
careful nothing I hear something
nothing I am so not scared anymore now
that I have a
shovel yeah
right the shovel has freed
you it's going to take me like 20
seconds to CRA over to my shovel when I
see an
enemy you'll see a Bracken and then you
won't be so bra well he's different
he's he makes me nervous he's tall dark
and handsome yeah he's just like an
Enderman you
know what's happening over
there come here come
here what what is that
sound
nice nice the way I killed it epic
murder a present I have a present for
you yeah open it oh my God wait and I
brought you m can I open it murder yeah
you can open it
how
oh how did you do
that always wanted it's so romantic a
stop
light you I swear to God I'm going to
kill you you mad that I killed your
friend well guess what uh mother I'm GNA
do it again oh [\h__\h] I'm dead help help
he doesn't like
me help
Meo po I know you're there poo Healy puu
I don't know where you went goodbye
everybody I'm critically injured it's
all over for
me
um I'm alone must be the win drop off
yeah around and find out I'm alone I'm
going to die
no let's go there uhoh oh somebody
everybody hi I'm here I'm scared I don't
even see my body think there's a bad guy
yeah I don't know how to get home
they're going to leave me came from
somewhere over there and I
dropped cuz I uh didn't I think there
was a monster close to where I was
before okay from here I don't know where
we go what do I don't know either me
yeah uh was it this way okay no there's
no door is there something
running oh I can't oh oh he where you
have to kill it my hands are full it's
it's down there now where did he go he's
just
chilling on the ice P I see AA I see
[Music]
Kiana
oh
aa [\h__\h] he took something he can take
something yeah that's what they they're
obsessed with taking moov oh what is
this red I don't know oh I think you're
right I think you're right what
the and then from here what the hell
from here I have no idea I felt so
powerful we didn't go that deep in no I
think so powerful I remember remember we
killed this guy right here yeah I so
powerful
wielding the right here
oh
now I'm nothing they were probably
worrying about us now I'm nothing if
they were so worried they would have
come and gotten us I'm [\h__\h]
dead they're probably about to leave us
behind I'm dead look at this look at
this
Kiara W it's a laser p are they actually
there you girls hi A's
dead how did she know no wait how did
that
happen but there's a monster nearby
somewhere the shovel back up oh what you
get I thought I was holding it oh 400
ooh there's lots of here I I only
brought a big valve and we we were like
almost lost don't look yeah find our way
back don't look oh there's so much loot
by where Al died right I think it's the
loot bugs I think it's the loot bugs the
Lo when the bug grabs you you drop
everything yeah we
surv hi we we'll miss you we'll miss
you a byebye
goodbye
goodbye well nice
guy wait a took the
milled no why would literally it's on
the ground
okay I was cred literally that injuries
I was
[Music]
cred was it a loot bug no it was the
things that like hang on the ceiling and
then uh the ones that drop down onto
your face and like Eat You
Alive what I was like yelling I was in
the room beside where you guys were and
I was like guys help
me I heard someone scream that was me I
didn't I didn't hear anything I'm so
sorry oh she heard oh man oh Manara you
left to die me I was I was alone already
at that
point
okay for
you wait why did it only give me one
item wait I'm going to buy you another
Pro flashlight
yay
yay your muff
[Music]
oh okay I guess I can only buy one at a
time just ate me
alive then you everyone chats like
you're not pomu she
heard
what do you mean have no idea stream
open have I have no stream I have no
stream she 100% heard yeah I'm innocent
spell
proof watch for the thing thank you and
everyone charge your flashlight yeah
thank you Christmas Mommy momy
respons Falls I'll CL
the shovel mommy has purchased for me
[Music]
[Laughter]
hopefully where is the
tree oh it was right
here thank
you
nice pick things up like a normal person
it takes me 10 times more effort started
Christmas without us woohoo good okay
you got both of them yes thank you y
let's
[Music]
go oh my God wait I've never
seen I didn't know you could go up there
oh if this works then I'm sorry it's for
the content oh my God no it didn't
work just slid right
off oh no there went all alone I'm sorry
I wanted to know where Santa
Liv I thought it would bring me to the
North Pole I thought so too I thought
you would go for sure D that been so
funny where wait here's Pomo who who
this who's this for you it's me Le
where's we I think she already went ins
yeah I think she's left us she's
fast oh God it's so
dark why is it always so
dark
ooh all righty Bring It On is the
Nutcracker in like all the maps or is it
only in the house
one
yes
it huh what box thank you what are you
killing I I my
it I hit but you they're on the ground
they're on the ground right there a
without
you because it was already on my
face you think you're going to like turn
oh God I think there's another
one
scary oh turret I hear them walking
around in the
vents you
I'm going to go this
way
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm going to go
[Laughter]
back
okay it's Le it's just lethal company
it's just a silly game made by a
singular very brilliant Dev nothing can
hurt me too bad it's just it's it's a
game made by One Singular very crazy e
Dev who is very good at making a very
good game I'm
scared oh hell
no one Dev I I think so
right oh Jesus it's a spider
[Music]
no it's just a loot bug it's not
it's not it's not it's not it's not
wrong
way it's not a big loot
bug yeah One Singular very big loot
bug a
fish yes
oh I did my part oh there's a light in
there
too
I did my part I did my part I did my
part oh yeah I put that outside
too the railing cheese got patched out
wait when you're fighting a spider and
you jump onto the
railing they patched
that no
way she
coming she's here hi behind oh I was
fighting for my life wait there's
something really big in front of the
door I have to grab still
wait there's a
spider no it's just one
thing unless you want
to there was a
spider and died yeah I got really scared
so I ran
away that's okay I like lowy want to
turn on the
Arachnophobia setting just so that I can
see it it's so funny yeah it looks so
funny that's why I want to see it I'm
not that scared of spiders but it's just
funny it's just
spider
spider oh actually there's a power core
right
inside oh should we get it yeah I think
we should I forgot about that thank you
chat there's like a power core yeah
don't be in here spider where it's like
right oh [\h__\h] which one was it this one
uh okay I can't remember anymore yes yes
yes this way in here oh oh I see I see I
see grab
it okay we'll go out follow me okay I
have no stamina
okay okay I have
stamina
yay
yay I totally forgot okay we got to be
careful
oh God I see these things again
no these things
new
no they
not make
[Music]
noises get away get away get away get
away get
away oh they get intimidated if you
scare at
them it's like the opposite of every mob
in this
game y I thought they were new it looks
like a reskin of an older mob yeah we
made
it yay or maybe it's like a all right
I'm going to go get it there's a there's
a there's a giant we have to take off
first are are you ready there's a giant
let's
go let's go wait no hold on I don't know
where it is where is it there's a giant
there's a giant there's a giant start go
go go start
start wait did you start
it oh um sorry K keep holding on to it
don't let go people said that if you let
it go it might glitch out go I won I'll
never let
go sorry
Ki sorry
kiaha I was caught in
between you recovered my body
so oh yeah cuz you died in the
ship it's so squishy e oh yeah right
okay keep holding on to it and let's go
to the
company
e how much is
that a
lot still doesn't say how much it's
worth when I put it down oh good oh
beehive
19 19 that's it oh 90 0 no it's got to
be way
more
it I thought the Beehive was worth like
crazy I thought it was like
I thought it was worth at least 200 yeah
I thought so
too be high value 90 apparently they
vary from 67 to 100 plus that's only 90
for us even though we're this cute I
know give me a better PR so easily not
worth it not worth it oh Jesus not that
that
guy I think it's full okay I can't yeah
oh god oh watch out watch
out that was terrifying he doesn't like
the
teeth beep
professionals DK you is that everything
professionals professionals baby is that
everything I'll call them again
oh remember you heard the screaming
before it was from the phone
oh
yeah this take wait he's taking it right
now don't sell the
mask why not we got to we got to use
it no it's evil what do you mean I want
to see what
happens okay I'll bring it
back
no wait so we're not selling the we
still we still have a one thing up here
though watch a YouTube
video come on Chad you literally watch
the clip you know you see yeah but like
I want us to experience it
together be right back two seconds okay
okay
okay now put on the
mask no no surround we can surround her
no and no
I'm
scared kill us
all wait who's going to Lear the mask
not
me is that a sound oh God what is she
opening we have to protect her P your
mic's not
[Music]
muted what's happening I don't know your
mic wasn't muted so I needed to protect
whatever was going on oh I just got my
French toast
oh wait the one from
7eleven yes oh my God yes the oh my God
I know exactly which one it's so good
I've never had it's so good the one from
7-Eleven oh my God Japanese 7eleven we
got to make it
clear I heard I heard american1 is not
good hold that
I've never been hey we made so much
money oh God our quot is going up higher
and higher okay so we have
$1,227 can we go to the mansion one what
one is the mansion Ren or
Dine uh which one is okay wait there's
two of them but one of them the cheaper
one is the more worth it I think
ah um
yeah what
one dine dine is better dine is better
but is that one the Mansion
yeah F okay let's go will this one be
the last one because remember when you
girl said off stream we're going to do
two hours it's been two and a half yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we can do three
more days then I haven't noticed yeah
this game is so fun we're going to have
to die anyway because if this is the
last one so um we could just go
exp and then do the mask yeah oh my God
I'm
so oh a little love
fight it's a little love tap you
know little love tap yeah charge your
flashlights everybody it's r r oh no
it's raining uhoh is there electric is
there lightning I think it's okay F take
the mask it's all yours and leave your
flashlight and your shovel oh no
okay going to do
it all right sh ready ladies you're
going to die
right wait let's go in first all right
yeah let's go in first okay let's go in
first okay okay you lead the way
pomu this
way where shitty
weather should I buy the TP where you
are I'm in the ship still
what hi I'm coming don't
worry I bought
something wow okay let's wait for it
yeah let's wait I I don't know what it
is is it the jetpack oh is it the zap
gun what let's see suit oh it's already
in the ship oh I don't have to wait for
it
did you get the teleporter to it's here
it's the toilet
[Music]
what nice wa
light why is this a thingy please
privacy okay let's
go where we going sorry guys that was
$300 we're going to kill pomu when she
puts on the mask
okay what if we do like a hide and seek
we'll do like a I'll go hide and you
guys find me why if the coil head finds
us
first yeah I love the coil heads they're
my number two Oshi after the
Bracken
really yeah he's pretty he's pretty
cool he's got a good thing going where
is the
entr I'm in water this is water don't go
in don't go in
uhoh guys it's water by the
way you
got guys this the water hey where
where's the building how do we get in I
think we have to go this way we were
baited by this light thing no the
light's right it's cuz there's raining
and the water like piles up really
fast uh-oh I don't know how to get in I
don't know how
why don't we leave and see if the
weather is better tomorrow okay that's
AA well we can try our best yeah no we
fine we came we saw we died it's fine
it's fine yeah we D that D dying oh cuz
the Moon is called dying you're so
[Music]
silly [\h__\h] weather ah defeated by the
UK
yeah do you want to use the or do you
want to wait until it's
clear no we got to look yeah we got to
go inside the building we got to show
Kiara this is my favorite map
okay everybody
in let's go British Beach I flushed
before we
left did you wash your hands we don't
have a sink
oh that that is it's conundrum isn't it
it's okay I put my gloves
on Can we is this okay that we didn't
get anything yeah because we're not
trying to win cuz either way we're going
to start stop playing after after this
so okay yeah okay moons let's see dying
is eclipsed so now we'll get to see an
eclipse oh
no what you can you don't have to go to
a new place or you can just oh yeah can
we I you can just land yeah okay yeah
let's do it yeah you just land again
okayli
we can't believe there's a toilet oh
skib skib toilet let's
go
no okay I think this place is always
Eclipse no it's not always well it's not
it's not eclipsed right now right it
didn't say so it is it is well then
we're about to die probably right
now going the same
way I think I hear a giant why do they
call you the
nisler um because B called me nisler
oh
mhm my little bi boo
Zoomer it's okay we also have a
Zoomer in our wave our third
is W in your wave yeah our third is the
[Music]
Zoomer oh Jesus it's
dark God mine can I play
chess oh that's I make my
move okay Ron calm
down a perfume bottle those are
expensive something else what is that I
think it's a tea kettle oh it
is oh there's a spider in here oh hello
oh really yeah oh you're right there's
another perfume bottle right I hear him
walking around stop girl you're going to
kill me once I make my move
what if you find one too would you want
to turn with
me what happens I've never I don't know
I've only seen the clip where Millie tpd
you I don't know what happens like like
oh you put it on you put it on oh
okay do I just hold it
yeah are you holding
it yeah so left click is it on how do
you
feel right
[Music]
click Jojo Jojo I'm scared of you can I
oh
who
yeah no you hit me no WEA you're okay
right we you're just
standing oh my God her ping the power of
the power of the
Ping oh my God The
Nutcracker
[Laughter]
Fu
cracker what is that is that the coil
head yeah Hing it yeah oh my God there's
a too oh my
[Music]
[Laughter]
God hi how's it going I love how we even
connected in death not even
death that was like so much so many
things happen Nutcracker there was a qu
there was me with the mask
on yeah wa the first thing you started
hitting was that Pomo I thought it was
an enemy uh I don't know what that ver
thing was but apparently it it moves if
we're not looking at it oh that was the
coil
head yeah that's a coil head this has
been fun We're not gonna meet a quota
that's okay we can just go in and do our
best yeah we're still we're still at
weit we have one more day right yeah
yeah so we can go in and do our best how
much money do we have left oh and then
we won't make the quota and then Kiara
can see what happens when you don't make
the oh yeah cuz I guess we never saw
that before no so you'll find out today
hey you'll find out
today oh there it
[Music]
is let's go let's
go go I'm honestly
surprised that
we we're Pros we're Pros yeah for
real we're kind of
amazing atast
round we lost at the 130 quota it would
have been so
embarrassing
you can take the Nutcracker shotgun out
of his hands
what oh it's not dark this time but
there is a land
mine oh it's bright yeah it's not dark
for the first
time wait where are you I'm in the other
room oh we're here again let's go I want
to go upstairs where did you I'm here
there's a robot but I don't want to pick
it up cuz it's loud yeah we're not going
to make any oh there's a land
mine might as well just have fun
exploring
yeah I hear the land mine's right here
the land mine
yeah I'm following you mug number one
mug number one mug that's what it
says
your ping makes you like float a little
it's
funny oh no like you'll move really fast
and like float over and I'm like whoa
oh everything looks normal yeah oh
oops oh my God I'm so happy
wao
painting
painting key watch out for the land mine
I ever used a
key oh what was that a
clock oh my God there's so many
landmines I
know I'm
scared it's this side it's right here
yeah it's side it's like in the little
corner
yeah I like this oh yeah it is a then
this way we
go
okay AK my
show I wonder what the enem is
here I know there's another land mine
here oh almost R into
it
whoa again you guys good oh bottles
here
oh oh there's a gift box open it up
what' you
get this is mine no it's for you
yeah my God a Rubik's Cube I've always
wanted oh my God
yay wish it wasn't so dark this is a
dead end too oh we got to go upstairs
then I can just manage to escape nice
where are you guys guys yeah where are
you guys hi I'm in the entrance oh we're
almost there I found a ring found a ring
we're here yeah and I
found you found a oh it's aard what is
that a clown nose oh billiard
clown found a mug that says number one
mug and I was gifted a Rubik's Cube nice
shall we try to bring these back to the
ship even though we're not going to make
quota do we want to to keep exploring
yeah me too I want to see what's
upstairs
St yeah land mine that's what
jeez feel like I don't think they're
proposed to Kiana that's a good
idea
use is she having fun I hope she's
having fun
exploring yeah she's definitely alive
and oh she's kicking
it
she's
I know you want to die on to the m chat
stop wasting my intrusive
[Music]
thoughts I want to see a coil
head okay I'm just going to follow
you
this m doesn't say
anything says
World she's
downstairs maybe did she leave what does
that sound oh God I'm being haunted by
the little girl no why is it always
[Laughter]
you if I die I hear her breathing she's
like oh my God she's right here oh she's
gone now oh my God I'm going to die to
the little girl my head's going to get
exploded guys it's okay just come here
come here that's what happens I'll get
you out
yeah oh uhoh I think she put on the oh I
think so too wa she found
one I guess so she put it
on what you say oh my god oh oh my God
you wouldn't kill me right you created
the you created the the Wu the Wu web
you wouldn't kill
me remember who you are Creator the w
web
the web oh my God am I about to get
[Music]
cyon I do that's
me
youst oh my God he's running
did you like putting on the mask
BR pain in the ring you you you kissed
me to
death she
dead you kiss to let's go back
to I hope I don't die as a little girl
if I
[Music]
die why would we D the little girl
she'll come out here she'll explode my
head oh my God pomu is getting haunted
yeah do
that um what the
[\h__\h] oh my
[Laughter]
God it wasn't Evena it was the
dog yeah I actually I found a mask and I
I I actually didn't know what exactly
would happen happen even though we
already experienced it so they told me
to put it on and I thought I could
freely haunt you guys when I put it on
but I didn't realize that I would die
and
then it was so
funny that was so good you just got
quiet all of a sudden I turned
around but it was just because I went on
my own to find some stuff so it was
natural that I became quiet but it was
fun watching you girls looking for me no
we were looking for you
um because we
have we have nothing we can sell the
toilet we have nothing we don't have to
go to the company meaning we can just
explore dine one more time oh you can do
that oh fun yeah and then uh once we end
this day we don't have to worry about
collecting anything because it's day
Zero it'll just uh we'll experience the
losing thing so nice we P good to be
here we just go again a I say yeah oh ye
and we don't even have shovels anymore
we have
nothing I didn't know you could go to a
moon on Day Zero I thought you had to go
to the company no if you're going to
lose anyway might as
well what the hell is this what is this
water it's a Quantum Rock hey okay
everyone look away look away water look
back hey what the hell is going on wa
yeah we're getting
baited we go the wrong way can we
no where is every at the ship is there
another
way hello
hi are you in the ship no I'm beside
you oh where' they go how do you can you
not go around it not from what I could
see not from what I could see you can
try again maybe we just can't see
period actual Quantum
Rock have to go around The
Rock
Dwayne what the
hell like up above the rock I'm climbing
it me too oh okay I made
it oh I'm stuck in the
tree oh oh no you're here
yay I've never seen the rock me
either behind
you there's a little girl no there no
she's gone now it was a bug I was
looking at the bug you were looking at a
girl what about me I thought you only
have eyes for me oh my God I'm upstairs
is pomu
living oh
no oh my God the coil head oh my God I'm
sorry oh [\h__\h] me oh my God oh God oh I'm
going to die oh this is so bad oh no oh
my God I'm going to die
cck
no oh my god oh
no blow him up St on thebody else
Dead all together why' she oh my God
wait when you why does the line might
not work on where are you little girl
just kill me
now I hear you bra
one oh my god did you guys see the
little girl from my no we can't it's
only you my own it's in your head oh my
God it's in my head take your pills that
was so evil how wait which one did you
guys die
to the yeah the nom nom nom nom yeah
they died to the
coil oh the coil head it was funny did
you die before us um I died outside cuz
a dog ate me alive in front of died to a
dog with us should have climbed it with
us as you have
not your performance
[Music]
has Welcome to our disciplinary with you
get in the
corner Among
Us among
us we're
fired yay hello
hello what
yes hello helloo oh should we Discord
yeah yeah Discord byebye
game so fast I CL game
okay that was fun actually yeah see you
are so worried that it was going to be
not fun and then look at you yeah well I
I think I you were Brave today it's
quite repetitive though it is a little
repetitive but that's why like uh the
the worst levels get like the the more
things that are kind of introduced but
it felt like we kind of had really bad
things right off the bat you know yeah
we were a great team of
w and it was really nice with this group
I like this group it was so fun Wu web
we're all so pretty we're so beautiful
like oh my God slay
to you for wait wasn't that P who
invited yeah thank you P yeah thank you
P yeah thank you P I'm glad that we
could play glad that after you ended
your stream you were able to play for
real for oh
yeah sorry I keep do seeing no that's
fine as long as you didn't have to leave
completely I'm happy yeah no I have fun
I had a lot of fun thank
you thank you girls I love you girls oh
my
God oh my are we
onb
World winning
world
winning web
girls web girls yes oh why did take your
picture because are not playing the game
anymore but it's
weird it's cute that's my Discord icon
how could you say it's weird yeah let
her
cook oh oh okay I I'll consider it she's
gaming she's gaming yeah this is me I'm
gaming what was I going to say I was
going to say something but I
forgot remember
uh uh I'm
remembering uh [\h__\h] subscribe to the
worldwide wle web everyone yeah
subscribe subscribe leave a like
and yes everybody type type into your
search bar on your browser worldwide wfu
web winning.com
everybody don't search
ww I'm GNA buy that domain right now
worldwide I mean actually
winning I know I don't think what
happens if I put it in connection failed
connection failed what does that mean
we're not real
uh we're real we're real we're real to
me we just need to establish it you know
yeah yeah yeah I think with this collab
we have established it
yeah that was fun thing you girls I I I
wish you a happy New Year soon and Merry
Christmas and and I wish you much love
and um don't forget about the fun times
we had together the love that we shared
it's happening I don't know like don't
don't don't divorce me okay I could
never I wouldn't even dream about it
never ever
ever we're the
www W now W yeah we're the quad
W so many W I'm gonna make food now okay
okay thank you guys that was so much
fun C
[Music]
some K to everybody making
out there e ew now I'm freaking out
ew why you say ew
too much k
bye bye everyone thank
[Music]
youe oh yeah oh wait I forgot my German
we say Z oh I
forgot byebye byebye too much too much
I don't know if I was supposed to leave
the
[Laughter]
call I couldn't see which one I was
supposed to click on my steam deck let
me close lethal
company
I'm so
[Laughter]
[Music]
eepy
Jesus the loudest cheesec cracker known
to man my
[Music]
God play on stream steam deck no stream
deck I know they sound so similar the
stream deck is like the little
application like it's like a little
thing that you can buy that has a bunch
of buttons that you can like add your
Macros to so I just like press a button
and it changes
the the scene for me auto like for I
press a button it changes the scene in
OBS for
[Laughter]
[Music]
me thank you for the gifted thank you
thank you thank you thank
you that was really fun collab I'm glad
you had fun it was really fun for me too
thank you booa
true I'm glad you had fun I had a lot of
fun
too I sacrificed my sleep for this
collab I'm so sorry I hope you have a
good rest of your night I'm
[Music]
sorry I'm really
tired there to end stream I wonder if
they're
talking
they're done oh I guess I will I think
they're
talking um yeah nura was really cute I
was so nervous that was my first time
talking to her so I was really
[Music]
nervous I was really nervous it's my
first time talking to her but she's
really she's
so
a
[Laughter]
leader she's like she's so she's so
mother she's so
responsible yeah she's literally mother
it was oh my God she's so she's so nice
she takes care of me I love being a
[Music]
baby I love being a baby
so when other people are mother around
me I'm happy so I can be
baby I guess they're talking so I'm just
going to wrap up real quick then so I
can say like thanks to them
for
um I'm going to go and say thanks to
them for the collab but I do want to
apologize for not being able to stream
uh
yesterday there's a lot going on I'm
sorry there's a lot going on right now
like last week there was a lot going on
this week it got worse there's a lot
going on right now in my family and it's
really
really weighing me down to be completely
honest so I don't know what's to come
for the next little bit but I will do my
best
uh tomorrow is kill's birthday so I
won't be
streaming I was originally taking uh
tomorrow off for GU this
[Music]
but yeah it's kill's birthday tomorrow
so I'll be joining his TSU for his
birthday at some point and then on
Saturday uh still my original song will
be premiering so I will do an after talk
stream after the premiere for my
original song has ended so I will do a
Afterparty for my original song on Sat
Saturday night and then I'm not sure if
I want to do anything on the 31st yet
everything is really difficult right now
for me to plan ahead I'm really really
sorry this end of the year has been not
so good for my
family but I'm really excited for my
original song to Premiere finally so at
least that is very exciting and I'm very
excited for all of you guys to hear it
finally but yeah really sorry I couldn't
stream yesterday I will definitely keep
you guys
updated whenever things are going on and
I just need to take time
off but I apologize
again thank you to pomu for organizing
this collab I had a lot of fun playing
today yeah and thank you guys for
watching as well I'm really nervous but
one of my goals for next year
is uh to make more friends or to reach
out a little bit more I like being being
a solo streamer like it's more you know
like I like playing solo games a lot but
I feel
like I'm in like a position where I'm
able to reach out and make so many
amazing connections so next year my goal
is to try to reach out a little bit more
I feel like I really worked on what I
like to do as a streamer this year and
then next year I want to Branch out a
little bit
more while still sticking to like you
know I still like doing solo streams but
I do want to like reach out a little bit
[Music]
more yeah who's streaming right now
sorry I'm going to wrap it up so I can
go and talk with them and tell them
things but hopefully the original song
after party will be longer so oh fana is
streaming perfect
I will send you to
finana the
Zoomer
yeah thank you for the stream no thank
you for coming and thank you the for
organizing make sure if you don't I'm
pretty sure you probably know but uh
make sure to check out Kara and Nissa
from Hol live Ian they're so wonderful
I'm really happy I finally got to collab
with Kiara I feel like I talked with her
so much that it felt like I'd already
done a collab with her but I guess this
was our first time even though we've met
and we went to dinner and everything but
I guess I don't know like it always felt
like we had already done something
together but I guess this was our first
time you didn't I guess not I don't know
I thought maybe but I don't
know dinner yeah we went out to eat
dinner together
before I don't remember when it was
though this year I think it was like
almost a year
ago I thought you already collabed
before I don't think so I don't
[Music]
know I was like yeah I was almost a year
ago I think it was at the beginning of
this year so almost a year
ago all righty thank you everybody for
coming to today's stream tomorrow is K's
birthday so no stream from
me
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay yeah it
was with Nina and Ros and me and Petra
and me and her and then we went it was
in like February or March I think when
we all went on a trip together I
remember uh no stream for me tomorrow
tomorrow's K's birthday so I'm going to
be on his stream whenever the tto is
happening also my brain is just not
doing so good so I'm going to take
tomorrow to
just
sit yeah it was when Rose and we showed
her underwear why do you guys remember
these things yeah she had just bought
some and then she was like guys look at
the underwear that I bought and then she
opened up the bag and showed
us uh and then on Saturday I will have
an after talk stream for my original
song so I hope you enjoy whenever when
it premieres at 8 p.m. espd
PSD on Saturday thank you everybody for
coming to today's
stream thank you thank
you and I will see you on
Saturday I'll see you on Saturday for my
original song I'm so scared but I'm very
excited but I'm also
nervous thank you everybody for coming
to today's stream thank you and I'll see
you on
Saturday bye
bye I hope you have a great rest of your
day night morning evening afternoon um
wherever you are and I'll see you
Saturday good night
byebye oh thank you everybody for coming
sorry I'm such a
[Music]
mess sorry for being such a mess but
thank you for being so understanding I
love you guys so much thank you for all
the messages on Twitter too I cried so
much yesterday reading them you guys are
the best I love you all so much thank
you see you later
bye