I I was laying in my bed and Kiana came
in the room and she looked at me and she
told me to stand up and I was scared I I
don't know why I thought she was like
going to beat my ass or something I was
G maybe but you know what she did she
gave me a hug I was like oh how
cute she's so cuddly I I thought you
needed a hug baby I just give you random
like unexpected hug so she does so that
so that you don't like get
cocky but I don't okay I still want to
hug you but I don't want to like give
you too many hugs and like two two
regular like scheduled hugs or so
they're like random to surprise you know
what else she laid on my lap but I need
I I I was so un she was there for like
over 30 minutes though so it couldn't
have been that uncomfortable but your
lap was worth
it