[Music]
[
Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
[Music  ] Don't
believe,
that's where
the bridge that wakes up crosses over time,
Shinjuku's
[Music]
Stand up, bring your
courage
together,
If you call love a rule,
smile and hold the hands of the moon
[Music]
Deceive the darkness and stand apart.  The
love of those who evade punishment
opens up the future.
[Music] It seems like it's going to
change every time. The
wounds of the dust that won't disappear rise to the surface due to the fate etched in the bloodline.
[Music]
Clutch it tightly
[Applause]
Strike against the overflowing power.  Haacchiichi
[Music] It's the way the stones in front lead the dawn while hiding the
seeping
pain and the
meaning of living now.
[Music]
At a high pitch
Towards the shining, scorching sky On a
journey where our souls collide
Saving a future shaken by sadness
[Music] Towards the
destination where I leave this rabbit wind
Without fear, without hesitation, the
ripples of fate resonate in
my heart
[Music] I
deceive the darkness, dodge the sky, and get through the day bus.I
won over their love,
and the feelings I pierced
were etched into my heart as I embraced the future.
Close the bond of dust that rises up due to fate
[Music]
Yes,
Alona I can see you, I can hear you,
wait for me
Yes, I'm Akilo Seko Taki Rosenthal, the healing half-elf of the 1st generation of Hololive,
Arrow
And so the Akiroze 5th anniversary live
has begun
[Music]  ]
Today is going to
be the best! It's going to be a great live show until the end. It's
getting a lot of attention, so make sure to keep an eye on it.
And here's the hashtag.  I've
posted it, but please tweet a lot at the Akirase 5th Anniversary Live. Please
tweet lots of cute screenshots, small videos with cute cutouts, short videos, etc. Aim for the trend.
Trend
1, please.
This is the buddy who gave me this.
This is the American car Aki-chan. Wait
a minute. I
broke down the wall behind me, so I'll win consecutive games later.
Okay.
So, it's just the beginning.Enjoy
it till the end.It's time for
Akiro.Let's
change clothes.Okay, I'm going to change clothes, so
turn over there for a moment.What the heck,
Jajaan.This is the
flight parade.We're all the
same idols who came.Cute
and...  This
hat
has something cute on it, right? I'm
curious what it is on it, right?
So let's move on to the next song.  The
guests were
Fubuki, Matsure, and Mel who appeared earlier.
[Applause]
[Music] It
seems like a shining night,
carrying you with the spring breeze, and the
colors of summer will welcome you. If the
turning autumn pushes your back, you'll take
a step that you don't know anything about.  I've moved on and finally
made it here. I'll
definitely show you the wonderful stage I've been walking through the city. The
seasons
run around the world, and the days turn into dream-like days.  I want to
be attracted to you
Fortnite has just started
[Music] My
heart is filled with colorful
festivals I'm pouring out a
lot of happiness I'll
ring it and dye it brightly The feeling of tomorrow The
sound of the 12 o'clock bell has changed and it
won't melt forever Let's
cast a spell My heart
flutters and
my heart dances  I'll pass the time, so be
sure to follow me.
Even if you know the five rules of not moving or
slowing down, you're getting involved and making a lot of noise, so you're
not dancing enough. Curve
all the way past the curtain cold.
[Music] Let's have fun
at the Con-Conkey Festival.
Happy 5th anniversary to everyone, and
thank you. Thank you. As
long as we have the will to enjoy it, we can surely
become the protagonists. [
Music] Let's
explore this world together
Even if this melody ends, it will never be a
memory that's only for today.  I won't go, I won't go [
Music] As the
seasons
travel around the world, into dream-like days
[Music] Let's
continue The
spotlight will
never end
[Music]
That's why it's Plasmagic Season 2, an original song by the 1st generation.
[music]
So,
what was not included when we first appeared?
[Music] If you
watch it, you'll know what it is. It's our
5th anniversary. Yes, it's the 5th anniversary of the 1st generation.
There are a lot of debutants, so today is a special occasion.  So
once again, I would like to introduce myself and do some kind of
advertising. I see, I would
like to do that, Matsuri-chan. It's a
festival.
Well, on June 3rd, I'm
planning to do a commemorative broadcast, although it's not 3D.  cage
So, even if you have time or don't, please make time to
come and see it.Thank
you very much.Alright
, next, Fubuki-chan, I'm embarrassed to say that greeting,
so, um, I
'm planning that project for June 23rd.
So I'd be happy if you could look forward to it. It would be amazing.
Thank you very much. I'm looking
forward to it. Well then, Mel-chan,
Genius Vampire Hololive of Matchmaking Party 1  I
'm Yozora Melo from the season, and I'll be broadcasting a commemorative stream on May 13th.I'll be
selling archive goods, so I'd
appreciate your support.I'd appreciate it if you
could subscribe to everyone's channel.
So it's not just this hat, I actually
have a surprise for everyone.
[Music]
[Music] It's
not like we're all lacking in exercise.BasketballI'm
going to have you do a shuttle run now.
Well, today's a live show, so it
's a bit of a cat-sized gymnasium, but if you
look at the back, you'll see a
huge monitor.What
is that?
VTR, please.
That's amazing, give me up! Well, I never expected it to be. When I debuted, I
honestly didn't
think I'd be able to celebrate my 5th anniversary, so I guess it's amazing that it's almost
like a miracle is happening now.  I
couldn't do something like this in 3D, and it
was like a dream to me, so I'm
really happy to be able to do it now. You're
not thinking about it, are you? I'm definitely
lying.
This is
right, I'm
twisting my brain.  While spinning,
there are things that I've always wanted to do, and
everyone has their own youthful days,
right?They
play both wind bands and marching bands.
There was a time when he devoted himself to club activities, and I think that was the
epitome of his youth.I wonder if he was able to develop
that strong spirit of never giving up, not being able to write, and never giving up.  [
Music]
Have you ever wondered if we could do something together? The
5th anniversary is a pretty big milestone after all, so I wonder if we
can do something
[Music]
Good morning, what's your job today?
Yeah, that's
kind of scary.
[Music]
Yokohama City Kanazawa Industrial Promotion Center
No, where is this
[Music] I
can hear it
[Music]
This is a
marching band team, right?
[Music]
Yes, this is a general marching band from junior high school students to working adults.
Home of the team Yokohama Robins
Founded in 1990. Since 2000, the team has participated in national tournaments for
23 consecutive years and has a variety of careers, including
collaborating with Masaharu Fukuyama in Kohaku.  They
are a very famous matching band team that is in demand for GM appearances and movie appearances, and
Autumn Rosenthal is also a big fan of the
team.Really,
really, are
you here now?
There is someone who seems like you can talk to me.Hello.
[Music] I'm
busy and I'm bothering you.  My name is
Aki Rosenthal, and I would like to thank you
for taking the time to speak with me today.The
members who have been waiting for you, please
gather.We have gathered
together.Today,
Aki Rosenthal is here.
So, I'd like to say hello. Take care.
Hello, hello. Hello
everyone. Hello everyone. My name is Aki Rosenthal from Hololive.
There's a huge difference between us.
By the way, how many people are there at the moment
? It
's about time for the April changeover,
but there are currently 130 people.  I'm currently with the team, and today almost all the
members are here.Thank
you very much.Well, since I have this opportunity, I would
like to ask you a lot of questions, but first of all, thank you very much.
Can I ask you to tell me who the two of you are? Yes, my name is Ryotaro, and I am in charge of the team members.I
serve as the leader of the band as a whole.I am also in charge of this team.  I
'm Haruna Arai, the leader of the band.
Thank you very much.
By the way, what instruments do you two play
? Yes, I play this big tuba, a
brass instrument.
Actually, I play an instrument.  Although it is not  I
play the role of a dancer, which is called color guard, which is unique to marching.Actually,
even at Gero, I used to do
color guard for a little while.
[Applause]
Thank you.
By the way, I also played the horn.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much. I'd
love to see you later.
There are a lot of members here, so I'd like to ask you one thing. Is
that okay? Do you
know about Hololive? Does anyone know?  I
mean, the
two leaders are also raising their hands,
right?
By the way, can I ask who this is?
Yes, I'm a fan of Shiragami Fubuki-chan. I'm
Shirogane Noel-chan.
[Music]
By the way, that one.  Akiloze fans:
Yes, I'm a little embarrassed to raise my hand. After all, it's
embarrassing to raise your hand.
Well, that fruit has a request for me today.
Can I ask you to listen to my request? I've
always
had a dream and I've loved Matching Band for
a long time, but I've
always been a fan of Yokohama Robbins and
wanted to perform with them.
So this
fall, I've always wanted to perform with them.  Rode's 5th anniversary live is coming up, so would it be possible for
Hololive to collaborate on a song there?
Yes, we should
definitely do it together. Is that true
?  It
has been decided that we will be
collaborating with Yokohama Robbins. I never thought that the day would come when I would be able to perform with Robbins. We
have been practicing so hard. All of our first-year students will be singing with us,
right? Everyone in your household.  I'd like you to see it too.
Everyone at the Robins, let's go and
do our best together.
[Music] I
think this is our first attempt.
So, what are you going to do today? The
Yokohama Robins gymnasium and this place.  The
broadcast from the virtual gymnasium is connected. I
wonder if the Robbins will come? It's been a while since we've seen each other, so today we'll be collaborating on a performance with the first generation
members and Mr. Robbins.
Thank you, Mr. Robbins,
for the original arrangement of Hololive.  I
want to perform that song with you.
But first, since it's a special machine, I want to see the performance that
Mr. Robbins always shows at the park, saying how cool he is.
No, it hurts, it hurts.  Is it
possible for you to show me the intelligence of the vice-captain?Yes, I would like you to see it.I
will do my best.Then I will prepare it.Please
[Music]
That matching band that I have seen before is
cool, isn't it?  It's
cool, is
n't it? Yes, it looks
like it's almost ready, so would you like to take a look at it?
Yes,
please, I'mexcited,
it's cool, it's
cool. It's big, isn't it? It's cool, isn't it?
[Music]  They're so
cute.
[Music] I've
heard this song before.
[Music] It's so
cool. It's amazing.
[Music]
[Applause]
The teamis
beautiful.
In fact, Akiloze also played with them for a while.
[Music] They're
holding their instruments so cool.
This is so cool.  That's
right [Music] Wow, that's amazing to be able to step back
[Music]
There are 130 people, that's a lot
Yokohama Robins Special Performance It
was my way
[Music]  It
was really great, so I'd like to ask the leaders a little bit about it.
But Mr. Arai-san, can I tell you a little bit about it
?
Thank you very much for your wonderful performance. I'd
like to ask the other 1st generation members of Hololive.  I'd
like to hear your impressions,
but Fubuki-chan, what do you think? It
was really cool. It
was really good. Thank
you very much.
[Music]
Well then, Mel-chan played everyone's breathing
movements and it was great.
Thank you,
Matsuri-chan.
How was that big tuba instrument? It's really heavy. But if you have something that big, Matsuri-chan will be able to
lift it with ease. I'll do
my best.
Why am I gaining weight?
Please help me lift it.
Thank you again, everyone. Thank you. I
just wanted to ask you something. Um, I heard before that you
kind of like the other Hololive members,
but I
just wanted to confirm.
Mr. Rice, I fell in love with Akiloze. I
love the color guard, so
I hope you will continue to support me. Well
then,
how about Echino-san, who lives next to me? Of course, you
pushed me. I'm so excited.
Even though you told me that you love me,  Okay
, I
love you.
Please, I love you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I want to be a little selfish.
Thank you everyone. Now, it's time for
Marching Banta and Hololive.
Collaboration has finally come to fruition Let's
celebrate our 5th anniversary and sing together.
Everyone at Robbins,
please get ready. The
performance looked great,
and I was able to do it. Let me tell you how amazing it was. We
just did it together. I'm sorry.
[Music]  ]
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, that's me. Well then, let's
get ready for our collaboration performance. It
's a little special, but just
like always, smile and be
cute.
Please bring us super idols with energy and love.
[Music] I
wanted to do this with Ha-chan too. I'm
waiting for her to come back.
Okay, then everyone, let's do it.
So,
let's listen to the Above Bright Parade, a special collaboration with Yokohama Robins.
[Music] It's
shining. Using the
voices calling to each other as a
signal, I go looking for someone
[Music] It starts
over and over again.
[Music]
[Music]  I
spoke to myself,
just wanted to start, so I ran. There
was a light in the distance. It was
a name that was too bright. It was a
memory that was too gentle. I
reached out my hand to bring it closer. We were unexpectedly connected.
Now,
the lost child has become my own.
[Music]
Hey, I'm
proud that I found you. From here onwards, we'll fry a frying pan
[Music]
[Music] If you
listen to me now, I'll scream "Welcome home"
[Music]
Isn't it obvious?
Who, who, who?  It
's shining,
all the regrets and love
[Music]
Dreams and all, I'll
jump on them
If I don't whisper, the light will never end I'll
jump in with you, the
wonderful height From here onwards
[Music] A
frying pan
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you
[Music] There are
so many things that we can't do anything about.Everyday reality
is tough, but
if you can sigh and stand up from here beyond the trials, something will begin again.Wherever
you go, as a country
Let's hold our breath and enjoy it
[Music]
Well,
I know that I am the one who will change my destiny
[Music] I know you are the only one who can change my destiny [Music]
How much is left of my heart that can be reduced to dust and dust by interrupting convenience stores? I do
n't have to wait for the intersection to be the
position of tragedy
If you smile as hard as you can in seconds, you'll be upgraded to a better day. Let's go,
raise your garbage head. Look,
take the same steps as you are and create the future.
[Music]
Don't blow it away, I looked like I couldn't see you today
You know that only you can do that
[Music] I want to
give you all I want to see you again I'm
sure it'll open again It's
still far away right now Even
if the scenery changes, even if it spreads, I
can grasp it with my hands  Until
[Music]
You're the one who's going to change It's time to start In the river of HAPPY YOU You know
Yes, it was the fateful circumstances surrounding you, and  It
was a special snare drum performance. Thank you.
And Taiko Tai Atsumare Pan.
There were fewer people.
[Laughs]
Thank you for such a really cool performance.
Yay
. Bye bye. It
was really cool.
Alright, the 5th anniversary live is still going on. Let's
open it. Let's take it off a little bit.  I'll come,
so wait a little bit.Okay, are you
ready to get even more excited?The
5th anniversary live at Akira has a long way to go.
Let's get excited, then this is the next song.
[Music]
Let's dance.
[Applause] I want to
do whatever I want to do. A
hidden love is a beautiful romance.
[Music] I
won't give you my passion like a fruit.
[Music]
Show me your true face, I'll
show you everything that's just about me [Music] I
don't want to spoil the miracle of our encounter,
let's go back with love
[Music]
How much do you laugh and
worry about?
Even the days when I'm lost are such a wonderful drama.As I
search, feel, and layer them all together, I get a little closer to you.My
actions almost scream
[Music] It's
instinct.I ca
n't stop it.I'm
smearing the world.Let
's dance for you.
[Music]
[Applause] I
want to give all of my last-minute, last-minute heart to just you, baby. I'll
give
you all of my last-minute heart.
Let's go back and fill in the history of how we met you.
[Music]
Come on, come on, come on, come on, I'm getting excited,
and my battery is
running high. It
's still going on, but I know what the next song will be.
Who is the heroine, Ardition?
[Music] I
remember
your kind words, and I'm so excited, then.  I
couldn't say it, so I
tried to smile instead. I felt like I was wishing. That alone made me
jump. I
thought I misunderstood your wish.
So, in my heart, I
sent a passionate gaze.
Turning around, I was
wishing for a
wide audition.
If I enter,
will you choose me?
[Music] My
serious
personality will be conveyed just by saying good morning.
[Music] I'm
looking forward to it.
There are so many dazzling wonderful people, and I'm
not confident, but even so, I fall in
love with them,
365 days a year. I want to
get closer to them at my own pace.  But if I
muster up the courage to go through a wide audition, you'll be like
a cat, and you'll be able to withstand it.Everyone
in the moment I met you was amazing.I knew this
chance was red,
so I
pulled myself together,
believing in fate, and going straight.
Who is your heroine? I'm sure I'll
move your heart. I'm
not quite there yet, but
choose a wide range of auditions. And I definitely want you to do it someday.
Thank you, I'll love you forever [
Music]
[Music]
[Music]  ]
[Music] Even
though I can't do it, I
love rubbing.
Something that reminds me of you.  Dress up
like a sunny day,
just like my brother saw
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music] The living room is
next door
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
[Applause] [Music
]
[Music]
Hello Akiloze 5th Anniversary Live New Strip
Route 5 Thank you for watching this far.
Thank you.
This time it's the 5th anniversary, so it's super special.
It's a collaboration with a marching band.  We
performed 5 songs, including a new original song by Akiloze, together with Hololive members.I
think it was a really special stage.I'm
waiting for the cute screenshots of today, the cutouts of the cute parts, etc.  So,
please use the hashtag Akinose 5th Anniversary Live and release it to the sea of SNS.I'll be
waiting for you.I'll serve you ego.
Thank you for your
support.Now then, everyone has
been waiting for the goods.Now then, I
have shot an introductory video, so please take a look at it.Here we go!It has been
decided to release goods commemorating the 5th anniversary of Rosenthal's activities in autumn.We
will provide detailed information on the goods here.  First of all,
this is a big towel written by Akitake Azumi.
This is a super refreshing version of the
Ros squad marching. It's
super
cute. It's also the size of Victor.  It's
pretty big, so you can decorate it,
or you can use it by covering it with a futon or something like that.You can also use it as a regular lap blanket,
or just
put it on.I'll definitely
use it.I forgot to use it to decorate my fingers.
I would be really happy if you could get it.Next,
today's live theme is Historic
Route 5.This logo acrylic
keychain
has a really stylish design.It's a
super fashionable item.
I hope they can show it off.By
the way, the key chains with the logo that were released as Hirose 4th anniversary merchandise are
actually in the same style.I think the
combination of the set is really cool.I think it makes it
even more emotional.  I think there will be more, so be
sure to get yours.Then, the
next item is here.Marching
band prevention coin case key
chain.It's
super
cute.
This time's Nelive power comes in as a fluffy
key chain with the design of a marching band hat that looks like it has feathers.When you
open the zipper, it
becomes a coin case, so it
can be used for everyday use or as a decoration.  This
is a super product. It's
really cute. Please get as many as you can.
Also, there's a storage case that looks like the
snare drum that you worked so hard to practice at this live show.  It's a
really cute snare drum with a special Achilles spec,
and
it's quite large,
so I think it would be great as a container for small items.You can
use it at home or display it in a shop.  I
think the Moyoshi band can use it, so I'd be happy if you could
enjoy it in various ways.And for those who
purchase this 5th anniversary commemorative full set, it will
come with a handwritten autograph by Aki Zentaru.
& A postcard written by Akitake Azumi with a foil-stamped reproduction message
Also comes with a bonus voice It
would be nice to have a bonus
However, the handwritten signature
will be delivered in a limited quantity this time.However, if you
do not have a limited fee.  The full set will also come with a bonus voice
and a
foil-stamped signature and message,
so I'd be really happy if you could get a lot of them
to commemorate that moment.Thank
you very much.Please be sure to
check out the necessary information if you haven't checked it out yet.
Please prepare them as soon as possible. These are
5th anniversary goods, so we put a lot of
thought,
thought, and love into preparing them, so
please take care of them.
Yes, the commemorative live show is also very
cute goods.  Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely,
absolutely, absolutely, definitely,
please get it
Check the summary column
Yes, and today is our 5th anniversary, so it
's a special day, so I
'm a little embarrassed, but I always don't get too excited.  I'm
not good at expressing my true feelings, so I've written a letter today, so can I
read it a little for Rosetta? It's
embarrassing, please
come.
It's been 5 years since I debuted on Hololive.  It's a slightly more special day, so I
wrote a letter. I
don't know if I can express it well in words,
but I'd be happy if you would listen. It's
been 5 years already, and I'm surprised that it's been that long.
[Music] I wonder
if I've grown a little.
As I go about my daily activities, there are times when I suddenly
feel sad or
in pain.At times
like that, I
can always muster up my courage
because of Rose-tai.
[Music]
You've been by my side ever since we met that day. Now, for the
first time, you're
Akira.  Thank you for finding the star, and for
never giving up, for meeting me and falling in love with me.
[Music]
Akilose is
n't good at many things. I'm
also not good at doing things that stand out in front of people.  I
can't say harsh or strong words even if it's a joke, I'm
not good at being nice to people or relying on them, I'm
not good at communication, and I
think I'm really clumsy.And
since I don't feel any pain myself, I'm
fine with trying to make things up or being weirdly strong.  I
often think that I've been pretending and putting on a false front all my life, and that's true
even after I debuted as a vtuber,
and that's why it's so difficult to love myself.
[Music] I
often feel that way
[Music]
But at times like that, what
always saves me
is the words and support of Rose-tai. They
praise me and say that I like things even when I don't like them, they
acknowledge me, and they're by my side.  They
give me things, they enjoy the time we spend together, and they
make me love myself just a little bit more.
[Music]
So,
thank you,
always. [Music] I've always wanted to deliver moments that add color to everyone's daily lives.  I'm thinking
That still hasn't changed,
and I
want to be by your side for as long as possible.
[Music] We've
celebrated our 5th anniversary, and we
're heading into our 6th year.
This past year, I
might not be able to do anything that has suddenly changed,
but
this year.  In the 6th year, I
want to embrace my life-sized self
and
have lots of fun times with everyone at Hololive.
[Music] I think I saw
new scenery today as well. I will continue to take
one step at a time.  one by one  Let's
take a look at all the different scenery
[Music]
Well, I'm going to show you, so Aki Rosette, let's take a leisurely
walk together, holding hands, and enjoy it
. [
Music] I
hope you don't get bored
[Music] That's
it
[Music]
So many different feelings.  I'm
very, very happy to be able to stand in front of everyone like this, and I
look forward to your continued support for the 6th year.I'm
not going to give up,
and everyone from the 5 households.
Today, tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow, I'll meet Hirose again
in the future. Thank you very much for your support. It was a really fun concert.
Thank you very much. I
have to close it for the last time. I'm
really sad, but I'm
going to tell you a lot of things.
After this show today, it's usually
limited to Menma.  We do some after-live shows,
but today from 10:30 p.m., we're going to have a
normal YouTube live where we'll talk about today's
impressions and other things,
so please come by.
Please come and visit us.Subscribe to the channel and give it a high rating.If you haven't turned on
notifications yet, thank you very
much.Thank you very much for the 5th anniversary, and see you in the 6th year.Bye-
bye
[Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]