[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you foreign
foreign
[Music]
happy birthday to me
foreign
[Music]
welcome to my birthday party
wow
young and fresh so true I'm three as my
crown says
I'm three petals more since I joined
Ninja
this is my third third it's hard to
believe that's my third it feels like
my first birthday
feels like I'm back in the womb
basically
oh yeah
I don't know how much it is
compared to human years
probably really young
probably unbirth
my unbirth thank you for all those super
chats and and and and
uh birthday wishes thank you do you guys
like the cake this year
him
the ass is so fat there's even a little
frog bird too hold on
he's got a little legs
the cake looks really delicious this
year
thank you thank you
um
actually the artist made my cakes like
every year a little asset so I've just
updated every year
and like a bite of that
hmm
yummy yummy
oh gosh I don't even know
what to say I have some stuff today
um
I have uh I have we'll be chatting for a
little bit and then I have some Collins
and then
uh
what was I gonna say oh we're gonna play
a game and then I have a cover
coming out later there is a waiting room
up
Goose yeah we're playing the goose game
Goose goose wait duck duck whoosh
Kush goose
duck not duck duck goose
yummy
[Music]
thank you for all the gifted memberships
you guys thank you
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
I have some birthday marks I should
probably show that right online
don't
don't buy it if you can't afford it
wait where do I have that picture say oh
here
then
I had some canvas panel and an acrylic
photo frame with a photo card and I
wrote a little something something on it
and then there's a metallic charm with
my signature
and some button badges again with my
signature and they all have well all but
the metallic charm has the art by ayami
Sanchez
so
um there's also a voice thingy
I don't remember what I said
[Music]
I don't remember
you you you're in your epic superhero
right
your voice birthday voice pack was super
sweet and wholesome oh I was wholesome
oh redo redo I have to redo it
I have to redo it
thank you guys oh gosh
I allotted a lot of time for us to just
kind of sit and talk but I don't know
what to do
why don't I even last night I did a
countdown and I had no idea what to do
when did I allot the most time to
talking
why did I do that
happy birthday johane
I think you have the wrong house
you have the wrong number
[Music]
that was my day it was fine
um
a lot of laundry to do
so I just did
I just did laundry
that's about it I haven't really done
anything special I got ready
I was I woke up and I played cross and I
then got out of bed and I
I
finished up stuff for
dog the the cover
my space traveling criminal eldric
horror lawyer made double agent tag
cookie clicking Minecraft edit Kami
Yoshi is having the best day of work
thank you
what gift almost Gonna Get You
here are
he um snuggled up with me really nicely
this morning so what is the cover you'll
have to watch
oh
it's okay
if I wanted you to know you know what
never mind even though I didn't make it
obvious in the thumbnail and even though
I didn't I I censored it in the title
I'll tell you just because you asked is
a Gangnam Style
foreign
why
can't you just let things be
as they are why couldn't you just let
the surprise happen hi dog hi dog thank
you
thank you so much
[Music]
it is Gangnam Style
oppa Gangnam Style
is it really
you'll have to watch him
denying that the cover is Gangnam Style
[Music]
happy birthday thank you
totally not clickbait no no not at all
not at all
why is the thumbnail sideways
so that you can see my tummy
thank you
you know the cup speaking of the cover
um
I came up with the idea
uh a month ago
I had a little I had about a little less
than a month and a half
[Music]
to do everything
awesome
um
so I organized everything
very very quickly
very very very quickly
it's the first of this color
as such I didn't want to leave it blank
I bought the birthday Goods the art and
voice make me feel warm but fuzzy inside
thank you
speedrun cover for 27 people yeah
but um I was very grateful for everybody
I was a bit of a I was a bit of a
um I felt like a soccer mom I was just
like can you please send me your mom
can you please
please give me her stuff and I'd be like
okay I'll do it this weekend and then
the weekend would end and I'd be like
[Laughter]
[Music]
actually I might have been like a month
and a half but I had
but um I just like but it was like less
than a it was a less than a month and a
half for the artist to do everything
um
I I tried to I asked a couple different
artists and they were like sorry I can't
do that much in a month and I was like I
know
I know it's hard
but I really wanted it to like be all by
the same person for consistency so
um the artist is insane
absolutely insane they would be like
okay here's four more people and three
days later they'd be like here's four
more people
how are you doing this it's crazy
um it was the video was finished this
morning
oh man thank you for the gift and thank
you Jeremy thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank You artist yeah I'm excited for
the cover I'm also very nervous
I'm always nervous
I'm always like
birthday
um oh
what should we do first
um I
um I'll save the letter that I wrote
last year for
for the end of the stream probably
uh I think there were some videos that
people made it was like I watched uh
duckies while destructive one earlier
um we won't do a watch long of it just
because it's like hella long
I made it to like 45 minutes and then I
was like I really gotta go do my laundry
[Music]
um thank you thank you
uh I don't that probably took a long ass
time to edit it and get all the clips
and everything so
um
Nani just premiered one
oh yeah you're right should we watch
that
let's watch that
um before I get someone to call in
um I'm gonna do them first because
uh they're not need to Sanji
so let's watch Nani's video and then uh
give me one second I'm gonna turn off
the music
okie dokie am I gonna cringe at this I
also was cringing out at well this Ducks
because I can't watch myself so watching
right now
open up that link and we'll do a little
countdown there's no Premiere so we're
gonna have to count down ourselves
just let me know when you're ready and
we will watch the video it's very nice
to know how long these are so thank you
there might be an audio issue what
you messed up you messed up
it's okay wait what's the audio issue
it's gonna blow my eardrums out
okie dokie I'm gonna not ready ready
standing by awesome you guys are so fast
okey dokey and we're watching the pinned
not tweet pinned link
and we're gonna do a three a two a one
and go
okay good
okay
I that's that's my alarm
what
oh my God
where is she going who are there in the
jungle where is she going is this a pull
request
[Laughter]
that I see
oh my God I'm on the train I
ah
is that me
[Music]
ew what the [\h__\h]
why are there so many toilets
that was three toilets in a row please
oh now we're in the sewers and we made
it to the ocean
oh God it's terrifying
oh my God
we found it
oh Nina
oh Barty
I thought that was me for a second but
thank you for the gifted
oh we're in the back rooms now Bob is
this the whole thing for eight minutes
oh my God she's she's huge
[Laughter]
now we're in hell
well God knows this is awesome oh the
diamond City Lights
this is the whole video
oh I'm Palmer
one of those sounded like a lyro oh my
God
there's a there's an alien following us
now oh space
we're going to the Sun
oh my omnic
reader
who ended the audio
is that
laughs
let's take your red song whoa whoa
whoa
I feel like I'm taking probably
Five Guys
that's my mouth
[Music]
people pop people
Cowabunga thank you
[Music]
I want this to be my intro
[Laughter]
Jack oh I've been checked oh my God no
not even
still oh my what the
[Laughter]
it's like all my favorite things stop it
I'm Pomo
the poem request
to the Bowser form of vacation was so
scary
oh
no
foreign
oh my God I'm gonna die right now
oh my [\h__\h] god
I listened to hers too much
what is this oh no not a sandstorm
there's more
oh my God no
oh
my God
[Music]
oh my God
tissues oh my God
yes
yes I heard it I heard it I heard it
foreign
oh my God what
oh my God it's the boss
that's the boss
oh
she's so in my left ear thank you
I know I know about it I know about it
oh my God
she's so so not some timeline
not the timeline
thank you oh you got me
oh ppdc
[Applause]
I hate you
I cannot believe you got the lady the
lady who narrated sexy filthy boss
I
thought it was a poem were born
oh my God
hold on I need to get my music back up
[Music]
I don't have any tissue I ran out the
other day
ah
thank you if you just if you came in oh
Saloon I saw your red thank you we were
watching a video the one that was pinned
in the in the but you came in like right
as I saw Donna Burke so I couldn't I
couldn't say anything I was just like
perks in Diamond City
oh my God
[Music]
how did you how how do you do it every
year you guys are so crazy
oh my God I can't believe
it sounds so beautiful
[Music]
sorry about the left ear audio it's okay
let me know if you want Donna Burke's
voice yes please
oh my God oh my God can you I want to
use the I want to use her like
the pomu bound Express for Diamond City
Lights I want to use that I want to use
that I want that I want that she sounded
so good oh of course she did she's on a
burke oh oh
anyway hello people hello
it's my birthday
um
[Music]
thank you happy birthday poem I hope you
enjoyed the video we put together for
you you better have because it cost me
much
[Music]
I want the I want to turn the Puma
question to like my intro or something
I'll have eight minute long intro every
time every time before streaming
oh thank you
okay
yippee
before we do the the
um other Collins from Ian add I had one
if we were
[Music]
oh I can't believe paulu is now in the
same universe
how the hell oh thank you thank you
thank you thank you
I wanted to draw artwork today but since
I'm a failure shut up kimoy I want to
see your Arts please
no matter what it is even if it's
if it's done in Ms paint I want to see
it
okay I have a Colin
I have a call and I have a call and I'm
going to call them right now
let me make sure my audio is all good
okay
let me save their picture
it's so cute
[Music]
hello
I heard that she's so cute
look at you but you're cute
I was looking I was looking so closely
at your mouth and like uh her mouth is
so cute and her eyes are so cute
and everything about you so cute
happy birthday happy birthday yo we're
so close in terms of birthdays right
yeah well yours was just last week and
now we're talking like weekly now so I
guess that means next week we have to
talk again oh yeah okay all right back
to your channel we'll just alternate
yeah wherever whatever whatever
as long as we're together
that video was so funny I didn't know
that lady I mean I mean generally I
don't know like the other stuff she does
but the train voice I recognize Stan
yeah she does the shinkansen wow she
also does a lot of like metal gear songs
and ah songs yeah she she did a song for
one of the games and ah yeah and she
also did like the voice of like a race a
robot how do you how do you get a job
like you know voicing a shinkansen
actually she has like a video where she
explains it I watched it once it's like
the person who did it before her sounded
really similar to her and they keep just
hiring more people that sound similar to
each other they can Gaslight us I think
it hasn't changed except that this
person is eternally forever speaking
these lines exactly so when they get a
new lot like a new stop they have to
like
they have to have them re-record like
record it and then oh yeah right so they
only record the one station or like
everything oh
I would think everything because
otherwise it stands out weirdly oh yeah
they're like tone has changed or
something yeah yeah
that's the same person it can it sounds
so different no yeah no I agree
especially if it's been like what if
they don't make one for like five years
and then you'll yeah yeah man I wish I
wish actually that was something I've
had in my mind every once in a while
like oh wouldn't it be cool if like I I
could like voice train the English lines
of Japanese trains no I believe I
believe that I believe in a hello live
train takeover and then yo that would be
cool
and then and then you guys take over
if we take over the trains will you take
over the buses the taxis
wait but there's no voices and taxes you
mean you replace the taxi drivers yeah
yeah it's like Crazy Taxi but crazy Ian
oh oh cool idea
[Laughter]
wow wow wow Pomo
yes
I have written a poem for you no wait
was that what your Tweet was about ah
you saw it
yes I wrote actually I wanted to you
know write lyrics for a quick birthday
song for you but then I realized that
maybe you don't have audio stock perms
because I always use instrumentals for
from audio stuff oh so I thought maybe
Bella without audio so now it's a poem
it's more it's more personal okay I
guess so yeah honestly it's this way I
could put more feelings into it oh I'm
gonna turn off the audio okay I wanted
to ask you that yes yes
it's um it's it's a it's a whole story
okay okay
so
here is my poem to pomu
okay
you may think it's a poem poem
writing it in a chat
nice okay
once upon a time she strand
small fairy in big land
with just one wish in her hand
one day she will be real grand
little did she know over at that needs
you Sanji rainbow
there's a place she will learn to know
however far far away at another Bay
there was her destined love clear as day
glowing like a sunshine Ray
unable to touch this way
endlessly in the corporate Gray
time pass and the glass wall broke and
that what was their Eternal hope
became a common trope
pomeo and kiwawit soon to be
romantically wed
so against all the odds they fled
under the soft and cozy bed spread
now that we are finally free
I need to ask I go on my knee please
answer with we we pee pee Palmer will
you marry me oh
a thousand times yeah
I think I found my my calling oh my God
Chihuahuas spear
shake shake
[Laughter]
[Music]
I wasn't even planning to turn it into a
love story but it automatically became
that it's okay I understand it's how the
destiny happens you know yeah
oh my God I'm so proud to move when I'm
not I'm I'm even proud of you Pomo you
are now
old I know
I know just like me
together we're six hmm and you know in
German six is
um pronounced as sex oh um
I learned that I learned it yeah so if I
ever say sex I'm just saying six in
German
yes so wait you knew that before no I
knew I learned it from you that's why I
always feel very embarrassed when I have
to count in German you know in front of
my rewards oh of course well I don't I
always actually so you you write it with
um
s-e-c-h-s and in German the CHS turns
into an X kind of sound okay okay but if
you say it really carefully and really
slowly you would say sex oh
wow that was a little essential oh
really oh
wonderful
it's like oh my I feel my heart skip a
beat I think
come on please it wasn't supposed to be
like that
you know
um I I I I really I really am like
so happy that you exist it's because
like oh my God you know I don't know how
first like all happened but I don't
remember because my brain is jelly but I
was really happy to find out that there
is a a fairy in niji Sanji who likes me
oh my God what what so and then I look
at you and you're like the most adorable
girl ever you're so cute and you're so
likable you have such a great
personality you're so funny you're so
talented and then you're even drawn by
an artist that I really like so what the
hell like everything's falling into
place and I think it was Destiny and
yeah you know I love you no I
after I got off our call last week for
your birthday I was just like oh my God
I I was so like I was so nervous um I
felt like I didn't even get to like to
to like praise you enough and you know
what you are like the most hard-working
person ever at your soul you put a
hundred and actually no you put like a
thousand percent into literally
everything you do I've always been so
you know inspired you know you you are
streaming queen and I I want to I look
up to you so much for that and you know
how you are a real Idol like you I want
I oh [\h__\h]
no I don't know you are you are
you're so yeah see that was another
thing that I felt like a connection
because you know we're both kind of into
idols and storms
just goes so much harder than mine I
feel like yeah I I
I am inferior what
no I'm saying though and we
yeah yeah I keep it simple you know I
keep it no I think hello Pro is not
simple at all there's so many groups
I don't know I guess we when I was hello
project otaku actively I guess everybody
just focused more on copying the
choreographies even in the audience yeah
yeah yeah and then so the otage is more
simple but you just dance really hard
that's so fine though
I don't know I don't know how long these
calls are supposed to be at your at your
place oh it's okay uh I have more time
for Ian later so Paul you know what you
should do what
show my video from last time I was just
about
the song say last year I asked if qawwa
could come onto my stream and I
um it unfortunately didn't happen
for whatever reason yeah for you know
but I'm really happy I'm so so happy
that you could come today and I could go
to your birthday last week I'm so I'm so
happy that yeah it's possible do you
still have the video I do
you too yeah I kept it of course boy rid
of it
I don't even I don't remember at all
what I said anymore I have to find where
I saved it though but I actually saw it
not too long oh no I found it I found it
oh my God oh my God do you want to be on
call while I wait how would I I I will I
will I think I will leave okay because
otherwise it will be difficult to watch
um
but yeah I just I just want to say for
the future I hope we can do more stuff
together so that I can be less awkward
and nervous around you yes yes yes yes
have a great birthday I love you goodbye
thank you
she's gone okay yeah I have the video
from last year actually
let me play that real quick
um and I have another video also uh give
me a second to hear all
even though she's so cute that I want to
keep her there
thank you thank you thanks for showing
up I know you're so busy thanks for all
the donos you guys they're they're sorry
that they were behind her head I really
really appreciate them though thank you
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you
um
I'll read all the messages after the
stream probably when I have more time
because I see a lot of you guys are
writing a lot
everything okay let's see Chihuahuas
video from last year uh give me a second
I gotta set it up
uh wait why isn't it showing up
obs
o
okay I want to hear it too
so I'm gonna put it right
here oh my face is fine
and uh
and let me make sure okay okay I turn
off so that you guys can't hear it or
you guys it doesn't double audio
output oh whoa that's me oh I think I
did the wrong thing uh oh
um I'm gonna draft there we go I don't
know if you guys heard that but I
accidentally did I messed up okay
okay I'm gonna play this
no
why surprise
[Music]
English can you guys hear it hello yeah
um I am just here to say
[Applause]
yeah
who is pomu from my point of view
besides everyone because everyone is
pomu obviously well from my point of
view Puma is very very hard working and
you make creative really creative
original contents that is really
entertaining I love watching your
streams
that's cute obviously adorable and sweet
and kind of charming oh literally every
positive word should be added to you and
I am proud of you for being a strong
promo so thank you for being Who You Are
I hope you're happy and healthy because
you deserve all the best I hope you have
a lovely birthday and get so much love
from everyone that you're drowning in it
literally yeah
[Music]
so let's go to an adult concert someday
yes
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
and then I have another birthday message
what time did I sit for Ian to come in
uh I think I have another hour yeah
so we should be okay we should be okay
double Wawa messages here I know right
lucky lucky lucky
okay and um
hold on I need some tea for the messages
I'm sorry for the donors the academos in
streamlabs I'm sorry you can't hear the
song but I I'm hearing it so thank you
so much thank you
okay and then my other which this one I
haven't watched yet
um told me not to watch it so the other
one I obviously watched because I was
like oh well I watched it later I was
like it's it's been a year ish so I I
should probably be able to I should be
able to watch this now the one with
Chihuahua so
so next is this one let me pull it up
oh
who's that
[Music]
she's back from the dead stay dead damn
it
[Laughter]
OMG I know her yeah right
I wish I didn't no I'm just kidding
Okay let's listen to Minar
her uh her uh uh her video actually it's
three minutes okay her video from the
dead
rain puff oh wait I can't hear it hold
on stop talking Nina
God oh can you imagine oh my gosh I wish
I had a button that I could just stop
make her stop talking anytime oh this is
this is perfect actually I can I can
just get her to shut up
I think rain Puff
usually on occasions like this I would
say the pleasure is all mine it's not
but I would like you to know that I
derive absolutely no pleasure from
interacting with you I know any way
shape or form me too
today is your birthday yeah which is a
day meant to celebrate you
and she's not going to
yeah okay
celebrate you
well you know a birthday is also a day
where you realize that you will one day
eventually die and I hope this birthday
as you're getting older and older you
come to realize that death
is coming for you baby okay you too
though girl knowing my love speak for
yourself your luck we will most likely
die together on the same day but if we
do I hope you die very early in the
morning and I die very late at night
um so that I may finally be freed from
the clutches of you
um no I'll be out of here first I will
have the peace first still
[Music]
um
thinking of you
not just on your birthday
still talking about you so obsessed with
not just behind your back and I hope
that this birthday is a really really
good one finally for you since I won't
be here to annoy you although I mean
hopefully this message finds you unwell
and bothers you and annoys you it is
absolutely
not that I'm trying to you know be
purposely annoying to you or anything
it's just I'm naturally like this you
know oh we know and uh yeah I'm looking
forward to this stuff that you're doing
I saw your poster where you used my
likeness so I am looking forward to
seeing what you come up with and uh just
know that I'm watching and I am cheering
you on and uh I love you
strangely enough oh I know
I hope you have an amazing birthday
wishes filled with lots of
uh fun and as you have fun for your bro
oh sorry what's that
what is this oh hi oh what is this I
hope you have such an amazing birthday I
have to go have some food with your wife
um so yeah I wish you were there with us
because I wish you could see your wife
having a date with a real woman and
having a fun good time with me uh but
you'll just have to know in your heart
I'm turning this off
um thank you Nina for your message I'm
just kidding we'll finish
art that we are currently having The
Best Time Ever uh enjoy your birthday
bye
bye make sure you spoil her everybody so
she doesn't cry while I'm out having
Korean food with Elyria Pandora and not
just in my imagination okay
happy birthday
um every day that you live
Angels Cry and you
deserve to
die
bye bye
oh well I thoroughly hated that
[Laughter]
maybe we should have watched this first
so I could have the palette cleanser
that is kiwawa
oh my goodness
not for taking the time before you left
to to to to do the video for me thank
you thank you
oh my goodness
you share a birthday with my dog oh my
God birthday to your dog your dog is
Palmer
Chop Suey yeah
the Angels cool cry you deserve to die
she could have gone a little harder with
that she should have committed to the
bit not gonna lie
thank you thank you Mom thank you
I'm so good for you
um
happy birthday
thank you thank you thank you
proud to say you are my Oishi I'm
delicious
hahaha
ah
yay I have uh other em people coming in
um later so uh they'll be on
later later
happy birthday Saucy Bobo okay I saw
your video I saw it with the suit with
this song with the with Armstrong's
voice actor I saw it earlier
and I realized a thing I've been saying
your name wrong this whole time
avocado
it was so awesome though thank you
you're like yeah I'm jakato and I'm just
like what the hell
I'm saying jacado like potato potato
avocado potato potato you know Armstrong
wished a happy birthday yeah it was
since
it's like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] money
[Music]
[Applause]
her name is jacado now
thanks mod
thank you mod
yeah he was just like a low Saucy poem
I love how people just get cameos of of
of metal gear voice actors for my
birthday and it never gets old for me
it's my favorite thing in the world keep
them coming
keep on coming baby
who let Tomodachi speak yeah get out of
here actually don't there's a lot of
people here I need I need the mod help
probably
um yeah
now what
maybe I should have done the Collins
earlier actually what if I just scooch
everything up an hour and then I can end
earlier
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
I need time to finish my gift oh okay
you're all good you're off time probably
add more time to Goose goose duck yeah
maybe
[Music]
actually my throat is like all messed up
I can't stop at editing
I don't know why
I just noticed the cake it doesn't look
delicious
I love strawberry cake
and I mean it is cake for sure
it is cake four
sure
I take a bit um
take a little a little bite
oh
the key cards cake yeah
my throats mess up too I know
I'm still thinking about cars from last
night I know
I want to watch it again honestly
last night I did a countdown and Kaz and
ocelot and some people from from from
mother base saying happy birthday to
me
um
I love cake
yeah what kind of cake I I think I
actually have some cheesecake in the
fridge
um what kind of cake do you guys like
though
what's your favorite kind of cake I
really like I like any cake with
with
oh wait I have my my cup okay I think I
said cupcake yesterday but it's literal
cake in a cup it's not like a cupcake I
just realized that's probably really
confusing
it's cake and a cup cheesecake
[Music]
um yellow cake
really lemon blueberries yes
yes yes
today's my friend Brendan Welsh birthday
tool he doesn't watch YouTubers
oh okay I'll sing it like really crazy
Marvin
Murphy
okay Brendan Welsh
Brendan Welsh thank you so much for
being such a dedicated YouTuber fan
you're the biggest weeaboo I know
um
uh I'll speak
um I'll speak to you
um in a language that you would
understand so konichiwa Brendan Welsh
um anata no tanjobi
is today Destiny
um I will sing to you the greatest of
songs
from your Oshie pomeran Puff
I'm sorry you're I shouldn't say Oshi
you're senpai
Brandon well
happy birthday
I hope that found you well and um
arigato
[Music]
be there here to celebrate all three of
your birthday oh wait that's a different
one oh my gosh wait I'm losing track
sadly I couldn't show you my Namaste
snake for Diamond city lights that Anime
Expo I hope
World chaos reverse World chaos wasn't
too yakai for you never nothing is too
yakai for me thank you
thank you thank you
nihongo Jojo
gracias
very much
yeah maybe we should stop celebrating my
birthday and instead celebrate Brandon
Welsh's how about that
how how about that
maybe we should yeah yeah
happy birthday Pomo thank you
thank you
[Music]
July 12th is officially Brandon Welsh
day it's true
yeah let's go Brandon Welsh whoa it's
his birthday
[Laughter]
I kind of want to go get my cupcake my
cake in a cup do you guys mind if I go
get a cake in a cup
happy birthday Brandon oh even from
kiwawa
I wish kiwawa would say happy birthday
to me I'm just kidding
I got the double Chihuahua birthday
I'll make one too okay cool
get the cake cup okay I'll be like two
seconds hold on
[Music]
okay I'll be like two two seconds
I'm just gonna run for it okay I'm gonna
run I'm gonna be like
and then I'll be back and I'll be like
[Music]
that okay all right I'll be right back
laughs
[Music]
oh I didn't mute
I'm back I'm back
I'm back I'm back with my cup cup cake
in a cup
oh
I was saying earlier I like any cake
that has a cream cheese frosting
you know that is the best that is like
the only acceptable frosting not gonna
lie
[Music]
I don't know who this Brandon Welsh is
but uh happy birthday from another
Brandon well
who also happens to be celebrating is
wait
what
no way is it you
two of them
huh
liquid Brandon
hey
um
that was just frosting but it tasted
good so I don't care
[Music]
we're already playing Goose goose duck
right I want to play Goose goes duck
with chat one day but I think I don't
know if you I
if there's a way to turn off the but the
part of it is the proximity chat
I think we would have to have I don't
think we could do it because we'd have
to have the talking one
hello
oh the chat break
come back to
practice I'm lonely
come back to me
maybe a week oh there we go
um
I might tell people to come in in like a
half hour instead I'm gonna update my
schedule
happy birthday
thank you thank you all righty let's see
Collins all day 6 30.
and we'll go to
7 30.
and then we'll play Goose goose duck at
7 30. I just want as many people to come
play as possible because
we have people a lot of people oh well
we might not even have a full room I
don't know
okay
save my updated schedule but it's really
only for me to follow
[Music]
oh I'm covering it
thank you
[Music]
back out
the donuts help a lot
because
I'm not gonna lie guys
the cover was really expensive
I paid for all of it myself because you
know I'm not going to ask anybody to pay
for
a project that I come up with
and instead of buying a car
I paid for this cover
thank you very much
[Laughter]
for the donations I really appreciate it
my current car still works so it's okay
hmm
[Music]
um
you
thank you thank you
[Music]
I don't know oh gosh this is so awkward
I'm so sorry I think because last year I
had things that I was doing like out of
schedule right like if you watched my
birthday last year I like I got a tattoo
I had to have like a little bucket list
of stuff that I went and did and it was
you know it was easier because I like
had a schedule but now I'm just kind of
sitting here like twiddling my thumbs
like
I'm just kind of like la la
[Music]
you know
well you got a birthday tattoo yeah last
year on stream you can check it out
you can check it out
yeah just search Pomo rainbow
birthday
2022 actually let me see if I'm home
rainfall's birthday 2022.
[Music]
no it doesn't show up
PP birthday 2022. now repeat birthday
2023. a real one
yeah on stream I um very real tattoo
that I drew myself
still on my back probably but everyone
always forgets when I when they do fan
art they always forget that I have my
tattoo there
yeah that's so peculiar okay
have it updated in my I should or I
should have it updated in my um
in my
uh official art official you know
you should get it removed this year
oh wait I can show you a picture of it
um
oh here it is
this is my really real
official tattoo that I got done on my
birthday
last year
[Music]
[Applause]
that's my back and I got it drawn I did
it I tattooed it myself so I couldn't
really see you know what I'm saying
I couldn't really see because I'm like
holding the pen like trying to reach
it's like washing your back you know
it's really hard and I couldn't really
see it
um it's a lira if you couldn't I mean
you can obviously tell but um it's a
lira
as my top back tattoo
oh what if I got one of koalas here
Chihuahua back tattoo
or kiwawa can go on my butt
my butt cheeks are her boobs probably
because she's got a really big chest
um
and then the lower back above my butt
cheeks can be like her face you know
and then my whole butt can be her like
shirt and her her
boobs
[Music]
best idea
[Laughter]
I vote for her oily thighs oh
he did tweet about that didn't she
stamp wait what's that
I would be honored with a [\h__\h] stamp
oh oh
oh it's like a lower back tattoo yeah
but mine like goes okay I'm seeing a lot
of stuff I really need to see it today
um
um no okay hold on I'm gonna dry I'm
gonna draw it okay
I'm gonna draw it give me a second
thank you
[Music]
let me Crop this right quick
all right I'm gonna draw this for you
guys
actually let me make this
[Music]
I almost click stop stop streaming
okay so
so here's me and my butt
right okay
I got that hourglass figure y'all
and there's my butt
and they touched
the the cheeks do touch this is
um uh images
okay
it's just an image it's not real life
okay Meiji this
I have my
okay
so okay let me pull up a picture of
kiwawa
takanashi
[Music]
okay and so her face would be here right
right
[Music]
um
got a neck
and then there's her shoulders go out so
she's kind of wide she might be a little
wide sorry my ass is just too big okay
but then it goes down to the cleavage of
my butt okay like so okay actually a
little lower
okay
and um
like so
it's kind of Genius
right it's kind of genius oh I should
give her hair shouldn't I
um
[Music]
you guys like it
so far so good right so far so good
and um
oh she's got her little like
oh stop it
got her Little Neck
[Music]
she's got some green in her hair
like that she's got her hat
yeah so that's how the tattoo would be
does that count as a [\h__\h] stamp I don't
know
does that count
all right two hats
how could I forget the other one
like that
it would oh man
oh man
but that's kind of the gist of it you
know
I allow anybody to get this
it's kind of a genius idea so
if anybody wants
this tattoo
um
it is trademarked I've already I've just
submitted the patent for it
but um
I allow you to use this
no thanks
what do you mean no thanks
you were perfectly good tattoo idea and
then you would like go to the pool and
people be like whoa
people would start flirting with your
butt probably
look out soon to work
[Music]
#art of ass
you should get a Pomo version of that I
don't think I'm big enough
I'm big enough
am I allowed to use this trademark
tattoo person
um
what it sounds
don't let your dreams be dreams no it's
gonna be a Pomo version there should be
an inner version and a milli version
um
uh Anna and Emily version
okay
I'm gonna do Colin soon
at everyone
I feel so bad because I've been adding
everyone so recently lately I'm sorry
two at everyone
I'm moving my call-ins
a little early earlier
um feel free to come in
uh together if you want
and then
uh in about one hour we will play Goose
game
oh I didn't set up foogie or anything
let me do that real quick
uh
oh
or Discord there we go that should work
mm-hmm
okay wait does it work
uh
I don't know
why didn't I set this up before
streaming I'm an idiot
I'm so stupid
uh
oh no
I
think I'm gonna Smith
oh gosh
[Music]
thank you are you doing a rainbow thing
oh
please let me put me out of my misery
please
oh yeah I think
where's the stuff
for the discords
[Music]
all right here
uh I want them
we'll do
horizontal
uh why is there could I not sneeze
oh if we want
am I horizontal not yet
okay soon
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday oh [\h__\h] whatever my tweet
uh metal is solidus liquid is
um possibly in the future gaseous
I mean a snake
happy birthday YouTube
[Music]
I just want to say that um I did not go
to Korean food
um that was against my own will I was
just as shocked as you were when I came
up on the screen I was like huh I think
she gaslit you oh I found it okay maybe
I am eating right now are you yeah I had
Korean barbecue at this moment you might
be
do you have an annoying person around
you
I live with my brothers
yes oh no
Mina has been your brother this whole
time
oh my God don't say that
no
imagine Nina playing hockey game
obsessed with the NHL how Canadian of
her
oh [\h__\h] why does it work
[Music]
wait yeah Ellie wait that means you
kissed your brother
oh
um don't okay never mind are we we
retconned this we're getting past this
all right yeah anyway we're getting this
happened out the window oh yes how has
your birthday been it's been fun I've
just been hanging out yay how's your
birthday been
oh well my birthday's been pretty good
um
I watched your video
watched I can't believe the [\h__\h]
audio book person for the sexy filthy
boss
spoke to you that was definitely a
highlight
s
truly I that was probably the last thing
I expected
well if she had like a cat how do you
want can you just hire her for freelance
maybe maybe
she we gotta get her to read fanfic
no we have to get her to read
the dirtiest book of all time oh the
dirtiest story ever written right you're
right yeah oh my God I don't I don't
know that might be it
that might get us a little oh
oh I get a little hot and steamy yeah
oh my God I hope oh I want her to read
that and then you do voice Act
the worker in the store
okay
you know when she's like where are your
where are your largest melons what are
your largest mountains no that's the
lady
right here
foreign
[Laughter]
oh I'm probably very quiet like always
hi actually you sound you're showing up
oh I have you at 200 and that's probably
why yeah that's probably but you know
what what works works yeah
suddenly loud oh [\h__\h]
you were like
always crying
my bad
yeah I don't know what to do for
birthdays alera
I don't know either I'm watching your
stream as reference for what I'm gonna
do don't watch me
I don't know what to do oh I gotta
change my Twitter icon I forgot I have
to put the ribbon on
oh yeah oh wait you don't have to do
that you'll lose your check mark
I don't have a check mark anymore I have
nothing to lose
that's so sad that is so sad oh I have
to not press use this Frame
I think
if I press use this Frame
it's just gonna use the frame and my
icon will be gone that's what I did last
night I saw that's so funny you're just
so white space I was like oh yeah it'll
just because it's a PNG you just think
it's gonna fit on top of it
it did not everybody don't you have to
put it on top of your picture and like
Photoshop or something
I don't
what how do you do it
you don't have to put it on in Photoshop
you just have to make sure that the icon
that shows up like you have to make sure
that the website has your current
Twitter icon set
oh the webs I don't know that website
it's like the icon
yeah
oh
now I have it hi oh my God
[Music]
day
earlier I'm excited to hear you in the
cover later
I'm not yeah
I'm I'm so excited I'm so excited I'm so
excited I'm so excited for everybody to
see you you did so much work oh my God
you're crazy you're crazy every year
nah
yeah
I heard you I heard what you said no
when you were like no thanks guys I no I
no I heard what you said no you didn't
I heard what the hell
it's okay
no it's not I wanted to
you're insane
last year yeah last year I got a tattoo
you got this year too
well that was the concept art oh I see
it works for you too
just put your face on there I thought
you meant on my ass so
well I was watching you draw it though I
had to look up your I was looking up
your character reference because I was
like I needed to know if that mole I
needed to know if that mole was drawn by
you
I was like there's no way but I had to
look it up in your reference sheet to
make sure if it was there or not because
I was like no only Petra has her butt
out yeah I was I was literally about to
say only like the only member I know has
their butt out is Petra yeah so there
was I was like no way
oh
happy birthday
to you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
[Applause]
oh did you make a wish did you make a
wish make a wish oh oh
a
day day
[Music]
hi happy birthday thank you
I hope you've been having a really good
birthday so far I love you I love the I
was gonna say I love your cake and I
realized that there is cake on top of
the cake and then I felt weird
oh my gosh yeah see that rump
it's
a show stealer honestly I can't stop
looking at it
it's highlighted too yeah it's got like
a
power to it oh yeah
the entire time you were saying that I
was just staring straight at it like I
wasn't trying to it just kind of might I
kept getting drawn back to it every time
I
am I set up I'm just like wow that's
that's a rump that is certainly
something my hopes my lovely lady lumps
oh God oh my goodness
oh shoot you got those apples oh hi Kell
it's kyungus thank you
thank you
bird
s
[Laughter]
[Music]
you don't know you ever seen those
videos where it's like no sing happy
birthday but only say birthday
boxes
laughs
[Laughter]
look at look at this guy it's my
birthday
oh the birthday party oh yeah yeah here
I'll send it to people too okay this is
why we're referencing you guys
how do I oh oh yeah of course of course
it's a guy with the shirt that has a
binary on it
[Laughter]
this is the tech talk oh that's a
YouTube short just kidding this is the
YouTube short oh but it's a repost of a
tick tock so you're not wrong okay yeah
let's hope the tick tock all YouTube
shorts are they really are yeah yeah
they are controversial take not mine
though I mean it's it's kind of factual
not my take but like
do you guys ever think about the fact I
mean you've probably seen this posted
somewhere but like the fact that getting
sung happy birthday to you is like an
unskippable cut scene in real life yeah
you can shorten it
I mean by only singing birthday no it's
this it's the same way it's just it's
just more quiet oh yeah oh okay you're
right it's not shorter oh actually maybe
it's a little shorter because you take
off the 2u at the end
right oh I'm gonna wait like two seconds
and then go
yeah
or if you consider like the down time to
not like be separate cutscenes
skip
yeah mean median and mode you know
what
okay
have you ever played frog detective no I
saw you play it though I feel like this
is like the equivalent to book fables to
doppio now uh-oh I feel like I need to
let everyone know what it is what it's
like you know it looks it looks really
interesting I'm kind of I'm kind of
curious about this about this frog game
okay
um uh this is your pitch you're on Shark
Tank go alright happy birthday promo
recipient's first name pomu gift message
oh this is not a good very good pitch
that's that's all he needs so
if have you ever thought about the
second best detective in town
um it's basically like Edgeworth and
Phoenix where the Frog detective is like
Rivals with the lobster detective
because they never interact oh
but yeah
oh
I'm sorry I'm sorry that I happened to
yawn during your description of the game
that probably sounded really rude
where's the yowie then
please
[Music]
hey what kind of restaurant there's
there's something that might develop
around I'll have whatever he's having
the third game is that what you said
each of the games are like an hour
though oh that's fine yeah it's like
gotten a ban ban
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
okay happy birthday pomu did you really
send it
yeah
no she gave me oh my God you received a
gift
yeah I like this game yeah
I think this likes to do this game it's
like a calling I think you're uh look at
your bottoman and the first comment is
probably the most shuyamino game ever
you were right it might be
it's great it's amazing yeah oh my gosh
yes yeah
like this yeah oh my gosh wait you be
like that that would be amazing and the
Frog detective
honestly it'll be so good it would be it
would be frog bird
wait are the other ones
oh yeah they're all on sale
if you like the first one you should
play the rest okay
yeah well that's the pitch everybody
[Laughter]
yeah the most true Amino game ever yep I
feel like I understand everything there
is to know about the game from that once
more I think I feel like that too right
like yeah I'm gonna add it to my
schedule even the graphic the graphics
honestly I was just thinking about my
schedule to one
hahaha
the graphics and frog detective really
do seem like they were based on
shuiimino's drawings you know like it
looks very very much like something
it's a great art style
gifted by Shu yamina Wednesday the 26th
26 okay
oh my gosh definitely a game of all time
it is for sure it's
it is a game of all it is a game
do you like it then alira
um
oh I think you have to you have to be
prepared to read a lot oh that's all I
have to tell you oh [\h__\h] I'm screwed you
have to be prepared no but it's just the
whole thing yeah okay
so is Phoenix right okay that's that's
true too yeah Phoenix mucho texto so
real yeah
and a lot of other games well yeah but
you just have to be ready that day to
read a lot
in two weeks yes yes
give my two weeks notice that I'm ready
yeah
the day before we have Salem
oh no but in that game you don't really
talk right
what can we RP when we play Salem
absolutely I think you have well
is it wait are you are you even supposed
to have VC for that game
oh I'm supposed to be well the first one
was text based but that's because it was
just like a I'm pretty sure you could
play it well the problem before
difficult you could but like the whole
point was that if you your your identity
can't be
what do you call it discovered oh boy
yeah yeah yeah so if somebody's typing
too loudly and you hear them typing it's
like oh
[Laughter]
crab game because like every time we
would make a Lobby randos would join
because he couldn't just have a Lobby of
just us yeah
well we played it one other time and it
we actually played it did we yeah I
wasn't there then I wasn't there I don't
know if you were there but I remember
like
ogre killed like half the map or
something and said like oh that's the
that's Fame right probably oh
yeah maybe I remember he killed it and
like
I don't know if it was like
I don't know there was some one letter
that was funny though remember that
it's all muted yeah
you might be able to find
oh yeah it was fair and it was fun yeah
yeah yeah I used to play town of Salem
with my friends and we'd all go into
separate rooms but oh my God typing it
was over for you just type in all chat
I'm at my friend's place I heard them
typing at night
get their ass
you could say though you could be like
oh I heard someone so typing and gas but
it was uh oh
and then you switch out your keyboard to
a different keyboard oh you'd be like
you thought I had this clicky key
switches well look
that's not what is oh my gosh I just
opened like three things on my computer
oh
I was like oh this is a different
keyboard so it can't be me
yeah oh my God he's the Frog Detective
oh
yeah I'll look at look through my
magnifying glass and I'll see who did
The Killing
oh that's a part of the game
I Framed Roger Rabbit
that's a great movie it is
such a good movie I saw like I remember
the I remember the first time I saw that
movie it freaked me out like the way the
the way that like the guy got ran over
by a steamroller and then he was like a
pancake man and he stood back up I was
like it's weirdly like freaky but very
good
[Music]
she is
but like the like the like Twitter
Anatomy crowd like the people who are
like um where are her organs none of
them speak when Jessica Rabbit is on
screen no one no no no one can dare word
against us
yeah isn't she a rabbit
no she's just married to Roger Rabbit
Oh that's oh yeah yeah it reminds me of
a wee look oh
what look at her that's the compliments
that's too high of a compliment I
remember when we went on the run a
little bit ride oh my God yeah
yeah so which one yeah it was fun it was
so silly it was I think I liked waiting
in line
for that line is nice I took your Disney
yeah yeah there's a Roger Rabbit ride at
Tokyo Disney oh I had no idea
I believe I had no idea I've been on it
so many times I've never been to that
Disney it's pretty oh yeah
the weight is usually very short because
it's in the kids section yeah because
they're not there and kids who what kids
know Roger Rabbit these days none that's
why the line's so short because all the
kids are waiting four hours to go on
Beauty and the Beast oh I know oh my
gosh
in the in the in the real juice right
juice yeah yeah I have kids in that line
the biggest scap oh sorry one time there
was like this like kitty ride where you
were supposed to row a boat
I rode like so terribly as a kid that I
was splashing the ryajes behind me
there's like a at Disney City there's a
Toy Story ride it's the biggest scam
ever it has the longest weight all the
time it's always like a four hour wait
like the Beauty and the Beast one but
it's oh yeah it's like the you guys
remember the or do you know the Buzz
Lightyear ride
um in the Florida one where you shoot
the actual it was like Men In Black too
you shoot the actual aliens and like
you're going around and
oh I think so I think so yeah yeah yeah
but instead it's all just screen
from one screen
oh I hate uh
yeah well the Naruto one moved more than
this one this one barely there's a
Naruto one
yeah
funny that's awesome who's dead
or something or yeah yeah you shoot the
kunai again oh yeah
here comes the man no dressed in blue
seize this I will allow I will allow out
of those words because it's her birthday
happy birthday Paul move thank you
do you let all of us call him the man of
sex too yeah
it's a birthday like it's a birthday
it's my birthday wish I'm trying to
think of the people that have that have
yet to out of those words
I think it's like in the single digits
at this point I'm gonna I'm gonna ring
see why everyone remember
the glass is half full I'm gonna need
you to shut up
see how full the glass is you know the
appreciation wait sure have you said it
the man of sex
well he asked now
I definitely have probably I could hear
the sonic boom from how little you're
hesitated there
I I need I need to find I need to find
the original man of sex meme uh because
I have it saved yeah
the man of sex oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
today it's just that like I remember
once when Vox was looking for it and he
spent like a good 15 minutes because he
couldn't find it where did this one come
from there it is
I made it uh so it's a I didn't make the
original screenshot so it's a screenshot
from TF2 where you can see the outline
of a spy through a building and his
health bar is there and it just says the
man of sex and it has that song playing
and so I just kind of but I I don't know
why I felt just this this carnal urge to
put Ike Eveland over it and like I think
I was like hey guys
spam this meme to get like out of jail
[Laughter]
posted that the day that I got on jail
so it worked it's no I got unjailed
before he posted this oh yeah I remember
debut oh did you oh I remember playing
Tetris on stream and then
go
yeah I was gonna say like just like yeah
Elon so I was gonna say Elon saw the
meme and let you go but then I remember
this is so long ago this is previews
yeah
oh my God
I'm gonna oh I hate that the people
before Elon was like did you say the
people
like Evelyn
yeah
we still don't know why now we're in PP
now we're in PP wait
oh
yeah pomo's present
wait present present gonna fight Mark
Zuckerberg
oh yeah
have you seen that Mark Zuckerberg is
[\h__\h] ripped now yeah my dad was
telling me how he does like fighting
like actually in his free time he's been
doing fighting for a while let me send
you a picture let him cook when I when I
first saw this image of Mark Zuckerberg
I legitimately thought it was like deep
faked it's actually it's 100 it's real
it's real look at this I saw the other
day and I was like sorry the hell is
happening
oh
he's being trained by actual UFC
fighters yeah yeah he's he's in like UFC
fighting like in his free time
yeah how's Elon doing elon's gonna get
[\h__\h] destroyed
I'm like I don't know my dad was telling
me how like apparently Elon also hired
like a trainer to help him this is
actually happening
is it actually out of my dad's
gaslighting me or not he's that kind of
guy you know billionaire I mean I can
speak from experience you know it's like
it's like when people when someone hires
a personal trainer they don't always
necessarily get to the same level that
other people get to right I feel like
Elon might have hired one but he's not
sticking to the diet like he's not
really getting to the right level with
it he's too chronically online he is
he's spending too long on [\h__\h]
Twitter everybody Zuck doesn't actually
use social media that much the most he's
done recently is like Beyond threads but
I feel like he's only doing that at the
beginning to kind of give the platform
some wings and then he's going to kind
of clear off because he doesn't give a
[\h__\h] training his fingers
um no like elon's just gonna like
verbally be rude to Mark to the point
where he just makes Mark just like cry
or something memes about him
pulled up a slideshow on his eyes
no no no because here's the thing Zuck
literally Zuck the name is a meme and
that's his official account name on
threads Elon Elon is Banning people who
are the instant Elon took over Twitter
he started battling who were making
parody accounts of him if anyone's gonna
cry at memes made about him it's Elon
like Zuck probably doesn't give a [\h__\h]
you know he probably has cried at this
point maybe oh maybe at some point for
me I think it's 50 50. listen I'll round
it off by saying I feel like it it could
go either way Zuck is clearly training
harder but if you've seen those pictures
of Elon Musk shirtless he's kind of
built like a jug of milk so I don't know
what that's going to be like you know
oh yeah
have you guys ever seen the movie Robots
you know uh what what is it the main
character
[Applause]
yeah
so Hub copper bottom the dishwasher is
built like Elon Musk
oh okay okay you really tied this back
together because I was up for one second
just like what this is the most out of
nowhere Segway of her talking about like
social media like Emperors duking it out
and then you know what this reminds me
of the 2005 animated movie Roblox
I mean look I've sent a picture of
shirtless Elon and I've sent a picture
of Hub copper body you can see the
comparison cut here wait is this real uh
cause shirtless Elon don't even look
human like be foreign
he really doesn't it's like everyone
makes the jokes about about Zuck being
uh being a lizard but I think he looks a
lot more human than Elon does I mean
look at like the size of his chest
relative to the size of his stomach it
shuts out so much I'm trying to build
like an alien too though oh yeah true
I like I like being um poor compared to
them you know I always thought I look
human well okay
okay oh bro I gotta race that one on the
back of my head poem you want me to die
this no well
um in Minecraft yeah Minecraft Okay
Minecraft they'll probably lose because
I just figured out how to actually hitch
it with the little timing bar I didn't
even know that was a thing until like
last week so oh all right I forgot about
that yeah
robots
robots you guys know that like they're
you know the red robot in that that's
voiced by Robin Williams yeah Bender
Fender yeah yeah did you like I wasn't
until way later when I went back to
watch the movie I think it was just a
fever dream when I was younger when he's
taking a bunch of invasive photography
of one of the characters and he just
leans it and goes give me big anime eyes
yeah that's a great scene
yeah he's a good character back in like
2005 when it was like really me she was
just like what was the script writer on
like the scriptwriter would must have
been like a really like
right
it's probably Robin Williams yeah
probably just him shooting off being
crazy
give me a big anime eyes
though I didn't realize the clip I sent
has a really bad [\h__\h] edit at the end
but it's kind of funny in its own way
oh my gosh anime eyes
that's not even the only anime reference
he's made in a role you know the movie
One Hour Photo yeah
yeah when he just can't who just there's
this um
this kid in a store he just goes oh Neon
Genesis Evangelion
he liked that he liked anime though yeah
yeah I think like oh that's cool they're
talking about an angel though and just
like yeah that's the hero so he must
have like been suffering on the outside
when they did that just like I don't
know about that
he was a gamer too yeah isn't his
daughter named Zelda his daughter yes he
is oh my gosh
so cute I always cry at that one ad when
he's talking about saving the princess
and she just goes dad are you confusing
me with the princess again and he just
goes hard to say you're both pretty
magical and I'm like
[Music]
it was the Ocarina of Time remake
because he he and his daughter grew up
playing that oh yeah
oh
on the 3DS yeah
anime no it's cool anime
let's go to the animation of the
Japanese variety
yeah
in 24 minutes per episode
oh good time
they don't make him like
yeah
conventions need to start doing
commercials again come on oh
I need like old con culture to come back
because I'm a sucker for Nostalgia you
want yowie paddles back yes I do
I saw a few that like they're they're
not like made out of like solid wood
anymore I think they're paper now they
have to be but like there was a few
during our meet and greets where I saw
the Yahweh paddles I'm like I feel at
home
ever become a thing why I don't know why
not an ore and was just like you know
what this reminds me of oh it's a pal
that just says oh yeah it's just a
paddle that says yowie on it it's been
one of those weeks pasta yowie yeah I
just need some Vampire Knight cosplayers
some auron cosplayers a little bit of
Homestuck and some yowie paddles and I'm
good
hahaha
I haven't watched most of those shows by
the way but I'm that's not like
expensive
you'll see him dying his skin gray for
the home stuff cosplay
[Laughter]
why does it only set off warning flags
when you win I said it you didn't say
anything
um
we all just collectively kind of blocked
it out but then it was sent too many
times
it goes a little into my brain like
to this guy I'm still not entirely sure
what Homestuck is me neither I had a
friend I had a friend who um I had a
friend who used to tell me about it like
obsessively when I I was I used I used
to go to a class with this guy and he
said his life is like so I've been out
of the watch on the show called
Homestuck and I was like oh the show no
it's not a show what the [\h__\h] he's like
I'm reading this thing I don't again I
don't know what it is and he just kept
talking about I was like yeah it's like
this thing where this thing does this
thing I actually cannot [\h__\h] remember
a single thing about it is because I
think the instantly started talking
about it I would just zone out instantly
maybe that's like a sleeper agent
response like as soon as I hear the word
Homestuck I just black out and I wake up
when they've stopped talking about it
hmm
about these kids buy this game and then
they're playing this game and then they
figure out that the game like can do
stuff in reality but then I think they
go a little too far and then it starts
corrupting their reality and they find
out that their reality is about to break
apart but then they find out that the
people who played the game before them
had that happen to them and there's like
this evil mastermind also who can like
who doesn't want the world to get reset
because he wants to take over the world
we're coming to theaters
2025.
so then the trolls are like the internet
game trolls and they're like trying to
help it's like I don't even know I
watched like a like a five hour
documentary about what the plot
it was like it was like yeah it was a
long like part by part and I still don't
that's the gist of what I got from it
that is way more than I knew before
though that moment yeah I I knew it was
about a game I knew it was about a game
I thought it was about getting sucked
into the game I thought it was like Log
Horizon or something no the game can
control their reality I think okay and
then Jumanji so it's like your thoughts
shape your reality
who are playing the game they're like
all internet friends who've never met
before or something and then they
um
it's like a butterfly effect but in a
video game
all I know is that Toby Fox used to
write some music for it he writes he
wrote one song called the baby is you
and then he snuck that song into the gym
battle for sword and shield wow
oh my God yeah megalovania began I
believe it was in like in like an
Earthbound thing and then next it was in
Homestuck and then it was in undertale
oh my god
wow and now it's in Smash
the most famous couple maybe it's the
way you're dressed
[Music]
oh yeah Patrick the first appearance of
megalovania is like so cosmically funny
in hindsight with how big of a phenomena
that song has become because I think
that the final boss of like where the
game that Toby made I think it was like
an Earthbound fan game
where there's this character that just
said something
which is like really problematic and
edgy but like it's the fact that right
after they say that you hear the first
ever appearance of megalovania that is
cosmically funny
foreign
specific image and I'm not sure why let
me let me let me let me send this I was
like when I played Earthbound I didn't
know that that one song was from
Earthbound
yeah I didn't know some Earthbound so
when I started when I was playing it I
was like hey it's that one song from
Tick Tock please tell me that your
entire chat with what yeah yes but then
everyone was like molding they're like
how did you think this was a tick tock
oh no you did the thing I remember you
did the Zoomer thing yeah I remember I
was watching that I was just like I
didn't know either that it was from
Earthbound so when it happened I was
like
it's that Meme song guys and everyone
was like please oh my God but why is it
a battle theme it's such a perfect theme
to express like what yeah
so good it was so fun
[Laughter]
started playing metal gear and this call
sound happened actually every day I hear
the metal gear like sound because so
many normies use it in YouTube videos
too we really all the time yeah yeah
that's true that's I hear it so often oh
like the surprise sounds
just have like folders from random IPS
that they just collect and they just
can't yeah
one more
it's like the variety show Japanese
variety show wow
[Music]
wow is that what it's from though of
Japanese variety show I don't know I
don't know that's what I imagined it is
the first time I ever heard it was in
fairy tale
oh sorry where are you going 90s
[Music]
people are saying fairy tale oh they say
this from fairy tale okay oh there you
go I think it is from fairy tale okay
[Music]
I don't even know
it's just so all over the place these
days
that's weird that sounds like that come
from games and stuff
an anime be like become part of Normie
culture yeah imagine being a normie and
then they're like oh this comes from
like a video game yeah released in 2000
and something something and then they'll
be like what are you talking about
the sound I hear on Tick Tock yeah I
know the Earthbound one really
looked me up
yeah every now and I don't hear myself
we're listening to some Tick Tock and
there'll just be some like random anime
OST in the background or sound effect
I'm like what the [\h__\h] my sister's
watching anime and then I'm looking at
some random meme videos
[Music]
like some some things just get get
adopted into like Normie things and
they're just like yeah this is thing
that exists I don't really know where
it's from or why it's in Japanese but it
it's in Japanese the the grand the grand
high of Might of tick tock have deemed
me deemed its Soul so therefore I will
be okay with it yeah I think that's what
happened with that like really
crappy illegal remix of tiny little
adamantium
I know I know you know the songs
that don't know what it's from what the
[\h__\h] exactly
happy birthday thank you
birthday
baby
[Music]
that's good I'm tired
oh shoot it's just started though
[Laughter]
Captain it's Wednesday
oh
can I see what were we talking about
that was me me
can I see Mimi though
oh yeah let me take a picture she's
she's like she's like I would like to
see the baby I would love to see the
baby
I say that to my cat all the time the
baby he just doesn't know it I would
like to see the baby and he's like well
what baby you talking about where
Patrick my check
huh you guys ever heard of um the time
when Steven Spielberg said like
konichiwa Steven Spielberg does
I think you sent me that once I love
that clip I just thought it I don't know
why I started thinking about it again it
was really talking about Japanese just
like one of my Japanese animes huh all
right birthday girl happy birthday
oh my God
[Laughter]
the first one is like hey what's this
the second one she's like squint and
like
side eye bombastic side eye
bombastic
criminal offensive side eye
yeah it's like
you was she's so cute she's so cute have
you ever shown your viewers sir
yeah but staff private in the Stream
what I do what whoops
you have to protect Mimi
protection
she's too cute honestly I know we have
to preface
she looks nasty yeah
remember that last picture that I sent
what she did to her own bed in my studio
yeah
wait the first wow was known from a
parodius the parody of gradius
the wow seriously the wow it's a video
game that's so long ago
parodius I know that game that has bunny
girls in it
mm-hmm
[Music]
the game about
it's a shmup right or it's like a it's a
gradius you know
uh oh yeah yeah oh I see I see but it's
parodies because it's a parody of it a
parody oh wow they just colored that
it's funny yeah
all right where's the wow sound effects
Now gradius by Adam Yeah Yeah by animals
wow yeah but anime oh there it is oh my
god wow that was nice
Australia's female voice best known for
fairy tale wow sound
oh wow
the chat all all the new correct
incorrectly that's where it comes from
well they did the they did that from
Tick Tock they did that's from fairy
tales oh my God you're right everybody
have no idea what's so funny where does
the high quality version come from this
is so compressed
oh yeah I don't know I guess I guess
someone went to the recording studio and
they're like oh can I can I use that
yeah
maybe someone who worked on fairy tale
like worked on this game or something
and or knew someone and wanted to use
the sound they still had it yeah they
stole the sound
a parody game
I was like wow
you know that was pretty cool
[Music]
every time you do that
what every time you do that he throws me
off so much I don't think about it like
I do it sometimes like entirely you're
just deflated balloon involuntarily I'll
just be doing something and then just
kind of
[Music]
oh this one's Super Nintendo
oh
wow oh no what happened to him just
spooky magicing images
it looks like a World of Warcraft gnome
wait I want to see what Mimi looks like
how dare you ruin the integrity
oh no
in your own birthday I'm sorry
it's freaking lost that right it's fine
it's a funny dog
[Laughter]
me and the boys after after consuming
the [\h__\h] the the spite of us meal
from Burger King I should have said that
picture dang it
now as well
Dunkin Donuts
they have like I think it's Duncan
although I might be I'm pretty sure it's
Duncan and actually I can't find any
results maybe it's not Duncan hang on
I thought I said Bobby
[Laughter]
these are some for these are some pretty
adorable Donuts I like these oh it's
blue oh my God he's so cute
this is this is great at all when are
they gonna do the Krispy Kreme
Oppenheimer meal
never team Barbie why I'm seeing both
they both look amazing guys look at this
okay why shouldn't they do that kind of
meal I think it would be the bomb
because Barbie
clothes
what did I say
it's okay it's fine
yeah ah
that was so cute
oh they have a whole cake
that's so extra ice cream cake
oh that's good
wait are there spoons are they Cutlery
sparkly too it looks like it yeah
is that just for the is it just for the
picture though or is it oh maybe
I was a little bit on the fence but the
cutlery sold me
you're so cute though
there's a chance for you to win a Barbie
Dream House
Canadian so none of these matter to me
yeah we never get any of them
you win a movie ticket oh the Burger
King one is in Brazil only no I was just
about to send Brazil
Pepto-Bismol Burger Brazil please Brazil
mentioned Brazil Brazil man should come
to Brazil
maybe we should check out the Barbie
Latin America give it a good reason
no she's mad because I got banned from
seeing him
show me the pictures
Amy Mimi we're just talking about Brazil
oh
it looks good I'm probably gonna have
diabetes after eating it but it looks so
good it does the Brazil Burger
maybe
let her speak do not silent her yes
oh wait I have oh
sorry oh
I just I just remembered I had a
screenshot of it on my clipboard because
I made that edit
oh
I see Mimi still
after the censorship
me love me me so much revoked
I'll get on my hands and knees or
everyone don't please let me sing with
me again it's her birthday come on it's
her birthday
it's my birthday wishes
again again
we're star crossed lovers Tana Bata is
about me and Mimi
oh my God we meet once a year oh yeah
this guy
I'm getting a new cat soon oh oh
yeah he needs surgery though before I
can get him
oh yeah he's got like he's he's got
funky legs he's he's fine
it pops his hips out he like he's gotta
go he's like
yeah he's slaying for real
um
hold on let me see if I have a picture
of them but I can't show yet I can't
show chat yet I have to wait until I get
him
this little guy
he looks like you just walked up and
slapped his drink at him he's so cute
bro meme was the cat it's that it's like
bro
[Laughter]
he's got like cool markings on him too
he's really oh unique like you can see
on his arms he's kind of like it looks
yeah like the tiger yeah
oh so cute he's so cute
I don't know what I'm naming him yet
I gotta get him first how old is he
he's like a couple months
baby yeah he's a baby
okay
too that's what I'll name him yeah
that that cat like lying in the bed like
that he looks like he's looking at you
like if you don't turn the lights off
and let me go to sleep right now I
cannot vouch for your safety
yeah he's really nice though
oh baby
okay
I swear to God
save image as
me me dot PNG
wow the whole PNG quality yeah
I wish I could share you guys um share
it with you guys chat I'm sorry
we wanted an archived
yeah yeah
you haven't earned the rights no
yeah too also
eventually maybe maybe we don't know
eventually yeah
hopefully
this is this is a birthday
it is
yeah yeah
hey birthday yeah goose are you guys
ready to Goose are you guys playing
Goose I am let me close Asian mythology
first
time
1v1 sure I'm gonna beat your ass
not before I drop a bunch of meteors on
your town center oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was that that one wasn't even good
she just wanted an excuse to do that
all right wait do you stream it removed
no we don't oh
my god oh we we both haven't been trying
let's Goose let's goose
let me see
I switched to
uh
[Music]
we're playing I guess so yeah I have
like no schedule wait I was there oh
okay I was I was wondering if you had a
schedule no I'll just play until until
it oh my God it's just start like
until what's it called time
oh whoa I just discovered that whoa
the studio yeah whoa whoa hold on a
minute
well a new studio mode but I never never
used the slider I've never used the
slider before yeah you could transition
like do the slowest transition ever yeah
I don't know this thing you haven't
where did I type that
um duck
I know it's a little early so stuck
figure anybody who won can't play now
and play later probably if we can switch
out or stuff and yeah acting
oh my God
I think that I've just realized recently
in OBS that it actually has blending
modes
what do you mean I mean uh you for
example like you know how in like
editing programs wait it does
like a fire element that is on a black
background and then you just change it
to add or screen yeah OBS is blending
modes wow oh my God yeah it's so handy I
I did that for my uh
my poop transition for my position
my new outfit yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
that's how you did it
yeah
I had a stinger to transition in the
poop yeah and the dog I've always tried
to figure out how to do the blending
mode stuff but I couldn't figure it out
yeah how do you do it you just on your
stage you right click it and then you go
down the list until you go to blending
mode then you have normal add subtract
screen way worse
there's actually proof slang in chat
yeah you didn't hear what I heard yeah
yeah oh I feel like I've gained
knowledge
you just saved my life
[Laughter]
why is that goose opening for me Goose
duck
game duck duck duck goose
the ghost fought there's this one thing
nope
uh Heaven thank [\h__\h] God would have
done that before so probably now that's
why I love playing this game because I
can lose my best though
girls don't fart so I love playing this
game because I can live out my dreams oh
it's true yeah actually hi I'm actually
I was born without the ability to fly
like Evelyn why did you just open up
only uh because it was a reflex
it's a reflex oh no you had it open
earlier too I saw it
is running install script
oh maybe I'll uninstall reinstein yeah
me too yeah mine's running install
script too uninstall inside if okay
okay shoot did you say you were gonna
strip POV
I just opened up
you had to change your time because it
was different from oh no it no no
worries I was what do you call it
I was free the whole day anyway okay
I love the mobile game ass sound effects
they're on this game like the Boeing
when you open up a chest
is there a mobile
no it just sounds like a mobile like
sound effect from a mobile game you know
this game would do great on mobile oh it
is on Google Play oh nice yeah it seems
like the kind of thing really well
okay it's opening
oh yeah it's like a mobile game size
sized game too so it's like
you could you could probably install it
real quick too
[Music]
yeah
okay
okay oh what was my game capture there
we go
this game is so loud
oh yeah
wait they're saying go master volume
there we go
[Music]
oh no go back
um what's activity
I'm using the slider oh yeah oh my God
however like when you discover a new
technology for a stream it's like
this yeah
bye
I want to join a room
uh if someone makes one yeah I'll post a
game okay
wait is it on private or no yeah
uh yeah I think
yeah as long as your code isn't showing
up on the screen I think it should be
okay oh host gameplay okay
I'm just gonna put it at Max people
what's privacy mode oh I think that's
when you can't see the names right so oh
yeah yeah I think so it's the ancient
sand
think undertale
oh
true you know some some apps aren't even
like the oh the maps to play is just an
RP
map
oh yeah wait I hope this isn't just an
RP map I didn't think about that no it
says it says oh wait okay no that's the
number that's not the code that's not
the code no the one I posted sorry is
the code there's a number that's on this
oh yeah yeah
I'm in
here oh let me add everybody
oh yeah yeah oh here it is rainbow
any of you [\h__\h] inside a
pyramid right now thank you
I think I'll start my POV then
oh my gosh
hey guys
happy birthday
[Music]
never mind sorry what what
oh sorry
I have so much money
yeah the devs bless you thank you what
about me devs what about me oh do you
have anybody check down here they've
never
[Music]
notice us notice us oh here's a picture
that you can you guys can screen cap
this next to that's no money and then
tag no I'm just kidding don't do that
Notice Me Senpai notice me oh whoa
there's a oh
oh oh my God there's a Breaking Bad one
at least it kind of looks like it holy
[\h__\h] wait where is it I mean it says I
heard you have an and problem it's
called exterminate but I'm looking at it
the yellow color just made me think of
Breaking Bad oh my God wait wait wait
I'm gonna try and find it oh I was
adding people uh at everyone
oh yeah no Ike it does look exactly like
a Breaking Bad one and you can get it
for silver coins so all right I'm gonna
start grinding I'm gonna start grinding
for the Breaking Bad outfit
Jesse Jesse we need to play Goose goose
duck right now Jesse
uh Mr White uh oh we missed the white I
don't know
let's see is there a code yeah
oh
it's at reimu endo
oh I said the code oh no
oh no oh I'm gonna mute so that um I can
use the in-game audio oh yeah yeah all
right I'll use it again voice activity
oh yeah
ah
wait did it work oh am I already talking
again oh no oh wait am I talking in game
I don't know how to set it oh but it
should be hello hello hello
I hear you earlier can you hear me yeah
oh no it's on the wrong thing I hear you
hello oh yeah hello
am I am I talking properly yeah oh
you're loud oh oh god oh [\h__\h] it's okay
you can turn down manually yeah yeah you
can turn down people
Wilson
uh it might that loud
I turned you down we could adjust it
it's you're good you're good
to be louder than quiet I don't know why
my games are always in games my mic is
always so loud
is it okay if I don't play the tutorial
am I gonna
be okay this game you don't need to be
serious about anything yeah
oh
okay from the mall oh my God this is
Pablo's birthday it looks like mine's
working is it is it actually oh my God I
Jesus Christ
can we do a mic check real quick uh
what's everything
what's everyone's what
sensitivity
a hundred
what having four an episode
I can just turn you up
100 then the amplifier or or yeah
I
have everything at zero wow
he doesn't he doesn't need to loud yeah
he doesn't need to do anything wait
maybe he's born
I don't think I'm LED I think there's
pretty or loud on my say
my amplifier is loud I turn my mic up to
a hundred I do everything again
yeah you're pretty loud
oh and I'll yeah and I'll turn it down
now you're good you're good at we you're
good at it
which one is it
well like we already adjusted yeah
well sucks to suck
okay are you talking yeah
now I'm setting up my waiting room oh
okay
I'm just gonna set my sensitivity to
fifth
to fifth that had hundreds
I don't even know what the sensitivity
is hello in this game certain people are
loud and quiet and it's like random each
time wait zelly are you talking if
you're talking I can't hear you yeah I
can't hear you oh yeah I don't think you
have the right mic yeah you got you
gotta go when you talk your name goes
yellow
what's the font button again
F to fart
oh my gosh
GTFO fighting on me
oh hi adults
oh mine's the Jillian mode how do I fart
is he so cute I'm so mad at him uh oh
you could have a fart cosmetic
oh oh so cute
shows a few enabled Parts though
it will it doesn't show up for me
oh if you don't have a cosmetic it's a
it's like a invisible fart oh you're
right
oh
I do
fart money
oh there we go
oh hey
hey hello
finally arrive
[Music]
I'm gonna buy this footsteps sound is so
cute it really is
oh my gosh how do you fart
and then you can customize
and then oh there's a there's a fart Tab
and then
and then and then and then you you gotta
no what is this right team but he tons
of your playlists how many words how
many times I've played like four times
and every time the devs have given me
another so I just kind of lucked out
[Music]
uh
you buy it
oh
you want Cosmetics it's down here ramu
bye
yes
I want your eyes oh there's a lot of
maps I don't know I bought it bought it
it was like the anime pack or something
well I don't know I bought I bought some
Cosmetics because they're cute
so cute but yeah I don't see it usually
it's flashlight but
not in this game
and my money yeah
no more I have a wink fart that's right
draft mode is fine
no you're kind of cool for that you're
kind of cool for that having the regular
duck face part because nobody gets that
one so you stand out zelly oh I wanted
to be special I guess yeah
and then the rolls
frog detected that's the game we're just
so cute there's no like it doesn't get
more intricate than that
you're gonna be so recognizable if you
end up being like Oh
I'll be yeah
I'm the Frog detected from far away oh
work what does that mean let's add it
ew ever you want girl
whoa this one costs 15.
yes we need the party
which one's the pelican
that's the one
there's so many things in this game it's
crazy I know yeah awesome
oh where where is it the one that makes
the person turn into the chip
into the what you cut off
it's a party baby
already rocking in the house maybe it's
Falcon I don't see the Pelican you guys
God there's a there's a yellow tongue
what you mean the pigeon
you copied me
crazy you copied me
do you think that's my problem
that's not mine either
listen you cannot copy my character
original OC do not steal
I'm gonna do two yeah
Emoji we're not even going to play the
game we're just going to chase each
other party on each other
did I save it correctly
I think so I hope I did oh God uh what
do you call it what's what is it the one
with the
I see dodo bird Vulture pigeon Falcon
Goose vigilante oh you can see it
Canadian Detective
oh if you press the eye it does show
everything yeah that should be good then
okay
wow oh my gosh yeah if you're if you're
new to the game the eye on the top right
has all the tutorials yeah I'm frog
detective you are frog detective on it
please
yeah the second best detective in the
detective
the really big boobs Uki
one leave for class
oh you overslept oh no wait oh my gosh
your bag actually has like is that is
that yeah but that actually makes it
what is that read you need the toast
cute
yeah
oh doves doves
oh cool isn't
it I think the floaty is so cute
whoa this one's crazy
how come your eyes look so
shiny I bought them oh sure you need the
banana hammock you can't get them
anymore
I need to restart the game for this okay
wait baby no I'm so sad I'm like I got
hella currency but should we ready up
sorry oh I think rainbow yeah she's got
a restart oh okay okay
oh what the hell is that it's freaky
wait where's the so slay yeah under
clothes whoa
thank you hey what the hell could be
level six bro God damn did you just fart
yeah
there's one that's literally baguette oh
blade yeah yeah oh my God yeah now that
I look at it
it's true yeah
okay let me switch okay
come back
I can't find the banana uh banana thank
you really oh my God you don't have the
banana hammock
under if it's under clothing where's the
baguette
I did not use real money for these leave
me alone
oh there it is I am Metal Gear Solid
why not
look at the outfit I bought too I know
oh my God rainbow you're so lucky
okay
I bought it
oh my gosh oh you got it it might be a
little too revealing wow
[Music]
oh my God I'm going a little crazy yeah
my chest feathers are kinda
[\h__\h] you
dude put that thing away there are like
children here oh no there's chicks here
put that away
feathers are too revealing
Ox there's a gorilla you gotta get in
oh yeah
oh my gosh you have the whole kit
um
do we want to do a game
we're in everybody hit the big ready
ready
I'm ready I'm ready let's go if you're
new to the game
good luck oh I'm the detective yes
yes
not the not not the duck I'm the
detective
oh my gosh I'm the Frog Detective
okay
wait what does the detective do again I
didn't read the rule um but you can't
investigate players to see if they have
killed that round oh okay oh have you
killed anything shui Amino oh
uh let's see
whoa wait what's the smoke whoa what's
this whoa what is that oh it's like oh
it's a sand stage there's like sand the
fox just went in there though oh
oh
tried killing him it goes and it goes
away okay
oh let me check you now
space okay oh
okay nice I see how it works now
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
oh by the way I'm the silencer Ducks I
could silence someone
um I'll silence the rain move here okay
remove silence why why
what
what I guess rainbow I guess you're
silenced rainbow huh
um
I don't even know where I am wait
I'm by the courtyard that's where it is
okay oh okay
good I'm glad a little while ago
so I don't know
uh I saw kill earlier I think even if
that's my Metal Gear Solid okay I was
with Wilson and Kim
we all just went different ways there
was a sandstorm
oh yeah
and then I went Lefty and then I lost
track of them I don't know what happened
okay why do you have eggs as your
background
because I love Ed what do you mean
are they duck eggs
I bet I bet this [\h__\h] hasn't
said anything
what
oh my goodness oh this is everyone is
safe for now foreign
is this a new map I don't know what's
really cool though
I've we've never played here before at
least I haven't me neither look at this
little frog he's so cute
oh my god
um Rockford
um I have a pretty miserable existence
oh really
yeah look at him he's like what really
I'm happy
oh
he looks really sad it does it looks
really sad yeah
it's coarse it's that it gets everywhere
everywhere
that's so cool wait how do I oh I just
accidentally used my roll
what are you I'm the detective brainy
I know who it is actually I know who
killed Kyo
really yeah
ooh
Joe yamino
yeah but like
I think we should
save him we can fix him probably I have
I have to tell you the truth are you a
duck I'm awesome
hahaha
um
so
I found the body
in a womb
in the womb to the left and
um I I'm a I'm a mortician but I don't
know how to investigate a body oh no I
think you're supposed to do it before
you report it yeah
oh
I I don't know how to do it so I just I
just clicked and then oh yeah if you oh
yeah I press I should show you the the
all the roles in the the I think if you
have a roll space is usually how to use
it oh yeah
I'm a professional uh I saw nobody I was
doing my tasks so I was trying to find
nobody
if I ever somehow find a dead body I
will check in next time who the [\h__\h]
voted for me I will find you in game
Jesus Christ why are people voting for
me what no I was just like other people
are oh he's gone
by myself
tab
we should probably do our tasks right
detective in the world you guys
oh oh did you vote for me no
no okay
it is
hello hello I'm doing my task hello
hello yeah there is a task here
yeah oh you can see it oh oh I think we
lost what oh we did this
a lot of bad guys
yeah there are two neutrals okay yeah
we'll we'll uh
[Laughter]
there's like three to four imposters I
was laughing the whole time
I'll never forget you freaking [\h__\h]
dare you play with my trust
I know that's what this guy uh
more tasks
for some friends oh oh it shows you the
last game summary so you don't have to
yell over each I'll be like who was the
What role who is what role
oh right that's great where do you see
that
oh wait rainbow could have killed me
Rainbow's the sheriff raymu could have
killed me
oh grandma could have killed me I don't
know
everyone
yeah Rim was like
rolls on so that like uh
the Traders don't know who is who
nope we knew oh should we turn that on
YouTube caused more chaos
I call it fun there's the there's the
role of the what was it it's like the
the the one that's supposed to be
not
there's like a fake imposter
like a Jester oh yeah oh yeah there's
like a
a guy that's not an imposter that shows
up as an imposter the mimic yeah oh
yo I got the party duck and then every
time I use it on someone they died I was
so excited to hear it but then he died
they always kill me first bro
I'm never gonna Target you ever trying
to I was trying to make sure that pomu's
role is working you know
yeah yeah thank you for telling her I
appreciate it it was so
[Music]
it was so funny
[Laughter]
three imposters in her Lobby of wait how
many I infected half the map and then I
died I was so sad
wait no I'm not going count on clockwise
what am I saying I'm dumb
oh yeah I think I might lower the number
of Dexter
two ducks and then one neutral roll
[Music]
hey thank you Sally thank you for
supporting the the clockwise thank you
very much
you know everyone's roll when you die
is that is that good
yeah
I guess if you have like a medium or
something that would be bad but we got a
thing in this game I don't even know it
only shows you at the very end right oh
no like in the rules you could make it
so that it reveals the moment you die no
then people can't Gaslight
well no you're done
yeah but what if some what a few people
were claiming to be the same rule
what do you mean
wait it shows after the person dies to
everybody you know you know everyone's
role when you die
oh yeah yeah yeah so when you're
expecting you see everyone's rule
oh this one us and a fire this BET's
kind of Fire
foreign
[Laughter]
Ovid
he he looks like a certain character
from a certain game series
yeah from niji Sanji uh the game
yeah who's that it is we're done I think
[\h__\h] Ovid you're allowed to say The
Witcher and geralt you I know I'm
trolling okay it goes oh yes
hello everybody
foreign
click to run
we I've never I never thought I would
say that those are those love farts
yeah they're love farts well one thing
SOS so I think there
mine says 505 it's my division number
oh oh true yeah yeah 505.
exactly
I'm back
welcome back
[Music]
we should learn a number of ducks
lower number of ducks okay
yeah and then maybe one neutral role
okay uh wait
number of ducks
neutral rolls to one
all of these roles kind of make sense to
me what the [\h__\h] is the Canadian role
hey oh as soon as you die you get um
announced like the person you apologize
at the at the start of every single
meeting
apologize for dying
you get a complimentary bottle of maple
syrup wow
are we ready to start
[Music]
no I'm not ready oh just kidding happy
birthday
[Music]
move away
wow I know I have my swords on
about
nothing
[Laughter]
are my tasks fake I don't know actually
what does this do
what do I do
oh
what do I do with this what do I do with
this
let's go find a wee one I don't know why
am I even bothering with tasks we need
to go oh
hello Pandora says oh
sorry I'm not a Hitman for me
oh I feel like the what's it called has
The Voice
French man
you didn't know that I was watching
the other one that could talk for oh
because he reported it you have like uh
yeah
I was on the boat the whole time I think
I guess if I just see me going on the
boat and never returned
[Music]
you know what this is I actually believe
you I'm not biased at all I believe you
I believe it
I don't trust you are you sure about
that um ookie was just kind of standing
there when I came up so are you sure
about that I don't trust
[Applause]
tricked it's always a friend she's
bandaged
who should I stalk then Oh I thought
that was a room oh
that's pretty freaky who do I stock then
that murderous look in your eye I know
you oh me what the [\h__\h] is this Tusk
some of these tasks are weird
how's this one do I break it oh
oh wait what
this one uh you sort them right you sort
those diamonds and then you swords
there you go the trinkets yeah
[Laughter]
hello I found the body in the pyramid
near the top
um Ike is looking kind of I don't know
maybe we should stop
right now bro I literally just passed
him wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait yeah was I
not just in that room
it's in the pyramid
if you open the map like the red red
wait is it is it red for everyone for me
oh you know I was just there I was
literally just there I was just there
I think I just saw you go by me it was
it was the Northern end of it wait it
was me and pomu there what and then keep
my name out of your mouth I don't know
where the hell you are
wait a minute
I walked by from the from uh left to
right like yeah and I passed kill and I
mean kid was like hey what's up Mike and
I was like oh hi was that from the North
or no
okay I was I wasn't able to check if
anyone was like where was the body was
it like this is literally the one room
one room of both oh
[Music]
um
yeah it is
oh [\h__\h] okay
I did not mean oh tide vote oh It's
gotta be vulgar shoe
they're in wait why me
muted oh yeah yeah he's probably silence
um
you guys I've never been the stalker I
really want to stop the first person I
see Rainbow
haha
oh don't kill me please I haven't
finished my test no I'm I'm I'm stalking
you
oh okay
because you're so cute
thank God it was a girl
remember there she is down there right
move oh
toy time
I can't hear you
I can't hear you fujan it's very good
he's communicating with the cardinal
directions
but you can't be silenced during the the
the game yeah you can't be silenced
during the game oh maybe how do you get
in there
you get it in there I know where Raymond
is she's over this way
I could smell her rainbow rainbow scent
oh
who was that hey hey come here
oh why can't I go in there what
um
[Music]
uh did you guys see who that was or uh
it was kyao
oh so man I was stalking rainbow wait
was it no Rainbow's dead oh
oh I found Ike I think it was Kyo that
went upstairs
[Laughter]
it sounds crazy laughing so much you're
running around trying to figure out my
audio problems
um I saw Ike and Wilson moving together
for a while
yeah I'm a little sister Wilson it's
it's true
[Music]
no I literally saw the person run away
from the body and my chat says it was
cute
so wait you're asking
but wait but you're partied are you
partied but okay
um
well I guess is
I I feel like food chain would have
partied you pomu and yeah I feel like
this is the other killer I'm gonna be
honest
Wilson was with you guys when I found
the body
[Music]
so I can hear yeah get out of here
thank you guys
[Music]
um
I told you listening
I'm not gonna lie again
let's go
wait what roles
he's acting sucks why are you lying out
of your mind about me
I know you're [\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
how long
what
okay
super loud oh my God
okay why am I
[Music]
thank you
damn
ready up by the sound that means that's
so cute
[Music]
let's go
let's bully him in this game I'm
actually the frag detective no I uh do
detective work we're gonna have Van van
and Willy let's go
[Music]
I'm in crisis
I have to unlock it as first letters in
the name what yeah you have like levels
in there hey where's the button okay oh
I'm sorry I just clicked start
Ed
an event
[Music]
that they were buying things I didn't
mean to start the game
hey I can end it very quickly for you
are you it again
no I'm actually the you know what I'm
the Vigilante you tell me did you almost
say you're the one free kill did you
almost say that you're the mortician
no I'm Batman I'm the Vigilante just
give me a name and I'll kill him for you
um kill kaneko
okay let's go find it the hell now let's
go find them
first there's Ike
wait what is this what is this one lie
oh hey Ike how you doing
I'm just sweet we can't go in there I'm
sweeping I'm sweeping oh
leaving the Coconuts
actually kill kill um
magic trick
yeah
there you go
woman
[Laughter]
wait with left shift
[Music]
what did I do
I didn't see anything I guess I didn't
have a roll Maybe
oh hello I'm recharged and ready to go
oh no
that was really fast
um I thought I know it's crazy I thought
guys needed more of a bit of a cool down
than that
um nah I'm a Witcher I could reach out
pretty quickly no one dies oh go in here
go in here
oh
wait Sally's dead
I just wanted to share that the the
North Port and the Southport if you look
on the map you could actually ride a
ship and go north and south oh yeah
it's a funny [\h__\h] guy let's vote
wait anyone see Sally
guys I'm I'm old I saw that the Imposter
the wait the girls talking um
I think he's too young to be playing
this game
Joe is a cheerful guy now
I love this game it's so fun and
energetic
thank you
holy words
I'm skipping we did it who did it we did
it I'm really good with the pump shotgun
I promise
you're not answering the questions
quack
come on dodo give him the dodo win
oh
I really stopped for a second he might
be the dodo
I'm eating I'm eating something oops
I messed up I mean sunflower seeds you
guys
and they are delicious
um no oh this is the okay
oh
hey
what else do I got
oh [\h__\h] I got a lot
hello
bye squeaker
I didn't never heard that before
oh
my god oh
hey
okay [\h__\h] you too No One's Gonna find me
in here
no one's going to find me in here
everybody's gonna pass over my ball
actually you can see it from here
good thing I wasn't in here I knew it oh
hello
um Dad me too oh
they found me
hello are they gonna talk futon
hello good talk good time
way too hard to be funny
oh my God
where did you report
I can't hear you I know but I like to
pretend
this is a mess up the body is in the
garden see that's all you're getting out
of me
doesn't like having nuts in her mouth I
know that much
said no what in these lobbies
is
Master today
[Laughter]
what if it was dodo
a bit
oh hey guys oh no I really thought you
were a Dodo I thought so too you would
have done a perfect dude I killed in
front of you oh yeah you're right you're
right it's [\h__\h] Wilson
never trust the French man Canadian
French or French French never trust him
okay
oh shoot you dead man
okay so I walked into the little shed to
do the task where you get the the the
the the Scythe out and you cut the wheat
and then when I came back
um it's chew isn't it she was dead uh I
cannot remember who I saw him with but I
remember earlier on I could hear
Rosemary talking I don't know if she was
I literally spawned it okay let me tell
you I have information I spot in with
shoe and then I literally left five
seconds after like five seconds before
you reported and I quiz with him but I
had left them and chew and I Quan the
same way
as well
I went up to do the water I didn't even
think
and the only thing I heard from rosemary
was just like please please don't put
the party on me I'm already a squeaker
I don't know who to believe
it's both of you I don't know either I
know who it is Wilson you're awfully
quiet
I'm listening to the testimony man what
do you want me to do talk over them
come on now I want you to provide your
perspective to add to the conversation
okay okay
maybe Rosemary was right
um
it's not me Rosemary I don't know about
getting this from him but wouldn't it be
like such a brilliant thing
was actually the one with the party and
was doing the whole squeakers uh get out
of this Lobby
where are you getting this okay we're
talking so much okay I think I'll be
honest
what does rainbow have to do with
anything
aggressive right now I've been I said
two things
decision
[Music]
mm-hmm it's not over arrows I mean hey
because because no squeakers in this
Lobby oh my God
[Music]
oh my God
almost like I called it okay
Rosa didn't even marinate me he just
came up and I just want you to know it
wasn't me okay
something that happened I was starting
to freak out is that I did
and then I went to the boat and I saw
Elyria there
too I kill alira and then I'm stuck on
the boat and I'm like oh [\h__\h] someone
fights me I'm done
girl
[Music]
oh wait summer oh you're making might
not be honest oh yeah check if it's the
right mic and everything good day oh
yeah thank you
ice cream oh my God yeah good ice cream
oh nice ice cream
unicorn now let's go oh
your mouth
[Music]
oh my God
thank you so much
happy birthday
[Music]
thank you
how can I be friends
[Laughter]
you're doing a great job so far buddy
Library
[Music]
you speak French
so there are the books
kind of want that one where's the frog
the frog hat yeah everybody's like lined
up over here
no raymu just became a chad
what oh my God the world is so much
Switzerland so
Glenn just showed up as a chat hello
11k oh my God they gave us so broken
[Music]
thanks to the community for helping with
trans oh are these like oh
mystery
alrighty
I kind of want a friend
yeah
yeah the friend is nice
oh yeah yeah oh they actually get you
stuff they like wow they collect coins
and stuff for you wow so cute
I love the ghosts yeah
[Music]
is my mic working now yeah yeah yeah
hello happy birthday
thank you
everyone's over here
I look stylish today thank you
nice otters
oh my God what you're so sweet
it's cold out here
in the desert
you gotta tell me where you get your
your product from I need two of those
yeah actually
oh
yeah
let's go
I'm ready to go to the local pool
this one's like this one's pretty pretty
hype it is actually I'm gonna it's the
summer only one right now
swimming camp
but I'm still gonna wear my little bra
it gives me a like a like a natural
swimming boost when I wear this bag
um I am Metal Gear
Well I can get it now
she can get it so it doesn't work
anymore
like the swimming tubes I tried to pay I
tried to pay to win can I please get the
alira eyes
oh
I can't still stop looking in there
my eyes are you sure you're looking into
my eyes
there's a baguette shirt Sally now are
the shirts like looking down at that
okay
sure
if you buy things in this game sometimes
you have to restart it and then it'll
show up the next time
I'm pretty sure it's a shirt whoa this
one's so fast
[Music]
oh you're a cow see a chat
thank you
that even says Coco that's a baguette
it looks like a hash brown
he's like dangerously French oh my God
it's the 5500 ones Ellie
what is that it does look like that
that's the tourist track
you get that
I don't have it oh this is the one
it's like a blue striped shirt blue and
white striped shirt oh cute
he writes I
um
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh it's funny cheeky
the dubs are based they know
[Laughter]
gold
um you're a little too late I know how I
become rich
uh I had like 50 gold in my inventory
and Mom's spaghetti oh really swag
[Music]
where's the much love oh awesome
clown
please have my friend let my friend have
some drinks really ready up I'm broke
yeah sorry yeah whenever you guys we're
ready ready
let's go oh again
ready spaghetti I'm Canadian hey
[Music]
famichiki family
hey oh hey happy birthday thanks
I'm connect
Ed
[Music]
what what oh what did Uki just do that
oh vanta did huh so I just pressed that
because it was shiny and I didn't know
actually what it did that's my bad
girl
[Laughter]
wow
I walked by it and it lit up and I was
like okay I clicked this and I clicked
that and then it was like we need to
talk and oh my gosh I don't know what to
do what you don't like it
[Laughter]
wait wait we should we should have a we
should have a conversation about this so
like how is how was you guys today is
everybody doing okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
how do I get through here
you guys for all that don't knows I
really appreciate it oh
oh
what the hell is this
no oh yeah
oh
[Music]
where is everybody
oh I get out of here please kill me
please please
oh
so um I was just um in the area trimming
task on the Hedge and then I went over
to the shed to do like the little the
little wheat shopping task and I found
um I found the body uh in there um saw
someone walking away but I can't quite
remember who it is it was sort of like a
pasteli like a purpley pink color I
think I can't connect with me can you
give me a map no why are you excuse me
sorry to God if it's kill again
on the map where is it on the map oh oh
let me check let me check yeah it's um
and I realized like I could have gone to
check who they were but then I realized
I'd be running away from the body and I
didn't want to like implicate myself
with a happy person
[Music]
when I approached yes and then she left
because they were with me
don't kill me
you can't kill me
yeah so I would regret it wait so what
does that means
I'm sorry I want KFC um
[Music]
I'm hungry now
yo what the [\h__\h] y'all hate me like what
real time
oh my gosh everyone's safe for now
I'm always by myself oh oh wait there's
a boat here
I I missed my ride oh how am I gonna get
home how the hell oh
just go in here sleep in their bed I'm
sure they don't mind
whoa I'm the bestest ever
I'm gonna trim these bushes I'm the
bestest ever fluffer ever ever to ever
exist in this world
can someone
who is speaking wait what's this oh
that's the thing that calls
salon
hey
I'm just a regular goose in a duck World
wait is the docker the goose bad I don't
know
I don't remember I mean it's called
Goose goose Ducks I assume that
[Music]
Jesus Christ Vox is us as hell chatting
with um with somebody else second time
and I was just on my way to another one
of my tasks and I saw Fox's sauce as
hell
it was it's in the pyramid in the top
right
okay um
how did you get to the top right of the
pyramid what path did you go
I walked through the pyramid I walked
through the pyramid like um through the
middle from the left-hand side and then
up towards the um and then up towards
that and that's where I found I thought
the room was called
through like the top you went to the
middle then to the right or to the left
up and then I went from the from like
the middle left through the middle and
then up to the right
word because you can't go through that
area during the smoke cloud unless
you're a duck oh
I don't think it was during the smoke
cloud it was super recently
they just ended recently I voted
for Vox
can I set you up there was no smoke
cloud there was a small
smoke
oh my gosh
it must be the imposters
[Music]
you are not wanting to talk about a
squeaker
oh whoa there's something
whoever's a killer please kill me I'm
just a goose I have no purpose I'm
Canadian I have no purpose either I'm
the second sexiest well you do girl and
Ian bites my lips you can't kill me I'm
a Canadian I don't kill anybody
oh well whoever kills you like if
Rosemary killed you right now it will be
reported no I can't I'm Too Sexy I can't
do that oh why do we need to talk who's
pulling this
sure making sure nobody's dead
wait is everybody alive still or
get em out get em out get em out get
them out
of here
[Music]
it's not fair exactly
right but he had a purpose
I know what is it I believe you
yeah you would Wilson because you're
[\h__\h] guilty too I'm the squeaker now
please give guilty of What Not dog
Kyle on everybody
Ren is quiet maybe he was silent I don't
think we have any silencers this time
though
that was it I just had to find the mummy
who was that
whoa there's everybody here I'm just
trying to divert the I'm just trying to
divert the attention so I died and you
live so you were throwing me under the
bus
we can settle this okay okay are we
figuring out if she was a bad guy or not
oh gosh yeah oh no oh [\h__\h]
wait they're both dead
I was just gonna run away wait okay I
don't know what happened but alira was
like we'll figure out if she was a bad
guy then alira and someone else died and
I was confused and Palmer was there too
died
yeah I think um if the [\h__\h] someone's
the sheriff because if they shoot the
other person and it's not an imposter
they die also
okay
yeah told me she was the sheriff so I
don't know like I was trolling because
you were I was the word that I'm looking
for you tell me that I would regret it
if I killed you right yeah the rock
started the route started Rosemary was
like you're gonna regret you know it's
like I'm the sheriff though touch me
what the hell was that that's what
happened I don't know right you sound
pretty sincere normally when you're
aligned and you get caught you get a
little bit more Angry is
the sheriff killed the wrong person and
they died yeah yeah yeah yeah well a
lyric that it's a proven point oh yeah
okay why are you the sheriff's salon
no I'm just a normal I'm actually the
sheriff so yes
yes I'm Detective
I know
you scared me it's your birthday wait
you get to select one person to die
yeah all right okay
[Laughter]
catch me first little boy your tiny
teeny tiny you won't even be able to
reach me
I'll step on you
with what feet you have the teeniest
tiniest feet
my foot's bigger than you no it's not
probably that's crazy
see you later
you're wearing a Halo yes you're gonna
be preserved
nice preserved
that wasn't me
hey
do you like being a detective
hello do I have a task right there but
I'm afraid of stacking bite slip
hey
bite slip
oh I'll do another thing actually what
does that do
wait what does that do hey
hey
I'll leave I'll leave you guys
[Laughter]
why was Wilson so weird
I don't know
oh my gosh I stuck here yeah
how do we get out ducky yeah we're
actually stuck
here together yeah fight slip
oh we're free oh there we go yay
you can Tab and you'll see them
I think she's gone
wow isn't ready
wait how do I get in here let's oh here
okay hi first of all I hope you're all
having a great day second of all I saw
two bodies like next to each other and I
did see Raymond come from there which
makes me wonder why what the [\h__\h] you
transform into a run and then you killed
him and they went down no Rosemary was
with me the whole time we bite lip
together I was literally biting my lip
with pulling the entire the entire time
I went up to the pyramid oh it's
definitely rain it's probably rainbow
and celeb okay
I was like what the [\h__\h] and then I went
down really I'm sorry but we were biting
lips we were biting lips the entire time
I'll tell you fuel insulin purple with
rose to me she can transform into it
what did I do
yeah
maybe it is Wilson but he tried to do a
task a thing on us and it didn't work so
um
goose
sorry it's really late I wanted to be
here for Palmer's bus oh I'm sorry I
know it's really good it's okay this is
the EU debt that said I do have to go to
bed now though um I have stuff to do
tomorrow Happy Birthday promo thank you
for having me I hope you have a great
rest of your birthday
[Applause]
so true
[Music]
if everybody wants to change
bye
wow six people had no role I I know
that's crazy I have been an NPC every
single round
s the neutral stuff then
that's uh okay detective and you press
space what does that do
you sure
like uh
like an angel there should be like a
yeah angel or uh something I I see that
if it's an angel they're good if it's
like a devil or something they're bad
hey
I mean like for the like literally they
have to have killed that round when you
search them though
okay so it can show like everyone Angel
if you just start using it early
do we have tooling dodos on uh I can
turn it
up
all good I still haven't learned about
anything I'm gonna get a pet anything
all right I'm gonna get the lizard get
you a pet but uh I think you learned the
hard way
I thought it was a tasked up when I
walked by it I didn't know what it was
even if you're being chased even if
you're about to die I'm so ready for a
month yes everyone yeah oh God you're
not ready to help you I mean oh sorry
I'm still ready I can tell
I don't like that everyone has to ready
open it oh wait there might be another
person joining oh it might be another
person someone else is running uh I'm
ready I'm ready
I'm ready oh still on your spectator oh
[\h__\h] oh there you are lagging yeah yeah
oh you need to buy it first you need to
buy the fart like I'm lagging I don't I
don't have any money I think I'm broken
down my screen for a second I thought
your internet but then I realized it
wasn't then
I just like how red like himself and was
just like oh it's me and then die I'm
not a moment of self-reflection it was
crazy
after this round we changed Maps
that's cool though he rose in me it's
not basically yeah you like jazz
um by all known mods
too small to something
a bee should not be able to apply
that little bunny off the ground a bee
of course flies anyway because the bee
doesn't hear what humans think did
anyone watch that movie it was still
crazy it was like a cord Drive
yeah I watched that movie
yeah it's crazy I didn't watch it when I
was young yeah
is it like
oh we didn't get that yes
[Music]
I think she's coming actually wait you
guys can ready yeah I forgot it's not
like I have to press start
[Music]
who knows
Ryan you're literally only wearing
bondage
a face masks
[Music]
no no
I paid so much money for this game Salon
ready up
spend money on this game
that's a great game yeah that's a good
game oh
every player in a single round okay
okay nice oh it's not okay you like
Jazzy like jet what's so not okay
that's not okay
oh
hey
no please
where am I going
where is everything
all right
[Music]
there's a lot of people
there's a lot of people how the hell oh
whoa oh no hello
your little emo hoodie
I know
try to clean
wait L shift oh
[Laughter]
I come coming for you I'm Coming For You
Ike no no I'm coming for you I'm coming
for you I'm coming for you no I'm coming
for you come here no no no no no
I'm just fishing I'm just fishing oh
fish fear me we're fishing together
I'm not getting anything nothing's
biting oh wait you can actually
yes it's a task oh
I have no idea I just found it it was in
the house full
time I'm still learning this with this
map uh it was there's a map you can just
click on it
it shows you where you are what the hell
it wasn't too far from the location
there was a few people like kind of
congregated in an area I know it was
on and then yeah
[Music]
who is down there it was and who killed
am I crazy I think you're crazy
wait who's the Buddy
I found
he's clearly confused give him time
what a smart class
[Laughter]
oh who are we voting
I don't know I I wanted to test if you
could vote for yourself
I'll do that next round
if we like if we do that then somebody's
gonna be like oh whoa my buddy
you guys this is too hard what if I L
shift
what did that do
hey
what's up
I'm just vibing
what's up with you happy birthday thanks
are you feeling any symptoms or are you
[Music]
rifles or uh
feeling pretty safe right now okay
finale
good talk wait what what you reported
the body
you reported the body the only one that
can talk for like the first
me
no later
I think I killed yeah oh my [\h__\h] god
bye [\h__\h] please
[Laughter]
I'm so sad you know what that's okay
because I killed everyone else
call out to the other person all three
of those kills are mine
I'm proud to say so
I said I'll tell us who was that partner
of yours yeah call him out call him out
yeah call him out they deserve it who
voted for me before you die
[Music]
the silencer
I have no purpose once again
did I just die
thing of the first round I was like
please kill me and he was like I'll do
it next round because they're Witnesses
my way out he was your way out
and now I'm still still alive
find a purpose in life you can't just
like well if you help me infect everyone
I'll get you out
okay all right let's go find people how
do I help you let's go find people
right behind us oh really okay
hello
hello I could come back oh wait I
already got Ike
oh oh Wilson okay I got him how are you
guys doing here
what are you doing we're playing the
game what are you doing
uh I'm almost done
okay don't be a good little boy and
finish your task okay
yes
yes I have no purpose I'm just a goose
oh
[Music]
it was vanta
that's all I was standing right there
and he came in and did it
can you hear myself wait it couldn't be
me I was wiping the golden egg
are you trying to say the birthday
girl's a liar oh
it's not that exactly it's that's uh huh
who was in the room with you
uh I heard I heard I heard Uki Senpai uh
right behind me and then suddenly
a body which in the body that was found
the body yes
dead no
no oh come on
don't play it up too high okay
it was vanta though he came in while I
was watching him stroke the egg and then
he came in also and um killed him
that was the only thing my hen was doing
was stroking the egg I did I did not
murder I did not know
I was I I
the thing is like with how much of Venta
has fumbled I'm inclined to believe him
because he sounds genuinely puzzled
let's see
Saul avanta kill it was a vanta
there were two of them by the way it was
uh someone I don't know
[Laughter]
yeah maybe
oh shoot I don't think we got the right
guy
oh no you could have foreseen this event
oh ookie wanted to die anyway so I
probably I didn't want to like you know
okay you know if that's what he wanted
yeah he kept saying fish I still haven't
been able to fish that's your thing
isn't it to fish yes okay I'll come with
you
oh it won't let me
know
I wanted to fish too
I also wanted to fish
um hello
hello
[Music]
is anybody around rainbow
hello
she didn't see I didn't see why who was
what
who haven't I infected I don't know who
all is left
hello
blind mood what did I miss oh
damn
oh I missed the land
Selena's left that's it no one Wilson
right
yeah it's all people in a single round
hello
yeah Selena Wilson
[Music]
is anybody alive out there
oh we're so close
no
[Music]
oh
is that the end it wasn't vanta no I
know it wasn't I knew it was Wilson
wait who's still alive uh Selena
oh my gosh
I was so close
that didn't
I have to go hard mode there dang let's
switch the map I realized that was the
winning crazy yeah I was literally I
think it was one kill away too I was
right next to Raymond I was about to
kill her oh I love that book
wait how do I change them
[Music]
oh here here wait did you did you morph
Wilson I morphed into Salen initially
and I was like I gotta kill someone yeah
and then I morphed into I morphed into
Venta I went out of the room and
literally came back in like a second
later and then killed it was like oh
my gosh okay
is your mic on I'm in but I have no I
how why are you typing that in my chat
[Laughter]
wait did you change I'm pretty naked no
I don't know which one which one do we
guys we have the chapel we have the
manor we have the temple we have among
us we have the basement with him
humongous
I don't know which one it is
yes
oh yeah switch on back yeah
okay
I don't know which one is the role play
one
that's the club yeah I think there's a
space one too though because there's two
space ones
oh let's go to space
I don't know which one it is
oh my God my first message happy
birthday
did they follow oh yes okay this is this
is Among Us
RP
oh my God hello hello hello
Sophie online
still feels working I don't know happy
birthday
I dropped in
we know
[Laughter]
where's my cycling
oh someone yeah
yeah I hear my voice through somebody
else's a little bit
um
[Music]
okay
hello
that was gone oh my gosh I don't hear
anymore
yeah
I think we're good yep
okay okay this is my first time playing
so please go easy on me okay
you'll learn
real quick yeah
yeah so so don't kill me okay
what if what if that makes you
suspicious
[Music]
you mean suspicious
oh
[Music]
the Dream Team honestly what are the
rules what are the rules oh oh hello
oh it's just ducks and oh it's just
ducks and Gucci do you are you good
wait there's three bucks in four
neutrals what are you wait what how does
that even work I'm a goose again yeah uh
the uh
I put him out of his misery
yeah there's the the
um the rolls are just goose and duck
right now boom what oh
oh yeah yeah so you want to end my
misery
oh that mystery
okay
yes oh just doing the test thank you
thank you you've been saying that every
time
we might always have two one
what is this Daily Report captain
what are you doing oh my God I forgot to
add more rolls so um
why are you laughing
um so uh so I was I was uh yeah
the hall ran into uh Ike pomu and uh
when somebody and I have just walked up
uh why does rent only get the Senpai huh
yeah I'm the senpaiist I'm not well it
was I was singing like like one two
three and then Senpai so that I wouldn't
be I wouldn't be saying Senpai like
three times in a row because that's a
focus okay okay yeah um yeah
from where we were yeah you're
disrespecting them
on her birthday wait wait hey this is
kind of suspicious they're distracting
me you guys you guys see that we're
trying to try again
first names
it's possible that uh
I see you dopio might be a suspect call
me might be a suspect as well I don't
know I think
because she always does this I saw a
vanta like yeah
go towards him so you know
down down oh we're voting so then
okay
I didn't realize that there were no
rules though
oh hello
the ghost of folgerovan speaking we can
get you out of spectator mode between
the next game you accidentally selected
it we'll get you out we'll get you out
we'll get you out
you better bite your lip right now
oh
I see bite slip
hey Miss you're a oh
the heads hey to me hey
I'm glad she bit her lip otherwise that
would have been bad news wait what's
this dude
what did I just do
hello
honey bunny hello
hello what am I what am I targeting oh
oh hello can you still please do the oh
hey bites it hey rainbow are you gonna
bite your lips
do you buy do you bite slip
oh no
you're gonna kill me
hey uh
[Applause]
bites your lips
too late
I double click ready and that made the
game really easy I could see everybody
I gotta add more rolls okay let's see
okay I almost ruined that for you
because I was in a separate part of the
ship I killed everybody that was with me
and I didn't know how to come back so I
was like do I just self-report
okay I I killed everybody in my room too
on this map you could you could like
activate the intercoms and send messages
okay
no I think he was in Discord yeah yeah
it does say he's a mechanic the shuttle
the shuttle will kill any player that
stands in his path
wait yes
[Music]
thank you
that's so authentic oh my God
I like that being the leader was just
having herself a friendly Giggle and
then I killed her
no not so friendly anymore Santa didn't
see anybody oh actually no Sally didn't
see anybody like I killed Shu and Uki
and he just kind of was doing his task
and didn't see anything yeah biting God
chose you pull more I I couldn't speak I
couldn't see anything
oh wait I think this might be the last
game
[Music]
fish
let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't have anything yet what's this
oh am I doing an actual task
oh what is this
what is this
oh
you didn't see nothing hey
I I I was I didn't see anything you
didn't see nothing
I don't know oh not me not you no sir
what are you even what are you even
talking about yeah exactly I was just
doing my tasks and so are you yeah I'm
doing my task right now I incubated an
egg what have you done
uh I was actually walking to do uh
destroy the viruses uh but you know I
feel like I should wait to do that one
last I feel like that's a good idea
that's a good idea right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you've you've got mine we were just
chilling in teleporter over here we were
just vibing together yeah yeah
I came from uh decontamination and then
came over to teleport and that's where
you were perfect perfect easy
hmm you should teleport away
okay
I don't know how to teleport oh I don't
know either
um oh wait something
what was that
what that was it
what's this
oh
okay so I found the body in where am I
where is this place
prior lab cryo love the seats I think it
was red oh
I was I was chasing okay that was just
trolling him and then we both went to
the room when Ren was and then he was
like oh watch this Ripple I can't
guarantee you it is
but I can guarantee you oh just so you
know roseme if you're the detective and
it said he was an angel that could just
mean he didn't kill but by the time you
got to him just so you know well I saw
that like three seconds before the thing
happens
am I partied
unless unless he wants to you know
I was talking to Ike a little bit before
and then
she was there sure did you see Ike pass
by you
did I I was just Salem invested in the
LST
what are we voting for
eign
[Music]
oh
he's pretty quiet he's dead
I said Phantom
oh man is always quiet
dumb dumb no no oh
hey salon
I'm not waiting for a countdown or
anything
it would be funny if I just die here
wouldn't that be so funny yeah it'd be
so crazy
yeah because that would never happen
right what the hell is this
that would never happen right no no no
no
no no no
no way
oh you are
owl owl
you evil
oh [\h__\h]
I think I am I can't tell what my rule
is
Oh you mean you cannot tell it really is
I just don't know if I'm evil that's
funny
I wonder who killed that
we're part of the oh
a silenced rainbow
what
I don't think so I was just worried if
it was why would you think that oh no
because I don't know I stopped I stopped
I think
we don't know ran up and then finano was
done I think it was rainbow though was
next to radio was next to pomu and then
she didn't see it
where is the where's the body so then
you sure know a lot of information
[Laughter]
I am
thank you
thank you boys
[Music]
what's this
yeah
nice
oh
hello
is anybody alive
is anybody alive oh my free time Palmer
don't do it I'm no do it oh I'm not I'm
pushing the button
what the
okay I don't know why I reported
technically cylinder said she's the cop
and then like the sheriff and then she
killed
or it was the other way around anyways
it was none of them because they both
died at the same time
okay wait okay do you want to share
where the body was from last night
oh it was in
the bio
lab I don't know where the bus where the
bus takes you or the tele
Vision
go to the right side yeah
okay I took you guys to the Loading Bay
you got off of the loading bed okay then
that road then
and there were like four other people
and I and I really did not see I just
saw the
saw that I reported it then I got muted
I mean it was either salenremu or pomu
and selen's dead now
well you can Silence Yourself
you can I mean yeah
I don't know I think it was horrible no
I can vouch for pomuk in the first round
uh yeah on the body I was I was chilling
with her in teleporter we didn't okay so
it's Paul moon what hey what that's
crazy we're jumping to a lot of
conclusions
[Applause]
oh I'm doing what I'm doing is pushing
the button
oh I meant the previous round oh
it has chicken wings that makes me
hungry
very true
come on oh I'm so hungry
oh logger wanted this is so mean
yeah you're no longer one honestly shut
up you killed me like two times in a row
Mr Wilson so I don't even want to hear
it from if anything if anything I am
flabbergasted that Venta trusts you
yeah also with you he is
what's up
I don't know about that
like can I oh I can't do the Imposter
tasks now oh get it Wren get it
red
kill rainbow
the one where we start singing
Evangelion
what the oh yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
because I can infect people and then I
started following rosemary and red and
then they both were together and I think
Ren killed Banta so it's either roasted
me in red together or just run alone
okay
for a bit of the time and I also like I
made sure and back then I don't think he
had killed anyone but maybe there is a
point where he did
I don't think
out for now and then like see who it is
under the bus I'm voting for you silly
rainbow you're wrong for what
good job
[Music]
what can people you're still the bad guy
though
you knock
that uh
Ren why did you kill my Ally
oh I can't I can't possess people what
deserved
yeah you click on
we need to talk
friend was next to me and I got scared
kitten
that's it
I think it's red because the resume got
run up
[Music]
It's gotta be
fast
she should have killed me in the time
that we were there together she was the
killer she doesn't kill me because she's
rose with me but then we were waiting
for the bus together and then the last
second she ran out in Colorado
she didn't have a ticket I had to do
what I had to do get ready
that's
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh
my God that was so [\h__\h] funny when
you ran in front of them
don't kill me otherwise you have to
protect me I'm the detective and then I
just died
and he just goes oopsy here's a body and
you believe him
Discord
we returned
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] they're so tiny
surviving perfectly well you stepped in
front of the boss
get hit
I was spectating you and oh wait you
trouble
oh wait I've been muted my POV I was
just standing there talking to you so I
was like don't kill me look at you don't
kill me
[Music]
no thanks you guys I know I was really
annoying meaning
that wasn't annoying that was doing
doing work yeah you can make it up to me
by playing bug Fables
thank you for bug fables you're welcome
Happy Birthday Thank You
everyone's saying it's not annoying it's
work and then and then you'll be like
you can make it up to me I know
I'm gonna open the link I gotta open the
link
[Music]
wait are we are we ready
yeah all that and if you're in chat
right now
comment
on Instagram
and ring that Bell
[Music]
okay
all right hang on honestly play Goose
goose doc the devs are so amazing yeah
but they actually did it
[Applause]
yay yay Happy Birthday
[Music]
hello
I mean since we have a minute to kill
and this is the most people that's been
here so far want to sing Happy Birthday
again yeah
[Music]
happy birthday
what you gonna do tell me
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
hi hello everyone happy birth
okay it says it'll begin shortly so I'm
gonna turn off the music and mute
hello
waiting room oh wow
IE I'm nervous me too I'm nervous
why am I so nervous I don't know why
this always happens whenever there's
like a Premiere I know that like it's
not a stream so that we don't gotta like
worry about anything but it still makes
me afraid did I upload the right one
um
[Music]
[Applause]
he's in someone's front pocket
we can sing Happy Birthday again yeah we
should yeah
everyone's actually here now
[Music]
happy birthday
[Laughter]
[Music]
ideas
it was like the happy one yeah oh yeah
this one's this one 39 38 37 36
oh the colors are so like bright I know
I know
magenta I don't go outside enough for
this
deviantART Sonic fan character palette
oh my God
Ms paint
My OC dopio drops
[Music]
it says what oh God that's 25 30 seconds
for me here we go
I'm so confused please
times two oh you can do it rainbow
that's what I've been doing the whole
time oh sorry oh it sounds so huge I
love it I know so the most foolish thing
ever
let's go
[Applause]
oh
my God
I wish it's all gonna scream everyone
chills
[Laughter]
sorry if you can't hear this song
[Music]
[Laughter]
hahaha
oh my gosh Petra oh my god um
I love them
[Laughter]
[Applause]
thank you
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh my God
I know those people
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
my playlists
oh my God you're so talented it's so
sick I'm sorry I hounded you all for so
long
[Music]
thank you for organizing this you did
such an amazing job
[Music]
again
but in silence
I actually heard the Audio I don't think
anyone actually heard it it's okay
they're gonna play it on repeat right
yeah
make sure to like it and add a comment
okay yeah make sure to subscribe yeah
no yeah Super Chat
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
I want to thank them for like making all
of Ian's well pretty much all of Ian
touch grass it was great I know
[Music]
this is nice
[Laughter]
for organizing this but what's up in the
description I have a crazy idea
yes thank you yes the art the video the
mix everything everything
all of it and she didn't shout at us
when a couple of us had to be a few days
late
no it's okay even last minute she was
like frantic frantic frantic trying to
get everything perfect
[Music]
thanks for joining me
thank you
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'm gonna finish
we love you
oh my God
that's why I [\h__\h] use it
thank you so much lips
[Music]
oh
oh thank goodness it's over not them
live talking to them just the cover
hahaha damn I got the bites lips from
Rose and me
[Music]
oh my goodness
yippee we will not be silent
oh gosh
thank you guys for all the super tests
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you thank you yeah I
I I like I said I I said it earlier but
like I came up with doing the idea of
like like a month and a half ago
[Music]
oh
so you know honestly it's like you know
the it's the mixer who we I was like we
were all doing stuff literally yesterday
uh Jairus was still making the like
doing stuff on it to the instrumental
yesterday and
um was was still mixing yesterday
and
um and uh everything we were just doing
everything like so crazy last minute
so um because you know I was waiting for
everybody's lines and then also waiting
for the art and everything but it all
turned out so perfect
um I'm really really happy
with it and everybody who you know
everybody who agreed and Ian I've just
basically kind of I kind of put out a
thing I just I I tagged everybody on on
Discord and I was just like I I want to
do this cover and I want to uh you know
I feel that maybe
um
I feel like maybe Ian has gone through
some a bit of rough patches this year
and I just really wanted to put
something out that maybe would
um
maybe would bring back like a sense of
you know everybody coming together and
doing something together again so
that's why I was really adamant I I was
just like please as many even if you're
not a confidence singer you know I tried
to like pair them with you know like
people like I didn't want anybody to
feel self-conscious or anything
um because it was such a big group it
was my first time like dividing lyrics
too with such a big group and
um hopefully it
did okay oh thank you and to fill in
some spots that like the
that like
um the mixer would come back and be like
hey um I'm missing these lines and I'd
be like okay I don't want to bother
anybody so I'll just I would like get
all my stuff get my mic back out and my
interface and I'd set up my whole little
blanket for and I'd be like okay I don't
want to bother anybody so I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna
um do it myself
but I just feel like the song is really
you know it's a really inspiring song
and
um you know it's by anytime I'm feeling
sad it's the song I go to First
so it's like the money I was I really
was just like if there's anybody I want
to cover the song with it would be you
know all of Ian and for the people that
didn't sign up
um please don't like ask them or you
know I'm sure you know everybody it was
really busy that's one thing is and you
know I don't I don't want you guys to be
like why weren't you in the cover or
anything like that
um everybody has been really busy and
you know
um so everybody had their own reasons
for
you know if they couldn't join so that's
totally okay yeah yeah yeah
um
even even Nina I was missing a line from
her and um
and I was just like like up to like
yesterday I was like can you know please
and then so we had to substitute it but
that's okay
um she's still sang in it um actually
the one person if you're listening I'm
so I'm if you're like or rather if
you're like trying to hear her actually
Scarlett couldn't participate because of
her
um because of her bronchitis but I was
just like I was like and so she tried
really hard and I was just like well if
you like if your throat is feeling well
enough to do like the Yeah Yeahs or the
fools but
um
she said it was really hard but I was
just like you still signed up so I don't
want to exclude you if you you know
signed up so I um as she's still in the
video for the parts that
um
yeah for some of the parts so yeah yeah
yeah
um
but yeah so let's well wishes to scarla
by the cool oh no
I'll be okay it's totally okay please
please please don't worry about it
but um
next time
whoever decides to organize a full Ian
en virtual to live maybe right but it
won't be me
I would I would like to if anybody is
listening I would like to financially
contribute to that as well because I
know how much this cost me so
and then um tuna was like working on all
the animations
um and everything I just kind of came in
and I was and I I knew I wanted those
for like the I wanted like a little pop
of something
for like the yeah yeah yeah yeah so I
didn't even actually tell to know what
the song was I just kind of sent I sent
him a gift and was or like a you know
sagitty dancing in the ending of of um I
sent him that and I was like I want
something like this
and they were like okay
so
sorry I didn't tell you what it was for
and um
and the artist the illustrator they were
like I'm I've done work in a really
short amount of time before so I'm used
to this kind of like you know or not
used to it but like I've experience with
this and so I was just like okay
please I need 27 people actually uh back
then it was like there was a few less
people but some people joined late
um I had to like after I made the lyric
Division I had to squeeze some people in
because a couple people joined late
and so then I had to go back to
everybody else too and be like I'm so
I'm sorcing
a 28 stab away
but I wanted to
I wanted to get as many people as
possible so you know
um so that it
um like I said I just really wanted to
bring everybody together again and this
was kind of the only way I could feel
like
I could and I didn't want it not just
for like us the livers but also for you
guys I wanted you to feel like
like I don't know
I just wanted you to feel inspired or
something
um yeah I'm still gonna read the letter
don't worry don't worry
um but yeah hopefully you guys liked it
everybody worked really really hard on
it so thank you everybody thank you I'm
sorry that I kept having to ping some
people being like are you big can you
send your lines in this weekend please
ASAP
[Laughter]
so oh sorry it's not virtual to live for
everybody who was really looking forward
to that but
sorry sorry
it was so good thank you for organizing
this promo thank you
[Music]
you're so cracked I'm so happy like
every time I get to sing with
so many of you guys
everybody sounds so good
so um
um
oh gosh I have
uh I have a letter that I wrote last
year I'm kind of embarrassed to read it
now
thank you for organizing this thank you
[Laughter]
oh good uh ookie tagged Us in someone
someone
um clipped him running over Rosemary I'm
so glad I can watch it afterwards
um okay I have my letter even though I'm
embarrassed to read it
because I don't remember what I wrote
and then
um
we can skedaddle
uh
I'm gonna change the music
[Music]
the actual virtual to life
virtual to live at home
okay oh gosh I'm nervous I don't
remember what I wrote
last year
I remember what I wrote last year
beautiful coverable thank you for
organizing happy birthday thank you I'll
be reading the super chats from last
night and today tomorrow
uh before I go on my little bitty break
so we'll hang out I actually wait do I
have two streams tomorrow yes I think
I'm playing Minecraft also
[Music]
I should probably wait right
until some of these are done
[Music]
do not open until July 12 2023 well
that's
today in my time it might not be for you
anymore but um it's called letter to oh
letter2pomu.txt
[Music]
laughs
okay
okay all righty I think I wrote most of
this on stream last year but
um
oh we should write another one maybe
I'll just I don't wanna I don't I don't
have too much time I gotta get ready for
a meeting
I'm signing a little bit so
okay but very shortly actually okay
all righty already
sup bro and bro mudachis
happy future birthday today it is July
12 2022 and I'm I am writing this on
stream with all my pomodachis and
Friends keeping me company smiley face
around this time I hit 1 million views
on Virtual to live which now I think
it's all like two and a half two two
million or something crazy and 400k
subscribers oh my gosh and I'm nearing
600k subscribers
um on my channel I wonder how many
Milestones you've achieved in one year
from now is gothgar still trendy in 2023
yes
are you still in love with Solid Snake
and Metal Gear
yes
how was your wedding with elira and
Millie
more friends have you made and how many
more pomodachis you get to hang out with
every day is more being still a thing I
hope not
kind of is
Minecraft 2 finally been released to the
public
how many cowabungas have you choo-chooed
a lot actually
did you like the new Kojima game for
Xbox
oh that hasn't come out
are you still having fun every day with
everyone in niji Sanji and yeah
yeah please remember to be kind to
yourself and take breaks when needed I
am bad about that
yeah
um about that but hopefully future me
doesn't stress
so much as the Pomo writing this today
actually I lost hair from this cover so
um
uh the pomodati of today want to say
that they love you and they are still
pomu and here's the part
to my future pomodachis
I want to thank you every day for giving
me so much encouragement to be the best
person I can be even on days when I
think I'm not funny enough or
interesting enough or cute enough you
all make me feel like a princess thank
you for everything I wouldn't be able to
do anything without you all my love for
you is under there
it's under there you guys
it's under there
[Music]
sincerely Palmer rainbows
[Laughter]
thank you guys oh I forgot about this
thank you guys for another wonderful
birthday thank
so much uh we're under down under
underwear
how many days are two months ago so I
haven't been able to cat watch dreams
glad our quirky fairy is doing great
here's to another year of Awesomeness
I hope your move wasn't so bad thank you
thank you
all righty well
thank you guys I really appreciate
you guys celebrating my birthday with me
you and everybody and Ian who joined as
well thank you so much thank you thank
you thank you
um
I'm gonna go before I Cry
so much fun thank you I hope you guys
had fun I hope you guys like the cover
and um
thank you
[Music]
so much
cry now before you go
[Music]
cover was amazing thank you
yeah I had a really good birthday I've
I've almost eaten my cake in a cup
like it's almost finished
I should have dinner though oh God I
have I only had cake I haven't eaten
dinner at all wait
what do I eat for dinner
um I'll figure
something out
thank you for this
soup thank you I was laid off recently
Sean please don't super 10 then please
oh wait and today was my first day ah
so I'm happy I'm so happy I was I was
worried for a second
so it's cupcake no it's it's not a
cupcake that's the thing it's a it's a
cup it's wait it's a it's a it's a cake
in a cup I think I said cupcake
yesterday because to me it just makes
sense right
to me it doesn't make sense to say
cupcake but it's a cake in a cup
[Music]
it had like frosting and then cake and
then frosting and cake like four layers
it had layers like Shrek
it's a cupped cake
[Music]
um but yeah I really do appreciate you
all and um
thanks for making me it feels so special
on
um this one day thank you
thank you thank you thank you and um
yeah I'm gonna head out
um
did is anyone streaming no nobody's
streaming oh I still have Nina on my
subscription she's at the very top I'm
so sad
[Music]
well I think you guys dinner more cake
yeah
1.5 years and counting thank you toucan
welcome
party Happy Birthday promo thank you
thank you so much okie dokie yeah I I
don't really know how else to end this
so I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna go
um
yep yep
oh it's a baby
bye bye bye-bye thank you
thank you thank you so much wow thank
you I'm sorry I feel like the
notifications don't end thank you
Anthony
thank you guys so much thank you
bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you