[Music]
and I still if I was made for you if I
could
[Music]
don't
queen
[Music]
of you see
you are
[Music]
me don't
this
[Music]
do
this
me your heart
[Music]
could
it's
[Music]
I'm
remixing guys how long does this game
patch
[Music]
it's my first patch so maybe it takes
longer hadde it open
maybe 15
minutes oh we got
[Music]
well this should be less waiting time
than
[Music]
Poe h on H on
po server
crashed
surprise was there really over a million
people in the
[Music]
quebe it's kind of insane
holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
hello 1 million EA
purchases 924 th000 people watching poe2
on Twitch
wow m
yeah okay I'm sorry for changing the
plans uh in any case I didn't have a
schedule this week so it's like you know
you got to you got to
adjust to sudden changes every now and
then and uh it might you know take a
long time to get in I don't even know if
I would have gotten in at all in that
case cuz oops sorry from what I
somehow my setup is weird from what I've
heard show
oh
so and from what I heard it's kind of
insane oops what
was
oh uh see I'm patching I don't think I
can do anything right but yeah from what
I've heard
uh even when you get in you can get
kicked out or something like that I
don't know that sounds very frustrating
I don't think I don't know cuz like it's
8:00 p.m. my
time
and and
I I mean I would have been I would be
willing to go you know Over Midnight a
little bit but I W with the expectation
that maybe
after two hours maximum I I didn't want
to wait more than two
hours on stream and I don't know how
that would have gone I would have liked
to play the game so better to not uh
waste my time with that when there is a
collab tonight at my usual streaming
[Music]
time that is so rare and I did say that
I'm kind of interested in giving it a
try if you don't like League don't worry
most people from what here don't like it
if you play like online with like randos
we're not playing with randos as far as
I know we have a full team uh and also
uh it won't become a like a usual thing
I won't be playing it like every week or
so and also usually there's like phases
people play a game and then they stop
playing it after a while it's always
like these
phases right like maybe maybe is
currently a phase of LOL and then it
will be gone and like
next the coming January or so who
knows my IRL
friends they play League of Legends my
closest friend Circle they play League
of Legends every once in a while
apparently without me and they had some
comments to me to seeing that I'm
playing
League friend number one friend a not
let's say friend M says oh no why about
my stream change FR T says oh no top
friend e says good luck ha friend T says
hey uh when you lose with being top
always blame the
jungler
easy friend M say sounds fair friend e
says don't forget to Ping a lot it it
shows that you a very polite player
FR T says yeah especially with uh
question mark pings on your teammates it
always gives them the feeling that you
have everything under
control I don't know what this means but
it sounds
[Laughter]
funny 10 out of
10 sounds does that sound like good
advice now the last one definitely
sounds like trolling like not not like
trolling but like asking asking to piss
people
off how long is this patch going to take
this was the last minute change so you
know I
uh I'm not ready
apparently but we're starting early the
other girls are joining an hour later I
think the other girls all played the
tutorial and stuff at least and maybe
more but uh I never played anything
before restart the CL should I really
but what if it's really still patching
and I'm
like I when then it has to like start
from the beginning
again yeah they've done a few streams
right restart should I restart it do not
restart it's suspiciously long yeah
that's what I was thinking it's weird
scir is that loud May that's
loud yeah okay that's maybe
better do not restart it will pick up
where it left off usually
really top left
corner there's nothing
here is there a progress bar no I don't
see
one and this is grayed out and I can't
click anything do you think that's
bugged people have different
opinions it's
bugged restart it okay okay but then I
restart the game right
okay
goodbye uh exit Vos I am not finished
with Breaking Bad by the way I mean the
last season I thought I could finish it
today but there a surprising amount of
episode
still um but let's just say Walt is
just a piece of
[\h__\h] okay
[Music]
vonos should restart the clients
too client's probably fine
right always has been
I feel like he got a lot
worse in the fifth season like oh my god
oh oh it looks different
now is there anything I'm not supposed
to
show I don't have friends
yet
I
uh now I'm fine yes the game
yes the game H why is the client so
small why is this window so
small this window is so small now
there's a progress bar yeah okay was
good to
restart ETA 32 minutes
[\h__\h] what's your EA what's your
EA what's your e what's your EA not my
fault not my fault it's not my fault we
have time I heard the tutorial is like
20 minutes or 40 if you're really
slow what your ETA what's your
ETA what your I chose na I asked the
girls what region should I choose and
they said na
probably 40 into tur as wild I I would
hope it only takes
20 uh respect to New Y I was thinking of
like cuz you know I don't have a
schedule for for this week I was
thinking of maybe doing a new jeans
respect karoke tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow and mix KDA songs in as
well I don't know
[Music]
like I want to sing new Jean
songs got to pay my respects to new
jeans my
beloved and K KDA I was going to say kfp
KDA you know how it
is kfp
yeah take it to the
top new jeans quit no it's complicated
It's
Complicated by the way thank you for the
raid uh to the chatini thank you I
appreciate it welcome welcome we're
going to I guess wait now so the the no
yeah my girls are gone
[Music]
lady they're
gone G
[Music]
going tell us about their visit well the
thing is um we have a a a stream planned
next week
Tuesday uh to like look back on the trip
and share some photos and talk about
everything so I think I shouldn't uh say
too much you know yeah we got to save it
for that collab then
mhm but they were they both were
like I
was um
it's hard to find words they were
so
[Music]
I it was
good it was good it no I it's not a
secret it's not a
secret they were so yeah
appreciative appre appr ative is that
how you say it and they really enjoyed
Austria they had a great time and they
conveyed that plenty so that I really
felt like you
know like cuz I was really nervous about
that like also they stayed at my place
so I was nervous about my place being
comfortable enough and nice enough for
them but also like you know I made a
plan for each day uh to show them around
as much as you know possible show showed
them in a short amount of time showed
them a good amount of stuff um yeah they
were yeah they were really enthusiastic
we had a lot of fun there were some even
some weirdly emotional moments uh
especially on that one night where I
wrote that I I
cried like
everybody was like
really into it and I think we bonded so
much
and yeah they seem like they want to go
to the mes with
me I can't believe it I had this moment
where I felt like you know we've been we
like we're getting along so
well and like I asked okay do you also
like feel like maybe wanting to travel
to like a more beachy destination
ever and they were like yeah hell yeah
of course and especially Lia was very
keen on the idea of snorkeling in the
mives when I told her about it and I
told her that I'm I want to get a diving
license next time she's like oh my God I
totally want to do that
too so yeah I was struggling to find
someone uh for the longest time and
might I I was already going to give up
that it's not happening
but it might actually
happen probably not like in January or
February not not uh that
early probably like very very giddy
giddy uh close to the end of the good
season yeah it's a tradition the local
probably know nah I'm I'm so far okay
I've been there twice and I've been to
different uh Islands cuz they have like
a million Islands there and um
you know the fabled good season yeah
there's there's different islands in the
malds and uh different each island has
like its own Resort and you know I I
don't unless I go to the same place I
don't think they would know
me
uh would you ever go to a different
tropical resort yeah totally totally I
want to like I've had some ideas already
like I've been even thinking about uh me
uh or you know of course I want to go to
Bali and so on but uh I I wanted to go
during these like winter times when it's
Austria and
winter when it's winter in Austria and
uh from what I what I've been told
that's not the right time to go to
Mexico or to Bali
[Laughter]
so yeah yeah yeah yeah we have beaches
in the UK to get out of here get out of
here with your UK
beaches beaches of the UK are are only
good to get some fish and chips out of
the water and perhaps I don't know
uh I have some more jokes but I'm not
going to joke around okay I want getting
messages from my friends
[Music]
too much sand too much sand no I love
sand if it's like purposefully there for
reason for me to enjoy
it vamos vonos
vonos how we looking 74% is is this less
than the 30 minutes that they said feels
like kind of less feels like pretty
good should we look around this menu a
little bit Aran
[Music]
please ignore my windows noises it's not
actually windows it's um uh
messenger what is
this what is
this celebrate Arcane season 2 Bridge of
progress RM trailer Arcane braw so I I'm
I I want to play an character release
that's from uh Arcane that shows up in
Arcane so I'm thinking VI but ambessa
would have also been interesting
interested interesting yeah but I've
been told that VA VI is easier to play
than ambessa but she's really new
huh but VI is like only close combat
right so that's a bit concerning to me
that scares me a little bit but she does
seem good for Top Lane so oh I want to I
want I want my beloved her daughter I
don't want
ambessa then I would love to play her
but she they're not going to implement
her until much later right so Jinx fixes
everything oh is this like a mini
game finish Act One Finish act two
finish act
three I don't really know what's going
on I know Jay is also an option yeah and
Caitlyn I love Caitlyn actually like as
a character in Arcane and and her looks
nerfing but she wasn't recommended to me
as a top laner I've been assigned top
laner so I need to go you can look at
skill pre
oh it it's time we can't run away
anymore
guys it's time play
press okay please help me guys I have no
[\h__\h] idea I haven't even watched much
footage of people play this game so I
really I I just know it's like one of
those games like the Pokemon game that I
played before so yeah uh intro beginner
intermediate
intro is that the tutorial Co up versus
air
training training please training is
this is training the okay learn the
basics in this instructive tutorial
floor let's
go and now it's a start now thanks for
the
membership oh oh oh now game becomes big
oh oh full
screen well I guess I have to change
this here oh oh oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait what's going on I
can't T I can't Tab
out I want to change the window let me
go task
[Music]
manager won't let me tab out so
have to do it like this oh come
on
uh
uh what's happening you can move your
Champion by right clicking a
destination actually here
window and sure let's leave that for
now I still can't Tab out
but the SI the size is okay are you
[\h__\h] kidding me I can't a classic
leak streamer
[Music]
problem here D
go borderless can I Tab out with bortas
oh this isn't even fitting minions have
spawned minions I love
minions how about this
oh no I still can't T out
bro I hate that what's the other game
that I had this ah fallout Fallout yo
that triggers me oh it's already time to
quit League of Legends for
me I'm already
triggered okay uh here chat you go
here all right so I'm Misfortune I've
heard about her oh oh what did I press D
is that rushing dashing
okay let's kill uh can I not attack with
left click it's right click huh
okay okay this is my auto attack yeah
yeah
yeah I did a different attack a good
feeling about
this are these mine I guess they're mine
okay so would they follow me am I in the
Middle Lane huh okay
oh sheon
I'm going to use some skills here that I
don't
understand surely that's a good
idea First Blood
oh in League of Legends you oh I can
change how
powerful light it up Champion has unique
and Powerful abilities I heard from
other Champions no two Champions are
alive was in like a straight line but it
disappeared so fast
w a they're killing
[Music]
me slay you should wait for more to's H
back away when enemy Towers attack you
okay where are my
minions there they
are this isn't too difficult so far what
is that we're not going to play Lu so
I'm not really going to look into the
skills now okay
ow do I have a healing skill is it
[Music]
f help help
minion GG no no no no no I'm not dead
yet
this Yas guy is really strong but I'm
slained him you want me to try this one
now okay maybe it heals me at
least yeah it heals me I'm brand Brand
New
Me Get Wrecked yourself okay this this
character was not an Arcane so far no
Arcane characters I'm very disappointed
Js Js
Js powder powder I love you I don't
understand these skills it's okay
ah ah they hurt ah [\h__\h] Jinx is crazy as
I
thought no
[Music]
surprised po you're not a jinx powder
get a hold of your sense as [\h__\h]
that's Jinx from Arcane yeah I SL no
what have I
done what have I done to jinx but she's
okay she's she got Shimmer in her body
she'll be
[Music]
fine always be wary around enemy she on
again you have a lot of phoenixes here
huh
ow will end
oh y run run run
run is this tutorial not supposed to be
easy I already feel like I'm doing
really bad clear a path to an enemy and
destroy it is R my ult like wild
fire
how how how do
I how I how do I do it they're not
really good at EXP
a [\h__\h] I'm dying oh oh oh
oh oh it doesn't work on Towers only on
Champions
oh okay okay okay
okay but it's on it is on uh cool down
so I guess I did use it at the end there
without
noticing you have slain an enemy BL
let's
go no no no I don't care about the
abilities right now it's a tutorial I
already know I want to play
VI don't have time
here don't have time let's kill this
power
Yas here eat my
ulti that doesn't look flashy at all
[Music]
I want to play by
yeah oh no abilities work on Towers at
all oh not just the
ulti the object of League of Legends is
to pierce the enemy's defenses and
destroy the Nexus located in the heart
of their
base
okay the Nexus okay this body is just
one oh oh I got a whole team now but I'm
stuck with brand
why let me
choose but oh look look at us
go so strong we're
winning how do I do the question mark
thing
huh oh scary scary oh scary
scary no scary is still flashy now
G okay maybe I can't do it right
now maybe it's too early oh dinks is
here
again no she died but she died with her
heart shaping her hair shaping a heart
that's
adorable really sad she cut her hair so
short at the end of the
show and I mean she looks cute either
way but yo nobody cares to dodge that
attack there he is double kill
w turtles will come to the defens of
friendly Champions Turtles a [\h__\h] get
out of here do we have a Healer is there
a Healer in this
game if yes I would appreciate some
healing oh I feel like I'm getting
healed
[Music]
will to the def all these towers I just
attack with auto auto attack right oh my
God not on my team right now oh
okay surely you can win the games
without a Healer too right or doesn't
feel like the
necessary
thing what's your league username DM me
okay me lady uh it has to be with the
clode
right I know it by heart actually
because I choose I chose a really easy
[Music]
one okay victory in it but uh what
happened with the Wind
window it's it uncaptured the window
because it became smaller again it says
unlock your first Champion it's I guess
one of the ones that I
[Music]
played I I'll choose the hottest one
Misfortune Fortune doesn't favor
fools it's like but that's so annoying
why so there's like millions of people
who stream this game right right and
then OBS can't capture this properly
this is
unfortunate brand is the hottest one
well request sent I have a friend
request where do I I'm still in the
tutorial window I don't know where I can
see my friend request let's do the next
tutorial and then I'll when I finish the
tutorial I'll look into accepting your
friend request
madelle it can Capt if you add it to OBS
oh Su
R oh
well it's just two Capt oh so people set
up two different windows for it spend
your skill points that's still not ideal
for a game that is being streamed by
millions of people spend your skill
points is this like forever or like only
for this one
[Music]
game there are three on this field of
Justice each with its own turrets
inhibitor and Minion waves I know what
I'm doing yeah that's a lie you don't
have to lie about that Misfortune I
guess I'm going I'm going up I want to
already get
accommodated to the top maybe she's not
meant for top but I don't care I forgot
to buy buy what oh return to the shop to
purchase items it is here okay you've
got dangerous eyes I like that oh she's
so
spicy she must be popular okay do I talk
to you or what what do I
want generally good a Dorn's blade or
this boring long sword what
okay I thought
so so now I'm attacking with
this and in each game you do this stuff
in between you buy
items and a potion po po
potion po
potion potion health potion
uh uh uh I was smart enough to look it
up in the search
yes but thanks for telling me where it
is did I buy it oh there we go okay not
a
problem all right then let uh ikim
show right click to buy quicker oh okay
already Min maxing I see I
see move down a lane okay I'm
moving stay close to the battle to earn
experience points
uh-huh there is no battle to be seen
yet now you can use a potion with two
okay and the the sword isn't that always
activated now it's like a is a a Time
limited uh buff for my attack nothing
but powder monkeys powder
monkeys monkeys made by powder
ATT the sword is permanent okay do I
have to activate it once though no
doesn't seem like it I pressed one your
Champion has leveled up good great
additional levels allow your Champion to
improve their
abilities I'm so ar ar R Arcane brain
water that is
true trets will come to the defense
scary so
scary I'm dying
help ah wait I have a potion I used it
but it didn't is it only slowing slowly
slowly healing
Me Maybe press f2 right that's that's
healing no pre no
P okay okay only overtime heal huh get
out of there not good
idea well I'm I'm applying pressure this
is probably
fine wait level up should I just do the
same
one use the to return to the sonon
a turrets will come to the defense of
friendly Champions who are get all free
first okay okay don't get
cocky she's like a pirate isn't she
isn't this fitting because M senpai's
concert
it's tomorrow oh good job let's
crank I got it I got him and I got first
Blood
yipp
no a an enemy has been pirate Captain
perfect maybe this is the character that
M and Senai is cosplaying all
along I've got a good feeling about this
cool down is really long for for the
dash an enemy has been slain money you
can buy item turret and Destroy wa they
gave me items do they give me items
automatically if I run away from the
shop oh exed
ah you shall die now how dare you
intrude our
territory
die okay now I I think I upgraded
everything once uh and one twice so
let's continue
There Mal fight I'm going to get you I'm
going to geta I'm going to geta geta
geta always be wary around enemy
turrets my Twitter is full with twice's
new
song that's actually not a reference to
the uh the other getcha
song you can use e to slow
them hold
oh really ah look just like normal
attack range Mal fight you're going
[Music]
down get out of
here you should wait for more of your me
to before advancing no prey no gay no
prey no
gay why are you gay
okay I'm being
targeted okay okay here the ultimate
gets an upgrade and I shall use it
on return to the suon why would I
Retreat why would I Retreat
now no no we got to stay strong guys
let's Frank do something oh no ooh what
is going
on always don't move when you use your
alt does it get
cancelled has been slain no no who was
that what who was that who is that dead
body from sure you can handle me
Summoner
Retreat to buy and heal no no no no no
bad idea bad idea D wa greef I got it
from Walter White blame it on Walter
[Music]
White someone's got to you know push and
apply pressure
fun
begin
[Music]
me the power will kill you if you attack
people in the real
game Oh Oh you mean it will be even
harsher than now is that what you're
saying that's
okay the defens friendly Champions were
under attack we're so we're so close ah
okay to getting the tower we're so close
blitzcrank come on I've been like
soloing this Lane for a while without
you no you got to you got to come on
gambat what do I
buy health
potion there's so many items how do I
know as a beginner what to buy they got
to give me like recommended
items maybe I look in
fight click un
recommended uh ah here
okay Yus ghost
blade blood firster
maybe this I don't know did I get it no
I got
it let's go blitzcrank let's go oh no
they're on our tower under
attack go even faster go go go go go go
go
go you've got 12 minutes good
luck does it not look like the time will
suffice no PR no
P what are what is this by the way
pickax just a little bit of more
damage you
en 12 yeah 12 minutes until the other
girls join
advancing the spell to return to the
suon destroyed turet oh we did
it we freaking did it
oh let's go let's go let's
go push to the en ready the other girls
will help you better to play as a full
party with friends yeah yeah yeah okay
if you say
so I think uh yeah might be might be a
good amount of
knowledge you should wait for more of
your minions to arrive before advancing
your team has destroyed a we did it my
minions are so
strong do some damage before I [\h__\h]
die come on minions don't get
c ah There She Goes
use your Al okay okay okay okay ex okay
okay should I buy stuff again your
turret is under
attack I don't know I don't care sure
you can handle me
Summoner uh okay oh but the Top Lane is
looking really
good actually the Top Lane is already
completely fin though but they're coming
to our tower now okay
okay always byy items are extrem
important
okay bang bang
bang you have an enemy oh malfi
disappearing in the jungle we shall let
him
go destroy all Towers in the lane I
already did that Quest I'm already
finished with that St
two maybe they want these ones here too
there's one more okay okay this
one you should wait for more
your not the first time I'm being told
[Music]
that okay now it's good to go let's
go desty exp enemy
inhibitor yeah slow him down slow him
down
destroy the exposed inhibitor okay this
is yeah bab we don't have many
minions how to activate this is it
activated I'm pressing one and two
but I know what I'm doing is F1 F2
no
exeed active items will have an outline
aha one
or
no
youer
distracted so this one's
active Ste destroy the enemy
Nexus okay or is award that's active
Okay okay
okay oh I don't know what to level up i
l count oh I did these dots how often I
leveled it up ah ah ah ah ah monkey mon
your Champion is severely wounded oh I
know I can tell that's why I'm screaming
like a
monkey ah all the guns all the guns
bring all the
guns oh look at her go look at w go on
the Rampage
still
not gaming wow so far you guys are still
nice to me let's see when you guys are
going to get toxic towards my my game
skills my non-existent ah game skills
has SL turrets will come to the defense
of friendly Champions who are under
attack never pretty soon and it
shouldn't happen oh oh really oh we'll
see about
that your team destroyed we
did insane once
again okay okay ooh they're losing so
hard to have the Holo girls been playing
against NPCs previously all the time too
ex I'm guessing yeah use the Reco spell
to return to real
people your team has destroyed a turret
your team has destroyed a
turret
crazy they're so
brave got some guts no pay
get out of there get out of there get
out of there too much your team has
destroyed too much too
much Annie she's so
cute who left this Lost Child
here oh
upgrade yeah run Mal fight you better
run you better run to your mama
your team has destroyed
your you twoo you too yeah go back to
your
base I'm just going to do some little
dot damage
here yeah oh look how it's going down a
I'm doing it allone and Bam wham bam
thank you ma'am victory
victory
woohoo
bory GG
where where is she okay shop for GI buy
items from the store to make your
Champion even stronger didn't I do that
during the tutorial what do you
mean what's happening it's opening the
game
again oh what the [\h__\h] they're all Bots
right it's not real people right we're
playing a Nava game wait I don't have
time for that
buy items here sh purchase an item the
shop has many items for sale some of
which are components for more powerful
equipment yeah okay the people are
already leaving though enemy minions
deal the killing blow killing blow to 12
minions you can leave okay exit
game okay cuz I
guess oh tutoral completed oh that's
that's all I had to do Hallelujah okay I
got 300 blue Essence and now we're going
to check where my friend request went
to
um
here
acceptance I've Got a
Friend
yippee oh I've been invited to a
game yippee are they in the voice chat
uh oh yeah they are do you think I
should join the voice
chat be ready hello I'm streaming hello
oh hello I'm ready I'm ready I finished
my
tutorial I know I was watching good job
thank you you ready to go Top Lane I'm
so ready to go Top Lane I know
everything that needs to be known about
Top Lane and that is that I have to go
north hell yeah hey that's pretty good
yay but I don't have the character that
I want to
play who Do You Want To Play I think I
want to play Vai cuz she's uh hottie VI
is a jungler oh but no I so she's a
jungler and a top laner
maybe maybe
maybe I mean you can play any Champion
anywhere yeah okay yeah how's your kitty
cat he's doing good he's sitting by my
chair so I can't move it at all or get
run over oh c I know I love him
baby my little baby so now we just wait
or
what until you girl start your
stream yeah should I mute so that you
can continue having a conversation on
screen huh should i m should I mute you
got girls from my
stream I I'm I
I don't I think it's fine I think we're
all going
live yeah I just my soon soon up am I
FAS placement in this stream yeah oh
yeah
okay yeah yeah you are
yeah I thought fauna was going to be
here that's the only reason why I accept
it just kidding
wow we led her
in so everybody else already played the
game we just had a c out of corner come
here spirit is here with us yes
oh spirit is enough I guess I feel it
was she the top
laner yes so you will have the most of
her spirit oh but also the most pressure
how can I follow her
footsteps good luck I can't don't feed
it's okay feed
don't well we'll we'll play Bots first
so it's fine okay you don't need to
follow you just need to do what you do I
mean most teams have like multiple they
don't just have five players they have
like you know extra peeps in case you
know you know someone needs to fill
anyway uh I'm going live so I'm going to
do my intro real quick okay okay I'll
mute myself as well I'm going to okay
bye bye goodbye I'll be
waiting hi Darlings this is H life
English
one and only narissa Raven crft I'm sick
but thank you for coming to more leg of
Legg legs for days we love leg I love
leg I'm wearing a mask so I don't get
these lovely ladies
sick thank God we're just
virtual yeah thank
God how' I R do it
today
Jin
jimin
Jin I'm ready for Lega lean me I'm ready
for Lego
le me too and then Path of Exile 2 came
out today did you see kiaha I was going
to play that but then I you know the the
queue isn't looking very good with over
a million and um just didn't seem very
likely that I was going to play anything
today so
inv came at a good time yeah over a
million it's really bad the server is
down too so right now yeah it's down and
it's an hour in and people in Kyla are
not in but I didn't expect anything else
it's not running the game is not uhoh oh
yeah the game is not up so there is no
queue okay so good luck gigy
later all right I was like should I be
logging in right now to get through but
it's not even up
you can't can't even get in path of EX
out we should we should play yeah I'm
I'm I I I
would y yipp I must play When the
servers calm down more yes all right
yeah I was thinking so too maybe like
next
week yeah would be sa definitely want to
play next
week are you girls showing your like
this the screen
like the where the names are yes
okay I shall wow I'll even show them my
DMs with you what the one
dm I just opened my Steam and it's
redownloading all 80 gigs of Path of
Exile so I hope I lag in League of
Legends amazing
amazing this will be
great this will be hello wonderful hello
okay I'm back okay
hello
[Music]
hello what are we
airing what what what what happened wa
wants to steal my cats even though she
has her own
now m up no Rissa no messed up messed
up get yourself more then don't take
mine away steal them steal them you
should have gotten two minimum anyway
narissa I could have told you
that
no why no you just want to steal are you
kleptomaniac are we ready to play some
League of
win can we do an audio check can we do G
yeah everyone introduce
oh silence
amazing League of Legends Cecilia
spin League of
Legends don't think that's the game name
Elizabeth oh League of
Legends sounds narissa Raven CR spin a
win leag of
likess it sound like nerve nerve say if
you're
nervous I am she
is uh Top Lane uh and and himer Dinger
checking my ass out
W
questions what what is he doing look at
my ready to find a match thil he's
checking my ass
out I am too AR you ready aren't we
matching um am I ready uh yeah I think
so where I yes we
are loud it's very
loud going I have to switch to window
anyway do I choose a character here yeah
I can choose
VI exciting
uh yeah yeah whoever you want we
okay I'm going to start off
with uh uh uh uh rats rat rat rats we
are the rat rats fight yeah don't rat
rats we are the rats rats rats rats rats
ooh we said choosing seraphine I see I
see I'm your support wait I'm I didn't
pick
yet uh got to click lock in I think you
have already locked in haven't you oh it
says
uh uh select your runes oh
God I have no runes okay there we go get
the ruins ask questions while punching
hot I
think I think it's good now okay okay
sorry guys I'm I'm struggling with uh
audio balancing my biggest weakness me
too it's okay okay window switch
there we go oh my God I love your AR
skin wow hot
KDA k
k down down down down down down down
down take it to the
[Music]
top should I buy this world
Adas good luck what do I buy you girls
not buy items
yeah bu little red potion K I think what
what what sorry what buy the little red
potion I think that's a nice starting
why is the camera so
weird so oh you CLI the camera the click
the camera at the bottom and it will
follow you oh thank you hit Y and it'll
follow and unfollow you you'll have to
answer a lot of beginner questions it's
okay much you W Senpai
um so well in the shop W Senpai it does
give you suggestions so I mean I buy the
little starter that it pops up with at
the at the start when you open it
initially okay I did that too but Gigi
and narissa are the peeps like that know
it inside out yeah careful with the
tower who did you say that to to me and
kill everyone
and and and and kill the minions okay
and don't don't die all right I don't
have don't die a distance attack anymore
a ranged attack I like the way you said
minions CeCe
minion let me change my thing I'm going
to make fet minion out of them yes yes
oh
God goodbye thank you God
goodbye goodbye and I clicked no I'm
still alive oh and click and click click
the things and press the buttons yes yes
yes I'm here for you my clean I have fed
the
Enemy No do that they're Bots oh what
what would be what would be
do B is to go back to base to go home
like
teleportation yeah
[Music]
oh it has a channel time and people can
cancel it by hitting you
oh
uhoh am I
Alissa your your your skin keeps making
me think I've accidentally got dmca
music on or something no I'm so sorry
like I'm always like do I leave a tab on
no just you're listening to League of
Legends
just I strugle the most with in the game
is like the camera to just like have to
hold it down and I keep
forgetting I die again hold it down how
like
space
oh you don't have to if you don't want
to you can press y to keep it fixed Fe
CH oh really oh
yeah let's go let's go oh shop
oopsie uhoh it's
okay press y to lock oh
interesting she was waiting for me even
even
now here I'll come thank you are You The
Bard yes thank you I ped the wrong butt
please avenge me that snake lady has
been bullying
me thank you that was good
yeah why did the they have a
jungler is that a jungle character okay
they have a
jungler I don't need a plan why you
leave her I thought she was doing
fine I guess not rat rat rat
rat you must live
rat I am
rat hey turn get
her okay okay are you ready getting
better
CeCe what CeCe right here right here yes
okay yes she is so confused she has no I
thank you yay she's dead we did it f
transfer a
little chat what you in in short words
cuz I can't look at the the text what
does w you do in this case
with the passive it breaks armor okay
wait now I can
read
that I don't have to do anything it's
just always
working what's always working my passive
an
enemy we got her okay here I come no
reset rats rats we are the rats yeah
Rich world of
Atlas was it not
good yeah I think the way Vice works is
you hit something three times and then
they take more damage and then her Q
goes through terrain and walls but you
to charge it
up and she has one more skill forgot
what it does
something it like does AOE stuffs
oh sorry it's a bit much right now I
don't understand anything snake there's
a snake
Okay yeah why have a snake here
snake grubs grub grub I don't
understand to eat oh the grubs she shot
my
[Music]
booty too late okay
did I not sell it did I sell the wrong
thing what' you sell I
know an item
that I didn't need I guess but uh
whatever an enemy and I bought it
again
skin why is she back here what is she up
to
ding ding ding D
I'm see if I can take grubs I'm leaving
where's mid laner what how where are
they yeah where are they Q to fly
longer the mid Lina is here it's
Misfortune their jungle bot takes void
grubs ew what's void grubs
is this an objective I just can't
believe the bot in this game take
objectives they're
annoying
what
uhoh
no so how what how many times have you
girls played this as a collab already
third time this is our third three yeah
hey you are in bottom Lane mother the
trucker I remember you I'm dead I'm
dead don't die don't
die help me kill them Liz no no wait
come back don't do
it the deer is here the deer is here oh
dear oh dear oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
dear thank you she's being really mean
yeah screw that
an you got this this that is a deer
you s a little
dear it's okay I'm almost back blz I'll
support you she's Charmed she's Charmed
kill her I'm a from Tower okay what get
away from
me what oops I ran too late I I ow ow ow
where my
minions minions they're dead that's
messed up power don't worry I'm here to
take your farm why would you do that to
me I'll
leave I'm coming back narissa spots are
kind of crazy all the things they're
doing what is
this don't be afraid go my little
minions go minions oh cute cute cute
oh no Cecilia is GRE
now how do I buy
that time probably oh there's another
one I didn't even see that one
uhoh watch out if you see that white
thing around her it means the next spell
she hits you with you'll get
stunned oh okay Killing
Spree
y Gold Blood flame go blood
flame uhoh she's a queen I'll get dragon
you
fool walk Tower what an idiot true what
an
idiot ah a
fool an enemy is unstable
is there like did you set these Bots to
a high difficulty or so they're
normal could they be
easier
yes I a bad
matchup no you're
okay question difficulties is it normal
intermediate that's normal why is the
horse on our side horse kill the horse
oh she's running away never mind she's
like um oh the the dragon I still don't
know she just explained like a million I
still don't understand explain what what
the what the um the chem Tech is Drake
what is
oh um gives us gold and gives us some
passive stuff so it's a good objective
to get W it's an enemy we have to kill
or
yeah it's a jungle mob don't worry okay
usually in like actual games people
fight around this and then you have to
be aware but we're just playing Bots
doesn't matter too much I I got
this you sound like you totally got this
i got this go top a little
bit you going to be good down here
did I cannot tell the one thing I can't
tell in these games it's like winning or
not evil jungler just took my my my
Raptors your Raptors yeah I can't
believe that Bots counter jungle you I
just can't believe it it's weird it's
weird right yeah it's so strange that
that bot will counter jungle you
so should I CH choose someone that's far
away chat
probably yes run after me you
fool an enemy has been
slain get out of
there nice [\h__\h] me you oh to get all
these before I kill that ma'am get out
of here what the freak are you doing in
here I'm here no go in the forest
careful careful careful
get a B I'm
running oh that completely missed that
was nowhere near her where did she go
wait where is she yeah maybe I want
raged oh Caitlyn is the blue one goodbye
what nice one citn is not
little mm- I
said yeah blue blue blue blue did you
watch ourc did everybody watch
hav seen the second season yet SE the
first
one I watch both finished my Twitter
feed has the second season ofan I love
it although the second season was a bit
rushed yeah a lot of things that they
were she's charm she's charm getting
down
mhm copia is going back so you should be
able to get the tower pretty much
undisturbed mhm okay oh another one GG
Charmed she's Charmed she's Charmed
oops she did not run where I wanted her
to run ow ow good job oh I'm turning I'm
turning
ow she stunned she stunned
owie an enemy has
been thank gosh damn you're having a
party there are you a
DJ yeah it's a it's a it's a party
a the snake is
back that's okay sake oh careful back up
a little
bit I wanted to use my
ulti
yeah did I use it at all oh my God leave
me alone
aloop all right let's come here mother
TR going
if they stay we can kill
them okay let's just kill
her watch out she knows how to
combo oops that's that's a
minion oh you
here careful
careful careful
careful I'm dead wow kill her kill her
kill her G yay
I'll kill her for you thank you good job
I shouldn't have gone in there see the
second enemy let's
get how do I do the thing that I she
jungling again Annie's going back to
Jungle ah no she's not okay I've got it
back good luck
Kiara get
this I let my hands do the talking
oh
no Ari has nine kils is she related to
Naruto back off buddy no she's a goho
well she is a ninetail block so
yeah oh goho like a Korean
yeah regret she
says thank
you Unstoppable yay we got her come back
come back
nice you're getting toxic you're
learning the ways of League of Legends
yes it's true
I'm I mean no you got this enemy bot you
you go come here Lil jungle wonderful
bot let's go out of range
[Music]
I'm going to try a different character
next time I can't get
that your team has destroyed a
turret what boots which
boots there's so many boots which boots
should I
buy sorry I didn't have my heal up you
can get the mar TR I can't afford I need
cheap boots the basic boots
Min you are Gucci I was being
py oh there's three why are there's
three people in mid that's not this is
not fair guys this is not fair top
obsessed with you yeah they they just
you just are very
[Music]
intimidating watch your
step on my way ohop on my way mid never
mind everyone left you yeah I she one
died
leag
Legend leag of
leged
okay I really like like I don't know if
this is like the character always does
it or if it's just the skin but when she
teleports home she like creates a oh
that's the skin yeah it's she cool
invisible SS and then she sits on the
throne that's so of
leg Throne of legal
legs
of my favorite top Champion was always
Riven she's voiced by Christina V
yeah can't fight her suffering great got
this I pressed the wrong button dang it
oh what's that what's that what the
infernal blazes what does it mean they
took the dragon so now there's things
that'll pop up on this map oh
okay an enemy has been SL nice job
yay got I'm zoning
out like mentally or in the game yeah
in my brain I wish I could zone out but
I can't even Zone
in just chilling playing league with the
ladies we
vibing you got this you got this got
this
yay yes yes awesome kill look at you oh
you're so
good thanks to Nissa
she had to go it's all because of
narissa I'm going to die no you're
not I I'm I'm going to back you got this
no you're not you got this you're so
strong Rampage oh my god let's push the
tower push the tower yeah yeah get the
tower they'll never know what hit them I
guess I'll push a tower too no she's
behind you
your team has destroyed the turr don't
worry oh oh oh you're you're going crazy
you're going crazy you you're crazy
you're crazy you're crazy you're crazy
in a way and because of that yes in a
good way and we have a friend and I'm
going to bring you a friend and then
don't worry where am I going why is I'm
running this way friend he's also crazy
ah I died oh no oh no oh no well I
sacrificed myself for a good purpose
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah going to
go crazy again first successful dive
let's go why am I
turning I dived
wow without my diving license can't
believe it unstable hey you're doing
really good no I'm not don't lie Nissa
no you're doing you got this you got
this sure first time is V this is great
I sucked this high when I first played
by
a by look
difficult let's
go I
[Music]
one
no is really hard yeah I can't tell yeah
she's really really difficult I thought
she was going to people were saying
she's like one of the easier ones she's
no they lied to in the jungle she's a
pretty simple jungler yeah your team has
destroyed a to yay a tower is destroyed
unun oh speed for a
moment
wow I'm here I miss should it's
okay let's get her let's get her you got
this yeah get the kill get the
kill nice you're so good look you
sure you did it you're doing it get her
two get her two get her
two oh Annie going oh you got you got
this you got this you're crazy you're
crazy she sleeping you oh oh no oh
no I was trying to figure out how to
make my how to make my ulti work but I
think I have to stand still to use it or
what I don't think you have to stand
still I was press pressing it the whole
time you have to press and then click
again on the person you want to use it
on or if you press um in the settings uh
in um there's like these little arrows
that you can if you just hover over a
person you can use them instead of
having to click on
them
okay hey if if someone can help me just
get the inhibitor
bottom we'll have mega creeps and we can
abandon Lane
te thank you
hello oh is it left thank you thank you
everything be right click in this game
is it left
click it's it's left click I don't
actually I don't remember I just do it
by muscle memory I have no
clue
yay ooh okay
let's try again an
[Music]
ally okay let's go M
timey but it worked this
time an enemy has been SL oh the setting
an ally has SL no it's just
me how dare you kill
narissa how dare you take her away from
us nice Li how do I buy
chilling you're
dead Okay what are we doing
team um what do I buy when I'm out of
stuff
what do you mean whatever whatever makes
you happy I always like to go for a
rabbit On's death
cat a hat Rabon Des okay I forgot to if
your ability power yeah
mid I
forgot oh recommend there's a recommend
list
okay don't kill you ran out of
recommended things to buy um no I ran
out of the things on the one list that
you sent me like the three main items
you lived by this and then I did on
that's
amazing
[Music]
hello nice I thought the de okay she's
TR she's TR nice okay get her too get
her too get her get her get her she's so
fast don't worry we're here get her get
her aesome nice nice nice nice get the
tower
okay that
work get the
inam what is that called what did you
call it inhib it's an inhibitor team
destroy an
inhibitor now
what now what now behind two behind us
ah oh I'm
dead no are not thank
you K kill her
nice
soara if you attack uh your team desty
if you attack them
over when when there's not Creeps in
front of you or if you attack someone
over a
tower like the the tower will start
attacking you so if you're in the
tower's vicinity don't attack one of the
enemy champions
okay and if there's no creep don't don't
go up by the
tower no creep yeah what's the creep
team the little guys fighting for you oh
minions yeah okay
[Music]
Dom live live live it's okay our creep
are going to end
it's
fine your team okay I'll end the game
don't
worry woo we
won y easy easiest game of our Liv so
easy so easy easiest game easiest game
ever winners we're winning we are
winners winners we winners dinner easy
yay first win of the day amazing our
first win of our
lives so
easy so
easy you guys want to do intro Bots or
let's do real people oh actually K
should pick what pick what yeah do you
want to play keep playing B you want to
do bots the real people going to be
easier than the Bots
just depends also there might be a
chance that if we go with real people we
still get bots like I'll be right back
you guys talk about what you want and
then tell me when I get back can we do
easy
Bots I mean I I I don't mind either way
I like playing against real people I'm
not sure if we can play against real
people yet since Ki is on a new account
we might have to do a few more b games
before but we can see if we can go into
Quick Play H
yeah uh maybe we should do bots first
and then um well right now we did M
medium Bots and we won uh so either we
should
do maybe we should do hard to see if we
can keep up against hard Bots before
real people mhm
mhm maybe can I do Caitlyn and Top
Lane you can
yeah whoever wherever yeah be whoever
you want to be just have just yeah just
mix it up I want to try her Kaitlyn
Kaitlyn Kaitlyn's
fun Caitlyn and VI perfect
match all these discounted skins
purchase purchase I'm
back welcome back
thank you okay what did we decide on
what are we up to and
Bots okay Bots and do you just want to
do beginner Bots I'm not sure what was
the
conclusion we'll
do oh I feel like we can handle the same
level of bots you did really well yeah
we did beginner Bots we were playing
beginner Bots okay oh we W playing
beginner
Bots oh we'll continue doing middle BS
okay
okay okay I'll I'll intermediate I'll do
whatever continue continue are we all
ready uhhm we're waiting on Kiara okay
I'm pressing
buttons okay let's play you're already
perfect at the game except icept accept
Caitlyn let's go lock in our
relationship
yeah she's like a narissa but with a
gun what if we all made a star Guardian
team who is that do I need to buy a skin
for that I have so star Guardian how
much there star Guardian Ari how much
cost usually like I think star Guardian
skin would be around
$15 oh 15 or 15 yes
I get to use
my if I want to invest into this game by
giving it money I will decide after this
stream okay that is
fair although I do want to look pretty
in the star Guardian skin why are you
Sona wait let's talk real quick what's
What's Happening Here for
funsies okay we'll
win a problem she or both supports is
the only issue just one of you you can
build
AP go carry yeah you can be anyone
anything okay
so anything you
want okay what do we
have are we already running TR in you
lot let's see this can we do the thing G
where we like kill them in the in the in
the bushes yeah we can we'll have to go
over here I'm so fast okay I'm fast as
fudge
boy I'm
speeding let's
go
hi I like your hat thank
you I like your
ball oh no not the snake again why do we
get same characters there's everyone
here they killed my w messed up we can
try killing them still I'm sure they'll
follow rata she
running kill her kill her is it a her I
can't tell yes yes get her get her kill
her get her get her get
her first
Blood uhoh I'm dead I'm dead no no no
help me no you're not dead you're not
dead you're not dead i y thank
you to an En
very strong this I'll take this this is
mine now wi
open the minions are here you guys can
go to your lane thank you
goodbye you're welcome thank you it was
all it was all us always maintain a
proper chain of command
oh we kill them tried eting through that
wall
Sona can't believe you're here with
us
yay do not move I am running but I am
low in health where are you
running what do you mean you
better you sound like you're directly
out of the game like I wasn't sure if
that was a game Voice or
not voice all the characters let's mute
the game and just have her do it yeah
can you make the noises Bard makes I
don't know what can you make my no he
sounds like wind
chimes scream when she dies
[Music]
anyway oh oh
beautiful
pushing I cannot afford to
fter oh always missed the last hit and
it's stupid me no you're so good
not bad though not bad I don't know how
to ad0 carry sarapen you don't have to
ad0 carry just 8 carry I don't know what
that means oh just just build like
normal AP items I don't know how to AP
carry your
rabadons RAB I just get my rabadons yeah
you can build your rabons where is she
going cuz she's a coward mhm she's a
coward kill her she's Charmed she's
Charmed to heal is normal okay what was
she
doing I'm out of
man if we can just keep getting them to
go back even it's not too bad because
then they they don't get to level I need
healing Duty no Mama no Mana no Mana I'm
out of Mana can't do anything she's so
low but I can't do it I'm out of
excellent
shot guess I shouldn't have used all the
Mana on the
[Music]
meanion
Sarah is oh you can hide in the bushes
too like in the in the Pokemon game too
like you disappear when you're in the
bushes What's Happening Here you
couldn't become stealth what's going on
an assassin of the night
dragon dragon dragon be oh
man Dragon we Dragon we the heart of PTO
is Where Are You
Dragon Killing Spree What's Happening
Here how do I can't are we still on
beginner
bot yeah they're very
strange he keeps like booming behind me
it's so
frustrating I aim to
win
I what if you want what have you want
what have you want nothing nothing
nothing nothing nothing
nothing what do you want what do you
want though what do you want an ally has
been oh
in ma'am stop it ma'am stop it ma'am
kill
you thank you Yay good
kill so if I don't get the kill if the T
gets the kill I don't get any like exper
work on
leveling oh you're only level never mind
I'll stay be
back out of
here oh
how does she know I'm
here I don't
know secret
Ward yeah I'm just trying to hit this
how does she have the knowledge that I'm
here these Bots are cheating of course
they are are always
cheating
Rampage they're stream sniping I heal I
heal I heal I heal yay
yay how could they stream snipe that's
so rud I know it's so cringe of these
bot to stream snipe have minions now
have my
Min minions minions minions minions
minions I heal and then I go back to the
bushes thank you thank
you thank you for the
assist so should I go back for
really I'm I mean l I'm fighting your
mirror match oh match it's a double
ganger a double ganger yeah do
that nah no more cat and mouse an enemy
has been slain nice one thanks you're
the best you're the best
music woo
o what why are they getting these an
ally has been slain how of this Bots
know to get this it's
over no it's not over on the it's not
over the reset over there somebody in
the bushes BF sword what sorry BF big
[\h__\h] sword I didn't know what to buy
wow is is that what I got oh I did get
the BF sword another wrong with the BF
sword someone called for a
sheriff best friend sword oh okay okay
but it
sful takes a moment to channel and line
up the perfect sh then she fires
dominating oh
no oh no can intercept
it all
right no no he's running away I that's
not where I wanted to flash
oops think
again
big big large
wall big very large
wall oops I don't like
aelier like her no she keeps like she
keeps like I'm about to charma then she
teleports behind me and she goes
nothing appreciate that
now yay I got her
yay my bad how does that happen because
I'm I'm connected to leave internet so
what your stream died yeah oh my God
that's really weird what your stream
died I know yeah in peace OBS issue it's
okay it's back it's back but yay the
book welcome back from the dead ow ow ow
ow back sorry woo well you missed me
killing 20
enemies yeah all of them Happ all of
them killed every single one of
them don't kill me this is mine
as expected an enemy you cannot outrun
your CR oopsie I forgot if you hit
someone it's okay ah be good while I'm
gone won't you he's confused he lacks
critical knowledge oh God out played
her I went into Caitlyn I sent Caitlyn
back into her closet she was
invisible you you you heard her yeah you
heard
me let me kill you let me I don't think
we should do that no I got her oh
god let's go
[Music]
minions let's eat more Snake
flesh snake for dinner snake
sausage snake sausage I already ate six
sausages today m
yeah
impressive impressive display I know the
impressive display of very unlike
Caitlyn o I should have done the
AL uhoh what's
this everything I've got a back oh
okay can we have a
Like A League of Legends voice pack from
Elizabeth yeah we need
one oh oh God she's going into the
bushes you're not going to escape me
imagine running away from a Healer yeah
imagine running to be for ignite why I
have to before ignite I feel like often
I press it and nothing happens come here
come here come here you hover over it
you can see the
range another one can break a case
and another one you'll be fine you're
Sona another one okay okay okay I need
to
go do not the
crime no we
running maybe not one maybe
not so many unactivated traps so sad no
no what do I do okay don't die
oh
God how low are you very oh my God
you're very low 26 HP I died to
sarapen oh she aled me she how could she
do this you're the seraphine though I
know how could she I have a
SK yes get hit by the turret yes fool SL
yay these Bots are awesome I like yeah I
like when they run into the turret
because it's like I would do that if
time never sleeps then I another you
would do
that yeah
but I haven't today oh yeah I remember
last I kept getting confused which one
which which which Towers were ours so I
kept running into the wrong
Towers I think I think Le Riot gave me
free RP so I did buy more sarap skins I
want too Riot please we can we can we
can
ask there's two of them why are there
two what am I going to do okay one run
away no she's back next time
boots I'm not here to Riot give me free
stuff or I'm a I'm going to R something
in the floor I'm going to
Riot yeah before we start r
rting just kidding just kidding I'm
sorry Riot I have so much respect for
you sorry Mr RI we already are RI what
get away from
me good trade it's good if I if I die
and I say good trade is that like does
it nullify any negativity I feel yeah
yeah yeah yeah it create good trade good
trade good trade it's creat space for my
skill create space for your skill good
trade good trade good trade good
trade nice no teams finally the turret
is
gone we can now move on with our
lives yeah we can all move onose our
lives and then the next
turret Target the
Aurelia level 10 no come why would you
come here aelia I'm trying to get this
Rift
Herald here
my Rift I work so hard
[Music]
on open and sh I'm a little bit too
happy when I uh kill a champion you as
you should be that's good that's your
life
blood uhoh forgot come over here Al has
been slain walk over here I'm so
low your little watch brain wants me so
bad I'm so
low walk over here just walk over
here
delicious yeah come get
me come on go over here keep pressing D
nothing happens so annoying I don't get
it me a little
closer oops do you also have it quick
casted oh
yes walk up here BS for no one I okay
I'll her her I'll charm her oops I
pressed the wrong button she's charm
she's charm yay that'll show her for
trying to take my Rift heral excellent
shot Rift haral wonder if I can get it
now it's okay it's okay my 3,000 gold
it's okay
oh why
can't got to get a needlessly large
Rod needlessly large yeah needless it's
so needlessly large huh that's why I
need it that's
F necessary necessarily large
Rod
yeah uh-oh uhoh I slowed
live live I live I live ignored me no
respect
oh no yes come here SAR yes you want me
you want to eat oh she ran away yes walk
over here you want T yes I'm on
over
damn okay Retreat tack
ret tactical
retreating leaving my minions
behind for a better time and I'm going
to buy
boots boots boots
boots boots maybe can I buy a potion too
your team has destroyed a turret crime
is common goic is
R Killing Spree killing oo nice new let
me get her let me get her get her get
her get you get her you get her I'm
letting you get her yay crazy you guys
are really
pushing ride into their base the
inhibitor I'll have this finished before
shall we go and
help your team destroyed an inhibitor
inhibitor I thought you said that an
inhibitor does okay an inhibitor an
inhibitor an inhibit
destroy an
inhibitor
goodbye dude stop following me dude dude
stop buts attack them attack
them oh yeah I keep forgetting about my
old see yes oh hi hi n hi I'm here to
[Music]
help
hi hi everyone ow I'm standing in it how
am I standing in it destroy thank
you o what's everyone screaming
about okay okay okay ow she jump she's
Charmed she's Charmed kill her
[Music]
crazy
yipp you're on a rampage kaaa you're
crazy that's
fine I'll avenge you ni to have M I
won't let them get away with
this Char uhoh uhoh uhoh uhoh okay oh
why did you run over
[Music]
here yes yes you're
crazy uh-oh oops I didn't mean to do
that run away run away run away an ally
I'll avenge you
too I you but I clicked I clicked oh my
God let me out let me out out let me
out am I clicking I think the hardest
part is like the moving with the mouse
because like I you you you click because
you're trying to get away but your mouse
is completely in a different place than
you thought it was G and then you always
walk into wrong
areas
hi
hi te for the
heal always maintain a proper chain of
command you got
this I don't think I do but like I
scroll over to you and I just see like
four
enemies walk up this if I had more Mana
I could have done it you can do it you
got this one
more one more
what music I he all music maybe it's the
star
Guardian it's so
pretty
godl walk back over
here yeah don't be a coward Bots come on
yeah come on walk over here we're just
beginners just beginner Bots
owie heing
now we're winning
feeling
Victory eest game of our lives so
easy I think we're ready for
intermediate Bots what indeed I need to
get water okay okay me too actually
sorry I'm like since I'm sick I'm
drinking so much water that's good drink
more more
water I am so thirsty do I still not
have this skin oh I just need the
icon I was about to kill myself okay
I'll be right back do
it okay I'll be be um yeah I'll be be
mhm KD guys are still on my stream water
her
KDA
KDA KD kill you know how it
run around again what it mean that K A K
A what does it
mean look within
you
doggy animals oh so they sing it's
killed def assist yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah wow you got that way faster than me
and Cecilia did really really I don't
know if that's really
fast yeah yeah
yeah yeah I didn't notice until Cecilia
brought up she was like oh kill death
like assist and I was
like why is this why is this yellow are
they telling me I did bad for what my
character could do
potentially or is it just because that's
me what's yellow my damage dealt to
Champions is it just because it's me
okay okay yeah yeah I thought they were
dissing me
can you get skins with the blue stuff or
not um there's the they sometimes bring
back like a blue Essence store but it's
usually a lot of blue Essence it was
here recently H don't know where it went
I don't know if it's still here what are
these mystery boxes oh that's here oh
the mystery which
one what one what you need I want can
you explain them to me like these loot
Loot Crate Box thingies are they the
ones in your
inventory inventory is it in your
inventory in my inventory sometimes you
get these like chest that you can use
and it give you character shards or skin
shards or um Wards and stuff but you
have to unlock it
with this other currency that you get
from breaking down what you get from
boxes h
h i maybe
see so none of these loot boxes have
skins the loot boxes have skins if you
buy a loot box you can get a
skin they're will gold too right no
where there's these
blue b City mystery mini icon icons
welcome back welcome back how we doing
Amer is good good yeah are we ready do
we want to up the bot difficulty sure by
one maybe there's only one more to go
okay let's go nice okay let's search we
got this we got this we got it let's
search let's search for BX that want to
us yeah I hope we find I am seeking
Bots let's change the world
I'm on okay KDA skin time yay woo for me
I flexing so
hard bro I had to play to unlock this
skin I'm not flexing still flex no I had
to play so much to unlock her we we'll
get you a pretty skin too K don't worry
next
time I don't know who this guy is but he
reminds me of like someone from Myspace
so I'm going to he looks beautifully sad
yeah yeah he looks like a MySpace why
why oh sorry wa I don't
know party Kaitlyn po pool party pool
party pool party po party I want pool
party there we
go
sure yay no snake this time oh there's a
cow
cute oh there's a CO
guy cute cat very very quart Lux oh it's
Lux oh no I hate Lux oh it's over oh
yeah I feel like I heard some bad things
about Lux but did not understand the
context what do you mean I don't know
evil she so evil
do um her bot AI is really good because
she's really good at aiming skill shots
because robot
yeah can we kill them all in the bushes
again yeah over here it thank
you oh this guy has a big paint brush
let's go seconds until
minion okay I'll wait for everyone to
get here oh n you look so cute thank you
we match now y We Ready sparkly yeah I'm
ready I'm ready to press the one button
I have I just going to look up this guy
way he's like I'm in the was that ow
flash why did he
flash always maintain a prop
flash anything you say can will be used
against you oh you thank you for the
heal yeah you're welcome nice thank you
everyone
goodbye goodbye not here I'll just go
back to my uhoh oh no look Lux is in the
middle it's over she's in the middle
she's always she's a l and she's in the
middle hey
she's Lux and she's in the middle it's
okay I'm not the same person I was two
weeks ago Lux in the center I will not
lose to this spot this time yeah you are
not the same person what did I do he's
like the guy
from uh from
Naruto which one
sigh name I love s you drew that's
right he drew stuff yes
arti how does he see me in the
bushes if you hit him and then the
minions aggro you they'll reveal your
location in the bush yeah so if you're
aggroed by something it'll show
yourself you cannot outrun
your he's so
cool
yeah cannot outrun your crimes is what I
want to say to w
[Laughter]
are you planning on watching saw after
yeah
totally I'm so
excited like halfway through the last
season of Breaking Bad a you're so close
think I'm going to finish it tonight
maybe oo Yi also I saw I saw I was in a
museum
yesterday and um I saw a painting
that really looked like Walter White I
took a picture of it I need to show it
to you guys later to anybody understand
what he looks like in the first place it
looks so much like him bald and and
glasses and
everything and depressed fa not really
depressed depressed no push me in push
me in it's just like his face just says
he's got issues wow I agree he kicked me
into the the thing he's
rude Target
inside
[Music]
wow I'm a cute Myspace boy that
draws yeah come
on I never used my
space even though it was popular when I
was
smaller uh-oh an ally has been Fair my
space was too cool for me do you run
into our Tower no but I I should have
gone home like ages ago ah and I kept
thinking I should use my Mana before
going home and then I
didn't oops wrong button if time never
sleeps then I best put on another pot of
tea a pot of
tea a PO water bottle of
water bottle of water bottle of water
bottle of water here I'm ready for
you are you back yeah I'm here I'm here
ah she's charm she's charm she's charm
she's charm all right all right I'm on
her I'm on her I'm on top of her I'm on
top of her okay thanks
GG I feel like when it's two versus one
it becomes a little bit unfair why come
here little cow what what do you do when
you're
not ideally in the game you're not you
have like a better understanding or like
you you know where the jungler is and
you know when to not overextend so she
wouldn't have been in that position in
the first place if she
was watching a map or
she when I'm in the middle should I and
you are close to the middle should I
tell
you um when I'm about to engage it's up
to the jungler because it's like um they
usually evaluate the kill potential if
you if like if they went mid would you
guys be able to get a Kill do not mhm or
if there's like other objectives cuz
even though you might engage they'll be
like oh it's not worth it cuz I have to
go to this other place right now and it
would waste too much time here I wanted
to I couldn't in a game though but since
there a black I can just come break a I
wonder what skins he
[Music]
has oh you're so Mana poor good thing
she's not level six
yet oh I'm dead nope I got her don't
worry don't worry going home go home go
home going home yes go
home uh zigs is missing any minute now
oh there we
[Music]
go can you believe that is
here he here in the night sky are like
shooting stars I can't believe
nice nice oh I'm in a back good
job robot yeah you sound very Rob body
right
now
guys oh
intentional I'm almost there I'm almost
it must be
the is it the ping okay charm charm
charm yeah yeah yeah
aome I'll fix it in a moment
am i w am i w i do the
W oh wait I need man really
good like you sound really good hey you
just sound really
good is there no Mana potions got you in
the shop no no oh in the shop I actually
don't
know there's like a refillable potion
but people
don't usually get it or it depends on
what Champion you're playing an enemy
has been to why is it locked here to
protect they used to be but
removed cookies give Mana
uhuh I love
cookies have you girls had some
Christmas cookies yet oh it's evil I
thought it was no have you girls been to
some Christmas markets yet I will not
not yet I did in a voice pack not yet
yeah right it's so it's all just a
lie I did in a voice pack in the last 3
days I went to like six Christmas
markets that's
awesome speed running Christmas markets
I totally did competitive Christmas
monke made it even more obvious like I
never noticed how like all the shops are
so repetitive in the Christmas markets
but it's it's still nice it's still nice
but it's really nice what's your
favorite Christmas Market uh snack
this will deide
everything
[Music]
get the Germans are talking about German
things
yeah
yummy those are like candied almonds
they're like roasted candied almonds
caramelized roasted yeah they're really
good they they sell them at the
Christmas Market
eat them and she was so fascinated she
was like oh my God this is the [\h__\h] in a
good way yeah it's really good it's like
just the right amount of super sweet you
know and
crunchy and crunchy yeah uhoh he pushed
me away thank
goodness I'm going to heal up o y go
ahead oh level 8 strut
away I
painting he's
painting he's a
painter God he's a
painter on the
trail do I still sound like a robot you
were in
no oh it fixed itself
cool soundful I didn't even touch
it elabe Rose blood FL in
oh wait did my flash and my fire twitch
oh that's why I keep flashing why would
they do why would the game do that to me
that's why would they yeah why would
they do that to you I had it I had it
rebound and it it reset
itself oh my God Arias is not interested
in me anymore he realized I am uh not
interested in him
either good good go somewhere else there
he is stay
moving he go what oh he channeled so
fast oh I lost the eye that was the your
team has destroyed was is where
you uhoh oh my
God okay there
damn my aim is so bad man come
back stay here ah for fire no F should
be flash flash it's the okay I got B be
careful FL it's the
Lash the
Lash can't give up I can't give up for
the Lash no for Flash for the
Lash the heart of is it go for pilt
over pilt
over y destroy turet oh my
God everyone's crunchy
uh-oh everyone crunchy why do I have how
about now oh I got
[Music]
boots good now okay get guy with time f
f launches a vision of Despair that
sticks to an enemy Champion for 3
seconds
oh I've had this real weird issue
recently it happened like started a week
ago where my audio just becomes like
really roboty but I can't hear like it
hears sounds normal in my my ears audio
jungle audio jungle you came to the
wrong neighborhood not by
jungle you cow jle come here you cow
nice let's get this mid
turret yes this game is teaching me
restraint no
stone wow he's so good he's scripting
this
scripting yeah what am I looking kill
him kill him kill him kill him kill him
kill he's so fast you got died from the
y yay I'm going home oh should I stay
with you I don't know n I'm afraid of
this killing
you I should have gone home
g g home I should have gone home I never
bought this just
run go Tower
two I'm here
oh let's get the
rumble Rumble come
what no no
no no please Darius please have mercy
okay let me go let me
go let me go little hi hinger that's
zigs Dragon Spa he does look like hinger
though I fought the same when I was
watching the show I was like is this
character going to turn into digs or
what no no they they're their own people
oh unable I have finished before an
enemy has been slain are they
related no they're just little just the
same they're just are they y yeah
yort oh that's what I meant are they the
same species oh yeah yeah
yeah someone call for a
sheriff his crazy
cousin there's another guy down here
Rumble it's who is ready to
rumble
dominating wow oh he healed back
up
the let's finally get someone with this
let's go Oh yay
finally I'm like no
no
no they are celebrating my death they're
cheating up there celebrating your death
yeah
yay W dies let's go it's okay cuz she's
a
phoenix she'll be back yeah he'll be
back BRB
I just wanted to go shopping anyway get
her oh we do now I'm Oh no you're not
we'll get her we'll get her I'll flash
for her oh I don't do enough
damage it's okay we got him we got him
we got him we got him we got him oh he
flashed oh my God so annoying come back
come back oh
God come back okay we got got him we got
him we got
him shut down wow shut
down shut down you know we were
ambitious yeah I mean we have three
people against us yeah yeah yeah yeah we
did really well yeah what is
that it's no issue we still beautiful an
ally I'm a beautiful my space boy so she
came back and then killed you that's
rude kind of mean very rud that was like
this giant arrow on the map and I was
like what could that be but it was on
top of an enemy so I thought the enemy
was doing something but it was her
teleporting I understand now at least
now I know what it looks like you get it
you get it I get it now I get it now
does your guy have a Santa skin I feel
like he suit one always maintain a I
don't think he has a Santa skin this is
his winter one right now steady he would
look really cool at Santa yeah he'd be
really cute
please have
mercy I'm on my way on my way I'm so
okay don't let her kill me Top Lane is
so
depressing you
got take me I you she knows it you
didn't yes yes your flash is crazy you
did it you did it so that's it's on the
wrong butt no it's not my fault you did
it you're
[Music]
crazy
yo an enemy has been SN no don't let me
kill you please I will kill you give me
that
satisfaction whoops B for No One you
scared
me
please there he is the turret W you
coward
enemy
no oh no I love a good
Chase I'm weak again who is this Rumble
where did he come from he the Jung can
you kill this Rumble
Rumble Rumble can you control your
jungley he's just chilling he lost his
jungle he has no idea what's going on
you know oh oh is that a
Teleport that is a Teleport okay I see
it now I see it now
kill
uhoh there he is there he is please let
me
go should have done anything this it's a
lesson I have to learn when there's more
than one
enemy at full health I should not tickle
them cuz me them you out play them no I
died no no next time
what if you play them next time okay
okay I see yeah yeah see what if you
what if you I'll play them but next time
that's a good St actually maybe I didn't
think of it about that way okay okay
thanks
teacher there he
is get away from
me
Rampage we got them got this your
cries get away from me I
can't there's just one okay I can take
on
one your team has destroyed a turret an
enemy has been slain took me long enough
an ally has been
slain securing the per ATT
your team she's a singer she's a
singer she's working late singer she's a
singer listen topress out now Spotify
thank you J listen to Blackbird out now
on Spotify [\h__\h] out now on
Spotify your team has destroyed
I'm on a roll look at you Kiara you're
slaying C all baby all
alone team has destroyed an in all alone
it's okay it's like it's it's a
character
development my
character it's like the an probably
what's that why is that red cirle on me
what does that mean oh no no no it's a
buff it's a buff you have a buff please
okay okay okay okay it's good good yeah
good good good good good okay you got
red buff from
Jungle don't let me
die oh I'll protect you I'll protect you
thank
you
ow oh there's so many of them yeah leave
leave wa I was about to dodge that but
that came fast it just happened she just
got the both of us I'm glad we died
together yeah at least we're here
together okay she's D it
uhoh ooh thank you oh there's three of
them um get him okay okay he's he's
Charmed he's not Charmed never mind I
light unable I flashed again damn it
you're
okay every time
oh the music cute your character makes
cute
music the case and this time I will not
fail
uh I'm
goinging she's working
late uh oh there's two left your team
has destroyed a turret he's Charmed he's
Charmed nice he's dead he's dead kill
him kill him I'm
trying okay it's I'm running oh I'm dead
you're all alone it's
okay over
dominating oo nice Domina
dominating
um yeah destroyed tret
yeah destroyed
[Music]
tret yeah
you guys are
[Music]
crazy oh I'm going to
die that damn
luck damn it luck all her
fault she's tearing us
apart playing the cloud Drake nice
honestly when we played her against the
ls the first time I thought she would be
like super toxic character like you know
like no no the way her character is like
her characteristics she's all positivity
yeah she's like super positive Peace and
Love Somehow that makes it worse I don't
know why someone that's like peace and
love stuns you and then like you in a
line H nothing personal
yeah nothing personal at all yeah she
doesn't mean it she's just
joking I see I see Ally be my wall is
logic is rare go g go kill her kill it
get LS get LS oh there there there's
like the five of them I never miss
go wait no run
run are those the flowers from the show
no
flowers no those are too the Cog wheel I
got it I got it I got
it o oo I can just figure out how to
drive this
thing I'll hit there I'll hit it I'll
hit it this way you D I'm driving here
has destroyed did you become the thing
team destroy you can drive it I didn't
look like driving it seemed like you
possessed it no you're driving it
destroyed an inhibitor
who is
this it seems I may have a new
suspect only the spawn was closer that's
confusing an enemy has been
slain we can end yeah you guys can end
right
now the game we're
waiting we're so good
YY easy easy easy easy easy easy
easy well your first time playing that
guy Liz how did you like him I loved him
I thought he was really
cool nice I'm going to see if he has
skins hell
yeah can he be part of pup
Stars skin time
[Music]
I get more more gold all of a
sudden function describes it
well I got more RP too yeah how do we
huh
yay
RK Ryan thank you Ryan I can get my
m i to buy more sarap pins woo
what my space boy skin did I also get
stuff I I don't know how did they give
me stuff yeah we need to we need to
submit to them your username and stuff
but I got some stuff how did I know my
you did oh you did you got
some how how can I wait I also got some
okay it's time for a new skin what do I
buy thank you Le you know of
uh cuz they can probably see it on my
stream
oh oh it's here thank you Riot I guess I
won't Riot then you you get away scof
free has a winter
skin I'm going to get it how much is
that like the the how much is 3,600 is
that a lot it's it's quite a bit you can
buy a skin where do I buy skin go go to
the right by the RP there's like coin
stacked up you click
there uh uh uhuh uhhuh and then you you
buy stuff there
okay short hairin I think he only has
one skin and it's winter I love winter
oh oh requ Champion I don't have Caitlyn
yet even though I'm playing her she's
she's probably free this week get her
with your your blue stuff my blue stuff
yeah yeah the in game iname go buy her
if you like her
okay I do like
her you know sarapen has a skin called
graceful
Phoenix
o is it red orange
ory it's nice perfect oops don't have a
lot of
I'm a little bit annoyed I doesn't have
a single green type skin yeah believe it
can messed
up am I still in your party I can't tell
yeah uh probably maybe I'm not in it
right now I believe so I'm buying things
you're buying things oh you're not in
here I'll invite you to the game
thanks here press something wrong hi
guys okay money is gone Riot thank you
thank you Riot thank you money is gone I
spent
it I had a billion dollars but I I spent
it
all billion dollars wow very base
billion what is chroma what does that
mean it's different color variations so
if you go to chroma and you look up the
champion you like they might might have
different variation like color
variations for the Skins you already
have oh so it's like in skins chroma oh
chroma yeah oh Ari so for example yeah
if you go into chroma and go Ari she has
green here yeah then you can buy the
chroma and then you can use that
one instead you
know oh this is green
yeah she has literally an emerald KDA
skin that's nice yeah purchase it bye
bye bye bye byy now byy now wait I have
to pick I'm going to get the the the
oama it's time to go to
bed time to go to bed it's time to go to
bed it's time to go to bed oh Jo
s so we're ending the stream no no what
everybody's saying bye and it's time to
go and bye
bye
[Music]
bye Jo summer so if I I should always
prioritize using the blue ones right
since those are in game
uhhuh yeah that was something I did
wrong when I first like got got
characters and stuff okay I got a green
one y are we going to try try real
people now or can we still not what do
you want to do what is this Gwen looks
cool sissors can we play against real
people sure I'm so ready I feel
extremely prepared for the challenge
this going to go
great I
believe nothing can stop me mm nothing
can stop you uh I'm going to change my
thing Cara you need to select uh top l
Cosmetics winter he has multiple
apparently everyone wants me to tell you
about an
Niva I've been seeing it in my chat too
I don't care I just invested in hot
outfits for
Caitlyn play Kaitlyn where do I okay
where do I select an is a bird I don't
know uh right under your character icon
cn's character icon there's like a
little squ where that you
can and then oh you click on the
character and okay got it okay okay is
it possible to change the skin now no
mhm in cosmetics yes
okay okay hot
cute hell yeah hell yeah how do I change
the color of my skin Oh H you hit the
little chroma button you can use the
blue stuff woo got it I got it I got it
let me know when we're all ready which
flash have I did flash flash flash flash
[Music]
flash
bottoms blue stuff use the blue stuff
the blue stuff only theu ready 99% 6
Purity use the blue stuff female dog
you're ready everyone ready I'm ready
I'm
ready we're looking we're going to play
people we're going to play people scared
don't worry they might be B too they'll
think I I I'm just the like 5 years
we're 5 years old with how bad I'm
playing we're all bad you're doing so
good you're pushing top it's okay
because we're together with you so
you're not going to get reported oh okay
okay yeah that's what matters it's okay
even if they reported me I have Riot on
my side what can they
do a
lot it's fine a
party and a lock no there's a lock no
that might this seems like a bot team
you know oh okay okay that's good yeah
yeah I bet I bet they're I bet they're
Bots I'm a star Guardian look green and
gold my Orbit is gold the
green I'll charm them with my swimsuit
[Music]
Green Oh do we do the bush thing I'm
here to protect I don't
know people or are they not real people
we'll see I walk in if I walk in and I
see them maybe they are not real people
check this out everyone I'm about to
face check to see if they're real people
do it I'm holding it do it they might be
Bots that's
fine oops I hope they're
Bots who's pinging me yeah who's pinging
us what's pinging someone's someone's oh
the
robot oh who's that I oh no
are the is the robot intentional robot
again how do you even do
that maybe it is intentional we don't
know I don't think so Robo Liz in the
house Robo Liz am I back there a robot
again yeah you're a
robot
exterminate exterminate exterminate ooh
it's red no I'm so scared
exterminate
exterminate I forgot I canack for a
moment cuz I'm ex terminate there's a
die drop your weapons I'm
here as
expected
[Music]
exterminate can't tell it's a bot or
not you you've been don't worry she's a
bot she's a bot maybe she will walk into
the thingy then that's good all right
all right you ready for this get her get
her get her ah okay she flashed I'm
leaving goodbye I'll take some of this
while I leave you're so nice take this
while I leave goodbye no don't eat
them surrender out of
here believe it first oh oh nice First
Blood oh you back thank
God suspect
engaged I Avenged you don't
worry nice good
job okay CeCe in in about um in about 10
seconds I will come to you okay okay
okay
yes a true is aware of her
surroundings all right all right make
her come back make her come
back okay she will never expect this she
will never expect this she's not
expecting this one what is
D my snowball goodbye thank you wait who
are
you Noo-noo
and will and oh sorry sorry you two
people and will and will okay okay I
have all the evidence I
need I'm so scared I'm going back don't
be
scared you're
beautiful I am retreating I put on
another pot of
tea that's a jungle okay oh
no don't hurt me I am just a Noo-noo and
will
and
willump oh Liz what are you doing by the
tower I'm I'm
reading okay that's I'm reading uh some
bits to do with um this skin makes my
weapon like super super visible compared
to before it's crazy super visible yeah
it's it's nice it's kind of nice
actually super super visible
super visible so slow I am so
[Music]
slow oh
God help
minions super
visible super
visible I'm going home stay out of my
way time for your treat let's see what
animation okay guys I'm going to run it
down bot Lane are you ready have fun no
okay well I hope you're ready for me to
run it down bot
Lane an enemy has take him down
[Music]
woo come back
up oh thank you thank you I did how did
you know she how did she know I want her
to come back an has been goodbye Hi
Li hello I'll help you with this guy for
a moment thank you okay okay okay okay
okay oh I love playing people or totally
people and not B I love playing against
people yeah these people I love playing
against
them I get it oh I
believe oh she's
there crime is common two of them uhoh
uhoh
uhoh why is
there yeah I heal there go is it yours o
cool oh she's nice oh no my guy's not a
Healer I just had that on me I aim to
win okay I might have to retweet here
retweet retweet
retweet like and retweet get oh I just
ran to the wall never mind I know I F oh
no oh no oh no I need to run run run run
run run run
R even
the the okay we going going home we're
going
home I'm done the skin is like she like
hearts and stuff it's kind of like an
astrologian kind of cool
don't know why pref is freaking out a
little I'm a
no someone might be outside today is my
first
time you'll be fine you're doing nice
wor yeah you're doing great yeah is it
easy to stream snipe in this
game we're probably against bots right
now M yeah but is it easy to stream
snipe no
like ow shut
down you look like sa V thank you I am a
magical
girl
highs oh there's a guy there's a guy
here
kill him no I'm not worried about it if
anything I would have welcomed it
getting stream sniped maybe maybe they
would be nicer to
[Laughter]
me feed or I'll ban you yeah they'll
just kiss my feet my beautiful bare
feet please stream snipe
us oh God or don't I
die I'm so sorry
okay shut down it's okay I died too in
solidarity shut down
solidarity yeah I'm slowly but surely
overcoming greed that's good no you
should keep being greedy oh really yes
continue your greed not by a long shot
okay boom continue your greed be greedy
okay okay oh they're they're right here
why are they right here okay wow I'm
coming top oh you're welcome to come as
long as you don't steal my
kill okay I'll let you have it I'm going
to set it up so you can get him where's
he going why is he leaving okay
okay he's never going to expect this if
he just walks up okay okay okay
snowballs get him get him get him get
him get him ready okay okay get him get
him get him get him get him
I took it oh it's okay it feels like I
did it oh okay we did that together yay
there's like four of them
what
expected okay so you're telling me if
there's two people I should still attack
them you should kill them enemy
has you got this okay
oh there's someone else teleporting in
so three people should I still yes you
should kill them I should still go okay
okay okay okay don't be a coward kill
them out of my way nocturn got a blue
buff to get an enemy has been y I killed
her I'm running home see green is good
who's pinging what did I say I know
unless not I not us it's not me I didn't
even know how to Ping what the heck I
don't know how to Ping either which
means is
us I didn't I didn't click anywhere
there so um anything else I should
buy ow come back hit me under Tower
investigate okay okay are you
ready are you ready go in go in okay
he's charm he's CH you're crazy you're
crazy's charm you're crazy
okay I'm going home I will also go home
I
suppose focus on completing one
item G doesn't work guys I was writing
to my chat because they were like poo
box I'm like he's a
parrot he's a coao
actually well he's a type of par he is a
cocka
so like and parrots can like you know
mimic a lot of yeah can mimic a dog
sound very impressive if dogs really do
sound like
that an enemy has been SL ni yay I got
killed I'll have this finished before
time
yes crating
I let out an alt and it did absolutely
nothing it was so bad hey the thought is
what comes yeah yeah my aim is so [\h__\h]
man you spooked
him
what what is that what is that what is
that why are they all doing the
apocalpse
US not turns thing ow why are they why
are they all here
they want you and they what they're
crazy BS are crazy I want to take it I
walk up is it dead is it
gone
[\h__\h] oh oh it reset okay I'll
leave you won't
Escape you got this two of
them yummy
no come
back where is she where is she come here
no that didn't hit
her oo I can do this oh that doesn't go
over there yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum
yum I'm going home okay
going home they hit me your team
destroyed perimeter SEC
[Music]
yay your team
has turret kill her kill her yay the to
the to killed her nice walk up to me up
to me okay you don't need you don't need
you don't need to do that Liz
oh oh it's that oh we got a mountain
Drake
ow ow well I got
Dragon the CH plants bloom so it's worth
it what does it
mean what does it mean what does it all
mean what is you doing what the what
whoa someone call for a sheriff he does
a r done run he was teleporting uhhuh
into the
minion sometimes that's just what you
have to do be good while I'm gone w't
you biscuits heal you oh these god I
didn't even realize I had biscuits in my
inventory H yeah biscuits
oh that's why you guys
a I didn't realize I had any
[Laughter]
biscuits I thought you guys were cuz you
guys like cookies that's what I thought
cookie
cookie sometimes you just wait why did I
leave I can buy more stuff oh my
God yay I got
it you got her
Yum Yum Yum y yum yum
yum um if if okay so I am spending a lot
of time barely killing the the Bots and
then going home should I rather play it
safe so I don't go home and push the
lane instead n kill n n you should kill
them yeah kill them okay what is that
that's the
nocturnal are you dead no I'm alive I
came to help you oh oh no I killed him
he's gone now don't worry okay I just
did what Chad told
me more
mins
singing why she singing don't sing okay
okay I'm I'm roll I'm rolling I'm
rolling she's I'm rolling okay
okay there go my
hero 12 is this
one never
a I'm just a girl
I don't know
the I'm going to go mid I don't know if
I'll survive a dive you're not just a
hello welcome
immig thank you hello please assist me
oh no get away from her oh oh
oh oh oh W you what happened push the to
down so crazy than you for the
help just
morb kind of work you should morb more
often she's almost dead she's almost
dead she's almost dead is it the power
of women that compelled you to do this
it was the power of woman that really
pushed me into doing that that's so
strong I also believe in the power on
the right
side it was very powerful okay I'll
charm her she's Charmed oh I'm inside
team it's okay we're fine it's okay
she's Charmed yeah kill kill you got
this I don't have any
he it's okay you got her you got her
kill her kill her no no
you it's
okay it's
okay keep chasing me sarine come on what
are you doing
yeah nice try Lux your aim is as bad as
mine all right I'm here for you I'm here
for you I'm rolling I'm rolling down I'm
rolling it down go go go get no I ran to
the wall wall I ran to the
wall oh nice nice you got it
nice
double double kill um now I buy this guy
oh yeah oh yeah oh nocturn the heart of
pilt is it
people
wo windows I don't know what that means
I scared him away
you win you win them you know you window
those no minion don't kill me yeah you
win you
Windows oh God your team has destroyed
Windows you Windows Windows you lose
those that's okay sometimes you have to
lose in order to yeah activation key
does he have the same exactly oh ohow I
I'm right behind
you bad idea AR he's going to come out
for me he didn't come
out nice nice nice nice nice he's low
smoking is L there's another one coming
from Top jungle I guess okay did not in
in fact
come why not oh here he's there he's
there oh more friendly people oh
hi I'm being going I'm going behind yeah
I brought them over sorry about that
okay it's okay charm
charm Nice kill kill kill kill kill kill
kill
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice into
the
thing oh
finally
oo let's get this Tower let me kill you
okay Tower I forgot about him
has
destroyed do you have your old kiaha yes
if you use it it's like a sniping if I
can get him low enough maybe you can can
kill him get away from her
Inhibitors I don't know I'm
sorry she just walked into
it but she's she's showing me her pretty
butt
get her get her get
himage
goodbye come back come back he's dead
yay come here saraph be Charmed y yum
yum y yum yum
oops I'm in there I've got got walked
into their home this time I will not
oops you walked into their home and died
yeah oopsie press for it's it's
okay guys guys kill them all fine
planted my ass there worse yeah yeah
yeah worse worse worse
oo we're so good at this game yay not
bad not badara you're slaying no right
now I'm just running because I died I
have been slayed though you're sl you
were slayed no good
though
cating that is
questionable why am I here where is
everybody an ally has been SL
[\h__\h] no we're on our way
away
away will I die to this no nice I did a
thing I got
rooted H guy's right behind
you destroy
tret don't die
Kiara for stamp
oh oh I hey I was here yeah we were we
we were here we were here we
wono we're
[Music]
winners winners
winers this was us leveling up does
honor players just never show yourself
or H yeah you can't honor yourself it's
just the others oh oh this is a screen
where you choose
oh I why would you honor
yourself I thought this was showing the
the good players of the game already no
no you get to
pick I haven't seen that one do I skip
it by accident I don't
know um I just want to go get drink be
right back okay
okay we're doing it wow we're so good
yeah we're doing it we're doing a League
of Legends with the with the
professionals um quick see like some
terms that only professionals would
know um um I think I need to restart my
League of
Legends profal would say that is what a
professional would say need to restart
my League of Legends yeah I see I see
I'm going to yeah I'm going to I'm going
to restart League what why I'm going to
Lane Swap and then I'll I'll midgap and
then I'll and split push and then okay
and then I'll uhuh tower Tower tower
Tower to tower Tower I agree with
everything Sol solo Baron um um um um um
flash yes what what about your
micros oh all of them
yeah I I got it I understood did you get
what I meant yeah I I got I I understood
that solo bolo jungle uninstall un
jungle uninstall that is what League of
Legends Pros would say proxy proxy I am
just very confused about all the words
that are being thrown
around um um they're good words jungle
jungle diff What does diff mean
difference diff diff yeah it basically
if you say it to someone it's like
you're complimenting them jungle so if
you go into a normal game you should say
that and you're complimenting them
you're lying to me I can hear from your
tone of voice don't try G you say don't
even try you're gapped it's a compliment
and gamer yeah oh I see I see so make
sure to use that in your next League of
Legends game teach me more what else
should I say so yeah just because I want
to be a good player a positive mindset
what should I say okay okay okay so next
time you go to a normal game just go
just say like pick any role and say like
I don't know mid Canyon mhm yeah can
someone tell me why I got promoted to
bronze the game yay she's
bronze you're BR I'll do that thanks for
the I've invited you bad oh you invited
me I just checked their
stream they made it for the
queue damn did they do that did they
cheat what did they cheat the poe girls
got for the like bibu and Kyla got uh
into their they did they did
nice I'm trying to get in and it's
telling me that I need to purchase a
code but I purchased a code huh so what
does it want from me why is it lying it
wants more codes what's more that's all
you had to do wait damn skill [\h__\h]
okay
after true right it's okay it took them
it took them three hours they waited
three hours that's crazy that is crazy
I'm glad I didn't do that
hello hello I'm glad I'm
here welcome back I have no regrets can
play uh Exile 2 or I have partially
regrets but mostly no regrets no regrets
no regrets reget yes no regrets
absolutely no none
regrets no regrets allowed in this
household none of that
no none of that no
Cecilia you jump scared me are we in are
we ready for c yeah yeah oh I haven't
said anything in like a while you did
you did
something oh getting ready for
kill sorry oh I
oh okay okay
okay we're queuing we're queuing we're
going to queue six people I doing accept
are we doing yeah we we'll do real
people yes yes yes yes I
believe I like real people Me O heart
throb
Warick oh heart war will
Warwick B
[Music]
oh yeah I am a
Harding inde at the end
[Music]
yeah
remember darling you you'll love her be
on that one
k for
me do something
[Music]
special you'll see I won't spoil it
I'm so fast do we go into the bushes
seconds until we can check we can see if
they're real
people how do we know if they're real
people um
Instinct yeah okay I think they're
Bots that's a
bot at least I I don't have any CC I
didn't start with it I'm leaving oh
thank you if it's a bot they won't judge
me too hard ah
minions anything you why on my Lane
hello no you look so different how could
you I should have started dou
you should have start you double
you oh the music inviting me I do love a
good get them get
them oh Nissa it's woring is it I can't
get
anymore
annoying trash man oh nice it looks cool
this yeah quick bye
guys
goodbye heal up I miss you
oh really
really you little [\h__\h] ah they're low
there's two that are low here guys
get
running worry not boom
head oh there come back okay I'm I'm
here for to harass her
jungle okay okay
okay an
enemy good that was totally worth it I'm
going to die leave leave run away run
away it's okay the minions are keeping
everything up I don't even have to do
anything
yay
yay you can go home you should go home
I'm going
home she's going home she's a woman
who's beautiful she's a woman wo woah I
said she's a woman who's beautiful
she what are you trying to say huh oh my
God W I didn't know we were like that I
didn't know we were that kind of League
of Legends team
for aown I oh that's the experience that
I was looking forward
to wow he has to
heal uh what's that what's what's his
name good Chase GA
Gallo Gallo G Gallo I hate that guy hate
him but he has a chicken costume and I'm
aware of it kfp I'm aware she's
aware everybody told me to look at it
the an En seen a
nice I'm
back nice brilant where are you running
Charmed Charmed Charmed where are you
running
to an enemy has gave me a kill for free
he's so nice yay
paid
actor all
right it's working
L my head forever it's hard to get out
is people cuz she's
a singer beautiful woman a
singer I'll switch the order
now cuz he's himer
Dinger oh my God oh there was a sparkle
in the
world wait why are there two of them
that's not fair that's a bot you know
she just doesn't know what's going on
doing her best I'm going to
die you're not going to die not today
not today
an look at this guy what are you doing
keeps going back and forth what is
that what's the're doing B the best is
not good enough they're trying really
hard back up the Bots are going to kill
you or the
minion m oh God I'm going to die no okay
now so you're going to Flame the
bot are you saying I deserve this yes
you deserved that you deserved what was
coming for you for flaming the Bots yeah
don't Flame the poor Bots this one
yeah maybe I should have blame M this is
what you get for being toxic and this is
a lesson we should all win
early okay
oh that's so cute Bigg snowball ever
learn get okay okay okay he's charm he's
charm he's charm I'm killing this
Gallo oo kill him yay we did it it get
the other one get the other one sh
okay shut down okay I she's Charmed it's
Charmed
it's okay okay okay no don't
go no did you get oh no wait there's
another one behind I'm going to get this
dragon
now get
it he could have killed me if he wanted
to I think he's in love with me I think
so the only logical yeah makes
sense I have my ult now I'm unkillable
because I can run
away oh I will just I'm leaving
obviously
okay wait there's two there's three it's
over I'm doing my best I'm definitely
you're doing greata you're doing
fantastic you're doing great I lost my
lane and it's it's 100% because of the
jungler yeah because of G way wow GG
yeah my bad it's just how it is
sometimes I'm going ocean grapes I'm out
of Mana I mean I can try him for you
okay I'm going
mid okay okay I'm eating him all I can
do now I have to leave okay I'm running
away too oh he's confused he's confused
hit him hit him awesome okay okay hold
on he's Charmed he's Charmed I have okay
go in go in go in go in yay it's it's
easy easy easy easy easiest game okay
now I'm going
home nice
yay yeah
war did you use your ult already
yes no oh you not asking me don't know
who you
asking oh
really cuz I know I'm alone here so no
one's talking to me it's okay no I I I
watch I'm looking I'm watching you yeah
if he's really low like that and he's
far away you can save your ult for last
and you should be able to kill him you
actually talked to
me what I want I have my eye on you you
watching me watching you I'm
Charmed W thank you I'm
ding thank
you
damn uhoh do do you have my stream open
in the second screen or I am I just I
click on the map and I look at
you why I why do you even have time for
that wait I'm losing my Lane because of
you you should focus on your lane
you don't want to watch prows they
they're like crazy with doing that yeah
I can imagine they got their eyes
everywhere ow there's one guy here up
here there there there there there I'm
Charming him he's
Charmed okay let's get get him get
him oh no no make him regret living
okay okay there's another one there's
another one right
here wait never mind kaha is dying I'm
going to kill that Warwick no don't
steal my
kill don't die don't die Ste her kill
I'm going into my locker bye no no no
here I'll set up this kill for you I'll
set up this kill for you I'm already
gone I'll get this kill I'll I'll avenge
you okay oh my God he feared
me can you
are you seeing what she takes out of the
locker is what does she take out of the
locker it's a picture of VI oh really
I'm rolling the ball I'm rolling the
ballute she he has no idea what's going
on oh wait don't spoil it's fine I
haven't see yeah don't spoil please it's
fine oops what I don't know anything
what it's the animation in the The Bee
no no no I didn't mean that I was asking
follow-up questions and then I I took it
back don't worry
killing
[Music]
sprink fool you stand no chance I killed
him what is that I see he is dead you
did that because I said that I lost my
Lane because of you previously huh yeah
I had to I had to get rid of him I I
really got it back
they don't care chat you won't
Escape We Care no no no no
uh I I don't mean
you it's okay of course we care about
you no no no no we love you we care I'll
come back and kill him again no don't do
that I'll make can regret up
there oh someone's
teleporting who who's teleporting guy
tell him not
to I'll do that next time oh yeah I need
the eat the cookies eat the cookies eat
the cookies geky my ALT is ready and I'm
like lowkey dying oh it's okay he's
leaving I don't know what he's doing
over here do not move stop stop fearing
me I keep forgetting to eat my
biscuits at least you have
bis goodbye
unable double
kill all right good Tower
yay there's some people up here but I
don't think they're coming up here yet
all not mean the flash back finger that
do you need help right here right here
it's okay don't die to her I can do an
Al
y okay
okay oh God oh God we can do this maybe
yeah we're doing it give me the kill
give me the kill I'm get it get it get
it no no no yum y I'm just I'm going to
leave right here right
here look picture
time
no yay close that was
close oh just a little bit of power so
none of my letter abilities work on on
the towel ah what the hell was that no
that
sucks oh he has a lot of Health no weird
he's a tanky Champion he's tanky don't
appreciate it quite
tanky wow what's she doing over there
I'm going home home yeah charm the tower
the tower starts walking towards you
yeah you're like uproot
oh byy stuff where did he go there he is
I came for you Warwick I'm getting my
kill one way or
another grow legs and then he starts
walking towards you that'll be
cute
[Music]
oops we got
him I damage I be more damage
good it doesn't matter who gets him as
long as he dies
right oh I mean no I me I me I don't
know how I got
him
good oh back I I don't mind who gets him
tower Tower tower
Tower kill
him got them in my
sight no come back come back come back
come back come back come back oh
no get
herant all right all right I'm here he
has no Mana he has no
Mana keep going keep going
yay
destroyed oh he's behind me
he's he's behind you oh it's a toad why
is the toad attack toad I mean just kill
him
teesty why are you attacking us Mr Toad
that's not very nice a toad a
toad I'm coming jungle
minions I'm in
Jungle if I'm welcome what is that what
was that oh is that a b yes Hi Li thank
you
your team okay okay okay let's go get
him I'm
leaving oh wait this K I'm
stupid I I I thought played play last
time so I was like oh oh I'm done down
he's Charmed he's Charmed
oh I'm dying it's okay run an enemy has
SL I'll stop them oh
wa wao he's still
running oo
o oh no one
H he's running at me we all here though
come back mid we all here okay
Domin
nice nice nice nice nice
nice get the turret okay
awesome
nice
oh oh what oh I died from the tower my
bad time I will not fail my
[Music]
bad
oops oh you think you'll walk out over
here yeah yeah he's coming your way walk
over here come
back no he's not I think he's so scared
he's too scared of you what is he scared
of oh he's coming
back don't be scared go
ni Gallo's
too no you got him you're two people and
there's G right behind
you killing spree
what is is that an elephant no tiger a
Bo I'm not sure an animal play time is
never over welcome to the table I guess
hello fluffy
monster of course she wants to play
league is she only she thinks I'm done
streaming cuz I'm so
quiet destroyed girl I'm still streaming
let's get top Tower oh guess I should
talk more this is my
sign it's okay we're all locked in we're
we're all locked in so hard ah ah ah ah
locked in but
not goodbye chunky
wonky okay uh
I am here but I am low ah shoot
shut okay we did get two it was worth it
was worth was worth
worth what's worth wor
worth okay he's almost dead do you see
him yes on the right yes oh it's you
nice nice nice
nice
legendary your team has destroyed an
inhibitor charm
charm nice
nice from the long AR of
the where's my mouse I'm
[Laughter]
coming uhoh again not again I almost
died I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine goodbye everyone good job Ending
game you got him fine uhoh uhoh I'm
dead it's fine you guys can
finishes you got
this CRA a triple
kill you so good you so
good no no live she's weak you can get
her nice you you you got a triple kill
you got triple kill oh look at you
Kara you're crazy yay
League of Legends
Pro League of Legend
Pro g
g g G's good
work
[Music]
GW oh my God I can honor more than one I
can just honor all of them yeah
oh oops
not
biased do you
think what would would l b okay going
top does wa want a bot Lane oh yeah you
want to support what the hell is bot
lane or she can still play Kaitlyn yeah
Kaitlyn is spot I don't mind uh doing
whatever okay don't bother me I mean I
love I I love you
Nissa I love I mind switching it up oh
bot I thought everywhere is bottling cuz
the Bots are everywhere no
oh what so should I go bottom yeah go
bottom oh I'll I'll see a different
scenery for once mhm okay
okay yeah and then narissa will set up
all the kills for
you
okay oh she will steal them all is that
what I hear from that
giggle I I nothing
intentional I believe okay one second
I'm just getting water up but I'm still
like here okay you will steal them it's
okay like if I don't she can't steal
anything that doesn't exist there are
nor kills in the first place with
me no she she's going to set them up and
then you're going to kill steal her it's
probably more like she's setting them up
and she's killing them
I'm just there for mental support we
have to do it together
okay okay play play again okay I'm here
okay okay let's go I'm
baby I'm baby I'm baby I'm
baby I'm sorry no no no no Liz where are
you just practi Liz we need you mine's
still loading
uh Lo loading back into the thing yeah
now it's doing it well I've recently met
a baby so I think I'm pretty good with
you know baby sound you recently met a
baby yeah and I Rec the mystical
creature and I I I I uh it it pulled my
hair it was pretty fascinated with me I
gave it an elephant it like the elephant
yeah I think it was in love with me
so I'm good
baby baby do I need to click something
different now no okay no you can just
swap you can go top baby was cute don't
have to swap the
thingy you pulled my hair
yeah and I didn't mind I would I would
like to go back botom after this game
though
okay it's just a test
yeah with
grades so I'm going to go Bottom
now yeah go back waa fairy C this looks
like
Victor I know it's so pretty the
guy oh we on the oh no we on the other
side oh no oh no oh no is that
bad oh that's
me personally it doesn't change anything
but it gets really confus no is
confusing let's see if they're real
people so is my bottom the top now
because we're the other way around yeah
go this way right here uh wait wait wait
why is the view always so weird in the
beginning why do I always have to change
it I don't know we going into the into
the into the bushes GG we can see if
they're real I'll poke my head over
should I
follow are we going into the
bush yeah we might die okay I don't see
them they might be starting
blue blue should I walk over there just
to look yeah I'm behind you I'm behind
you okay oh are are you guys real are
you guys B guys are you real are you B
yeah you real people where you going
Sarah where are you
I'm trying to be my individual person
wait there's someone there are they real
are they real I'm too used to
being oh no that's that's I'll come
hurry we'll just go to Lane okay are
they real an enemy has been SL he's dead
it's okay oh they're here hey wait
that's a real person that's really yeah
they're they're definitely real that's a
real person that is a real person back
to the tower back to the tower wow okay
I'm at the tower you're playing against
a real
person the Lux is real the Lux is real
no bot Lane is definitely real
people it's okay I got this we've
trained for this
guys no we haven't yes we have yes we
have sorry sorry oh
hey what ELO are we playing against
What's Happening
Here what's the best thing to do
now
wow
um you just are supposed to kill kill
the minions last hit them you get money
so when you die or go back you can um
you know well
to get stronger
yeah I meant more like she's running
away from me I know why she running away
from you are
scared h i mean there is no retreat we
just have to keep doing it if you're
struggling you can come back by the
tower
okay I carry the Legacy blob blah Ari
blah blah blah blah tell us she's
telling us her entire life story blah
blah blah blah blah
blah I'll make this quick
okay this Le is being careful whoops
what the
hell come here
CC where is here up up yeah where I am
I'm coming to know what others do not
okay charm good good kill him kill him
kill him I don't have a ward I'm afraid
of walking in I'm very
low no I have okay he there's two now I
can't
okay I die to this oh I die to
this cie
[Music]
owie music go peaceful it has to go so
peaceful here to ser
I'm here to
protect ow ow ow ow
ow I prefer playing against
bot no no it'll be okay I like I like I
feel more fulfilled when it's a real
person than a bot yeah it's a learning
it's how you learn it's how you actually
get
better I mean from like minions ow I'll
use all my man and then I'll leave yummy
yum yum
no no I'm going to die have confidence
nope have
confidence oh no oh no oh no I am dead
oh no oh no no no
no all right I will come smack him soon
maybe let me kill all these little tiny
[Music]
babies you leaving they're pretty good
they're pretty good
bot that's a little look Gigi you're
going to have to
carry I'm I no new okay okay I'm here
Liz I'm here the of the I'm going
to I need get closer to be able to do
what I want to do oh no where go no he
healed oh I shouldn't have
flashed oh I don't know where they are
well nice
try predictable there they
are okay she has no Mana I'm running up
okay go go go go
go nice can I blame the Ping have 170
ping blame the Ping thank you
though it's that goddamn ping every time
I can maybe I can maybe if I charm
her ow ow he's
hurting
appr I'm going to go back let's go I can
walk bottom
wow he's iceing with himself it's so
cute I'm going for the Draven or the Jin
go on okay well I hit them but I have to
leave they're they're leaving back up
back
up I want to go get grubs so careful b
side
okay crubs crubs
grubs grubs back up we're really low
always aware of
surroundings
nice
thanks go my minions oh your minions oh
uhoh what was that does this music come
from you
I don't
know yeah the music comes from
the so
caling double kill
uhoh may have a new suspect uhoh got you
[\h__\h] female
dog help
me jilbert please save us I can't I
can't I can't fight this no no she's
level seven okay I got I can't fight
this Warick a good investigator always
remains it's okay he's on
grubs can't really can't do anything
here I got you
biscuit no Lux leave leave I'll power
alone you
Fe yeah leave it alone
take my jump off
it's we can go kill Warick if you want I
don't think we can kill Warwick oh two
people two versus
one oh he's just standing there we can
walk towards him I don't think we'll
make it there in time is the only
problem by time he leaves he's they're
already level six we're screwed oh he's
right there I see him they have alts we
don't I'm
it's okay
I'm to you I'm walking to you oh no Al
SL I'm too I'm too behind to do much
it's okay it's okay sorry it's
okay let me grab this
chares please stop pinging
randomly ma'am um I've been told it's a
polite thing to
do if you do it correct correctly oh I
think retreating was the correct thing
to do it was just too
late wouldn't you agree
chat ow no she rooted me she always
Roots me no he rolled at you let's crack
this case wide
open goodbye what the heck
oh my
God where' you go that one is like a is
that the stun I can't
tell I think
it's an ally has been
SL this this
be oh just walk oh he walking okay I'm
coming from behind the war might come
back I'm I'm dead I'm running away no I
missed I miss don't worry I scared her I
scared her I scared her I scar oh oh no
oh no oh no oh no I'm going to be more
careful oo it's good go go go go you got
him an ally has been slain o okay never
mind it's okay no you got this no I just
I was trying to W the bush
no wait that's messed up only the bear
dies and the girl still lives and then
she just like lays next to him on the
floor what do you mean the bear which
bear Noo-noo and W which one I don't
know your animal your pet yeah morning
the and she's fine and then she just
lays down on the floor she's living
that's messed up she dies of
s a oh it's a Yeti Yeti Yeti is a bear
if you think about
it okay we can still turn this right
guys yes we can still turn this around
no yeah yeah yeah turn this around we
can do it
duh I should have just played
team I'm a te melted
bottom oh my God okay what Strat do we
do quick do the Strat numers seven I
think number seven if we do seven I
think we got this so can you tell me my
first day was Strat number yeah of
course I can tell you I'm sure everybody
else knows but you got to explain it to
mece thank you yeah so the Str read the
manual on the
strats coming behind me is coming out
behind me he's behind me he's behind me
oh behind you okay I'll charm him over
here yeah he's over here somewhere by
myself what it is okay I'm running away
again pleas okay running back to my
minions your turret has been destroyed
over's I work for its people no one else
that's not
good oh he's here oh where okay okay
okay he's charm he's Charmed oh I'm
going to try coming Mondo's on his way
Mondo's on his way going to try coming
back we're both dead okay yeah I need
try here for the Gin oh he
flashed I mean I need help top I'm not
bottom
anymore you need help
okay yeah I need help top for my watch
out for this Warwick Let's Get
Him whoa what is
oh actually as
Mundo what is this what is all this fire
everywhere fire fire like fire fire
fire like the fire high as you desire
very
collector an enemy is legendary no not
legendary that's fine he got executed he
was breedy ni nice what a what a fool
what a loser fool just kidding he's
kicking our asses no no he's a fool he's
a Los like a fool fool
let's go where am I to go even the
smallest clue can break a
case we're getting stomped no we not
it's okay it's okay we're fine we're F
yeah we can turn this
around I don't know I don't care just
has to come up with some Strat and tell
us what to do that like really one kills
and we have two are you sure two expect
uhoh uhoh uhoh oh got that they're all
here the war and the freaking M got
me I will die can you come up with like
a cool Str no don't die we going to
fight them okay that's a good
idea that is my plan mhm going to bite
we bite them them okay what if we just
went next you know re like a reset okay
okay like like we go to the next
game what if we what if we went to the
next game that sounds like surrendering
not winning that feels like the opposite
of winning no it's winning it's
winning I can't get this nothing ow
they're all here I'm coming I'm coming
I'm coming bring them mid uhoh there's
so oh my
God your dead body and the dead child so
messed up the dead child
too we can we can go next to reset and
maybe we'll get worse people no they're
going they're going mid I think they're
all going mid
hooray surrender
what
enemy who voted no
wait who voted how many people have to
have to vote it has to be unanimous for
early surrender anous
man oh if only that was if only we knew
who that was too bad we can't figuring
it out oh it's only oh it is unanimous I
suppose that's the first time I see that
today it's very depressing I know no
it's okay the d stands for done well
done and
the I finished my second liter of water
give me a sec I need to grab more
more BRB okay
BRB okay you are still not muted on my
screen you know
okay
[Music]
H 13 kills from that cloudy Jester
gin
13 oh speaking of J try sh Shak Shak
shako uh let's see do I even have him
yet we fed him too
early but I am a fast food restaurant
owner so I'm here to feed people no
that's true I need to feed them they're
also
hungry I would be evil if I would let
people
hunger yeah
thank you you're just so kind and
giving I I I do like to receive too but
that's in my private life I
suppose as a professional businesswoman
I like to
give
yeah yeah what's your love language
herb what's my love language
[Music]
uh
uh h
we should all take one of those quizzes
yeah I feel like I'm the only person who
didn't take this like Omega quiz thing
oh I haven't done it yet cuz everybody
was taking I is it that
short no well I don't know we can we can
still look at it afterwards after stream
after after stream cuz everybody was
taking posting the results while I was
busy with L and uhad I even and still
what a mega verse means it's it's
important it's important apparently it's
very
important it has 40
questions 4 oh that shouldn't be too
long returned hello did you take the
Omega quiz
Cecilia no not yet you haven't wow I
haven't yet why I should I should what's
your excuse I forgot about it I saw it
and was I should do this and I forgot
about it really how can you forget about
it when it's been going on for like
three days everybody's it Ki is
saying and me haven't done it yet so
yeah I see I see but I have a good
excuse what is your excuse I was busy
the past three days with ladies in my my
house should I have picked that one yeah
ladies did you have ladies in your
house I'm a
lady I mean excessive amount ladies
excessive
there's too many ladies my mom's a lady
have you been having a nice time yeah me
and the ladies or you and the ladies me
and the ladies we had we a nice time
very nice time and magnificent marvelous
time so beautiful they love
Austria everyone loves Austria so two
out five of us here have taken the O
Omega I will say one thing yes
how much longer do you girls want to
play because one person in this room has
a uh thing to do that I I can't even get
on don't even worry I want to apply uh
not pressure but I want to remind oh who
is it who has the thing to do
a someone sounds very guilty
I
see it's practically done it's just I
whether I whether I want to add a cherry
on top you should you
should you know yeah sure I'll add the
cherry on top add the cherry on top and
I will eat
it should we play another one yeah yeah
we can play one how long does the Cherry
take last
um shouldn't take too long all right if
we do one more then yeah I'll have I'll
have time all
right let's go hold on are my runes
correct okay finding match Comfort P
Teo oh you're doing P Teo this time okay
did you guys comfor P Teo I oh I want to
change my
catar everybody
in room has participated in the Advent
calendar already except for one
person I declined it you can switch your
character thank you sorry I can try try
Lilia an actual jungle
looks oh my God te with the be skin is
called that's so cute beo I love beo
beo beo wait who are you Arcanist sh can
I go top again bottom with stressful
yeah you're going top why would you say
that like you want to get rid of
me you're not a good
goodbye how do I learn then how will I
ever learn you're limiting my you need
read you need to read how to play it
read how to play and then try again w
w hey I I am sensing some hostility is
this the toxicity that I have heard of
hovering over the report
[Laughter]
button no I'm just I'm ready now I don't
care either way I broke up before you
broke up with me I already said I'm
going back
up should she already sent a letter good
fine then good I hope you'll have fun
down there being bottom without your iot
lane yeah
goodbye I already
have who's who's joining you down there
H herb me
[Music]
a I said off I said before the last game
I want to go back I'm ready you want to
go oh okay I wish you two happiness I
see I I've seen this coming in the past
weeks and months anyway the signs were
all over the signs oh my goodness
gracious well you knew that that we
would be like pairing in the in
the I I've seen this paing since the
very beginning I've seen the Synergy in
your colors and your designs
mhm well she's monitoring me you know
yeah I mean I'm monitoring yeah I mean
Cecilia and Gigi also monitor Nissa too
so
yeah o I'm ready
I don't see
[Music]
us are we checking if they're real
people again they're real people I'm I
hear KDA
music of
me are we going into the bushes or not
nah that's the most fun part of the
game I'm finally my own 30 seconds until
minion spawn me and my minions we're
going to do it guys you want to you want
to want to see this oh my God you're a
little clown you're a little
clown my goodness who are you playing
against is that lux okay no Lux it's
okay my goodness wa no what is
this have smolder smolder is that
a what do I need to know quick I know
nothing about him I I I think it takes
him a really long time to ramp up he
needs a lot of
farm and his old is this big line and he
flies around and he's
like and he throws a ball at
you Moulder from a cane
hello yes that's crazy wa turn turn on
your screen question mark someone is you
can't tell me what to
do okay okay do whatever makes you happy
that's fine I have to I have to task
manager my way out of it why is it not
Window mode anymore what happened
actually you wait why is he doing more
damage than me messed up even the
smallest clue can break a case he's
going to farm huh anything you say can
and will
be so nice to see you again you thought
I was alone did you
you are
wrong yes you wrong I think bot is real
people I'm pretty sure they're real
people that's
still war behaves just the way I like it
so I think he's a
bot mhm can the team be like half bot
half real
people not sure I think that's what
happened last the time we played yeah I
think if they don't have like a full
team and there's like not a good amount
of people who can join with them they'll
just like supplement with Bots that
would be
evil oh drop your weap okay she's
backed is it like common that the Top
Lane is always played aone on the bottom
is always double yeah
yeah Bottom's not as aggressive as last
time which is good maybe maybe maybe
they are bot may you should have you
shouldn't have Judge Me by One game
against Real players I'm not judging you
I'm not judging you I would do better
now
perhaps I'm not judging you just bot bot
all the lanes in all the different areas
are play differently B oh they're all
Bots they're Bots for Wheels is mine bot
guys yeah they're all Bots yeah
[Music]
y the jokes on you come here come to
come to where I am you yeah yeah oh guys
going to want to come see this oh don't
run up to him though he's melee don't
run up to him he's he's a melee range
champ
I wasn't looking at my HP you got him
you got him you got him you got
he I don't know anything about this
Champion messed
up no his life
steal well an has it's okay they're Bots
it's okay it's okay nothing wrong with a
little feeding
I see right through you oh she's so
close so close to death I'm dead why'
you die all I thought she was going to
die she's so weird I thought she was
going to die
narissa oh God now I'm going to die he's
going home wait wait wait yeah kill him
kill the bot kill the bot oh he just
left yeah he teleported away oh he went
bot
mhm oh what that's a skill Oh I thought
he was going home if it's purple it's
teleport I think it was
gold don't
remember wow if it's blue it's the
back an enemy has
[Music]
SL get her get her get
her oh
minions enemy has been slain thanks Dy
that was very very productive no
problem
thanks no problem thanks GG just doing
my part
thanks oh no I'm out of
man
ow by my
I'm living my best life she says
actually I'll leave one of these byebye
oh okay
goodbye oh I can zoom
in I'm coming oh God oh
God
funny jungle attacks got them in my
is that what you is that what you
need is that what was GG jungle attacks
yeah yeah is that part of League yeah
it's part of League you know it's normal
you should get used to it yeah all right
it's a normal thing that everyone does
all right all right all right I
understand now
no I don't think so I don't think the
boss intelligent enough for that oh stop
him
oh oh wait there's so many of them
there's three people in the
jungle HHH has it's okay you distracted
them I'm sure that they won't get the
last grub the they're going to go to k
though okay I'm running oh my God they
killed my guy you got him kill him kill
him kill him jle tax jungle tax jungle
tax jungle tax ta jungle tax jungle tax
J jungle tax come on I'm getting the
jungler the jungle tags a
owie he charm okay you're crazy do it
again uh give me like 5 Seconds change
my mind nice okay bye goodbye do you
have like a heal or something nah it is
what it is that's fine so when they do
damage to the to the Jungle people to
jungle animals don't die can you like
kill kill them and then steal their kill
yeah you can steal the the jungle
animal that's a
strat that's why you always want to
fight objectives and take it from them
brilliant I
[Music]
miss let me have your let me have this
no
please let me have your blue
do not disturb the crime scene until I
return oh where is he oh he's right
there can't hit it take
it take your blue they're weak we'll
fight it together Voli
bearby this together prer to walk oh
smooy is also here sleeping baby hi hi
oh my cat why do
that oh he's he's flying he's flying
he's
[Music]
flying did you hear that so cute he just
jumped up chirping man home don't press
buttons thank you I must always be three
steps ahead she wants me to watch the
enemy she's so cute the enemy oh the
enemy she
left to be my enemy she's an Arcane
hater don't be a hater arane from League
of
Legends yeah from League of Legends
League of Legends you know they made a
game based off Arcane oh my God League
of Legends how it feels to me
crazy you're fake fan fake League fan
they made they made a game off not
before joining you guys of course we're
fake fans what you
think I'm an Arcane fan oh what's sorry
Ryan it's my first day well you're
playing league so wrong
one
so come here you little bot get him
clone get
him
aim I do love a good MST
weak an ally SL what was take away my SK
yeah that was like a wave oh there's a
guy oh that's his old run oh that's his
old okay uh level eight I love taking
your farm I appreciate that you know
someone should take it I never hit the
last hit
anyway I was might as well make this
quick are you dead no I'm running
down oh they leaving oh what is he oh no
oh no you don't you don't see me I I see
you I'm helping I'm helping I'm helping
you're helping you're crazy I'm helping
I'm helping nice you're
crazy oh nice nice nice you guys are so
strong oh there two oh
no no but G said
engage don't be afraid do not be afraid
always always I'm not hitting any of my
shots that's fine come be here now okay
okay okay
okay ow up it's my
job perfectly
planned get him almost oh my God nice
nice nice nice nice who the heck is
[Music]
that worth did you what did you do worth
worth let him die dad he's a bear now
what really is that still
Warwick yeah that that's still him no
it's a bear why is he a
bear is Vol Bear right yeah W bear
that's not war
rck I've been they're both they're like
the same you know are are they yeah
they're basically the same
Boozled oh okay I see Warwick and Vol
bear at the same time now so I think a
she's so low you bamboozled me no no I
would not lie to you fine I'm fine I'm
fine I'll scare him away from your lane
help thank you please continue doing so
ow
I'm an enemy has been
slain
goodbye
okay is it fixed
ma'am stop
it I don't know why that is I have idea
are we sure they're Bots yeah I'm sure
they're
Bots I'm not sure
Bots an enemy has been slain I'll to the
pretty
flowers
a what that do turret plating will soon
fall
sorry about the audio
stuffff maybe I should reinstall like
all my audio drivers or something yeah
ow every every single one each one of
them what's your audio
problem oh every while since like last
week every once in a while my audio just
becomes like super crunchy but I can't
hear it only chat can hear it for some
reason it's like what is you know it
must be OBS I don't know
no go go get him get him get him he'll
walk back to
us now is as good a time as any
nice an enemy has been
SL surrender
now so now G when I have like this much
health should I still what is happening
to my hold on something is going on with
my computer you got something very
terrible is happening I admitted
something
bad my I think what is happening my
second monitor is flickering oh
everybody's got issues today maybe the
table is is loose crunchy uh it's it's
like look let me take a video of this so
you can see how curs this is it would be
so funny if you put my screen
[Laughter]
recorder I'm going to start screen
recording what no that's not going to
work if it's the monitor okay let me
send this to you uh-oh what what is
happening an
has my computer has
SL has problems with
connection let me upload and then send
this oops what speed it up can't believe
he's at my tower your team has destroyed
a
turret here he goes no more M where' It
Go
y oh my my goodness what is going on yay
Tower broken
finally ooh I don't have boots yet I'm
slow put it here and then I'll also send
to kiaha you can see thank
you check after the game I I did have a
lot of uh flickering issues a while ago
yeah do you see that like what is what
is happening that's fine just hit it
once I'm sure it's fine o you're okay o
yeah
yeah yeah it's fine it's fine don't
worry don't worry you think it's fine
you think it's okay yeah I think it's
fine I'm pretty sure it's fine
we're
winning I'm glad it's okay and nothing
as bad bad as happening no no it's
[Laughter]
fine I don't even like what are these
circles and question marks and x's on my
screen uh what let me know if it turns
into a blue screen I had that
before I can make it through this League
of Legends game yeah yeah we'll we'll
make it to this I bet it's Path of Exile
it's mad at me oh you are you do you
have Roblox on in this side as well no I
don't have Roblox on today I don't no
very
surprising what it became dark what's
going on my greed I will die now oh my
God shut down I deserved
it I deserved it for my greed what is
that oh that's that's pretty bad
die your team has
destroyed I'm already in the middle I no
longer have second
monitor like at all no it's still
flickering but I I just can't use it you
know oh that's
okay okay I don't need a second monitor
feel it you know yeah I I feel it I
don't need to read
chat all right an ally
has what is oh we're doing well is that
Twitter that's flickering on my page
what is oh my God takes another video
she a shy
puppy what
is oh what's that
looks
funny what do we want to do we're all
we're all doing pretty
well whatever you want to do beautiful
lady do we want to all go mid and push
mid do we want to push bottom what do we
want to do oh this wait they're all here
no I'm here I'm here I'm here let's go
let's go let's go okay okay okay I'm
going let's go go
in un
okay
I'll get
himy nice scared me get this one too get
this GG I'm dead you got this though you
got it get this one
too Quadra kill
goodbye the P the p over what the
hell what's going on what he run to wait
guys oh yeah you you got I'm running
you're all running behind
no oh nice
shot I'm too far I'm too slow are you
still running he's just ating you
goodbye my War
wellest very nice you guys are just in
their base destroying things it's
amazing that's beautiful
would it make sense like if you just
kill one lane and then ignore the other
turrets and then you go into the base
you could do that but um why don't
people do that the the more people that
are in a lane the you have to split XP
with them I just put that on the outside
so if everyone went mid and tried to
push
mid in theory it sounds like a great
idea sounds like a great idea yeah but
if you're all level one
oh the the the single person in that
lane on their side is going to level
faster than you and everyone else is
getting lots of
exp your team has destroyed an inhibitor
wow double
kill good job my poor poor
computer oh no I did my thing chat it's
okay we we've
almost yes oh what's this it's it's fine
my homework is done will I ever hit and
ignite wait how
legendary
double w she's singing oh that's you
right I was like am I oh not walking
backward she's singer he's Charmed he's
Charmed he's
charmed's
sing he
s she's a singer himer dinger
sh
nice
nice this is so nice we're so
good we an end y
y come out twin she's a
singer we won
[Applause]
[Music]
my was here see it
too my
clone good job good work everyone one
good keep up the good work all right I
got
to I'm ating your
[Music]
D by bye-bye byebye I guess everybody
just is this the end oh that's the same
one oops what yeah I think I need to
restart my computer I really don't know
what is going on it really is not having
a good
time I mean you played really well all
things considered yeah this this is my
second monitor something's happening to
it I can't explain your problem yeah I
can't either I can't explain my problem
either have you tried turning it off and
on again
yeah to help you've got it good job
today
yay guys thanks for joining PR you save
the day thanks k for joining thank you
for playing with us yeah
did she's like in a coma she wakes up
what did I
do I mean it would have just been a bot
otherwise
right no it would have been a random
person yeah oh better this it was very
nice that you I love playing with you
yeah join us again sometime sure
yeah we can we can Bot game I can hold
hold your hand and I can teach you sure
yeah sure sure okay bye everyone thanks
for
playing going to go computer byebye
sure
[Laughter]
[Music]
sure no I had fun Top Line is Chill
Caitlyn was chill V also like uh after
like a few games I like uh like I feel
like I got better
when I like I mean you even it's not
just me learning the characters it was
me still learning the game itself like
the basics of the basics and how to buy
items and like stuff like
that I didn't even I didn't even know
the simplest things so you know yeah but
now it was like Smooth Sailing around
the end at least against the Bots like I
was so fast with my Top Lane I'm so
proud I was just
chilling but yeah I felt a little bit
like uh lost and
like it's was somewhat easy to pick up
just get thrown into the cold water it
kind of
[Music]
works yeah I mean I don't really know
what's like going on with all these like
popping up objectives that are like
enemies I guess that you have to kill
like I haven't seen a single one of them
I think I only saw the effects of it I
guess they show up in the
middle I just said yes to everything
until later I just said no to
everything yeah no I do think it was the
right choice to switch the game because
I would have waited just for three
freaking
hours and I don't know about that so
yeah this was
fine at least now I I can at least like
conclude that I have tried the
game so that's behind
me and you know I could even be part of
my like IRL best friends
circle games now but they're also much
better than me cuz they've been playing
for years I
guess now if they ever need a plus one
to play with cuz somebody's not joining
or so they could consider me perhaps I
don't I've never been considered they've
never even invited me
before maybe now play of go yeah that's
one f i I was like you
know but goo is probably really good
too and there's still a big language
barrier I don't know if like uh this is
a good oneon-one collab
game especially if I'm still a
beginner
yeah oh because she's on the Korean
server so we wouldn't be able to play
any yeah I I saw something
about like you have to kind of commit to
server right but I could make a I could
change it but it's like uh kind of
annoying it's better when you have a
full team yeah yeah yeah like oneon-one
would be weird but
no too bad I do want to I do wonder how
good she is she's trly really
good if you get someone to coach
you yeah but then probably not go good
because of uh communication
problems you need Korean SSN oh to join
Korean server you need something special
what's an SSN
Faker yeah I'll get Faker to coach
me a social security number
oh all right uh
Korean social security
[Music]
number Social Security number two
please just
[Music]
kidding just kidding ask R for an
account oh I wonder if they would be
able to do that cuz they're they seem to
be supportive oh now I'm all alone I'm
all
[Music]
alone yeah but yeah so yeah I'm back
we'll have uh you know solo wa streams
again tomorrow I'm I'm like I'm not sure
like I'm so indecisive about the streams
tomorrow and the day
after I feel like I want to do a
Kad and then maybe also a rebroadcast on
like the
same
weekend but also Path of Exile do you
think I mean if they got in within three
hours today how do you think it will be
tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow people were saying like oh it's
the weekend so it might might be
really
rough should be easier tomorrow only
people did I opened Kyla's stream and it
looked like she was
in oh she was just watching people wait
is she still not in Kyla is in okay Al
so but first she was just
watching how
long how long was she just watching
I guess it's four and a half hours now
since the supposed opening but they
didn't open right
away today is the rush after it should
be a bit better I thought so
too but yeah I don't know like geky was
saying that she's going to play people
and Kyla I guess are like a
Duo gig was saying maybe let's play
together I don't really know if I should
just start on my own anyway
though I I haven't
really heard of
any
anything in
particular I don't no I I I don't know
about like partying up with like you
know a giggy uh biu Kyla me group or so
I don't think that would be good because
that's too many time zones I that's just
suffering
again
unfortunately I I I've made like plenty
of experiences now how difficult it is
to even find a date uh with so many like
first it's just like the amount of
people it's hard to find a good date and
then it's the the amount of time zones
it's hard to find a good
time yeah no need for a fix script just
do open VC real really though like what
about the scaling of like the
levels I'm fine playing it alone too
honestly like I'm fine doing my own
thing I don't know like what kind of
game it is at all like I haven't really
done any research so I don't know what's
the best way to play it but it seems to
be a good game on your own
[Music]
too but perhaps if I would level stay
around the same then every once in a
while we could get
together I don't
know yeah I don't I don't even know now
that this game is out are the girls that
said they would want to play the DLC of
the [\h__\h] I wonder if they're even going
to still think about it I feel like it's
not even on their mind anymore now it's
path
of Exel on their mind completely
[Music]
they forgot about Diablo overshadowed
yeah that I was kind of fearing that and
I'm pretty sure it's going to
happen what do you think of leag now
after playing it no it's fine it's a
it's
a fun game I mean uh I guess I haven't
really played much against Real players
and that will would be a little bit of a
different
experience no there's nothing wrong with
it it's
fun it's all right
yeah has a big linning curve
this this
game
well got to get
good gotta get
good a learning
curve
massive
really H yeah I no how to get good I
mean even those real oh hi chunky monkey
I mean even those real players that we
played against they are not even like on
such a pro level Evo right and even
those were
so they seemed really
good how good are people like the
pros she's like walking around the table
blocking the camera with her fluff
you're so cute you
baby you baby oh fluffy
baby she's so good best Kate
player I
really I really like her in Arcane and
her her design and her
character she's very committed
and what's the word I don't know but
I
forgot also her her ulti
is called Ace in the Hole right I read
ass in the
hole that's what I thought was funny but
I didn't say
it
openly I'm glad you guys are laughing
I am glad you are anyway uh yeah so you
may have
noticed uh we are
uh awaiting a
video today the first day where it's
cutting it close the previous days I'm
actually so surprised I mean I I did
have to like every every day I'm like 24
hours roughly before sometimes 30 hours
before I'm like reminding the girls I'm
like hey your video is up just reming
you but like so far everybody like
submitted it like 10 hours early or so
sometimes 15 hours early and I'm like
heo and my whole team is like hey yo
what's going on everything's so early
this
year n yeah I've had it uh ready
before we already kind of spoiled it
so whatever we can joke about it she had
it ready but she wants to add a little
something so she's welcome to do that
it's fine it doesn't as long as long as
it's not
late you
know mhm I'm looking forward to it me
too I wonder what the Cherry is no I
mean I kind of know but not really have
you guys been enjoying the Advent
calendar
videos where you going chunky
[Music]
wonky
yeah good good good good time is going
by so fast
I um have
like like a few days un assigned still
but most of them are signed I'm
like three four three days one two three
four days no actually I guess five
because I
guess I wasn't even counting 25th but I
guess we are doing
25th so I have five days
unassigned and the finale I still still
don't know what I'm going to be doing if
you guys have
ideas yeah I don't really want to do a
sock puppet finally
again I don't know I'm not feeling I
feel like I feel like I grew out of
it finger puppets
then that would be cute
too t to pull it off twice but wouldn't
it be the third time it would be the
third time also some of those puppets
are so Fallen apart they they may have
been able to you know survive two years
but the third year would be really rough
and I would have to remake them and I'm
really not in the mood to remake
anyone's
dolls that might make it funnier no it's
so
scuffed I shocked you with this collab
but I'm FR to see more of Ian trying to
leag even in passing so I shocked you in
a good
way
right I'm
glad oh thank you for Super
Chat last year sock puet finale was my
favorite I always did put a lot of love
into
it uh and and you
know a lot of fault
[Music]
too you're the queen of passion project
ooh thank
you I try my
best you kept saying it was
cringe the
finale nah oh yeah the last one I wrote
right the one before I think FAA wrote
the script but the last one I wrote see
that's also a thing like I I wouldn't
even like be able to think of any other
more original script cuz that one was
referencing the ghosts of Christmas
right the like going back in time and
and like improving yourself or whatever
and I wouldn't know like what else to
think of in terms of Christmas stories
like a complete original one I don't
know man
A Christmas Carol what you you want me
to make the puppets sing but that's also
a thing like
asking my worry for the finale is like
trying to get everybody's participation
for
[Music]
something is
rough
so I prefer something more
more
flexible what was that sound
spooky Grinch parody
finale kind also sounds
so like it needs a lot of effort
too I guess I'm just lazy this
year Well if you have a good idea feel
free to throw it at me
in the kfp hashtag or so thanks for the
memberships thank
you so I guess I'll read super chats
from the last stream and this
stream it's already past midnight but
I'm I I don't I don't mind I've slept so
much like cuz the past days like every
day we were out walking and walking and
walking so much doing lots of
sightseeing
and and and I I was like oh the last
morning when I woke up I was like oh man
one more one more like big outing but I
want to stay in bed and sleep
longer but we ended up like walking so
much every day I guess I was just really
exhausted and I had to recharge energy
and social battery and I slept so
much but it was worth it it was so worth
it it felt
really
fulfilling and I think I did a good
job a segue no that's so
lame was worried about you not getting
enough sleep H the nice thing is like on
the first like when I picked them up I I
didn't have any sleep like it was really
bad but it was still like early
so everybody was very open to just like
take a nap right after I picked them up
so we went to my place and I set up the
beds everybody had like their own bed
and then we just slept for like I said
oh let's just sleep for 1 hour I guess
cuz I felt guilty I didn't want to like
uh spend too much time sleeping if they
didn't want to do it but Thena was like
1 hour only are you sure and then I was
like okay two hours then and then I
ended up snoozing through some
alarms and then end I think I ended up
just napping 3 hours or three and a
half but that really helped and we still
made the most out of the day like it was
still so yeah yeah
still so much
time hello hello chunky wony did you
hear that that was so cute she's such a
baby when she jumps up here sometimes
she goes
like Oh
meow no has not really been delivered
yet apparently some stuff
crashed maybe we'll see if it's going to
be on time but if not we it's all fine
it's not a big
issue oh although I do have a tweet
scheduled cuz after that one time when I
wasn't at my PC uh and I couldn't do
the couldn't do the wait did I yeah no
because I was sleeping
I was sleeping and I couldn't schedule a
tweet then I ended up scheduling for the
next couple of
days have you starting started
decorating for Christmas no not really
no not at all I don't even know if I'm
going to get a
tree this
year probably
not are you okay I'm okay why not I had
a really really nice past couple of
days that felt
[Music]
really yeah
fulfilling like living my
life and bonding and having special
moments even though I mean you know like
it's always nicer when it's more spaced
out and not like all at once because my
energy man I'm not used to 3 days in a
row just be out and about the whole
day yeah I was kind of
crazy was very
intense I'm going to get another hand
can video of you I will make another
hand cam stream soon for cooking for
V and I guess maybe a separate
one maybe I'll bake cookies maybe I'll
do it as a member
stream the cookie baking you hear the PE
really she's kind of far from the
[Music]
mic okay I'll I'll open my super
chatos vter Vite
so yeah you know one more thing is that
I was I was not sure at what time I
should do the Koke because I kind of
wanted to do since I'm since I want to
do a focus on like uh new
jeans I was
thinking since there a Korean group to
do it at Korean Prime
Time and no I'm not still playing League
not anymore more
today and then rebroadcast it during na
prime time or so or when I say Korean
prime time I would probably just go
pretty late like 11:00
p.m. Korean Standard
time
but yeah then it's really early for you
guys for some of you guys but it is what
it is I don't know what's like best to
do I'm I I can't decide
but then I might do it uh on Sunday
instead and try Poe
tomorrow you know
[Music]
we broadcasted free times free times
no my ear is
clogged damn it cute junkers how do you
know how do you
know I haven't given you the most recent
status update how do you know she is
actually really
cute she's very loud how do you hear her
she's so f are she's purring
loudly the girls they were so confused
as if it's their first time hearing a
cat purr every time chunky wonky was
purring they thought she was angry and
I'm like no no she's purring she's
happy even though I explained it to them
again and again each time when she Pur
they were asking me is she angry and I'm
like no she's
happy yeah it does sound like growling
but I I I assured reassured them again
and again I'm like she's happy she's
really
happy she's always
happy can't believe some people are
misinterpreting these purs but I guess
it kind of makes
sense your father was dying a
well I mean it could be honestly if I I
explained to them that cats also purr
when they're hurt physically and they
purr to like heal themselves back
up as if it's like an HP
thing so yeah let's move
somewhere
here uh ignore
that hold up let me write
[Music]
and I am
oh
I'm I'm
here yippee
oh that's what you mean with earthquake
okay so I think uh from last stream
where we were cooking I hope you liked
that it was kind of stressful for me to
set up because I never did a setup
before with like three different
microphones in like one scene in one
OBS never did that before on my
own yeah and then they were like
Wireless
some of
them the camera worried me
too yeah but overall it worked out I
forgot the [\h__\h] potatoes but thank
God like that also kind of worked out
timing wise cuz we just did some
chitchatting in the
beginning so this stream if you missed
it go check it
out
roet what type of potato just normal
potatoes what do you
mean was a cute stream right I really
wanted to do it I thought it was like a
great way of like cooking for them but
also not really cooking for them and
welcoming them with some good food there
was like so much food left over I don't
know what to do with
it I didn't even buy like I feel like I
I like held back a lot I didn't even
like buy all kinds of like different
Meats like previously when I did a party
like this for New Year's I had like uh
pork no did I even have pork I don't
know but I had chicken I had beef I had
uh sausages I had
Burgers burger patties and I had uh some
fish stuff too I had um what they call
those
EBY shrimps and shrimps that even I
wouldn't I wasn't going to eat but just
for other people
M I had like so much more
stuff still have M to good for once no I
I did eat like a couple more servings
but somehow I don't know I'm like pretty
sick of
it I was pretty sick of it I don't know
like every
time when I like warmed one up and tried
eating it like my appetite was just gone
immediately I don't know what's wrong
with it cuz it's not bad but my it's
just I don't know it killed my
[Music]
appetite but I made a good curry that
was good for leftovers it was kind of
spicy but the curry was good my
spontaneous
Curry I didn't even eat that often but
yeah anyway I should probably play some
bgm do do you guys think I did better
at this game than the Pokemon
[Music]
one she's still purring yeah or maybe I
should leave the bgm often so you can
hear
her 100%
really and I didn't even really I mean
no I did I did like kind of like
honestly there really wasn't time to
read my skills like I was trying to but
there genuinely it didn't feel like
there was
time but I I
I uh flew over it and and then also just
by using it I realized okay like in the
beginning I spamed those traps a lot but
then I completely stopped using them and
just focused on the the the one that
goes like straight in a line and the
other one you guys kept on saying that's
not good for the minions use it only
against the big ones yeah I just ended
up barely using any skills besides the Q
skill the Trap is important for the
combo
a oh the traps don't work oh they don't
work on minions either
anyway oh I was trying to get minions to
go into it
M that's why they like stayed up there a
lot
[Music]
ah also it was just like draining my
Mana a lot so I stopped using
it but yeah I feel like I had a decent
understanding of my skills around the
later rounds
baby you are so soft I keep on petting
her you had some sick skill shots of the
C thank you I I just used it to clean up
all the Minions
always that triple kill was great can't
believe I had a triple kill was that
real
I didn't even notice that I did
anything I probably just stole
kills but that was like when there was
like a lot going on
so a lot of action of lots of people
around so it's not all
me everyone was cheering for you and you
were just like yeah cuz it didn't really
feel like
I was doing
anything I wasn't sure if they meant
me that was fun
though thisa kicking you out from bot
was funny she should have given me
another chance when we were playing
against bots she wanted to get rid of
she wanted to get rid of me
immediately bro how am I going to
learn the one round where I'm like
helping her out down there is like the
roughest round with the real
players no I also felt like it wasn't
going well so I was like I'm going to go
back up I
guess good
attempt good try
by they were so
strong you didn't get the full
experience as the Bots were super
buggy I know that the one the one that
kept them going like left right left
right left right all the time and let me
just Auto attack him to death also and
even when he had really low HP he kept
on coming back to me to continue Auto
attacking him thank
you thank you for giving me
kills yeah they're Idol stepping
[Music]
all right let's read super chats uh
unknown sent a
rainbow wow today F December is my fifth
birthday as kfp I can't believe it's
already been this long so that was a
birthday party for you too not just the
welcome party even after all this time
you are still the absolute best in the
world and you still somehow keep getting
even more amazing every single day thank
you for everything W you make every day
so much better you're always a source
our source of happiness so my birthday
wish is for my beautiful perfect oie to
find nothing but happiness too love you
w more than anything ever thank you
unknown happiness huh actually me and L
and Laden we had some deep talks in our
dinner last night also talking about
like finding happiness and future plans
and all that was very deep and we we had
like a lot of
interesting m k then
uh like things that we thought the same
way or
felt the same way about surprisingly
like really
surprisingly yeah there was really a lot
of
bonding Aladin said one thing that was
like it just made me feel so happy uh on
the second night when we were like you
know I was
um on the second day I was leading them
through the sh Brun
Palace uh and the
gloriette and like all all everything in
that area um lots of sightseeing there
and uh we're going to talk about it in
detail again anyway but probably also
partially in Japanese
so that's that but um
I know we were all in a really good mood
and we were we were like uh stalling
time so hard in the Christmas Market cuz
we had
like basically even though I already
aimed to get there later a little bit
later in the day because of how um late
the dinner was reserved I didn't get
like an earlier dinner dinner was like
reserved for like 900 p.m. so looking at
things we could do until then there
wasn't much in that area because the the
museums would have closed at like I
think
6 p.m. or so and the zoo that I was
considering was also like closing around
the time or even at 5:00 p.m. or so and
considering all of that there was just
like a big gap between
Museum and uh
dinner and like 4 hours in a Market is
kind of rough we went through the even
though it's a huge Christmas Market we
went through it like five times did like
five rounds looked at every single store
twice like really exactly like looking
at every
detail um and had different kinds of
foods and all that uh I was I was
thinking like after the museum like
maybe we can like you know look around
some more in the area there's like this
big park that has like lots of statues
and other cool stuff to look at but the
problem was when we got out of the
museum it was pitch black dark already
at 6:00 p.m. and no I think it was
actually 5:00
p.m. yeah so it was pitch black dark and
nothing was lit up so that's when we
made that video that I think Lia posted
the video post where I threw my glove
cuz I was like ah well it's it's dark
but let's try to light things up with my
phone and still look at things because
we have so much time until dinner and we
can't spend all of this time on the
Christmas Market let's try anyway and it
was kind of like a really interesting
horror mystery
friller
game but not it wasn't really scary were
constantly joking about
it but it was really dark and there were
these spooky trees and we couldn't see
things at
all and this whole time it was just like
such a friller
Vibe interesting atmosphere but we were
just little giggling the whole time and
holding hands and laughing about how we
really can't see
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] um cing but somehow that was also
so much fun just wandering through the
darkness and pretending like we're
seeing
things even that was so much fun and
then yeah we spent some hours at the
Christmas Market stalling for our dear
life and then when we finally made our
way walking over to the to the dinner
um there was this moment like we were
all just so happy and and that
said I quote
for the first time in my life I feel
like I'm alive and living my
life I'm like what did you really just
say that like we were all like w and
such a happy happy excited mood and she
said something so deep we all we all
kept on saying such emotional things but
she said and I was like oh my God no way
you just said that that makes me feel so
happy your happiness makes me happy and
like I can't believe you sad
[Music]
Dad we were just so giddy everybody was
so
giddy
yeah I I I was just like shocked that
cuz I was so worried if I could really
make them enjoy their
stay that pressure felt like a lot of
stress to me I was
worried if they would really enjoy it
and feel like it was worth it spending
their money and and their time on such a
short trip such on such a far distance
and all that in such a small country
where there's like you know there's in
Europe there's so many great countries
in so many great cities so I do feel
like a little bit like
intimidated but I do think Austria is
amazing
still and and they show a lot of
appreciation for
it but when she said that I was like
really
relieved like oh man she really is
having a good
time so much that she would say that
like for the first time in her life
she's living life that's a crazy thing
to say that's like the highest
compliment
ever like
what what
[Music]
what
what a man I missed them
already I was also worried that like cuz
when I visited
ladin
um you know for that one off collapse
she was was so energetic and I was this
whole time I was thinking like if she
sleeps over at my place and we're like
together 24/7 for like 3 days for an
night or so is this going to be too much
for me but no we were all fine like I
was I was uh enjoying everybody's
company and yeah was well well
balanced and she had her calm moments
too unfortunately she like had some
moments too where she got kind of sick
sick and didn't feel so well like on the
the thing is like on that
night when we went to dinner the moment
when we entered the restaurant she
started feeling sick even though the
whole day was so so so
great she like started feeling sick and
like basically ate nothing she kept on
like uh having to go outside to get
fresh air cuz she felt like throwing up
no not
in that's pretty
sad but the next day she felt
better and ate
properly
yeah yeah yeah
yeah also I she she really wanted to eat
Sak the problem is like I mean you can
get Sak to anywhere in Austria and it
even if you don't get it from the Saka
Hotel is still very very decent but
ideally I'd still want to bring her to
the Saka hotel to like see the fancy
decor and interior and everything and
have the original but I told them that
they can easily get the original uh as a
souvenir even in a fancy packaging at
the airport and like it tastes really
good it's just it it is the OG but here
we will eat it elsewhere because I tried
to get a reservation in the Saka Hotel
Cafe but it's impossible and standing in
line we saw the line standing in line
for an
eternity didn't sound very
Charming so I got them Z from elsewhere
and and they both really liked it and
but especially like that it was like her
request to eat s
and she really loved it ad C her up nope
nope nope I'm awaiting it I'm awaiting
it s is so
good I did end up getting it from obala
which is uh a really good Cafe in
Austria a cafe chain for cakes and stuff
really really good like really great Co
quality and honestly The Taste from the
zakat is like on point so
[Music]
no I still tell all of this but I don't
know like how much we would go into
detail next time so a little bit of
tangents for you a little bit of early
tangents a sneak
peek also because yeah it might be like
more Japanese than English I'm not sure
though when we do have the
collab yeah okay let me read Super Chat
unknown thank you for the rainbow sorry
for going into a tangent but you know
you saying the thing about source of
happiness and all that kind of got me
into a
tangent a big one
H thank you so much and happy belated
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday birthday in your
shoe happy birthday in your pants too
happy birthday to
you by the way did nobody wonder when I
sent that birthday video to narissa and
it was played there was everybody just
too focused on the dance and didn't
notice that I sang weird lyrics that
they probably don't know the context to
why I'm singing them
like nobody commented on that like from
the girls maybe the chat
did like I sang what I just sang like
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants too yeah I think
they were too distracted or didn't
listen that
closely they don't understand they don't
understand I was thinking I was going to
sing it normally but then I
automatically ended up singing it that
way and I just rent with it I rolled
with
it he legit
lyrics anyway thank you un you M for the
pinky takash Ki from H life English move
Small industry my beloved oh yeah
oh yeah I did end up I I I prepared like
or like I planned for like 1 hour or
even more of preparation but that was
not enough at all I was so stressed out
trying to get everything to work sorry
for the delay in the end but I did warn
you I did warn
you small Indie streamer please
forgive thank you take a 47 sh
[Music]
Rex valdian oh thank you for the red
super chat Pro tip ret tastes even
better when you grill your cheese on a
hot Tank Engine tank after I thought you
were going to give real advice right now
bro but I I do feel like uh maybe trying
it like the proper way sometime soon
next time like cuz people from
Switzerland were like Oh no you're
supposed to only bake the cheese down
there in the tray and then pour it on
top of the grilled things on your plate
and not just not the way you do it with
like
the like mix and then the cheese on top
as I said like I I don't know my friend
Circle my family everybody we do it my
way even back in the day with like
rmt uh when we did rocklet parties with
like work colleagues everybody we all do
it that way with like making a little
bit of a mountain of food and then top
it with cheese and then put the shovel
in but I wouldn't mind doing it like the
other way it's just kind of fun to make
your own little shovel
you know if it works it works Germany
also does it ah you do see okay okay
okay I feel I feel
uh validated or
so your way looks more fun it really is
more
fun if it wasn't supposed to work that
way then why does the food still taste
so good exactly
[Music]
exactly doesn't make a real difference
exactly yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah we even use no no I did actually
have bread prepared and I I know like
usually I always have bread on the side
for ret but uh I forgot about baking it
and then honestly in the end it's good
that I didn't bake it because it was
already plenty of food it would have
been too much more than too
much yeah but I did have like herb
buttered buet prepared to bake in the
oven did the girls try aome bread yeah
um yeah yeah yeah uh I made at least at
least
uh yeah no they did I also brought them
to like a normal like bakery shop where
you uh can you know take all kinds of
things with you and then on one day I at
least managed to get had raden to order
a typical uh Austrian breakfast with
just like a sem bread and uh jam and
butter and
just I told her because she started like
ripping off pieces of the bread I was
like no no no no no you have to take the
knife and you have to slice it through
the middle then you have to uh put the
butter butter spread it over the bottom
piece of the bread and then Jam
up on top then close the bread then bite
into it I told her that but she already
like kind of ripped off the pieces so
she had troubles doing it my
way but still she still enjoyed it she
said the bread was
good you know trying to make her do it
the Austrian way because she wanted the
austan
[Music]
experience instructions unclear rip and
tear exactly rip and tear
here and I had them try schwat the black
Austrian bread the darker bread uh with
butter and lots of
umit uh was chives chives many many
chives it was like top with millions of
tries so so good so simple and so good
you know not necessarily what I would
eat in my everyday
breakfast but I wanted them to have some
Austrian style breakfast I
guess they weren't really familiar with
jives guess it's not used very much in
Japanese
cooking when I showed them the Japanese
word for it they seemed like they never
heard of it
before it's like a small
Nei yeah and Negi is used a lot in
Japanese
[Music]
cooking so I'm surprised they don't use
chives very much cuz chives are
awesome Austrian cooking uses chives a
lot as
topping chives and
parsley yeah small spring onion
basically without the onion
really but also not really like chives
have a more
gentle
and different kind of
Aroma ches are amazing chives are
superior
to spring onions honestly to
me honestly to me they are except for if
it's like if we're talking Ramen that
you can't top a Ramen with chives you
got to top the ramen with uh spring
onions
really depends on the
usage anyway thank you for the and the
non advice nonserious
advice I'm glad you made it to the
Stream it
seems or maybe you didn't but maybe you
did I don't
know but you know it's kind ofet
a it's kind of a Switzerland and France
thing so how did you
feel did you judge me don't judge me too
hard check your channel d d d as a Swiss
person I very much appreciate this oh
I'm so
glad CH the gondra D
[Music]
and
y
y okay and then today's stream and then
I'm going to dip let's see uh I have my
eyes on my
Discord video should be coming
soon my tweet is out uh also I guess
oops oh
well thought there was more in that
stream no apparently
not too bad
but I'm going to read the stre the Super
Chat from today K Super
[Music]
Chat
here himer
Dinger it's like he's about to um what
do you call it when when when in the
hospital they go like three two one
stand back
you know with the two Fang on your chest
and so on it's like he's about to do
that with my
butt yeah defibrillating clear
clear he's defibrillating my
[Laughter]
ass he's he's experimenting with my ass
he's giving me
m he's giving me a
pilt over PT
[Music]
[Laughter]
lift putt
[Music]
lift yes
PPL hex tech
dumpy the hex tech dumpy
yo it's going to be out of
metal not good how to twerk with metal
butt
help maybe we can make it like twerk
like a machine like you know just
automatically but it's going to make
like machine noises and it's got to be
well oiled yeah
Hydraulics oh yeah that should be
possible anything is
possible so check 47 d d thank you D
pink I went to World Tour in Singapore I
have many Precious Memories sseeing
around country oh wow w wow watching W
performance making relationship with
other H life fans all over the world I
appreciate you made me go uh made me
good
opportunity call was
um ra maybe raging out in
[Music]
venue for
did you guys see once
again I think last year
I cat hair in my mouth well not last
year I guess this year oh hey chunky
W uh I was like oh yeah two years in a
row no way I'm going to be on the extra
stage this year as well
[Music]
H
well well
well here we go
again they said all right
bet I can't believe it wait what the h
it already what it already has a set
list where did you guys even see it like
I only saw the other
tweet what they showed the why do they
spoil the set list I think they did that
for honeyworks too
right but like what why did they do that
it doesn't say who's going to sing what
huh
okay they showed on stream but I think
it was to list the songs made by the
music
creators well
well I still hear leak sounds let me
close the
game I like the ambience yeah it was
just wind blowing though chunky won keep
sitting in front of me and just staring
into the
screen very close you're going your eyes
are going to turn into rectangles
girl
[Music]
anyway py stud pinky happy
happy originally I was um cuz the girls
were also really motivated I mean they
would have been open to doing streams
every day but in the end we didn't
really have time we were really tired
and also ladin was sick
yeah it's a little bit unfortunate but
it led let us focus more on the vacation
and you know the girls were there for a
really short amount of time so I did
want them them
to get the most out of it
yeah yeah yeah yeah uh slave honol
thanks for the red super chat if you
want to be a top laner remember free
things be make annoying your enemy be
brave be
crazy I think well be brave can also be
said as be greedy greedy which I was
here and there but still under
control did I annoy my enemy maybe not
much but because it was also mostly bots
so not much to
annoy I would have liked to play Top
Lane against real
people like bottom Lane was stressful
with real people but Top Lane I wonder
how that would have
[Music]
gone you were audacious
oh well done today oh comes on new dog
Honolulu you also play League of Legends
I
suppose yeah surely everything's
stressful but I I wonder if I would have
done well enough um
regardless probably would have still
lost but I want to test how I would have
done your Bot line enemy already played
multiple
months oh ah bottom Lane M mhm
thank you thank you thank you sa simply
thanks for the pinky I hope you'll enjoy
leag Gua I know the game gets a lot of
flag but I it can be a lot of fun with
friends happy Independence Day T finish
chickens in the chat oh yeah okay
Finland let's go let's go let's go to
Independence thank you I did have a good
time so all is well will I play it again
that is up in the Stars
maybe maybe
not maybe one more
time
sure I don't know I don't know I don't
know depends on my mood and the time I
don't know we'll see we'll
see at least it's at a good time for me
you know that's
rare and Y
mean comes
Amia s
chicken NCG goggles and Nathan cotton
thanks for the pinky just remember that
to get better at the game to read your
tool
tips what tool
tips
reading like also that like the items
there's literally no time to read what
what the items do bro just losing
time in the
game thankfully you guys told me what to
buy I have time what do you mean no I
don't have time cuz while I'm like
taking my time with like after dying
going to the shop and buy like reading
for the items other people are still
killing stuff
like the time doesn't stop ticking from
me oh chunky
wonky chunky wony
purr I think even gigy uses a sight whoa
she's
cheating just
kiding louder baby louder they need to
hear you they need to hear you come on
yes yes yes yes do you hear it do you do
you
okay good yeah she's looking at
me okay um thank you Nathan somebody D
Jus the thanks for WR Super Chat league
is very hard boss as long as you're
having fun then that's all that matters
Ania is an ice Phoenix an ice
Phoenix whoa wait I like the
wrongness of
that you might like her flavor saraphina
is so not a music theme don't let anyone
salty ruin your
fun what does she look like that's
important
Ania oh it's just a bird it's not like a
personified thing it's just bird
the idea of it is cool though like I
like the concept of it a lot just not
really what I would want to
play please don't hate my first M no not
at all not at all I love the concept
really ice Phoenix that's just so
illogical it's wonderful it's um it's a
paradox it shouldn't exist
that's so
[Music]
cool we do not interact with birds
here yeah good to know though thank you
Jesus potassium Su D slay D give me oats
D Raina Valentine d
em d d Sean 7812 D thank you medor D 13
D V D next angas D TR for fun D mental J
dang Cru dang I feel so unhydrated oh my
God Cruz than
Bane primaries than thank you for the
first Super Chat you ever sent first
time message but wanted to say you're
amazing K you were in my music rap 2024
Mirage was amazing keeping you and
you're the best thank you for listening
to my music I appreciate
it I hope you guys all listen to my
stuff on your preferred Music Services
every once in a while i' I'd really
appreciate
it reminder to do so
C coin d vagabon d luckless Luke D GD D
who close D for the r
chat with no text he who eats faces D
Viet Dragon thank you D although I
haven't been to Austria I have deployed
to Poland for a year I wish I stayed
there longer because even the McDonald's
tasted way better than the US and I
enjoyed every bit of my onee stay
including sseeing heart oh
I don't know Poland right I don't think
I've never been to Poland but I'm sure
it's also very pretty Sean R thank you
for the pinky dear Ki if you're reading
this then that means my birthday has
come to pass unfortunately it was my
30th birthday as this tradition
visitations for my funeral will be held
in the back next to FR for your
funeral has been an honor serving you
wait a second wait wait a second I'm
confused this is giving me all kinds of
messages and signals so you're funeral
because you're you're like
um wait why are we funeralize
you you're not dead yet with
30y are you being
dramatic or are you talking about you
know like being bucket cuz aren't you
past your bucket time you're you already
be alive
again where are you sha are Show
Yourself H where is he there you are
you're being a dram dramatic am I
influencing you to be more dramatic I
wonder why are you just uh genuinely
dramatic about I don't I don't even
think it's it's reasonable cuz like it's
[\h__\h] stressful to think about aging
man let us be
dramatic let us be dramatic about
something that is honestly just so
mind-breaking the concept of aging and
dying
is
terrifying so really there's nothing
wrong with panicking about it and being
stressed about it even though I wish we
could take that stress
[Music]
away but 30y is still relatively
early if you are good to yourself in
terms of health then that's just one
third of your life approximately
although that is really not much either
and that did not help did it one3 is
like holy [\h__\h] especially cu the last F
will just be filled with pain in your
body as you get older everything gets
more painful and difficult and slow and
in the last couple of years you might
not even understand things anymore your
brain might be a goner and you might
be [\h__\h] into a bad pan so really I
guess most of your life is over so
great Franks for encouraging
speech by the way Breaking Bad taught me
find like I I I always was kind of
wondering I mean maybe I had an idea of
how but it it made it clear for me how a
bed pan works
I finally have a visualization of it
good to know good to
[Music]
know and that's why we should shame the
age dooming around no no it's it's
reasonable poty talk
[Music]
there I go validating what they wrote
again AL isn't even that old he's like
50 no but he's not the one using the bed
pan but um yeah he's not that
old but I'm currently also rooting for
him to [\h__\h] die or get caught like
I'm really I'm really rooting is it
normal people who want watched the whole
show I think it's normal right like
you're really rooting for him to get
caught like please [\h__\h] up already [\h__\h]
up [\h__\h] around and find out already he
needs to find the [\h__\h] out I'm so done
now I'm
like like I I was with him even
after like all the [\h__\h] that he did I
mean no I I said I already was kind of
like very much against him
and feel like he lost himself after he
did uh like force his son to drink on
that pool party day but I still was
comfortable watching it
and watching it with like and not so
disgusted mind but now in season
five
I he's just scum he's just scum season 5
he's just scum
a
bro he's so scummy I really want it to
end for the sake of his wife first and
foremost like
bro bro feel so bad for her in season
five she's just
like poor
woman poor woman what are we talking
about a little bit of Breaking Bad right
now yeah he's also
so what do you call it when
someone's
like what's that
word not like privileged uh similar
word what's the word
entitled yeah he's such a [\h__\h]
entitled [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] n
nah nah I can't please but I'm still
like like only one third I think through
the last
season but okay now um in the fifth
season somewhere like already in the
first first episode I think they do
spoiler
uh I guess maybe the last episode um
showing him with hair and a big beard
and that's when I knew that Netflix did
indeed spoiler me with that trailer so
he did get hair again later okay okay
okay why did they spoil me well while I
was watching season 4 Netflix showed
showed me I guess the [\h__\h] ending of
season
bro what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
[Music]
you I clicked away relatively fast and
you know I was like you know able to
look over it and not get too influenced
about it
bro n
H crazy [\h__\h] small Indie
company can't trust Alo based anything
of a delicate story but that never
happened to me before I also rarely get
trailers anyway
but yeah out of out of all the things to
show that's just insane
yeah also
that that scene was
so uh the scene where they showed the
the German boss from that company first
eating the chicken nuggets and then just
like yeah checking out that
was something
like bro really didn't want to go to
prison
huh he really didn't want to go to to
prison he went that far but he was like
also so sentimental about it with how he
had his last
meal and then properly took off his
clothes and
everything H that was so weird that was
such a weird
scene the the
German uh voices by the way in like when
they have the phone
conference is so so bad like it's proper
German but it's like really like they're
reading a script with no
proper
acting very exaggerated and fake
sounding if you don't know German then I
hope you don't notice it and you only
notice it when you know German
[Music]
the Spanish is also apparently mid is it
is it so for that I definitely wouldn't
have
noticed really this breaking bat spell
is over
yeah
yeah all right I'm almost done with
super chats anyway or I am done um
pretty
much so yeah Sean
are all of the negative things I said
put aside I hope your birthday is lovely
and I hope you're doing well I hope you
can look at life
positively let's do our
best happy birthday happy birthday to
you happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants too happy
birthday to you go get yourself some
Saka cake please go go
go boohoo 72 fre
D
and uh
oh oh sler k your name looks like Skyler
oh man Breaking Bad brain rot hi K first
time here to say hi thanks a lot for the
h life world tour 24 store in Singapore
that's my first H Life concert and it's
wonderful thank you for bringing so much
wonderful performance a such wonderful
performance we'll start listening to
your Originals cheers for the Phoenix oh
thank you I guess you must have liked my
performance enough to listen to my music
from now on thank you I hope you
do I hope you do than you and I will
continue trying to make good music for
you then I'm glad you enjoyed the
concert I'm glad you were able to go
hopefully it won't be the last time
thank you for your support Moon D soon
she stopped purring I need to turn the
engine on again can you can you Pur for
me
again yeah no that's a weird sound can
you make a nicer
sound okay there we go the engine is on
again
H that's kind of she's she's being a bit
weird oh wait let me check my DMs oh
okay there we
go the video the
[Music]
video the Cherry
okay yeah yeah yeah
okay I already sent it over so
hopefully uh they'll put it up on the
website
ASAP and Dominique
sign thank
you get as comfortable at moving
attacking and Skills game sense and
itemization comes with experience mhm I
thought so leak is a game made of many
parts start little grow big sounds like
somebody's knows what what they're
talking about who and who go school than
for one more pinky than thank you thank
you I'm done with super
chatos
yippe
a
cute she sent me a little Doodle of me
that's really cute it's more than just
the doodle
honestly well you'll see it in the
video I wonder I didn't get to watch it
yet so I wonder what it's about if I am
appearing in
it uh yeah I didn't have time for the
polars yet but I'm sorry I'm I didn't
think it would be so late
again perhaps I can get started next
[Music]
week I quote herb you're the only one I
know that can rock two hats H am I
really the only one with two hats in h
life
though oh comes
CR Ki Oh both crony and
Ki why would anyone else I don't know
because it's
cool can't think of anyone
else well let me look at the roster
whole alive we just got to make
sure we got to make
sure um
wait here I'm looking I'm
looking
[Music]
H there are many hats but not two at
once
paa has ears and a hat and a bow and
it's kind of crazy but I guess it
doesn't quite count
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah it seems like to this day I am the
only one with two hats
really
well see that's the why I recently don't
wear two hats or most of the time is
because you know I I I I I I tend to
intimidate people with how I wear so
many hats people subconsciously get
intimidated by it so I need to be
careful with my hat
dominance you
know you don't want to be unique I'm
unique without them
too anyway I'll go now because I'm so
dehydrated holy [\h__\h] and I need to think
about what to eat
goodbye everybody um I think we'll play
Poe
tomorrow
goodbye I Le we could start earlier
tomorrow for
pe oh cat my really is it releasing for
purchase in 10 minutes oh thanks for the
reminder yeah those cozy looking
new uh
winter hoodies and everything apparently
they're going up in 10
minutes with
socks and everything so go check it out
goodbye goodbye I'll soon
[Music]
n