I'm going to have a drink. Let's
have a drink today. Good
luck. I'm going to have a drink too. I thought the little girl was flying,
and the dragonflies were flying, and it looked beautiful.
Roco girl Kiki Bird's
voice Cicada's voice Roco girl's sound Wow,
what the heck Oh my goodness, I'm lucky, the moon is
coming, I can't help it, deer
But this, this, this, this, I
can't see all of the first questions of Jufuse Boat. Well, the story frame is called Chufu Boat. I
can't do Rakugo properly yet.
That's it. I'm going to have a nice drink. Let's have a
toast.  I'm going to drink today too.I'm going to have a good time, and I
'm going to drink too.I see the girl flying,
and I think it's beautiful, and the flying dragonflies look so good.My
image is that of a spinach-colored cicada.  The
sound of the voice loco girl Wow, what a thing
! Yuro, Yuro is lucky
[Music]
Yay, Kiki Kiki
Kiki Good evening everyone,
can you hear me? Hello,
welcome Welcome to Japan Welcome to Japan This is an off-collaboration! Off-
collaboration!  I've already eaten some meat. I've
been talking a lot. I don't want to talk to you anymore. My
senpai is crazy. I don't have time for that.
I don't have time, so my
senior is really in a hurry. He
's a professional. He's a professional streamer, so he
prepares a lot of things an hour before the show. That's why he's in such a hurry. Just
when I thought that, Chiara-senpai started
an hour early.  It seems like I made a mistake,
but I was in front of this computer 5 minutes before 8 o'clock
and I said that I was barely ready, but
then I realized that I was going to do it 5 minutes earlier,
so I lied and did that, Raden-chan.  I
always
thought that it was true that I knew everything all the time, but when I became a senior, I
always said that I had a solid hour beforehand, and even when I was eating, I was wondering if it was okay. There was still 30 minutes left. Good, that's fine.  But I told Ga-
chan once, okay. There's still plenty of time.
Because she hasn't said it once. I
thought that was it, but no, no, no, it
wasn't 8 o'clock, it wasn't 8 o'clock, it
was 9 o'clock. Broadcast from 9 o'clock.  I am doing it today.
Well, when Kia-senpai taught me some English,
I froze, right?
Then, it moved, it moved, it moved, it
stopped, it stopped.
There's something written at the bottom of the green.  If you call me this, my native
language is German, and people from Germany can say it. That's
right. German is amazing. It
means that you can speak German and English as well. That's right. You can
go, so it's amazing.
Let's go to that off club.  When I said that, it was a bit ok.  I
made a lot of suggestions, but
Raden-
chan would teach me something, either German or English, and
Rané-chan chose to teach me English.  I've
taught English to a few people, but I'm a
bit of a dork, so I'm sure
there's someone better out there who can teach me English,
but English is a bit devastating.English is also devastating.
But I couldn't ask him to teach me German, and I thought he'd say that he'd have to study before that.Yeah, well, that
's true, but he's pretty fluent in English, so yeah,
thank you very much, that's amazing.
When Japanese people come to my stream, they say that
Chiara's English is
a little slower and clearer than that of Boko's,
and that
Chiara's English is easier to listen to because she speaks in simpler terms.  often  Yeah,
yeah, that's amazing, oh, yeah, that's what's being said today.That's
right.Kia-sensei called me that damn thing,
Radenglish.Radengrish,
Ladengrish, oh berry.
Instead, I studied a little bit of
English related to art, and I
took notes so I'll try to teach you some things,
but thank you very much.
Before that, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait a minute,
can I say something off-topic? Yes, please first, can I
tell you my impression of Raden-chan? Yeah, she's
so energetic. She's so
cute. I wonder what kind of person will come before we meet.  I
tried it a little early,
but it's completely different right away, really. It's kind of
amazing. Can I say that
? Well, you can say anything. The atmosphere is
young. The atmosphere is very young.  I don't
know what it is, I thought a unkempt person would come.
Well, it's said that that person is restless. Well, that's true, but
there's no excuse for that.
But cute fashion, fashion is
cute, so yay.  Yeah, it's cute, it's cute, when
was it here all this time? I've been
holding it for a long time.
Yes, that's right. When we met up,
what did you give me first?
Um, I caught it with a UF catcher.  It's like a
stuffed animal, a stuffed animal.When I
was waiting for Chiara-senpai, I was waiting for him at the game.I was
lucky enough to get two stuffed animals, so I
thought, ``Oh, I got it!'' and
decided to give this to Chiara-senpai as a present.  It was
n't the Popon Purin that I said I was
talking about, but it wasn't the Popon Purin.But when I
said Papa Papa, there was already a
person with that beautiful shining light.
So I thought it was definitely that person, so I dashed over there to
get Latte. He was so kind, and he seemed to be a
genius catcher. He
just happened to get those two. He
caught one of those two.  I said I got it in one shot, I
got it in one shot, and the other
one I got in three shots, yeah, I got it. That's
amazing. I can't do it. It just
so happens that UF is the catcher's way.  You should do some
advice streaming That's really good Thank you for
doing it I
got the Woopa Dopa That's right Minecraft The
axolotl stuffed animal is UF
Gacha It's okay I got it
Axolotl axolotl
Minecraft
Palpa Oh tell me one more thing  Wait a minute.
You see, we talked a lot before the broadcast,
so there's already a lot of things I want to say to you,
Lale-chan.
Yeah,
well, you probably like alcohol, but I don't like
it and don't drink at all. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know if you know that,
but I already know that you don't like drinking.
He didn't have any alcohol,
so he bought me some kind of fancy juice,
but it was really fancy.I
thought it was some kind of alcohol.It came in a box or something.Yes, it was
stylish.What did you prepare for me?
Well, this time, there's a
mandarin orange juice from Yamaguchi Prefecture that's not alcoholic.In
Yamaguchi Prefecture, there's a delicious orange juice called, erm, I think it was
called Mikan no Hanayome.
Atsushi: That's right, this time it was that off-collaboration,
so I thought I'd like to drink it with you, so I bought
Jisoo Juice, Yatta
Mandarin Juice,
Mandarin Juice, and Orange Orange.
Mika is a mandarinmandolin, manlima,
mandarinmarinmarinmarin, ohhh, I
gave up on it.Oh, mamandarin juice,
mandarin juice, yeah, orange juice is
a little different, you know,
different.Okay, so you can understand that.
When you look at it,
and when you cut it open, you
can see that it's different. Oh, of course, of course, it's a
mandarin orange. That Japanese man is a mandarin orange.  I
love them so much that I eat them a lot in the winter,
so I eat them one by one with the skin on them.Yeah,
oranges aren't really suitable for that, so I
can't really eat them that way.  He
looked like he didn't understand,
but the orange one is a little bigger than the orange one,
so I guess he doesn't eat it in the form of a snack.  Should I
just drink that juice normally? That's a
good thing. I've
learned it. Before I learned English, I was
taught common sense. I thought it was common sense, common sense,
but maybe it's not common sense.  Do
you eat sweets? What kind of sweets do you eat? Osebe Osebe Osebe Osebe I love Japanese Osebe.
Of course I'll give it to you  I'm
preparing a little introduction, Oishio
Oishio Oishio Oishio Real Real
Alright then, when Raden-chan is looking for something to choose from, there's
still a lot more.Is
there anything you want to say?Show me a book about Japanese art.  After he gave it to
me, it was amazing. He looked
happy and happy and
showed me something like that. The only thing I
didn't see was Kinji's, but then there was Raden's. I
didn't know that Raden was Raden.  We
talked about what we wanted to know,
we talked about Yakiniku, and we talked about Yakiniku. I
hope I don't forget. We
went to eat Yakiniku together. We weren't planning on eating Yakiniku, but the
restaurant we originally wanted to go to was closed.  I went to yakiniku,
and I love
yakiniku, but when I go to yakiniku in Japan,
Japanese people always ask for something inside their body,
like internal organs, so I don't get that much.
I'm really bad at it, so I'm like, oh, what should I do?
That's what I always do, but that Raden-chan, Raden-chan, just like me, loves ribs, so she just ate moldy things. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, she's been eating ribs forever, so this is it.  I
'm sorry, I forgot to take a picture, but there's a sweet ostentation in the shape of an inner ring.It's so
cute.It
's kind of cute.
But what's this face? It has
various patterns written on it, like Chidori, and
there's also fireworks, and there's also a pattern of fireworks, and this is
something that looks like a tower, and
there's a picture written on it.  It looks sweet.This is a
rice bowl.Whew, I'm thinking of eating this with you.It's
not a cookie.  The
fragrant and sweet type of delicious
yakiniku.I don't think it's delicious, but it's amazingly grilled.However,
in terms of classification, it's delicious.It's
delicious.That yakiniku is delicious.Yakiniku
Neon YakinikuLaraden-chan mostly grilled it for me.
But after that,
after I ate a lot of Calbee, I was
thinking of having ice cream, and I looked at that menu,
but when I saw the ice cream on the menu,
all I could think of was 31.
So I asked Da-chan if I wanted to go to Thirty One,
and someone brought me Tiwa, and
it was nearby, so yeah, they're
playing something like Super Mario right now.  The one that I
always ask
for is the one that I always ask for.
What is that? I wonder if it's Berry Berry Aun.
Love potion, oh yeah, that's right.
Unnaden-chan is only available for a limited time.  I
ate a lot of stuff, right?
Well, I guess that's Mario
's double crepe. If I ate a double crepe, it
would be like Katara Grape Star. It
was delicious. It was delicious.  Uh, I
ended up here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's
delicious. It's delicious. I'm
not actually chatting today. I
think we can do it while chatting, but it
's actually a video for teaching English.
Berry, that's so cool, try introducing yourself in that English.It's like I'm
Raden, and
Kazafune's name is Rakugo.That's right.He
also taught me a lot about Rakugo.It's the
first time I've heard of it, and I didn't know about it.It's a
Rakugo name.  E rakugoka name arago mins japanese
traditional
ah
speaking yang
yang yang ya pin yup yappi so
interesShetoldme
aboutknowwhatthat
WasaGUsit Oh, you're probably sitting, right? You're sitting, right?
Speaking, comedy, speaking, comedy.
[Music]
Havetell Yeah, we've been doing the same thing for a long time.
Yeah, it's been the same thing for hundreds of years. It's
been about 400 or 400 years.
While continuing the same thing brush -up brush up brush up brush up Asemsem Tail Um
Tairybrasia Brassia Aspitradish Speaking comedy Raden -chan also wants to do that.  PR
withTE I want to see it I want to see it I want to see it I want to see it I want to see it
Yo Ral-chan looks good in that kind of
training training training training
Nan Waiting
Soaran
Chan Past NEXT Generation
No, I'll
pass it on
to the next generation, yeah, I understand.
She Got from the
Restaurant was Like a
huge STEAK that was Way
bigger than
her faceIregetnot
listeningproper.  I
learned a lot. I have to study hard.
Yeah, but I
'll do my best to think that I'll probably forget all the words I'm going to teach you today within a day. I'll do my best
because the archive will remain. Study By
Archive
O willTry
TE I hope even just a little bit of that will be helpful.
But on the other hand, I learned a lot of things that I didn't know.Where
's the mouse?The mouse is here.Oh, okay, this is
this.What's
behind the in-wah?
Yeah, it's golden!
Yes, how do you say it in English? Gold
Experience No Golden Ratio
Goal Golden
Gold Ratio Ratio Ratio Oh yes, it's famous.
Up warm up I
understand Warm up Let's warm up a little bit Let's
warm up our bodies Let's warm up
our bodies Uh jin oh ee ai How do you say this color in English? Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to
Magenta
Ah, well, first of all, there
are those easy colors, like pink and blue. Yes, those are
boring, so I'm going to quiz you on colors with interesting names. I did the quiz, but Genta is still easy, so yeah, what is this? Blue.  There are a lot
of splashes, right? It's really indigo. Uh, indigo was a lie. It was cute. I was surprised, but yeah, it's not that great. I did it, too. To be honest, I've added some of that blue, so which one is it?  I'm so
glad you said that.In Japanese, the
word indigo is often used.Indigo
sometimes appears in that dyed material,
ummmm, in textiles.Indigo
often appears in textiles.Uh, okay, I
don't even know what this is.
Uh, no, it's not yellow, it's
definitely not yellow.  What's up, Amber? Amber,
Amber. Amber, amber.
But Amber, it's actually
a little bit more orange. Actually, it's a little bit
more orange. Actually, it's ah-ho-ho-ho-ho, but it's
ok to be amber. Yeah, it's amber. Wow, Amber.
Anyway, this power point is mine.  I made it,
but later I asked my mom to
add some colors.To
be honest, I don't really know what will come out.I see,
thank you, Senkyu Manager, Senkyu.  It
was amber. I thought it was mustard.
But mustard is a little different. Yeah, I wonder if I can
understand this. I feel like I can understand this.
Scarlet.
Maybe it's scarlet. Wine red. A malone.
Malone. Eh. This is marron. Maron. This is maroon.
That's right, it was Maron,
so I thought it was definitely Krims Crimson,
but hey Maron,
Maron is really Mane-chan.
[Music] ``
Maron'' It seems like that's the case.The
name is a little like that
brownish red color.I wonder
what this is
?  It's called light
green New Grass color I'm not
sure what it is Gupapa Hmm New grass I
don't know Olive Oh maybe it's olive This is
probably olive It's olive Olive
Wow
Olive Olive Isn't it a good color?It's a good color.Usually  I
wonder if the colors on this monitor are correct. Well, there's a bit of a difference between the colors everyone sees right now
and the colors you see on that Raden monitor. They
may be a little different, they may be different.  I'm
sorry if I'm trying to be charming. Yeah, it
's an unbreakable olive color. Olive
Yeah, then next time I think it's a bit of a rug.
Oh, oh, I don't understand this. I definitely
don't understand. I wonder if it's a
thin village or something.
It's lavender. I wonder if they put lavender in it. Lavender. Lavender. Oh, lilac. Lilac. Lilac is lilac. It's good that you know lilac. Lilac is a song. That's right. Okay, nice. Banchoiro.  I'm
saying, ``Terua Bunchi'', it's definitely Bancho color.
Now that you mention it, ``Bae Lila'', that's a stylish name for a color.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I think the next one will be good. It's
pretty bright. It's definitely a little bit of red.  It
feels like raspberry, but I do
n't think it's called raspberry.This is
cranberry.Cranberry
cran.It's crimson.Crimson.That's
not crimson or cranberry.I
thought it was darker.I
see.
Crimson, right, Crimson. Is there a name for that in Japanese? I
do
n't know. Yeah, I don't know. This is, uh, sink,
sink.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's not deep red. I wonder if it's not deep red.
What is this? It
may look very yellow to everyone right now,
but when I look at it on my monitor, it
looks quite yellowish-green.  Yeah, it's a bit dark,
but it's a bit brighter when you look at it from my angle.
Even with this, it
's not like an egg. It's not an egg
color.  I
know diff Eshiru
Eshi Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeehh nowersies for a while I think that people in Japan
usually leave their walls white,
but yeah, most people overseas
leave their walls in this kind of color.
Well, I'm going to make it a little brighter than this, but it looks like it's
going to be a famous color, and it's a famous color.It's a very famous color
no matter where you look.It
should be a lot brighter than this,
but, oh, oh, marigold.
Marigold,
maybe, maybe,
maybe, oh, maybe, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa that flower, uh, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Yes, Tapo or Deraio, I see,
that's right, that's right. I wonder if that's the official name.
Really, Dandelion. It's definitely, definitely, it's Ta-bobble. That's what I'm
told.  Well, next
thing, this isn't indigo. It's a stunning blue, but I
wonder what it is. Yeah, it
's not really an ordinary blue.
Hey, there's a blue called navy, but navy is
not dark, it's navy, isn't it? In Japanese, it's gray,
or something like aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Colors: I
think there are some colors that have completely fixed names, but I
think some people are free to choose their names, so
it really depends on the person.  I don't
think it's even an official name, but there are a
lot of things like that.Ah, well, well, well,
there's something young and sexy again.This is matcha,
matcha, matcha, green tea, macha.It's really
different, isn't it?
Green tea, yeah.  So lime?
Lime seems more yellowish, but
emerald emerald emerald
Ed, wow, the one I mentioned earlier
was sapphire, so I thought it was emerald.
Nice, yay, nice, safe, nice, safe, yay, wow,
this is so bright. It's so
bright. It's an old guy at a construction site.
The color of this guy's calyx is a little
green. Depending on the screen, it looks a little green. To everyone else, it
looks a little green.  I wonder if
it's a lemon, but it's a little greener than a lemon,
but not quite a lime.I wonder if this is possible.What is
this, oh, what is this?
Strass, why is it disappearing?
Treshatrius Shachatrius Chaturius I wonder
if it's Shachatrius Chatot Briand, not
Shatochatrius Ah Shatrius, yeah
Shahun, that's fashionable Shatrius Shi Fluorescent-ish
stuff I heard it for the first time today I
heard it for the first time today I remember, I remember Chatorius
Sid  But it's French. It
might also be used in Momo.
Hohohohoho It's originally from France. I
see. I got a gray-ish one.  I
guess this isn't gray,
right? Is it concrete? Is it
concrete? Is it concrete?
Nya, you think it's different. This is gray. Jeans, jeans, jeans, no, Ash, Ash, Ash.  It's
the color of a mouse, let's take a look at the mouse.
Yes, it's pew, pew, pew,
pew, pew, that's pewter. I
've never heard of this before.
Pewter,
Mane-chan, where did you get that information?
When I went to the hair salon, I said ``
Kopewta'' and tried it on.I wonder if it would work or not, but I would choose the color.Yeah, I do
n't understand, ah, I don't understand, I definitely don't understand.Don't you
think it wouldn't work in America?
Wow,
this is dark. Yeah, this is
asphalt, asphalt, asphalt color
. Uh, this is ash, ash, ash.
What do you think?
Obsidian, oh,
Obsidian, uh, Obsidian.
Well, it's a word you know in Minecraft,
right? Don't you know it? That
's how Minecraft
is, isn't it? Obobsidia. That's what it is.
That's Mike. It's been a few years
since I joined Hololive, and it was my first time playing Minecraft.
But yeah, I've been playing Minecraft for several years.
That Obsidian stone called Obsidian.  Is
n't it? So, recently I
realized that obsidian does exist in real life. Is
n't it a word made up by Minecraft in Minecraft? Obsidian is
such a
fancy word, no, I can't believe it exists.  I
thought it wouldn't,
but I do because there are also blocks made by Minecraft, and
Retton Redstone's
redstone
doesn't know what redstone is, so maybe it doesn't exist.
Yeah, obsidian is something like that. Yeah, it was used for hunting. It's
hard and sharp, so if you
try to use it, it'll look ugly, but you can manipulate it.
Yeah, oh, I see. That's Obsidian. Yay, oh, orange, orange,
orange.  This is the orange we drank.The
color of the juice.The color of the orange juice.It
's delicious.That's right, that's what it means.The name of this color
is, ah, it's not an orange.Wait, it's not an
orange.Yes, but it's not an orange.  It's
not Mandarin, it's Tenzin, so it's
called Tarin.  It
looks like it's a different fruit,
but it's from the same family hahahahaha Let's go to fruit.
There's also a clementine. I
know clementine. Clementi.
Clementine Clementine
Clementine Yeah, that's it, that's it, family
too Yes, yes, yes, I
see.  I
'll teach you some art-related words, please. Um,
well, it's a bit small
. Well, first of all
, let's start from the top. Yes, this is a
fashionable ah word. Howe, the top right one is
Yes, you can read Japanese, right? Aesthetics Aesthetics What is aesthetics?
In English, it can be called in many ways,
but let's call it esthetics.
This word is used to describe things like really
beautiful buildings, things like buildings, things
like the atmosphere of a room, things like
this, things like that, furniture, things like that.  I
like
esthetics. I like esthetics. I like esthetics.
But I'm like, oh, oh, oh, oh,
yeah, I like
that feeling. If I say I like this kind of atmosphere, then
this is esthetic.  It's
so cool that I looked at that wetness
and thought it looked red, and it's Itis
esthetics, oh that's great. This A
doesn't read A. It's not A stick, it's
A. It's esthetic A, not stick.  Yes, I
understand, esthetics,
esthetics, ah, na esthetics, next. I think this will probably
be useful for Rale-chan.
Yes, it's an
exhibition. In Japanese, it's an exhibition. I understand this.
I know, I understand, but what kind of
thing have you ever been to?
There's so many, so many Vermeers,
Vermeer exhibitions, Fefes,
Vermeer Vermeer, what is it, Gaga-san,
Fermeda's Ao Vermeer?  There
were so many art exhibitions and so
on. Wow, I never go. There are so many. Let's
go together next time. Let's go. Let's go to as many as possible.
Eh, the next thing is, I think you'll understand again, but I
just wrote it down, and there's a pollet lamp.Yes,
this is a
different land scheme.  The
trendy
way of distributing is
portraits. When you take portraits, you
use landscapes, but they
can also be used for other purposes, such as when you draw someone's portrait.  A
beautiful background is a beautiful background, or rather, a
landscape. Yes, a beautiful landscape is beautiful.
Landscape Yes, there are many, many
uses for that word. Yes, I know this word. You
look like that.
Nice, nice potole. I'm happy. I'm
happy. You know that.  I'm a little happy.
The next word is, yeah, try reading it in English.
Te Avant Gran Ga Guard
Aaaa Avant Avant Guard Avant
Garde. Yes, that's
right. I sometimes hear the word "Avant Garde" in Japanese.  It
's a word, but yeah, how do you read this? Well,
this is avant-garde. Yes, avant-
garde. Avant-garde. Honestly, I'd
like Raden-chan to explain this to me.
For example, if
you make a bowl like this
in a hexagonal shape,
it would be very avant-garde, like Avangeld.  I
mean, it's something new that hasn't been seen before, right, right, it's New Generation-ish, it's Avangeld.
Composition
Composition This is composition composition, right? It
's composition. Yes, you
know it's composition. It's Japanese, so you can understand it.  It
's esthetics, and esthetics is good too.If the
composition is good, esthetics is
good too.Sometimes, something that is
important in composition is
symmetry.
If you want to say that it's the enemy of symmetry, don't use symmetry.  It's a
symmetrical trick.
Yes, you can say that. I
see. Look at that Raden-chan.
Raden's front hair is quite symmetrical.
But Piara's hair isn't that symmetrical. That's
why it's emery.
Wow, you're smart.  Okay, you're smart.
This guy did a pompom pudding face, a
ponpon print face is symmetry, a
poplin yup, he did it, and the last one is here. The
last one on this slide is PER.  I
'm sure there are many different translations of pastite, but there
are angles, points of view, and
so on, but I thought this one was the
closest in terms of meaning.  The meaning I want to convey is
that it seems like it's going
to be a good idea.  I
want to see Scuti, hunhunhunhunhun
Io, I've learned a little, I've memorized a little, but I've learned a little, and there are some
words that I already knew.
Mass, mass,
mass, mass, mass, mass, wherever you went, mouse
, mass, here you were, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here,
oh yeah, I found you, yeah, yeah, let's continue, uh,
hey, those verbsverbs
I'll teach you
Babas what are the verbs in Japanese? What do you
do ahoh oh eh verb verb naun uh oh oh oh that
scraping
scraping scraping this is Unraden I
think it's an important word for chan ho shaving
When you make Raden, you scrape it, right
? Yes, that's right, that's right.
Scraping Jiji Raden
Yes, yes, I see, that painting
is just painting.Pain
hehe, ShePainPiof is also
making some kind of stuff.That's right,
that Shaden pokes at the shadow.There
's a shadow, right?Shad is a shadow, yes, a
shadow.  When I learned to poke, I realized that it
was Shaden.I
didn't know the proper Japanese word for ``to create texture''.
It's like this, but I think there are
various techniques for tech and tech,
but for example, for
example, toilet paper or something
[Music]
Well, that's it, and
there's also blending makeup, haha.  Yes, there are many ways to mix things up.
Yes, there are many ways to mix them up. Yes, Ray, this, this, that,
Scouting,
Scouting, Scouting, and whatnot.  Let's
make a sculpture that looks good for scouting Sculpture Kapchi
That's right.The result is a sculpture.Hahahahahahahahaha
, the last part is too easy,
but coloring to color Eho.
Good, no,
nice. Who is this next? Who is this person in the upper right? If you
don't know who this person is, you're fired.
This person is, uh, wait, wait, wait.  Um, uh,
Da Vinci, Da Vinci,
Da Vinci, Da Vinci, that's terrible, that name was
about to blow up right now, it looks like it's in danger, it's in danger, I don't
know if it's right, it doesn't matter if you don't know,
but it's in danger,
thank you, let's go from above.
Um, don't look down yet. That's a
whim. Yeah, it's difficult. Yeah, it's difficult. It's a
musical. But let's
say "Usko." It's a whim.  It's okay
to be a whimsical house cat
. There are some cats that are like Wesco. Yeah, yeah, I see. I see
, Kia is really cute.
But it's okay, it's okay. The
next orgasm is clean and
clean. The innocent Landen-chan has been a little lately.  It
may have become cleaner,
but it's so clean that it
doesn't have that cigarette alcohol or anything like that.
But you don't do that now, do you?
Smoking,
smoking,
doesn't it? Seriously, it doesn't really smell bad.
Yeah, I'm surprised. You can call someone anytime. Welcome, welcome, all people. I
really quit. I really quit. It's
amazing how you can quit. I
quit. I quit.
Yeah, I quit. Yeah, I don't feel like smoking. I
want to smoke, but when that happens.
Haha Acandy Yeah, Gum, Gum, Sweet, Sweet, Coffee, etc. Add another thing that you endure to your mouth.  It's
okay to become beautiful right now
Moamoai Kirei Rade Do your best
Do your best Where did you go?
Okay, nice Aye That Raden-chan
is lofty, but I
really like those words I'm Dedivine Divine
Divine Divine Divine is so
beautiful  When I see a goddess, I
say, Wow, that's a goddess.
Define, Wow, that's a goddess.
When Raden met Chiara-senpai today, he said, Wow, that's divine.
That's what I was thinking. You
can use it here. It's appropriate.
[Music]
Other than that, it's
exquisit. I
think it's often used for things like food.  That's
right, you go to a really fancy restaurant and
eat some delicious dessert or something,
and then you say, ``Thissoexquis''.  It's
increasing, it's amazing, it's
perfect, it's amazing, it's perfect, it's complete, it's amazing, it's
revolutionary, this painting is revolutionary, the
technique is revolutionary, that's what I
mean.When you want to say it,
say WOWThisis revolutionary.
Aww
Revolutionary Sinner
Ah Revolutionary Ille
Revolution 21 Soul Revolution
Soul Revolution's Revolution I I see,
that's right, Revolutionary Revolutionary
Yeah, yeah, yeah, illustrations, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I
see, so this is unshiru, I think it's a word that is also used when it's called serial, but unshiu, yeah, the reading of this is sil, serial real, or something like
stage.
That's the kind of feeling I get when I stand up,
but I also have that kind of feeling, but
there are also paintings that are like that.  I'm
going somewhere soon. I'm
not running the live 2D this time.
This is this. This is it.
Hakone Pola Art Museum. Oh, I
brought some books. Uh, Sil Sil
Real Exhibition Sil Real
Exhibition Realism No. Hmm,
a bit.  Wow, it feels a bit
real, but it's so surreal
. Surreal originally comes from literature,
right?
Yes, this is what I was talking about earlier.
But this isn't Asraku. I
think it's Asu, too. Asu is written below it.
In Japanese, it's written as "Abstract."
I'm Asura,
and I've taught you a lot of those amazing and fashionable words
in Struct.
This vibe is so
good. When do you want to say it?
[Music]
I've got a
vibe. It's so
easy to understand that I tried to make it into a galgo. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I understand.
Oh, it's so nice to
be with Lebechi, I see.
For some reason, Galgo also
taught me how nice it is to have a good time with my mouth.
Mouthbaby, you can use any of these, you can use them for anything.
When Birarun-chan says it, it's cute. Always bye, oh, nice, nice. I
'm going to use it. Yes, there's a slide in addition to this. It
seems like there's also a slide in addition to this.  That's
right, this is the one that Chiara-senpai wrote to
me when she asked me if there was something she wanted to say in English. That
's right, that's me.  I
didn't understand anything about this at all. I didn't
know what Raden's name meant until
today. Well, that's what you did for me today. Yeah, that's
right. I think this episode will probably be used for that. I
don't think it's a meeting, but this one can also be used.
Today I learned about
name Yes,
Ashika also showed me a necklace made from Raden.  I'm
sorry, but it's Japanese, but it's
Japanese, but you can watch
it anyway. Yeah, yeah,
no, it's a bit difficult to translate Masuraden into English.  Well, I don't know
how to say Ma of PER, but Pearl
's mother is Pearl's mother, so it's leverage.The
second word for ``Yes'' or ``Un''
is ``Nei'', ``Maker'', and ``Ma of PER''.To be
honest, I learned it today, so I
don't really understand it either.  I
guess that's what a nail is called.
Yeah, that's the technique. It
's called in-rein, where you stick something you've shaved off on something like a necklace.  It
's rain, it's in rain, it's in
rain, but I don't really understand it, Ren-chan.
Wow, it's so difficult, I have no
choice but to explain it one by one.  I
got it, I got it, I got it, did I get it? These words are difficult to explain, but yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, but it's funny, very funny. I learned a lot of Laren-chan's name today. Yay, Kirakubo.  I do
n't know about that, but I'm happy and I learned a lot.What Raden-chan said was so funny.Illustrated by Ushiushii and A-chan.Thank
you very much, Illustrator.  That
's what I heard when it's called lacquer lacquer in English. Yeah, lacquer is lacquer.
Yeah, that's right. In Japan, sumac and
lacquer are two different things.
But what makes it so delicious
? There's a tree called the Rakku of a tree.  I
think you were the one who explained it the best,
but you showed me the
thing in that bag.
I wonder if it comes out of
the bond.
Ahisaib, that thing sticks together,
right? Yes, yes, it's
sweet. It's like syrup. Yes, right now
that bowl is right in front of me, and I
took it from that bowl, and the bowl is right in front of me. I
want to show it to everyone.  I thought it was a great C. It's
like a blood pack. The
stuff inside is amazing. Actually, this is the one. The
on-location video I took of the cow is also in
Japanese, but it's in Japanese.  You
can watch it as a normal length video, not a short one, so I'm sure it's a good video.Recently,
there's a video of me going on location.
I want to
pass on this story.It's interesting.I feel
like all of the words you taught me are connected to Urushi.Yes,
this is it.Mom,
you're beautiful, you're beautiful.
[Music]
knows
ADD It's easy to understand Mae, but
there's no English word for it, so this is a simple explanation.But
when you explain to someone in English what Ma is, you
say Raku Decoration.
Silver Laca Decoration
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there's also platinum. It's
not always gold and silver, it's platinum. It seems
like there's also platinum, oh, platinum, platinum. I wonder
if there's a lot of gold in it. It's
beautiful, it's beautiful. I'm sorry, everyone.  I
can't see it yet, but right in front of my eyes is the stomach and intestines.The
place called Wajima in Ishikawa Prefecture is
famous for its beautiful Wajima lacquer.It's so famous
that it's so sparkly.
What
do you mean by that bowl, that plate?
That's why
Japanese tableware is so beautiful.
There are things like happy maki and happy lacquer.
Japanese tableware is the best. I'm really happy. I just
learned about it today. I didn't know about it. I'm so
happy.  I
didn't know there was such a thing, so I'm looking at it like this.
Now I'm
happy. I've
learned so much from you. I'm so
happy that I have one more.
Kim, this is a beautiful word, yay, but
there's no proper English for this either.Even
overseas, kinji is kinji.So, you
might be able to read this, too.
The lulacca technique is cool.Oh
yeah, that's right.When something
breaks, you fix it with that gold and that
lacquer lacquer.Well, I
did some research today to find out what this is.
At the time, it became the philosophy of Japan.Philosophy U
live and live
Hmm, I don't mean it, but
Philosophy Ahhh Philosophy Philosophy Philosophy Philosophy
Philosophy Philosophy Philosophy How to live Ah
Yes, yes Yes, that's right, right? I read something about that
on Google.
It's not just about making dishes like this, it's
also about how to live, which also applies to life.
Yes, that may be true, but I think there is a more beautiful way to say something like, ``Do
n't throw away something that has been discovered, fix it, use it,
fix it, and make it even more beautiful.''
Yaorozgod
's
Zugocho is seriously seriously too difficult to
ask, but now he's saying that the question he was asked for the first time at Yakiniku is
a little distorted in English.  I do
n't understand what you mean, Meni Meni God, Meni Meni God For now, Meni Meni God This is also especially true.If you keep using something without words, God will dwell in it.Yeah, there's nothing like that, it's a great explanation.Well, it's
all God.It's a little
difficult to explain.I don't like this either.  But it's beautiful, I
think it's a technique. I'm glad I did
it, but I've come here to see Ra-chan and
seen a lot of things, but it's all about the money.
No, no, no, no, no, no, I've never
broken anything, so I've never spent money on it.
Well, that's because I broke it in my own house, and I
had to pay for the broken item.  It's
not like they're selling it. Selling it and buying it are different. No, it's not a no-no. In fact,
Kinji's technique is used in the slightest part of the vessel.
There is
However, I feel like the meaning behind Kinji's work is to
repair it, so it feels like he's
repairing his own things just for himself.Of
course, there's also artistic value,
so there are a lot of things in this area.
That's the golden experience class that has a trial class.The number of people who
want to try it has been increasing recently.Oh, let's go, let's
go to a trial class.I wonder if I'll go to a trial class.
It's a used second hand that doesn't have a second hand.Oh, I
wonder why they don't sell it.That's because someone uses something inside, so it would be a waste if we didn't sell it to the next person.  If I look for it, I might be able to find it.Yes, do you want to go
try it out with me?Let's
go.Let's go to Kinji Kinji Experience.There might
be a flea market or something like that.Maybe there
was an antique shop or something like that in the past.
It's not there, it's this, this, this, this, this, this, this, antique, antique, antique, old, old, old, old, all, ah, antique, antique, antique.  I
think I've seen a lot of tableware that looks like Kinji's, but I
wonder if it's a fake.  They
only do it on the outside, but it doesn't really matter if it's
broken or not, it looks like it's because of their eyes, so it's
fashionable, so they just make it that way.Maybe they
incorporate it into the design.I
don't know.  It's not that gold-plated one, but the
rolls that could be rolled are also made of gold powder.So I put
a little bit of lacquer on the surface, and
then sprinkled some gold powder on it.
I'm sorry everyone who hasn't been able to
see it for a long time.  I've been
studying a lot and I
can speak a lot of things, so thank you very much.I'm
a bit of an expert, so
this English pronunciation is
a little too high, so I
suddenly thought it would be better to learn from that base.  I
think I'll do my best from the basics. I've
learned how to say things. She's
cute. I
like white.
Yay. I
felt like Ra-chan was a little shy on Discord.
But she's really energetic and looks like a dog,
so today was the day.  Because I was really looking forward to it,
after I found out that you were going to come to that collaboration lab, I got a little excited and prepared too many things,
and my power
point was so short that I got sidetracked by that addition.
Yes, of course, of course,
of course, we were talking about ramen over there, and I
said, ``Yeah, I'm a bit of a ramen eater, so I like that list.'' You know, I'm relieved that no one can see me.
There are a lot of ramen that are much better than Ichidan,
so when I said that, I was told by all kinds of people that
Razen-chan was the most delicious.  If you
promote it so much, you might be
from Fuku.
Then I asked you, and you said, Oh yeah, then, yeah, Laren-chan's
opinion is bias, bias, bias,
bias. Well, she's from that area, so there are many opinions that are biased in that direction.  Yes, it's
good, it's good, it's bad, it's
bias, it's bias, it's bias, it
's like, yeah, I'm surprised that you know that. I
just said that the list is delicious, and
then you tell me that you're from Fukuoka.  I was so
surprised by A-senpai's white style and experience that he
said in the loudest voice in the taxi, ``Do you
understand?'' But
Rade-chan also said, ``Yes, I can't eat that ramen.'' I'm
sorry.  If I do
n't have it, how will I eat it? I don't know either. But
why are you chewing with a spoon and chopsticks?
Yeah yeah, I'll wind it up.
Yeah yeah, I'll eat it quietly tomorrow.
If you don't mind,
please try my technique.If you
ask me how you eat it, you'll
start sprinkling on that ramen.  So,
add some soup, and then
add some corn, green onions, etc. to make the mini ramen.And
then there's the cat tongue, so when the mini ramen is
done, you can go fufufufufufu.
Even if you're a Japanese person who likes to eat,
there are a lot of people out there who do.
There's a big
one, and I'm
really confused about how to eat it.That's right, it's so big that I
can't even fit it in my mouth.The
truth I saw in the anime.
Mini ramen is taboo in Japan,
isn't it? It's not taboo at all,
but eating it that way
takes a hell of a lot of time, like an
hour. Eating lame noodles takes an hour, but as long as it's
delicious, I'll give it a try.
Seriously,
if you eat it the normal way,
only the noodles will go into your mouth.I don't
know.
Karaun, yeah, it's the best,
but I feel like I'm happier if it lasts for an hour than if it ends in about 10 minutes or 5 minutes, even if it's just an hour.  I've
never made mini ramen before.
I'm not the only one who makes mini ramen. It's
delicious, and I think everyone will try it. Even
in the chat earlier, everyone made mini ramen.
Since I said that, I'm sure everyone will do it too.
Everyone in the chat probably takes 5 minutes to
finish making the mini lame.There
are people who do it.It's a lie.If you've
never done it before, try it.It's
delicious.There are people who do it besides me.  I've never seen it before. I
ate ramen yesterday. It was so rich. It was so rich. That's
not a list. It's not a list.
What was the name you posted on Twitter?  I wonder
what it is, I think someone probably saw it,
but the one that's
thick and thick is probably miso or soy
sauce.I think there are three kanji in it.Jiro-
type.Oh yeah,
that's it.  I think it's white,
but there are 3 kanji, right? It's Tenka Ippin, Ane Tenka. It's
not Ipprono, it's Iprononoe.
There was a Musashi restaurant
near where I ate, and I
ate a lot there.My
ideal ramen would be that Fukuoka pork bone
ramen, and that Hokkaido miso
ramen.  For some
reason, Fukudate's ramen is perfect as it is,
but I really want them to put batter and corn on top of it.  It's
corn, it's corn, it's corn, it's corn.
They don't have corn anymore in Ramen in Fukuoka. If they had it, it would have been divine, but the Kogo that was so hot is Debai. Debai Debai. The slides on Debai Debai are a little buggy, but everyone doesn't care.  So,
please, there
's a bit of a cat bug. This one doesn't have a bug. I wonder if this is Debye Debine.
This one's like this one, it's delicious, it's delicious. I
want to bring a corn to the list already.
I just want to bring it and put it on top of it.I love ramen,
so it's delicious.It's best to eat delicious Unmi in a delicious way.Nya
Nyan Ninini Nin
Nya Un Ramen has everything.  You
can put anything on Raden too
Ramen raden ramen raden Ramen raden Make
ramen, make it, make it
Make it, make it butter butter and corn.  Let's do it
with that Hakata thin feeling. Add pork bone
butter and corn. The
raden ramen has set.
Hey, good raden. Wait for the raden to go on sale.
Everyone, wait for the original ramen.
Please taste it.
Eat raden.  He's such a cute and kind Kyuta and
has such an interesting story. I can really tell if he's a fan of Raden-chan. I know he's
doing something that other people wouldn't do. It seems like it
's true. I just learned the truth today.
Sorry, I don't have any time to watch that stream.
Yeah, I don't
really know what kind of content they're streaming. I do
n't know, but I thought they were talking about something like
Rakugo. I
thought he was an interesting person.  Today, I
spent about half a day with Chiara-senpai, and I thought she
was a really fun person to hang out with, and I was so fluent
in Japanese that it was the first time I saw her.
Raden also did a lot of research to learn how to
use English in everyday conversation,
but he didn't need it at all.He
spoke surprisingly fluent Japanese.  The one who
bought me Tasou Yakiniku was Ao, but I
lost the accounting battle. But
instead of buying me ice cream, thank you for the ice cream. I also
have ice cream. I'll
buy you anything. Please tell me anything.
Raden-chan, you say that I'm good at Japanese,
but I haven't really had a
chance to speak Japanese anymore, so I'm pretty
bad at it, so I asked you to collaborate with me.Of
course, of course, let's
collaborate a lot.  I've
never
done that guesswork too much. I've
done some with my hand camera. It's
kind of like a painting.  I want to
do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it, I
want to do it, I want to
do it.  Someday, someday, Kinji or something,
let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go to a museum, let
's go to a museum.
a
Of course, I'll take you with me.It
's okay.Even if you're an advanced Japanese
speaker, there's absolutely no need to worry about rakugo, because there are always things you don't understand.Of course,
if you could just give a simple explanation of what you were talking about afterwards, oh
oh.  Of course, the chin is already
enjoyable, and everyone is saying it's awesome
Ah, I
can do it. I'm looking forward to it.
After the collaboration, let
's go to Fukatcha. I'll take whatever you want. Leave it to me.
Oh, it was fun. Just put in the money until you get it. It's
okay. I can get it in one shot. Nare-chan, I
can go in one shot. I'll do my best. There's nothing like today. I'll
do my best and get as much as I can.  Latin-chan,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, no, no, no, I've been
spoiled by Chiara-senpai's kindness all day, and
I'm really, really grateful. It's
been great, and I'm also grateful.
Thank you very much for coming to my house.
Thank you very much. When
I'm in Japan, I'm in a hotel right now, so it's
difficult to stream from a hotel, so it
would be helpful if I could go to that member's house. Thank
you for coming. Thank you for coming. But what time?
But I'm always opening the door, I'm always leaving the front door
unlocked, I'm giving
you the key, I'm going to drop it, so I'm going to give
you the key too.  He's
been talking about Europe for a long time, and keeps saying things like ``Loppa's place is nice'' and ``this place is
nice here.'' No,
come quickly. I've only been able to go once,
so I'm going to Europe and go
to Striasure.  Let's come and go together from there to the
Netherlands or Italy or
wherever we want to go.I'm
so happy that I'll take care of that conversation, so
I guess I'll just have to follow you.  I'm
really happy. I
want to see the palace. I want to go to the church. I
want to go to the church. I want to go. I want to
go.  I
say I'm going, I'm going, but you're not coming.
Then come on. I'm serious. I
'm going. I'm going. There's so many things I want to see.
Promise, promise, promise. That finger cut.  I'm
going to drink Pompompurin because I'm a liar.Okay, but I
have to come in two years from now.Until two years from now.Oh, too much
time has passed.  If I
were to be more specific, would you
be able to watch it? I'm
going to do it this year. I'm going to do it this year. I'll
do it this year. Oh,
okay. I can stream it from my house,
so everyone, I'll stream it.
Okay, now I don't have to do everything in front of the rules.
Hey everyone. Hey,
if you get the ticket first, you'll probably be able to go.
Yeah, let's go, yeah, let's go.
I went right in front of the Louvre and couldn't get in.  I do
n't want to make the same mistakes again. I've talked about this before.
I've never been inside either, so let's go. Let's
go see the Mona Lisa.
Raden is more beautiful than the Mona Lisa, though.
a  Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa---a---a-----a-----------------------------------------------------------------
I enjoyed
it too.Thank you very much for preparing the slides.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much for the points.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.Thank you very
much.  I hope
you all enjoyed the first collaboration with Kiarade.
Thank you very much.
Video
Senkyu Overs listeners thank you
for Kamin
Senkyu Senkyu Berri Berri Berri
Ultra Berry Atsu Bye No No
No No Bye Bye
Bye Yeah Yes No That's what I'm
looking at today.  Thank you very much for coming to
Senkyu.
Then we say goodbye and say
goodbye. After this, we will eat mochi sweets.  I've
prepared a lot of
things. So, from now on, let
's eat that takeaway. Bye,
bye,
bye, bye, I'll
do it properly. I can't wash it off properly yet.
That's it, hey, I'm going to have a drink.
Cheers to you.  I'm
going to drink again today. I
'm going to drink it too. The butterflies are flying
and it's beautiful. The dragonflies are flying and it's beautiful.  I ca
n't help but think of the image of a bird's voice, a cicada's voice, a girl's sound, Wow! I'm lucky, the moon is coming, and I can't help
it.  This is it, bye bye.