[Music]
K KY
K oh hi oh
hi hello everybody
welcome to the stream uh I am takiki wa
or Ki or
Wawa I'm I'm I'm the leader of Hony yeah
and who is this above
me I am Nashi M oh hi I also go by mum
or MERS and possibly more that I am not
able to remember right now hello yay hor
underling of H yes yes an underling no
no you are a proper part of hotori not
underling I'm I I just feel so small no
no you're not that small I think is
smaller than you that is true that is
that is something that's hard to wrap my
head around yeah she's small you are you
are important part of we are the two Ian
horis and I don't know why but um we
like here
hashtag
m for some reason this is specifically
you know about hot toi promoting
chocolate isn't that wonderful yeah they
acknowledge H we're famous M we're
famous we are yeah I actually just
noticed that yeah you don't know I just
noticed I I don't know oh my gosh
M but uh yeah yeah yeah we have a
hashtag by the way for the stream yes
specifically above mhm I if you guys
have like anything you want to say about
the stream or I would like to see you
guys showing off your magic chocolate
that you've had before or have at home
right now if you have any then show it
up on the hashtag
okay yes I already saw some you did I'm
jealous
jealous well well well um before we get
like really into it um I I want to have
a little bit of small talk we're already
in the small talk but have you had any
Japanese snacks recently mum recently um
recently oh I did take some things home
with me so I ran out last month oh no
time to go again let's go Japan I know
kind to go on a grocery trip to Japan ah
yeah just for the groceries nothing else
just go
but I think you wouldn't have to do that
because I've been told from my uh Na
viewers that uh they do sell mag
chocolate in some places here and there
so I'm sure they do I'm sure you can
order it yeah you must be able to order
it mhm and and I think for me at least
in the Asian supermarkets I could find
it in Europe in like specifically Asian
ones I think I could
too I just haven't looked yet now I I
know to look next now now go look look
look and and yeah so just make it really
obvious if it's not obvious enough we
are sponsored today by the Japanese food
manufacturer M so we will tell you all
about their most famous products I
suppose they have they have a huge
lineup okay it's a huge company they've
been making chocolate for a long long
time and there's of course way more than
we can show um but there'll be a couple
that we'll focus on and maybe you guys
will you know next time you go to Japan
or you go to a supermarket that has
major chocolate uh you can try one of
these out yeah yeah amondo
amooo is there already a most
popular I don't I don't know I think
they're referencing
P ah
I see I see I see yeah yeah so uh on on
this picture that is on the screen right
now uh do you have a favorite one from
these and have you tried any of these
before mhm I've tried quite a few last
time I was in Japan I had the macademia
quite a
really but mhm I also really like the
Almond ones mhm the both have you tried
both of them cuz there's like
two the the middle one tried both of
them je I got my the
dark she just jumped on the table she
wants chocolate too but you're not
allowed chocolate is poisonous to uh uh
cats and dogs don't feed them
chocolate and so the Almond ones and the
Macadamia ones have you tried the the
famous kinoko and takoo
chocolates I tried the K but not the Tak
oh so you can't even make like a proper
opinion
yet no I don't no I can't oh oh it's
poisonous to birds too well not not for
us we're special Birds we're hybrids you
know we're special
birds do we look like birds right now hm
no right oh wait I just realized we're
both wearing glasses I didn't even do
that on purpose cute oh I didn't even
realize either uhhuh cute cute I like
your hair pins or
you so uh yeah the kle the the ones in
the bottom left the kyama and the Tak CH
those are the ones that you guys may
have heard about through Hol life uh
certain whole life members mentioning
them like when they like try to get to
know each other like are you
or
taka it's it's uh yeah an important
question an important matter to clear up
before getting to know a person right
totally I don't I don't really have I
have to try the other one yeah wait you
tried the Kino you said
right M yeah okay well then next time
tle I personally I'm pretty sure I tried
the almond uh chocolates a long time ago
but from this list my favorite actually
is the Galo
chocolates you see the ones in the
middle on the bottom middle mhm those
the the strawberry one and it's not on
this picture but I'm pretty sure there's
a a white chocolate one where the outer
uh part is white chocolate and the
inside is just like the same as these
but those twoo I actually really like
them uh I ate them a lot
back in the day yeah the strawberry one
they have a a pretty pretty uh how to
say Fruity Fruity nice flavor I haven't
tried the chocolate only one but I'm
also a big fan of white chocolate so I
tried the white chocolate one
too is white chocolate your favorite out
of the three main ones
uh I think it's just like between like
depending on my mood I'd go for milk
chocolate or white chocolate but then
people say white is not chocolate can
you believe it why chocolate not being
chocolate I I will not accept this
statement ever why would
I this is a debate for another
time oh somebody in the comments just
said this and I actually can agree with
this um I can confirm this that the Galo
chocolates somehow when you touch them
they don't melt on your fingers so you
don't make your fingers
dirty what
yeah actually this might be a case with
the all others too I'm not sure but I
have this memory of gble chocolates
yeah pretty nice I I just know that they
all have really nice packaging very
convenient packaging like oh you haven't
had the ma you haven't had the Macadamia
ones the way they're packaged
is so I saw a picture of the inside yeah
yeah they're like all in their own spots
little I know it's like they all like
their own little bed or something a I
got to be comfy hang out in yeah comfy
oh also I think the the bottom right one
the yanan Su B those those are I haven't
eaten this one uh this one but I've
eaten like similar type of chocolate
before where you have a stick and you
put it into the chocolate container
right I love that that's so genius yeah
that's what that
is I love those those are like sometimes
I would just eat that as like
breakfast is an easy like they have like
the little too ones you know or small
ones that exist like that little little
something I want bigger versions but
yeah so that's um like a general lineup
of course they have more way more than
that um the up the one next to the
bottom right one that's also really
famous one they're all great and of
course the the classic one the milk
chocolate on the top left yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah there there's classic as well M
mhm but uh today we're going in detail
uh about these ones the nut series y nut
nuts yes nuts nuts
nuts many many nuts H so this is the The
Nut Chocolate series that you have also
already tried a couple of before as you
said and me too cuz they
are they're they're they're just they
stand out and they they're beautiful and
they're yummy and I actually if kfb
remembers recently when I went to Japan
I found a lot of like H life related
chocolate in the convenience store and
one thing that I found maybe you saw
this too M but T I took this
picture there's even more subu subu's on
the um on the pistachio one ah subu
wasn't lined up uh when I took the
picture
but can you see guys there's a whole
life collab going on with these
chocolates and they're like big our big
faces are on top of them it looks really
pretty and you get like a card what is
it magito mag toito there's a magnet
sheet uh of each member in
these you can put it on your
fridge I wanted to buy them so badly
every time I saw them I really wanted
them I wonder how long they'll have
them M they're so cute um I I I don't
know how long they're there but if you
guys go to Japan go find them they're
really special how who knows when
they're gone go get them now I need to
ask my manager to save me so good idea
yeah I recommend by the way they did not
asked me to introduce this I just uh
remembered that I saw these recently so
I felt like showing you guys again the
colors are more vibrant in real life
though so I keep that in mind yeah draw
your attention yeah they they're so
pretty so uh that's the nut series um
they look really tasty but we want to
learn about them and you know we we may
we may not eat them during the stream
today but maybe we can get an image of
what they taste like by you know
watching some videos and hearing some
Orin origin story of the chocolate
yes good so uh I'll show you a video
M okay and you guys too so pay close
attention the I have two videos the
first one
is this one hope it's not too
loud
wow
not just any almonds oh sh oh my good oh
my goodness it's
raining yes strict super
strict they have a they they have an
interview with each ask them questions
ready
meas passion and
carefulness
making sure they have no
conditions I didn't know they would
do speed breeds delicacy what high
requirement to
chocolate
[Music]
for how do they not stick to each other
during this progress I don't
[Music]
know so
glossy I
know oh was this packaging sorry I'm
mesmerized I love videos like this oh
yeah packaging wow oh my gosh
years
60 for 60 years theyve been producing
this
chocolate wow I
mean oh my gosh my brain I don't like
thinking about the year because I'm like
oh wait it's not this long ago it's
actually not that's like 1980 I think no
wait 60 60 not 40 19 1960 wait
what
1960 19 she's jealous ignore her ignore
her she wants chocolate oh no no no no
no not for you not for you so wow um it
looks like they definitely made the
whole W process as perfect as it
possibly could be um I hope you paid
attention with me because I'm going to
quiz you no my eyes were glue oh there's
a quiz yeah oh oh I see okay okay are
you are you confident in your knowledge
that you have gained from this video I
think so it wasn't you know it wasn't
too much out it was like the perfect
amount of information yeah and I was I
found it very interesting and when I
find things interesting I'm more likely
to remember so okay interesting so all
right then we shall start the interview
process I if you fail it then I guess
I'm kicking you out of this collab
immediately no that makes sense sense
sense okay then uh I think it's this SL
okay wow so active what's wrong animal
oh my gosh she's sorry she's excited wow
she's trying to distract me wow okay uh
where do the almonds in mag's almond
chocolate come from and number one one
Kenya number two Australia or number
three
USA I think USA because I'm pretty sure
like most almonds in the world come from
California what wait I honestly already
forgot what's wait what you think it's
USA that was I don't think no I they
didn't say I just know that most almonds
come from the US is that a fact from
California pretty sure unless for some
reason they decided to get like a quaint
one in Australia or Kenya
but hey what makes California almond so
special I
wonder I think it's because almonds were
originally where were they originally
grown mostly like shoot like southern
Europe or something so it maybe similar
climate also California just has a lot
of Agriculture especially M you sound
smart what I this is like random trivia
that I
know damn it's perf
stream stunning for this damn okay okay
it seems like you are correct ding ding
ding ding it's USA wo
USA California indeed California wow
damn I I I am amazed woman you're paying
attention good
job did they say this in the video I I
guess they did but it was so fast SLI by
it could it could have slipped by I was
so I was so
mesmerized okay well uh that one was too
easy for you let's go to the next
question and T question two which
sentence describes the quality of the
nuts on the package
oh uh I don't know you know this is like
I think Japanese people who put this
together I wonder I wonder if you know
they understand what they're doing but
number one amazing nuts
selection number two premium nut
selection this just one nut uh the other
one is nuts several nuts or number three
pure nut
selection oh no
amazing nut selection premium nut
selection pure nut ah okay I think I
have a feeling like what would sound
best is
it oh is it translated from Japanese
actually or does it say an English on
the packaging can I like try to squint
and see if it's there no it's not there
right now right now it's like they
censored it but I think they might have
English I don't actually if we're going
off they seemed really focus on the
quality of the nut yeah in the video mhm
and I mean I feel like premium would be
like the most closely associated word to
Quality would you please say the whole
answer the premium nut
selection that's your answer you're
locking it in no I'm scared maybe not um
wait wait wait if it's translated from
Japanese would it be PR prium or or
would it be something more like
amazing amazing
not
premium what makes but what makes what
makes it what makes it lot pure though
that's that's that's why I don't that's
why I don't think it's that one I think
it's often important to to emphasize
that something doesn't have anything
extra in it you
know like enhancers of FL or whatever I
don't know but you
know no foreign things in yeah the
chocolate yeah or the nut I this is
about the nut
um well go with I will walk in number
two nut I will lock in premium I feel
like premium is used a lot in Japanese
advertising so I'm going to say premium
okay M it is correct yay pre premium not
selection so mi mi uses only almond Kels
that exceed the strictest standards set
by not usada but
USDA us it's almost it's perfect Amo am
oh my God am usba is
that big
wow amazing okay we have another one how
many M almond chocolate boxes are
produced daily did they say 2,400 box
that's that's to little in the video
they I'm being I I think you can imagine
cuz like this is Japan and it's a
popular chocolate 24,000 or
240 240,000
boxes those I feel like it's going to be
like the craziest number it's always
going to be the highest number I think
so too so the others are too small I
think I under 100,000 is too little so
three mhm I would say so too let's let
me see yes the answer is correct ding D
ding H it's a huge amount indeed if they
were piled up apparently they would be
taller than Mount Fuji what the tallest
Mount piled up as in like one on top of
each other properly not just like thrown
on a like in a in a in like a scatter
pile yeah pile probably up right like
one on one and one on one one one one
it's like stacked most likely it must be
like that we could do the math to prove
it but it's okay we'll trust them we'll
trust them yeah we'll trust them but
that's crazy that's that is co wow okay
so many many boxes of just this specific
one no busy busy
Factory that's
insane that's insane how many they make
like
I even 100,000 seems like a lot oh 20
240,000 * 1 cm is already 2.4 Kil
kilom ah oh oh oh you don't speak this
uh meter language M but that's that's
already what are those where what's
what's a kilometer uh it's is that like
is that like a mile what's a centimeter
set is that like a
foot uh actually I don't I don't really
know how
to how the like equivalents are I think
they're quite different but oh 2.4 kilm
is 1.5 miles math is a lot easier 1 mile
is 1.8 km okay well who cares we don't
we got to move
on
so the next one from the uh famous Nut
Chocolate series that we want to talk
about is the super popular Macadamia Nut
Chocolate so you know this one to
wom I do let me move these away then
we'll watch the Macadamia tast you taste
them I don't think I don't think I've
even ever had macadamia
nuts themselves you know I can't I can't
tell you what they taste like aside from
they're nutty they're they're nutty like
all nuts usually are I if I think of
macademia I just think of chocolate
around them because that's I think the
only way I've really eating them but
macademia nuts are quite the like
expensive nut are
they compared to other nuts I don't know
no oh compared to others for sure like
compared to and cashew yes yeah yeah
yeah okay they say yes they also say yes
oh oh they're fatty
oh fatty nuts are fatty
okay they go well with white ah I do
think I see a lot of white chocolate
macademia chocolate stuff yeah okay okay
okay so let's watch it h let me stop by
bgm and
[Music]
go oh number
one number one
oh tell us a secret chapter one Miracle
nuts Miracle
nuts oh
really
oh who who
who they are excited
[Music]
about
they look
good oh to Australia
[Music]
oh because Ma's chocolates are the
highest quality macadamias that we see
anywhere in the world oh really we're
looking for exactly what the consumer
what the customer wants that very famous
soft crunch but the freshness and the
flavor of a major
Macadamia it's known throughout the
world as the best
Macadamia oh my God my cat are
zooming golden wait I feel like we
should keep track of that Kenya to
Australia to
[Music]
Japan those
are
I think the
[Music]
show yummy yummy yum
yummy
[Music]
small does it just look
small balance of texture and flavor
texture and
[Music]
flavor
love oh they're crushed uhuh they put
more than one in
[Music]
there I do shaver the distinctive taste
and
texture that's good to know wow golden
[Music]
ratio it looks
like
someone
oh opening an
oy
[Music]
the king of nuts is the most valuable in
the world it says there
macademia the packaging like we all know
Japanese packaging is like really pretty
all the time but like even though it's
like just like one of their normal
chocolate lineups right I mean a pop one
but still um compared to like overseas I
feel like the way they package even
normal chocolates is like how we package
like expensive pearlene chocolates here
right yes so that they don't move around
and you know everything stays put and
secure yeah mhm but it's it's very very
carefully packaged with love so I love I
love it so cute how do they make
chocolate so cute right they're cute
really cute nice to like share as well
with some people M so never mind did you
remember everything
M for sure for sure this time I remember
everything from that video could recite
it there was a lot going on again though
so we'll see we'll see going to be
careful I remembered I remembered things
okay okay okay I think uh here we go
yeah question number one
macadamia nuts are kind of rare right
how long do they take to grow from a
tiny plant to a fruit bearing tree did
they say this cover this no they
didn't well okay okay three years 5
years or 10 years
I I know most fruit trees take like 5 to
15 years o and Ma
macademia are like Treasures right or
shoot I forgot what they they're they're
it seems so I think they're so they must
be harder to gr it can't be that easy to
get a Academia if they're so special
right
yeah got to be lot of effort I'll say 10
years 10
years I would probably say so too
because they seem to make a big they
wouldn't ask this question right if
there's a big deal yeah yeah right
thinking thinking too hard I know I know
I know what they're trying to do they
can't trick me chat says like two or
three like a lot of three no Chad I know
okay wait wait no I'm not sure what
because okay but 10 years is a long time
and if they produce if it's the most
popular one and they can produce so
many then it says 10 years makes
sense okay but it's going from a wait
grow from a plant to a fruit bearing
tree not just like the so when it's
already a plant like not just a seed
thrown into the no yeah but I I would
say that seed to Tiny plant is probably
really short time like not that big of a
plant um yeah I I would also say 10
years M
honestly okay because I mean it doesn't
mean like oh the it's not like that the
trees cut down after 10 years and after
they get like you know the first fruit
or fruit the first nuts they're like all
right this trees is useless time to wait
another 10 years for
another that would be that would make
that nut really really a lot more
expensive than it already might be so
hopefully it's not the cze not the C 10
okay yes it's correct M ding ding
ding yeah it certainly is a precious
knot that takes a lot of time to grow
but honestly I feel like 10 years is
reasonable for a tree to grow into
something that works fruit to start
being I think 10 years is makes sense
it's like in the middle of the yeah I
think I don't know that's
fun so you guys a lot of you guys were
wrong but now you know now you know
we're learning a lot of stuff here we
learn next question special 10
what is the manufacturing method used by
Mii that gently warms the macadamia nuts
to the core and locks the flavor and
sweetness inside nuts number one golden
this was in the video this was in the
tradition like Ro I liked how she said
traditional and she said traditional
multiple times traditional uhhuh she was
very sure about it they're traditional
okay and how they roast
are you sure wasn't there something
about Golden
too wasn't that just how they look huh
okay when you crack them open oh you
don't want trying to trick me trying to
trick me you okay what wait regend what
what does that mean is that I think it's
supposed to be Legend legendary
roast yeah how I roasted uh Ren that was
a legendary roast okay um so
yeah you you might be correct M I guess
you're correct this one this one is like
the only one I spin from of the video I
swear okay okay yeah it's traditional
roast the secret of the nuts delicious
taste is the traditional method of slow
cooking in low temperature oil which
requires a lot of time and effort yeah
yeah yeah yeah but Japan knows how to
yeah they just know they just get it
okay good job so far you answered
everything
correctly does that mean I
passed there's another one
okay here where is the factory with this
large chocolate sign in Japan where the
process of combining macadamias and
chocolate takes place which that's cool
it's like it looks like a chocolate bar
Tokyo Osaka or
hok I don't
know I I don't think it's in Tok because
I feel like I would have heard about it
and I've only been to
Tokyo there's many things you probably
didn't see in Tokyo put a giant
chocolate
bar GI chocolate bar I'm going to go Hol
I didn't see it before either like IRL
you going going to go for
Hokkaido I feel like I would have heard
about it being in Tokyo I don't think I
would have seen it but I don't I I just
want to go Hokkaido because there's
certainly in Hokkaido for a big Factory
and H may also be famous for a lot of
things like maybe milk that they also
want to use in their production but
you're wrong mum you couldn't be
wronger wait so I
failed no get one you you're out no I I
maybe I'll kick out your a just a part
one small
okay okay can you do it after the stream
because yeah you have to cut it
off okay all right for you it grows back
in like 5 seconds but if you want me to
cut this one off I'll do it m okay so
it's Osaka actually Osaka number two you
know Osaka Osaka yeah I've never been
though you should go Osaka is really
great I love Osaka I lived there before
I want to go I've never gone outside
Tokyo let's go next time so the size of
the original signboard is equivalent to
about
380,000 pieces of the classic mag milk
chocolate and it was registered in the
Guinness World Records in
2011 it's a record record for for what
for for largest chocolate thing that
thing that looks like a chocolate bar
maybe yeah H 380,000
chocolate bar sculpture yes and inside
here they are doing all the
magic Wow Wow Shashi as uh
our would
say okay okay okay okay so that was all
the questions good job me wow I almost
kind of it's okay how could you know I
don't think they mentioned this in the
video
so okay did they I learned that's all
that matters I learned something and
maybe now I don't know if people
actually go there like for sightseeing
but it seems like something people would
want to see in person so maybe let's
meet at the giant chocolate bar exactly
you can go there it's a it's a a new
tourist goal destination for us I need
to see it too okay then next up um you
know so far we have looked at the Almond
chocolates and the Macadamia chocolates
in detail and in addition to these two
products there's of course more like um
the almond chocolate with extra
cocoa and the hazelnut chocolate the
pistachio chocolate Etc so this time we
have actually a special guest who tasted
all of these and they're telling us what
they think about it yeah mhm we are
going to live by curiously
through welcome welcome she is here in
spirit thank you she she looks like she
could be relate it with you she has the
same hair color I know and she has
an oh you got to do a DNA
test uh wait
[Music]
yes just for fun just for fun like it's
even like the same kind of tone of like
beige hair it's and even our highlights
look at that yeah the same kind of
highlights oh my God mama mama mama
mamaaa okay so uh first she's giving us
an impression of the Magi almond
chocolate would you like to read her her
you know her comment all
right the crunchy and fragrant almond
texture and the moderately sweet
chocolate that envelops it are the
perfect match it's the classic flavor
that I love oh that sounds like it's her
favorite maybe you
think yeah okay that's the the one that
we saw in the beginning and I see now it
does say like in Katakana but in English
premi H the the not selection okay I see
I see she knows she knows written in
English because that makes it like even
more legit you know trust me okay then
we have the next one that we also heard
about please
read Macadamia the king of nuts oh my
gosh she knows so much king of nuts the
crunchy texture that gently crumbles
will make you addicted chocolate also
has a sweeter and gentler taste than
amazy almond chocolate oh can you can
you confirm this
m is it sweeter and gent I think it is
sweeter I I I'm not as good with words
or understanding so I don't know if gent
gentler gentler gentle I I I can't
remember but I think it is sweeter but I
think that's also part of because of
macadamia I think Macadamia is sweeter
oh by the way here on the mark it
says traditional roast on the know oh
yes
yes just to make sure everybody knows mm
yes yes yes a good a good uh nut a king
the king of the nuts who's the queen
king of nuts who's the queen do we have
a queen the queen queen of
nut she must
be okay then we have
the M almond chocolate C caca please
read this one
too c means um c means like like
smelling uh uh what's a good word of
smell scent scent scenting oh like
strong like more pungent or stronger
smell oh okay stronger me okay scent
scent okay okay I see I
see the moment I put it in my mouth the
taste of
caca spreads through my mouth the Mellow
Taste of chocolate and the texture of
almonds you'll feel rewarded by enjoying
both the aroma and taste you'll feel re
rewarded
wow who she has a we with words she
really does yeah she does she's good
with words oh mellow Taste of chocolate
mellow mellow oh because it's like like
more like a a dark chocolate right m m
do you like dark chocolate I love dark
chocolate really mhm I think I like it I
like it more than milk chocolate it
really okay I'll remember that cuz I'm
more of a milk choc chocolate kind of
person I love both but like that
chocolate you got me before that was
good chocolate I think that was more
milk milk chocolate yeah it was good it
was very good okay
k
kak sorry this joke comes from somewhere
else I just really like saying it in a
in a crow Crow kind of way Raven wayak I
like so similar to Kaka yeah yeah
exactly okay next one is the hazelnut
chocolate wow please this is one I
haven't tried before to know I'd like to
know
mysterious texture oh mysterious texture
what can I say it's crunchy and every
time I bite into it I sense its Aroma it
is Pleasant the round chocolate shape is
adorable it is why are round things so
cute what is the science behind it why
so cute by the way on the on on this
seal it says uh that it's like the one
of the world's biggest free nuts biggest
as in like how like how how to say how
how how they're like uh most popular or
whatever widespread yeah widespread yeah
yeah yeah ha you know and since they're
from from uh turkey they use nuts from
Turkey
oh I interesting so it's like nuts all
they all have like a different kind of
region where you would want to get the
best nuts from and in this case it's
turkey hey did it say something here
here it says Ah premium nut selection
okay okay but oh it says the the cacao
is from
Ecuador Naro interesting okay globo and
this also with milk chocolate as you can
probably tell cute need to try this one
too we need to try all of them shiny and
cute yes we we do M and then next one
this one I didn't eat before but I'm
really curious about cuz I love
pistachios I really wanted this one cuz
that's they had sub around the Box oh
yeah this one has a sub sampai oh it's
it's too shy it's it's fate we have to
get it mm so please read let's see small
grains that are easy to eat and have a
gentle texture the chocolate had a
slight Touch of salt which matched well
with the rich flavor of the pistachios
the match was very delicious oo I can
imagine I love
pistachos yeah so this one says oh hey
this one says it's the nut
Queen this is the nut Queen oh we found
the nut Queen bow to your queen oh my
goshow wow I can see I can see how it
would be the nut Queen like pistachos
seem like
somewhat maybe on the feminine side I
don't know like compared to the
macademia I don't know pistachio oh no
it was Ammons Ammons was the King right
no Academia we're the king really okay
okay okay okay they're the King and King
of the nuts King of the nuts yeah
pistaches are so addicting you can't
just eat one and also I love opening
them up you know oh really mhm I I like
opening them up if they're slightly
opened already but when they're closed I
get really mad yeah Dan it's difficult D
it's like almost impossible I have weak
fingernails they're going to oh by the
way these ones are also from California
the nuts yeah yeah more California nuts
California no how to grow nuts H is did
you just make that up no it's like a
based on California knows how to party
you know
oh they know how to make nuts yeah know
how to make nuts
California okay then California get now
okay
oh uh okay let's let's read this
[Laughter]
one I would be happy if the image of the
taste reaches the two of you and the
viewers
she and move Son please do your best in
streaming thank you thank you um it it
happens when my I think even on the no
this is just like an auto auto
translation thing every time my name get
Auto translated yeah key how does key
become
chei maybe maybe cuz the name like
exists in this writing in in in in Italy
for example I
think okay okay that makes wor that
makes wor yeah yeah I'm Italian B
no okay and I have uh um one more slide
but uh yeah so thank you thank you so
much uh Nan for teaching us about the
other chocol that we may have not tried
yet we're very curious right about
giving the ones that we haven't tried a
try I am curious thank
you have a chat about our history and
past so we can figure some stuff out oh
yeah yeah it's important
figure it out maybe in private later on
if you meet again at some point have you
met her I haven't met no I haven't met
her yet me neither I think I think time
to go oh wait have I wait I maybe I I
think I
did I'm sure uh moving on moving
on H so next up after we have you know
looked at everything in detail now we
want to rank what we want you guys to
try when you go to Japan and find the
chocolates in the supermarket or in the
convenience store and also what we want
to you know try again like what we most
recommend for you guys and us and um let
us know guys also if you have ever eaten
of the any of these before just in case
um and and and yeah would be interesting
to hear your opinions so mumay what
would be like your
number one
recommendation all right tearless time
yeah or should we start from the bottom
like the bottom oh from third from third
I I have I I I would personally put the
hazelnuts one there because I haven't
tried it before and and it's it's I'm
curious about it but not as curious as
the others yeah I'm also I'm curious
about the Hazel especially cuz it's
round and cute yeah true yes should run
things congratulations hazelnuts you are
in in number free placement out of 5
million chocolates that made you
producing that's pretty good that's
pretty good yeah good nut it l it
literally has nut in the name so it must
be a good nut mhm kind of logic but the
others actually you know
stach nut I know they come second they
come in the second word yeah
what what does that tell you well well
what's your number two
M my number two recommendation would be
the
macademia what would be your number one
my number one would be the classic
almond okay okay
but you're forgetting one that I want to
put there oh you go ahead you I I
thought this I I I misunderstood I
thought this was just mine what what's
yeah no I just I just I think you you
should remember this cuz because of
subai pistachi I want to try the
pistachio you're you're sorry I was just
thinking of the ones I've tried already
pistachio yeah I would put this on
number
two because I love pistachos and and and
it's got to be
there and then I just I would just say
we put makadamia and almond both oh yes
yes this makes this makes absolute sense
here we go it's almost as if I like
decided it beforehand
oh oh my gosh it's like that I didn't
realize no this is good this is the
perfect outcome I think in my opinion no
this is actually this is even better I
didn't realize I didn't fully understand
that we can have two in the number one
we can have anything we want M anything
we want I understand now this
no this is true this is true I recommend
cuz I Macadamia is so good but then
almonds like also so good but so classic
and pistachio I just I haven't tried I
really want to try and then Haz on I
haven't tried and I really want to try
yeah also because they said the
pistachio one is like a little bit salty
like I don't know if I normally ever
consume like chocolate that's a little
bit salty but I'm interested cuz
pistachos oh is it like an American
thing like sea saltt chocolate like sea
salt caramel chocolate
ah I have mixed feelings about it it's
it's still a little too much salt
usually for that might be too much
yeah a sea salt chocolate oh interesting
it's giant giant CH or
salt giant little like giant like giant
grain of salt at least to me at least to
me it's it's a big grain B big green
interesting yeah not so much my thing
but I feel like this is like this would
probably be like um a an amount of
saltiness that is like totally mixing
well with the sweetness and works well
together I would I would assume I would
imagine okay it works it works so that's
our ranking
yay congratulations ma chocolate for
making our ranking top
[Music]
threee everything is peaceful is fine
fine me chocolate yeah now actually um I
had a little idea to make us draw our
own ideal or like some chocolate that we
want ma to
produce so let's see what kind of
chocolate we came up within um 15
minutes and let's see if M might want to
produce
them do you want to start or should
I you start you start M basic no no
mine's pretty
basic so I there's so many kind of
chocolates I'm I'm I eat so much
chocolate I'm like it's it's actually
concerning how much chocolate I consumed
in my whole life
um and so I I couldn't it's hard to make
up my mind for something I would want
them to create and I I saw they created
something similar to what I came up with
but not quite so oh uh wait
wait what oop where where is this where
is this a here get out of
here
chocolate so my idea is a crunchy cream
cookie um that makes your dreams come
true it should be like the the texture
of the cookie is really important but I
don't know how to explain it it should
be really like M really crunchy not soft
really crunchy not like a yeah do you
have you tried graham crackers I don't
know are graham crackers a thing outside
of America gr maybe something like that
yeah that could work that's what this
kind of looks like to me but for me I
don't only want one layer of some cream
inside I want two layers I feel like the
balance uh when having like a layer of
like a Milky cream in there makes
everything so smooth and refreshing and
not too heavy tasting so I would put a
layer of milk cream and then milk
chocolate or uh as a second version yeah
raspberry chocolate as a second
layer yes the raspberry sounds ooh but
they shouldn't be like too liquid it
should be pretty solid um but like still
creamy I'm sure Mai would you know make
this perfect and figure out what's
what's the best texture to get it all
the perfect way and we can have other
variations like with dark chocolate
instead of mil chocolate or strawberry
instead of raspberry maybe even caramel
and this and that you know you know and
of course it made you branding on top to
make it look like it belongs to Mii it
looks extra cute I like the the style
like it's kind of like not it's kind of
like a flower in a way but not just the
you know change the shape it doesn't
have to be this shape though no it's so
cute like this that's what I mean thank
you and Mii cute Mii makes cute
chocolate yeah they can do it they can
make it even cuter than this and I was
thinking maybe you could even coat the
top partially or completely with a layer
of milk chocolate but you know you know
we can go from here you can hit me up U
miie and we can talk about it you know
experiment here and there I was also
thinking maybe you can get rid of the
Magi logo and then in the middle just
have a hole so you can see the cream cuz
that reminds me of certain Christmas
cookies in I know what you're talking
about I know cookies like the F inside M
you can see through it's like wow cute
so yeah you know many ideas um doo
doo um it's just because I really like
um like uh I like uh cookie chocolates
you know I love them oh I I love cookie
chocolate too yeah okay and then is the
the yours is is special I would more
more interesting than mine I don't think
so I
just
[Music]
ta cute so kind of like round and and
like a like a
PR similar to the like hazelnut like
that level of roundness but maybe you
know uh but yes I said I like an owl
like a barn owl so you don't have to
worry you know about the toughs breaking
apart so just round ow chocolate
chocolate round owl and then the the
image above is supposed to be like the
profile from the side I guess it doesn't
actually matter if it's the it's a
circle anyways um so I would have on the
inside I don't know why I said white I
meant to say like white CH white
chocolate or something creamy yeah
creamy creamy or it could be it could be
like solid like yogurt oh I don't know
you have have you had like yogurt
chocolates yes I was say maybe something
like that and then I don't know how
realistic it is to have a really tiny
Berry like that I think cranberries
would even be too big but something
representing a berry inside like the ber
cream or it could even have a liquid
core liquid Berry uh core you oh yeah
yeah that' be kind of is that okay to
have like on something that looks like
an owl's
head that would be great cuz if you bite
only into half of the owl then you have
the liquid the red liquid coming out
like it's blood
yes exactly okay I'm glad you're on the
same page as me okay we love that we
love that kind of stuff
right
Gres that's actually genius but it looks
so cute like I can totally imagine like
this like being made into a proper
pearline I wonder how hard it would be
little tiny round round cute can try it
we can try it for
Valentine's oh my gosh I I feel like
they turned out so they would turn out
so cursed yeah yeah this is probably not
the first chocolate you should try
creating you should start with something
more simple but it is ambitious and I
like the idea very much very cute very
aesthetic thank you definitely something
that would speak to a lot of um
chocolate lovers imagine like a bunch in
your hand at once looking at you looking
up at you before you eat them you you
would make them like pretty small maybe
like the hazelnut chocolates from Mai
yeah I think so you're cute cute small
small BBS you can have so many
mhm and and they would be like more on
like on the softer side not like any
nothing crunchy in here right I don't
think so I don't think so okay nice
something's a little a little crunch is
good I don't know leave it to the
experts leave it to the experts
yeah nice nice nice nice I like these
ideas so maybe May son you can uh you
can hit us up uh if you want have have
to copyright you know not we won't ask
for much
yeah just like
90% not just just 90% just
90 okay perfect well but I'll I'll I
guess I'll show for the ending I'll show
um this our ranking again
T So
H today we have studied nut based
chocolates and I hope I hope you guys
enjoyed it hope you guys learned and got
curious about the major chocolates and
so oh yeah that's like hopefully
everything covered and uh if you guys go
to Japan swing by the convenient store
and find one of these they're like easy
to find ma covers sure I I I honestly
have seen them in the grocery store I
think my brain just doesn't fully
process but when I'm in Japan I'm like
yes Mai but I don't need I need to buy
chocolate more at home yeah I never buy
chocolate CH cuz I'm always like
American chocolate just isn't very
appealing to me but Mai I can agree on
that American
child not to like really be like Oh I'm
suddenly craving a Milky Way or
something no no but no no
Mii I I I'm dead serious I'm dead
serious I choose Ma I CH okay all right
America you
lose lose guys does know what your
thoughts on the chocolates and on the
stream or maybe some chocolates you have
eaten before are and which ones you want
to try the hashtag is m
h and
uh yeah thank you thank you miie for
sponsoring thank you M for sponsoring
thank you thank you it's an honor it's
an honor is I get to talk about
chocolate
chocolate chocolate is is is I one
chocolate a day keeps the depression
away you
know trust me trust me so I trust thank
you guys thank you M for helping me out
with this thank you for being so
organized this is far more organized
than me no
problem no problem it's it's it's U the
job of a leader you know mhm yes number
one saleswoman I am I'm two
oh let's see let's see how the sales
will go up after this m so do you
remember my
greeting the greeting or ending my
ending yeah my ending oh I Fe yes and in
German we
say
happy thank you for
watching thank you eat chocolate every
day bye by
thank
you bye
bye
[Music]
byebye
for