[Music]
you
do
[Music]
you
do
[Music]
so
you
[Music]
do
hello
the legend of
takanashi
kiara's awakening
starts today sorry for the word
how are you guys good morning
[Music]
uh
i need oops i need a logo
links awakening
switch logo okay
me i'm still a bit tired
and such
but
generally i'm okay
thank you for asking i had a a quick
speed breakfast
um
of uh croissant with nutella but now i'm
running out of nutella
which is a
a threatening
state of life to be in no nutella
it's like
holy
like what's gonna happen is such an
uncertain moment in your life
well
terrible terrible i don't wish any of
that upon you guys
yeah it's a tough time that we live in
um
yeah tough only i see only a little bit
left in there and you know seeing it
fading away in front of my eyes hurts
even more
than having it being eaten away by
somebody else maybe
because i'm the one i'm the one doing
the damage i i know it's me
it's me
my biggest enemy is myself
anyway
[Laughter]
hello
yeah the sad jar of an empty nutella do
you also do you guys also keep like
do you also keep empty jars of nutella
like that that are like pretty much
empty and you just move on to the next
one but you still keep the old one for
whatever reason
because i mean for me the reason is
probably i'm too lazy to get rid of it
but
yes
no yes
there's a bunch of yeses let's go
just a couple okay yeah i mean also not
too many i just i just have one
one standing there
meow i heard a whimpering meow from
chunkers what is it i already gave you
the snack i already gave you the snack
stick the stick snack
meow
oh
i
oh man
uh
let's do this new
new adventure
took the weight desktop audio are you on
okay good let's go
yeah i had to stop this because there
was an opening and i think i wanted to
see this with you
[Music]
just like inna's house in minecraft
oh it's it's it's a wind waker
it's wind waker
my favorite game
my favorite zelda game
oh that's so cute though
the style is so adorable i already love
it i already love it
no tacti
[Music]
put your hands up in the air let's go
and that really looks like a yoshi egg
[Music]
kiana's neglected egg excuse me
why is it pink though was it pink got it
was it not a different color in the in
the cover
[Music]
i didn't do my stretches
oh oh i didn't press oh what is this oh
this is just opening again right okay
sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
louise egg oh
maybe it's louise egg yeah
but
be aware
be wary of the hawks there are i think
very protective of their eggs
exciting oh my god so this is um
uh the second zelda game that we are
playing on my channel
and this one is the first one after our
sky awards sword adventure
wow
interesting
remix
um
yeah and
we're playing the remake obviously
and uh
for people who don't know my favorite
one is wind waker but i have never fully
played windbreaker i just played it when
i was like younger with my brother
but i think that's the one i enjoyed the
most
the one where you slam dana into a dark
beast exactly you remember
yeah skyward sword all in all i i did
enjoy skyward sword it was very
frustrating with the motion control a
lot of times
but looking back on it now i i do still
have some fond memories i think
um
sky water soda no
that was a tough one but i i know that
this one will be easier it will also be
shorter so i expect three to four
um
episodes depending on the length
uh and my mood
and um
i think uh i've heard that you know this
one is more classic because i mean i've
seen a certain fairy playlist as well
but um
uh i know that it's like it has the
typical
you know the typical look to it just
remade into uh a more modern
graphic
but yes with the typical dungeons the
old ones and
um and and funny new bosses it shouldn't
be too difficult as far as i know
[Music]
how
link is not okay
total weight
i
let me tap something in i'm always
worried that
that's with the switch is gonna
you know
how it's me no no okay no suggestions
but before like we had success
suggestions
wait should we do link yeah
nevermind nevermind look at this look at
this oh there we go
[Music]
[Laughter]
the controls are the controls i played
playstation yesterday
what's
uh okay okay okay okay
no that was not even because of the
playstation controls
[Music]
excited
sounds okay let's go let me drink some
tea i got some tea
[Music]
oh okay thank you
thank you
is that your first super chat in the new
year or did i miss something happy new
year though
[Music]
i thought you'd never wake up you were
tossing and turning
she has orange hair guys
wha what zelda
no my name is marine you must still be
feeling a little woozy
you are on koholind island
well you know you got a
thick ass nose you look like
i don't know you remind me of someone
nice nose though it's so cute actually
it's pretty cute nose i want to touch it
can i squeeze it
[Music]
oh well lincoln i finally snapped out of
it name's tarden hope you're feeling
better here we go with the voices again
here we go
what how did i know your name you think
it's weird huh
well i saw it on back on the shield
i wrote my name on that okay
this animal crossing is awesome
[Music]
should i bring out my shield and my
sword as well
[Music]
chocolate
it's been a while it's been quite a lot
i usually don't take it out
but today's the day
[Music]
nope nope nope i
which one was it
no that's not it
guess it was this one
[Music]
the shield is kind of low so oh oh and
the sword yeah i did i forgot to
mention that this happens oopsie
it doesn't work so well
[Music]
uh but
nice sword thank you
thank you i need my shield my shield
yeah i'm protected
[Music]
remove that but i like this hat i don't
know i feel like because we're like on
an island i guess and it's like kind of
tropical i felt like this
this hat would work well but
where did i have wait i want to bring
back my zelda hat totally oh where did i
where did i save my zelda hat
[Music]
where
my nose is running again
oops does someone know where or my zelda
hat
is oh
i made one myself and i also received
one before
did you wash it
a warrior doesn't wash their hats
what do you think we are
supermodels or what we go out to war we
don't have time to wash our shitty
clothes
and uh besides
the more blood and the more sweat on it
the better
because it proves on how many battles we
wear and how many how many lands we've
conquered
uh-huh
[Music]
yes i'm trying to look for my resources
right now uh oh
remember that i have a kaze no i have
the
i have the this one
not quite the right game for that yet
but i do want to one day play a
windbreaker on this channel as well
i found my own hat i found my my
self-made hat at least
[Laughter]
[Music]
well for today maybe this will do
until i find the other one
yeah
i don't know where the other one is
shitty hat man
i want this city hat but it's green it's
green i like the green it's so shitty
it's so shitty
hey let's go
let's promise as always i just move way
too much
where will i be looking at most of the
time probably here
[Music]
somewhere here okay okay mcconnell hand
is gonna
maybe bigger
[Applause]
[Music]
okay i'll i'll leave it here
[Laughter]
perfect perfect oh
what is this
is this a stand for something it says
piranha plant
huh
okay
[Music]
oh this looks heavier than heavy and
your current strength won't cut it
linky are you weak ass
link
oh what are you doing
that's your chest oh this is where you
two live where'd you learn to do such a
thing
i don't know i mean in every other game
i like to check out everybody's things
i'm sorry
noodle arms excuse me
[Music]
i can lift you huh oh let's go on an
adventure together
oh my god yeah i remember there's like
all kinds of weird elements uh in this
remake
[Music]
it already looks so cute can't be let's
go you look so plump and cute
[Music]
oh my god does it actually do me damage
if i get too close
she can protect me can i hold the fox
too
no no
no i just killed
[Music]
okay
okay oh wait where do we go
where do we go
[Music]
what does the fox say
hello grandma
[Music]
grandma yahoo
it's almost jungle
what
[Music]
i'm good i think what is there a
telephone on top of this tree
come with me simpkin we're going to the
beach um where's the beach is it left
out
there's there's water here
stop playing with the ball here it's
dangerous
in some way oh i feel like this is not
oh dear
there's enemies
no this is probably not it
probably not it
don't hit my thinking with that
don't pull that off
this is kind of weird of the game to
start it off like that where i have no
idea where to go or did they tell me
and i already forgot
[Music]
it was the right way really
without the sword they want me to go
there
[Music]
okay jim can you come with me
[Laughter]
this is the legend of kiwawa
chimkin's awakening oh they're not
attacking me
[Music]
oh here we go
hold on both shores wait is the chicken
ever gonna find its way back though
excuse me ow
well if only i could hold my shield
game over coming soon guys
what the okay i need to let you go
now
because this is scary oh
[Music]
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
shield
my
sword oh
there are signs where are the signs oh
got gunman
that looks like it looks like uh
his friend
oh dudes oh you are the lad who owns
this soccer ball
no i understand why the monsters are
starting to act oh my ho ho ho let's
leave courageous lad has come to work to
win fish
it is said that you cannot leave the
island unless you wake the wind for heat
[Music]
okay
i will wait for you there
okay see ya wait where where where did
you say mysterious forest
found my sword it must be yours because
it has your name engraved on it uh-huh
smart
[Music]
north north okay
you can swing it with b to attack any
enemies in your path
oh you wanna fight you wanna fight you
wanna fight
[Music]
i think someone said me that the way i
said me
told me that the way i play what is this
that the way i play games you know
panicking and stuff will be very handy
and i think i already know what you mean
because
like
the way he fights
i i think i understand
[Music]
so we must uh save the chimpkin
don't kill the chicken that was close
that was close come with me
[Music]
i would leave you here alone huh no no
no
[Music]
no way
i'll protect you
until the better end
oh god
[Music]
oh it's a dangerous mission you know can
i eat those apples
hello brought your friend back i needed
him for some emotional support you know
heart oh
[Music]
isn't this pokemon music
is this not pokemon music
[Music]
am i going crazy
i guess not
i know i felt like i heard this in
pokemon before
nope this is just zelda okay
give me those
rubies rupees rupees rubies
you found a secret seashell but what do
you do with it listen listen listen hey
listen
okay so you gotta clean up you know
this is so much easier than an animal
crossing oh my god it takes so much less
time can you give the characters an
animal crossing a sword please
for
eating
the
uh
that would make things so much faster
and efficient
we need swords for animal crossing
villagers
[Music]
and we earned quite a bit of money from
that
it does sound perfect for pokemon city
now or like a pokemon center maybe
[Music]
drinking tea
okay okay
oh my god what is twitter burp
doing here
haven't talked to you in a while for the
boob
is that your friend are you friends with
him then you are my enemy marine
hi tiny went to the horse to look for
toadstools but i'd rather sing
you're kind of like blooming
[Music]
listen to this it's called the palada of
the wind fish
[Music]
you know what's annoying here though the
sound of this stupid blue bird over
there
[Music]
wow hitting those notes let's go go
nice are you just going to continue
saying the same thing over and over now
should i stop you
it was beautiful
oh oh you're you are i have i have uh
started an uh eternal singing contest
for you i'm so sorry
you're in an eternal loop there now
it's like a death loop but at least you
don't die hopefully
good luck with that someday you're
you're gonna lose your voice if you
continue singing forever and ever
stop regarding the forest this is not
exactly north but i guess it's north of
the city this is where i'm supposed to
go
no it's probably not really considered
north
it's east
but i went up first
and there is no more
oh unless
[Music]
no
northwest
i want to run
i'm here perhaps
[Music]
oh
we'll talk to you later buddy
left left i guess the house is so cute
sorry they look so fluffy when if we
throw them in here i'm sure i'm not the
first one to dry
but don't worry don't worry i'm not
going to do it i'm not going to do it
i'm not going to do it
i have to hold back
[Music]
you again hello hold
on on your quest to the wicked dreamer
welcome home to the mysterious foreign
[Music]
ireland
i'm afraid you might find it it's really
difficult to leave the island while the
winter snaps
what have you ever visited through tail
cave which is the hoof of the village
oh there was the key you'll find in this
four
the wind fish is watching
okay okay okay anna
kiana is the key
okay
no problem
oh dear
okay no problem see i i i've seen some
but uh not only in the forest fairy but
someone else as well i've seen people
play this game and it it looked fairly
simple
combat wise oh
oh
wait wait wait wait wait
okay
no it's not so difficult
oh wait i can hold my shield and attack
okay okay that's that's good to know
no but it really is simple um
from what i've seen i mean the enemies
are
not very strong
what is this
we wear the floors with cracks don't get
too comfortable on them no problem
so i think oh
didn't i just cut this grass did it
already grow back holy
ah
my nose is very sensitive to
that
so cute
everything is so cute even the leaves of
these plants
everything is adorable here
come on
[Music]
and he reset er now i have to cut
everything again
wait what do you mean i'm going to be
lost because of you oh there's a hole
here
hey what happened what the happened
[Music]
why can't i move on now
oh my god
first fairy
[Music]
you've still got plenty of pep come see
me when you feel like you can't go on
ah i can hear myself at your uh spring
okay okay okay
[Music]
sorry i can't stop cutting those stupid
grass
oh i got a shield
oh okay okay i see it
hey
i understand completely
a little come over here come over
here
so cute it shouldn't be allowed man
so adorable i'm i'm not in japan no no
no no i'm not in japan
oh
can i jump will he jump over the hole
i'm too scared to try it out does he
jump automatically over holes like that
oh
okay no problem
corner the enemy and then kill him
yeah
oh heartbeats wait i'm out of the forest
was i supposed to get out of the forest
am i not looking for a key in the forest
what if i go in here
is
supposed to go in here
no i was supposed to ah exit
oh okay okay okay okay
you guys already played the remake or
did you all play the og only
nice look at me doing combat so far
pretty good huh
i mean it's not difficult oh gee only
both
played the original both
grew up with the og oh a lot of og
players yeah
did you not feel like playing the new
one the remake
oh i know these buddies
uh
[Music]
can't go here can't go there
boomer is in the chat
don't call
because you're also calling me boom i
mean i didn't exactly grow up with this
one but what
wait was i really supposed to go this
way
i can't do much here
[Music]
it's fire
that place looks safe um
no
[Music]
a witch and casper
so cute it actually looks like a hamster
not a mouse
no not a hamster but like what do you
call them i don't know it looks like a
mix
oh i can't destroy them what
[Music]
a guinea pig
chinchilla yeah that's what yeah that's
a chinchilla no that's what i was
thinking of i cannot talk to you
from here okay
tyler and truffle a toaster mix makes
powder up for tricks
she wants toadstools what are toadstools
okay so this is kind of a dead end who
said i was gonna i needed to come here
who said that this is a dead end
[Music]
oh here we go
maybe
maybe burn something with his fire
[Laughter]
or is there one specific hole that leads
to
somewhere go back enter the log and walk
along
[Music]
you lied to me i don't need to go here
i must find a tanooki first ah oh will
he give me a feather
jump over things
okay
a guardian acorn oh not as good as corn
but it's acorn
it will reduce the damage you take by
health
oh oh i can't it will oh oh activate
itself oh i see it now
how long
i don't need that though because
what's going on right now what's going
on right now i'm on fire
die
i'm gonna find the tanuki and kill him
holy
move out of the way
where is that tanooki
tell me i i bet you know where he is
where is he
i'm on a mission need to destroy him he
brought me here
i will find him ah he's not here
hey when did i say i wasn't gonna swear
as much oh there you are a little
wait a second did i just reset the
forest
by going
in here and outside a few times
well i found you
you're going to be lost thanks to me
okay
okay okay
so i should not leave okay
oh i hear it i hear him
must be down here oh my god i'm already
rich man
okay so far i'm doing way better in
combat than i did in skyward
i hear you
thank you
he says the same thing
hey is this really my mission
what
i need a mushroom where the hell do i
get a mushroom from
from the forest
or from somewhere else
to get into the log
that looks so dangerous though okay
you're gonna tell me that every time oh
oh yeah right because oh well with
this speed
i'm going in
okay
okay okay
uh
i can't get to the chest anyway right
because i probably need something to
make it go boom
okay
well now i can move him
shut the lid
i want the heart piece
i want a heart piece
no
no i can't can i look at it
i don't think i can
i messed it up you think i could
actually make it
is this reset
can't get it yet right
i don't think i can you know
the chest probably neither but okay so
i'm out on the other side of
this i hope voice is the same no there
it is there's the mushroom
find me
[Music]
as you hold it over your head a mellow
aroma flows into your nostrils i don't
like it because i don't like mushrooms
so i'm supposed to give this to uh
[Music]
our little friend
you can get the chest okay we'll try on
the way back then
if we can make it
out here
[Laughter]
yeah i remember the witch now
as well but i i still gotta go back this
way right
i thought i was lost again for a moment
oh okay okay
no
i really can't get there can i
can i can i can
no
yep
okay
[Laughter]
first puzzle
uh
oh i can break them like that yo
can i only open a chest from one side
no no i have to run around over the left
yep
please don't break please don't break up
come here come here before you hit me
again
okay
open
oh whoa purple
50 rupees let's go
sorry i need my i need to drink my tea
it's already getting uh lukewarm
okay slowly slowly carefully
i wouldn't it
i put it can i save by the way
can i save any time
[Music]
zero it says zero deaths guys yo
unbelievable what the happened what
the happened
what are you doing
okay my health is back where was uh
where was that witch
where is that one i think up here
oh no you're something else
i need to go to the witch who how how
was i supposed to figure that out
without you guys
i'm not that smart
[Music]
it can be maybe sometimes
so
uh
basic logical think
[Laughter]
you're roasting me huh ah
i thought it would yeah i know she says
toadstool but i thought she'd look for
later for later mission or something or
i thought it was like a collector's
thing where uh like in skyward sword
where you bring them a lot of
things and then
they give you like uh heart pieces
at a certain amount of time
but
okay there's a sleepy tongs
all right we'll mix it up something in
the tuffy we will
now
well that your mouse wants a bite of
that too
it's already it is take care and there's
not much there oh
why not try a bit in my heart
i don't know what it does you got some
magic powder open the sub screen of plus
and then set it to either x or y
[Music]
uh uh how many times can you use one of
those
okay so it's on y now
what does it what does it even do
what does it even do
use it on her torch outside
outside the porch outside
are the trees a torch
no
what
ah this one
ah
what
use it on the animus and see what
happens if you're out go to the forest
pick some toadstools make you more oh
come back without toadstool and you may
have to pay a price for my leftovers
what
okay
ah ah okay okay i mean i can also buy it
without getting a toaster no no
that is uh
a bit drastic and and brutal to kill the
tanuki on by burning him alive but
if that's what the game wants
oh
[Music]
who am i to you know
say we can't do that
you
yeah
you're amazing
[Music]
cut me
no not with you
now with your shield
[Music]
well the shield does not work on my back
we uh know that now
who wants uh
who wants who wants fried tanooki
yakugaku
what the is going on
[Music]
i guess you sniffed too many
i see
that the last thing i can remember was
breaking into a big juicy toadstool then
i had to talk during this dream i was a
recruit
oh it sounds strange but it sure was fun
uh-huh you should go home friend
i'm gonna talk it out i think i better
set a spell before i head home
did you set a spell
should i burn you
with my
powder
yeah he looks like a mario yeah i guess
so
wait is that this game has a lot of
references right
why did i not open this before oh my
god the tail key this is what i was
actually looking for now you can open
the tail cave gate wait where was the
tail cave uh
yeah where was that
[Music]
oh tank the crane and go to the tail
okay
which rehab the instrument that is
hidden there goes
[Music]
the beach
you guys are making this very easy for
me
it goes up it goes out you better get
home soon your daughter
is worried about you is that it's his
daughter right
is it
is mine and his daughter
yeah
i hope so
okay so you said at the beach
let's go to the beach beach
oh my god
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i
did that by accident
why the colors of the apples different
now
[Music]
curious
i'm not trying to kill you
believe me i don't even know where where
i need to go
is it here is that a dungeon
hey you can shoot through
[Music]
these crabs are so cute
oh yeah right what did you guys think of
kanto's new kimonos banana trees bananas
i told you before mumei was my favorite
maybe you maybe you understand i don't
know if she's uh she has a pretty simple
one but i love the the white and the
the red monkey
[Music]
i mean obviously they were all gorgeous
though
[Music]
um
very simple but i like the the
simplicity of it and then with the beret
i'm sucker for the raise
and um
and and and the the the little little
scarf cave cape she has
that is so cute too
french mummy yeah i guess so
what is this why that's so cute
i want to live here
kokoni sumitai
no no i said mume but i also said crony
was maybe my second favorite
i remember what i said but yeah crony is
i hot
think it's um
pretty interesting that uh they for
crony they went for some really bright
colors like the yellow and the bright
blue is like kind of like a summer
summer color theme in my opinion
wait that's so dope what the man
you have a little like
not a pool but
foot bath i guess
a psycho jungle
psycho
this is my house actually my army is
collecting rare and unusual cat food
my brother is an artist so i guess
strange robbies run into family you are
a weirdo
you are a weirdo but cute
corn is my favorite oh mama that's a
teammate ah
you
give me that heart bath that you stole
from me wait where is that cave i'm lost
again guys
we have sea urchins okay
um
is this somewhere around your south from
the village
this is south
some is somewhere here
i have a map
i don't have a map
why do i have oh
he didn't tell me game didn't tell me
about that
i don't see a dungeon here
but
it must be somewhere here
i'm too far south okay
[Music]
let's go back up then
zoom in for a better look oh
oh
now what would be the dungeon this ah
this here probably there's a keyhole
now
[Music]
perhaps
um oh but um
uh
yeah so now the only one we have left
over is iris
i wonder what kind of
kimono
she has
asked for
[Music]
very very curious to see what what she
wants to
look like
oh
hopefully it doesn't take too long i
have absolutely no idea
[Music]
uh what's
what's it how long it's gonna take i
don't know i hope it's not gonna take
too long here we go dungeon time
hopefully
level one tail cave
okay
okay are they looking at me there's so
many eyes
okay we go up first
ah smile small cute dungeon
typical zelda dungeon this is the first
time i'm playing stop uh a zelda game
like that
hey do i need you do i need to place you
on this thing or so
whoa
i have to say
the riddles
in these dungeons are too easy though
like i already like have seen a couple
like i forgot everything but it's too
easy
it's just too easy oh
or like the like this is this is
supposed to be a
mid boss
but
that's just four bats i guess
the difficulty is that you're not
supposed to like
uh walk over these too much but
it takes one hit it takes one
hand
oh wait i have a key
is this is this what the key is for
kiwawa
they get tougher later oh girl
i'll see about that
yeah i mean a little bit a little bit
toughness
must be
uh
i would expect this
what the are those
[Music]
this is nothing to do
with the difficulty of the dungeon
riddles that i was roasting which i have
nothing to do with that
this is a difficult
a different it's different
yup yup um
uh
who the are you
the beatles that shoe is saying
something you can't make it out okay
wait can i even open that gate can i
no
okay
okay then we have to go back we can't go
here yet baby
i'm not gonna die here i'm not gonna i'm
not going to die here
coco
like you're not
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
stupid baby game stupid baby game stupid
i have tears in my eyes
oh so this is already opened okay we're
gonna go this side first
oh they jump away from me i have to
corner them huh
[Music]
okay interesting
the dungeon map press minus to look at
it okay
oh
okay
going game over is not so bad
in this game
oh no i don't like these fire electric
balls man
okay
[Music]
come here
let me kill you let me kill you
[Music]
there you go
i also feel very small right now
okay
i saw the door over there
um let's check out what else is here
what do you want what do you want huh
oh it's so cute
what do you want do i even need you
i want to take it as a pet oh god
dangerous
dangerous game that i'm playing
what do we have here
[Music]
what is that what is that
what is that
what do you want
um
no restart restart
i mean free hearts it's really not that
much to play with okay
[Music]
now this is all just part of my journey
i told you to go away but
it's kind of obnoxious that you're doing
it anyway
okay
so the door is already open right okay
maybe
okay okay okay
why does it
why does it hurt so bad okay we're gonna
do this one
this comes after the heart after the
heart
don't touch me don't even think about
touching
yeah i know
i know
okay
orange that's the orange again
[Music]
okay
i'm suffering smoothie i'm suffering
[Music]
thank you i don't need to waste my time
on
you okay okay okay
okay let's do this
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's oh believable okay it's the heart
comes after the blue one okay
okay
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
i'm not gonna
say
anything about that anymore
shut up
don't make fun of me
what turn around the spiked ones with a
shield okay but hey did i i gave you the
beak but
oh
it's temporary okay i thought it would
be on you forever okay
turn around despite the ones with a
shield sure
um after first i'll go somewhere else
uh
come on kiwawa
come on
left side now i suppose
we're going this way
spiked ones it doesn't mean
uh this thing here though does he
i need that other key i think it was
somewhere here oh wait do i wait no that
that's still uh oh
the key that i got before still counts
right
uh so yeah cause normally i would have
gotten the key here i think
wait let me fix one thing really quickly
i need to fix my chat
because um i forgot to use
chat and this is broken
it's broken
i don't know i don't know no key in this
or check your map for any sport yeah
yeah yeah we'll do we'll do
we'll do
give me one moment
okay don't give me one more oh
that's me oh that's that is me
check
pop out chat okay there we go
hi buncha let's go
okay
here we go again uh minus
ah i can still go to the left i didn't
go to the left there must be something
there because it's like a dead end
hold talk with kiana no oh speaking of
hot cause just seeing my
announcement people are so
excited i am having yaagol over for
whole talk
uh
we're not spiky
next week and oh
[Music]
okay that's it that that was fairly easy
as well
[Applause]
you got the compass now you can see
where the chests and nightmares are
hidden nightmares this compass has a new
feature a tone will tell you if a key is
nearby nice thank you
[Music]
yeah i think there's already a lot of
questions i have to go for them early
because um we are pre recording this for
reasons that you will see
later on
um
can i where can i go i can't go that way
can go up and left and then
ah maybe now i can move on here i don't
know
can i
or open this door i have another extra
key right where do i see it key
do i have another key
can i open this door
hmm
i missed the key
did i go in both directions here i did
uh
let's see
where is the key another key we
can't kill you though huh what am i
gonna kill with this power that i have
this new
newly uh
acclaimed power
oh how the hell do i get there
oh
i need to go through there but i can't
jump
what do you want what do you want stupid
thing
no it's running out already and i'm in
one heart again god damn it
[Music]
hey it's in the first room what's in the
first room whoopsie
first room
a bit
of it
that snake is following me it looks like
a slivered on io snake
there we go
oh
oh i just need to kill all the enemies
in this big room
that's how this one shows up
[Music]
oh
it's just rupees
[Music]
i need some hearts
oh thank god
i can't go for them though
but i i was i was able to come through
the other way but okay okay we don't
need to go there i got another key wait
where will i use it
good question because i can't jump over
there
no wait i don't have enough key what am
i saying
maybe
i already did this
oh
room
left off the first room has a hidden key
a hidden key how dare they do that
what
okay
going back then
i mean hidden like oh wait what i see a
bro a door i can't break it with my
sword can i
it
can it
maybe i can
no okay but i remember this i remember
this uh wait maybe with the with why
no
then it stays a mystery to me
i need bumps am i getting them so soon
are we just coming back here
eventually so wait which room
secret key
is no this one i already did
oh
i need to just push these off right out
of it before they push me off
[Music]
my dioness
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
we got another key but i still don't
know how to get to the place where i can
input the key
because i have to jump over it
i don't know how
[Music]
killing these all over again won't do it
either because i already killed them
didn't i
yeah
is there something i didn't i already
went through that's where the
where the game was yeah yeah yeah
check it out the sun is shining into my
face so strongly right now
[Music]
i mean this is this is totally sus as
well like what
what am i supposed to do
something here something
but what i can give him i can give him
the beak i didn't listen to
his opinion yet
oh god i don't like this place
that's so mean to put them right there
that is so mean i'm telling you if
there's a door that you can't open move
a square block
[Music]
wow now i feel so smart
man and now i can do this
[Music]
let me listen to you as well turn aside
the spine yeah somebody else already
told me that i think
thank you anyway though oh
welcome to super mario today we're
playing a super mario game
so cute
so adorable
underground
underground world
what
what what does that mean
i can't can i jump later and get these
hearts
maybe there's something to jump here
rock spinner
wait how do i use it
do i just jump automatically
uh-huh
yo let's go
i can jump now
jump jump
jump
look at me parkouring
what a pro man okay i'm out of here oh
shortcut
let's go
okay
love it
how about that
now let's go here
after we kill let's look at that
okay okay okay see it is easy i just
needed to get used to the whole
zelda
vibe you know
oh nightmare key you mean like the boss
key
you can open the door to the nightmare's
lair they why did i call them nightmares
here
oh i know why i know i just remembered
the ending of this game
i think i just remembered it i i i had
not gonna spoil you guys although it
seems like pretty much everyone knows
what's up
that was dangerous holy what the
are you
okay come at me i understand
this is fun it's like
like playing the the rope game in school
wow
oh fairy
i don't have a bottle so i guess i'll
just take it like that
it's a portal back to the start i think
and we can go up
oh yeah
oh that was a i thought that was the
final boss but it's just a side bus huh
oh
another underground part that's so cute
no bottles in this game what oh
that beats what happened
eh
deadbeats
are you good are you just hanging out
here
just hanging right yeah
should i be worried
oh i can attack while i'm jumping nice
i don't see anything else in that room
so
open up
with three hearts another boss fight
oh
what are you are you like a papaya or
something buzz buzz outsider
moldorm um
[Music]
i see it happening already just be
careful just run away from him
when he's raging
oh
you
that's three hearts three hearts what
can i do with free hearts
oh my huh
it was i i tried once but it looked like
it didn't work on him so i stopped using
it but i guess maybe that was just a
coincidence
uh
let me go get those hearts again
because i'm not going in there without
full free hearts
killed by a burger oh you're calling
that a burger
i see
yeah
i guess i got hit by these ones as well
so it wasn't quite
the full amount of hearts oh
don't get too close to me
okay
probably just prehistoric
just three hits probably or four uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i was close i was close the last time
as well
oh my first heart container
let's go your maximum number of hearts
increase and your health has been
refilled too
oh first dungeon complete
i think
and one more heart that's already
a big difference
what
a violin or
it was pretty big for a violin instead
of um
[Music]
a cello yeah that's what i wanted to say
a full moon cello i don't recall there
being a cello
oh
beautiful
[Music]
wow
thank you for the red super shot thank
you thai tea
i did my best
swamp
shrek
are you good is this shrek's dream i
mean he is green a path opens in the
blooms that link is the ideal form of
shrek probably
hmm and he wears this hat to hide his
little ears
there you go i told you the big secret
guys
[Music]
oh
hello again
that is an instrument of the silence
whoa
i have to admit at first i didn't hold
believe you who were real
[Music]
maybe i'm not
that instrument along with the seven
other cinder set has the power to wake
the wind feast
you must go who left them all i was
instructed to give you direction
[Music]
the next cohort is north to go poker
swab
[Music]
bye bye
bye bye little birdie
thank you a swamp it is okay
i can jump everywhere now
[Music]
what is it with these apples huh
what is it with these apples
what what happened did you lose your
balls
you're really serious
[Music]
oh
yeah that's right the whole gang of
goblins
that
to the is
and they did something like that
bowser it was a really bad scene with
the
goblins so i mean
it might be faster to find out for
yourself what happened oh i think that's
just uh that was not the kid's voice but
okay
oh no oh no oh she's panicking too are
you good
it's terrible my power was darkness
oh the dogger
uh you got probably better off without
him please somebody help me out
oh
is that side quest or is that a main
quest
i've got some stuff to do lady
kiowa
[Music]
i'm busy man i've got so much to do
where would they be
[Music]
are they already gone they took your
donkle right where did they go
where'd they go
[Music]
main quest
i need to go into the forest again
can i run faster please
so slow
[Music]
dangerous music do you feel threatened
guys
yeah the holes where i couldn't i can
get the heartbeats now
let's go
[Music]
heart piece heart peace
what is it here
there we go
[Applause]
again
who wants to who wants to fight this
part-time warrior huh
they're scared of me
okay let's get this heart piece
well i mean that's ridiculous
okay
did the grass really just push me off
the edge what the
what's on earth
that's that is not
what okay it say
crazy tracy mambo's pond
okay but legit i'm not sure where
to go let me see
ah here maybe
but i don't hear the dangerous music
anymore
cemetery
but where would they go where would oh
what the hell
oh my god they're
endlessly spawning
okay there's probably nothing you guys
say north
i'll try to head north then
[Music]
uh yeah
tall tall heights
oh you hear me
maybe moving here
oh
i hear dogo
uh who is this suspicious looking around
okay boys let's get rid of him oh you're
talking about me
sure you can try
yeah but is this like a moblin music oh
what
what the
you kidding me
okay still no problem though
[Music]
with a shield
that can protect myself it's all good
i'm i'm fine
oh
you look like a wrestler
you must be an assassin senpai better
meow meow to rescue the mutt but we're
planning on grilling him tonight
and putting an apple inside his mouth so
no thank you you came here to get me but
it is i whoever who will get you
[Music]
oh
you're funny
funny
oh you stopped
why would you stab
okay i need to stop touching the enemies
because that hurts as well apparently
[Music]
is
i hate this
it's terrible also hyper chat broke as
well by the way
[Music]
why does it hurt to just touch him
i'm starting with three hearts can i get
more
let's do this again
what's that
i was pretty close to him now too but it
didn't hurt me
oh okay okay you changed your mind
okay okay much easier
this time
you gotta learn by doing
oh
let's go
kiwa too strong
nothing can beat me
[Music]
just talk to me uh one extra try
would you see if oh wow
what hey i'm trying to rescue you i'm
trying to rescue you i say vowel come
with me
come with me
i have acquired a doggle
yeah
come with me come good doggo good dogger
you will protect me right while i have
you on a leash right
well i i have to go go sorry who toot i
went on the side mission
hello
don't get too close he will eat you he
will chomp you look at his mouth he's
like really really first thing after you
oh daughter so first i'm looking animal
you after animal that's exactly what
mumei would call it
maybe you're a mummy after all
do not forget our next instrument is
okay
i will bring animal back first
if that's okay
uh which way down
uh can you jump like me too
yes you can
good boy is there a shortcut for this
stupid forest
maybe not
yeah let's go
[Music]
oh my god good boy where is the exit
though can you show me the exit goggles
i want to keep here
okay
we have arrived safely
and
i brought the dog where's the lady did
she die because she was too worried i
brought you a dog what
oh
you i'm so happy you brought my
baby back now would you build your
attacker for a walk i already did it
would really help me out a lot okay so i
get to keep him for a while
whoa
did i just read
i can't ah wrong
there's a hard piece here
really
really really though am i getting
trolled
there's a chance
that i could get trolled but here it is
i've been so tired yeah
nice thank you
nice
okay so we get to keep him we gotta go
to the tall tall mountains according to
to chat
i'm getting babysitted here
oh wait i always think i can go there
but i can't
okay through the stupid forest again
i think i need to
extreme heart peace
so oh yeah let me talk a bit more about
the jaguar appearance we're we're
pre-recording it for
a specific reason
um but i'm still gonna just because i'm
gonna still
broadcast it at the same time as usual
but on a sunday because um
you know i saw lucia as her birthday
um
and i don't know when she when exactly
she'll be screaming there's no reason
for like no no rule or so
for me to not overlap with her
oh but i just felt like
you know
it's a big event to have yaku at holo
talk so i don't
i i want to lucia to have her day and
and usually whole talk is like at 11 p.m
japanese standard time which i guess is
still kind of prime time i don't think
she'll be doing her birthday stream at
that time but just in case you know
just in case so that's why oops that's
why i moved it to sunday
oops
[Music]
um
heights damn shack is right nearby are
you down
ah you may not hear that that's very
small or you're really okay
a little job i'm getting my job around
the atlanta to dig our business things
off when you have some time to spare
cars see me but shackled it
oh that rhymes
wait that looks
cool just a couple of different colored
blocks put together nicely
why not why not
[Music]
so
you and all the others here
kill him
kill him too
nice
[Music]
that thing in there okay
yeah yeah yeah did you already ask a
question guys
the
um
japanese tweet has so many replies holy
like just reaction replies rather
than
question replies so
[Music]
that will be difficult to go through on
it
[Music]
i still can't lift them though
i need to go left no
[Music]
okay
can i walk over here no
can i walk through here no
i'm holding
[Music]
i'm here
go
[Music]
here and then
through
either the top or the bottom and then
left left and the left knob okay
okay well that's uh
a little bit of a setback
but can't help it gotta go gotta go
gotta get buffed
don't pay for that
um
oh yeah the the picture the picture of
jago in in the whole talk thumbnail by
the way
i didn't get that taken just for this uh
occasion that was already a picture that
was available but it fit it fitted
nicely so
so i put him there
looks good doesn't it
swamp right okay
phone house what are these enemies
[Music]
ask me anything about the eyelid if you
get lost give me a call
the indigestible flowers of gopunga
swamp these flowers are about our
favorite
why don't you take him for walks there
click
oh yes i mean
i don't have a choice anyway i can't
can't get rid of him right now but he's
uh he's a welcome fellow mm-hmm
annoying that's what those enemies are
well thankfully thankfully we have uh
our doggo
is that gonna be taking the usual sofa
of course
where else would he be
gonna be sitting on my sofa
my whole talk sofa danger keep out
except
i i do have to say i am pretty nervous
about this
[Music]
he seems to be a pretty nice person can
i really go into that water and swim
you'll not want to kill the the fish
you don't like fish is that what it is
oh my god oh my god oh my god
what is one of those
i ate them i can't even figure out what
it is
oh what the what the what the
stinky bomb
uh have i met him before yes yes i have
i think yes i think so
i think so
yeah i have i huh
yes i have what am i saying of course i
have
oh yeah
uh
[Music]
oh there's a chest there can we destroy
those flowers though oh he ate him
oh you are hungry
[Music]
will you ask his panty color good
question will i should i
did i ask him yes i did and she said uh
who says i'm wearing any panties
so
that's why i need to double cause maybe
that's the only way to get in here
bow wow pow wow another
dungeon here we go
i must get some power to lift something
here huh
thank god i still have some pow powder
already wasted a lot but i still have a
little bit so doesn't it
okay
i hope he'll give me more answers than
just so disney
but
i'm sure of it i'm sure i'm sure of it
i
i don't know if we can get much private
info out of him i know you guys are like
you know
hoping to learn some private details but
i don't think we'll really get that much
info and also like too much deep insight
about
about whole life in general don't get
your hopes up too high you know there's
a lot of secrets
uh iago has a lot of secrets
or
no
we we don't want you to know everything
oh god he's scary what the are you
he's so scary
okay that's not so scary
not so scary
death sensei too scary
[Music]
dead feet stabbing now
okay well this dungeon already looks a
little bit more interesting huh
uh am i getting the bow here
oh no wait i can just jump i thought
i thought i had oh powder i thought i
had to shoot with an arrow here
eventually
i guess not
[Music]
um
anton is the last money
yeah well i hope i hope we can get a lot
of interesting information out of him
not only about himself but about the
company maybe
what would be cool is maybe some insight
about
uh audition process
i see
i think i see it
i see i see i see
i see i see
uh
why the are you shy guys here get
out of here
yeah i have to kill them don't i how do
i kill them
[Music]
is i don't even know about the spin
attack
the game didn't teach me i wouldn't know
how
bruce spin attack but i i did hit him
just now
on the back i think but it didn't do any
damage
hmm
or what
oh oh i separated them oh but it
doesn't do that much does it oh
yeah
oh it did damage now
[Music]
no it didn't
there we go okay i have to be right
behind him
[Music]
i thought i was hitting their sides at
least but that's not enough apparently
okay okay i will pick you up later
hoping i won't die here
okay
i got the power
oh yeah so make sure to ask the
questions that you have in your mind uh
within today because i'll be um oops
i'll be uh collecting the questions oh
women um
women
tomorrow i'll be collecting them already
we've been tomorrow they gotta be
checked and all that by management for
sake
that's dead
i hate those enemies
those might be my least favorite enemies
so far
oh my god uh
you know what let me go to the left door
now
[Music]
stupid bat
come here
oh there must be like an extra key
or so for putting on the line no really
hi
uh
[Music]
now to find an all statue
to fit it into okay yes yes we will oh
wait there's more uh
more lights there shall be more lights
if i don't miss with the fire
oh
i thought maybe there was a hidden door
or something but you know what maybe not
maybe not
oh oh
so cute
oh they disappeared so quickly
not a long-lasting fire i see this one
stays
wait why is this one staying but the
other one isn't is that a riddle
uh no there would not be subtitles i
decided to just um translate normally
this time
uh
the reason why we're pre-recording it is
a different reason
yeah yeah yeah
let's talk to you part of the floor is
raised tap the shiny crystal duh
that's not very helpful but we didn't go
right yet i think ah here's the key
now we have so many keys
and so such a few doors to open
oh he goes up
okay
are you guys again i hate you
i miss the lock door
we'll get back there eventually
ah we didn't talk to this
you
windows
[Music]
[Applause]
make every block design the same a new
path will open
okay
that's it
oh wait
is there a secret if i
like is that a secret
i'm not gonna get hit by this how do i
how do i how do i escape him
is this a secret no
it is
oh
[Music]
i hate you i hate you so much i hate you
with all my heart
signed it
that was close
playing with fire
use the powder on the fireball oh what
okay i will next time get my revenge on
him oh
[Music]
the powder
how does
it
oh no not also little hearts
two hearts
okay that's not gonna work okay
oh no no what
[Music]
huh i don't know how i
how to fight this dude
[Music]
so
anyway
what just happened yeah good question
stay back let him charge i will try
i think you're smart huh
you think you're smart
um
[Music]
let's go chests and nightmares are now
visible
a new feature tone will tell you the
keys
i already got like a million keys i
don't even think there's any more left
maybe maybe there
okay
we're here again
oh
oh he comes with me i hate that i hate
that
run
so we go back here because the monster
was over there
[Music]
i'll give him another try but i don't
have to use the powder on him do it
not you guys again
would you mind giving me some hearts
please have mercy on me
i can't i can't find him with two hearts
i have found the solution to fight him
to fight these stupid mobs jump over
them
it is that easy yes yes yes
dodge his grab attack
um
right there's a triple heart over there
true true true
what if i turn on all the
all the fires in this room
why do that why did i why do i want
[Music]
just nothing
and now my heart swings to the waist
wait do they come back if they leave the
room
[Music]
okay i'm going back
i need some hearts
okay now that let's just be
and around the enemies are dead
do the shy guys ever give you something
[Music]
ah
wow
[Music]
hello everybody
am i able to
proceed on this side by the way
where did that lead to
how did i get up there
probably ah so for the underground maybe
it led me for did it
i don't know
uh come back
it's okay i'm fine
i'm good i'm good i'm good
i'm good
i'm
so good
i'll you
i am
good oh
what a wonderful life
you i'm gonna destroy you
[Music]
and you don't even give me hearts for
that
okay
we're going to kill this dude now
we're going to kill
the whatever the hell that monster was
i know drops are random i know i know
[Music]
do a flip link do a flip
do a backflip
can you do a backflip no
lama
flame link cyclops i guess he's a
cyclops yes
that was just you know to make it a
little bit more difficult
i don't know how to find him
oh
he got me stop
laughing oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
ah
[Music]
oh
huh
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
scaling
nope
[Music]
and now
okay
okay i'm back
[Music]
however he said i can pick up lots of
pots and stones okay
okay
hello everybody
time to eat all that
time to destroy it
everything
uh
i'm good i'm having fun
she's my my throat hurts a little bit
i'm good
i gotta go up though
i'm gonna eat some chocolate who just
asked that
accra you know me so well i do want to
eat some chocolate i do
i don't
thank you for asking
i love you
i'm good though i'm having fun more more
than in
skyward swords maybe maybe maybe
you
[Music]
go away go away go i won't have you
control my life
no no no no no no
[Applause]
i don't know if i changed the way i
screamed recently or if it's just
that recently the games
make me scream differently
but i feel like i'm damaging my throat
recently
with my
streams
what is it about this place down here is
there a shortcut for later
uh i have another key
[Music]
i am not a streamer i'm a screamer
don't tell me you're gonna be trouble
[Applause]
[Laughter]
couldn't hit them properly
there we go
is that the only way to smash
uh pots
on top of their heads
is that the only one
[Music]
so
well this is a waste of a power
thingy
a power upgrade
big waste
what's the matter with you
what what's your problem go down
uh
do you want a pot
ah
wow big brain kiwawa
oh i can't even bring it up the stairs
oh but now it disappears okay i don't
have a boss key yet oh i came here for
nothing
[Music]
oh no don't tell me i need to go all the
way around here and up and then
here this way
that is
that is quite something
do i need to go all the way back
backwards
oh no no i don't
i at least uh us all the other
way around but no
okay so now i just need to ah go down
here okay okay easy easy
okay you're not scary to me either
but i will throw this at the bunny i'm
so sorry
it's kind of brutal like can i
could i have crushed the bunny of these
holy that's mean too
[Music]
oh no maybe not
because i can't move the ones on this oh
what can i do
no
okay
so i am your mate for today i i clean up
all the rooms oh by the way i thought it
was so cute how fauna oh my god
super mario i thought it was so cute how
fauna did the whole cafe theme and then
with the omurizu
so so cute
cute
yeah yeah i like that i pushed it wrong
what did that push oh oh
the hold on
the blocks mm-hmm
come here
coward
21. first defeat the imprisoned paul's
voice
last the skeletal stalfos okay
i will try to remember that
uh but wait what do you mean why am i
here now
this is confusing
you need to kill the enemies in a
certain yeah i'll get that i get that
yeah santa with the horse mask
i wonder whose idea that was if it was
santa's idea or or her uh papa's idea
i can imagine it could have been her
papa too because her papa seems like a
pretty funny
type of person as well
like he has a
a good sense of humor just like hookah
papa
but well sana was the one who brought
horses into the game
i know like she she made up that horse
but i i wonder like who actually thought
of the idea to implement it into
into the kimono
did she say that it was uh herself as
well
he's like okay yeah they got some
similarities i feel like they would get
along very well
[Laughter]
and cronies mama as well
um
they seem to watch their children's
stream
all the time
oopsie what am i why do i keep on
pressing that i don't know where to go
should i go
there's still an unopened chest down
there
shuttle wait
can i open the chest
is that the entrance
yeah yeah yeah
oh
oh it's just money okay
well
um
i need the boss key well it must be in
that last room that's uh i'm not uh
uncovered yet
how do i get to that room it's kind of
confusing this map is kind of confusing
because it's not like all connected the
way it looks like
asaki mama even members
oh really fana's mama shows up in our
streams a lot i didn't know that's sweet
that is sweet oh i i burnt the bat
well hopefully it will never come back
then
did i miss
something
i'm confused
huh
i have another unopened yeah didn't i i
tried to go there no
how did i
how did i get there
[Music]
okay see those two are connected okay
good i wanted to go here no no no no
wait didn't i already kill everyone here
before
does the chest show up when i kill
everybody
did i just move the blocks wrong these
blocks it is there such a thing
there will be a chest here but
oh they meant in this room the order oh
i thought they meant like a boss fight
what can i redo
yeah okay
uh then the bunny first huh
they said something about the skeleton
last
but what about the bats out you
oh
it's pretty difficult pretty difficult
pretty difficult not going to lunch
[Applause]
stop screaming like that kiana it hurts
your fruit
there we go
[Music]
wonderful
so
how did i quickly get to the bosque
perhaps uh
up here and then right
hello bunny
no no no no no
okay i don't need to be bothered by this
stupid bunny
oh
oh oh you little
what a savage bunny that is
blocking the
exit
i will
i will tell everybody
in the pet shop to not adopt you
because you're a stupid savage shitty
bunny
wait there's no
no healing item here
i can't do this with one and a half
hearts
i got seen
it will take me at least one try to
figure it out oh god
what the are you
what are you
be nice to me please
ho ho ho have your back corner
[Music]
um okay
fire
juggling with fire okay wonderful
wonderful wonderful what the um i'm
gonna die
oh what
what could
yeah that's it that's it i thought i
could block them and shoot them back at
you that's not gonna happen huh
shut up shut up i know what to do i know
what to do i know what to do i know
okay
[Music]
hmm
huh
where do we go
i need to go upstairs huh
yeah i figured out the fight but then i
had a little oopsy a little accident
is it this is the right way
me too
[Applause]
no no no no no no no no not this time
yeah yeah i just realized i can get a
heart from the goombas
oh that was very nice of them
why would you take that away from me a
full heart fight huh
it's oh it's always a heart for the
goombas
cool
i need to understand why they
uh have so many mario references in this
game
it's very
interesting
are you guys ready
was i not supposed to
like i must pick it up but i can't touch
it
it's a bit difficult to not get too
close to touch it
but close enough to pick it up
[Music]
i already understood it the first time
in sports class in school this was also
the best the thing that i was best at
running away
[Music]
keep throwing after me but i'll keep
dodging and running
[Music]
that's okay a little bit of damage
now hit it and then pick it up and then
throw it
what you gonna do now huh you got you
lost your bottle
what now oh phase two uh
uh
uh what what when
what
damn oh damn
okay i'm somehow managing it anyway
okay
easy
[Applause]
i like the dramatic explosions at the
end
[Music]
we did it it's our second hard piece in
our second dungeon
[Music]
what is this beautiful instrument
the crunch porn
okay
[Music]
we're gonna make a band we're gonna make
a band yeah yeah
who wants to join my band
prairie prairie
okay we're going to the prairie next huh
could it possibly be the prairie is
waiting
why did you not join me inside by the
way dogos huh you could have helped me
there
but okay
it's not
i'm going to get out of here can i am
can i introduce i can lift those doors
so many new paths open and wait
uh
do they want us to go back to the
village though
or just straight to the prairie
[Music]
really
prairie is it is this area what
[Music]
it seems like we're keeping the doggo
yeah
okay i'm already i'm already going too
far it's just here
[Music]
don't don't even
don't even say anything
[Music]
don't
yes i can pick
let's go
were we in this house before can we keep
the dog outside
oh why would you bring the dog inside
he's gonna eat the rats in here
oh cute though
hi there big guy i'm crazy tracy i've
got a little secret for sale that'll
pump you up
how about it 42 rupees for my little
secret 42
is this lady worth it because that
sounds a bit um expensive
should i get the secret
she's cute
worth it yeah
all right come here and i'll rub it your
what
rub it on you there i've applied my own
secret medicine
it'll take effect when you lose oh i
will not die once
nice thank you behold your hearts are
full
okay
nice can i also sleep in your bed
link yeah check the chest wow there's a
nice
mm-hmm
sorry
um
reflex
so okay it's like a revive revive once
only
oh it's uh it pronounces uh a bird up
there
eat it yeah please please thank you
so where exactly are we going here
is this the prairie no that's not the
prairie
that's the wasteland
what about the water
[Music]
nothing
but we can
take a little foot bath very refreshing
speed running no i'm not trying to speed
run
i would say i'm pretty slow
or or how what do you guys think is this
is my progress very slow
i'll go to the phone house when i'm lost
i guess so
i don't
[Music]
i don't quite understand though why am i
not
[Music]
slow run
yeah no need to
uh
no need to stress
we have a lot of time
what about here
oh is this where i need to go
perhaps
is it
oh
well first time play it's kind of quick
yeah but i have you guys that's why i'm
so quick
oh who died here
me
probably me
one of my many devils
[Music]
should i check it out where is that for
later
i need to go a little bit further down
more
should i check it out anyway
ow
yeah i think the game looks really nice
they did a good job like keeping the old
look
and making it look very updated
i need a shovel
uh-huh well i'll just go back into the
city i guess
uh the village it's not really a city
okay guys i
actually i know i always tell you guys
about my cats but
one thing
you do not know
about me is that i
in the past
i used to have a dogo
i never told you this before isn't that
weird
you guys
you guys want to see a picture of my
dogo
i was pretty young you know back then i
was pretty young and um
yeah
i'm like playing with him
it was small
small baby dogo he never had the chance
to grow up he died very um soon
um
yeah was a baby doggone
uh uh i think it's called a elaborate
labrador
labrador dog
let me show you a picture yeah yeah he's
a very unfortunate or not maybe it was
not a no no it was a labrador i think
it's called labrador
yeah
very very very unfortunate i'll show you
a picture
i'm not gonna put it on the screen i'm
just gonna give you
no way do you know what i'll show it
i'll show it just one second
i need to
need to censor something out of it i
know
i know it's a long time ago so
i'm okay
i'm okay now he had some other doggo
friends and um he went to the doggle
dog of heaven
but yeah that that pain was i guess just
so much i could never get a dog again
because it was too painful
yeah
um
let me show you
[Music]
dogos are are happy everywhere they
laughing don't no matter where dogos are
always happy
okay so here is a here's a picture
this is mine
this this
this
gotcha
i knew it no way you knew it i
got you i got you trolled
[Laughter]
yeah i used to play nintendogs on my ds
i did never have a dog only on my ds
yeah
no but it would be like
[Music]
heart challenge
hey
oh come on
it's joke it's
joke never had a doggo my uh
no no never had a dog no never had a dog
i don't want
except for nintendo i don't want the dog
one day though don't play with my heart
like that
ah
i know it's um it's a painful thought
but
it's also sad about the dogs inside of
nintendogs
you know how many nintendogs have been
abandoned
so far
eh no i never mentioned having one when
i was younger i didn't have um oh
like a baby
a kitten
when i was younger that
i mean this one is for real which like
that one died when it was a kitten
unfortunately
um don't worry i'm not gonna show you a
picture i'm just gonna fix this sound
really quickly something's weird
good luck surviving the next dungeon bus
wait wait are you saying that because
you don't like the joke so now you're
abandoning me and not helping me anymore
or is it because it's dangerous a
difficult dungeon i don't even know how
to get to the next
point in the story
yeah you remember that story because she
had uh he had some he actually was a boy
a boy kitten
he had some oh
some
like
cat illness cat only illness
oh i got another one
i found a secret seashell
the third boss is actually painting oh
no
okay
maybe i shall prove my gamer skills for
that one and show how good i really am
so did i need to come back here
or was that totally unnecessary
[Music]
maybe
maybe i have to go to the prairie from a
different side
[Music]
ah
okay well i guess okay there's a
different prairie
ah
i thought there was only one
how are you here i saw you somewhere
else too
could you go get your other stuff
straight away for right now in that case
let's step into my i don't wanna
i don't wanna you can't force me
um
what there's a new nintendos called
puppies and kittens on the switch
[Music]
what
let me look it up
puppies and
kittens switch
oh
wait is that
basically the same thing just like
updated
oh my god the kitty cat paws
and this time it's with cats and dogs
together because like wasn't it in 10
dogs there was no cats you had to get in
10 cats was it that
but then
nobody got that game most people only
got in 10 dogs because it was way more
popular i don't know why why was that so
much more popular
not exactly the same but similar it was
cute but yeah
don't know if that's a good game for
streaming
okay so we are in the prairie
oh there's your phone house let's check
it out
do something
it's not from nintendo oh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay i'm strong enough now on my own
i don't need the doggos help anyone i
guess is it like free choice could i
still like continue
going on with him
if i wanted to
i'm just giving let's give him back
though cause like if i were this dogo's
owner i would want him back as soon as
possible sorry
i just wanted to
just wanted to help her with a garden
wait this is not this is not the right
place he's eating those bananas
potassium
she gives me an item for it i don't know
what this is the wrong house too
this is the house this this is it
well then i gave it a dog back but be
careful with him he keeps on attacking
people outside when you have him leashed
oh
i really appreciate what you did for my
poor precious bow wow you're such a nice
boy nice moving
how could i ever repay you something no
not a kiss no
no need for that
he's
he's blushing
it
didn't someone in the chat said that i
would get an item here
everyone checks out no give me an item
really
from
no i did not need to get kissed by this
old dog lady
her breath smells like dog
because she keeps on
getting
licked by her doggos no i don't like it
okay we can by the way buy some things
here 200 rupees we can afford it but
then we barely have money left it looks
shovel
wait we can afford that too should we
get it to look shovel
i feel like we will get more use out of
that
shovel
i'll take this one please
oh i i think i know that you can run out
of the shop of items wasn't in this
zelda game or in a different one well
you can leave with the item but
then
you're gonna be in trouble you can't
ever go back or so
[Music]
no i'm not gonna do it
it was this one yeah i'm not going to do
it i'm paying for it
[Music]
returns
oh you can't steal it
[Music]
um
i am an honest
warrior an honest good part-time warrior
and see there's so much money in the
grass we don't need to
steal from people
[Music]
so
how does this work
let's see
i only have two buttons to choose from
you're kidding me
so i can't just dig anywhere
i
am gonna be digging holes everywhere
and it's gonna look like a mess
but the dog would have told me where
things are hidden right so now i don't
have the hint from the doggle
damn it
should have kept the doggo
we're already back to 100 rupees
[Music]
did you guys do this too when you got
the shovel
did you also like dig up literally
everything in front of you
or is it only me this is also way faster
than an animal crossing
you welcome me tired other night
yes you did but i did it at the beach oh
yes yes yes of course
absolutely did that
nice we're all just the same
with one chicken brain
that rhymes
remember that rhyme maybe for a future
carefree song
we are all just
[Music]
the song is called chicken rain yeah
yeah
but not r
a i n but our e i g and
chicken rain
okay now that we've cleaned up once
again
wait where did my hose go
i want this house to be there for a
reason
okay you get rid of my home so quickly
it's supposed to be like that
meow
[Music]
what's up how's it going i don't know my
my i feel like this is all just a dream
because the holes that keep on digging
and the grass i keep on
hitting keeps on coming back it feels so
surreal
meow
[Music]
how are you doing you want to say hi to
the tim
oh kills so cute you're so sharp you
want to sit here
yes you're welcome here
smoothie it's moving some kind of
special fertilizer yeah
wait where did my house go didn't i have
some holes here i looked away for a
moment and the holes are gone
schmovie
what's doing behind my monitor huh
where where were we supposed to go we
gave back the the doggle and now let me
ask the telephone
i'm going into the cell phone
gotta go this way
i guess now i really have to be in the
prairies
cause i'll ask again
mia hi
hi
uh
[Applause]
have you met everyone on the island
there's a man and richard who lives in
pothole field southeast of the village
why not pay him a visit
is that main story though or is that
just heard
giving me some side tips
south south what south west
[Music]
part
what top
i don't remember what she said
south was itself was
southeast
[Music]
uh uh maybe this one
it's a crane game
that's not it is it
hello
no
trendy game
let's play
okay how do we play this it's a crane
game crane
game go over to the buttons to play good
luck okay
oh
dude
there's a usc
uh
okay
let's try
uh x move forward a move right okay
one more one more one more
one more please
can you do it again
yes yes yes
oh that's pretty good
[Music]
so close
and when the is there and you'll
see
one more one more
oh perfect that one is perfect
wait
yes
just don't fall out of it now i would be
so mad
oh thank god we got a hot container
we got a hot container
wow should we try to get the shield is
that the same shield that i have right
now or is it an upgraded version
get the yoshi
we can get it all
easy
yoshi's important later okay
take him
we're kidnapping your seat
[Music]
you little you little yoshi
i thought you were a good boy
i've always liked you
not anymore oh
the only other thing i could do is get
uh
those whatever is in the bag when it
comes back
ah no
ah oh
that wasn't fair it was indeed not quite
firm
oh there goes all my money
okay i'm right on top of it oh why
did i
it was a reflex it was a reflex
one more one more
once again
yeah one more
wait but i have to move
okay
oh yeah his nose might be in the way and
his eyes are in the way
stupid yours
[Music]
i don't even need him right now but now
that i started moving him
i can't help it
oh
i wish instead of moving forward i could
just go right one more time
[Music]
maybe his tail again
you're gonna get me broke yoshi
[Music]
last last try
[Applause]
see
this is the real toy story
new movie okay i'm done thank you
thank you
give me my rewards
a piece a piece of it
a rare find mm-hmm
[Music]
you can't count how many games you've
seen him in now
true
that is true yeah he's a very popular
character
for a good reason
oh
whoa you won the yoshido we've been
trying to do that forever our mom is
really desperate to have one
okay
where's your mom where does your mom
live
should i give it to your mommy
oh
where is
that in that house over there
hi taco i know you're happy to see me i
know i know is that this more looks like
a museum though
it's a library
i think
i know a secret here i think
what are the secrets of the whirling
blade
oh this is where it teaches you
maybe i learned something new here
yeah maps and memories you can see an
island map by pressing minus zoom in
okay press x
how convenient how about this the
properties of warp points no i don't
think i care about that
one with bombs
i guess
after you put a bomb down you can pick
it up by pressing a again
you can then throw it by pushing a one
more time
did you know that i'm probably gonna
learn that by doing
selecting the item that's right for you
read this book yes okay
the sub screen you can ah
yeah yeah okay okay okay okay what about
this book this is fancy dark secrets and
mysteries of color do you really want to
read it
what is this you can't read the tiny
print without the aid of a magnifying
lens but where would you get one of
those oh maybe if you lend some people a
hand they'll lend you a lens haha
interesting
are those are those chilies on top of
that tree
how's it handling your shield like a pro
yeah yeah yeah
push
me right
okay reflect beams okay
okay anyway um
anyway
uh where's your where's the yoshi
infatuated mother
maybe that
house are you the mother no you're the
grandma
do you need the
figure
they have a stand for it for maybe a
different one
cheap cheap
you want a cheap cheap one
ask ahmed she has one
can i uh borrow your magnifying glass
please
where the does your mom live
she's probably back in our house the one
up north for the two doors open
up north with two doors
two door
i don't know
is ann berlin in here
hi baby
[Music]
hi
oh
oh you have a cute baby and so many beds
are all the children in the village
yours
oh will you give that yossi doll to my
baby
oh thank you you're indeed a generous
person
i will give you this in return
a ribbon
ah this is like a trading quest right i
remember i remember a training quest
i give the ribbon to someone else oh
eventually i get a magnifying glass
probably
[Music]
here we go
what's in here by the way
i was supposed to the
dream shrine the the phone told me to
go to someone's house right to someone
some dude's house
what happens in here
[Music]
maybe this is for later
a dream it's really a
a dungeon you can only visit in your
dreams huh
oh we should save once i suppose yeah
[Music]
well that went up quickly
let's just say what's his house
or maybe this one
is it this one
was i in there before
is it the one on the beach
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
huh
not the one on the beach more southeast
uh
and just maybe an uncharted land maybe
over here
ah below this leg perhaps
so how do we get there can we go from
above
we go from both can we go from below
from here
[Music]
if we go
if we go this way and then down
can we go past here before we go above
i don't know
i'll go from above okay
[Music]
we're going to the next adventure
thank you for the membership
welcome yeah this new this is also a new
area that we didn't look around much yet
the prairie
i'm trying to go down
let's see
if we can
enter the beach from here oh yeah
looking good
don't know what these weird figures are
though a keyhole slime keyhole
okay
that is
for later i think
[Music]
uh
oh
would you look at that maybe it's this
house
[Music]
i like the
the shapes and the designs of the houses
a lot
is it you oh franco it's cute franco's i
love francoise i had a dream a problem
appeared in my dream
i had some weird dreams about some hello
project idols that i was hanging out
with i was watching a secret
concert
and um
then one of the
idols i don't know why but we were
looking at some froggers and she picked
one up and it was huge and then she was
like trying to prove to me that she
likes frogs so she
bit off the tap the tongue of the frog
don't don't don't ask me i don't
understand either
hello nice to meet you richard
salutations you wouldn't know by the
look of me but i used to live in the
castle
my servants went berserk and i was
forced to flee to my villa
so you're looking for something aren't
you i may have just what you're after
but first i want to retrieve the golden
leaf i left behind in the castle when i
fled
smashing to tell you the truth there are
five leaves and i want them all
okay you'll need to do some digging you
buy so buy a shovel i already have one
okay
wait i need to do digging
at the
castle
wait my fruit first i need a real candy
i need a fruit candy
and frog gone wrong yeah
when those were some weird-ass streams i
had
well don't tell me you don't have weird
dreams as well don't don't blame me
don't say i'm weird
you're just as weird
[Music]
would you like to take a seat
here
[Music]
come on
she's just saying hello to everybody
hot milk and honey are great against
fruit eggs uh yeah i had a oh
i had a um
a tea with honey
before the stream or like i was drinking
it at the beginning of the stream but
now it's pretty much empty
wait where the hell do you want me to
speak at the palace where is the palace
here
so i'm here now i go up up and then up
here okay
[Music]
how does one fight you
oh there we go
there we go
[Music]
hello
tell me the obvious you haven't found
the golden leaves try bombing suspicious
places
hope that helps
bombing
i don't have bombs i only have a
shovel though
[Music]
suspicious looking places oh my god
but i'm guessing i can't go inside
yeah okay
thank you for the pinky thank you for
the super chat donkey oh monkey
nice movie she keeps on coming back
[Music]
monkey monkey
what do you want what do you want is it
something i have
i'll try to look out for
something
oh there's a lot of these pig
warriors
[Music]
what do i do with this new acclaimed
power
what do i do with it when they keep on
running away from me
where where are those obvious looking
holes
there are some holes but
crocodile has the bananas true
do i need to swim
if you can't swim
[Music]
i almost died from that
oh wait wait about here
[Music]
strange warrior can't swim yeah i find
that a little bit
weird you're not quite prepared for this
world are you like
those trees look funny they have faces
on them
well there was a surprise so i tell you
a secret you use your sword to poke
attention huh
i have to hear a hollow clank you can
break the wall of the bomb
oh we also have a secret
weird bowl all by itself in the middle
of a cave sprinkle some magic powder
into it it's a pretty good joke on the
thing that lives in there uh-huh
i'll try to remember that
seashell mansion
oh
[Music]
i am spirit of the mansion
i have been waiting for someone
one who can overcome the darkness
find the secret shelves
then a center platform you will receive
the ultimate sword
sounds like you should come back with
lots of shells and try standing on the
platform
okay because how many i got now
that is not much damn i need a lot of
shells
[Music]
i need the sword do i
scary place down here
near that house you think
but
is that where the golden leaf is why the
are the golden leaves
[Music]
there we go
i got once in my five play first ah the
the super power sword you got it once
oh is this an endless spawn
50 places
oh my god all the speed does
[Music]
your mom can ask eh
i have to give the monkey bananas
oh i thought it was like an optional
thing or something for later okay it
seems like in this game you really need
to help everyone huh
uh
can i get him to bond with his skull
it's not you you're your friend your
mushroom your flying mushroom friend
would you like to come over here
no okay
[Music]
where the hell am i
wait where was the what was the
crocodile
where was it
i don't i remember i need to mark
stuff on this map oh maybe here was the
crocodile here
no where's the crocodile on the beach
that would be fitting right if it was on
the beach
okay that makes sense yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
you got a trade of ribbon at the village
first
oh because you won't give me bananas
otherwise okay oops
okay we're going to isle we're going to
the village
[Music]
i want a bump i want a bomb
canned food yeah
so who would want the ribbon
maybe maybe this lady for her doggles
and she must have canned food because
she has douglas
that's a logical conclusion
oh oh my god
that's a pretty smart phone of mine
because i thought you know she she would
probably like to put it on her dog
mm-hmm
uh
yeah yeah okay
what here i'll give it to you
how do i give it to you
to the dog house you would direct them
on your dog okay okay
[Music]
what kind of dog are you raven yes take
the dog food
how adorable
[Music]
although i know if i had a dog
i don't know if i would be the type of
person to put clothes on my dog to be
honest i don't think i would want to do
that
you know like
all kinds of it looks funny
i guess on smaller dogs
maybe
but
i don't know
if it's too cold then it would make
sense but some people just put uh like
clothes for fun at any time on their
dogs right
i don't think i would be the type to do
that
going to the beach beach i need to go
down here
[Music]
holy time stunning time
taking the small dog's place okay go go
go go i'm going back i'm going back
[Music]
okay did i have a heart piece maybe
must be a heart piece
i can even dig in these houses that's
crazy
well dog will help me
where is that oh seashell not a heart
piece i guess okay
right
no heartbeats
no but you look absolutely adorable
with that
ribbon cute never dress up your kitties
no no no no no no
no no no no i wouldn't do that
i think cats are probably why is it
green now
cats are probably
even more annoyed by
getting dressed up than dogs i guess
dogs are pretty
um open to the thought of getting
dressed up
but cats hell no
hell no
what about a collar i know my cats don't
have colors collars
because they don't go outside anyway
most cats deactivate interests of you
yeah yeah you know you know those videos
of cats with socks on nice movie you
want socks no you don't want socks i
know you don't want socks don't worry
i'm not putting any clothes on your
smoothie but you can come up here
it's uh they don't seem very happy about
it
when having uh
socks put on them
this movie agrees
wrap yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
give that to me please i'm gonna lose it
if i can't get that can
can i have some of your bananas in
please
that was great i know it's not a fair
trade well here's some bananas
that's pretty fair
the bananas for the monkey
oh sh
on to the monkey
uh
let's have a little wait not this monkey
right i wonder what would happen if i
gave it to this monkey i can't
probably
he doesn't seem to even want to have a
conversation
so guys uh recently you know how i've
been watching all these historical
shows the tv shows
i am done with the whole
uh storyline
of what hap now it's red again
of what happened before the tutors
um well like not before the two days
before henry the eighth so i know the
whole story about
uh
edward and then and then
uh henry the seventh mm-hmm
very interesting
i finished all of that up to the point
of catherine of aragon
uh
being henry viii's first wife and then
you know i've already watched all the
tutors so i know how henry dies as well
very educated takanasi kiwawa
and
so because of all these historic shows i
was watching i got a recommendation
in my
on my tv
for a show that's called
the great
and it's about catherine the great
who was a german lady who married the
russian emperor
but
[Music]
catherine the great or the great the
show is just called the great kind of
confusing
uh
it's it's really
not very accurate i mean the show itself
in its title says an occasionally
true a tale or a story or so
so it admits that it's really not very
true at all
um
so that's fine
do i need to go from above how did
i get there before
from
it's not this way at least oh i can only
go back from here
mayota
yeah occasionally true
very roughly true
uh but even then i find it very
interesting and the show is so well made
like holy
below last year himself
ah
i see it okay okay
because um the other shows that i've
been watching recently they were just
historic drama shows you know
but this one is a dramedy it's like
a huge focus on comedy
and i think that's the first time i've
i've seen like a
like a real story
that's happened in in in the past
being
um
presented in such a comedic way
it's very very interesting i mean
there's a lot of swearing
i'm wondering if they really did swear
this much
uh back then
this is by the way in the 17th
century i think
yeah historical comedy
but it fits so well i must say it's
absolutely brilliant sorry i'm petting
my cat right now
it's absolutely brilliant
so funny i finished the first season
yesterday
um every episode is one hour and it's
the first season was i think 10 episodes
so that's like 10 hours i watched it in
the course of two days i think
18th century okay
it's so good just one thing that kind of
disturbs me or just feels kind of off to
me even though it's like i guess
it's cool but
all the actors speak british english
and i highly doubt that everyone in
russia and the german lady catherine
uh all
have a perfect british accent
that just seems kind of unrealistic to
me but what can you do they just chose
um british actors only i guess
but it it killed the immersion a little
bit that we're in russia because
everyone is speaking absolutely perfect
british english
it the immersion is ruined i want rusty
russia
russian accent no you know what probably
if they were all speaking with a shitty
russian english
i would probably
be bothered by that as well
[Music]
british english is really really nice to
the ear isn't it i really like it i love
listening to british english
i love it
am i on the right path
yes i am
[Music]
yeah um
so
uh
while
while um
being very aware of the fact that uh
the story
is just mostly a story and it's not very
accurate to the true history it's still
so well made and i love it it's
so good the last episode was brilliant
it's so good you guys need to watch it
the the second season i think it just
came out and that's why it was um
recommended to me i just started to
watch the the second season as well
really good holy and yeah um
the main actress
uh fanning she's so pretty holy
she's so pretty
are we gonna get a monkey dance monkey
dance
monkey dance
oh they're building a bridge what but i
need an item to continue training
thank you
uh
thank you ah i got a stick okay
who the wants a stick from me hmm
it's like a leftover from the bridge
thank you
one of my
uh favorite idol groups betty's cobalt
they had a
they had a very funny song with a very
funny music video what was it called
monkey dance
do you see that
monkey dance or something and they were
dressed up in monkey costumes
and singing a monkey song
yeah
i can recommend it to you guys it's very
cute
stranger we should take a closer look
does it teleport into somewhere oh god
oh my god where are we going
what
[Music]
do i have to activate a different one
and then i can teleport in between those
two i suppose
also smoothie has seemed to settle down
next to me
i can provide with some russian accent
[Music]
what i do think they captured well
probably is the spirit of 18th century
russians
um
there's a lot of
intercourse and a lot of
breaking glasses a lot of alcohol
and a lot of killing
fascinating
talk to me
and around the five golden yeah yeah
someone stole them to begin with i bet
the boss trooper in the castle still has
one okay
now i don't want to do that then oh
i wouldn't say that
uh
people liked to go hunting back then i
suppose and uh
yeah
they were just discovering
a lot of new things back then mm-hmm
[Music]
the people in court i guess
not
people
normal people living in russia
obviously
[Music]
i
i have no idea how many times
they have said the word huzzah
in that show though like it must be at
least
oh wait
you might be useful it must be at least
300 times
so many huzzahs
[Music]
oh
okay nice
[Music]
i'm inside guys okay so here they want
me to dig is just random places or is it
kind of like
somewhat
obvious
and every time they said that they would
break a glass
so many broken glasses man
but the emperor
he has been um
portrayed as an absolute idiot i
i don't want to believe that he was
really such a idiot but
if he wasn't then why would have uh why
would would they have kind of
like kicked him off
and have him abdicate and throw him
from the throne
why why would they have done that i mean
there must have been a reason he must
have been really stupid then
but not as stupid as in the show
that's the only historically accurate
part him being
an idiot
[Music]
they said something about letting him
throw a bomb somewhere but like where
maybe here
dude can you come
to this hole
and throw it there
[Music]
come here
would you please
what
um
do i need him to throw in here
killing him gives me a leave
i see
oh it's not that difficult
[Music]
one out
um
where would that be
[Music]
okay
uh someone said the crow but how do i
kill a crow
[Music]
what what the
and i no
i lost movie
maybe another
another
[Music]
i need to use my shield less
but
[Music]
oh i got him once
come here ah wait i think i understand
yeah yeah
you gonna let him like come down into a
certain direction and then go
um try to attack him from behind okay
two
okay are they all here
[Music]
where's the rest can i go inside
oh i can't i'm scared
am i safe
oops
and i don't have my i don't have my
free death
my one time revive i don't have that
anymore my phoenix feta
phoenix down
what year oh what the
oh holy
those are some aggressive boys
[Music]
looks like a
looks like
a feather
nice
what does that do oh
open the big gate it sounds like the
castle gate opened you can easily leave
the castle now okay for escaping
in case i need to
i can't stick here by the way
good to know
okay
oh no not those buddies again
is there something here i need a i need
a bump here
this room
doesn't seem to be of any help oh hello
that will be fun to fight that enemy
will be fun
looking forward to it
exit
oh
should we go down nah
we'll go through here
i need bombs buy bombs at the village
it looks like they don't want
to let me pass anyway
okay
it is time to buy bombs huh
[Music]
okay
at least now we've made it relatively
easy to come back
a shortcut perhaps
a doco
[Music]
hopefully uh this way
oh
boom
[Music]
the door told you how to get it yeah
yeah it looked like a bump didn't it
oh what are you doing here now you want
some honey
i was just gonna say maybe he can make
use of the stick by poking the
the beehive
yes please take it then you'll give me
some honey i suppose
boom boom boom poke poke poke
oh yeah you're gonna regret that
are they gonna come after you not after
me nice
[Music]
what an idiot
and i get the honey yeah you're not sure
how it happened but take it i'm taking
it of course i'm taking it's mine
[Music]
okay
oh we're going back for bombs who would
want the honey
[Music]
who would want some honey
yeah if you want some honey just get
someone else to poke the beehive
as long as you don't do it yourself
bombs
okay
bombs please
i need to sneeze
[Music]
how many can i hold
can i hold more than 10.
wait he's selling
a bow and an arrow what the
nope that's not happening right now
thank you thank you
you want some honey does the fox want
some honey
no
hey what now we go back
oh box steal it
maybe if i have the other items and
don't need anything else anymore from
the shop maybe then as the last item
i could steal those yes
i'm scared i don't want to steal
well
wow
[Music]
in here
oh hello
i don't need anything right now though
hmm
[Music]
okay
i remember this place
wow
[Music]
sorry just talking to my cat
oh
come on
can i make this go boom and then we will
have a shortcut
[Music]
explosion
nice nice nice
we're getting revenge from everybody
who's been hurting us out
that was not so smart
[Music]
on the road today with big brain moments
thank you i mean
not so much in the in the first dungeon
i feel like i had some issues there but
now i'm in the groove now don't you
think
oh
[Music]
okay
it's as simple as that
oh
okay okay okay okay
okay
oh that hurts man that
hurts
you're doing great thank you
it's fun playing this game
even though i had some uh gamer moments
meow hi it's movie oh i can oh make
those
oh what did i do
what did i do
what i'll get yeah get something out of
this at least
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe we shouldn't have activated them
both at the same time but that's okay
that'd be okay can i throw a bump down
there
oh i can't
can i kill him from here
holy
[Music]
is like could you also kill him like
normally
oh too far way too far
no i'm gonna
i'm gonna lose all of my bombs
yes yes yes that's that's good that's
good
it resets
okay better not better not uh
waste all my bombs
stop giving me weird nicknames
well i'll give you some weird nicknames
pasego how about
um
how about
[Music]
got him wait what
what do they want from me
oh
[Music]
this music man
i need some heart
is there ever hearts in it yes
hey maxine
i was using the shield i was using it
i need the bombs though like do i really
need them you guys said you need your
bums but
[Music]
see i'd still take damage what the
oh
okay what did i need the bombs for
i guess for that one
one of the feathers needed the bomb
definitely
[Music]
ow
wow
oh
[Music]
i have the most ridiculous deaths ever
in this game for some reason
aside coming from a milo
it but i have the i have the feta right
the
uh where would it show them on it
[Music]
i don't see them here
ah at the top left okay so i have them
all okay i'll go go go go get
wait let me destroy the
jugs here
what the actual
we need a epic fail
compilation
of my
zelda
links awakening playthrough
oh man
yeah that
[Music]
is michael here
what why why would it be a one hour
compilation excuse me
well i wouldn't be that long
my roots are not my good
sorry
we're right does he live here
yes there okay
ah potholes because all these pots have
holes okay
uh how do i get there down
then through here maybe and then around
i think i was able to walk around here i
think
oh my god the fruit candy
oh my god so
oh no
it's so fresh in my mouth right now
in my fruit
why is
[Music]
i was looking at the super chat
wait wrong way wrong way
[Music]
up
around the telephone house
[Music]
don't call me and stop calling stop
calling i don't wanna learn anymore no
no no no no
on the dance floor stop calling stop
going
[Music]
you know that super old lady gaga song
do be old
[Music]
it's do me very old
i have arrived my friend uh
michael or richard
sorry i forgot again
ah tillerbeen i see you ever covered all
of the leaves now move this statue and
you will find your reward
huh
the frog's not joked
honey
i just see another dungeon where is the
reward
oh oh
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
exactly
oh why do i do that
no i keep on i wanted to i actually
wanted to
do this
hoping to find something here
no no secret for takanashikiwawa
nice
oh come on how how did that not work
dude
ah
you've been playing around with me a
week a little collared
ah
oh oh no no no no no no no don't
fall in
oh this is dangerous
[Music]
why is everyone playing games with me
huh unbelievable
think i got time for this
[Music]
i don't know i even thought that i
should continue moving on there
[Music]
oh this is so funny
oh the container the hot container is
the real price isn't it
[Music]
worth it
i can't get it yet i need to like be
able to like do double jumps or so
what's up
oh
[Music]
games
you got this slime key now you can open
again with the ukulele
[Music]
i would have hoped for some
for a fancy feather to like jump over
there but okay
[Music]
all right don't you want to go straight
over there or
what are we gonna do
[Music]
i love cutting grass
so
that was a sign maybe
oh
you have to work tomorrow yeah life is
tough man the writing is on the
other side shut up
uh
uh this one
i i will take monday off if you haven't
seen my schedule look on twitter uh and
did i post it on the community board i
definitely posted the jungle question
thing the yago talk
question thing i don't know if i posted
the
[Music]
what
if i posted the other
[Music]
thing the schedule ah wait i thought you
would open the gate for me do i have to
huh how do i get there
over the water
maybe jump jump jump jump jump jump
our schedule is not up okay well it's on
twitter if you want to see it i uploaded
it a little bit earlier than usual
uh
okay
so go up here go up here
i need to find an entrance ah here here
here here okay i'll go get all the way
around it is
you spin my head right round right round
and young
[Music]
i know the other day in the minecraft
disney collab it was kind of ironic that
i was the one telling telling gura uh to
not challenge uh the mca i know it was
ironic but i did that because of disney
there's
no
no messing around
so
yeah
just saying what a stand on the pedestal
wait did i miss a pedestal to stand on
ah this one okay yeah i never actually
stood on
it oh some strange energy is pouring for
me you should find out eyes at the
teleportal thingy teleportal
oh is that a shortcut
not exactly
but
good to see that thank you
thank you for the hints
i completely ignored that
[Music]
okay okay
um
on that note you guys will unfortunately
never ever hear me sing
disney songs
on
streams before anymore not even
unarchived ones r.i.p i really enjoyed
singing and blasting out those frozen
songs
i love singing my frozen songs
yeah
i freaking
loved seeing those
where are we going where am i going ah
this way
no way that's
good times um
well
i found a couple of them
and there's oh there's some clips
from it so
you can always look back on those
[Music]
oh yeah uh
did you see on my schedule i wrote um
that there is a stream
on someone else's channel
it's pretty early for me but
please check it out it's gonna be
um
worth it
yeah i think for esd it was like six am
right holy man
i'm sorry you don't have to guys you
could also watch the archive also the
korean snack box stream i'm also having
that one be pretty early
again because um of lucia senpai's
birthday i thought uh because 12
o'clock for me would be 8 p.m japanese
no
yeah 8 pm japanese standard time
[Music]
and i'm not sure
when she'll do her birthday stream
um i might have to move my stream as i
said i don't need to
move it around for her but i would
prefer so
we will see
if it
if it uh
overlaps 100 percent
then i will
move my stream my korean snack box
stream if it's just overlapping
[Music]
a little bit or so
then
i will not move it we will see
korean snack box
oh
level three key cavern key is there many
key at artists here
nice nice thank you so i don't have to
go buy them
more bombs holy so many bumps
let me uh
switched in
it seems like this dungeon needs a lot
of
bombs
or jugs haha
what the is that
ah do you suck
are you able to
oh no you push me away
anyway maybe that one is for later
um excuse me what the actual
what just happened i almost died
i need running boots ah
to withstand that wind not a little
interesting
really really that's the challenge
really
killing four slimes
clutch chill
you said that roland's still skin
you're a clutch kingdom
uh
can i eat
can i even do anything here
i don't think i can right now i need to
activate
some crystal somewhere
really nothing
how will i make use of this power
oh so many key doors
let's open this one
hope i won't regret how many kids have i
think two
what is that are you a bird
no i can't
wait wait wait i think i know how to
kill him
send a bomb there
or maybe it's too slow
oh big brain man is this how
it's supposed to be done
i don't
know i could have thrown it too maybe
maybe i could have thrown it too
that was still pretty smart
so far so good
[Music]
deadbeat's lurking now
wow
oh another challenge
no challenge for me
a key here as well
what hope the order of like which keys
the key doors you open first isn't too
important
and it won't me over
no way it would do that right okay how
do i fight you you want to bump don't
you oh oh there we go there we go
smart smiles mine
no
take it eat it
stupid
[Music]
okay okay
you know i totally understand the
principle of
this enemy
not so difficult
just gotta
i ran out of bumps though what do you do
when you run out of bombs
[Applause]
damn it
i'm out of here oh okay
can i go up to get books
please
okay that's how you reset it
okay
uh just need more bombs please
oh
that got one of them
ah yeah
an unconventional wet use box i don't
have any right now
unconventional way but we managed
[Music]
here we go
okay
um
what what even was that i need a beak
i need a beak and i need more bumps but
i wonder can i do it with nine bums
ah
50 rupees let's go
might need to buy now i'm not gonna pay
for bombs
no
i'll find them
somewhere okay this is a dead end
this is a more complicated game
nice to see
[Music]
one of them played well like corona did
on the hit to stream and ina on hl2
oh okay
glad you like it
i i'm not sure if i'm really uh
william
considered
a good player when it comes to these
games
i may not be bullied by this stupid red
jellies here right now so
uh
hmm
can i get some bumps
so one of those only really gives you
one that's stupid it sucks
he's ground pounding me
that's it that's it
is that it
okay
i played a lot of this and died a lot
more really
you died more often than me
interesting what what what
man that's like hell
but i'm kind of zooming for this dungeon
i feel like i'm uh absolutely doing
that
okay we got the compass
i'm not dealing with you guys again
[Music]
another yes
i didn't realize that was so low on
health
[Laughter]
well that goes into the compilation
[Music]
that is going into the compilation
hallelujah
um i'm just after all i'm a content
creator i know what the people want
and i just give it to them
yeah
where is that
what the is that on the left side
boss monster now with 12 bombs i have a
feeling it might just be enough
is it was it this way
wheel
anyway we'll get that chest eventually
[Music]
uh what's this way
go away
i don't have time to deal with you
this melody used to make me incredible
sad but now i just love
which melody the the
melody when you die
you're welcome
i want to see you smile just like in in
the myth song
i wanna see your smile
i'm gonna wait to use some help
something like that
let's give it another try all right i
hope let me save
do you reckon i have enough bombs
oh there we go if i don't fail too often
that's already another one okay
uh
which way you gonna go don't leave
come up here
okay
[Applause]
what's your problem with that bomb oh
[Music]
we already got the teleporter well that
was quick
damn
um
well that's not how it's gonna work
can i reset this please
um
i know how i know how i know how
yes yes here it is
[Music]
if you hold out you can dash try going
for a longer jump wait so i don't need
the feather anymore no i do
i'm pressing l and then trying to jump
but the jump won't we won't combine
what's the timing for it
i gotta get used to it
oh what a weird object there must be
some way to tackle this obstacle
bombs
nope
wasted my bombs on that one do i even
have anything to fight it with yet
just
you just jump when you're dashing wait
am i stuck in here
oh i need to use the boots on that okay
ah
and now i'm not stuck anymore
okay
oh
will the boots help me
oh somewhere here
no
i've already done everything
in my power what was it telling me about
the chest up there on the on the second
level i wouldn't know how to reset but
but at the very beginning of the dungeon
stop it
at the beginning of the dungeon there
was something
can we return once
bombs thank you
always good to return for some
bombs
[Music]
okay so i wanted to sit here because if
you go left then there were some of
those weird tints
yes
okay
oh and now we have the chest but i still
can't open it
how about we open one of those other
doors
[Music]
wait which color was it when i entered
it was blue right i think it was blue
because then i want it to be
orange yes yes or red or whatever
i still have the beak
but i wonder if i go back now
oh wait that was not where i wanted to
go but okay we'll deal with this room
now
uh is this a riddle
don't disappear don't disappear
how dare you
okay okay now deal with that stupid verb
oh don't disappear could it could it
like fall down
is that a possibility
more bombs let's go
use the boots
oh
yeah i didn't think about the boots i
need to get used to
the boots first the existence of the
boots
no yeah okay that's fine i totally
forgot about the chest
what's inside
yes it can fall
the key can't fall down there oh
then
you will be missing out on some
item somewhere
you gotta reset the dungeon also huh
uh
okay
nice position so like does this work
i think i need to jump
it comes back it's not lost forever i
see that's it i'm trying to run and jump
but
it disappears before i can reach it
huh
leave a bump
how far does it even throw
oh
okay i feel like that's a waste of bombs
though it only even does one damage yeah
[Music]
oh
wait this way it actually kind of works
well
oh ah
oh i'm so stupid
i am so stupid i thought i for some
reason i had to
just go from this side i don't know why
i
i was so focused on it
[Music]
holy it's pretty big has two floors
i don't even want to look at the map man
what do you have to say
far away do not fear dash and fly
okay
he's telling me to use my new skills i
suppose
do you want to change this back to the
other color now
let's go
[Music]
oh
let's go
this way again although i feel like
maybe that's not the right way to go
right now
there is yeah there's a keyhole that i
haven't opened up there let's open this
one
and then another one
oh i don't have any more case okay
that's fine
remember maybe here did i miss something
here
i sent that one flying though
hook it to death hell yeah
if only chiara had more case i'm gonna
get more don't you worry about that
don't you worry
ground pound skeleton no is that dead
ahmed
ahmed will never die
never
dangerous
18 bombs now that's pretty good
[Music]
defeat the black monsters with the hard
shell feed them something explosive i
already i already fought them thank you
though
i didn't even need your advice i
immediately understood
um i would like to
go there
wait there's next
a wall that could be blown up
with a bump which means i will only be
able to enter that room if i
blow it up from a different side i guess
they don't want me to throw bombs down
here and then have them like hope that
one of them will explode by that door
yeah
nah it's like eventually i
or or is that what they want me to do
massage
okay
please
oh wait
they just die
oh wait i can just throw it out the door
good to know that they give more bums
though
well put the key i can't reach it now i
need to go down there anyway where where
where where does that door
oh it only opens from that side
oh because i was wondering
like if the if the crack is on this side
why is it not on this side i guess for
some reason and you have to enter from a
different room
so i was like it can't be this room but
apparently it is this room
oh
okay
i found a little
a one way to make us a little bit faster
as well
okay wait so i have to go up
i want to talk to the beak
let me talk to them
poke suspicious parts of the wall with
your sword and listen to the sounds it
makes
how do you how are they poking
how did
how do i poke them
guys how do i poke it
[Music]
hulk by charging
i don't hear any sounds
hold spinning pork butter
well
does it just not make any sound at all
when there's nothing
a direct angle okay
so
oh i have to get pretty close
ah
and then it will make a funky sound or
something huh
okay wait do these bombs only drop bombs
if i kill them with bombs or what the
hell because i felt before when i killed
them before
oh
it didn't it didn't drop me that
oh oh
yeah see now it doesn't drop it
nevermind that's okay
is there something suspicious here
no
yeah was that just random
probably
you can see the secret find usually okay
okay okay
going back how do i get up there
ah
this is what the beak was talking about
probably to not be scared here
about that big gap
okay
i believe i can fly i believe i can
touch the other side of the room
[Music]
see naruto told me to believe it but
it's all
okay i made it i made it i made it
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay
we already have the nightback creek guys
what the hell
we're zooming through this dungeon but
someone said that the monster the bus
in this uh dungeon is pretty difficult
yeah with confidence with confidence
did we already see it
oh yeah it's on uh
b1
somewhere here
but there there's no door leading to it
where did i
did i not explore yet
wait i have one more key that was there
was one yeah this one this one this one
this one
that one is maybe the last one the last
key
ah wait no i need one more
one more
[Music]
stop
wait
oh
where
where could it be
i already cleared this room before
thank you for the membership welcome
i also cleared this room before but i'm
gonna get the bombs
hell yeah
you
yeah there's nothing more on this side
side
ah i need to go here
shut the weight
i love it how they always welcome me
here
so let us go back
let us go back
and try
oh wait there's two chests
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
it was a bit difficult to control
but we got him he kind of leads you
or tries to push you away
into a different path
what's the maximum of bombs i can carry
ah looks like it's fruity okay
wait should i
[Music]
go this way
see if i can get access
to that other chest
here
what was holding us back last time
ah
okay good that i kept it on orange
because
otherwise we would have to fix it again
here
what do we have what do we have
oh the map now
kind of late for it but
all right
now
how did we get to b1
was it here maybe
[Applause]
[Music]
those stairs do they go down or up
just go up
acorn
i'm missing a chest yeah well
i guess so but like i'm still oh this
one
huh how the did i miss it was that
a secret one
how long is that
don't tell oh i never killed you i
definitely ah but i see i think i
understand the obvious part is not on
the wall the obvious part here
is on the ground uh-huh uh-huh
the red slime
you kidding me
can i throw a bomb over there or
doesn't it respawn when i go all the way
around
[Music]
no it won't go over there
but they respawn
they respawn though
slime is it you did you follow
me
i'm coming for you wait for me see these
all respawn okay hopefully the slime
doesn't respawn
oh oh oh oh
[Applause]
you're lucky that didn't kill me
hallelujah
hello
[Music]
i heard there was a secret chest
that you only get if you kill them all
but you just need to get a bit more
brain juice holy 300
300 rupees will be worth
just be with your brain
or ask the chat
they will lead you to the right path
hallelujah
[Music]
no okay
i did not just discover something super
top secret big
brain it doesn't continue here does it
wait i have one more last silver key and
one more key one look here
uh
no that's not it i need to go up and
down and up and down and up and down
ah this stupid stupid area again
i always flunk my head here it hurts
sorry guys i'm by the way barely uh
barely small talking today i've noticed
not that there are no topics but
i feel very immersed into the game right
now
lucky
the hell is that
[Music]
no okay
i need it to come down i suppose
otherwise i won't make the jump will i
what if i poke it
oh
oh he shook
his face on it
i mean it did the trick uh somehow you
might be able to do it without taking
damage
oh yeah
is there ever items underneath these
does it work like destroying them all
maybe i get a secret is there a secret
balloons popping
bomb to face what
boots were a good mechanic
yes
oh there
okay
[Music]
wow this
is not really difficult is it
let me just kill up
all the bats
get them out of the way
flap flap flap oh
another key
where did we need another key is this
like an extra key
where does it say
how many chests i have left
or did i have them all where would it
say that
it's a safety key
in case you lose one like when you drop
one perhaps
a spare key okay i'll get okay okay well
then i think it is time for us to
do the boss fight
are you ready
i heard this one was difficult i have i
have 27
bombs and four hearts right now
so i'm also full of hopes
neither neither you can't find me
ah but i can see you because of your
shadow
but then how do i fight you do i leave a
bomb there or
or do i jump up to you
i mean i know where you are
no
that is an awkward fight
oh
oh that's just the beginning what now
you're so shiny beautiful oh
wait
oh wait i can't go i can't go
uh diagonally
oh
wait i'm not that fast
yeah it's on the high up and i didn't
no
straight ah
he goes to the side
maybe something else done
um
[Music]
oh
wait can i just hit normally wait
i can just hit him normally
but now he's like
too close to the wall
no wait i can't just hit him normally
ah no i can't
that's
what we're dying
i don't want to die right now please
help me what the
charge for the set ah
okay
from the middle or like
oh you
oh
that is so
[Music]
what the annoying
which way
huh
which way is this
[Music]
is it this way
load the safe yeah i think that would
would that be smarter
that's probably smart wait which one is
it this one
is it this one yeah
okay
wait what
what
[Music]
why does that not work oh they teleport
me to here why would they do that
man
[Music]
at least i have more hearts yeah
but i might lose them on the way
[Applause]
i'm not sure which one was the right
path i think leave me alone leave me
alone
i think this might be it
i don't understand what i was doing
wrong in the in the end he just
he
he fixes himself way too fast
oh this time no damage let's go
is this even the right path
i'm not killing you guys again
yeah this is the right path
[Applause]
oh wait
did i already get the thing okay
huh i was just a little off center
dash in the middle you keep praying for
no no
it doesn't
suck you suck
i was being so nice to you you know
because you're so shiny i really thought
that's that looks pretty but honestly
you suck
[Music]
how can i be like so fast
he turns to the side i hate that
[Music]
and now that didn't count apparently
that did not count
and that of course was too late
what a stupid bus
that's not gonna work either of course
not
[Music]
huh
it's not for this center right you don't
mean this
oh
i'm gonna die again
just because this is so stupid
why does he go back to normal so fast
can i hit him normally why does it have
to be charging this is the maximum
no i don't want to die
no they have to charge
[Music]
i'm slow i can't be faster than that i
have to bring myself into position again
as well
ah you little what it continues
no no
no
i'm not gonna let you do that
i'm not gonna let you kill me i'm not
gonna let you kill me do i just
continuously poke their eyes out now
no no no
i hate you so much
jump before they land
oh we're we're ending the stream after
after this because i have no patience
we have played more than enough
i'm gonna read super chats after this
dungeon
my my patience have has come to an end
wait what i thought i reloaded
did i just save over my
that was a pain in the ass man
pain
pain pickle
no no no no no no no
leave me alone
yeah passed up
let's kill a slime ball man
that won't really help me though
it won't really help me
you
because at this point he doesn't really
do me much damage here
but okay
why where did that friend come from
could you get rid of him damn it
off
nope that's not gonna do it
oh so why is the music suddenly so much
loud
no
can you go up please
[Music]
no he doesn't go up
no wrong
you
you don't leave me much space here come
up
[Music]
how the would i hit both eyes huh
how would i do that
i can't
part myself into two people
uh
go back
i'm so bad
[Music]
don't give up
don't don't
but i have a problem
no it's still the
same don't give up
stupid boss man
that's the most stupid boss i have ever
encountered
why is the path to the boss also so long
shouldn't that teleport thing be helpful
it's not helpful
[Music]
no
wait do i now get this all the time
um
i think i would have preferred the
defense one in this case but okay
does that does that mean that instead of
hitting him like four times i only need
to hit him two times to get him into the
same position i don't think so
supercharged only like one over
over
the
like if i have defense one and then the
power one then only the power one works
right
excuse me what's going on
uh wait uh you said jump
what's going on what's going on what's
going on what's going on what's going on
what's going on
[Music]
what's going on what's going on what's
going on
[Music]
stupid game
most stupid boss on the whole wild
wild white wild world
gamer of the and
[Music]
[Laughter]
see you ellie's belle
[Music]
how cute
it's pretty nice yeah
it looks pretty nice
three instruments how many are there
how many do we need to make a band
waterfall
it is hidden in the waterfall
okay
but we'll check out the waterfall next
time i still need to pick a cute bathing
suit you know
i'm not ready for that yet i need a cute
swimsuit
[Music]
hello
how many instruments have you gotten so
far
when you play the instruments in front
of the egg egg
the wind for ease will wake and leave
this island
no you must hasten to the order dessert
am i speeding for this game
how how far am i
there's like eight to nine oh
eight instruments nine dungeons
okay we've done
three or four dungeons today
[Music]
the dark monster is inhabited off the
sword we'll show you the way hoo hoot
ow
[Music]
okay thank you owlsan
one third okay and then when i say three
streams it might be uh
a pretty good estimate
[Music]
um sometimes i need to
yawn in a very
very very
exaggerated way
thank you for the super chat and happy
birthday
yay
it's your
birthday nice to
stay healthy and happy
playing an egg no no no no
but
we will now go to my office and read
super chats because uh surprisingly it's
already been five hours it felt like a
little bit less than that but uh yeah
time goes by very fast
so you can go to high end that goes
do we want you know what we know what we
can do we can play uh zelda music
ost during the super chat reading is
there a specific one you like
from this game
which one should we do
which one should we do is there a
specific one
maybe the one in the village
and
link's awakening
hotel heights
what how's that one sound like
[Music]
that's that's pretty dramatic for super
chat reading
oh it's dope though
it's really good
uh
but no gross is not in this game
gross ain't in this game guys you guys
are ridiculous
um
oh that's the og
that sounds like the og
oh
the title screen one is already amazing
holy
[Music]
i'm some good stuff man
always tastes so good
[Music]
i think it would help me to get for the
super chats pretty quickly
[Applause]
[Music]
this one is good
sixth dungeon
[Music]
no amount of what
no amount of music can get you for super
chats quickly daniel hey
you know i can if i want to
oh yeah this one is wow
wow
[Music]
oh
my this is wonderful i want to listen to
this one for a while
total wait
is there a solo version of that
winx awakening sword search
whoa
oh
[Music]
is it a violin or is it a channel you
guys say violent but we saw a cello in
the game as one of the instruments so i
would kind of imagine it to be a cello
but i don't know maybe it's both
maybe the little one is a cello and then
the higher one that we heard was a
violin
yeah maybe it's a mix
ah enough
[Music]
i'm beautiful i like this one too let's
play this one okay i'm moving over to
the office
[Music]
hello hello hello oh maybe i should take
down take down sword be kurendori
all right
[Music]
oh where the hell am i
where am i where am i
where am i
i can't find my own layer
oh
here i am
take down sword beautifully
[Music]
and put put down put down sword
sound
maybe instead
[Music]
oh who's with my hands
i've turned into a cat
i hope you guys are good with that
[Music]
why do i hear boss music it's not boss
music
oh yeah buddy buddy i didn't see your
newest clip yet i need to watch your
newest clip and the thumbnail already
looks really cool
[Music]
how the hell did i make it for this
stream without snacks so far
damn
what happened kiwawa
how's everybody sunday going by the way
how are you doing everybody
how are you feeling are you tomorrow's
gonna be monday guys tomorrow is a day
to eat lasagna
i'm getting ready for that lasaga
all right is the music too loud it's
probably too loud
it is too loud
a little bit
thank you
i'm riding on one hour of sleep holy
please go to sleep
don't force yourself guys all the time
to be here i feel i don't wanna i don't
want your health to be
um
detoriating yourself
i'm so sorry what you need to sleep or
so it's okay it's
okay i'm eating right now i'm eating it
what lasagna
oh give me what happened to the lasagna
give me stream too short excuse me it's
five hours and now we're super chat
reading we're gonna
if we're
if we do some tangents we're gonna be at
seven hours and you call that short
i'm on tv mom yeah
so proud of you my child so proud of you
myron version of telltale heights would
have been amazing we can still switch i
will eventually grow tired of this don't
worry i i usually grow tired of my bgm
after a while
[Music]
but uh uh i want to say even though i
was raging a lot um i am enjoying this
game okay so don't worry
[Music]
some
some things are just kind of savage
uh almost unforgivable but it's okay
i can deal with it
but some crazy things happen today
this is my birthday i don't know what to
do what you should you should go
have some cake meet some friends if you
can
maybe go do karaoke or go shopping treat
yourself to something or
i don't know play your favorite game you
don't have to go outside
you wouldn't let the baby game beat you
i was just trying to make the baby feel
the baby game feel better about itself
stop the game
[Music]
i think
i think the reason
[Music]
why i had such an impression of it being
much easier
but i do think it's still a baby game
still
still easy easy dungeons easy enemies
i'm just acting very stupid
um
i think it's easier than i present it to
be but i think the problem is that i
watched someone's playthrough of this
game a long time ago um
and
that guy you know he's very very good
when it comes to
nintendo games zelda games pokemon games
he just knows what he's doing
and um he just made it look easy i think
easier than it is
he didn't have problems with anything
yeah
i think maybe that that's why i had an
even
simpler impression of the game not the
og the the new one i think
uh
and the no i only saw the new one not
the og i didn't see a playthrough of the
og
he's too good at it yeah
kopcho why oh my
oh my god
[Music]
when you pacifier next time to play this
bubble bubble game you know what i will
i will i will
it gives off the air that is a vegan but
it can get pretty difficult whether it's
intentional because of junk
jack i say jack it is
huh or you must be roasting me again i
don't even want to rake it super chat
game looks fun and more fair than
skyward can't wait for cruise oh wait
you're not even roasting me you're not
even roasting me that is uh unexpected
but gross is unfortunately not gonna
show up
i think
i think bruce is not gonna come by
oh can i show you guys i'm not oh
i'm not gonna
um
wait what
not going to uh play it and watch it
together with you guys now but i do want
to leave you guys with a link
uh
of the idol song that i talked about
here it is
please watch it later or watch it on the
side now if you want to
it's very cute my oshi is in there
she's so cute
these are so cute so cute
monkey dance monkey dance
[Music]
yes please enjoy okay so
we have to read some super chats from
the last stream where i turned on the
super chats again
but besides that only the ones from
today
yeah we're pretty caught up uh
this time
doing pretty well
[Music]
watching it now thank you okay good job
you guys are oh
a really
a really unexpected person
just messaged me
um
as a celebrity
[Laughter]
a celebrity that i've known from uh
before hello live
[Music]
just messaged me asking if i'm in japan
right now
now i'm unfortunately not in japan right
now what do you want
i am i would call
that person a celebrity
the current
no
natalie dumb i wish i wish i had the the
phone number or whatever of natalie
[Music]
no no yeah it is very random um
nope i left
a year
ago
approximately
yeah i am unfortunately sometimes i wish
i was still in japan but on the other
side i'm also pretty happy to not be in
japan because i like my apartment and i
love being with my cats and i like
having my friends and my family
um in a reachable
distance yeah is it megan fox chris
pratt it must be chris pratt
[Music]
is so popular oh my god i'm so popular
yeah
adam said oh my god john cena
no
stop
it's not that not that famous but
you guys uh i think a lot of you guys
have seen
the person although i will not say the
name
i will not say the name
someone well known in in the
in the
anime
weeb
world
i would say
mario from
nintendo
gordon ramsay
what
no
no no no it's no not
not no no not the trash taste people no
no one is saying anything correct and
you may stop
i am not in contact with
the
trash-taste people and unfortunately
also not me
not with miyamoto-san or pewdiepie or
david attenborough
[Music]
man
would be nice to be friends with david
attenborough
burrow
lisa
[Music]
takes you castle cruel
exactly no okay you guys are just
throwing out random names out here as if
as if i would know them as if
question is it true that if you um pee
on
a
wheat
that it's like a pregnancy test
because it showed that on the great is
that also
because uh catherine the great had to
pee
on wheat every morning in order to prove
whether or not she's pregnant or not and
one day
it bloomed right after her peeing on it
and that meant that she was breganante
and she indeed was
prego
it works sometimes really
fascinating i just find something
fascinating that the people used to
believe in or used to do back in the day
200 300 500 years ago it's true really
what kind of transition i just wanted to
get out of that topic and that was what
i couldn't think of
i googled it looks like it was a real
thing what
holy how did they even find out
i guess
how would you find that
a pregnant woman would just casually
um pee on wheat for no particular reason
and then would see it blooms and be like
oh wait what the why did it just
bloom
is that how they found out
that is weird
they peed on everything until one word
i don't think that must have been a
coincidence an accident kiana is public
grenade
[Music]
a grenade
humans are weird yeah but so it's
fascinating also they had catherine the
great have a a frog on her belly
um for
an hour or longer in order to
ensure that the baby is gonna be healthy
or so i don't know
she had there's a lot of frogs in my
life recently
maybe that's why i dreamt
you know what maybe that is really why i
dreamt of the frog because i saw the
frog in
on catherine the great's belly
[Music]
like the first person to drink helmet
what were they doing to the cow
[Music]
i mean
a cows
um
what do you call it in english a cow's
thingy
it just looks like
i think it's understandable that you
would try to squeeze it because it looks
like something's in there and then it
looks i mean especially if you if you
look at the cow babies drinking from it
then you would maybe assume that there
is milk in there
others others yeah yeah yeah i have
milked a cow before when i was uh
when i was in elementary school
did i tell you that before we went on a
on the countryside weekend week i think
it was a whole week
um
yeah it was very common in my
in my
country i think to take
uh classes of children on a week to the
countryside for a week
and then teach them some like um you
know countryside stuff like uh how to
milk a cow and how to make uh butter out
of
milk
and stuff
yeah
that that's how and that's how i once
made butter before
but i don't think i could do it anymore
yeah yeah it's pretty pretty cool i have
fond memories of it that was fun
i mean i think that was
i think i was originally a little bit
disgusted by you know touching the
others i don't think i wanted to touch
them
but i had to
i did that on the school trip oh
and that was that was a nice school trip
other school trips were mostly like um
uh like i had a
school trip where we went skiing and
then i had a school trip where we went
to crow asia i think and a school trip
where we possibly went to italy
i think
uh see that's the cool thing about being
in on in school as a student in europe
a lot of the school trips go to like
different countries
i know of school trips to england but i
was not part of it
hmm
yeah
but but the travel to i remember to
travel to croatia was a pain in the ass
because we took like a we rented a bus
and we were driving for the night and i
just could not get comfortable in my
seat at all
i was doing some really weird
poses
in my seat
trying to sleep and when i say weird it
was really weird
it felt endless that bus ride felt like
it was never ending and that's actually
where i got my first mood
ring and that was when there was a huge
craze about it there was this one shop
that was selling the mood rings and me
and a bunch of the other girls got one i
think
and then we were all like oh what mood
are you in right now what's your color
what's your color oh mine is this color
in scotland we never really went
anywhere i'm jelly
but but scotland is beautiful and um and
you probably went on some beautiful
trips within scotland right
and the thing is you know austria
doesn't have a beach like an ocean
which is uh why we went like to croatia
in order to go to an
ocean but scotland has an ocean right so
you don't have to
go to a different country just to get to
a
beautiful sandy beachy ocean
for us austrians you know it's
it takes a bit more than just uh
going to the other side of the island or
the country
but i do want to visit scotland yeah
one day i want to visit all all the all
the places get my friends and spend
apartments actually
yes
um my brother and my sister
and my sister's boyfriend they went on a
uh they visited croatia
um
i think last year or so
uh and they told me that they went to
that city where they filmed a game of
thrones
and apparently like
you know it used to be a freaking normal
city
a boring city not many people not many
tourists at all
but then after the whole game of thrones
craze they got so many tourists that now
literally every apartment it
turned into an airbnb
we got actually yeah
so now everything is an airbnb
everything you can make so much money by
opening an airbnb down there
yeah dubrovnik i guess
i guess i'll check it out as well
someday because i'm quite a fan of uh
game of thrones
[Music]
and i also want to check out the places
where lord of the rings was filmed for
example it's
[Music]
it is uh it is really good business in
austria in austria uh uh the sound of
music was filmed
and
uh it was mostly filmed in salzburg
i think and they got a lot of tourists
because of that
there's so many americans
especially americans
visit especially
especially americans specifically
americans you guys like that
movie a lot apparently who come to
saxbook and uh i want to see where sound
of music was filmed
it's fascinating to me
very fascinating
[Music]
also have a lot of tourists thanks to
mozart
mozart's house
i had to say americans several times
there yes
it to be popular yeah have you guys seen
okay who here has seen the sound of
music wait we if you remember and he
wants to watch along then you probably
have
bad question because i made a lot of you
watch it even if you haven't watched it
since before it's bad question never
mind that
[Music]
sound over music
is
[Music]
i thought so i thought a lot of you
probably have seen it before
[Music]
what
there are these are a few of my favorite
things
lasagna
oreo shakes burgers and fries
pizza and chocolate and
thick riser spice
um
nutella and hot chocolate ice cream with
cookies and cream
i could eat so much i hope it ain't a
dream
i'm trying to rhyme here
these are review of my favorite things
what will make sense favorite things in
illinois last night okay what
what she did
oh
she did
it was sick
i like to say it was sick
that's like
that's a interesting way to describe the
say so
innocent
beauty of roommate singing it was
sick
it was so sick bro
[Music]
so a little bit from this stream first i
have no idea where i left off
does anyone know where i left off
where i started actually because i went
from top to bottom
i guess
did someone know or am i oh now
cause i don't remember and didn't write
it down
after dinosaur
oh
[Music]
ginger ranger which one daughter or
ginger ranger
[Music]
let's see
i see it i think i see it there together
[Music]
i think
this must be it yeah yeah
def loop no no official scream
compilation huh kidding as an fps did i
not read this before as an fbs enjoy
it's been awful entertaining to watch
you play like watching a baby figure out
how to walk i feel like i read this
before simply adorable take it easy and
don't worry too much just have fun have
i read this before
i feel like i did
uh
maybe i did maybe that was
where i need to continue
after this one
thank
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're awesome thank you you are awesome
too
mwah big kiss for you thank you for your
support and your generous super chat
thank you very much
got him
oh man
thank you
carefree project channel thank you soon
[Music]
not sure how to read your name one of
these it must be it hopefully
[Music]
let me follow up on the kfb mc thing the
current plan is convert the multiplayer
map into a single player one and upload
it to viva lakia there is down there it
is downloadable and playable as a single
player world it just needs some work oh
okay okay let me know when it's finished
i don't know if i would play it on
stream but um having it as an option
for the future is definitely good
and you send an extra run just some
extra yeah the world is 30 gigabytes
simpkins are busy a lot also writing a
small guide for it if we are we are at
kfp the office on twitter yeah
i know of you guys
amy you guys want to check it out too
the last time i saw that world it's the
same world right that we're talking
about the one that i checked out in the
browser
it was pretty impressive yeah it was
huge
i could go on and on and on and on over
long distances and keep on finding like
new little villages and stuff or big
villages actually with big towers and
stuff
[Music]
it was pretty impressive
same world ah
the one with the big sword yeah
i love you kiara thank you
i missed pistachios
let me get out the translator
[Music]
this is my first super chat and i wanted
to tell you i finally got your birthday
emerge noise i absolutely love it all i
also want to ask what you think about
the people that never comment i also
kind of replied to this
i feel like i might have just picked it
up
randomly in the chat huh yeah no problem
at all of course
feel free to write as much or as little
as you want in the chat uh although i do
like seeing an active chat
so
i would i would recommend you to not
lurk and there's a lot of people who
came
out of their lurking shadows and then
started writing comments and they look
back on their lurker past and they say
i'm happy that i stopped lurking i'm
happy that i
um
that i uh started interacting with
everybody because it's so much more fun
yeah so maybe something to think about
thank you for getting my merchandise i
hope you can get lots of use out of it
it is fun to comment right and then you
feel so happy when your comment is red
isn't it isn't that the best thing
[Music]
streams crash when you keep the chat
open oh yeah yeah that is kind of
annoying it's not very stable sometimes
especially on the phone maybe
that is understandable
brandon wood darkish in blue dancing oh
blue that was a rainbow thank you blue
for the
wordless speechless
uh
muted
red
rainbow super chat thank
how did i you that thank you so much
very very kind of you
you showed us a beautiful rainbow
in
a really really dark winter
night thank you i'm getting so hungry
can i get a snack guys
can i make myself a sandwich
really quickly
and an idol meeting
[Music]
i need something to fill my belly to get
through this okay okay brb
tell everyone that i'll be rb peace
[Music]
so
hmm
[Music]
thank you for waiting
um
[Music]
hi
i was um
before the before the stream i ordered
some
because i didn't have time to go out to
get breakfast so i ordered breakfast
[Music]
which was mostly bread and um this type
of bread we call
it's like a
it's like a baguette but not quite like
the shape is long like a baguette but
it's um it gets thinner on the on the on
each end of it and there's like salt
pretty thick salt
stuck on top of it is it's very uh
crunchy
very good
bread
and i put some salami inside of it
um
[Music]
oh no i don't mean the time i know
there's some um there's a sad standard
snack that's like thin and long and
brown and all that but nope
um not the snack i mean the bread
[Music]
not loud
mm-hmm
[Music]
well i'll show you
so the confusion here is
that there is a
there's a popular
cheap snack
that looks like this
right
this one is called
[Music]
but then there's
a non-snack
which is actually i guess
mostly austrian
uh bread
but i think you could get it in germany
too
and uh that is uh
it looks like
this
but this has the same name
but it's bigger and a thicker
[Music]
they have the same name i guess
and i'm eating this right now
now
very good
[Music]
hmm
would you look at that holy
it's so good looking isn't it
[Music]
smoothie just looking at me
i want bread too no you don't want bread
believe me cat
i'm almost done i only actually i only
cut off one half of it
i'm almost done with it
um
[Music]
news
no chips with sandwich oh my god
that's an interesting observation i've
seen that um
did i say i don't know
in a tv show i think so
um
i guess in america
when people make themselves a sandwich
they use with potato chips so where
where where do they do that
i wouldn't do that
i don't see potato chips as a basic
component of a sandwich
like a society sandwich no no no
[Music]
oh my god the tips of the bread are so
crunchy
[Music]
i usually don't have a side to a
sandwich but if anything maybe a salad i
don't know
potato chips as a side that's like so
unhealthy
that's not no you can't do that
it looks like a lot of you guys do it
hmm
[Music]
um
we got chips with school lunches a
lot i think as a child
i would have been happy about that
having potato chips
as part of my school lunch i would have
liked that probably
um
okay i'm done eating
and violet is hidden right violin is
sick
the violin be rocking
what are you eating did you just arrive
i literally just showed everyone
pictures of what i was eating
mean
although i do remember one time in japan
i went to
a little little little small
mini restaurant where they served i
think
kind of like american style
uh
burger sandwich and hot dogs and stuff i
think and i ordered one of those i'm not
sure which one it was
and they did serve it with potato chips
which i thought was very interesting but
the potato chips were tasty i
think they were um
self-made by them not just out of some
package from the convenience store
they tasted very fresh
self-made potato chips are really good
so i support that i guess i think it's
yeah i ate it once like that and it's an
it's interesting but i wouldn't like
always like have it as a side it sounds
uh unhealthy
i love eating potato chips though once i
get started i can't stop myself either
i just eat potato chips on on its own
like
yeah not together with a sandwich
but anyway
to eat their own there are there are
weirder things weirder ideas where their
food combinations like um
uh what was it oh yeah putting potato
fries in uh
like a for example at mcdonald's in one
of those ice creams
who does that
okay but i've never tried it before i
need to try it once because people say
it's really good
but i don't wanna i don't wanna
ruin my potato fries and my ice cream
like that
you guys do that
surprisingly good yeah a lot of people
say that i kind of believe you
fries in the milkshake no don't ruin the
milkshake like that
no no no potato
[Music]
we don't have wendy's here
i see
[Music]
um
it's not that's also not even weird
there's
that was a
not a good example it's not weird at all
you know that is actually pretty common
as far as i know the ice cream and the
potato fry thingy it's not
not that weird i'll give you that
i've heard many more weirder things that
i can't think of right now
i draw the line in bacon big shake so
thank god
hallelujah
fried oreos what the
wait what what does that remind me of
what does that remind me of something of
oreos that i've seen that i saw
yesterday i think
what was that something of oreos
what was
that i think i ordered
oreos oreos oreos
oreos
man now you got me thinking
no oreo oreo shake that's not what i'm
thinking of but that's amazing i love me
some oreo shakes
[Music]
okay okay okay
cat or fear or are you scared of cats
thank you soon thank you no need to be
scared of cat's joke cats are cute
[Music]
thank
sending a super chat super early today i
think i beat total son as the first
super chat is
oh yeah
used to always uh
send like the first super chat of the
stream tonight still watches the streams
i think but they're just like
not at good times for him anymore i
think
but yeah that used to be a thing slow
very slow
thank
i have to tell you that i recently
betrayed you
uh-huh
confess your sins to me my child
i could no longer resist the tentacle
priestess and joined her cult as well
still you are the most beautiful phoenix
i have ever seen in my kami osu so i
hope you can forgive me
that is okay
that is that is
i guess tolerable
um you have not strayed afar too much
and you're still
a loyal kfp
i suppose if i'm your kami austria then
you would always always always
prioritize me right yes yes yes yes
okay
oh wait for ziggler you changed your
name
you got a title from me
oh well that's okay well i mean ina is
very enjoyable she's a sweet sweet
sweet
person with so many talents
yeah permission to be diddy no not
really no not really but i know you're
already a dd anyway i know i know i know
i know you have a different aussie too
i'm aware
i mapped straight a bit too far
[Music]
uh now you still have kfp in your name
as long as you still have caffeine your
name all is good
to make it
um obvious where you stand um
you're not allowed to be cd but if it
can't be helped and it can't be helped i
can't stop your love if you fall in love
with someone else what can i do
kill that person
i guess i must
dramatic yandere chiara incoming
[Music]
chicken
and the texture
[Music]
foreign
that is a
very charming message there are many
cute and beautiful youtubers but only
one is the greatest and is in the form
of a phoenix i love you kiara
i am the greatest yes
at least in your heart and that makes me
happy thank you
see now the koreans are coming out of
the shadows you start talking korean and
they there they are i thought you were
sleeping
i thought you were sleeping
[Music]
foreign
you're just chilling here hanging out
thank you
oh
it's 4 00 am yeah
it's just a super chat reading don't
don't uh force yourself okay
okay
if you need to sleep you need to sleep
and tomorrow is another work day
probably for a lot of you
um for me it's just uh just a day for
lasagna
[Music]
what is this super chat he has my face
on his uh
profile picture
[Music]
here and
is a traffic light chicken
why
snowing cheese chicken oh
why am i a traffic light chicken what
does that mean what's that man
huh
[Music]
what does that mean
music stops
because my hair changes colors
i don't think they even fought that far
oh profo thank you for the red super
chat thank you
i have to tell you something kiwawa i
might repeat myself and i'm sorry about
that but i need you to know
i like to hear that listen up guys he
has something important to tell you
i need you to know that you're my one
and only ashi and thanks to you my sides
and stomach hurt from laughing every day
you're the best place that would change
oh not only his number one his one and
only he says
and no this was not a proof
not a confession of love to genma it was
to me
how it's supposed to be
bropher is a girl
have i been
[Music]
um
yes you are what
i thought i thought pearl throw
because uh
of a
like a like a german um
german male name like florian orazovask
sorry
okay
girl let's go
thank you
ah
you are very welcome as a girl as well
sorry for making that mistake
i've i will remember this
for fro
[Music]
what a twist oh my god
oh my god
cute
yes i guess i assumed fro froze gender
cancel me cancel me
[Music]
oh my god
thank you though here's a kiss
from girl to girl
[Music]
but you must you must always assume that
everyone
in the internet is actually male you
know everyone who
looks
female
you must assume
everyone who has a female mmorpg
character you must assume that there are
actually a guy
no
[Music]
although it wasn't from rapport i think
i heard that from her
said i think that she
used to make uh male characters instead
very interesting
uh
so
i i always made female characters
because they are pretty and i wanted to
uh
look like myself sometimes or like like
a better version of myself
[Music]
oh that's what mmrpg stands for oh
i i am i'm a girl i'm a girl i'm a gamer
girl
i'm a gamer girl specifically
don't doubt my existence as a gamer girl
please will you
zero 27
[Music]
i'm not a traffic light chicken
if anything i'm a traffic light phoenix
[Music]
thank you
i was surprised to see you again
yesterday thank you for coming by
to my stream again i guess you were very
very busy
but nice to see you again and as you say
nice to see some things never change
yeah
uh what was i doing at that moment
[Music]
i don't i don't recall maybe i was just
tangenting during a super chat rating
but
yeah kiwawa has a lot of
uh
traits that never seem to change
there's no shame in using girl
characters i understand because they're
cute
why would you not use them
i was when i was hanging out with movie
when i was uh talking to smoothie yeah
yeah yeah yeah that happens uh
still
every time in each stream
you can't stop me from doing that
unfortunately
i have to do it
i have to show her all the love that i
have and more
anyway thank you this logaria
hope to see you again soon sometime
thank you and hope you think well and
had a good journey into the year 2022
yeah
all the best to you dragon castle thank
you for the pink super chat
[Music]
it says to be able to commute to work
with the manager in life is really the
best when night and day are reversed
yeah i guess so i mean my my
life
uh in my life my day and night has been
reversed for or not completely reversed
but partially reversed for a long time
wait traffic like phoenix must mean
you're so beautiful you stop the traffic
i hope for that person that that's what
you meant because
that is
a beautiful
explanation
anyway back topic dragon castle yeah and
i don't know as long as you're happy
about it i wish i could fix my sleep
schedule
but so you seem to enjoy it so
yeah as long as it's not
doing any damage to your health
let's do it let's go to work together
yeah
yeah yeah
thank you
thank you for watching my streams
whenever you can okay thank you for
thinking of me all the love to you no
one who comes at me
thank you
for the pinky
oil baldi and
bobby
you back or is that just like a small
break
i like this chicken this chicken can
have my tank
this this is my my french tank person
right did you did you get a break or
something
attack commander yeah
yo
oh
um do we have weekends off or so
lucky
glad you could catch the stream
we miss you we miss you here
thank you for
stopping by and saying hello valden
thank you
hope everything is going well over there
yeah
thank you so much
[Music]
i'm going over to the super chats from
today's stream
um
[Music]
uh if you're wondering what the other
deaf super chats are i already read them
yesterday
next up this one
um
[Music]
so
cute do you guys want the png for this
one
i have the png
if you want it
you want it do you want it do you want
it
i think i saved it
there it is here take it take it save it
right click
right click save it
what's he saw
take it
i guess i'll try to upload it on on
twitter
if i remember
ah how about that will be my ending post
you collect them yeah some of you guys
seem to collect pngs i guess especially
people who make clips as well
[Music]
just to say how much i appreciate kev
thank you i appreciate you for being
here today
[Music]
she's pretty dope i agree
i'm not sure who who my wife would be
though
um
i'm not sure i'm not sure which zelda
with my
would be my wife
i know you keep on asking this question
you never give up to you
you're never gonna give up with this
question huh
i'm gonna do your favor
i don't have a favorite eye color
my favorite hair color maybe would be uh
for like anime characters probably like
white or silver
yeah there you go
now you can't stop asking that question
[Music]
uh you're released from your services
oh my god
[Music]
1.31 subs we did it
we've grown once again
it felt a bit quicker than usual
is it just me
trevor g dankeshen what is this a pinky
together it's a pinky let me read who
thought kiwawa so you're going to be
fluttering around coho linda isle island
in link's awakening wait did you change
your profile picture
and your name to mummy's basket owl i
don't know what to think about that why
are you now constantly
in the basket of mermaid
when you should always be close to
[Music]
oh me bros are i i mean you mean not
right now but in general yeah yeah
well trevor g
explain that to me
i mean yeah that owl is cute
so cute honestly what the man
such a cute basket owl
you better come back to me immediately
though
otherwise i'll have to steal the basket
from mummy
[Music]
birds have a feather flock together
i knew i knew when mumei's uh debut was
announced i knew that trevor g
would become a dd
and i would have to put a leash on him
he's an owl enthusiast i cannot hold him
back he wants to be with the owls
i knew it
understandable though i was so
cute man
uh
now i understand why the chickens are
starting to act so violently
a courageous lass has come to wake the
wind face
i do hope you enjoy your time in
this beautiful ephemeral toy box as you
aim to wake the windage it'll be easy
for a well-spiced and seasoned warrior
like you right panic attack to victory
toddy
i'll be hooting for you what
yeah in this um in this game once again
actually not only in this one in a lot
of zelda games there's like an owl
talking to you isn't there like in
ocarina of time
it's also an owl that keeps on coming by
and saying hello
and then here as well
what about other zelda games
why are owls always the ones to bring
the messages and explain
what to do
why is it always ours
not only not only in the
zelda games why aren't owls even
considered to be so wise and smart
what is it about owls that makes people
think that
where does that come from why do they
represent wisdom
one one
they never taught me anything
mummy definitely is not teaching me
anything it's more like i'm teaching her
she forgot everything like how the
does she represent wisdom
she forgot everything
effin
athena who is is that a greek goddess
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
i don't know she used to know you see
my mane is bird print too yeah so
hmm
okay i guess we're just gonna believe
the great people
and roll with them as they continue to
paint owls and something really wise
while right next to us we have a perfect
example of an owl called mummy
who doesn't strike me is quite so wise
but
if the greeks say so then it must be
true
[Music]
sorry i'm just roasting my man but you
know i love mommy
cute
cute mommy is this your longest stream
no no no i did 12 hours before
[Music]
yummy with some potatoes
and some gravy roasted moomae with some
gravy and and potatoes
[Music]
i will ask google how to pronounce this
i think even google doesn't really know
how to pronounce it
[Music]
is that about right
did i get it right absolutely nailed it
nailed it
[Music]
what do we have here
um
[Music]
oh
as if it's nothing thank you very much
and happy birthday to you
happy birthday
yeah
yeah yeah
congratulations
i guess by now it's already past
midnight
uh so maybe it's not your birthday
anymore in your country but in my
country it's still your birthday
yeah
happy
[Music]
i hope you will have a great year ahead
of you
with lots of fun and success and
happiness okay take care of yourself
thank you for your support
green wilder thank you for the red super
chat
new year resolution i green welder thank
you kiara for my lawful potential
to follow and serve from this day
forward for better focus for richer for
poor in sickness and in health until
death does us part i will love and honor
you all the days of my life
green wilder
come here come here you must come here
come here green wilder
come here
come here where are you here where are
you where are you
where are you
how sweet yes i will be your potential
i will be your tenta
until the very end
until death
hurts us
oopsie no yeah i guess uh put a ring on
that just kidding no no no rings we're
not getting married you i'm just being
your tension
chet chet put a ring on that
everybody put all the rings you got on
this hand
you'll be fine
and
come on
come on put a ring on it
if you like it on your shirt
[Music]
you accept onion rings you mean
onion rings
no
no thank you
well thank you that was such a sweet
sweet super chat i'm flattered thank you
yes i've seen
except bakeries no i don't like bagels i
don't like that i like donuts but i
don't like bagels who's who's with me
who's with me
speaking of i really want to eat some
donuts man
this would be so nice
also what am i going to eat tonight
donuts would be nice
donuts
i want i want the donuts from the
special donut place man
can i order donuts
can i order i've been craving donuts
since like a few days ago
but let me see if i can order donuts
[Music]
oh my god
there's no donuts
[Music]
wait i'm not giving up in
sends donuts but i don't mean
mcdonald's donuts
no
no i mean donuts donuts
[Music]
yeah mcdonald's and and burger king and
so on they have donuts as a dessert but
it's not the same thing
it's not the
same thanks chad for sending me donuts
are you a problem
[Music]
because i've been craving things lately
pickle pickles
so stupid is this the stupidest joke
everyone
[Music]
stop it
that joke was funny in that video
but like reusing it
i feel so stupid by using it
because there's some people who probably
don't even know what what the that
joke is about
i'm like
[Music]
pregnant
oh we have some stupid chad
oh man i am i'm losing my energy have
you noticed i'm i'm just
i feel like i feel like i'm melting
again
[Music]
my mind my brain is melting
i need some chocolate yes i do yes i do
but i think i only have like some rye
swamp
i mean i have some i still have leftover
chocolate in my
in my like uh advent calendar you know
the one with the 24 doors
i still have chocolate in there
normally when i was younger i would i
would even open the doors ahead of time
to get more chocolate
but this time
i was
so
uninterested
like the chocolate from the calendar it
didn't
it didn't catch my interest
yeah i eat less chocolate
than i do than i did before
maybe i should finish it
yeah i have leftovers from my advent
calendar unbelievable inconceivable
i i don't know what happened i i've
grown up i am adult
[Music]
that chocolate is always bad it's not
bad though it's from it's a lint
chocolate
calendar it was pretty good i ate a
couple
but uh
yeah
let me get one let me get one let me get
one
i brought the whole thing
oyster
okay
uh
which one
oh
i'm gonna eat the one from door 24
because it had a
an angel in it
a crisp
[Music]
chocolate
not as good as a donut but okay and you
know what i'm gonna eat ice cream
instead
after the stream oh jen are you doing a
rainbow oh my god thank you
thank you
hmm
it's not expired chocolate doesn't
expire that fast
[Music]
one
yes i will have actual food i had actual
food before chocolate i had a sandwich
[Music]
i said i would get sick of this
eventually but i'm not getting sick of
it at all
it's so good the music is so good
but we should choose a different one
anyway
no that that puts everyone to sleep
everyone will fall asleep by listening
to that
[Music]
okay well listen to this one now
[Applause]
it's instants
[Music]
typhon thank you for the red super chat
wow
pinto here's my birthday bonus yesterday
as i move closer to being a true bald
eagle
thanks alert that sounds very positive
thanks for the unintentional gift of a
jrpg stream best gift i could ask for
even if i'm stuck inside due to a
snowstorm what you've already made this
great birthday for me this a great
birthday for me it's really best boss
thank you
snowstorm
it's a snowstorm where do you live
alaska
damn
[Music]
was it that much snow
is it like completely
like uh shutting you inside because it's
like
10 meters tall and you can't even open
your door or something that would be
funny it's like like in a
in a tv show
eastern
oh
well
enjoy the snow while it's there maybe go
skiing or something well happy birthday
let me sing for you
ah
i want to sing in the rhythm of the
music but
happy birthday to you typhon happy
birthday
[Music]
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
and there he flies
like an eagle
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
take care of your health
and enjoy your wonderful birthday even
if you can't go outside it's a time to
do something inside i guess uh aka
watching kiwami's dreams
watching your favorite movie uh eating
some popcorn some buttered popcorn or
whatever caramel popcorn
yeah
hanging out with your pets
having a good time
while being inside and safe yeah get
cozy in a blanket with some cozy socks
and order some yummy food although
um
f to the delivery person who has to
deliver that in the snowstorm
yeah well thank you so much for all your
love and your support i hope to have you
along my side for much much longer until
the next birthday and maybe even longer
yeah thank you so much typhin i wish you
the best i'm glad that i could be your
boss
yeah
um um
rare find it dankeshan not a good
username for your sixty donkey shane
fava duncan
[Music]
thank you happy birthday early birthday
but you say tomorrow is your birthday
and you want my blessing well there you
go happy early birthday
hey cake thank you for the red super
chat hanging cake are you still here
yeah that's me this time
i think in the last adventure in the
last zelda adventure
i called myself
chihuahua maybe
but this time
this time i'm blinky and i'm becoming
one with link
together we're stronger
i will become as link
thank you
for being part of it i hope you're
enjoying this
stream so far
and i'm glad we were able to pick up
another zelda game um
now and it's not a super super long one
so
it's not gonna be
obnoxiously following us until the end
of time
yeah
i think it's a
good game to go back into the usual
kiwawa rhythm where i do a lot of long
long long streams
however i still want to keep on mixing
in shorter streams into the weeks as
well of course as per usual
it's also better for my own health and
all that so
yeah
but
do you guys feel it do you guys feel the
earth shaking because the new pokemon
game is coming up
you know what's gonna happen all of her
life is gonna play pokemon again
but i'm excited because this time it's
gonna be a completely new experience for
everyone
because there is no og to it it's a new
game
so we can like
play together guys
yeah
our chaos let's go
i'm excited for it
thank you cake did i give you a kiss
here's the kiss
i always forget if i gave someone a kiss
or not pathetic engineer thank you for
the pinky thank you
and let me see what that says
[Music]
i think it means according to google it
means fight inside
are you telling me to fight
i'm trying i'm trying the game was
bullying me a lot but
with your mental support
i was able to
do three dungeons at least yeah
[Music]
snake mario thank you for the red super
chat hi chiara first of all i'm really
excited to watch you play this the
original was one of my favorite games
growing up and i had a lot of fun with
the remastered oh were you not as
triggered as i was
also i'm proud to say i finally decided
to become a member of kfb happy to be
here i love you oh
you joined are you an egg now
welcome egg you know what to do
everybody we need to haste the egg by
dropping it on the floor and see if it
breaks
just kidding just kidding just kidding
don't drop it it's a real egg it's a raw
egg
don't drop him
be kind to the new egg okay be very kind
and gentle
but thank you for joining i hope you
will enjoy the members only content
next week we're doing a snack box review
only the strongest egg survives
[Music]
and i throw it on the ground i joined
the membership and she threw me on the
ground
eggy's broken hardest too who i am
[Music]
oh thank you i love you too and the kiss
for you
thank you for your support
i hope i am gonna do your favorite one
of your favorite games
justice in my streams i hope so
now that i could use the name 360 thank
you travis
[Music]
you got your birthday merch as well nice
an employee number
[Music]
let me look
[Applause]
[Music]
there you go that's your employee
number please write it down so you don't
forget it
okie dokie
sorry i have a lot of employees i need
to look for the paperwork
[Music]
thank you so much
wait what you gotta
you got a graphic design job oh
nice congratulations on that too that
sounds awesome all the best to you
holy that violin is popping off
nato 77 danke
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
while everyone else is making fun of me
for dying when i said i wouldn't you
clap for me and applaud me thank you
taiji
very sweet of you
[Music]
foreign
the hy is pretty difficult for me to
pronounce for some reason
[Music]
thank you
yup thank you
delusional dreamer thank you for the
pinky
can i get a chance proposal to ask a
question to juggle you asking for a
pinky
oh
question is are you doing hashtag will
catch you and your reaction is case one
don't know go to the usual room case two
don't
do that go to the user in case three
don't do that go to the user room
you want me to send yago to the usual
room
or delta what the go back guards
bring him back into the usual room
speaking of hmm
no yanko
it's probably too busy to hashtag well
cash that guilt but we have to forgive
him
he is
literally my boss boss boss
top top top bus bomb spawn so um
it would probably not be very smart to
send them to the user
i know you yeah that is a very eager
idea from you delusional dreamer but we
have to hold back
we could show him though i wonder what
he would think about it
cocoon
delivium gunner dankuchen black richard
duncan green wilder thank you dead
shrimp thank you inspector from baron
duncan mr casper
[Music]
bicolor
a cat named duncan for the pinky
fall asleep bus will change nugget or
going to the usual room and watch a
carefree training video you fell asleep
[Music]
no no no no no no no
please
sleep
please sleep you you'll be fine i don't
want to um
you know
scare my new
viewers away so quickly so i'm gonna go
easy on you guys
my
my fried buckets and all all those
shrimpkins
and the ones in the uniform they must be
here they must stay but the new eggs
you can you can go to sleep
i want you to think that i am a kind and
sweet for giving potential
and spread awareness of
the great working
conditions at kfp
so that we get more and more employees
so let them know that you can sleep at
any given time
[Music]
totally true 100
i mean as an egg you it's like the best
thing anyway right because you're right
now under my butt
getting warmed and heated
how could you not fall asleep when it's
so cozy under my butt inside that egg
coziest place to be in the whole wide
world
[Music]
wasn't even that bad but okay it doesn't
mean it's your birthday today chelsea
[Music]
happy birthday chelsea
apparently
chelsea's
girlfriend
uh drew
chelsea uh uh an etsy cheeky erotic
piece of art of myself for her birthday
[Music]
naruto
what a great birthday present oh
[Music]
happy birthday
celebrate yourself will ya
stay healthy
kara ji tangashin red zimmer's dunkin
darwin award
wait what was that about
who should be awarded to kfb darwin the
one with the darwin award
[Music]
what's a darwin award
i don't remember what we were talking
about
right after the golden armored monster
hunted moment
ah
oh
when i died
i died uh
yeah i died
a stupid death once again
the most
the stupidest
death ever
[Music]
you give it to someone who does
life-threatening things ah
i see
when somebody accidentally kills
themselves through something dumb oh
yeah that's me
thank you i will happily accept the
award thank you
thank you um my speech you want to speak
speech speech sweet speech speech speech
uh sure um um
[Music]
i would like to uh thank kfp
uh for making this possible
um although
um i do want to say
i am an entertainer i i could totally
play these games much better and avoid
all of these stupid accidents if i
wanted to
um
but in the end i do this for the content
let's go
yes
[Music]
oh chicken thank you for the red super
chat thank you thank you
hey mika tokyo mikael
if you talk about that one-eyed slime
absolutely worst enemy i've ever
encountered
maybe not maybe not maybe there were
worse ones but this one triggered me
really hard
thank you though
thank you
[Music]
thank you the narwhals king duncan happy
is a true entertainer and the master of
immersion in order to create exactly
content and give us the full experience
she's playing this baby game with the
skill of a newborn baby
[Music]
yes i mean i wouldn't exactly say
newborn baby maybe more like a toddler
or
maybe even um
kindergarten kid
maybe at least kindergarten come on
come come on
hey hey
hey please
thank you though for the the kind words
yes i am and detainer and um
don't be modest
i don't know how i'm being modest
was that really that bad
[Music]
game looks fun and more fair than
skyward start you can't wait for gru's
to show up yeah yeah yeah
i i do feel like i mean obviously the
controls are much easier i did have
troubles with that one boss to like
dash through the middle but besides that
the controls are
obviously easier because motion controls
are on on the switch is just
[Music]
horrible with that sword no
it was a horrible
horrible
experience
[Music]
but uh
yeah
enough nothing
nothing bad to say about skyward sword
either though it was a great game
both both are great games oh zelda games
are great games i'm happy to play
another one on my channel and happy to
see you here as well for it yeah i know
i remember you were a lot around doing
the skyward sword playthrough as well so
thank you for coming back yeah
it's time again for kiwawa to play a new
jrpg on her channel
[Music]
yes
yes i'm excited i know i'm not voice
acting for the new black rock shooter
anime unfortunately
keeper of the flame duncan oatmeal
cookie thank you for the pinky because
my cousin god you know what i had to
stay at home today and i couldn't
celebrate my birthday with friends it's
your birthday too
when i got to spend it with you so i'll
use this chance to thank you for always
working so hard p.s i know it's late but
can i get an omikuji yes you can
of course happy birthday
the least i can do for you is give you
an umi cuisine
let me
start it up really quickly
yeah my fruit hurts man
i was i was thinking about getting my
throat checked my my voice face you know
like like the japanese members do quite
often
because my
my bff she also says she wants me to go
there
since quite some time because like the
job the kind of job that we are doing as
a streamer slash
you know partially
voice
actor
um
it's very very straining on the voice um
[Music]
and i never had a checkup like that
before
but it's it's one of one of the
job categories where
your
uh vocal
thing what do you call them vocal
threads
are
uh
in in on risk in risk
so
pretty
uh
risky
easy to damage them
anyway
oh of course
um
what was i doing
she'll go away
[Music]
oh
okay for some reason
this has a uh
this has a
a filter on top of it but whatever we're
gonna do it let's go
[Music]
oh no
not on their birthday come on
okay this one says small luck
and
be careful that you don't play too many
games um
because it's not good for your health
you should live a
um a lifestyle that is
more
um healthy
[Music]
so be careful of that oatmeal cookie
okay
no i'm not playing too many games
i mean
it's i think it's a good
a good thing to work on
do you play many games oatmeal cookie
do you think you play too many
playlists i think the real message here
is playlist games watch more kiwa
yeah
i think that's the real deep message
that's
what it is senpai trying to convey to us
ah sorry guys i'm losing my energy a bit
more
[Music]
the pink super chat i love you tinter
you're adorable and perfect english is a
little bit hard for me but also it's
time to study for me thank you for your
stream no problem your english sounds
perfect at least in the super chat
thank you for watching today we're
almost ending anyway so don't worry
about it you're not missing out on
anything
thank you for being here today i will
see you on tuesday i think i um i put
out a schedule
on twitter are you following me on
twitter you all should be following on
me on twitter
otherwise here's the schedule i love the
i love the image
so cool i'm like
what does that face say to you guys
it's partially it's like what the
are you doing here now leave me alone
i'm doing i'm cleaning him get out of
here what do you want now
or or like oh my god another
karen get out of here
or it's like uh
what the it's already 4am and i'm
all alone here cleaning can't be what
the
i really like this face
or is it like well i'm alone at kfb and
who is this standing this ghost standing
in front of me
am i gonna be uh is this my last day on
earth today
or or
man it just says so much
[Music]
it says so much
but yeah um on on tuesday i'm not sure
what to play yet i wanted to play
something short but i wasn't sure what
to do either like sliver dot io or
something like that you know
um
yeah
i was thinking
there's a small chance i was thinking of
putting the tuesday stream
on
friday
uh like afterwards like at the same time
but instead on friday
because
then i can
take another day off if i need to
so there is a small chance that that
will happen
no wait
no wait it will not happen actually
never mind it can't happen anymore i was
originally thinking that when i was
making the schedule but it can't happen
anymore because
on friday i am going to um
make some purchases with um
with uh old rmt
all right all right i can't go anywhere
on friday i
think um we're gonna buy some stuff for
for my skiing trip
[Music]
i i told you guys on the community post
because i was so excited but i booked a
vacation with rmt we're going on a
skiing trip
[Music]
no
yeah it will be i think three nights
four days i suppose
and i'm buying the whole equipment i'm
buying
the whole like outfit and
sticks and skis and goggles and
everything have to buy everything please
don't break anything be careful don't
enjoy yourself don't worry it's gonna be
fine i think there are many reasons um
now that now that i talked to rmt she
said that she recently got some new
skiers and that they made a huge
difference because she got like some
really proper ones
that were i don't know really perfect
for her and she said that it made a huge
difference so this could also be one of
the one of the reasons why
skiing in japan
back then was so bad
um i think it was the snow and maybe you
know the rental skis which were just
yeah the
some overused old skis probably
yeah we won't have any accidents
i think
[Music]
um i'll get proper equipment and we'll
go somewhere with great snow
condo
vacation
i think it was really the freaking
snow back then
i missed the stream again well we're
ending it soon so you can watch the
archive yeah yeah
but uh yeah a lot of the things on this
uh
schedule are not 100 sure because i had
to put it out so early in order to
announce the whole talk with jako
um
so the the streaming time for the korean
snack box review might also change a bit
um
[Music]
um but minecraft and zelda are pretty
much set in stone and the appearance on
a different channel is set in stone as
well and whole talk whole talk is
pre-recorded so i could change the
streaming time if i wanted to but i just
felt like um
i should probably keep it on the same
time slot anyway because people know
that it's at this time usually
so it's probably better member stream
will be in the following week because i
had one this week right on monday
right
i think i had one this week right
[Music]
oh sorry i had to crack my my
my lower back
it's at least my lower back which is not
as as damaged yet
then that was nice
uh wait what's my question i want to ask
something i i didn't want to ask him i
wanted to say that i never thought
i never thought that i could really get
jungle on whole talk
[Music]
i never thought he would do that
so it's on was for me like okay possible
but juggle
seemed very impossible to me impossible
to me always but here we are
here we are
with yango coming to holotalk
answering us hopefully a lot of
questions i'm so nervous about it i
think it will be one of the shorter
holotalks
i don't think i can talk longer to him
than one hour
[Music]
and i'm nervous about translating he's
probably gonna use some difficult words
i'm gonna try my best
for
[Music]
i'll have to ask him to like talk slowly
and speak easily
use easy words
it is it is kind of a compliment to my
efforts i feel like it shows that he
um
i mean okay i mean he was on on less
serious uh
um streams as well
before but i do think he acknowledges
um the value of her talk i think he does
yeah yeah
[Music]
i hope he does
and
fried screwdriver
thank you for the pinky
nutella hot chocolate cookies and cream
i could eat so much i hope it's not a
dream
thank you for writing my lyrics down
those ended up pretty good
pretty well
respect to myself
thanks for all you do you fabulous
hard-working lovely tantra thank you too
you guys are always here for me
supporting me with my streams and with
my stupid chit chat i talk so much
all day and you guys are still here
thank you so much for being here book
book
thank you
so sweet of you
looking for the top down
oh final fight off
do your best
don't give up you're strong stronger
than you think you are
brandon wood duncan lorenzo from matajo
and thank you nathan westmoreland thank
you for the pinky i can't i'm not sure
if the rest of kfp have said this but in
my village go to the fishing pond to
fish out an empty bottle to catch
fairies i thought there were no bottles
in this game
no
are there no bottles except for this one
[Music]
no
hmm
i never knew that
i only ever found one maybe it's that
one
you can get free i think in the remake
there is oh
okay
hopefully i remember next time
i hope so i want to check it out
thank you for the tip thank you
pudding channel
and mistress dan kashan
[Music]
why would i let you out of the usual i
gave you a time didn't i
you will be let out according to
the the end of your sentence
[Music]
thank
is
[Music]
[Applause]
is that the same language
[Music]
the greeks really didn't think elsewhere
why is just good hunters athena was the
goddess of wisdom and the hunt the owl
was subbed to represent the honda
portion in a leo of a bow
oh
i see
so it was a it was kind of a
misunderstanding
a projection
owls are not really not even in the
greek world
considered wise it was only athena
uh-huh
uh-huh randy rj dan kishen
i have given you no sentence time
you don't want pop-tarts anymore okay
you can come out but be a good chinking
will ya
be a good chicken
i am very happy to see you my queen my
home is very close to japan known by
others as the kingdom of tea before our
new year
we will have a big meal and we'll get
bonuses
now this prize belongs to my queen
i'm your queen i'm an empress
i'm an empress
thank you pretty close though it's
almost the same thing isn't it
now where where is actually the
difference i would like to learn that
now because i've been
i've been um
i've been calling myself empress and
watching all these historic
shows about uh kings and queens and
empresses and emperors and i don't
wonder let me ask google what's the
difference
between
king
and m
emperor
an emperor is the highest power in the
region he occupies while a king rules
one fairly homogeneous
territory called the national kingdom
emperors often wield power over a fairly
[Music]
heterogeneous territory
ruler of many
nations
ah
[Music]
cool
good to know interesting interesting but
i'm tired
thank you so much alton for your support
and your love
i wish you all the best thank you for
the support thank you for being here
thank you for the beautiful rainbow wait
i missed one there's one more here
it sounds so charming when you say
dankasian raises my blood pressure and
i'm enjoying it i am in baka please
scold me no
what there's nothing bad about it if
you're like me saying
and then a super chat reading must give
you a heart attack damn
i don't want to scold you no
i'm back
i'll kindly scold you
anyway thank you so much for watching
today i hope you had a lovely time
watching my streams
i see you in the next one okay it's a
promise
[Music]
birthday kind of green hair too did i
not
i didn't i didn't
i did i think that came uh
that super chat probably came in before
i
read the super chat
i think so
very kind of you to follow up though
and del star danke said lunch box duncan
employee number
i remember
making me put out like my documents can
cook them at lunchbox
you should ask hr for god's sake
it's uh eight
two
five
there you go
don't forget don't forget it i only say
it once
only once
chickens are you sleepy we can sleep
even if we die hang in there guys just
kiara
oh
you guys are so dedicated
respect i think the rest of kfp is
is really respecting the korean fan base
for
being here at the shittiest times
possible
[Music]
it's a good argument damn you can sleep
when you're dead
it's a good life model actually but i
just really enjoy sleeping so much
the other thing is though that if you
sleep properly then you will live longer
so
you can still sleep when you're dead
but at least you've lived a
healthy life by sleeping enough and not
suffering so much by the lack of sleep
so
check you know what you have my
um you have my my my uh permission to go
to sleep okay so you live longer and
then you are in my services longer
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon my dear korean kfp member
for working so hard fighting
yeah that sounds like something inna
would have said i'll sleep when i'm dead
she definitely said that before
[Music]
thank you
don't worry
thank you soon
[Music]
i'm suffering together with you guys
uh we're almost done eventually
we're almost done
[Music]
skye
all right
[Music]
five
six
nine five six nine
five six nine
[Music]
thank you soon mrs thank you nathan
cotton thank you soon
[Music]
by my witness you know i'm gonna cry no
don't leave me no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
where the did it cut off i was just
crying about genie leaving
huh
where did it cut off
[Music]
eh
i wish you missed that i was
i was going like no titty don't go no
you can't miss you no don't go stay here
don't go you can't
don't go yeah that's what i said
just until friday just until friday that
don't be fooled was the last i heard oh
my god i have to go back a little bit
youtube why
but we're basically done
[Music]
okay did you have fun at summer camp i
guess um
no change of mods this week
um
not today maybe next stream
i hope it's okay for you guys
i thank you for the pinky oh my god last
minute thank you
last minute
wait huh
oh my god oh my god what what's going on
what's going on
[Music]
oh thank you
our first says payday is not too long
from now so here is a little pay dirt to
celebrate that's not dirt that's
beautiful pinky
also doubt doubling this as a tip
there are for sure three empty bottles
all and two of them are actually related
to the areas you've seen damp is got one
and that grave you found has never oh
right now that i can dig do i have to
dig in the grave holy that seems
kind of like a bi thing to do
i don't know if i want to do that i feel
so wrong
damn zelda games what are you teaching
your children to dig up graves that's
not a good thing to teach them
but okay i will i will hopefully find
the bottles because i die so
often that if i
don't get those bottles i might go crazy
[Music]
thank you
and yeah thank you thank you thank you
for the generous support i appreciate it
so much thank you
that's about thank you
[Music]
what i have confirmed with hr that my
employee number is 1066. that's okay
that's okay thank you for checking up on
it patrick and duncan
and oh
wait no stop stop
stop
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
huh
wait out f4 was that button coming
keyboard combination to close the window
all right
it's a legit game just in case
[Music]
very difficult to
no no
out f4
but it's an actual game
[Music]
wait are you
are you kidding me
but if you press alt f4 it will close
the current window right are you like
are you actually trying to recommend the
game to me
alt f4
out four
it's apparently really really difficult
oh
something like jump cake very soon
[Music]
i'm tired
i'm tired i'm tired no more
well thank you for the recommendation
but i'm not a big fan of games like that
if it's like jump
king are you trolling i'm not sure
but you always end your super chat so
kindly with i love your manager so
respectful and so kind
so well i guess
but you you you concern me
you worry me
thank you for the pinky
[Music]
yes zero six zero seven will be your
number
of course
it already it always has been
unseen danke shin
[Music]
professy
thank you
angel thank you for the red super chat i
think someone already has that employee
number angel
i think already someone is using elite
i don't think you can have that one
someone got that already i think
you can have one for every six
thank you now oh my
chi chi chi chi
[Music]
what would you like to find the value of
yeah let's go
let's go
please do
please please do i'm excited
oh okay
[Music]
okay this has been seven hours not even
that long i've i've become weak
new pink super chat you don't want me to
leave julia
they they asked me to let them sleep yet
they don't let me leave oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
okay i can't read it anymore i'm so
tired
[Music]
foreign
um let's sleep korean bros let's
sleep
in thank you
thank you
i will
i will rest now holy so excited for
monday rest day and lasagna day
and uh still i have to work it out
because i have to put together the whole
talk questions within tomorrow
[Music]
what
g men what a great game of the legend of
tenshuki i am not sleeping
[Music]
thank you
let's
let's cuddle with cats in bed now shall
we
almonds
[Music]
evil thank you
and we'll now watch
the great with my kitty cats
let's have a fun week
monday is my day off
uh tomorrow sleep slaps flip-flop yes i
will give you the png
okay
a good night
when i saw me
oh
[Music]
for the
it makes your life longer okay
thank you for the pinky they don't stop
they complain to me about wanting to go
to sleep and yet they spam me with super
shots black virgin thank you no
the manager can't go to work out f4 is a
real game we are the ones who keep the
store manager from leaving work i can't
go nowhere
[Music]
no
thank you for the pinky thank you i'll
go now i'll go now that cow corrects
thank you thank you though what are
you doing
what are you doing
dragon castle what the
[Music]
if you love me let me go says passenger
do you remember
dragon castle
[Music]
we set the manager's workouts no i said
the workouts you can't control how long
i stream like
thank you
still thank you
uh wait what what what
i missed one i feel like
no it's not coming up in hyper chat yet
[Music]
where'd it go
i saw it in obs
ah
i'm in control
i can leave any time i want ah navidad
one more second that's exactly how much
i will give you
and is this violet evil garden just with
a different profile picture again you
are down bad for chloe aren't you
thank you soon take it monkey okay
i'm leaving now i didn't hear when we
started
i'm leaving
you can't feel anything about it i'm
gonna go
listen to me thank you for today
it's gonna quickly quickly leave and
then they can't stop me i'm out of here
swoosh
you hear that sound of me leaving motion
thank you swoosh i'm so far away i can't
i can't i can't hear you anymore
[Music]