[Music]
okay
one two three four
[Music]
but
then we do it like this
[Music]
so cute anymore
[Applause]
[Music]
one two three four
like this
[Music]
one
two three four
[Music]
I wanna watch you
anymore
[Music]
yeah
then we do it like this
[Music]
so cute
look at this
point
[Music]
I'm a genius
oh you did
this now
[Music]
hi everybody
hello how's it growing
no you don't have to say
[Music]
oh my God
who are you this is again
[Laughter]
I didn't know we were playing Among Us
I think we are done because it's kind of
it feels it feels like I'm intruding on
a knitting girls collab did someone get
sick and I had to come in no oh no you
know what you know what no I I have a
bone to pick with all of you I sent you
all a tick tock this morning in our
group chat and nobody said haha Nina
this is awesome yet
yeah I didn't even watch so yeah yeah I
didn't watch it either I didn't watch it
either to be honest but I'll get to it
look at my parents do the same thing
they sent me like tick tocks and it
takes me like five days to watch them
talk
I can't
wow
I've never like been on Tick Tock it's
only when people send me like Tick Tock
links never been on yeah yeah
[Music]
thank you girls
[Laughter]
great I feel amazing anyway of course
how is everybody else doing huh welcome
to this collaboration we organized Lena
put it together yeah
[Music]
I honestly just want to hang out with
the girlies
now should we introduce ourselves
yeah yeah where do we start from
I think we start with you
okay we're not opening my ticket for
admitting to not opening my Tick Tock
first
I was the first to admit it and made it
easier for the others to admit it is
true no I'm not afraid to disappoint
Nina ever we're gonna do a voice voice
like uh volume check as well while doing
this and my viewers are already telling
me Nina is low so I'm raising her don't
worry I've never had anyone tell me that
before
I guess from Whole Life English uh I am
intruding today on this lovely cute
collab with these girls I'm so happy I
put a lot of cuteness into the thumbnail
I think it kind of looks like a purikura
thumbnail yeah it does
it looks like a gross I look like an
insect every time I take particular
because my eyes
is
when we can we someday
yeah thank you
yes one time I asked roseme and rainbow
to take a break with me and they said
later and we never we never took it yeah
I'm actually really sad
um
later next time everyone under the bus
today everyone will pay just airing I
wanted to take lead it's just we said
we'll come back and then we forgot or
something I have one question girls
are you playing uh Uno with controller
now or keyboard and mouse
either
that's how I think you would play and
now I don't know
but the jump in button is for keyboard
do you know I think it's w maybe yeah
it's gonna say it on the screen it's
gonna be like press yeah W or e or
something do you win a lot playing with
controller
um
maybe try changing some awesome keyboard
no that cannot possibly be the reason no
no no anyway I'm gonna throw the the
button of itself introduction over to
foreign
[Music]
what
don't you remember your underwear
I bought them when you guys wanted to
see you know like okay believe it is but
why did you have to say it like I've
missed out on a precious moment it
sounds worse than it is I can hear how
shy you are in your voice I can hear you
like being beat red
I was just taking the back I was like
whoa
you know I told that um story actually
on my stream before yes
[Laughter]
I feel like that's all you'll ever think
about now maybe I shouldn't have she's
never gonna show you her underwear again
oh no yeah you better have ingrained it
in your memory
every little ruffle every little ribbon
yeah
your next art stream you're gonna try to
draw a trip
[Laughter]
it's really cute it was really cute
can we go to the next intro um
how is the volume for everybody so far
you guys yeah
who's quiet who's loud yeah
for the streamers
William good okay resume a little low
I up you I had you a little down
actually so
audio good nice
nice
on next but we did yeah I gave her the
yeah I gave it to you Puma
okay
if an actor were to play me it would be
Jack Black
I like how we made that a thing
you are not Polo what because she's
sorry
is is blonde right now I thought I was
meeting uh uh yeah silver-haired girl
today what the hell oh I am I'm I'm you
know I'm a silver fox you know uh more
foxy than the other Fox the actual fox
that's here yeah that looks more like a
cat as long as that makes you happy
silver foxes looking at the screen and I
think we're all a bunch of little gray
people
except for the actual Silver Fox yeah
except the actual Silver Box
I'm Gray
yeah you don't have a profile picture
I was not on board I did not understand
yeah oh my God you're catching my jokes
when they film
bubble thanks by the way for buying me
Uno oh yeah
welcome did you see my message with it
no
I'm about me Uno even though I had it on
my Xbox
you have Uno everybody
we were scammed both me and Nina we had
to buy it a second time
I have to say this really quietly I feel
like every few months I buy Uno again
and again on both my Steam account and I
genuinely feel like I've bought Uno six
or seven times already yeah I don't
understand where my Uno game is going
okay
oh no I I see what they're doing it's
like it's they're making it realistic
you know in real life like when you use
like your deck of cards like you have to
keep buying it right so like they're
they're just making it realistic you'll
like lose one behind the cow yeah yeah
you'll forget at the park you keep
buying it who is unoing at the park
okay
one day please
my grandma's
surrounded by like squirrels
oh my gosh
who knows so many times and like I don't
understand where my Uno games are going
agreed okay Grandma sounds like you're
using your Uno
oh I think Mr Bigfoot is on to me I
think he's doing it on purpose he's
trying to rob me of my money John Uno
you the game is called Uno you can't
just buy it once you know
hey I thought little red one get it yeah
get it because Uno is one one yeah yeah
do you understand wow wow well next by
dos
[Laughter]
I'm so sorry everyone
uh okay is it my turn yeah
hi honey
no okay if you want a real tone change
hi honey I am Nina kosaka of niji Sanji
Ian's third wave etherea and I must be
in luck today hello everybody it's a
pleasure to be here with you
um I am excited I organized this collab
because I want to hang out with the cute
girls I already opened up some wine I'm
having a nice glass and I'm ready for
all the embarrassing batsuits and all
the fun times yeah
yeah oh my God I haven't heard that's
like debut Nina
is she I feel like that voice is too
powerful you know I try not to use this
whole atmosphere changed
it's fine it's fine I guess I can stay a
little cute but yeah we have a list of
batsu games on the batso wheel I'm not
showing it on screen but there is
um the famous good old baby voice the
grandma police the robot voice like I am
robot let's talk like this could you
demonstrate the other two voices the
first two oh yeah
Park
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's Flawless and everything she does
except this game clearly she just told
us how much he lost
no we will see who has the most cards
left after at that point when the game
rounds we'll have to do about the game
yes no matter how long you I want you
girls to be committed okay oh yeah okay
it's about drive it's about power
uh you when you have a seven you switch
cards with a person of your choice zero
oh it's the whole board right yeah
oh okay okay
can we wait for it oh wait it's a bunch
I think we should remake it I think we
should yeah yeah yeah maybe we waited in
the lobby for too long
[Music]
yeah okay
audio either
was there a game of you synthetics yeah
you can put it up or down
elevator music yeah it's like funky like
background music with Jazzy issue
my chat is saying Nina Auto Lost give
her a batsu
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm not afraid
I'm Not Afraid hit me hit me oh my gosh
oh my gosh girl she really loves that
battle my wheel is spinning it's gonna
be oh wonderful a British accent
why British accent is paying in it what
absolutely pink oh my God that's the
British slang she knows no way
boy
what's a Peng it's like a hot like if
you see a hot lady walking by you can
say ooh Peng or if that's a pain
sounds like you're saying
[Laughter]
in it
to join your game let me reinvite you no
I
haven't it's loading
bird oh wait I got a you know I'm
already in your lobby well I'm gonna
reinvite you again
okay now it's stuck on my screen I've
only been talking when we get into the
game
so I don't know if you really like being
British he can be British all the time
be British don't let Society tell you
whether you should be British or not
sorry
[Music]
I wanna hear British Nina
is that true
I think I'm loading it
[Music]
I want to play
it's loading and it's still loading so
slow
oh wait I think I'm in I think I'm in
yeah
nice
it's time to package
don't crash don't crash anyone's game oh
really
my dad my hand was so good like oh my
God wait my head is nothing oh yeah
back in some maybe oh or someone else
can make the lobby yeah can you make the
lobby I couldn't even hear you on
Discord
is it your Internet no I don't think so
I have oh I have really good internet
if you can Lobby okay why do I want now
oh my God I had the best hand too I was
ready to go all out are we quitting yeah
[Laughter]
okay I'll quit
[Music]
wait probably gonna win this one
wait Nina are you making the room again
please one of you make the room yeah
because I got another invite from you
for me okay classic Uno it's not you
so we're doing the jump in the 7-0
and that's it
yeah I think that sounds good enough
right foreign
okay I invite you guys
invite friend
uh we're not friends we're just
co-workers
wait I can see you guys oh invite the
game invite them since we are not
co-workers are we friends absolutely
absolutely
I'm friends with everyone except homo
it's true
friend of Palmer because everybody is
pomu
she got you there Nina is that how it
works
tell me
I know I timed you out because you said
you went into the chat and said
everybody spam
I said you are omitting the details
damn why did you do that would you like
to object yes objection
I said pomu is very cute today please
spam so it covers my text and she
doesn't see it
so yes I said please stop but
my dad
why would you compliment her if you
didn't want her to see it
[Laughter]
because you know are you gonna join the
game yeah wait it's it's not it's like
black screening me I'm so sorry oh my
God I'm your own collab is betraying you
the worst part too is the only reason I
didn't check Uno is because I played Uno
like two or three months ago and
everything was fine yeah
Ubisoft is like [\h__\h] you Nina yeah I
will [\h__\h] everything up for you now
thank you thank you be soft I really
needed that
you'll get it you'll get there Coco
just in case can you guys buy the game
on switch Yeah
I have a feeling we might have to do the
switch Uno oh my God I I don't even I
have I don't have my switch like set up
to my PC no that would take like two
minutes but
um or yeah we can also play a Barbie
party no
listen I am a big fan of Mario party so
yeah
[Music]
but yeah should be fine but let's let's
try this come on Ubisoft PC version
let's go come on come on it it should be
loading now can you check Discord real
quick
um
I'm just buying Uno on the switch right
now
I don't even know if mine is set up
either
oh my God yeah
should I go set it up like
she's playing Uno Nina
what I don't understand is previously it
opened Uno and now it's not even opening
yeah actually maybe Monopoly would work
right instead we would have to do one
player though yeah I mean it works
already
I love Monopoly wait what I only played
a lot I played it for the first time
like a few weeks ago
I will play Monopoly with you but I only
have it on the switch
oh I don't think you need it wait do you
need a bind
do you need to buy like Monopoly if one
person is controlled well it might be
different on the switch it might work
the only reason we do one person on on
PC is because everybody else crashes
every time
hold on I since y'all three are
streaming give me two minutes I don't
know why I'm just gonna reset my PC
sometimes that works you know sometimes
when things don't work so yeah right
back you tried resetting your PC okay
simultaneously I'm also setting up my
switch as we speak oh yeah well I should
do that too she's a multitasking girl
not really but
these uh desperate times call for
desperate measures
did I play
no oh yeah okay I already have Uno on
switch interestingly and I have Monopoly
on switch so I'm ready for whatever like
bring around baby
[Music]
Ian Kirsten does the encourse apply to
ninja Sanju too it dies
I think it is a widespread virus I think
I think I know what to call is though oh
can I just say it yeah that
all of us little shits do not test the
games
make this game so many times right yeah
I've played this game yeah
we know veterans Nina it's not really
yeah
[Laughter]
the Ian curse also happens so often that
should be a lesson to us to also test
everything then because if the encourse
keeps on reappearing and we should also
test things I'm also a culprint though
preparation that I organized huh
you know if anybody has any concerns
complaints or anything direct them to me
okay I should have checked the game and
I didn't so please
where from now on I will triple check
every game even the ones that I played
like the day before
I promise Nina Nina yeah yeah yeah how
long have you been in niji sanjian
uh too long
I don't install a game until 15 minutes
before
[Laughter]
doing that I did that maybe sometimes in
my early days but I stopped doing that I
I installed at least a day before you
know I thought of the difference between
you and I is that you are what the
people call a professional
yeah no
yeah all right
is it Ricky okay I'm invited
[Music]
okay don't get too excited until the
game actually the case is no longer
we've broken the curse maybe you don't
believe
[Music]
but yeah look at her she's like it stole
the game early what's what's next wake
up before the stream starts
okay okay
looking promising
oh wait are we in
[Music]
you're still there you're still there
though yeah okay never mind she's not
there she's
like she's our place how about this I
can just react to the robot and pretend
it's me playing
and I'll do the boxes if the robot loses
I just don't want to keep delaying the
streets I have Uno on switch ready to go
yeah I can download it right now if you
want
where I just like pretend to be the
robot and if the robot loses I do the
batsuit we can do that while we wait for
the game to download on this way yeah
let's do that we can like play something
else or play it on the switch it's up to
you guys
whatever you guys want
people wait you know I have two Unos
open right now
[Laughter]
let's go
I'm excited I'm playing with the robot I
know I I know you made me skip my turn
oh sorry
what are they gonna change it to no you
fool it's my turn it is I the AI green
come on mama
let me give you my does everybody have
to pay for Uno and then download it or
is it just uh I think so I have I'm
downloading it right now yeah let me
down my switch is all set up
[Music]
oh Chihuahua left oh inactivity because
I'm not much of a
multitasker but it's just a normal one
right there's like a Ultimate Edition
friend called oh
[Music]
for a moment my second one
the second Uno Uno
how is the bot winning what is going on
hey you just get my turn the Nina bot is
too strong I know all right I was like
you know what the box can play cause
then I'd win finally friends again
I could finally have a victory
Uno oh
[Music]
oh
on it
look like your Pearl pepper thank you
okay it's been a long time since I added
new Switch friends I don't I forgot it's
exciting it's a new time oh yeah oh I'll
add you guys I think uh only one of us
has to add you right because uh yeah I
guess because somebody makes the Lagoon
so it's easier for you okay
[Music]
than that
for all the Kiara fans this is something
new right Kiara
this is exciting
[Laughter]
one hour later but here you see the
behind the scenes now we we're so we all
got together so early too we were ready
yeah what happened everything was set up
yeah
oh I put in the wrong oh oh oh
sorry I'm putting in the friend code for
Nina you know people people in my chat
are asking if you verified your game
files did you try that I'm already
friends
Ian curse is alive and well so true
it's just I'm telling y'all I have
bought you know so many times every time
I don't have Uno that's why we shouldn't
play UNO anymore we should move on to
something even better which is Monopoly
that's what honestly I say we play
Monopoly because okay if y'all want to I
don't mind I have eight minutes left on
my Uno on the switch
homo what you can't say no it's three
versus one sorry oh I'm fine with
whatever I'm gaming sorry and I'm eating
my bread
okay I'm here with her to be fair but I
I don't know what's happening
[Music]
but when you're doing amazing
this is the only Uno now this is
Monopoly Monopoly
please thank you all by yourself
rosamy's here too how dare you insult
her like that no no how can you be
playing all by yourself
no no no that was a real bad that was
around
on
switch right
yeah I'll take it wait so do I have to
buy it too yeah oh then I would have to
download it it might still take some
time I'm saying that's faster
okay wait I just need to confirm it's
Monopoly for Nintendo switch
49.99 Yeah
continue
Uno right we can just play it on the PC
and have one person like control it like
we did when Paul and I played recently
wouldn't that be the easiest
I don't no no I don't mind buying it I
just wanted to complain about the price
[Laughter]
two girls here downloading Uno at this
very moment yeah yeah
it's okay I just want everybody to
understand I will complain but I'll
still do it
um
[Music]
okay so in this Uno downloading waiting
time
we shall we shall talk we're in the
waiting room
maybe you guys should make your own
robot room so you can play your own
the simple I helped you out I'm gonna
make it so that you win okay oh really
oh yeah yeah that's good that's good no
no I'm not even playing I'm alone
why did you do that
I don't know
[Laughter]
I was gonna ask you a question Kiara
since you're here um how are you
enjoying Metroid oh yeah oh my God are
you recommended yesterday I love Metroid
Prime I am so happy I'm so uh
um I I recommend it but it was like um I
had a lot of fun with it in the middle
and up until the end when at the end the
met the the fishing metroids were
absolutely tilting me and and the last
few boss fights were also absolutely
tilting me but besides that it was a lot
of fun understandable yeah it wasn't me
did you play the whole thing I played
Metro Prime like over a decade
yet
oh well yeah I also just remember like
playing the game when I was a child but
I didn't really play it I was just like
on the screen running around in the very
place where you spawn when you start the
game because it was too scary I wouldn't
go anything it was too scary actually I
thought it was awesome I was like oh my
God this is like it was a bit scary I do
agree but I was like this is so cool
I think your impression now would be
very different though you should play
Old teams that you played million years
ago you should play them now you see how
they changed for you oh yeah I used to
be like that as a kid if like if the
game was too scary at the beginning I
just couldn't play it yeah yeah
I don't think there was many games that
I like oh one game I thought was really
scary when I was young was um Final
Fantasy 7. I don't like the theme like
the the overarching like theme of the
game was so scary to me you know I know
stuffing around
cool okay
I saw something so cursed today about
Final Fantasy VII that I can't believe
is real
wasn't there recently a remake of Final
Fantasy VII yeah
um yeah yeah I saw a clip where the main
character what is his name Cloud
he gets seduced by her hand massage
person
I'm like this cannot be from the actual
game right because he's moaning he's
moaning
is this the kind of game Final Fantasy X
it feels like I thought this was fan
made like yeah
so what
what
kind of processing I actually don't even
remember I remembered I think that
District that area
it is real it's like you get the choice
apparently between free massages one
where he's like you know I don't know
suffering having a bad experience but
anyway one of them is being like kind of
seduced from a pretty lady you know in a
kimono and yeah he's fuzzy can you log
in uh thingy he's moaning sorry I like
interrupted you all oh my God
what's happening uh
imagine this one crashes
Uno on the switch
but yeah oh my God Kiara that's so I'm
so sorry for interrupting that that is
such a oh I feel like
like imagine oh I don't know Final
Fantasy is a little funny oh there goes
Rose in me now I'm actually playing by
myself
[Laughter]
we lost to the AI and I was like it was
Kiara would have had her win yeah
you would have been able to batsu all of
us baby girl
okay now they're just bullying me I'm
getting I'm leaving my download's almost
done
when life imitates art wait what the
heck oh my God
was downloading Rainbow Six Siege while
I was playing Uno
it's like your download has not been
complete I'm like what download
into the Ubisoft account as well in this
switch version just one second
me too me too okay okay oh I have bad
news you're gonna have to re-log in to
your YouTube channel yeah oh okay I
remember it it's okay okay I had a
feeling it would do that yeah yeah give
me a sec let me just get sorry chat oh
um
I guess one
[Music]
okay now none of us are playing with
Nelson keyboards so we're yeah
scaling isn't that exciting controller
gaming
we're on the same level with the
keyboard right
now we're on the same level of a
controller mm-hmm I I I'm using Joy
content
because when I play Mario Kart with the
wheel I always have to move my body to
move the wheel
yeah maybe we got aim assist now with
him with controller
oh my God it's not touch what okay yeah
I think they just do put it put it in
man uh wait what was that oh wait I
don't remember my email
yes okay do you oh Ubisoft connect so
you have to connect with that right or
do you have to or you have to I think
okay
do it
.com
all right let me
oh wait why am I already logged okay
this is weird but I'm already in
apparently what do you have anything
else on switch maybe maybe I previously
locked on to like another Ubisoft game
wow okay we got an invalid email or oh
no
is
I'm Zelda oh
here I have a profile picture yes yes
okay so let me set up my uh catch a card
then give me a second
yum yum yum yum
girls yes baby talk to me yeah like
early in the day for you girls I suppose
what did you eat so far oh I had chili
it doesn't make a new account
can you not log into the same one
Fruit Loops yum I had anpan
yeah like I'm Pan Man
I have a grocery store that has anpan
clothes
grocery store hmm
what did you have Cara how many meals
did you have today
actually it's like uh 9 p.m here but I
only had breakfast today
hey cook afterwards
so you can grow big strong and Tall baby
so you can reincarnate yeah right now
it's okay
as long as you're taking care of
yourself okay and being healthy yeah
um
I'm making pizza tomorrow
I'm making
thank you for that question yeah
tomorrow is April the 1st so I'm making
the following pizza from Little Caesars
the the advertisers
why is it fake right I thought it was
real until people told me it's fake
so I decided because it's fake I decided
I'll just make it myself fine I'll do it
myself yeah one time homo made a durian
Pizza by the way yeah I know like what
are you are you crazy I had the window
when I was recently in Indonesia and I I
expected it to be really really yeah bye
but they prepared Frozen durian for me
that's what I said kind of Frozen State
and it was like it was acceptable
because of that I heard it tastes really
good I'm having problems oh what's your
problem baby it won't let me make a new
account because the email is already in
use but it won't let me log in with that
email
what oh wait I haven't uh I don't know
it's like in the same email right that
you logged into the Ubisoft on PC
whatever right it could be about this
one I'm joining through your thing oh
wait no no it's telling me to connect to
Ubisoft try it with try it with the
Uplay account that you connected with or
do a password recess
what I did is I actually just retyped
like whenever you can type your email I
just type the same email that I had on
my yeah computer yeah that's what I'm
doing but it says yeah I think I promise
not I'm never gonna have another oodle
collab
when my gen first debuted we had an UNO
collab and then one person kept crashing
and then we had another Uno collab at a
completely different person kept
crashing
on why
okay so can I ask um because every time
I tell people who are in N A about corn
on Pizza they're like yeah that's so
weird I heard it's like the north uh
European thing like that happened a lot
in North Europe right corn and all of
Europe and and Japan but also yeah you
know when I say tuna and pizza as well I
get the same reaction from Annie
Pizza I guess that's more the tuna thing
actually listen Kiara people in an a
freak out over pineapple on people I
know like
like ready for the
where the pizza
from yeah
yeah
please try okay it depends I feel like
if they make it really well it can be
really good otherwise it might be a bit
like weird but if they make it really
well then it's like not that bad yeah I
had this like um I have this like mental
uh I don't know what to call it like a
mental block so I used to work at a
breakfast restaurant you know that
serves like two eggs and bacon omelets
and I remember one time somebody ordered
a fish omelette it was like an omelette
with salmon the restaurant smelled like
fish
like I remember bringing the plate to
the old man and it just stank like
the first time I ever hear about a fish
omelette yeah yeah it was a fish
omelette thing I mean Simon is great and
all but
yeah I don't think I've ever had like a
fish on my before either an old guy
right
yeah you can peculiar tastes with age
Maybe
oh
it's so acceptable I think yeah
is she dying yeah just a little yeah
we can help you yeah yeah yeah
okay for our collab Kiara set like
everything up
yeah you're like okay Nina add this here
do this click this for today you're like
okay girls boosted server for this this
I'm like oh girl okay I just didn't I'm
like
oh did you invite us the only things
that I learned from Mama anyway
you're not online Rosie
uh it won't let me there's no invite for
me
we but I see you on my friends list and
you know what and like what
the match I'm so sorry
cozy no it's not what it looks like
Rosemary stop AI Luna okay that's
how do we get out of this game
we need you Sanji member
you are honorary we're gonna adopt you
I'm sorry there's no way for me to leave
the game
hogwheel at the top you even play or die
how do I reach the Cog wheel
hit the plus button on your controller
oh plus okay thank you have you never
played on a switch before baby what
what is happening
turning it off and on again
yeah there's a Luna
oh my gosh that was so stressful Nina
how could you do this to us I invite
somebody the invite button and the
unlock and skirt Lobby is the same
button
it's in the same face so I just like fat
fingered it oh do you not know how to
play on a switch Nina
oh no
okay I'm back in the group Nina
who's my fingers look at me when you get
invited I'm not getting an invite are
you sure let me let me sign off of me
okay okay let me let me see
umu and
a milk so we should this is six minutes
until the stream starts girl so we
should really like get this going you're
right I'm so happy we moved the stream
back an hour yeah
friends list on Uno
how do you check the friends list on Uno
on the switch you don't need to check a
friend so no no because it's just the
switch front list
yeah but I like either I make the lobby
or I get invited right so how do I
because Nina said join off of me but I
don't have any invite
uh can you it just pops up on the top
left yeah and they don't have it I'm not
getting it invite wait roseme click the
little house and then go to the top left
to the friends and then like find me off
there hopefully I lost I'm out again the
little house
yeah at the bottom or you know what
Rosie you start the game okay but I only
have you I I don't know who do I have I
think I might have you in Polo I don't
have Kiara on my switch
only the person who will make up the
room needs the
people yeah yeah yeah
okay you know what I'll invite you Nina
and then you can invite everyone else
maybe yeah that sounds good
oh I'm so glad we're making it on time
in four minutes we'll start the stream
isn't that exciting yeah I mean in four
minutes but we still have like loading
screen time
yeah true true and then we need to do
the introductions
the sound soundtrack
[Music]
still got time don't worry don't worry
it's okay
and then you know things often don't
work right away in Ian collab so then we
have the Ian curse extra time oh yeah 30
minutes
it's fine we could just talk during that
time I think people will enjoy us just
hanging out and you know down the street
yeah
yeah my cat looks so excited for the
stream they're just like wow I'm excited
yeah yeah this is like a fever dream
yeah
okay okay wait wait I'm inviting
okay okay
I got the invite you got okay I'm
inviting it right now
I'm here baby thank you
I'm here
but is Nina as as not the the roommaker
able to invite me Rose you're on that's
me yeah [\h__\h] you let me join off of you
okay I don't see a way to invite anybody
yeah wasn't me give me a friend called
please okay
oh my God
he rose me on like my friend's list I
see yeah that's the same thing I see you
on my list but I don't see on Uno
but I thought
oh yeah I think you're the one who has
to do it
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay we can push back the Stream
do you want me to send you mine or do
you understand okay at typing apparently
she kills a skill issue
all right
um this will be it this will be the
solution for all our problems
okay I won't let you guys down one of
them you got this believe in yourself
okay all right I sent the friend request
now I'm going back to Uno this is so
crazy what is happening oh no we were
never meant to play this game apparently
I promise I will never for as long as I
live make another Uno collab
why is it searching oh wait get me out
of here
I think I've been someone no I think
it's searching for someone's game
okay hold on I'm just gonna force close
there we go the real friends is the
troubles we got into along the way huh
who won the troubles as friends
I am awaiting my invite was open wide on
me too okay you'll get a really big fat
juicy invite it's gonna be coming in
okay okay a big big inside okay I'm
waiting yeah all right you can't miss it
once it happens yep I'm looking it'll be
my eyes are glued
yeah you'll know you'll you'll hear it
smell it feel it smell it okay yeah okay
by the way there's a big question going
around who gave kiwawa the kiss on her
cheek on the thumbnail
oh
shout the small little lips
like small little lips on her cheek
I was sleeping I don't remember who did
it you know
it may have been Palma and it looks like
it's like call it like a what is it
called like um lip gloss
um I'll take the the DNA from it and
I'll test it on the DNA test
so on your thumbnail I'm on the other
side of you so it's not me it has to be
Rosie or poem who do you think it's me
okay well the only way I can find out
maybe is they if everybody gives me a
kiss and we'll compare the the stamps of
kisses
right who's going first okay
you go first
that is it that is the case but will you
go first
um
I don't see roseme or Nina
guys I don't think this is meant to be
[Laughter]
them here I'll show you but I invited
you there's no way what no I I promise
you
look at this look I just see
wow there's no way to scroll down oh my
God and maybe delete the other friends
yeah there's a smell of friends they
could display
get rid of them I don't know if we open
the game would that help let's try that
okay okay
what yes
Mom kiss you know what when your mom
like licks alive off of your your face
yeah
oh
[Music]
not enough time sounds nice
Yeah It's gotta be a little slobbery you
know
like like when a dog is like biting on a
chew toy that kind of kiss all right let
me started in here yeah
okay wait so does Nina have the game
open I'm about to reopen it to Rosie
again I'm back on the game let me know
if you can see me now okay I'm gonna I'm
gonna close I'm gonna close the lobby
and reach her eye okay all right so
weird
oh my God please oh no just let us in
let us play your game
everybody I love how it says classic Uno
because this is just classic
I think it's my most recent friends that
I've added and it won't let me scroll
down so I'm going to unfriend yeah yeah
yeah
okay I'm going to go delete you guys and
then react okay
okay oh I was gonna say don't delete
Nina it wasn't me delete all the others
that are in there oh I mean that works
too but remove Friend by Nina kosaka
[Music]
I know
friend deleted
if she and you
went
okay I think I see your code Nina
um roseme can you put yours in two on
YouTube do you girls have a physical
copy of Uno at home like right now
like we're there with each other like
okay guys I'm playing
I draw okay so I don't have a lobby but
I can't I can't see Rosemary in the
lobby no wait I'm not on the game right
I'm like giving my friend code too yeah
yeah okay thank you okay now I'm
searching Rosemary since I have everyone
like recently added at the top I'll try
and remake it again I'm back in the game
let me know if you can see me no no no
don't take my invite
oh
okay
you know we should have
actually okay if anybody asks
we can just say this was pre-april fools
the amount of copium that we're going
through this too we never meant to play
the game April Fool closed captioning
not available
[Music]
I don't think that has anything to do
with it it's just showing my friends for
some reason then
area European you Uno and twitch I agree
save us Kiara I'm gonna remove you and
re-add you I already did that I removed
you in reality you okay okay pull my
check again right now maybe
maybe no
should I restart Uno oh yeah let me try
restarting it oh [\h__\h] okay don't look at
it I forgot to accept your friends list
oh you did
what is happening
I'm so sorry I didn't realize you also
unfriended me
that's how it worked
it's a mutual unfriending
Mutual friendly
warm up
my head is still confused right now I
have no clue what is going on
I'm sending you a friend request okay
okay I am sending you a friend request
too wait you unfriended me too
ah okay okay
I'm making a Lobby
in the lobby
even realize
that
okay
okay I'm entering the lobby
I am
oh gosh okay Moment of Truth okay okay
I'm entering the game the game is being
entered right now I'm in okay let me
know if you can see me
oh god oh man I can't see you guys
before okay okay
what's happening what was that it's not
oh wow I can't believe there's 7 000
people watching guys guys I swear to God
we should just play like Among Us okay
not among us but like something else if
this doesn't work but I will try I want
to try I'm gonna try live in two pieces
I think I'm missing no do I have
everybody as a friend no I think so girl
you update your Nintendo switch minus
not wait what what I just said start
software
Maybe
I love this so much
okay I feel like I've said this before
but in Japan when we're going to meet
with Kiara right we were four girls and
cattle was alone and rosami's like I
don't know I'm just I'm nervous to meet
kiato I'm like why are you nervous he's
alone beating us we're four
then okay
do you guys
Nina you know my whole thing is freaking
I was freaking it
do you guys know that room now wait yeah
can you see me no no you don't see me
you're in she's Nina Cena
okay okay Nina I did not see
you okay wait I'm gonna try to join off
of Kiana because everyone else is here
like
everyone else is in the lobby let's just
play
[Laughter]
off of your profile
how do you write now right yeah
let me make the room okay see how if it
works this will be so funny please
please imagine
no okay how do you do this uh I think we
should do this at least once a year
where we just get together and don't
play a game
it's a non-game game you know
episode of Fairly OddParents when he's
on the escalator and he's like when do
we get to the ride and he's like and
there's parents are like this is the
ride
this is the Stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
one second
[Music]
in a dream someone wake me up
save me
but I had to take two all right all
right don't worry don't worry we haven't
even tried yet Nina also boosted our
server
anyway for you girls best 40 I ever
spent yeah
we can we can hear each other go into
despair in higher quality that's true
it's awesome
I have to ask how high is the highest
you can see
how high the highest is I think oh I've
done some like Vocaloid covers where
they get really high yeah so pretty high
but I don't know a key why I was just
wondering because there's this like rock
song called dream on oh
oh my God all the all the classic rock
fans are gonna be so happy
I think it's a fun song it is yeah oh is
it Aerosmith yeah no no uh yeah it is
Aerosmith Steve Tyler I've heard of
Aerosmith before like a different song
though I think and I don't know what was
it Iris
forever to touch no what the hell is oh
I've already seen that one yeah yeah I
thought that was them okay girls one set
one second when you girls created the
lobby how did you do it uh you clicked
the planet and then you click um
but they just keep it as free for all at
the top
yeah yeah I'm free for all classic Uno
what that immediately sent me into uh oh
no
I think I was in a different thing okay
you do the three first guys yeah right
okay you know more limits
[Music]
I can't stop thinking about when you
were singing in Russian oh my God okay
I'm gonna do this so I've known roseme
for over a year now right and yeah well
we were in Japan okay I was singing
through a Russian song called
drunk and then I look at Rosemary and
she's singing the song in Russian with
me
like well I don't know but like when
you're kind of drunk and I was just like
you used to be crushing and you've never
told me but it's because she was reading
the Japanese
I don't know
but I was like sneaking out I'm like are
you I was like do you speak Russian
like I felt so betrayed oh my God that's
so funny and that's simple you just
accepted it and I just kept on singing
like you and you were like okay
with like a big smile on her face she
kept going nasty
um
what happened we're here
[\h__\h] here I'm gonna print screen for you
the only friend that I can invite is
Pomeranian
yeah the others are all whole life
members why are you doing this I swear
it's just like randoms like who's on
your list and then you can't divide this
is sucks because I don't know what do we
do but I I am Googling right now
what if we do join online and then we
have a passcode
yeah test it
I'm trying it
yeah oh wait no no it's putting me in a
random match
laughs
[Music]
guys this has been one of the most
collabs of all time
said is it because your online status is
hidden oh is that oh my God tech support
who said that where are you Jay
well no because some people other people
can invite me like oh that's true the
thing is like a few of us can invite a
few of us but not all of us right
hmm that's true
um
how to fix Nintendo switch can't join
friend Lobby
how to fix
is there a way to make it so anybody can
invite some people
who is it like this okay okay here's a
new idea what if we just all join online
at the same time
surely that can't be that many people
playing right well I now delete all my
uh friends one second except
[Music]
don't do that
eventually
give me just a moment please I mean it
is a good idea but like I feel like that
would work right I'll do it out of
solidarity okay who am I dating I'll
delete anything new friends cause
deleting Kobo bye-bye one by one oh my
God was walking the street right now and
she's excited to be fine
oh
I apolog friend it gives me the options
to block them as well why not for the
other
I'll go delete them
adult dramatic yeah okay okay but
because I see in my friend list y'all
are online
um and and if I delete everybody else I
mean come on come on then the game has
no other options it has to show everyone
right are you sure that the list is too
small to like show everyone yeah there's
no way to scroll down yes
everybody except rosami still
I see everyone except for you so that's
like it's weird right
let's get out our laundry do you have a
problem with me do you want to talk
about do you want to talk about it
what's up Rosemary it's because this is
Nina you you saying that Russian song
and I really wanted to sing it I really
wanted to sing it that's why I was
singing it with you but yeah
drama yeah oh my gosh wait why did you
say I need my look really cute in my
jacket Rosemary and I'm glad that you're
wearing it and it's your jacket
yeah it's really you need to unlock the
lobby and have them join what's
happening at the chat now if anyone here
for real knows what's up how to fix this
let me know I'm looking good job okay
unlock the lobby but then what if it's
like a random player that isn't us I see
that from you again should I accept it
I'm in the middle of deleting all my
friends
I think we should try the technique with
like only a few friends on the list and
if that doesn't work then maybe we
should try something else yeah I think
so too yeah we are already all friends
from Ubisoft connect right
you know
yes yeah okay yeah we do so yeah we're
all all friends yeah we'll be
self-connect
um
oh God I got so many friends over the
course of like four years man I ran
around it's over
you're fired and you're fired
oh my God
and you're fired the lead friend we're
witnessing we're witnessing like a mass
deletion like oh my gosh on on air this
is
sorry please double take this they still
love you yeah I want to start from
scratch because I feel like maybe some
things went wrong here and there you
know
bonus restart also it's kind of nice
restarting from scratch because it will
give you all these like butterfly
feelings that you had in the beginning
a fresh friendship is something nice but
also an old friendship is also something
nice oh wow someone said kfp layoffs no
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's I'm playing a game of deleting
people this is the game today kfp we
used to give us a meeting to tell you
is it I'm almost done I have uh one two
three four left okay oh my God
delete because I'm waiting so sadly
where's Nina oh she's deafened
oh what maybe she went maybe she
couldn't stand us anymore
she's finally done with us she's just
like I organize this collab I can take
it out
she's finally done she left didn't kill
her motivation for organizing collapse
because she told me I really want to
organize more collapse now even when I'm
not the one Street yeah
yeah okay guys
it's done okay okay okay okay oh my gosh
I'll restart the game though oh close
Okay this is promising don't get your
hopes up I know I have big hopes for
this this is gonna work believe kiwawa
believe crossing my fingers
[Music]
warning right before playing you will
not be able to play it with your friends
because we will not show them in your
phone
oh
what happened
hi welcome back I have deleted all my
friends I'm not now gonna try my best to
make it I believe I believe this is it I
believe all your past friends don't
count we are your new friends we are
like a cult we are grabbing you away I'm
kidding uh welcome back you will know
enjoy a greater experience when playing
Uno as a member of the Ubisoft
connected
this is sounding a bit cozy now
they don't let you play unless you
connect yeah
please get that message too though
yeah I mean I don't think so yeah I got
that message because I didn't I didn't
because I was already locked into
Ubisoft somehow goodbye maybe I just
didn't read I can't read
share if you can't read
oh I'm nine centimeters tall and I never
learn how to read
Moment of Truth okay
when she laughs at your jokes
sorry for laughing
wait no did it get worse
and now it's only because all uh all the
others are ghosts
wow I'm sorry for laughing interesting
okay guys
maybe we should play something else or
just chat I don't know
only problem is since we counted at each
other on switch if we play Monopoly on
switch wouldn't that also give us the
same exact problem no no no no no no but
it's also it will be signed that's the
thing that's what I'm thinking right we
would have to like have a single person
play it or we can play something like
maybe like Como party
Monopoly is different give me a second
no it's also by Ubisoft it's the same
thing it's the same thing on the game
can you try to see if you can invite all
of us yeah I'm opening it right now let
me see if it even tells me to log into
Ubisoft
yeah yeah if you can well
how would it we don't I don't have it
installed so yeah I don't have it either
it would probably if she invited us we
would have to good it's a good thing
that we um you know delayed the stream
by two hours
[Laughter]
[Music]
that your actions have consequences
it doesn't work it doesn't count me too
long to Ubisoft that's a good thing
already oh
I like it
[Music]
um
I think you only need to log into like
Ubisoft once on the switch and then it
like transfers over it because
I think I was logged in from like Just
Dance and it like went over to Uno but
then again I don't think I could even
see you girls to invite you if you don't
have the game download but I'll I'll
check
[Music]
um
actually work yeah this looks I looked
at the trailer it looks way better than
the Monopoly on the PC
there's no in I can't invite I guess
because I have no friends who have
Monopoly right now okay so I'm gonna go
buy Monopoly
it doesn't work now one day I believe we
will play Monopoly together
organization
this is it this is the final Uno we
never got to play I need to ask Grandma
what happened because she didn't have
Uno working and then it worked
so am I buying Monopoly or what it might
take me a long time to download on the
switch do I feel like it would be bigger
than Uno
but last time I played Monopoly was it
on PC or was it on switch guys do you
know I think the switchboard looks super
cute yeah
the PC one does not work it's it's real
it crashes every time
I'm pretty sure it's the same server
though
um
you confirm your token first I don't
know if we're gonna get one guy but
confirm your token to see if that I can
add AI
oh
honestly you probably gonna be a better
gaming experience than you know Homeland
puff so wait who what's my name
what's her name
say my name
um
otherwise I know we could play garlic
foam oh okay oh yeah yeah wait I am are
we doing Monopoly or no hello
because if you all buy it and download
it and it doesn't work then we spend a
number of hours
[Music]
that's a stream of the hopes of
sometimes
again I just want to apologize I did not
check the game because I played Uno and
everything worked
you guys know that is
[Music]
just wait I'm gonna do a poll I'm gonna
do a poll do you guys want us to uh try
Monopoly or play garlic phone now hmm
firework film is fine for you girls is
it like in terms of you know I think
yeah I'm checking it let me check
uh it's even free guys it's free
oh wait no sure
let me take a look really quickly at my
games list
I had issues with Monopoly when I played
it was a collab
never I didn't have issues inviting
girls I didn't have issues with
connection either I think I maybe at the
very end somebody disconnected oh yeah
yeah Monopoly is a bit famous for having
um silver issues at least on the PC I
don't know on the switch
and I feel like it's this well it's the
same service so maybe
okay oh well garlic phone seems fun yeah
I think like
fall maybe like Pummel parties stuff
like that
yeah
I put it I put the I put uh some stuff
in the um
they're saying play garlic film now
30 are saying try Monopoly and 70 are
saying play garlic phone that's great
garlic
just love garlic baguettes
okay so we what do you mean it's called
garlic bone what do you mean it's
nothing
uh there is a game can you double check
on your end there's this game called
unrailed it's super cute
and on switch it's super fun it's super
easy to play we just build a train to
get like train tracks yeah like
it should be like maybe under a gig
there you go it's a super like if
anything I think I could really double
check on here yeah it's 700 games
I cannot play unrails
don't worry I think garlic phone is the
yeah
I can call it a garlic
okay I wrote you the reason yeah no
worries have you um
uh have you uh played Terraria okay oh
oh my God
new things
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
okay okay I'll start the garlic foam
Lobby because uh that way you girls
won't accidentally show it on your
screen
okay oh oh okay okay okay it's been a
while I love garlic foam garlic phone
will have to change to a beautiful
thumbnail later but I'll just change the
logo then yeah
there we go I'm having a lot of fun I I
know I know sometimes folks are like
stuff didn't work but this this is fun
for me this is the best like huge delay
I've ever had
listen I know I know realistically if
you're really looking forward to Uno and
you don't get Uno yeah it's
disappointing but this is an adventure
this is a ride we're all you know
yeah take this oh
sorry guys oh yeah German ads
did you guys hear the German ad no no no
but I kind of want to now
Deutsch Deutschland no
um
speed
a what besides English
oh gosh yeah Russian French what about
you speak something
um
English and Japanese right yeah just a
little
plant
s
she speaks the language of the Earth
speaks a lot of languages but a little
bit like she understands Spanish really
really well
the Russian right I mean we know that
yeah
um yeah Japanese
um I took a bit of Italian took some I
took some Latin
that's an Italian oh I just saw your
room Nina okay hold on one second
okay I um
because I don't have a phoenix yeah yeah
yeah okay chicken
you can change it
together oh how's it possible that a
free game is letting us play together
versus a 50 Euro or new Souls game
this is so easy is there any music on
this site I don't hear anything I don't
think so okay
okay
bring your own music yeah
[Laughter]
do you do you
[Music]
thank you for reciting my music
doesn't work
your what doesn't work my ad blocker
doesn't work but it's okay I'm just
cutting off the sides
yeah yeah I always I always like uh on
on websites sometimes um when I'm
streaming like the the wheel website
that spins the wheel I have to like cut
out all the sides or gyozo because it
just has like 15 different ads I'm like
I'm sorry I'm not trying to advertise
anything
okay
um
are we gonna like do some uh are we
gonna do normal first I suppose whatever
you all prefer yeah
okay my pen my pen I have a pen I have a
tablets please
it's more scarf
foreign
at the counter putting stuff into a bag
uio bags no that's genius
oh my God I keep getting ads on on
garlic phone is this normal I mean me
too a video in the beginning of the
middle of the school is it really in the
beginning yeah
but just I don't have an ad maybe my ad
blocker is superior okay
yeah just give me like a whole video
oh my gosh it's got like two hours to me
all right ready I'm ready
oh my gosh okay let's go
um should I do a zombie Jam like a small
bgm yeah
oh my God
how do you stock
this one are we starting is it starting
uh I can start yeah let's start it all
right what are you doing this game oh
you draw
write a sentence write a sentence
later I don't think you can hear it yet
[Music]
write a sentence um
okay yeah I'm good good
I'm so sorry
it's okay I wasn't including myself
okay
[Music]
oh
my God okay
oh it's been a while since I drew
something me too
did you change any time settings
okay uh
um okay how to draw I don't remember how
to draw
it's it's cute it's very cute
um I'm having the time oh my God okay
whatever
stick man I'm a stickman I'll show you
my Muslim Stickman
oh this is perfect perfect
oh why am I oh my God
upset at me
I don't I don't think they know we'll
know what this even is let me decorate
it I mean we have so much time we have
too much time we have to make a faster
round later yeah no no I'm not gonna
have enough time it's gonna go quick at
the end oh my God
does it look more like what it should be
oh no it's happening oh my God this I'm
already stressed out and we just started
how does it even look like I don't even
oh my God
I don't even know what it looks like
how's that everybody
snack
[Music]
[Laughter]
I eat as a fairy what are you eating I
want to eat the berry yes
oh my God bony
how do you know because she's nine
centimeters I got a meaty thighs sure
okay Nina let's see your thighs first
and then we can compare
I've been losing weights
try to gain weight how is this everybody
second do you like it do you like my art
I like it oh I like it oh my God why am
I lagging okay what do you mean you're
lagging the game lagging or you are
lagging
oh wait is it better now
that is Nina
[Laughter]
actually
a close team just in case
whoever drew that oh here I'm gonna move
what is it there what's Happening Here
you guys go
this is so good whoever Drew this what
is this
um
[Laughter]
I know it's one of you well it has to be
one of you I know which one you got what
the heck
oh
okay okay how do I draw a skull oh
God
decrepit
okay that's whenever I put my mouse on
the guard take phone it like gets really
laggy for some reason and don't put your
mouth yeah don't just don't do not draw
with your imagination draw with your
head
don't you have a tablet
s
though
[Music]
references you guys
no it's not it's beautiful
listen I think
okay guys I apologize for my drawings
but I am drawing out like two frames
right now I don't know what is your
computer laggy it's only like the garden
phone like window I don't know why
this is the John Ubi soft curse for
being like
[Music]
um
oh yeah I have to drop me sorry not
sorry oh my God that yeah that is so
accurately here let me help them out a
little bit otherwise it's too difficult
um okay I did my best I think this is my
masterpiece
I think this is
I'm looking forward to seeing that
oh my God I can't I can't okay
it's gonna be so obvious that somebody
is using a mouse and keyboard I mean
yeah a mouth
I'm just saying
you're right
there we go here here that's oh my God
what is happening
you're calling
okay
[Laughter]
I think I'll rejoin the the do you know
oh my God
the Karthik lobby after this are we
doing leftovers yes right oh yeah
voiceovers please please
four people ends really quickly huh it
does yeah that means we get more rounds
are you girls ready
wait are you actually Rosa me because I
know you're having issues I know it's
you can like show it and then after
Aldrin oh like I'll read you after that
okay okay
everybody else got to draw though did
you
um
all right let's go
uh Kiara describing oh come on
[Laughter]
Underground
oh well we just had the topic today
that's roasted pizza slices yeah those
are Doritos
the old Doritos these girls playing you
know you know you know hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're just gonna skip to the next one
okay no no no no no no no no no no no no
yeah what
what
um
the shape of the faces looks like uh
like a bird where the nose would be the
butt the mouth would be the wing
[Music]
all right oh my God needless one is so
funny though no stop is that one big
card or is it like one big Uno table
like yeah there's so many questions
listen I am not cheating like Kiara is
doing by using a tablet oh call out oh
my God scale issue
tablet issue
um
why are we always giving the same
prompts almost
it's pretty
[Music]
where is Rose
thank you
so cute someone has to provide you know
all of the Arts here you know hey hey
what if he wasn't drawing at two frames
maybe maybe Pablo Picasso of garthuk
phone okay I couldn't put in my entire
prompt it was gonna be
we're not allowed to brag while you're
using AIDS it's like you know when you
ride a bike and you have the little bike
wheels that help you ride the bike you
can't drag about riding the bicep on the
tricycle
cycling here take it back wow you can't
ride a bike well it was gonna be with
their with their babies Kiara and and
resume but I didn't have space ah
[Music]
I was
at 174 he's nine Nina's shopping for her
family I'm trying to eat me or like what
happened to you
skull face what happened to you Nina oh
my God
she's been shopping for a really long
time she did not age fine like her wine
a mode that we have never played before
oh yeah let me rejoin the let me rejoin
what's what's interesting
completely start writing and keep
drawing Until the End okay complete the
sketch start with basic lines and see
the other players interpretation that
could be cute
okay yeah we can try
I'm opening one sentence to ask
questions and have fun with the others
drawings
wait which which one is that one
Icebreaker compliment sandwich
sandwich
a little compliment is if you start to
complete the sketch start with some
basic lines
don't feel comfortable complimenting
in this room
start writing and keep drawing until the
end I'm fine with any of them
animation is fun too but with four
people We're not gonna get a really good
animation yeah I'm thinking that too
unless they give us yeah with four
people
I swear this game's doing it on purpose
[Music]
good one all right all right let's go
speed run I'm ready I'm ready okay time
you're going down
I know me too okay I I always I know it
has to happen but I never think about it
I know right
um oh gosh um um chat give me a prompt
um
isn't that a realistic
prompt that I came home oh okay speed
run
what is this prompt the same way okay
um
okay
I'm sorry
why is this still like this
that's my garlic foam like this
I'm excited for this
um oh my mouth is watering I'm getting
hungrier by the minute this is yummy oh
Brown wow
I mean this just turns me on this is
kind of my Kink here
beautiful it's seducing me wait I was
gonna say you're making me hungry
because I thought you were genuinely
hungry oh my god
um I am also genuinely hungry oh
okay
oh yes okay I even got done earlier
oh my God I had no time
Speed Run who oh
I know what her think is now
mm-hmm
this one's very easy
let them go
we'll let them guess she's a bone she's
literally bones
okay I have to drop it please this is
gonna end
um what does this mean what what is this
okay
what I'm doing okay you know what I have
an idea I have an idea I'm very confused
too okay I feel like some people here
are not taking the game seriously
oh I'm thinking it so seriously
seriously I'm just bad at Art
it's good
she has boobs too gliser or something
oh my God what is happening we forgot
about that
about what I forgot about the boobs
thanks for telling me reminding me yeah
of course of course
got other ears
foreign
together
that's it oh so fast all right all right
cooking corn Pizza
[Music]
here we are here we go
what is my pink
please explain to the class rosa music
oh I heard I don't know what I think I
heard service
yeah what is your name well making the
corn cob Pizza girl you got it wrong
you can't just put rules on the
flashlight we can vote I vote we spin
the wheel for Rosemary to do a bat suit
okay if I deserve back to you deserve to
for your past drawing two Nina what
about that huh are you joining us it's
gonna be majority and roseme will have
to do the botsu of your spinning choice
I think I accidentally closed it but we
can just choose one for her randomly
laughs
I've been bullied
bully I will not stand for this slander
this is your this roseme oh she's back
oh she's back welcome back I will not
stand for this slender and this bullying
here for your daily punishment honey
[Music]
I thought
she wrapped
this is clearly sadness what do you mean
well now yeah but why did you censor my
eyes because she has a visor
I'm pretty sure she does yeah she that's
her gun in her head
and she should be a little more gun like
maybe I should have been some pew pew
pew coming up you can see it looks like
a like a gun like a cannon what do you
mean it's giving me more Mario tube than
like
it's okay it's good it's beautiful
though but it's not my king
but it could be if you think about it
long enough I think you might like okay
Kiara tell me this like tell me you you
see Travis and you're like okay she's
not cute
I have to say I got some fan art of me
as Samus and dad was like mind-blowing
you see you see now you're starting to
yell where I'm coming from
all right let's go next all right
the British accent oh
yeah you're like picking it you're not
even rendering it
oh what the hell is this
recipe collecting Rose
[Laughter]
okay
I was butt crack I'm sorry I really
ruined this one giving me a hat
years
[Laughter]
something that looks like a hat that
looks exactly like that some characters
or some games looks like you have a
small alien on your head or something
the character who has a hat like that
but different color that's
[Music]
it yeah
oh is that this of my butt crack on the
bottom
my mouth and then the eyes are my
question mark That's Right
I don't understand it but like I watched
quite a bit of it
it's my favorite animal
well okay recommend it to me so somebody
who's not watched back in monogatari how
would you recommend it to me how would
you sell it to me if you want
um a long really intricate story and a
lot of cute girls yeah the characters
are really cute
but uh this is just like overload you
have to focus when you watch it but it's
so like yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
I have Kiara's chat open is that the one
with the tooth brushing scene yes yeah
yeah
fan servers in in the anime but there's
also a lot of like really serious plots
as well
it's really good it's there's a lot of
reading
there is a lot of reading
subtitles are of oh it's kinda yeah a
lot of what there's a lot of text on
yeah yeah
big recommend okay let's look at it I'm
just thinking uh
oh sorry I ran out of time
I ran out of time
oh
like Kiana I didn't have the time me too
that's what happened when we last prom
I'm too busy laughing so I don't have
time to like who's that extra person
there's a ghost I know
me
yeah right you're in the middle yeah
maybe I commanded the I don't how do you
even say that face
dancing Nina
[Laughter]
more more
Nina why are you always a skeleton what
is happening
Nina
you want to talk about it
have you guys seen her she's she's
literally wasting away she's so decrepit
she's she's older I'm only 800 and
something can you not Nina what is
happening there what does what is this
I'm not that old
ER YouTubers than 800. yeah right
yeah but like and I mean it doesn't
reflect in her beauty anyway like she
looks very young
I am cool Nina I'm just it's it's a
artistic representation of your soul
okay it's true you cannot critique you
cannot critique stuff like this you know
like there's Beauty in everything you
know yeah I am yeah
I like the shape of the left boob I know
right
or is that another butt on my chest
there's so many questions
she's bending It Forward ones and that's
the boobies and in the first one she
didn't have boobies she only had ass so
yeah so it has to be maybe like her old
butt went up and then she grew a new one
oh
do we have like a recovering skill on
your trade on your butt
yes
I love palmer but I have to say Nina is
beautiful she doesn't look like this
look at it
okay I'm sorry Mom I'm sorry
I mean like your body still looks good
it's just your face maybe like you know
what I'll give you some sunscreen Nina
you'll still hang this on the fridge
right you'll mom you'll still put this
on the fridge right
of
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
pay back pay back next time you draw
something we give promo about this game
now because she has not bad
game will be
um
well because related you have to learn
how it is to be a real grandma you will
talk in a grandma voice oh
therapy
be safe
we even learned what it means to be old
now they're so my face
my face is saggy but not with the rest
of the red looks good
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah we do it Rosa you need to change I
mean sorry you need to change that
sunscreen
oh no it's only a matter of time
anyone want a toffee I know some candies
in my pocket
why do you sound legit like why do you
I'm a method actor out of your face just
from this
I wanna very quickly like say this
because I know there might be a lot of
new fans watching uh we like please
don't think for a second that you know
they're bullying me or I'm bullying them
we we're that close like it's please do
you have a gun to your head
when they say I'm old and saggy and and
stupid I old and stupid end sticky
script it's a smelly on my screen blink
blink I'm going out script I mean smelly
I am contractually obligated to say that
we are the bestest of friends
yeah please curiously I know because I
feel like we we have we banter really
really hard in needy yeah we do and I
just want to make sure that you know
folks that are tuning in don't feel like
oh are they actually like being mean to
each other are they like I would not be
inviting people that I think are mean to
me to a collaboration with me you know
just to get bullied
to the people yeah I hear that Rose to
me
you hear this listen
I am very timid if I'm like saying stuff
like that well it's not like I like you
guys or anything I don't like you
like you guys it's true
I'm very I can say lots of stuff like
um
uh like what like what I like green tea
I like green tea can you say I love you
to these two girls
um these three girls these three girls
grandmother she loves her before she
dies yeah
um well it's it's been I guess like a
I guess you know you know
wow
I feel like if ever really grows old
Rosemary will be not will not be
visiting her in her I don't know I mean
no nobody's gonna visit pomu
wow that's a job
thank you
[Music]
you know what there will be no need for
visitation because all YouTubers end up
in the same old people home oh my God
it sounds like hell
we'll talk about you know the good old
days when we're really old yeah you've
already done that
okay Rosie you have two more people to
love say it
but no I said like maybe I'm having I
mean like I mean maybe not but like I
maybe maybe having a good I mean a good
time with you know
guys
you guys here okay
I said I love I love green tea I love
Crepes
um what else is what who is that they're
not there green tea and Crips are not
yeah I'm drinking tea right now it's
it's here it's right here kiwawa how can
you say it to things that are not even
alive but you don't say it to us where
it really matters they don't judge me
okay they
they're if I'm saying it or not it's not
embarrassing okay
you for your underwear but I was I was I
said it was good and cute really yeah
I can show you my underwear though but
there isn't much okay I'm okay
well well I mean I will take that offer
yeah yeah
I'm I'm actually blushing oh
wait wait you know freedom for the you
know I'm wearing pants
there's Pom-Pom oh my God pink have you
seen those underwear with like where the
butt crack is it's a heart
oh yeah yeah yeah I mean an open heart
oh wait what what wait you have them
and like okay I not right now but I used
to have underwear like that and then it
had a little like heart charm I think it
was wow sorry sorry can you just tell me
is the heart the Open Heart above the
butt crack or it's on the butt
oh it's like the top of the butt crack
oh okay okay okay so why don't you get
like cold making notes a draft and then
you'd feel cold I don't know
I don't know is that how it works
I'm sorry I'm gonna get a nosebleed
they weren't backwards boxers were they
no
no let's play another game please
okay Icebreaker yeah yeah yeah I just I
don't think I haven't played that long
before what's Icebreaker I don't know
but wait what is it oh my god oh no
everything's gonna be about underwear oh
my God
[Music]
try really hard not to make it about
underwear okay
challenge impossible level
I got it I got a decent one there you go
hmm
but but but but but
like one tea right
I don't know
a bite
wait
yeah
oh my God Panic instills this is a table
everybody
that makes sense that makes sense okay
that's cute though I can someone like
draw that for real this like a good
artist I feel like ninja Sanji uh you
girls you have like really great artists
in your fan Community these are such
good art can they draw this too
it's an e you guys gosh
there you go
this is now a Canon this is real this is
the the way it's meant to be
good
okay I want this to be real in the
future I want to see what it is what
it's you it's me
and what color should it be
I kind of feel like drawing promo with a
hat now instead of the headband you know
what am I getting a hand if I do this I
don't want to like get us banned if I
like
why is the table oh try it
I also feel like I'm gonna reveal some
things about my character that people
don't know well that's good we want
alone
so you know how I have the most
[Laughter]
um you don't have the markings on my
face
um I have to like in other places
worry about it
will we find out no that is
If your manager has a problem with this
I promise you I will apologize I will
write like a written apology for this
I just don't know how to like write this
otherwise
wait what don't worry about it
what what is happening wait is it is it
uh uh an ash goodbye we call it in
German called the ashkabai uh is it on
top of your butt
oh
okay I feel like we're just drawing a
normal
round what is what what is
what
are you okay are you okay
what am I
this is the joke yeah use your use your
use your fun jokey
um
it what is this
okay I'm just gonna draw this literally
because I don't know I'm so confused by
everything yeah me too I'm just going to
draw this literally
all right well I'm getting serious now
yeah I'm drawing oh wait I have to
go there we go oh yeah guys oh yeah oh
no lines
hey I'm having wine
I said lines maybe maybe you've had what
kind of wine are you having me brilliant
Shiraz
oh
[\h__\h] no space for face
[Music]
how to draw this
oh okay ribbon
[Music]
smell like a booty needs to be you know
more like this oh
wait hold on
but who is this yeah bye yeah bye yeah
bye I guess it's me
[Music]
there's a lot of
a lot going on here yeah this is not a
crazy crazy round
it's a very sensual round that's for
sure
feelings and emotions okay okay
I'm sorry
cute butt
it's not good everybody chat says it's
fine
I swear if I had a tablet
like I feel like you're meant to draw
this with your mouse right that's like I
agree say that to Kiara well if you
drunk well if you started
oh my God I love this meme who wrote
this okay I'm sorry who
wrote this prompt
well if you sing it like that I feel
like I have an idea and I don't mean me
I don't mean me
who picked this that means this right
that's like you know another way of
saying that
right I'm learning so much English today
like so worth it my vocabulary is
expanding can you give us an example of
what you've learned
[Music]
um
yeah
so first I thought Twin Peaks maybe a
mountain
but I think that probably means
yeah it's a mountain it's one yes it is
I know so much about climbing now
because I just watched a video about
climbing oh really one of the twins
sometimes
smaller than the other you know we
should go hiking yeah we should go
hiking together one day yeah we're
totally gonna do that add that to the
list yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we should
go now and this has two things and
mountain climbing 5 a.m karaoke
and it's I need some safety do you say
do you wait safety somewhere at the top
is someone at the top to save you yeah I
think Jesus Christ
Jesus up there yeah I don't see anybody
else who's gonna be at the top to save
you
here here's some nice armpits for you
guys to enjoy nice
I'm gonna love some armpits I don't know
why people love armpits so much
people love Iron picks no I'm so happy
it's cool to love armpits again armpits
it's never gone out of stock just like
the shoulders okay I'm not old armpits
are sexy and so are ankles ankles are
sexy oh yeah ankles can be cute
[Music]
did you guys notice
um this like the YouTuber or I don't
know if he's really a YouTuber but she
made like videos you know in Victorian
only fans where do you get like ankle
pictures but it was a joke yeah
and a lot of people signed up for it
actually
what really oh wait but for real yeah
yeah y'all not think armpits are kind of
sexy I'm a Touhou fan
[Music]
oh maybe because there's like not enough
people oh maybe or we compare did
everybody draw everything maybe maybe I
think maybe maybe that's what Icebreaker
means
oh yeah
yeah you were gonna need to do another
grammar round this was really nice
lacking Grandma okay
oh my God I'm trying such a lovely young
lady right now I'm gonna see me
young lady
it's so beautiful
I don't know what my prompt even was
like I don't know what I was trying to
accomplish with that I'm so sorry
me too I started trying to like be cute
and I'm like oh this is not cute
um
[Laughter]
yes yes
she is Conquering the world
okay okay
so much
that was my real grandma you know
what do you mean you loved her
songs
I mean maybe I mean I
I
[Music]
I think she would be a good grandma
that's all I'm seeing
how was this everybody
that's pretty good I'd say
all I heard was
hello
yeah yeah I'm really busy working on
this mask oh I'm so sorry
[Laughter]
about the prompts man I know we did
these probes I just I just want to say I
I am ready to write like my apology if I
knew
[Laughter]
bring it home yeah let's see it let's
see it oh God oh God
uh-huh you're aware yeah
um
[Laughter]
I'm just gonna put that on our fridge
that one pummel oh
my God
I thought it was like a bot prompt
because I didn't understand what it
meant at all but perhaps when you guys
got it like so good except the tree went
like why did you not like
wait you all you've never been told that
the joke is under there
only the tree under there under the tree
the joke is under there you want me to
understand the wear yeah
I'm gonna stupid I don't know what's
going on listen I'm numbering one okay
for anybody who doesn't know this is
like old trivia roseme is the first one
to have fallen for that joke really no
really no no no no I fell for up dog I
underwear I knew that you guys are
talking about underwear but up dog
Lizzy a dog is My Kryptonite
we're up down but like yesterday I got I
think I fell for a D's not stoked twice
oh no
twice isn't fell for even uh
it's not my fault they're all so
childish
chat and what are you doing bullying
cookies
I don't have anything you want to tell
us
sleeping
yeah oh
my God
what's going on even as an old lady eyes
still smoking hot
why do you have bigger boobs as an old
lady
with age you know no they get smaller
because they're sagging exactly that's
the point Cuomo decided that now it's a
nap she doesn't want to get called Flat
anymore so she got you know yeah
wait
[Laughter]
like like is that one you put like
Silicon yeah
you're a great candidate for that too no
I'm not
I'm not no
no Mina's attacking everybody today oh
my God in my defense you weren't
attacking me first
he hasn't said old woman
[Music]
just to be clear is justice as well true
yeah see which I'm not it wouldn't
matter to me no not at all exactly no
so uh Kiara we have this one co-worker
who's pretty flat and she always says
medium is premium and it's like oh honey
you're not medium
but it's true you know
medium is great like such a cope I think
she's gotten a buff though right like
she did she did
mine's foam
[Laughter]
well yeah
we can feel the squish when we hug yeah
failed I felt squish but I don't think
it came from me
oh for me right for me oh no I don't
know
I remember squished from Nina
[Music]
this is a good squeeze from Nina
that reminds me uh Kiara ages ago me and
Rosie were in a hotel room looking in
the mirror and I you know I I don't care
a bra because it hurts so I just like
not too you know I only have a few like
you know firm years left I want to live
them for how many years
it's not a lot of firm years left you
know genuine question when do the firm
years end yeah
soon
for you
they're about to like
really oh no that's stressful
honestly like I'd say any time after
like 26 27 The Firm years are about to
end what really that's soon yeah
something about it you can work out I
think working out helps like if you like
just kiss workouts yeah but you know the
bigger you are the more inevitable the
no are you just bragging at this point
it's just so hard that's what she did oh
my God
she would like shake them around and
look at me it was still messed up
did you take her she take them around
when she was naked no okay so Kiara we
went for food and I was eating and I
dropped something on my boobs and Rosie
has like really big blue Benzie
my big breast called the sauce that I
dropped
yeah she would she'd be like how could
you say that
she'd be like an anime it is
well we're at the hotel I think I was
wearing just like a tank top and I I
forgot what we were doing but I think I
was doing my makeup and I was like I
shook and something and Rosie's like she
turned to the side and she looked and
she went oh my God
so flat
the realization is
did you girls ever go to an Onsen
together I want to go I've been before I
want to go if Rosemary would you feel
comfortable going to a nonsense with us
like
maybe yeah
but like
oh look okay don't look it's all
granny's in there it's fine yeah
in Japan and it took me so much courage
to like get in there with her thankfully
we went to like we went to a resort that
had like several different onsets there
and there was one that was supposedly
like not so popular because Cali scouted
them all out for me because she doesn't
really mind at all and I said we could
go to this one this one's always pretty
empty so we went there and the moment we
entered you know there were like two old
Japanese ladies there they probably
feared the Gaijin so they left the
moment they saw us thankfully so that I
felt a bit more comfortable about that
and then well you know even even Justice
Cali I felt really nervous and I
complained that I was gonna look like
looking at her but you know oh my God
and it's oh it's rough it's rough it's
rough but I'm glad I got over it and
went to Affair but I also one one time
only I went alone to a big big big
public one which was a big mistake
because that one was so crowded oh and I
felt like everybody was looking at me
because I was the only guy Jean the only
Foreigner
and I I and I was like I didn't know
where to look because at every corner
since it was so crowded that I've
recorded it was a naked lady I didn't
want them to think I was looking at them
I didn't know what to look it was so
awkward oh your feet okay it's so funny
because when I went to an Onsen right
the whole thing is you're not supposed
to stare like you're supposed to be
respectful I'm not stare at any of the
Japanese grandmothers they sure as heck
did not get the memory
[Music]
I'm telling you if you need someone to
go with you I'll go with you I can scan
before before I'm good if I need to get
into a fist fight with an obach on I'll
get into a fist
like private ones yeah guys guys it gets
worse though it gets like I mean worse
in terms of comfortableness so I've been
told that in Korea they have also like
something like an Onsen but then the old
ladies will start to wash you
would they give me a massage
apparently
I'm like really scared that's like next
level Onsen wait this random Granny's
just started watching you
not randomly but like it's it's pretty
common apparently yeah I just have a
granny watch you are they naked too how
I mean yeah
maybe that's like a volunteer service
you know how like when old people don't
have a job anymore they're bored maybe
they sign up to be like a volunteer
bathroom okay and that's just that's
just uh exaggerated it's a service but
you know okay yeah
okay I thought you literally meant like
a random Granny's where they would just
come up to you and just start like
scrubbing your back yeah they are
strangers there's a lot of cultures
where it's like you know like a lot of
cultures are very communal and if you go
to the Onsen right and you're all by
yourself I feel like the grandmas would
be like hey like you know we can wash we
can help look at that I think it's a
community thing they're not it turns out
they're not naked okay so that's good
that's good anymore
wow amazing maybe somehow maybe them
being naked would make it fairer to me
like would make me feel more comfortable
because you're like equals right you're
the only one naked right maybe they
should be naked
make it equal make it fair I'm not gonna
push for this but I will say when we if
we are in Japan at the same time ever we
should go to an Onsen I won't push for
this I won't like but if anything
give me the side and I find like 12
private ones okay I'm fine we're going
to a water park
oh I love water parks there's a water
park
um no it's not a water park it's an
amusement park and hot springs together
that I've been doing
I thought there's a ferris wheel in
Japan where you can sing karaoke in the
ferris wheel oh you could do like the
Inuyasha ending well you're in the
ferris wheel you know that one okay I
don't know it but I want to do that
sing Inuyasha and the parents yeah I
like how specific that is
this is
cut out oh yeah who did that
[Laughter]
okay what the heck is that what is that
I don't know what they are now oh it
wasn't me so say so wait what do you
mean
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's what it's me
ant around with you guys see you guys
are like Rosemary so stay so but this is
what it was meant to be I've been
betrayed I thought I thought I was
getting the joke for once
what no yours is perfect thank you who's
that happening
wait what the heck is Nina I don't care
I tweeted it everyone's timeline needs
to be cursed
the evil Rock Nina looks like it looks
like a torpedo like it's don't worry
about it looks like those examples like
rocks that are like crazy yeah they're
evil volcanoes yeah yeah yeah
that we have now where are your markings
are you are the markings
yes allegedly oh illegal information is
news also like like Kiara's
yes what does it look like that
I'm confused what do you mean what do
you mean that's what the body looks like
what do you mean
like that
it's really realistic actually I'm quite
proud of this one yeah it's actually
really good no no yours is a good Kiara
I meant Nina's oh
my fridge I'm gonna print this
might need to go to a doctor yeah Nina's
I have no idea what is happening there
you know
roller this is what happens later on
apparently rests sag when you have big
ones okay
something you girls don't know
flat is Justice yeah all right all right
girls let's move on
okay let's see Rosa means
sweet very sweet
I just have to work I'm sorry I cannot
draw yeah why did she have like a beret
on her head
I finished the blanket
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow it's actually kind of cute what the
hell I like Grandma Puma very much I
told you I want to pull with my grandma
oh
have you yeah have you heard like any
stories about boma's Grandma no
she has a grandma
yeah what stories are there why do you
girls know her grandma Stars she tells
her Grandma's stories my grandma is a
little crazy
um
you know some okay so I'll tell the
story that people quote the most
probably so one time I was at my mom's
house and we were eating dinner and we
were just having a nice time and it got
quiet my grandma just says something
unprompted no no reason real no Rhyme or
Reason why she said this but she just
says
you know
if you come up behind me
you better fight me or [\h__\h] me
and and we were like Grandma oh my god
wow that is the feisty Grandma yeah
every she's gotten into fights at the
old people's home her roommate had to
move out
she's my Oshie I wish you were more like
her my great grandma would like flirt
with every like guy she would see it
should be like she's unable to move and
she'd be like flirting with all the guys
and they'd be like 20 years younger than
her and she she was so popular with the
grandpas it's crazy a lion what is that
called
every year that we get older it's one
year that we are closer to being cougars
girls
what's that again it's when an older
woman likes a younger
but what if you just don't want the
younger guys what if you just like women
yeah yeah
I think it's still a cougar
oh is it yeah I don't know though
hmm I just wonder like if I'm really
really old what could be my pickup line
like hey boy I'll add you to my will
you know
hey baby girl no one ready
you were too eager to say that
yeah
have you you know really hot girls come
to a funeral you want to come to my what
oh my gosh
oh my God that is really confusing yeah
yeah
well I'm I'm sorry in advance
[Music]
I don't think I could even I don't I
don't know
[Music]
I lost my phone number can I have yours
for universal one
[Music]
that is so gross
you don't know any pickup lines try them
try them
some pick up plans on us
oh grandmas have candy okay I have this
famous one that came up with that I
never brought it back because it's so
bad
hey girl are you a pizza cause your mods
are really cute
you're what oh my God
I've never said again whatever you're
what because your mom's are really cute
moths like matzo cheese Mozzarella
mozzarella mozzarella really cute you
wish maybe change it not Mozzarelli
mozzarella cute oh just mozzarella mean
awesome
[Music]
oh the whole thing is you're saying
because you're really cute but yeah
adding the mozzarella in it yeah
like are you cheese pizza yeah
I
don't love it but I'm also old and
cranky and stinky and stinky yeah
I got one oh
um uh
baby are you a side quest because I want
to grind you real bad wow
sorry
for experience makes you know for
experiences
I don't know
the grinding part
experience it really sucks man you have
to grind so hard for some games and to
get to you know go to this one area and
kill 30 lions and then after go here and
kill 50 salons
give me some proper quests lead me
through the game properly
I wanted to be done properly all right
anyway my God oh my God my cat is coming
up with some hey crazy are you
what's that guy's name Jason Krueger
who's that guy
the what what's the Moz guy's name Jason
Krueger
Michael Krueger
white mask
am I Jason Voorhees because I want you
to wear me like a hockey mask
no I want to wear you like a hockey I
don't know
I'm crying hey girl where did they come
from
yeah
are you Jason corgis because
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't play the scary games at all I am
so bad with the scary games
yeah me too I can't not play scary games
you and I can lie against the plague
right there the scourge yeah but again
like you know before we had you know
similarities in terms of uh free sizes
and now we have similarities in terms of
interest when it comes to games
scary games and not so scary games
anytime people ask me mine I just named
the three that Marilyn Monroe has and
I'm like those three same as Marilyn
Monroe
haha
by the way oh Rosemary you wouldn't
understand it's for people who have hips
and breasts
you wouldn't get it
I don't want to have no body I just have
like I'm literally a stick figure I
don't even have a yeah you're right both
me yeah I have them for you was me okay
are you are you Samus because I want to
glump you like a Metroid
oh
what does glomping mean exactly
I don't that's what it felt like to me I
don't know
I thought that was like an action
[Laughter]
yeah
what is it it's like a like a over an
enthusiastic yeah yeah right
apparently it is a Run and Jump hog but
for me it felt more like you know like
glomp you know I would rather be
um running hugs than die
it was basically like covering my whole
body in that Metroid
I mean I'm gonna be a metric for you
girl
you're the only Metroid I will not shoot
down then
oh my God everybody what are some good
pickup lines hold on someone just sent
me this one
are you a fossil sample because I'm an
impatient paleontologist and I want to
date you badly
that's really good I was aimed at you
because you're old
right as in you want to find out what
that where when that that fossil
yeah
wow good
um I'm getting Indiana Jones Vibes I
like it
oh that maybe that is a reference what
is NSP
m
U
that's paleontology joke has layers is
that a is that enough because because
layers you know you have to like there's
layers to fossils she's cooking she's
cooking
the kitchen's on fire it's on fire oh
she's burning it down oh God blow it out
Kiara [\h__\h] yeah
I have to ask you uh I was told to ask
you from the chat oh what is your type
and why is it me
I mean I just genuinely want to know
this is not supposed to be a pickup line
oh so uh I want to add really quickly
when we met up in Japan uh homo wasn't
there and Kiara kept asking about Pomo
and she kept being like hey what about
pomu do you know this about
so I'm just saying there we go
[Music]
actually
so my my next month's members only
wallpaper I will reveal something now
I'm sorry it's not related to the other
girls but I got a hoverboard with purple
I'm remembering tomorrow no I I
commissioned your artist to drop me my
members
and there's a little reference to you in
there
I can't wait oh my God oh my God
[Music]
oh my gosh I can't wait to see it
okay
um anyway so we play the game again
[Music]
I have to use the restroom oh okay okay
I've been getting too much excitement
and too much wine
okay
[Music]
thank you
oh I like
[Music]
um
maybe nothing that's related to oh no
that's interesting
that's an interesting one I will choose
this one
that will come out as an interesting
piece of art you have to think about
what will give you the best result and
the best confusion to the next person
who sees it
okay
[Music]
I don't know oh I like that one actually
okay hold on I'm gonna write that one
down
yeah
or cannot get Advanced from chat
no
[Music]
but why is it just recently that it's
become so popular
I don't know I don't know I guess more
people here Australian saying oh no no
[Music]
because I I saw it I think where I
started seeing it is do you guys know
new jeans
is from Australia and she always says
Nara and and then they make a joke about
it sorry
everywhere else too
[Music]
yeah we have a couple Australians yeah
and so they say nor I think that's yeah
that's why I got popular with us because
we have like so many Australians
improper British or or something else
action
it's really beautiful what did I miss
I'm talking about Noir
not really what do you mean what do you
mean not really nor like what's more oh
nor like nor why do we always say it the
same way or he's like Gnar more
um when I was in Japan the other day I I
was walking by like a store which the
name I took a photo actually it was
literally nor
[Laughter]
the hair and makeups I will upload the
pictures
[Music]
right s
oh that's when I was typing up your
script
oh and I just didn't delete it
it was okay well if you if you want to
go to the north hair and makeup place I
posted a picture now you will find it
easily
Twitter on Twitter
oh
no no
um
it's so trendy too
and I think it looks a little I mean
that sign is pretty beat up
like it's kind of cheap they have to re
renovate it
[Music]
maybe now with all the new uh customers
incoming they will have the
um
their popularity yeah yeah get your
horror and your makeup done yeah of
course we should go we should do one
more like we're almost
now
okay
I need a second one too
share some with me okay
um I like this one just take the one
that's already right there
they give our names
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
that is uh
why
I made it even better okay I'm ready
Freddy my name's not even Freddie
oh
the only one who didn't attempt this in
the pretty stream okay I hear you
laughing what's going on
I dreamed a dream and I'm gone
what does that mean you'll see
oh my God
I'll figure it out and and that to me
and that to me you don't let me down now
um
don't let me down how do I oh I'll do
this I'll do this
here is the head
all right all right I mean I'm just
being realistic here because I don't
think I could really do it
okay okay this is words
I think this will bring out some
questions like what is this
it's perfect don't ask questions just
create good art you know
all right when you're the one saying
that so I'm expecting big things now
give her a little t-shirt
some patchy holes wow he's always naked
let's make them wear some clothes yeah
give them some clothes
otherwise it's gonna get age restricted
so we don't want it I mean yeah I think
Eva Mina Drew her full-on breasts on
stream
ing I don't know what you're talking
about oh the Twin Peaks she did yeah
[Music]
oh shoot
beep up I didn't need a little patch
Tick Tock time is running
[Music]
okay I think that's good
what are you gonna cook after stream
[Music]
oh
I'm not
what oh what is this oh
this is so cute oh my God what is the
name of that Trend
um
wait
is this not as cute as I thought it was
is this maybe
I think so Rosie
so
that's super cute
oh
okay hold on
okay
why is it so detailed okay
I got this i got this I'll do my best
I'll do my best I'll do my best you
gotta hurry up you gotta hurry up we
don't have a lot of time
no it's still fine
yeah
we got plenty of time it just started
oh my God
laughs
okay
you guys singing
okay okay
hold the whole dream job let me I'm
getting to the point where it gets funny
oh it's so funny
I'm sorry for it whoever sees this
this know that I tried
it's it's
you know you guys get it right
chat do they really I think so
I think this is good
okay maybe it's not good maybe it's not
good yeah
veiny so done with their [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
no
you love us you love it take it back
[Laughter]
come on oh
no I'm honestly really honest all the
time that's my European jeans that I
can't hold back so I wish I wish I could
maybe maybe I should be Cinderella maybe
it would help
I think that's that right
giving my homework early
yeah
no filter at all
sometimes good though speak your mind
say it loud and proud you're ready for
the people in the back
I will always speak the truth whenever I
can all right are you ladies ready no
yes
yeah
kill me
oh this is so cute oh yeah
really we're working at Naya Sanji
daycare
[Laughter]
what's wrong with us
this is just too stressful I'm gonna lie
special
oh don't worry do not worry about this
if you don't know don't worry about it
yeah there we go that's fine
that's good yeah just to pay that
confusion
finana's been erased cute
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
is so cool I know what
I like how your breasts are touching the
floor before your feet
flying
[Music]
people told me
to play
[Laughter]
in case you don't know every time I'm
sick that's what Nina calls me
okay I have to tell you ages ago Rosalie
and I went on a trip
and uh she was like on another
co-worker's couch right Millie uh I
almost said Millie parfait Millie
parfait's couch and she was just like oh
and she really looked like that like
Victorian Tower she was like oh I'm just
not feeling well and Billy was on the
floor
holding both of his arm and like
caressing roseme's arm while Rosie was
on Millie's couch like dying
dramatic
that shows you who the real ones are man
when you're dying yeah you're dying
Victorian child apparently
I was laughing I'll be honest
I was like not feeling I was like oh my
God I feel so bad and you know it's like
haha you look like a dying Victorian
I did ask like do you want some tea some
water some Advil if you want anything
what you were taking care of and you
were still kind of like oh I I did you
know I did the air conditioner was on
she was listening to her favorite music
she was being really really caring like
that too yeah I think you can be both
caring and still make fun of your
friends
you know
accidental Renaissance
oh
no
um
till we're doing anything in like a
karaoke and roseme is feeling like a
little sick you're gonna love it it's so
cute
why does everyone want to see me in pain
he really does look like a dying
Victorian time
thank you
Rosemary twist I hope that will not
happen I hope everyone will be Genki and
at their bestest yeah
okay can you tell me like when we go to
karaoke until five in the morning which
we will what are some of the songs you
plan to sing oh
[Music]
I mean realistically I'll probably sing
some you know Idol J-pop songs like
songs like What tell us
do you know hello projects
because of your 3D debut yes I love
Brown project and and oh I guess I might
you know when it comes to uh like
English songs I might sing some um
oh
my life
Fergalicious I don't know
um
and maybe uh I'll sing
um Leaving on a Jet Plane by a rabbits
like viewers are crying now they're book
bursting out in tears hey oh
it's it's a song that you know it has a
lot of history because when I left Japan
after like a one year stay which is when
I joined Holo uh at the end we did like
an a karaoke me and Kelly did one that
was like a farewell karaoke and one of
the songs I sang where I started crying
while singing it it was a song Leaving
on a Jet Plane I don't know when I'll be
back again
it's kind of like a PTSD song Oh no
you could be crying in Japan singing
that song
yeah but you'll be back in Japan it's
like exactly a circle
what would you guys sing
to impress people
I am known for my Yokai Tai sodaichi
because I do the dance
[Music]
oh
let me always thinks the really really
cute songs
can you do that in a circulation dance
I know a little bit of I never learned
like all of it entirely oh you can teach
me
oh you know Kiara you know you know
Rosemary is really good Rosemary is
really good at singing one of marine
song songs
no I've actually don't know it I was
like what do you think he did it I was
reading the talking parts and that was
it oh you did it so well really I was
just really talking but it was crazy
they're gonna show you they're gonna
impress you I promise oh
but okay I know that Nina keeps on
talking about you know trying to improve
her singing skills
[Music]
in karaoke I typically will sing a lot
of like English like Dad Rock like
Nickelback stuff like that uh but my
favorite Japanese singers when I was
growing up was gagged Miyavi and I
really love Hot Springs
stuff like that so I sing like kind of
like I guess the dad rock version
but only old women love gack
do you have any young cool cute friends
that love gact be honest
ly old women love visual K and gact and
all that stuff come on
well visual K is still popular yeah
[Laughter]
I don't really know how many Zoomers
either right yeah
usually my go-to is like old anime
openings like you're talking like old
um Inuyasha openings and endings
we're talking like old Gintama opening
a bug take has like one of my favorite
uh openings uh endings from holic like
I'll usually do anime openings and
endings
oh oh I want to sing one song for your
girls
I like when we get there because uh
Mariah holic
um opening where there's a lot of
moaning
no
[Applause]
bleed basically I want to sing that one
I'm so good at that one
I'm so committed to it I can't wait okay
what about you what about you
um
please
why do you why are you always asking me
about them
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh I ate I ate
oh I'm hungry
[Music]
I sing I sing like a bunch of like chica
Idol songs that I can't sing normally
because there there's no karaokes of
them that
existing machines sometimes sometimes
like the more popular groups are will
you do the dads too maybe
and I like to sing Macross songs
[Music]
oh wow
who scored for not thinking that up
yeah okay macro song is always goat yes
yes
girls I want to feel this yes should we
do like one last round and then end this
because there's hungry people okay
one more or we can just zatsu for the
other round what do you prefer
oh that was fine too I don't care I feel
I feel as we keep drawing I don't think
I'm gonna draw any better because I've
had a little bit of wine drop better
the point of the Garth tech phone
I I I'd be okay to talk if everyone else
is cool with talking people want the
zatsu in my chat
probably because we stopped talking when
we grow up
I only have one brain cell I only have
one at least it was a like a free draw
mode or something that you could just
like oh yeah scribble and have a bit
more common question oh I have an answer
let's let's imagine a different timeline
where kiwawa gets into a ninja Sanji Ian
generation not to replace someone just
as an additional member which generation
would koala be in I think closet light
because you were early on and off in
vtubing right that you in terms of time
but where would you like fit I can't see
you like getting along well in the Syria
also though yeah I was gonna say
ethereum yeah because we have a lot of
uh yeah we have a lot of singers
and honestly I could use another
extrovert
yeah I feel like it everyone in like
ethereum there's just like so like
extroverted like even like and not like
I don't know I feel like
I wonder
of course that would want to be in
lazulite though because you probably
come come
I just feel like early on yeah I feel
like it would because uh uh myth debuted
I think before lazulite right yeah yeah
instant reaction was like well you'd be
in the first gen I'm your senpai
hmm do you girls have like a like a
quite the Senpai cool high like I don't
know thing going on or not at all
not that much I feel I feel like some
people call us Senpai but yeah yeah link
of it for example Ike calls me Nina
Senpai but I'm two months a senpai to
him and for example I have zero respect
for Pomo as my Senpai
oh my God
because like for example me and Rosie
have two months between debuts and
obviously I didn't trust her and like
I'll ask her for advice on stuff but in
a lot of times like I might have really
unique things happen in my stream that
Rosie might not be able to give me
advice on because she hasn't dealt with
that as a senpai I think in like uh for
holo live you guys have a much more
obvious like Senpai kohai culture yeah
yeah also because there's so much time
in between yeah that's what I was
thinking well I think a lot of us we all
kind of grew together because we were
all so short in between debuts
[Music]
and who's the most reliable
like you you did my freak I told Pomo I
didn't I couldn't find anybody for my
outro and she made me my outro despite
having just debuted and being busy
promo has been one of my most reliable
senpais since the start genuinely
that's so sweet
what's your statement to that
um
but you know I just
oh oh
growling I love her a lot and she always
will like give me her advice give me her
stuff
[Music]
good good Senpai you wear the Senpai
title very well
no
and she'll always I feel like everyone's
so busy and everyone kind of like for
example I don't I never joined any scary
game collabs I will not force myself to
do a scary game but I feel like homo as
Senpai will always go out of her way to
try and like make sure she's interacting
with everybody she's joining everyone's
collab she's there for everybody oh I
feel she really really goes out of her
way to do that kind of stuff
lying she's
I almost said
the Australian noise
ignore
yeah she's an ore what what doesn't that
just mean no yeah no no I feel like for
my senpai's personally a lot of them are
pretty introverted and like kind of you
know in their own little bubble and I
feel poem has been consistently the
Senpai that's tried our hardest to get
out of the bubble and to try and help us
and to like even
he's like kind of shy and not feeling it
she's always like trying
[Music]
yeah it's a bit of a like for I feel
like for last night in the city it's a
bit of like a weird like because you
were like we we all joined at the same
time right
[Music]
I don't think I don't know the Senpai I
think anything yeah the most reliable
I'm not really the type of person to
like reach out first like if I have like
a problem I'll try to like usually like
fix it myself I feel like one person
who's very like Tech oriented would be
like support
yeah but I don't know I guess there's
like a few people who are like
if you have an issue with this here's
this fix yeah yeah yeah there's a few
members I think who um don't use Discord
very often so like they just it doesn't
they just don't like answer as often but
there's a couple people that are very
active on the Discord so if we have a
problem they're really quick to answer
yeah yeah
and one of my so one of our one of our
co-workers Kiara his name is Shu he like
until I went on a trip to Japan with
like him and other people I didn't
really get to interact with him a lot
but he has always helped me with
different stuff that went wrong like he
he wouldn't be stupid he's like oh I see
that Nina and Scarlet have a problem and
he'll jump in to help us fix the problem
yeah wow I always told him like I feel
as a co-worker he's wonderful you know
because sometimes the closer you are to
people the more you kind of help each
other out
but having a co-worker that you're not
really close with you don't share jokes
with you don't you know but they still
help you when they know they can help
[Music]
yeah I like that yeah sometimes you
don't even like have to like say
anything they'll just be like here's the
fix for this if you ever have this one
issue
[Music]
I'm not really receiving much help just
because I'm a pro
oh yeah yeah but definitely in the early
days that would always get help from
Ahmed I think
um
I'm trying to also be reliable and help
out like plan some projects and also
tell people like give them advice like I
think I give I give someone like
thumbnail advice like I gave I give
crony from now why can you give me some
new advice
well I mean I wouldn't say my thumb is a
really really special
I think your little one is so cute it is
yeah I was motivated motivation
so I wonder I hope oh yeah okay the
Advent calendar yeah yeah I hope people
can see me as someone reliable
um it's nice to be relied on right it
feels nice so I will be more reliable
I want to be reliable yeah I want to be
that Senpai because I have to be I'm
from the first gym yeah
I think you know you you don't you
shouldn't pressure yourself that much
yes you're the first gen but I think
every other person that comes into the
company you know we're all professionals
and you can do your best to help
everybody but at the same time
like don't don't put that pressure on
you
I don't know it's not a pressure it's
it's a pleasure not a pressure
I am the old one that was very old
[Music]
sign of words
trying to get better at English for my
whole life now
another thing too is like sometimes you
want to be a really good Senpai but a
lot of people can be pretty independent
and that's okay yeah
I think in our uh Ian there's like most
people are always very moving very
independently that's what it feels like
yeah
[Music]
for help
we would have been here I know so often
I'll like want to ask about something
and my chat will be like you should ask
so and so and I'm like I don't want to
bother them
for sure they wouldn't Monday would be
happy probably get a message from you
yeah we definitely I feel like
everyone's always so independent the
only times I ever asked for help is
usually for like music I'll ask for help
for music We have a lot of people who
know music and Ian too
you have so many like Talent like Petra
oh my God yeah do so much stuff on her
own thing yeah production company
[Music]
she's cracked
I wish I had so many skills
though you just have different skills
yeah
yeah I guess so
I feel sad oh my God girls wow
where do we go for dinner if we go for
dinner
where do you want to go wait we're going
for dinner yeah oh my God I'm not even
dressed
I need to fix my hair I don't know where
do you want to go oh yeah
are you good at grilling can you yeah
I'm afraid of the grill
places they Grill it for you anyway but
yeah grilling yourself is more fun I
don't think so too yeah it's so
difficult
I don't mind helping to grill but I'm
always really happy when somebody else
grills because I can just relaxed I know
I used to always be the one who lets
others grow but like with like non-hono
friends in the past but every every time
I went grilling with whole life en
members I'm I end up in the griller a
lot of the time
look at me in the eyes do you want to
grill or not I think that do you want to
grill over I would probably over Grill
things sometimes
so many times that I I have like some
knowledge for example after like a
little bit of grilling you should always
ask the tangians and the the staff to
change your grill because it will change
I feel like every time I went they've
always done it like they know when to do
it right oh yeah sometimes they do it
for you but sometimes they don't notice
so you're gonna be like somebody Mustang
yeah I hate like calling out to people
I have a button
I'm just like oh my God I'd rather just
have my my doll grilled and
then Ohio
good morning oh
but I guess good morning yeah if you
want I will grill for you
I will give staff secret money to grill
for you here's the thing though that's
the thing about we should all be
grilling there shouldn't only be one
person
I cannot Grill that's what I like I'm
happy for you guys can Grill I bought a
little Grill recently I'll practice oh
wait something on top of the grill and
then you take it off after a few seconds
I know but I'm so bad annoying when to
take it off and I'll and then I feel
like I'm always like fumbling I'm like
I'm gonna drop I'm gonna drop the meat
everywhere
[Music]
okay we'll see
we'll see but free a lot of Yakiniku
places though the staff can cook for you
and especially if we tell them that
we're beginners I can pull the Baka guys
it's about doing it yourself but I
cannot so that's why I'm happy even
other people can do it at night
foreign
I feel like kind of embarrassed when
they they Grill it you know how they
think is best and then oftentimes it
like is still way too red for my
personal preference wait yeah
I've been
trying
all right let me know when we were
eating actually yeah really
but I think like you said like one of
the meats was like
right
ah maybe
um
your steak Kiara oh no no medium rare is
fine oh that's amazing yeah that's great
yeah that's good but maybe I maybe a few
more seconds
[Laughter]
what's the order what's the order
it's rare medium rare no no it's blue oh
blue is a thing yeah
okay wait wait wait what the heck is
blue
what that's just like really really raw
I guess who was like raw reeled the
sides of the steak
I've never heard like does it come from
a blue cow or yes called Pomo rainbow
rain puff did you saw jian's first wave
lazulite I'm green
I even cooked is it like cooked or where
medium rare medium medium well okay I
would probably prefer a medium don't say
the medium well don't say it don't say
it
[Music]
I don't want people to judge me
but no it's not let's find out over the
years I've been I've started to enjoy
um very much uh and and medium medium is
premium as we've heard
in your defense
again this is I'm just gonna say this
very broadly I have heard from people
who own Korean barbecues that you should
be well cooking a lot of your Korean
barbecue Meats oh really because
typically like it's better to just well
cook them just to be on the safer side
um home for a lot of you know since
you're not getting a steak at a
steakhouse it's like you're getting
dinner it's really nice yeah I think
that's okay
as long as it's not bleeding I think I'm
good
yes I'm I'm kind of the same way I don't
like it it looks if my plate turns red
I'm like but even like like medium rare
medium rare has like this can have a lot
of blood right
but I have had raw like really good
quality of course raw beef I love
rocking and the Capers and the mustard
it's really good it can't be really good
but I would prefer to just Grill it
that's fair that's fair yeah well two
year old girls have any like vegetarians
or vegans
I have met like I think I'm one of the
people who's met one of the most members
and I don't think anyone's been veggie
some some people don't like fish
no
at one time he got an Uber Eats and it
was just a chicken finger with tartar
sauce that's it
Nina someone said Mika is vegetarian oh
yeah she's but she's not Ian oh
yeah he's a vegetarian and to give it
more I always forget I always offer her
meat and she's like Nina I'm vegetarian
I've met Mika like three times and we
always have this problem I feel so bad
oh I wonder then if you remember my
preferences for drinks you don't drink
alcohol yeah
I don't drink either
yeah
we're not drinking and
things I think Petra wasn't drinking
ah I think did she
poor Lira I kept ordering drinks for
both me and Olivia so oh my God
but she wasn't drinking as much as
YouTube yeah
you and you you guys are good enough
Kiara and I were not drinking the most
sober karaoke that's what we'll do
yeah well you know gotta stay sober too
not accidentally say something and then
get bonked by my company hey
be careful okay well go be careful who
have to have control over myself my body
I remember the Drinker how is good
though it was like some like mocktail or
something oh yeah yeah
I just remembered the place where we
were at they had a limited amount of
people yeah
[Music]
and we were like okay wait do you still
have the pizza they're like yes we were
so happy we're like oh my God yeah it
wasn't even that great I feel like
everything else was better than the
pizza it was okay it was all right it
was all right it was just like we were
so surprised because it was late in the
evening really late and if it's so
limited they said what like five I think
it was like ten per day but we were like
no way they still have the pizza but
they did what's wrong why nobody ordered
the beans I don't know I'll have the
pizza yeah yeah yeah
popular what you learned the reason why
I didn't I honestly like did not think
it was below average I thought it was
good pizza
I was enjoying the other food a lot like
the pizza is all right
sorry you weren't even there and we'll
keep on talking about this day no it's
okay let's let's include her when we go
to Japan the four of us it's planned
it's already happening I want to go to
shimokitazawa to Thrift Store please
okay I mean
the ref on old people you know okay yeah
you know you'll have to like we go on a
Monday we go on a Monday afternoon
there's not a lot of people we go to La
foreign
um I'm the one I'm the one walking slow
that's me
when you get out of there it's better
and the other streets
every time I walk for Turkish the dolly
when it's crowded yeah oh I I think
about the things I would do to these
people oh my God please don't beat me up
one day
just gonna come in with boxing gloves
[Music]
um
that wasn't me I'm never gonna beat you
up
[Music]
she'll beat you up and desert you no
no
in my crate they'll be like oh no
because I just just walk even somewhere
I'll walk you in the boy
I have finana because she had never gone
before oh it wasn't so bad actually how
was it
mildly crowded but not so bad but
there's always so many aggressive people
around there yeah they like try to offer
you or try to get you to go places
yeah the story people yeah I think
that's way stronger in other places like
oh Shinjuku oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
not that bad and for these kind of
things
I mean you could get offered and once in
a while someone comes but then they say
hey would you like to join this model
agency oh my God yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'm glad so my Senpai told me at
the airport she's like people will
approach you Nina and they're gonna try
to interview you you have to say no you
cannot and he actually did because I
would have been like yeah of course I
want a Ninja yeah I didn't realize that
like you know my voice my
oh yeah oh I did once
um like many many years ago when I was
in in somebody asked you know you want
to join this company oh I did once go
ahead and like went for like the
interview oh and then I think they took
some pictures to possible
I don't think it was Polaroids but yeah
I went ahead and I mean it wasn't too
bad like they had a nice decent nice
like office in a good location and it
wasn't too bad but generally I wouldn't
really recommend because I'm so sassy
here yeah and it was fun it was like
yeah it wasn't too sus I don't know I
think it was fine but I went like
through a lot of
um like self-initiated uh interviews and
stuff as well like to you know do stuff
wanted to get jobs wow like in that
industry but yeah the self uh uh what
did I say self-initiated ones are
definitely on the less satisfied yeah
you can at least like look into the
company yeah not someone on the street
that's so scary
[Music]
no no
no fun what
okay
you had a good time yeah but if you need
me just tell me I can bark at people
like a like a little dog
[Laughter]
be that intimidating what was it mean I
like him yeah yeah yeah yeah
you'd be surprised just the barking
that's the intimidating thing they don't
call me Bros me for nothing Kiara
[Laughter]
I know you've met her and she seems so
shy but when she has like something to
defend she gets like fired up her arms
expand three times yeah yeah I'm like
Popeye
who are you gonna call
frozen meals
to be Busters
can I ask um Kiara when you're in Japan
do you have a favorite neighborhood or a
favorite and like please don't say like
your favorite favorite spot because I
don't want people to you know but do you
have like a favorite
stuff that you like to do
and like a favorite place I used to have
a favorite like area but not So Much
Anymore these days they're like
um I feel like I like a lot of places I
wouldn't say I have a favorite one but
things to do I just I mean I just always
like going to karaoke and put it
shopping also stresses me out at the
same time
yeah too much shopping yeah but I do
want to do like a bit more sightseeing
because I when I lived in Japan I didn't
do much sightseeing it just kind of like
I mean certain I know a lot of places in
Tokyo and Osaka but
I want to see like different corners of
Japan that would be nice but there's one
place that I used to always go to that I
always like when I'm in Japan with
someone who's there for the first time I
always bring them there it's called
enoshima oh my God I'm gonna be going
there for the first time next week
it's one of my dream places to go to I
just never had gotten yeah
no right yes
wait what yeah I'm going to Japan next
week
what
kind of is that something you're allowed
to say Yeah well yeah
if it makes you feel any better I too
was surprised she said it I too was like
wait what she said it yeah we've already
talked about it on stream before
let me if you already plan to go to
enoshima let me tell you so so there's
this I mean energy but this is like a
bigger place but the one thing that you
really need to do right no it's no no no
it's an island like a little island and
you walk over to it over a bridge and
then I know what you're talking about
ah you probably saw in an anime didn't
you no
Bubble look me at the eyes and tell me
you'd never take a trip based off
something you saw in an anime okay I I
used to play this game called love plus
and then you get to take your girlfriend
to enoshima and I just really wanted to
go he's going with it
oh my God
are you bringing your anime girlfriend
are you bringing her
because apparently I think recently it
wasn't in an anime again it shows up
quite a bit wasn't it funny girl Senpai
right
oh money girl Senpai I think uh
apparently also in Pochi it wasn't
recently
[Music]
be prepared you have to like walk up and
down so many stairs there are escalators
a lot of walking guys you're really
exhausted make sure to like walk around
the whole island you can easily do it
and even like
pops what do you like what do you like
in on the island tell us like everything
what's what's what's the tea
there's a secret spot that I showed um
you know people before as well
um but when I went there the other time
when it was bad weather it wasn't even
it was really underwhelming
[Music]
but there's like once you go up the like
beginning path where all the shops are
you will know it when you get there then
if you go to the right and then for like
I have like a secret path uh yeah um
yeah this is like a little store
um yeah and in summer there's a lot of
people there but during like colder days
not so much but it's like a really
serene
seen for me like oh you're there and
then you look at the water and just just
I don't know
I know I just been wanting to go to the
beach recently me too I really want to
go to the beach what's that one yeah I
want to go to the beach too but it's not
like warm warm enough for the beach yet
right
how to say uh
Japanese people will probably agree with
me but Kanagawa beaches are definitely
not the pretty beaches in Japan
[Music]
is in I mean there's a lot of surfers
there but it's not really like
especially I understand why you don't go
yeah I mean some people still go there
to swim but it's not that oh no I don't
want to swim I just want to watch the
beach I just want to see the ocean I
don't want to swim
yeah or or surfing if you suddenly take
up a surfing hobby I've surfed before I
want to serve I want to learn how to
serve me too later on in my life maybe
one day I want to move to Portugal have
a lemon tree and Sir wow
almost surfing fairy well not like well
okay so not I couldn't do like big waves
but there's like a really thin board you
can get and like you ride on like the
the really thin part of the water with
it I don't remember what it's called
but it's called
no no no no
I'm like we're running a long way so
I've never actually done some big big
ways you know like I think it's
skimboarding yeah skimboard camboarding
boogie board boogie board wake no big
boogie boards were too or too thick what
does this the skimboarding was like yeah
yeah yeah that was look that looks more
like what I
skin recording
oh
yo can you do a flip
yeah yeah
I'll do you know Kiara you're showing
your screen just in case
[Laughter]
oh God that's fine you know what's the
worst part I saw us talking on your
channel and I felt like I should have
been like hey we should make you should
make yourself like big screen to talk to
us
what what I thought you should like make
yourself like big camera to talk to us
like you know the big like
talking camera
the big talking camera excuse me
anyway yeah
[Music]
anyway where were we hungry yeah I am
still hungry yeah I think food time
I think it's all right wait guys what
what restaurant are we going to what
where are we meeting
we got on such a tangent after talking
about how to cook
I just want to say thank you so much for
joining me I had so much fun I'm so
sorry the game didn't work if you want
to do more collabs I will make a better
point to research them do you think that
is not Uno anything that is not Uno I am
down for it yeah I will look for co-op
games for us okay
that's good I love you girls I had so
much fun yeah
you know it wasn't there it wasn't
didn't pull me like say that she's
planning something big and I don't
really think you are you really planning
something big
even I heard about that
[Music]
collab a big one I can't even say that a
long time ago I think we were talking
about maybe doing something but we just
got busy yeah it never wait a minute are
you staying we should have a crab game
crap game I never played them before I'm
afraid we'll be too toxic oh my God
friendships are broken if we ever played
craft game
like you would never want to oh yeah I
go feral I go feral you're so bad
[Music]
and but you know
I I want to play yeah we should continue
on an idea I want something bigger you
know what do you want to play
I don't know how many ideas we can talk
about it yeah
but yeah I want to see if we can get
some I mean I would love to like always
have you girls to myself but I want to I
think some other girls
so thank you for accepting me like
decent and opening up to me and you
taking me in like you know I'm I belong
here it is really nice to be so welcomed
with open arms thank you I told my
audience after Alaska lab we like we
started talking an hour before the
collab and then we collabed and then we
kept talking and the only reason we
stopped was because we were both so we
were like we gotta eat but it's like
right now honestly
I know the thing that happens is once
again food to hunger always food that
prevents the further it really is I only
have breakfast and now it's almost
midnight so okay
you have to eat more
[Music]
it's a chicken or some fish because I
I've been wanting to eat more fish
because it turned out really well last
time okay well done good luck on the
camera wait what kind of thing I could
for you too
hake
oh
If Ever I could show you my recipe I
literally just take a salmon I put like
a foil around it I put lemon tomato
garlic garlic garlic yes garlic and then
you just put the foil in yeah
thank you girls for having me bye-bye
thanks for having me too thank you for
having me thank you for having me
sorry for the cursed topics no underwear
and yeah
[Music]
honestly the whole like one and a half
hours of figuring out how to play Uno
were really precious to me
I just have to say I love that when we
got to the
um switch part of Uno it didn't work for
different people so it wasn't just me
the problem
um
we know who the real problem is
sanjian's first wave sounds like oh hey
don't pick up my game right don't pick
up my granny I went to the servers and I
deleted your names
now I have to send all those friend
invites again tomorrow oh I feel so bad
for that
one by one step by step yeah
thanks for watching guys
[Music]
are you guys gonna talk to your chat or
are you gonna
talk a little bit I don't know okay you
guys are here after am I doing I don't
know
[Music]
okay
oh
bye
[Music]
here that goes
that was so great I was so nervous guys
I was so nervous because like okay
look I met Kiara IRL before him but I
don't know you know I'm so nervous to
collab with her it's like ah and I just
because I know I'm like a bit more timid
especially
like with people I haven't collabed too
much yet so I hope it wasn't too bad
when I get like that I try to like
push myself a bit to be more like
switchable but I don't know if I did
good enough or not I know full thank you
thank you thank you
um and you did them out I did not mod
that that did happen I did not mind they
can think it is so far thank you thank
you
[Music]
he really said I love green tea I did
I did say that I didn't see a little
green tea
foreign
oh my God I can't believe that was
mentioned so early on too
I will never be forgotten
this week is really pushed me with the
tech issues the like the weird part is
like okay now we talked is Ubisoft the
first time the last time was his last
numbers I feel like none of these could
have been like prevented or like stopped
this is nature has spoken this week
games will be against us
that's so crazy
but yeah um I did get um I will be able
to play Last of Us again
um which I was waiting for it to see if
I could play it again and I can't play
it again we're in a hole next month
um so hopefully we eat well I should be
able to finish it in the next month
um
but I also do hope that it gets patched
because I really want to like take my
time and appreciate the game and all
that kind of stuff so yeah
you like KitKat um yeah I love KitKat
yeah so I'm excited to play more of that
um and yeah I was happy about this
collab I'm really glad that Nina invited
me because I am a bit more shy and
um I might also be in two more clubs
with her next week I'm not mistaken I
think those are still being worked on
but
um she invited me to one
and when she was like you might want to
join I'm like okay
yeah
um also as you might have seen
I really wanted to bring this up because
I've been waiting
I actually I asked I asked us and I'm
like what's that son when are you gonna
like post this on Twitter and they're
like oh
like in an hour or two I'm like oh no
but yeah
um
I was a bit sad with like
um like this morning today but then
after this is a bit of like good news so
um yeah like 3.0 is finally gonna be
here in in a little bit in a little bit
it might be in like a few weeks or I
don't know let's see no date yet
um but just keep an eye out for it um
I've seen a little preview see the
little preview and it looks really good
like I'm not trying to toot my own horn
or anything but like for real like it
looks really good
it looks really really really good so
um I hope you can be excited for that
but she finally be able to wink without
tilting her head that's that to me issue
look
[Music]
just I like to do because it feels
normal just like
but yeah how's it going
[Music]
shiny
but yeah this is um
this one oh it's not
do it ah
you're awesome
this one
this one's fancy like this one's really
cute this is really cute
um
I'll remove some of the filter for the
good movie for the good facings
um this one's really cute though they're
like sparkly eyes one
Hawaii
but yeah the other ones are really good
also and I guess you'll have to wait and
see listen I would never say it was
really good unless it was really good so
this isn't it April Fool haha this was
my April's Fool's joke all along it's
not even April's fools here yet get
thrown
so yeah I'm not gonna see it with the
art because
you'll have to wait and find out but
they look really good
um and I will use them all the time I
just hope Peter just hope you're ready
because I know that sometimes when
people get a 3.0 they don't use it that
often but I will use it because
quite a bit
[Music]
when is the last Mario Party stream lot
available
um there are some just some tech issues
in the beginning so I was like cutting
out the beginning I don't know if
YouTube took it down or what I'm not too
sure how that works but I can check
thank you for the super thank you thank
you
thank you
finally someone who you see yeah I'm
gonna use it like very often
um so yeah
that is that
I don't know if it's still processing it
oh congrats on the 3.0 Kevin thank you
thank you thank you thank you really
excited for this to come out
[Music]
is that the Baka expression no this what
do you mean this is like a happy
expression
whether I'm planning on eating I had no
idea but I'm still hungry I have to go
eat right now because oh man actually
um last night I really wasn't feeling
good and I rested I just like sleeping a
bit helped and then I took some
medication and um I started feeling a
bit better I am actually a bit like
I don't know if you can uh here but like
my nose is a bit stuffed and went on
today
um but when I woke up this morning
um after I took my my Advil last night
my like headache went away but when I
woke up it was back again so I don't
know what is wrong with me I don't know
if I have to rest more I don't know if I
have to take things a bit easier but I'm
just gonna try it and be a bit more
mindful of my health because it has not
been the best lately I've I usually have
a lot of chronic migraines and headaches
but it's been really bad so I'm gonna
try and see um if I can hopefully
prevent that
drinking a lot of water especially
lately
lots of water last night and um today
are you really worried no I'm so I'm so
sorry really I feel really bad but I was
actually like last night I was not doing
well I was like between
um
I was between like feeling like I was
about to faint and like feeling like I
was about to puke and then I was like
just like dying on multiple levels
um
have I even taking walks lately what's
been cold I don't think I've been I'm in
uh
[Music]
um
but yeah um I took some more Advil
before the stream today so if I started
a bit out of it
which I was hoping it wasn't too bad but
yeah I gotta be a bit more careful I'm
gonna try and take things a bit easier
and be a bit more mindful
um but yeah um tomorrow is
um ASMR I hope you guys can look right
to that
um
thank you so much for watching the
collab today it was so much fun even
though things were a bit scuffed even
though the game did not break it was
still fun to hang out with them
right thank you so much thank you thank
you thank you thank you
thank you so much thank you for the fun
stream it was very comfy please go in
and take care of yourself
[Music]
um
so yeah
thank you thank you
um look forward to the 3.0 and I'm gonna
go eat
and take it a bit easy hope that my mind
that my headache does not progress
thanks for the French cream today's been
a rough day for me oh no I'm so sorry I
know how you feel I was really really
it's really a devastating this morning
but what do you think you heard it so
far thank you thank you
I'm trying to make a next stream
thank you thank you thank you for
watching I'm having fun today
memberships
[Music]
that I got them earlier in the collab
try to read them on the next stream
thank you so much guys thank you for
watching I hope you have an amazing
great day and I can't wait to get some
food in my time
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]