[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
this movie is so cute I was holding up
my phone
to read a QR code and she's just like
oh [\h__\h] she's just um
rubbing her chin and her face against
the phone
so I can't see the QR code
baby
guys
hello
ah
done
[Music]
um
distance
thank you
[Music]
one more
wow
[Music]
thank you
no
seems like I have to redo my
costume settings
oh well
[Music]
bunny
hello
huh
[Music]
just turned on the the fan ran away
because
I'm feeling heated
Karen
Karen Dice and turn
not you baby
you like the Dyson
why is this stupid ass person
[Music]
it's stupid
meow
meow do you hear Do you hear her
[Laughter]
oh you you oh
wow that's sad
oh no it's turning I have to get so
close with my remote and
I think there cannot be any like block I
am yes movie I know blocking it maybe
block blocking you blocking blocky
okay now we have to stop it though stop
stop stop
I have to stop it when it's in the right
direction
for [\h__\h] sake
okay let me just turn it with my hands
probably
that's probably okay okay
I'll make it stronger
I think that got to do that yes that got
stronger okay hi baby
hi oh okay guys
how you doing
no I have I have a Dyson fan that's like
hollow inside
it's just like a oval tall
thing and it's been helping me these
past it's not even that hot yet outside
but in my apartment it gets so hot
so I have to use my fan already
um
and um
it I have I've been having it on the
whole night but really low only only on
setting number two out of 10 but for the
whole night because it's so yeah yeah
because European buildings or like
Austrian German and so on apartment
buildings
why is she still in the room
they are built to keep the heat in the
winter which is nice but the problem is
they're also then keeping the heat in
the [\h__\h] summer
think about that when you build it don't
won't you think about both sides it's
nice that you can maybe have a warmer
apartment in winter but
think think
[Laughter]
um yeah no my windows it doesn't I can't
it doesn't help
um
ah anyway I am back
um I'm not
and I noticed when I went outside today
to buy pet food
that I'm not 100 healthy because
my ear my chest and my throat was
starting to hurt and
maybe tightening up
and I I mean that could also be
allergies I don't know but I've never
had this before all at the same time my
right ear the middle of my chest and my
throat
it was all hurting and uh especially on
my way back I was like really
feeling maybe
I don't know blood sugar or something
um
I was just feeling really really like
holy [\h__\h] okay I can't walk I can't
stand anymore
[Music]
um
that could be maybe iron deficiency or
something like that though
who knows might not be in connection
with my other things but I'm just you
know still uh recovering from
I'm dying
aren't we all always dying
still recovering from things
uh the past two days
um but peanut butter no no I don't
really like peanut butter
oh no I didn't I didn't prepare my
strawberries I have strawberries in the
fridge and I wanted to wash them and cut
them
[\h__\h] because I was like recording things
so I'm gone
I forgot most of them is
hey I was prepared enough I could bring
if I could bring the microphone with me
I could at least wash them really
quickly and then I don't have to cut
them up I'll just eat them the way they
are with the green stem no not with the
green stem but okay okay okay because
like otherwise I bought them yesterday
and they go bad so fast
okay okay I got the strawberries let me
bring my cookies too
okay okay okay okay okay
now we're talking
now we're cooking oh yeah cooking
because I brought cookies now we're
cooking cookies
wait cookies comes from the word cooking
even though you bake them why they're
not called bakies
my cookies
who came up with the name cookies
oh my God think about it
what
cookie dude
what I'm not doing a Seinfeld impression
it should be babies who cooks cookies
you bake them yeah
comes from Dutch word oh
oh okay well that makes more sense okay
because like I feel like out of so many
things that you could like name after
the word cooking
you choose cookies that seems quite the
honor to choose that you know
Chicago
[Laughter]
ah okay okay
what you thought you thought cookies
came from cook
I just now
made that realization thinking that oh
oh wait cookies the word cooking is in
that
don't don't
tell me as if that realization is so
weird like I mean come on it really
sounds like they took that word
don't make me feel stupid
it could be
[Laughter]
oh okay anyway it's not from English
[Music]
you know what I got I I thought I got a
twig wait a second did I get it to work
did I get it to work I just saw it
working I think I just saw it working
huh
oh no it's not working I thought the
color changing thing was working
a moment ago wait on when I saw it on a
different model what what
[Music]
see it's working on this one
apparently we have 3D small
oh my god did you guys sing We got 3D
Smalls now but like see on this one
whoa
this on the color are changing is
working is it just that one outfit that
doesn't work what about this one
yeah pretty small I don't know
oh it works on this one too
oh hello
oh I don't know how to connect the hands
thing by the way Amit all told me that I
can relatively easily use my hands now
without using any other weird tools
um but I don't know where that was
oh wow but see that it's working is it
does it only work on 3D models what
about what about this one
ah
why does it only work on 3D models
what about what about my OG
that's that makes no sense why why
they didn't specify they didn't say it
only works on 3D model it should it
should
blue blue note for the future
um when you draw arms they're usually
too short the hands are like you know
big and then the arms are too short so
just so you know but I tried to like cut
it off um
just so you know for the future
okay well I guess I figured out what's
what exactly they didn't reply to me
last time when I was like hey this is
not working for me
let me let me ride again
[Music]
how do I like uh here okay
no nobody
replied to me but just wanted to say
wait a second Maybe
did they did they
um
ah
wait no they might have specified
I figured out uh now it's only for a 3D
model
can we get the feature to 14g models
oh whoa
[\h__\h]
imagine if I like
stand here and it hits me can still hit
me down here
anyway okay okay
ah game sound oh yeah ah no problem no
problem man it's been a while
it's been a while
okay let me put chat
um
do do
maybe here for now so I was saying I was
saying
um
uh I am not
100 healthy yet so I don't know how well
uh I'll be failing throughout the stream
I have a painkiller next to me in case I
need it
um
[Music]
um I'm drinking sports drink Gatorade
gamer Aid
um
but yeah
um right now I'm feeling okay feeling
better than before the Stream
yeah okay
um yeah okay I didn't do my recap but
the thing is you would think that
there's a lot to recap I don't know
uh the problem is
like I was playing once on the plane I
think
and I was playing the day before
yesterday I think
for a while so it's not even that much I
didn't even find that much time to play
and
um
when I was playing
somehow
most of the time I was just running
around not really doing much
laughs
I'm Not Invisible I guess so yeah I
wasn't I wasn't doing much
um I couldn't do much where did I leave
off
I think
here maybe here yeah that seems new
um
because I was whoa was that I was I was
doing side quests and some of them I
just didn't
um I I just couldn't find all the
solutions to and I was I when I was on
the plane I couldn't even look up
Solutions on the internet
so that was a problem
um uh here I thought this would be maybe
like a quest or so because you go in and
and he's like oh hey I'm doing a lesson
if you want you can stay and listen and
I I waited and I was listening but
nothing was happening so I guess I guess
it's like they encourage you to come in
but then then nothing really happened it
is a quest
he doesn't give me a quest do you get it
from elsewhere
I did talk to him
I did maybe it doesn't work for me yet
I did before the lesson and during the
lesson talked to him
[Music]
um
when the children are here eh I did
weird
oh okay I'll try another time then
um
good to know
uh
this this was something I found in the
middle of nowhere
and I don't know I didn't know what it
means I think it was in the Gerudo
um lands
in a cave
no maybe not gorillo I'm not sure and I
I honestly I didn't know what that meant
because there was nothing like close by
that seemed to make sense with this yeah
but good I took a screenshot and I found
this I went into Zelda's house I didn't
even realize that it was Zelda's house
because I was uh really really really
desperately looking for the last person
to give um what was it the mushroom too
and um
that was my problem I couldn't find the
last person and I looked everywhere I
talked to every [\h__\h] villager I swear
is the last one like like hidden
somewhere because I was looking around
so much I found this in Zelda as well I
think I did read the diary too
yeah
um what ah are you getting the side
quests to look for the clothes I guess
I bet it's the guy who walks near the
lab
oh really around the lab is the only
place I didn't look I think
that could be it
okay for [\h__\h] sake
uh
uh then I met some more hands somewhere
I don't know why I took a picture ah
maybe because
maybe I don't know why
I don't know why I took a picture
hmm
um this was I think no this is not by
accident but I thought it was funny
there was like a lot a lot of uh these
grass balls and I set them on fire and
behind was a treasure chest
I was just looking through
uh caves and there was also a quest here
that I couldn't finish because you have
to find free Travelers
uh they're either in caves or taking
Shades somewhere or this and that and I
found two but I didn't find the last one
and again I went for this huge area a
million times
and I I couldn't find them questions
that's so annoying I I couldn't find
them
[Music]
um
this is another cool construction but
yours truly takanasikiwawa
this is
um
uh maybe and I had a lot of accidental
screenshots but
I was going for a shrine
oh and I found another ancient blade
let's go
ah
ah I I I I think
um at this time I was doing some side
quests in
in the grown land and there were hot
springs and then I found the dude and he
was part of side quest and he teaches
you how to make boiled eggs
it's funny
nibbling on the perfect spring boiled
egg while soaking in the perfect hot
spring yeah
is that a thing in Japan I know Onsen
eggs are a thing and I know people going
into Onsen surfing but do you go into
the Onsen is
okay you don't do it together
[Music]
yeah
you don't do it together with the egg
anyway
[Music]
the show
a frog
what why does this one look so weird
um
give the eggs some privacy
ah this was a side quest no or maybe um
oh tummy horde
um was it a side quest or Adventure I'm
not sure but uh yeah all these people
were running around naked because they
thought Zelda told them to do that but
it was a misunderstanding
and there was some kind of like Quest
where you know the dudes they thought
they have to fight all these enemies
naked so blink had to do it too it was
quite tough actually
for me I had to do two or three tries
yeah
yeah here here here you have to do it
took me some tries I got a star that's
next to the next to the evil Horseman
mm-hmm
but I picked it up quietly silently
um
oh this one
uh this there's a lot of accidental
screenshots here but I struggled I think
I struggled a lot with this shrine
no actually not really I cheesed because
I didn't understand it and I couldn't
look it up I chased this shrine
um a lot I don't think I did it in any
intended ways it's hard to explain now
um
I think and I don't know if you guys saw
the shrine before but you're supposed to
bring one plate with you I think
throughout the whole Shrine and attach
it in different ways to first I think
like a static bridge but then later like
moving stuff
um
and and then I didn't bring it
um because the second there's like three
stages and the second stage I kind of
cheesed but for the third stage which is
this one I realized oh wait I really
need
the platform now but I don't want to go
back and undo my choosing because it was
already so difficult
um this Shrine is in the middle of
nowhere I normally should probably
shouldn't have done it uh yet it wasn't
really in the path of anything that made
sense yet anyway I was really teasing it
that's just what I wanted to say
especially this last present
did a lot of time uh removal and it's
not supposed I don't think no I don't
think it's supposed it didn't it didn't
feel right it was not supposed to be
like that
I'm telling you and here somehow I ended
up on top of this mountain
um I don't know why I was just exploring
I think and there's this like heat and
cold test
uh which
also was interesting
behold the sun is sinking behind the
Western Horizon
and uh
I think there's like a lot of like
platforms on the ground
that can help you to build something I
think because otherwise I don't know why
the stuff would be there there's like
those those like sticky things that you
can stick into any anything and a lot of
platforms and you could probably build
yourself like a shade thingy
for the heat test
and you could probably also build
yourself a platform to put a fire on top
because the
place where link has to stand on you
cannot put a fire there
um and you have to wait for eight
minutes in the cold without your clothes
well without your clothes
and and and uh it was really boring
eight minutes
and I I tried to do something Midway
through with the platforms but I
couldn't really get it to work and then
uh I ended up just taking like
heat and cold medicines in the end yeah
you get quite a lot of money from this
first time I think it was 100 and then
hmm yeah eight minutes
and I just I just waited I just went
somewhere to do something
that was an accidental screenshot then I
did another horse quest
uh then this was already too late but I
thought when I was looking for the next
horse quest AKA when he asks you to
bring you something that's not a horse
uh I was looking for a bear or something
like that but I found a he knocks hmm oh
took a video
why ah that was accidental too
but hey it's proof that I did it
you had a lot of yummy food
yeah and I was so pissed off because
there was
a boar another board there was a uh
finally I found after a long time
looking I found a
uh
no I found a
Kuma a bear and I I I really quietly
went up to him in my chica uh armor and
with extra self medicine and I went up
to him and I I tamed him and then I
started going towards
the quest Giver
yeah
and it already took me a while because
it's really hard to control and then
halfway through
some [\h__\h] bats keep on attacking me
and throwing me off and they throw me
off once and I made it back up on the
bear thankfully and then they throw me
up again and then the bear was like [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h] and he runs away and I'm like
come on [\h__\h] bad so annoying and it
took me so long to find another animal
it already took me so
we still find the bear in the first
place
then I couldn't find the bear anymore
afterwards so I ended up going with this
one
that you can also ride but yeah
I have an interesting similar struggle
with the horse
I I I found a horse
a little bit too late and then I made my
way and then the first one it died
pretty close to the quest Giver
recipient because
um it was already daytime and it died
then I had to do it again so I had to do
all this [\h__\h] twice
um
ah this was
this was on purpose
[Music]
pretty yeah
isn't that so pretty
yeah I did that class for Shrine quest
for another
um
fairy great Ferry
yeah I think I'm I'm missing one more
one more fairy and then I did this Quest
where there's a lady singing down there
in the well
and it really scares the people
apparently
uh because they misunderstand what she's
singing like something like oh throw
down your arms
but she means uh something else and then
they throw down the weapons
leave your arms or I'll kill you haha
what kind of nonsensical song is that I
thought I thought she's gonna she was
gonna turn into a yika or something and
attack me but no it was really a
misunderstanding
she meant something else
um oh
around the same stable there's this like
mini game
where you have to run around the lake
which is not really a lake it's a pond I
guess
um
and okay
you have to uh uh uh you have to like um
go for it with the with the Box on your
on your uh horses
thingy but I tried it like three times
and I always failed right away in the
beginning
it was ridiculous I I I no I never went
past the first
it says free here but no it's not true
and everyone passed the second
even though it says free I never really
did I don't think I did
it's so difficult it's
old
oh then I did one of these fights the
one with the pirate ship
um somehow I missed all the other ones
there's more of these fights where you
fight together with villagers and all
that
um and I never found the other ones but
I found this one so I did that one yeah
it was actually pretty difficult because
like almost all of them died and I
wonder if uh you would fail the quest if
all of them die I had like two
of them left over at the end
I didn't protect them so well I didn't I
didn't think they could die so I wasn't
paying attention much yeah
then I saw like them fainted on the
ground and was like oh [\h__\h] wait I
should probably hurry up
then I finished the fairy Quest it's not
over just by bringing the flute guy over
you have to do something with the car
and right over there and there she is
accidental yeah
so I didn't do that much
I mean
I didn't do that much even though I've
been talking for oh it's 48 minutes
that's not so bad because half of that
was something else
oh
oh oh
on the way
on the way of doing things I found my
fourth Sage will
thank you for the Rica thank you for
listening
I found my first as well
let's go I'm thinking toolin
I didn't want to do it off screen
but I'm thinking uh toolin
because she don't I have
yet
to use his abilities
after the
um
shrine
maybe once for riding up a waterfall but
like what are you gonna upgrade and then
you know about okay maybe if it upgrades
if it uh I don't even know what it does
like does it lessen
oh it only upgrades his bow ability
uh wait it only upgrades the the
fighting part
not actually like the cooldown or the
strength of their like special attack
oh
damage up
okay
oh that's kind of lame
it would be nice if they would lessen
the cooldown or something
okay well then it doesn't matter so much
but I'll go with Tulin because tooling
seems to do the most
[Music]
with his bow
right
uh
at least for now we'll look at another
station and then maybe she will read you
maybe she will help us
um
okay
and
money
[Music]
now okay heart container I would say
personally I want a heart container
one day I threw an enemy into the water
to kill him two and struggled with his
arrows to kill him before he touched the
water
yeah Tulane's pretty damn good
[Music]
oh my God
I don't even know if it's in-game or out
game because in game it's also
thundering
okay
see him
ah it's indeed what
[Laughter]
in-game out game
thank you
that was in game that was in game
I'm so immersed okay
um
yeah
so hmm
this is the one I couldn't finish do you
guys know where the third one is you
don't even know which are the two ones
that I did find but um
I found one in a cave
and one not in the cave I think I don't
know
[Music]
you have The Wanted Quest from that guy
oh yeah I talked to him I don't want to
bother with that now though
um
ring I think the the donut is pondering
about what he should do
there's one who falls down the river
what
he falls what do you mean he actively
falls down the river
we're talking about the Gerudo Canyon
he falls down the rip what do you what
do you mean
this one
yep I was also thinking put on the
replay
I dropped on a cave and found them
um
well I also found one in a cave
with fires
and during the daytime I was looking uh
at like shady areas
drinking
um
oh I upgraded some more of my armor by
the way
eh could it be like behind this one
[Music]
I didn't check behind the Shred
oh yeah
I'll go away
yes I found the one that was attacked by
lizard Falls yeah yeah
can I make a boat
see if there's something
oh no
don't move
I'll make a little boat
uh lizard whatever
not worth
my attention
correcting those names just like
illusion
is this an illusion or
illuminate illumination
oh
[Music]
domination not illusions
I don't hear much about Illumination in
here you know in Austria so
let's go
what happened
by walking on the water
is it because I planted it too high
no
don't push forward
ah okay okay
oh because that makes it go down into
the water what the [\h__\h]
I just wanted to go front
okay is there something here
maybe a cool dog no
the sword a fish yeah
and even the fish escapes
my Lionel Boomerang bro
it it held up for so long though
I gotta
say
it worked pretty hard for me
goodbye Lionel Boomerang guess I gotta
find another Lionel soon
[Music]
what is the chest
let's just bring it with us for now
although it really puts on some weight
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Shrine of light nearby
oh toolin is taking care of the bats
all three missing people I was
I was 10 times
at night and at day time
you're freaking kidding me right
how can I miss the last one
so many times
foreign
is
who caught Plateau Plateau cave
senior oh hello
[\h__\h]
oh that one's uh strong holy [\h__\h] that
one's really strong isn't he
even death barely oh no no no no no no
no
barely did any damage to him
I made some strong looking cool weapons
like this he knocks hammer and the black
book let's kill him this one
yeah yeah that feels good
and felt efficient
very good
let it break no no I don't want it to
break no
when will I meet this
um character
that can repair who
[Music]
repair your things
have a broke
and that's that's for an ax
sheltered but
all of these all right one that one that
one maybe
looks sufficient
but not on these weapons okay
far more Talos later
oh yeah yeah I killed one I killed the
he knocks in a Talos off screen okay
what do we have in this cave
interesting
interesting interesting
that's sand right
oh endless
sand
waterfall
you're lucky with these most of the time
really
two things
see I see like Dom tando always getting
better [\h__\h]
always [\h__\h] rigged
unbelievable what is
this that one's for isn't that sus are
you supposed to like fill the holes no
that's impossible
[Music]
no I should have to stream along
streamer
um
where's the Frog
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah he streams sometimes I always
miss it though
everyone already outside
there's a there's dudes there
what
did I talk to you before wait are you
yeah
yo
[Music]
is this the no way this is
he wanted a spicy pepper
the other ones didn't want the spicy
pepper
yeah
[Music]
Dragon music yeah oh my God this cave
huh
that is so far from the main road like
this road because you get the quest here
and then this path it's really long okay
there was one like in one of these caves
and another one I don't know where maybe
like here I don't know
and then I thought okay you know
this whole area I checked 10 times
and then he turns out to be up here
if you find if you follow the river and
then go into the cave then okay
then it is
manageable however I didn't find the the
Frog
of this cave
how come
[Music]
oh
what are you doing what are you doing
I'm still wondering if you can hit the
the rabbit
after it runs away
sometimes I try and I never make it
can you
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
you can't you can hit him but nothing
happens okay
okay okay then I give up hello
I want all
of the
Stone materials
I don't want to lose any of them
they're very valuable I I needed six
feet six zero Amber
to upgrade
um
my this one my Hylian armor to level
three
Amber
and I had 70 so I was lucky but
um
that is so much
yeah don't meet shinies I don't get
damaged well look at that cheese
no way that works
oh it went up pretty high though
would look pretty high
uh okay thanks to that I can now finish
the main quest should I go back here
do I have to
sometimes the quests finish themselves
on their own and sometimes you have to
run all the way back to it
I watched the video where someone was
recreating the sounds
of like things like like
um shooting and a fire arrow
and the sounds oh man he perfectly
recreated them but it it was like five
million sounds
combined together
yeah I don't think I got a reward yet so
I have to go to it why is there a ladder
here
oh
unless there's enemies behind
and Rose
That's How Sound Engineering works you
know the thing I recorded
I was listening to the instrumental
closely and I realized wait there's a
[\h__\h] hick sound in this instrumental
why is there a hick sound
uh oh yeah I still don't have anything
[Music]
for
like I have fire resistance but I don't
have heat resistance clothes yet
so annoying one second
that's why I want to quickly go to
Garuda although I wouldn't even be able
to afford much
I want to quickly go to Gerudo town or
whatever
to buy it today that's my first goal
because I don't want to keep on eating
this stuff
your heat resistance 11 minutes probably
too long anyway because we're gonna
go to places but
any crops
no
what is that
look at that
[\h__\h] is that what the [\h__\h] is that
huh there's a chest in there how do I
get in there
no no
my frogging armor is not good enough yet
anyway
there's there's all these like freaking
ladders
that you would go up and then you see
and you get totally triggered by the
window you can't enter
yo
that is wait never mind
you can enter here never mind or can you
can you Canyon
can't Gerudo Canyon Canyon Canyon from
smilage
one of my favorite idols
so many can you can use
I'm playing uh association game you
can't eat what
what hide an eye
what about here
the same
Place yeah
okay
whatever
I don't care right now probably nothing
special in there anyway
okay
hi there's safe yeah thanks to me I'm
such a hero
you needed a hero
[Music]
nice bumps that's actually ten bombs is
really nice thanks for that
okay now
uh we must go to the city where's the
city
oh
is this the city
well I don't remember I don't know where
it is
it doesn't even say on the map
there's a lot of stuff going on here and
and the path leads there so ah this this
should be it right I think I remember it
was like um this shape
was a very square shape
so oh
would be better if I teleport to the
Skyview Tower I think okay okay okay
okay
yay
ah guys Zelda movie
did you hear and I know yeah we already
talked about it on Twitter and I know a
lot of you guys and generally Zelda fans
are already doubting everything and it's
gonna be good but come on give it give
it the chance okay
um
of course it's probably gonna still take
a long time
but I think you know first of all it
doesn't even have to be illusion let's
just say illusion
it might not even necessarily be
illusion
that's like what everyone's assuming but
right it could also be a different
um film whatever Studio whatever
within Universal right
they didn't say clearly that it was
going to be illusion
it's just uh
and they just assume it
is
yeah they're in the talks okay it's not
confirmed but the funny thing is like
come on okay
I'm trying to find it
below
what do you mean below
I want to saying oh yeah when I was like
watching the spider-verse movie with
Amel
I was like we were talking I think I
asked her if she watched the Mario movie
and then we were talking about like oh I
mentioned since I also I I started the
topic of oh hey we're both playing teotk
and we're really into it aren't we and
then I was like wouldn't it be so
awesome like or no no I was saying I'm
saying they should totally make like a
Zelda moving
the series even
just like with Mario
not like the same you know style art
style or so no please no
but
I mean they should put at least the same
amount of money into it and make
something great with it I was just
talking about it like a couple days
before Obama and and I think you know
she was I think kind of like doubting
that it would happen and I was like no
they have to like because like they got
this like genius thing this whole story
oh
they have so much potential right there
they have a whole like story
they have so many games that they could
use as a reference
I think people would absolutely like
lose their [\h__\h] [\h__\h] over it
they would totally
watch it 100 everybody went watching
and if they do it right it could be like
Nintendo's Lord of the Rings you know
what I mean I mean it already is
Nintendo's Lord of the Rings in terms of
like it's it's like a I don't know how
to explain cool fantasy
stuff series but it's a game so now they
should make it into a movie
[Music]
um
and I think
um I think they did do Mario the Mario
movie Justice they didn't completely
messed it up right okay there's mixed
opinions but I think they didn't
completely mess it up
and I don't think
um they will mess up a Zelda movie too
much I mean there's always always you
know
people have different tastes and
different expectations and all that so
you can't make every 100 happy
but yeah the Mario movie what the [\h__\h]
it was overall very good Brian oh you
stay up here
I want the materials
I'm A Material Girl
the only real problem is
how to solve the problem of the
protagonist not talking
that's something I also
don't really like no how I would go
about that
I
be okay with him talking a little bit
like really really really little
like being very very quiet
overall but giving him a little bit of
like you know just in the most important
times but then even then wouldn't it be
kind of awkward well excuse me princess
hmm what the [\h__\h] is that
hmm
we are in the desert let's make it
quickly to
oh wait there's like a
sand Cloud around it can I enter
maybe we should go to the Oasis first
foreign
would be I think
okay with giving him a voice as long as
they keep his personality and for people
who say he has no personality I in my
opinion opinion kind of does
you know Ben's protagonists
who's very neutral and and just humble
and
um kind of not really shy but just like
quiet introvert but you know he has
[Music]
um you know he's a hero
I think it's a personality
and you could show that even when making
him talk a little bit just give him like
a calm
um attitude
you know
[Music]
I think that should keep Laura yeah I
mean if they can somehow manage to do
that while not making it awkward
then hell yeah
of course
if they can
oh
see
oh I just time reverse
um what's that thing
[Music]
yeah because I just know what I feel
like it it seems like a difficult
challenge but I mean that they can
probably figure something out if they
want to
because I I think they see
the difficult like the possibility of
lots of criticism
if they make him like talk a lot and if
they completely change his personality
into like a really energetic let's go
type of character like nobody wants it I
think they would be aware of that
that's like
not link how we need we need um
we need those
why are they so far
so
the
that won't work
Nani
do I have to try to run against it
oh my God
hey how are you supposed to do this with
less stamina than me
I was clapping
you
[Music]
what I would say
is one enough
wait a second
where are we even going with that over
there first
[Music]
okay well it works it works it has like
a rough start but then it gets really
fast
you could go directly to the end of the
shrine oh [\h__\h] hell
come on right side
yeah it takes such a long time
to get started maybe I should go left
first that looks like
come on come on
looks like that's where the extra chest
could be
yep
it's not a big challenge to get that
chest it's just like have fun
have fun getting there
is it gonna stay there
maybe like this see I'm parking it
anyway
I'm just really excited I mean it might
still take two three four years
but I'm excited
for the possibility and the fact that I
was just talking about it a few days
before this news was released I mean
it's just a it's just a rumor at this
point right
foreign
I'll take the other one
Clairvoyant that's me
oh yeah maybe that was that's bad what
maybe by the time it comes out I will
have played all the Zelda games Sam
maybe not all
looks at Zelda too
I I did already watch
um playthroughs of almost all of them
like I watched the full playthrough of
the the train ones like pretty much all
of them even the DS games
um
thanks to Don tedo basically every Zelda
game that Don tando played before I've
watched yeah Spirit Tracks a full
playthrough of
and I think they're all really Charming
like even I was joking about spirit
tracks on on uh on Twitter but I think
they're all really Charming
they all have their time
yeah not the CDI ones
tonight
the train one was cute yeah I think so
too
wasn't the train one wait wasn't the
train one in Toon Link graphics and the
train kind of look wait am I imagining
things kind of looked like the the boat
from Wind Waker
am I correct with the boat too
yeah yeah
I guess that's why I liked it even more
I think
um they're in the same timeline oh that
makes a lot of sense
yeah oh it's night time now so I don't
need heat protection thank god oh
there's a chest
Twilight Princess Ocarina time with
Minish Camp
um
I think
after totk obviously there will be a
little break but
I think
I feel like I might want to play
um
maybe
Ocarina of Time
can I open these
oh
oh of course not
sand shroud
that was close if the others heard me
they definitely chew me out for using
slang on duty my mentor has interested
me with decorating a weapon in a stylish
way
she told me make a Sparkle and it must
radiate a burning passion but I don't
know what she's talking about
she's got an allergy to monsters too so
that means monster parts are off limits
oh
how about wait Sparkle Sparkle and
burning passion how about adding a
um a ruby to it
if I just had a weapon I could use a
reference for where to start that would
help a lot
Ruby right
oh my God I'm such a genius but I don't
have one right now I think I have an
opal scepter
um
I could put a ruby on my Royal Broad
Sword
or the giant boomerang
maybe not John boomerang
I found a [\h__\h] giant Boomerang man I
don't know where I even found that
I quickly figured it out I'm I'm a
genius
huh what what happened
okay look at this
it better be right
oh
wow
yes study it oh yeah
well you say if you attach a ruby like
this but I attached it by using my
fusion power
you can't do that so you'll have to I
don't know ask some what did what do you
call them again
the the people who make weapons to do it
for you
Blasphemous yeah
what I'm wasting a ruby and I get this
oh [\h__\h]
and I mean okay fire weapon is cool and
all but I didn't really want to make one
right now
okay
scam
what what don't you do for a side oh my
God
there's a bow headband can you hunt
450 I can actually afford that and that
should hopefully be enough
to get through the desert during the day
one piece is enough right
you can have it separated there
Tarrytown is that where you do it I have
yet to find that
but I keep on thinking about I know it
exists
have you heard of the store fashion
fashion Gerudo towns
and is that where I get the rest
what
wait yeah you're cute he's got earrings
damn
kind of cute not gonna lie wow wow
welcome there's watermelons
oh my God
I already found watermelons yet
exciting
watermelon oh all kinds of jellies well
I have plenty ah
so no need
what do you have what do you do
[Music]
um
excuse me well excuse me it's me printed
um no
okay looking for conversation go to the
regular store actually I like this it's
kind of cute
I like how the the bunk beds are built
into the walls
I like it
it's like a capsule Hotel
[Music]
so nice survey team's free Big Ideas
too bad I don't care whoa
well this recipe doesn't even need
watermelon though does it
is
no I never played genjin before never
all my friends play it
and even after so much time
most of them are also still so addicted
like they're literally like oh my god oh
crap it's actually insane how
addicted my friends got to the game
they played it every day and they
they're always like oh I gotta do my
dailies I gotta do my dailies
okay maybe I was kind of like that
when I was playing archonauts
yeah but
somehow
obnoxious
is he not gonna show up
you know about
you know about what the [\h__\h]
no
it's uh
really
no way did I froze
first and too far then I'm too close
sure
um
wait no I deactivated
[Music]
okay never mind but he didn't show up
even when I had him activated that's the
thing
Angel why
I don't need I have I'm not a single
time in my life and
totk have I used bright caps
there's too many items
for like
brightening up things brightening up
yourself
but even if you use them it's so
inconvenient why should you use
the items that brighten you up
when it's so much better to just
brighten your surroundings up it's so
much more effective
right
for forever else what
that bloom seeds is really all you need
I agree
is this really not a cave
it doesn't really give me well Vibes but
sometimes
sometimes the wells ah [\h__\h] sometimes
the whales do turn into caves right
uh you just use them for health
ah and you just accept the fact that
you're glowing as an extra
okay okay I guess you could do that yeah
it's not really bothering at least
no not costume
frag is dead is there so it is a cave
I know I can break them but I don't want
to waste my things
hello Croco
bloop to you too sir
[Music]
wow it's so bright
[\h__\h] now
I wish it was a different button
to activate them because you just run
into them and accidentally press it when
you want to pick up items
I guess this is the same
whatever I think it's the same
uh where did I not go
this way right
yeah okay okay
that's the thing I hate the most yeah
yeah right it's pretty annoying but you
can't change it right
you can't change controls on the switch
I think
maybe if you like a programmer but
normally you can't right
it's a d-pad
play you don't use the d-pad for
anything else right the d-pad would have
been good
you could put
all of them
and one
for sure
space in the d-pad
[Music]
can I go through this
no
that was weird
does that success
because the stones there so it makes me
feel like
that's also sauce
am I supposed to stop the sand
wait
what's up
the sand doesn't move at all
wait I I have some ideas like either
you're supposed to start the sand
no
okay maybe not
because like I can't attach it either
but wait
well I mean it at least reacts to me
putting it there I think what did it
maybe then
that means there's a sand pit above
wait you mean like one of those things
when you get stuck
oh I can't even go up here
nobody not in there
what is this
so confusing
ah sand Whirlpool uh-huh
oh yeah okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] uh
where am I
well thank God I made I I did the shrine
we still had reception when we were
under the cave like in the cave
oh [\h__\h] okay that's scary quina
wasn't there also a sandstorm here
and breath of the Wild
do they still have the same issue
do I just need to change my provider and
get better reception in this area
what is the matter here
[Music]
a different kind of sandstorm
um
yeah around the Divine Beast
oh what is that
what the [\h__\h] is that
doesn't that kind of look like the ones
that grow Underground
oh
I think this is Stone but no matter what
I do I can't put a dent in it
um
oh there's a spoiler
uh-huh
is it growing from underground
this is spreading
[Music]
as soon as I'd run into this oh dual
Beatles eyes just every time he looks at
my beetles
okay the thing is if you don't give it
to him he will threaten you
with um robbing you at night and I don't
know if that really happens but it
always always makes me cave
okay okay
hmm
yeah then you never see that he
threatens you like quietly silently
like he'd even be able to well I don't
know don't underestimate Beetle like you
underestimate the chickens in this game
too
okay guys let's go
um if we can
cut sand in my eye
sand it goes everywhere what what is
that ball
get a load of this orb seems really old
and really expensive don't you think
yeah I first thought it was one of the
capsules
I hear there's someone in Gerudo Town
who's investigating all these ancient
whatchamacallits you know he says that
so once I get into town I'm planning on
finding somebody who knows their stuff
about this stuff um okay
okay hey
um
who are we we're the first men who will
officially do business with the Gerudo
the Vol Caravan Squad
if you two want to go to Garuda town you
would do well to make friends with us
yeah sure what the [\h__\h] is this though
can I fly up with us
unbearable Heat
wow
my headpiece is not enough
at least it forces me to cook some
materials
yeah that's okay because like the thing
is I felt like it was kind of stupid of
the game to give you the
um
cold protection armor already on the
first Sky Island because then you didn't
need any of the cold protection items
materials
and elixirs
for going to the bird region you didn't
need anything
right
um heat resistance
I didn't need it you needed two pieces
I feel like it was enough for me
yeah it's
probably to help you have an easier time
going there
um
wait months apart
which one
I need more space
I cook too much apparently
I don't know
[Music]
what
oh wait the plants
only work with actual food
oh
[Music]
only insects work with
uh
uh monster Parts okay
good
I have learned my lesson
wait it's gonna tell me the same thing
again
let's eat the dubious food
okay one more
can I mix two different insects
um
what
I have big big issues collecting flying
insects like I'm really bad at it
uh what else do I have
um
I have this one
okay
okay hopefully you think that's enough
the nine minutes into four minutes
but I don't even know like where to go
how to go
let me let me let's eat one more thing
I'll make one more so
just in case
it ain't that hard okay
okay we'll do it
okay
let's use the long one
wait I'm not scared
also I have the green marker so it
oh green marker's gone but I know I know
the direction
it's this way
even the green marker disappears oh no
I wonder if there's any other
like markers on like that you can see
here like you know
what what is that don't tell me those
are undeads
the redheads
oh [\h__\h] no
what
the [\h__\h] no no no
uh
what is that gypto
a creepy bond with multiple sharp tips
attention what's a gift though
[Music]
oh
are you gonna scream at me
ah scary
oh no no no no not that one I thought
that was a ice weapon
[Music]
oh oh you can't actually throw uh this
one oh
it's scary
they're more scary and Wind Waker
I don't remember them
please scare me
why gypto guts yummy
or we could bake a car maybe
or not there's no tires okay
am I still going the right direction is
that a
[Music]
uh
Bridge Toko
oh I climb
I will climb
oh you could climb that was close
but I am more or less going the right
way I think
am I though am I
I think roughly
right
what's this oh oil Jack what oh
watermelon
let's go free watermelon
who died here
I don't know
cats
they're making some sounds wait now now
I really don't know what's the right
direction anymore but are these like
these things possibly any kind of
indication on what direction I should be
going
[\h__\h]
I don't want to touch it give it to me
wait [\h__\h]
uh
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is that
use the wind to fly up
huh
you mean that one what
ah
ah what is that
[Music]
money
is that a gift of butterfly is that what
they're
yeah they're supposed to be flying
normally
oh my God
you're scary I don't think they were
here
whoa oh
[Music]
these anyway I don't think they were
here in breath of the wild right
are we still gonna have trouble entering
the city even though we were able to
enter in breath of the Wild
they're new right mm-hmm
can I go in
or are they gonna kick me out
foreign
what happened
did they die because they had no men so
they couldn't make more of themselves
[Music]
what
oh what is this ball everything's so
mysterious here
see this is what happens when you're too
focused on only letting women in
they're so strong
what you gonna do what you gonna do
but this is really strong against them
the like I don't know some
maybe fire is is it the fire
what do you do are you hiding let me
talk to you
hi
another voice oh wait what
wait he looks familiar
[Music]
wake to Elemental damage Ah that's what
I thought you didn't find this person oh
the wild
oh you're just another real living
person I was certain one of the ghosts
haunting this place had come for me I
traveled out here hoping to meet the
wonderful amazing Garuda woman who lived
here but there's no one I do sometimes
Hear Voices coming up from the wells oh
are you hiding in the Wells Wells
obviously the place is now haunted by
the Restless spirits of the beautiful
Garuda Horse Lane by the strange
monsters if I'm not careful the same
monsters might get me too I should have
saved them and make many babies with
them and then this would never happen ah
why did I not arrive earlier it's all my
fault I could have saved them
oh man the beautiful women they're all
lost
such as destiny
oh hi
is that polka
polka
oh
oh did you come here to escape the sand
trout well you've reached the entrance
to the Garuda shelter but I cannot allow
any vote to pass through the store
sorry boo
well oh you've never heard that word
well means man in Gerudo there's a
custom really more of a law that we grew
to follow
younger rudo are generally not allowed
to interact with Bo what's wrong what's
going on
I've wanted in here ah they're asking
what did you say Bo there's nothing to
worry about the vow is very short and
can't even reads the people
he's outside and even on his tiptoes he
won't be able to see him
I can climb though
normally though aren't allowed to even
set foot within the walls of Garuda town
but this is a unique situation so as
long as you keep out of the shelter I'll
overlook your presence in town if you're
looking for some place to get out of the
soundtrack you can rest in one of the
houses on the surface
I can literally see see there's someone
there
oh
what's she doing
oh there's she's like throwing bottle
messages
As She's kissing them and then throwing
them
is she asking for help
why is she throwing them
it's hard to say
you're not gonna say anything about me
climbing in there
I wonder if I could go underneath and
then warp myself up
box use the box to peep oh
oh
except
I hope the water currents scares my
accent I knew what she was doing carries
my lettuce fine wine
may they find the phone I'm destined to
fall for
so many and this isn't a place for Junk
don't you even think about throwing
trash in
these waters are connected to the Wells
on the surface
they're absolutely not a garbage dump oh
I'm not throwing trash away these are
Leathers but it's to develop My Dreams
they're very very important
you say the Wells on the surface
foreign
like this one
[Music]
can I read one of them
it's you at long last you the vote
reading this letter out of all I was
waiting to me
and I am the why you were destined for
you must hurry and rescue me I'm locked
away from the outside world do not worry
though I will send all of my love to you
until you come and find me stay safe and
know that we will meet soon it's our
destiny after all
ever
I believe
I'll save you wait wait for me
it is indeed our destiny
I know it's to be true
I know it
my wife it's do being you
hey what is that pot ah for them to get
up the uh the Water
okay okay
so anyway hi guys
oh sheesh holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] her hip
bones
my God
damn
um will I regret this
is
no please no wait I'm trying to save you
girls I'm I'm the destined one
trust me
look at me and the hero don't you
remember me
come on
you must sleep at once
no no no no no no no no no no
oh
oh yes hold on
yes oh
is that both
yeah I reckon that perform of Kiara like
Tiara and then it's like the one that
bullies everyone
it was like a grown-up version of Rage
when it was gonna say hmm
[Music]
he changed
lady I'm not associated with her
Michelle let me try to eat a strawberry
I finally found
some Austrian strawberries being sold
[Music]
no
and this one already tastes weird
um
I bought the Austrian strawberries gonna
um be in better condition when I buy
them
but I looked through all of them
and they were like almost all of the
packages were already
like looking like they're starting to
mold
uh
this one tastes weird it doesn't look
like it's molding but
um
is it just this one
try one more
because most of the time the the
strawberries here come from like
I think the Philippines
and Spain I think
this one's I think a bit better
you had ants on yours well
and swell I mean that seems
reasonable
ants like food
yeah yeah these are supposed to be local
but they're like even more [\h__\h] than the
non-local ones
um
I wouldn't say we have bad conditions
for growing them but apparently we don't
invest in growing them
it's cheaper to get them from other
countries
um
[Music]
yeah these are very bad pretty bad
it has been sometimes swords men
so right this one has the chief's
permission to enter and he's welcome to
visit any of the shops and businesses
let's go spread the word let everyone
know this is the case
for you to come all this way and during
the strange storm that plagues us you
must have some important news to share
she's not even bullying me she's the one
who's like keeping me from being bullied
the princes of Hyrule is still missing
we had heard of the events at Hyrule
Castle but things are indeed dire still
swords men I mean link I am impressed
that you made it here for the storm that
surrounds Garuda town
[Music]
yeah we we don't need the skies anymore
like in breath of the wild thank God
because otherwise I feel like it would
be weird like making us do that again
even though they should remember us
the sand shroud settled on us some time
ago we sent out patrols to try to
determine what was causing it but a
swarm of monsters creatures called gypto
suddenly appeared yeah they're new
attacked our troops and forced us to
retreat
yeah I still want the outfits
I still want the outfit though yeah
oh
as a result everyone was evacuated to
this shelter for their safety
as someone charged with protecting
Garuda town I'm ashamed that our current
situation this is all to say that
although I wish I could help you search
for the princess now is not a good time
I'm sorry
how convenient that it's never a good
time when I visit these places
lady riju is currently training she's
trying to become strong enough to save
us from This Disaster let's go
or
more she should be a young adult now
right
if you are hoping to speak with Lady
original you should visit the ruins to
the north
okay do you have like another like phone
provider that I can buy a SIM card of
that works cute
uh outside in a sandstorm huh
because my phone's not working out there
what is this
ah
oh head pieces
Sapphire
makes hot climates more tolerable all
our earrings
yeah I think they had these kind of
things in breath of the wild too
well where's the rest of the armor
please provide me
rice I need a wheat actually I ran out
of wheat
where where armor
you must be done though everyone is
talking about saying are highly invo
interested in archeology would it
surprise you to learn that wait these
things must be parts of the temple I get
it now after much work I finally just
say the silver these
do you want to hear what's written on
them you do don't you if you insist
there's nothing written on ah these
things huh I meant the balls
first after Stella over here on the left
it says the seven hearings who protected
who protect the Gerudo their secret will
be expressed on Sixth Sally
as for the style over there on the right
it says the seven heroines who protect
the grudo and eight channels and guides
the power of these seven
ah
me
what
ah I doubt you know this being a
Highland bow but we already have
believed in the heroines for a long long
time they are said to have protected and
guided our people in times past
unfortunately I found little in the way
of documentation about the heroines
themselves
there are many debates and disagreements
surrounding these Enigma in enigmatic
feature figures some argue for a
referring all seven as a collective and
others for worshiping each one as an
individual certain rival rousing
contrarians even claimed they were not
seven but one or eight
if there's one thing skull as love it is
arguing with each other
but this style I definitely support the
theory of eight ah an incredibly
Discovery isn't it I could stop here and
rightly say that I changed to Facebook
archeology but if I found the other four
stealing who knows what else I might
learn about the heroines I wonder too
about this orb that I found while
searching for the Stella is it connected
somehow
if I gave a presentation on all of this
I'd beat Star of an Archeology Society
but I have not been able to find any
salary between these two
since there is nothing like them on the
surface the others must be on the ground
somewhere
how I wish I could see the text
inscribed on this style even just a
picture would serve my purpose okay
we'll be looking for those four of them
cute
cute they can't look at me cute cute
in a training
ooh should we break this can we break it
yo oh here's number one lady
there's another one right here
oh that reminds me I think we I wanted
to report
um the sky island thingies
that I found
on stream because we didn't do that last
time did we
yo I found one it wasn't even
Underground
we're talking about the same on the
ground
the seven hearings protect the Gerudo
with the powers of hard skill fortitude
wisdom flight mobility and compassion
all right
I I'm trying to figure out if that's
like connected to you know the the sages
that we always see in the Visions
because I think those are possibly also
seven plus one
I don't know does she mean the shelter
for underground
yes she's an intellectual because of her
glasses
okay it sounds like a riot
this Legend is well known but it had
never been verified but she thinks
they're they're uh Gerudo right and they
weren't all Gerudo they just probably
assume so
until I came along I'm curious about
what might be written on the Stella you
don't have more no oh
not yet but I'll find them
is this one
no yeah
can it be considered one
no okay
yeah Rizo doesn't seem to be in this
um
area she seems to be North
oh
armor no
not me
that might be I mean look at the arm
yeah what is that me oh it's a bow oh oh
la la teach me teach me about love oh
you're that special though the guard was
talking about my name is ashai I'm in
charge of teaching the vo and you class
to the Gerudo have you set your heart on
someone special yes
you don't hold back anything do you most
by value honestly never that's a good
trait for you to have you're welcome to
sit in on the lesson if you're
interested well aren't normally allowed
in town so it would be a rare treat for
the class if you showed up maybe you
could come by in the evening that class
is for the older Gerudo
the daytime classes for the younger
students I don't think they're quite
ready to meet about
is this the isn't this the older class
it's 9 P.M
um
ah Count Me In
hi so this is like the the lesson with
the kids in
uh hateno right I guess what I didn't do
is talk to the teacher a second time
maybe that was the problem
okay
today we're going to have a very special
lesson we have a role here with us just
try to relax and be your regular normal
selves when you're talking to him all
right oh
wait how come if they if the Gerudo
always go
for like usually like Hylian I think
Hylian men
but let's even assume that they go for
the birds and the stones as well
um
how come I've never seen
a child
that seems to be half Gerudo and have
something else
and not the fish
now I've never
seen children before
dominant genes of who
laughs
there's a quest about that no way
get rid of children are always in Gerudo
yeah but they all look fully garuded are
we in
there's one entire town really
oh
interesting huh
I never thought about this before but
now like it makes no sense to me that
I've never seen children of this I've
never seen a product wait a second I
just found behind her
there's a Stella
never mind one second let's focus on one
thing after another oh
teacher I
I can't
I can't look directly at his face
that's okay we can stop here for now
you'll have to some do something about
that bear eventually but I think once
you muster the courage to Festival even
just one time your fear will wash away
forever she's so say so
so say so I'm sorry I imagine it was a
bit unexpected wasn't it you see she's
never seen a bow in person she's only
seen them in drawings or in Recreations
like the vote dummies
I suspect that if you hit your face it
would be easier it's probably just too
early to make eye contact while chatting
I hope you aren't feeling discouraged
though I would be it would be wonderful
if you visited class again sucks stop
um
ah okay I take a picture from here I
thought I have to like combine it but
wait we're very smart about this
oh
oh my God
genius
[Music]
oh the plushies cute
this one got you you didn't notice it
really I I noticed pretty easily
that's mine now right because I found it
No One's Gonna Get Mad right
50 rupees
oh
wait a second one two three four five
six seven
down here seems to be about dead
doesn't it
how many are we missing wait there's
another one
um
I want to get rid of the
Sans I was gonna say but it seems to
work like this too you don't have to use
like a product
um fan
ha ha
ha
I'll see
inside
because I don't think tooling can be in
in a city right
doesn't work
how many more maybe one more
okay
[Music]
Valley of Silent statues
oh does it lead here by any chance
I guess Luigi would have picked like a
safe path to go to where she went
nothing like going to stretch your legs
and ending up in the strangest place
sorry I'm actually old so I changed my
voice Midway uh everything looks the
same down here it would be easy to get
turned around I wonder if the people who
originally made this place got lost on
it all the time too
hey what do you want were you lagging in
the shadows there are eavesdropping on
what I was saying ah you would have oh
that everyone has been talking about
right if I were younger I might have
been surprised to see you here but at my
age well very little surprises me
disappointed that I was instructed again
a gassed at the very side of you anyway
I'm going to go I'm feeling a little
part so maybe something to drink at the
canteen where what did I miss the
clothes before I go any further did I
miss the clothing shop
or will it only open after I'm like done
with the temple for example
that is only the second time that this
[\h__\h] happens in the game My Heart
after
um
okay
there's one on the surface but you have
to ascend in the well oh
it's like hidden
should be able to reach it now
oh okay
probably don't even have the money for
it though
but I'm guessing that heat resistance
might be necessary
um for the temple
and I don't want to use medicine all the
time
I will go back we'll find the armor
and
maybe the last piece
here
I have two more
look at these
the seven hearings who protect the
Gerudo their Spirits wrestled in the
land of the gurudo
so the spirits of the seven hearings are
hidden within Garuda region confirming
that these Spirits are not legend or
rumor but real is by itself an enormous
breakthrough I'm curious about the text
inscribed on the Stella did you perhaps
find any
am I even saying that right what is that
word
the seven heroines who protect the
Gerudo and the prowess return to them
the shrouded eighth will be known
if the seven
but that must mean there really was an
HP rain I don't believe it this changes
everything I'm curious about the text
inscribed
I need one more
hero in him
a grain heroine
Rowan
hmm
oh
cute
it is pronounced the same way
I'll keep my own pronunciation
in that case
nothing inside okay
there's a dude there
um
oh
alcohol or medicine
you must be the virus I've been talking
about no man I don't have anything for
you but yeah um came up with a special
version of my signature drink it's one
everybody from Vegito Baba can enjoy
I can't get my hands on what I need to
make it while we're stuck here and I
don't want to forget the recipe
when is the Strand sound
what
going away
I don't know man I don't know
when will I learn how to speak this
language after two and a half years of
streaming in it when will I ever learn
what is this special place
am I supposed to teleport up here or
this is that what I'm supposed to find
the other hand members aren't better at
it I I I think they are
definitely
here's the dude Robin
how long have you been here wait I
recognize you I've seen you walking
around out there I don't understand
you're a man but they let you just come
and go whenever you like it's [\h__\h]
unfair
why how come you're able to do that I
barely crossed the threshold between
town and desert day for me ah this is
jail
oh
one
found it I don't care about you anymore
well he looks so innocent though look at
his freckles
it didn't give me a chance to explain
anything at all I just wanted to see the
faces of my wife peridot and our
daughter ackled
wait is his wife I'll get rudian
I'm only telling you just because you
seem like a trustworthy sport I've
actually seen my dog a few times so on
average I'm more happy than upset
even though they have me in this Jayla
to see her occasionally however I
haven't seen my wife even once
and how can you have a daughter
what
did you like
put your
liquid
into like a garudian
s p e r m Bank
or he means since he got you
[Laughter]
maybe Amazo
I mean if they try everything to stay
away from Men
can say that they will not go to this
level
to continuously stay away from them but
still make children
um
I mean think about it it's not
unreasonable
[Laughter]
huh okay okay okay so they did meet he
just means since he's in the in the jail
he hasn't met her right okay I mean
I mean it could also be taken the other
way right
I got nuts
[Music]
uh yeah I know they're trying to romance
men but they're not doing very well
are they they're like I can't even
hmm
oh
the timing of the rain
thank God you just missed out on my
theory
of of what I think the gerudos are doing
um let's just not talk about it anymore
uh
I know she was planning to work at a
clothing store in Garuda town but that's
all I've got that's where I want to go
I'm sure my daughter could tell me more
but I haven't been able to talk to her
yet but I know we'll be together again
soon that's right yo everything is like
falling together automatically into my
hands I needed this
you aware of clients what do you mean
you have clients and you're listening to
my stream
wait can I just leave
like this
no hey let me out I'm not supposed to be
in here
there's obviously a jail sign another
place for business
the person who's supposed to be in there
like that bow who tried to get into town
but you're the chief's guest right
the fact that you got in here on purpose
or by accident without me knowing would
be embarrassing so get out of here
everybody
you
security
not much
secure okay clothing store it seems to
be hard to find but
uh uh somebody said I could have maybe
entered from down here
maybe the other direction
apart from the human girl blind there
was a human girl is that the child
the love child
what about this place
oh is that where I came from
ah
is this
oh wow eh
[\h__\h] scary
construction and service notes in regard
to work on the hole on the floor due to
a lack of resources a large stone slab
has been used to temporarily seal the
hole in the floor
God men dolls
in their homes
unbelievable okay so this is not wearing
the
see where the clothing store is
I think
or is it
let's go back down okay let's go this
way
uh-huh
oh
there's so many paths
maybe here oh
FBI [\h__\h] foreign
stay in a safe place
oh
how am I gonna throw aerial time
okay
oh there's more but I could make
another Hammer oh yeah let's do it with
the tree branch will that break really
easily
hey that's actually
like
like you know break
don't you think
how is how is the tree branch surviving
this
uh
uh okay should I
go up here
I think this path still continues
oh no
oh
yeah it adds durability but it just
makes no sense
huh
what I'm confused
isn't that weird
huh
did I Loop
should I Ascend for the pillow sweater
okay okay okay
confusing
is that where the shop is
so hidden
why do they make it so difficult to get
there holy [\h__\h]
yo
Client List check products
check huh
no about but the door is black how did
you
never mind whatever it's our rule not to
pry into the business of our customers
you're welcome in our shop no matter how
you manage to make it inside this is the
career secret Club the only shop in town
that sells clothing designed with bell
in mind like they're so hot yes
considering Belle aren't allowed in town
I'm sure you can understand why the shop
is a secret okay well that actually
makes sense
I mean
I don't think you have to keep the
sharpest Secret
because it's not a crime to make clothes
for ball right
but you have to make a secret passage
for the Vose yeah
anyway that's how we run a business
we're not concerned with who you are I
don't care I don't care about myself
obviously as an outcast myself I
appreciate your business
these are winter clothes right
[Music]
can I sell something too
yeah please buy from me
although I normally wouldn't want to
sell my gems to you
oh [\h__\h] why do I have so many diamonds
sell your couple
let's go no I was complaining about not
having diamonds
okay
that should be good
diamonds are chihuahuas best friends
yeah this one can walk better in the
sand definitely helpful in the temple I
would think
but I kind of want to upgrade it but
well first we'll go to the temple if we
can make it and then we'll get the the
like spawning spot and then I'll go
upgrade Maybe
spalder
oh wait
oh cause that doesn't give heat
resistance oh
okay but I I get another heat resistance
from this
and maybe eventually I'll buy the pants
too should I buy it now
um
to have a full set
oh I might as well
[Music]
is that enough
I didn't check usually seems like the
the Top's always like the cheapest for
some reason
oh wait no never mind sometimes it's not
always oh
okay
we got some new drip look at this
oh
yeah
that looks pretty cool also like the
more I am around the Gerudo
the more I realize
link has the proportions
and uh he's so small
it's just because I'm around the Gerudo
I never thought God he was so small
before
oh
tiny
what are the Garuda just really tall
I think that's it
yay we got heat resistance let's go
where is this I'm gonna make myself a
note
um
oh
for the shop I mean later on they'll
probably return to the surface I would
assume
nice Elemental
stuff works well
I wonder if there'll be a lot of beers
in the temple probably yeah
Mommy
[Music]
I need to find out lore about these
enemies
they're so tall were they once Gerudo
I wonder
okay now that we have the clothes we
should go back inside I guess
midnight is sent to go to the shop so
now I have to go
that way
shrine
Shrine here so I can teleport where's
the shrine it always like goes
what's it up there
I thought they were chickens
let's read this
I received an unsettling report from
bully hour today a strange haste some
have called it Gloom it's emanating from
beneath Hyrule Castle those who touch it
fall ill but my friends Link and Zelda
are in Hyrule I'm sure that those two
can get to the bottom of this problem
and you're much more worrying report has
arrived both Link and Zelda have gone
missing while exploring below Hyrule
Castle shortly after they were lost the
castle lifted off into the sky where it
was joined by countless small floating
islands so much happening all at once
what is going on in the world and our
these those two safe
things grow more and more dire across
Hyrule and now the danger has come here
as well a sand shroud the worst
Sandstorm in recent memory has covered
the area people are taking shelter
underground we traveled out to see if we
could discern the cause of it but we
were ambushed by new monsters called
cryptos
to make matters worse I wasn't able to
accurately hit them with the lighting I
can call down we're inundated with those
seeking safety from the sand shroud or
the gypdos and we still don't know what
has caused this as the chief of Gerudo
town I am to blame for these failures
ah
Nene is I would say it's the other way
around
we're confused the plushies oh really
they do look like items that I can pick
up
[Music]
wait did I take a picture of the last
yeah I did the fortifications protecting
the shelter are strong there's no way
the monsters will be able to break
through we're also lucky to have a good
source of water in the shelter but we
must watch for Invaders trying to use
the waterways another precaution we
should cover the hole behind the throne
ah
[Music]
sitting here feeling sorry for myself
oneself anything I'm going to leave
boliara in charge of the shelter and go
train the ruins to the north aren't too
far they should be perfect place for me
to practice with my lightning despite my
worries for my people and for the world
I must do what I can I know that's what
Zelda would advise me to do oh lady
orbosa if only you were here with us
watch over us in all these dark times
and keep telling links safe
thank you
always these secrets they're revealing
in their diaries with behind the throne
this is her bed
where's the throne again
but I also kind of want to see the
shrine I think the shrine is
on top of the stone Maybe
yeah it says above still
[Music]
there we go
shrine
[Music]
let me try another strawberry
um
these are terrible
but
really bad
they look
like the color is pretty nice
but they taste like [\h__\h]
weird
normally they're like a really vibrant
color
to me indicates
it's a good strawberry
I really saturated color
oh
I have idea
this was an accident anyway
so we shall use
uh wait first we need to get this out
apparently and then we feel
this liberal Shield
and now we can get red huh
what are these controls
no ghetto is it a key
actually
[Music]
I know it
know it because there's a door here
but it didn't look so properly yet like
what I'm what I'm looking at
oh my God how dare you welcome to this
dream
don't worry it's all good oh oh hi
what a surprise
were you really a one hit
well
what's that
all right that's new
what's this
I can't turn it on
but but it's uh
it's a donut piece
ah well good morning
um
no
let's use uh until my weapons wow
is there a chest up there for me
it's not really strong enough
I mean two next to each other is not
really gonna solve this problem right
also this is the smaller one
with the small ah because it's a weapon
uh
what do I have to use this thing
oh
[Music]
look at all these wind thingies
when how do I get up there
so silly
what confusing
you first found onto your Shield might
have been a mistake nah I don't think so
maybe it's enough ah wait wait
if I move it
a bit closer
might be enough
it was enough
yeah
wait this way
let's go I got the Jazz
that works too well what what what what
what what was the other way
[Music]
it's to me it looks like the only way
unless you cheat because you have a a
rocket attached
to one of your Shields or whatever
what did I just get it's on my charger
what what is this thing anyway
okay
hi yeah
uh what is this
ah arrows
speaking of arrows no
what is this
obviously I need to use it
a mirror
just do I have to go up there
ah
I need another wind
creator
maybe I can bring this one
because that looks like I have to go up
up here
or is there nothing there thanks for the
memberships
I forgot about ascent
where would I ascend
huh uh here oh
it didn't look like to me that there was
a lot whatever
oh oh
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
does to you
on
is he gonna no wait
does that hurt you
come over here no no
no
stupid little [\h__\h] oh no it doesn't hurt
him I think he went through
okay just testing out things for science
thank you
and like one hitting all of these damn
they're really weak
so these are mirrors huh
okay we'll see what we can do with that
I have to reflect something ah
my fan Guster broke on now
okay
maybe from here
[Music]
to diagonally over there
or not quite
uh
here
it's not really
High wait maybe at the bottom can I do
it at the bottom
hard to see
um
[Music]
that's pretty good maybe it's not tall
but
but maybe I have to hold it up
uh on my own
when I'm over there
[Music]
okay but how do I return
here
let's try
let her bake the Binkies yeah let me
cook the cookies
because we have an a mirror here as well
if I hold it up oh wait I mean okay I
can hold it up like this too
[Music]
but does it have to stay like this no
only for a while
yeah yeah yeah
yeah nice cool shrine
let's run
oh
[Music]
speaking of cookies
let me take a bite
from a cookie
[Music]
I even put them in a cookie jar
my brother when he lived here for two
months he bought himself a cookie jar
and he didn't take it to his new
apartment yet
so now I'm using the cookie jar
hmm
no it's just a normal cookie John
oh James
no he couldn't take it any time honestly
I encourage him to take the rest of his
things
he still has like a few
a few things
at my place
um
there's one of them
what is the next one for me anyway
go and check my
album
I have to scroll down so far that oh
that's Pokemon
um here
what is the next one
um
did we see the the one after the pure
pad I think yeah right
didn't we also already see the kneeling
well wait I'm confused
are we already at the dagger wait did we
see this one already huh
this is the kneeling one
did I already watch that one
oh I did it doesn't look at all like
it's there it looks like it's right in
front of me
okay
looks like a sky island
like a thing that would be in the sky
hey
okay
serious
cold
let me
go look for a reju now let's go open
open open the door please
you're gonna open it right
[Music]
thank you
I know I know it gets cold at night I
am thank God it wasn't really on the
ground Underground
mm-hmm
when you say about this one
the seven hearings who protect the
Gerudo their power is housed within the
seven spirits curious does this mean
that the seven hearings Powers have
changed form even now that they are gone
and what could they mean by spirits well
Spirits are first through the two orbs
like this one so Southern I believe I've
made a break first we did it we know
what all of the Stella is say now to put
it all together and the eighth of them
connects the other seven Powers wait I
know what to do shut up
no I'm not reading that because I
already know I'm smarter than you
or is this Quest done
it's done because I'm thinking this sign
that's on this orb
I saw this and other signs
in that Hall where was the hall
and maybe I have to collect all these
all these uh pieces
add this one
and place them here maybe I don't know
like this one that's the one you know
as I thought this seems to be the place
to return the spirits described on the
sixth daylight
the same person
how did you get here faster than me
I have an inscription on the Stanley
Stacks with the seven humor and some
protected gorilla after that it goes the
secret will be expressed in the six
monuments and eighth Channel and guides
the powers of these seven the powers of
the seven are hardly blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah
[Music]
um
I know what to do
yeah yeah yeah
I know what to do although I don't think
I've seen
so many of those
orbs
but there's this one
rude
well you know I am
you know time is of the essence
I cannot
continuously waste time ah
she reacts to it right away oh you
brought the orange so you agree that it
contains one of the heroine Spirits
right if we're writing something
interesting should happen when we return
whoa
I know it all I'm annoy doll
a
[Music]
um
this Quest is quite unreboarding no way
I had a feeling based on the shape this
should fit yeah placing one doesn't seem
to have had much effect yeah we need to
do all of them
one of Patricia's prophecies might be
what I need here but she's out of Lady
region right now okay okay
so we can't continue this until we find
the Jew
no problem
no what do you mean
I was just excited that I knew the
solution already
but I'm not skipping the lore I read all
of the texts of these heroine statues
oh you're not gonna get me again okay I
knew that
um okay
so
what
oh
I mean
why is that one
standing up though
I understand I understand there's the
Sands of carrying these things over
why is one of them standing up
big napping monster and thank you for
the rest of the chat thank you oh
I appreciate that
I'm glad you think so I read the subject
properly [\h__\h]
I'm not gonna use bombs
properly when I read super chats okay
[Music]
um
well I'm glad you think I make it feel
special yeah and you make me feel
special
[Music]
I'm so special
foreign
let's make a hammer
time
what
that was a roof it's so rare that I
never like pick up Stones anymore
I don't realize that this could happen
What
simple things
make me so happy for some reason
just Zelda things am I right
yo wait that
idiot now
let it be light holy [\h__\h] that's a lot
of light
wait but how
do I have to go around it
oh wait wait one goes here so
there
I think we can activate that one first
no I don't only read red super chats
I read the full text of pinkies and reds
and then I uh read the names of
everybody
sometimes I also read uh
texts the messages of non Reds non-pinks
unless I have too many
yeah I read it when there's like a super
chat reading time
not in the middle of the stream no
what
[Music]
um
I mean I think tooling could help us too
but I don't know where he is
Cooley never here when I need him
oh there he is but
okay no oh there's the next one this
already feels like it's the like the
intro to the
to the temple doesn't it
it definitely is
okay is there another one there yeah
okay
[Music]
yeah I like it so far it feels already
very zelda-ish and templish
[Music]
let's see I should tell you guys you
probably are waiting for America
tangents right
honestly I was watching I missed stream
yesterday
and you know I was there for a really
short time so there really isn't much to
tell
most like things I could tell you about
are about like the actual journey to and
away from America
then about my actual time there because
it was really short and most of the time
we were working on things
we we had some plans to do some stuff
like go to the beach but then we didn't
have enough time after all
especially because
um the one time we wanted to stream on
Monday
the I'm a channel stream
we were
we were planning on going
uh you went to the beach or to the
movies
afterwards
but
then the stream didn't work and I
personally thought you know
I we did two streams on my channel and I
I personally thought it would be better
if we do another stream
um
because you know
we tried and it didn't work and it's
kind of like
disappointing
it just doesn't feel
fulfilling
to us either
when it's so like half-assed and it
didn't work out
yeah
yeah it was definitely a work occasion
yeah wait I need that
do I have another Elemental thing oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
wow
hot
and yeah I also wanted to go to more
um places that you guys recommended but
I mean
some things you guys recommended just
wear nowhere nearby and then also I'm a
cooked for me a lot of time and how who
am I to turn down I miss cooking right
I know it's like so happy to cook for me
and on uh both occasions where she
cooked dinner for me
it was
secretly mixed in spinach
without even telling me
she really
likes spinach and I actually hate
spinach but she makes it
she makes it in in a way
dad oh
this leaves outside
that didn't even bother me
mostly yeah
because she made like a a pesto pasta
she said and I was like oh I really like
pesto
um but she made the spinach and some
other stuff but I didn't really taste
the spinach so it was pretty good yeah
and then she put spinach in something
else too ah in like the the sauce for
like a chicken steak I think it was
chicken yeah
chicken breast
you didn't know about this path
you're tracked for the sandstorm to find
her
oh yeah I was the whole time I was
thinking like this is just a side path
but then it was so intricate
that I figured okay
where is this leading there we go
making those watermelons still
I would like to check where we are but
um wow
yes we can
no I guess this is this is the easy way
because you can't you don't have to go
outside
a night's bow
I don't know
I don't really need to leave it in there
[Music]
German
me too
incoming
sick
oh she missed what the [\h__\h] killed hair
feet I don't even
so Shuffle his knee my gun says
[Music]
link I wonder is this the same voice as
in fact the wild because she was younger
then
[Music]
it's Dodge
huh
[Music]
how are you now
yeah I had merged my German Channel
to the English Channel that's why it's
German now
you can't write merged without German
just kidding you can
so Hyrule Castle rose up into the sky
Zelda vanished right in front of you and
now you've come here looking for Clues
oh link I understand how you're feeling
Zelda is a dear friend to me as well I
will do everything in my power to help
you but to do that I need to bring a
quick resolution to a problem we get rid
of our facing
I'm sure you've noticed that the desert
is even more difficult to cross than
usual
that's thanks to this unusual sand
shroud it appeared around the same time
the events at Hyrule Castle took place
it has blanketed the whole desert
including our town
and not long after that swarms of
monsters were never seen before began
attacking we're calling them gypdos
physical attacks don't work well against
them they are slow but they still make
investigating the Sands realm difficult
when you're watching just now
I've been practicing striking that dummy
over there with lightning
if I can aim the lightning well I think
it may be an effective weapon against
the kryptos yeah but you have a cool
down don't you
think that's really effective I'm just
gonna continue using my
elemental weapons
uh
yeah I don't know
emotional damage
we could use emotional damage yeah
uh then they are slow yeah but still
like it doesn't seem very efficient it
hits multiple targets okay
it's good for mining
AOE
oh
but this technique is unrefined I only
recently discovered it and I still need
more practice wait what did she have in
breath of the Wild
huh
nothing
what did what
what
[Music]
ah
the helmet I was or boss's palette okay
wait and the busan's power wasn't it
also lightning though
the same or was it like a bit difficult
uh different I mean
the helmet
same same one
okay so that one didn't really change
but not targeted oh
I'm just wondering because the other
attacks seem to have changed a little
bit but they stayed mostly the same like
in in
the idea of it
thanks for the membership welcome
you target an enemy with this one okay
it's a nerfed version
okay
I only recently discovered it and I
still need more practice
I want to master this power so I can use
it to defeat the gyptus if I can do that
we can investigate the source of the
sandshred and search for Zelda as well
link will you help me with my training
I think wait please don't use me as the
dummy
I think I can use your arrows to help me
aim my lightning strikes fire one at the
dummy over there
my arrows
to aim your lightning strikes sounds
like a stretch
okay
oh
there we go now let's try something a
little trickier
aim for those dummies over there maybe
we can hit them all with a single
lightning strike here's an idea don't
try to hit the specific dummy
instead aim for the area in the middle
of all three like right around where
that rock is jutting out oh but keep in
mind that the farther away the target is
from me the longer it will take me to
build up the energy to hit it okay
ah I see okay this line
I have to wait for it
and now they're all in it okay
everything that's within this line
but hopefully not this um energy
we'll get hit
oh
okay I'm like a conductor
I'm not getting hit though thankfully
wow what is this magic why are only the
things we want to hit are getting hit
um
I'm getting the hang of it now
oh
look at those don't stand a chance
against this power
she looks so cool I love her like armor
and all that her whole get up
sheesh so golden
I can't thank you enough for your help
link
she cute
huh
what was that it didn't sound like any
noise the sandshred has made that's for
sure
you heard that too right it was
if
we've received word that's a swarm of
cryptos are attacking karakawa Bazaar
bullier is already on her way there
she's already okay understood thank you
link we need to head to karakawa Bazaar
at once
I must ask you for your help once again
my lightning and your guiding arrows
make us a formidable pair do you
remember caracara Bazaar it's the Oasis
Northeast of Garuda town
Northeast
North is East oh the Oasis where I was
already in when I was on my way to this
Garuda town
let's show those gifts what we're made
of
ah okay okay
uh
what
oh
cute
um cute
wait bulliara's here too
anyway uh
North East
oh
how do I know she went that way though
right
at least I have the right pants for this
nice
I should take one of those wind thingies
try not at the Oasis do I what
[Music]
do I
oh and now I can see it ah
let's go
how the verb doing hello
[Music]
we're doing better thank you thank you
guys for your patience I was really
hoping to get back to streaming sooner
but at the same time I was also really
stressed out
the past couple weeks and
also wanted to take a break
don't let anyone get those get close
I was like already
looking up Spas but I could go to stay
over for two or three nights nice
it took a couple days off for that so
now I feel like I I guess I won't go to
the spa
I got a massage though a two-hour
massage
I was like I'm in so much pain one hour
is not enough and a half hour also not
enough I need two hours
I got a two hour massage
yeah right before I got sick
yeah
it was really good yeah yeah
I even like normally I I don't fall
asleep because
usually it's just one hour and I need
long time to fall asleep and and I like
to focus on
the feeling of the massage so that I
know that something's actually happening
but this time I actually kind of fell
asleep for a moment just a short moment
and then I woke up and I was like damn
it now I missed the whole massage on my
left leg
now it feels like it didn't even happen
damn it it really feels like it didn't
happen
it's like I skipped it no
they usually just zone out I can't zone
out my my head's like I'm looking
through the the massage bed window and
then I'm just thinking about all kinds
of things hmm
yeah you would think it still helps but
I I'm like damn she just skipped my leg
sorry to keep everyone waiting but I'm
here now and we're going to wipe all to
give those out at once
follow me
link don't let me down
so cool
these monsters said no chance
[Music]
so like this
foreign
[Music]
broke
nice wait why didn't get why did it not
get that one
was he behind
your rudobo what's the special thing
about the Garuda bow that goes in
damn we needed him who's alive
ah
[Music]
and she looks cute in the icon on the
left side
who else
[Music]
will be fighting others quite a few more
wait for it and
yeah I missed
here
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah that's pretty cool we're basically
getting free electric arrows that are
way stronger than electric girls ah
foreign
we need to destroy that somehow
otherwise they'll overwhelm us
oh okay no it should be no problem I
guess we'll just shoot the middle part
and
one in your face
come on in your face
anyone left oh no
she
yay Trypophobia oh yeah maybe a little
bit
um
[Music]
German name
oh
[Music]
foreign
I just plugged in something into my
video
no
what happened
wait we can probably Replay that but
what the [\h__\h]
Ed in the USB uh C cable
oh
we missed like two seconds
no
wait you guys don't see it
why
I saw it just now
on it
There It Is God damn it can I can we
wait oh
can we re-watch it
really quick ly it must be here right
um is it not here
I thought you can rewatch them
and one of the last save
pretty one huh time is wrong on my
switch
this looks like there's some Thunder
happening there
we'll live don't worry about it no
no so missed like two seconds maybe
it's not my
man why do you guys not care actually oh
this is this thing
what
oh is this now
[Music]
what where am I why what
oh okay
that screenshot was from like now
okay
Okay then if you guys don't care that
much then
I guess
why not okay
um I need to charge my controller though
I tried to plug in the USB CP but it's
it crashed
crashed everything
USB
I I see your cable
swan
this one
plug it into the switch dock okay
we have
an assortment of USBC cables
different ones actually
oh these are probably from my VR
stuff my mom moved my things around
okay control oh but they're so short
they're so short I hope they charge fast
okay really short I just need to switch
a little bit closer okay
look at us
oh man aren't the the fish people are
taller than hylians right so maybe maybe
you guys you ladies should go for the
fish people
ew well go back damn me I accidentally
combined good day with the root was so
lock in there perhaps I've lived there
too long which reminds me I've heard all
sorts of new greetings lately like
should I have been using nonsense
another Island Stranded by the sand
shroud I take it how challenging life
without wings must be the higher gold to
finish the Shroud cat so irito can soar
right over it for us it's a little more
than Sandy fog
um
oh
Cali would really appreciate link for
his shortness I think
he likes short people
okay so now we're going back again to
the main city then I might as well
teleport
he might be too old no what are you
saying
I think is same height as Ina with her
shoes on
how tall is Nina with her shoes on
sorry guys I keep on yawning because I
just can't get like a full breath in I
think we have to destroy this thing huh
oh wait but they're here
ah they are they are
let me go in here that's what the throne
is I want to check out what's behind the
bro and I completely forgot
where where exactly
can I move something here
oh
is this considered a well yeah
wait this also was a way to enter the
Garuda shelter that's it that's what she
was talking about in her diary
oh
it's nice that she has quick access to
it that makes sense
oh
are these things for me free to take
I'm guessing not
really
[Music]
she says I can take the things I'll take
the bombs
on the bombs
no the bombs
but the rest I don't want to take
everything from you I'll take I'll take
the bananas for sure because I have yet
to meet like more gigas
the ones like give me bananas I don't
think you even get them from normal you
guys you have to go underground oh
what a mirror
I'll take these two but I'll leave you
with the rest
how nice of me whoa look at these
weapons though yeah
um I'll be back
if I need some more things
currently I have plenty of weapons
so it's okay
I don't wanna
deal too much
let's take care of that
other weird plant looking thing
look link
there's a good Hive oh it's a hive
yeah okay that makes sense just like the
one that appeared near karakara kiwawa
kiwawa Bazaar both the hive and those
tornadoes were reported to have shown up
at the same time too
but it's not the only only the one Hive
they're afraid to deal with each just
outside the tailgates I don't need a
clairvoyant sand seal to know a massive
crypto attack is coming right now these
these those hives are durable and nearly
impervious to attack but when they open
and begin releasing gibdos they're
vulnerable the kid does one wait outside
our walls forever so when they launch
their attack that's our chance to strike
I'm ready oh
yeah oh yeah
car
come to me yeah
ask her again you heard it didn't you
yeah this time I heard it
um is it calling out to us hmm
link is something to matter
I thought it's nothing link for now we
should focus on protecting Gerudo town
from the enemies at our gates we must
prepare for the battle
yeah I'm ready
[Music]
speaker for the island soldiers okay oh
talk to Captain tiaki in the yard [\h__\h]
it's
[Music]
true because
I mean
work with her to decide how best to
deploy our forces
yeah right
it's in the courtyard she's in charge of
the materials we have on the hand we
could reinforce our defenses with them
if you need anything you should talk to
her oh
um
wait the materials no okay I already
have plenty
let's talk ah
two oh
types of monsters have been have
appeared outside the tunnels it won't be
long before I will need to deal with
this threat I should redeploy our forces
who should we send and where we could
spread them out to lightly cover all the
gates or maybe a concentrated Force to
protect a weekend position we need to
decide who to send where I'd like to
hear your thoughts
does it matter
oh
wait
it does
can I fail
Ure
okay then we should maybe take a look
I guess
why on Earth
okay okay that's it that's it
I already thought that this must be
coming from underground but now I see
these statues that are usually always
only see on the ground
what's what's what's what's what's going
on
statues are unrelated you normally
anyway why would a certain type of
weapon be better here I don't
understand
what should I talk to that lady or
you went with Canon North
Terrain
a man
it looks the same here though
you failed it four times
this also looks the same like it doesn't
look like anything specifically
um
let's flip around for Longford little
challenge our endurance she doesn't
really give me a hint though either
he tried to build turrets
eh you did the first try not that hard
tell me something
no no hand oh
right
[Music]
okay
use your intuition
um
my intuition
oh
tells me
nothing in particular
but
this is basically like gotcha
someone said it worked for them North so
I will go north
ah
need something strong in the north yeah
spare troops
[Music]
because there's e a in spare and EA in
East
and an S as well
sounds legit
sword troops
to the West because there's an S and A W
in the West
ah
yeah yeah
uh anything else that I need to do for
you
no oh
okay
how do I start this thing
good
that's that's where the teachings used
to happen right
yeah I think we can start
let's go oh
fire attacks oh it's fire and lightning
specifically
[Music]
um
do I just have to listen to all this and
listen to this one already
oh
Talk of the supply girl oh oh okay oh
because I felt like I already talked to
her beforehand
maybe I have to talk to her now
oh
barricade let's talk barricades there
are free gates from the palace to
northas Northgate is ahead West Coast
um iron bells and woods to blotter path
which North
because the cannon is there but no
people so
hopefully the cannon will do everything
I think is that logical
I think that's logical can we only place
it in one oh
[Music]
only one side okay
sounds like a good option right
okay can we start now
oh yes they're complete let's go
where where do I place myself
can we get like a strategy game kind of
POV from the top
from really far
that'll be cool
I just run like a madman
link
same height cute
I'm curious about that voice we heard
earlier but
oh
[Music]
so disgusting
ew they look like they're out of Metroid
Prime
yup is beginning before anything else
we'll need to deal with this
mm-hmm
[Music]
it all looks the same
looks like the same amount too
fully Howard they have the town
surrounded
stay strong
this threat is also an opportunity fight
well and we can wipe them out in one
battle hives and all
prepare yourself for battle let's show
them the true power of the Gerudo oh
everyone protect our chief protect our
town
I'll be up here I guess I think then
they have a like a better
Austin
East
[\h__\h] hell I'm here now
do I have to go east
is East over there
[Music]
it's a suggestion
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] my stamina
no
they may have
uh yes [\h__\h]
did that kill them
hey I bet
Austin
let me help let me help
[Music]
I'm desperate
okay here we go please
okay that was broken that one's broken
I'll I'll help a little bit more
is that right
it's not over yet wait guys
oh they're good they're good they they
killed some people I think
a bit
yeah
anyone
let's destroy the one in the east go go
go go go go
go
[Applause]
[Music]
there's some flying ones too what the
[\h__\h]
um I'm gonna go for a wing so we can
shoot from here
hey why what's
what's up specifically
okay
um you you disgusting
oh
let me help you ladies uh if you need
help
[Laughter]
squishy who is she
what I don't see her
I want to see her ah there she is okay
okay I'll protect you now baby
uh with my so cool little Reaper lies a
little easel lies a little easel
did that hit any of them
no problem no problem
I'm right here in the middle
oh did we do it
yeah
oh did we
[Applause]
guys that's cool
that's pretty cool
wow
oh fun fun how did you guys fail that yo
you're such non-gamers
how can you fail this
[Music]
sick burn
I've nearly failed that that was only
for the sake of making it more exciting
hmm
um link I'm incredibly grateful for your
help in the battle on behalf of all the
garudo thank you I suspect the crypto
threat will calm down a bit now and
we've wiped out the hives that were
surrounding the town
I noticed that the hives crumbled into
sand when we destroyed them I wanted to
keep those have some kind of connection
to the sand or maybe maybe they're
connected to the sand shroud did they
make it did they summon them
and then there's the voice that you and
I both heard the voice and lightning
this reminds me of something link
there's something you should see come
down to the mural in the underground
shelter
okay
and that was pretty cool
oh wait is the sand trout gone here now
Paulo's had a great aim are you
do you mean me is Paul lost me
like Kirby
use that to the store dad you mean the
the thing that covered the whole
I know Polo is
chicken
a boyo what
oh no
yeah I I know that you know I'm just
saying you probably mean me because you
guys always say I'm a chicken
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
let me try to follow the map
mm-hmm
I was curious about this too oh link you
came look at the mural on this wall
it is thought to have been painted by
the ancestors of the Gerudo it appears
that when they created it they were also
using the shelter to hide perhaps the
Garuda of the distant past were also be
set by some great disaster
anyway the writing on the mural says
standing back to back with the throne
witness red pillars across the vast sea
uh
unite the pillars in light to reveal the
lightning Stone and open the way
isn't that what I was already doing
and then I found Ranger
you who can hear my voice come to me I
await you
that mysterious voice that spoke to us
are this different
it's word its words reminded me of this
mural
this image must represent a location of
some kind and the engraved words are a
riddle to discovering its location
it's the only explanation that makes
sense
okay
[Music]
um
you guys are saying it's different but
I I I I I I I
feel like I still need to go back to
that place
that's what I'm thinking
I know thank you
thank you
you know I was also unsure though if I
should um
like go alone to a spa because like
spontaneously No One's Gonna join me so
spontaneously
but if I go spontaneously to a spa alone
should I just stay in the country or
should I go
somewhere outside like I don't know
Greece or so but then I feel like it's
kind of different going to
travel alone
[Music]
for like a spa
Greece did they undo my things
uh
like I think I would be a bit less
feeling awkward
yeah
if if
it's like at least within my own country
in a place where I feel like I'm I don't
need to
got it
don't need to feel weird about being
alone
why does it go up
ah
physics this now
oh
I'm thinking
you know we already opened this I know I
know
but what if
I put the other mirror
uh where did I found find another mirror
oh
I hear a frog in here so this is
considered a cave wait wait where's the
other mirror
first statue
true indeed
yeah anyway nah um I feel like
this stress from
the travel and all that is like mostly
gone
now
[Music]
um
I feel like I have I'm already
relatively rested
I mean a spa trip would be nice too but
now I took
days off for being sick so
and in my Japan trip uh is coming up
in a while too
so yeah you know
I I wanna stream wow Mr pan but I don't
know
because I'll be staying in a hotel
so if I want to scream I'll probably
have to use
the studio or do like off collapse of
Japanese members again
[Music]
yo this has a huge Zoom
foreign
I'm excited for the Japan trip it's so
soon
not like next week or so but it's
definitely soonish
but don't worry guys you got normal
schedule kiwawa for a little while
now
house well I will not tell you I cannot
tell you
I cannot tell you anything exact let's
uh not too soon but also not too knots
too soon what
you know
you know how it is
like a mix of being soon
and not being soon
can broke the shield
and
what the group of Shield somehow is
cooler and that one I got from the
monster
oh opening
what is the dungeon you know
what if you what if you merged a pot
doesn't it just break when you merge it
to your weapon
I'll be too easy
okay
more arrows
yeah this one I can imagine it would
break right away
oh well oh well well
but
ah
oh wait I don't die I don't think and
die
oh
good to know
wait is there anything down here like
that's worth looking at though
for knockout I don't know
wait I still didn't find the Frog I
heard the frog that was an opal
I heard a frog
hey
an opening year
not really though
I heard the Frog up there in the middle
you bought a PC cabinet what's the PC
cabinet
like a figurine cabinet instead you
display your [\h__\h]
your PCS your collection of PCS
or you mean you mean the outside the
case of the uh okay
okay I'm going back up
you're drunk
then it's not really you're saying I'm
inspiring you it's not really that I'm
inspiring you isn't it the alcohol then
that's inspiring you
it doesn't seem to be really my effect
I think you do that
okay where's this [\h__\h] frog
.com
[Music]
I didn't shoot the Frog and already
forget about it did I
don't hear him anymore either did I
imagine the frog sound
I heard it here
somewhere here
did I imagine
maybe I did
because I'm not hearing it anymore
you're ready too thank you okay okay
then I'm not crazy okay
didn't I kill you before
didn't I open up this door before
[Music]
okay we got it
now
what did she say
standing back to back with the throne
so we're gonna go to the throne witness
red pillars across a vast sea
okay so first we go back to
Gerudo town
that's not froggy Waba calm down [\h__\h]
you Mama it's green
oh
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay let me think what is there that I
need to tell you about the America trip
basically I think you guys already know
everything
because
I had Mexican food the mole like Anna
even told me she never had it before
but it's something Mexican so she
recommended it to me oh his chest there
I'm going to be honest with you guys
it wasn't quite my thing
it tasted better when I ate it mixed
with everything
on its own it's not good
don't like chocolate I love chocolate
but it didn't
like chocolate thank God actually I
guess
I don't want to lose these fences I
never use my Shields though
hmm
oh well
I feel like other items of the menu I
probably would have enjoyed more
but at least I got to eat something
really unique
yeah
but I wouldn't mind trying
some more different foods I was actually
surprised that it wasn't spicy
I just randomly basically chose
something
from the menu and it just turns out to
not be spicy
went back to back to the front but
there's something in the way
okay back to back
and then
maybe I'm completely off here but
at the back of the front witness red
pillows across
do you mean these
these plants though
wait red villains they don't look red
but there's pillows over there maybe
they're red if I get closer
when those red pills across the scene
unite the pillows in light to reveal the
lightning Stone
and open the way
uh
unite them in light
look for three of them there's free
but do they have to be like separate
what is this
oh melons they grow like this and the
sand on the ground
what
really
huh
is that true
way let's go I saw something red
Let It Go
is that so nice running around maybe
look for updraft yeah okay
ah
yeah
Mexican food and then
uh oh hi
and the rest was like Denny's and
oh
um
[Music]
and Amy's cooking I miss cookies and
Mama's dinners
so
fortunately it's not much then there was
that incident
with Burger King
where I really think oh I didn't do
anything wrong
because I looked at the menu
dangerous dangerous
yeah
when I arrived I was like tired and and
you know just wanted something quick so
I went to like a Burger King and they
they had um
crispy chicken on the menu too but it
was called I think
there was an extra word maybe Royal or
Royal or something like that
crispy chicken
yeah
and I
um oh I think there were like two words
uh
what was it you guys not go to Burger
King in America bro
um
but there was something I think like
classic you could choose between classic
or a non-classical so I asked like okay
well like what does that mean
uh and then [\h__\h] I don't see [\h__\h]
where did I where did I come from
and I asked if like
um
what was the difference and they said
well the classic one is normal and the
other one is spicy I think
yeah
oh hello
so I said okay I want the non-spicy one
but looking
at the menu
and crispy chicken
looked one more time please
there's one all the way over there
looked pretty much like ah
our crispy chicken so I was hoping for
it to be kind of the same
um
go back look at the hey
what why
that'll be worth it
it looks like it had pretty much all the
same ingredients
and then what I got what I got was
something completely different
it has bacon that wasn't on the picture
it had no tomato even though the Tomato
was on the picture
oh yeah it was just it was just not a
crispy chicken I don't understand
well I'm looking at it what am I
supposed to see here
oh no I was already going to the next
pillar
I was supposed to activate the other
pillars
what are you talking about
facts either
yeah they gave me something else but I'm
like how can you mess it up there were
like no customers
I was the only one and like because I
was asking so many questions I think I
made I made it very clear what I wanted
you know
I wanted a crispy chicken
Burger
Plus
they messed it up big time
it was so sad
I didn't get high enough
I'm so sad because I was so hungry and
then I was so stressed out so and I did
I did take out and I went back to my
hotel room and then I opened the burger
and I was like okay I'll eat this and
then I go to sleep yeah yeah
all is fine all is good
and then I open up the packaging and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] is this
I don't really like bacon and burgers
that much I'm sorry I like bacon but not
as burgers that much
I was kind of looking for something
refreshing crispy chicken is also always
so refreshing to me you know
because
it has the Tomato in it and without the
tomato
it's just not the same
this is not the same
made me so sad and then I was like
considering for 10 minutes should I go
back I huh
should I go back and and ask
[\h__\h]
to fix it or should I I just eat this
should I order from somewhere else I
don't want to go outside anymore I'm so
[\h__\h] exhausted from my traveling
I don't want to move anymore
why why did you mess with my order I
don't understand and then I was having
kind of a mental breakdown
like after looking at the burger for
like 15 minutes and like being like a
whiny [\h__\h]
not like
completely crying but just being like
why I just wanna eat why am I online
this I don't have an appetite for what
is in front of me you know
what the [\h__\h]
okay
I have the brain for this right now
why is it looking there can I turn it oh
wait
huh
I skipped ahead really
[Music]
go to the top
in the end I just ate it
after like 20 minutes where I was
already pretty cooled down
I just ended up eating it
unhappily I was like well Burger King
you and me I thought we had something
going
I thought we were gonna be besties
I thought you had a crispy chicken and
you lied to me
you gave me something that wasn't a
crispy chicken at all
[Music]
how do I go to the top
oh wait
look at this suckers
these ones float on on their own anyway
don't they
foreign
[Music]
second one
but have you guys not had crispy chicken
in America before what did you get when
you ordered the crispy chicken
I would think you got the thing that you
ordered right
I have trust issues now with with Burger
King in America I don't know if I can
ever trust Burger King in America again
oh no
that was just all wrong
[Music]
no let me yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh
no way
oh wait
how do I
what is this
do I need all four of them
are you food wanted or no better chicken
legs than quinoa what are you talking
about
oh come on come on
come on
foreign
[Music]
I think I've heard of that
I think I saw a Wendy's but I saw it too
late
um and I didn't really think of Wendy's
for burgers anyway
probably because my image of Wendy's is
still shooting greens like
from the Wendy's in Japan
like Wendy's in Japan though
again just like Denny's it's very
different it's like very
um
very much a
oh
Family Restaurant wait how what am I hmm
[Music]
hmm
this is stupid
this is absolutely stupid please tell me
I don't need all of them
what
just one okay
is he had a platform still there
yeah
okay
you use the weapon oh yeah I guess you
could just drop one of your weapons that
you don't need and attach them
yeah but oh it's cold now
[Music]
attach this so I can bring it up
and go up fast before my
battery is deplete
Five Guys I don't think I tried to Five
Guys but last time I was in America I
tried the
was it in and out
that was good stuff
but like I said
how could I turn down ama's
self-made food you know if she's so
sweet to make an effort to cook for me
it would be rude to not do something oh
I have to do it in the right direction
now well I don't know the right
direction
right but now I have a good look
where the next the
light source would be but
I can't roll and see is it maybe here
ah here maybe
Maybe
okay
ah
it looks so cold now so blue
[Music]
electricity resistance what okay
oh yeah also I was supposed to have
Korean lesson yesterday
no yeah yesterday
and
I ended up moving it because I was sick
and I'm glad I did because I I thought
that during my travels I would have time
to study
uh Korean a little bit that was my goal
do my homework and all that and I I
didn't
time at all
unfortunately
so now I was gonna do it like on the
days where I got sick but then what was
that doing
wait there there's a light thingy here
ah and the blood moon
so I need to practice I I ended up like
asking for the lessons to be moved to
next week so I have two lessons next
week
and one on Monday
and the one on Thursday so tomorrow at
the latest by tomorrow I need to study
some Korean guys
it raises the tower I hadn't realized
that's what that was happening
so tomorrow
before the stream I guess and maybe
after two
Bend this flute I hope I can study
enough
ah [\h__\h] hell
[Music]
it doesn't look like it's changing
the other way maybe oh wait now it's
rising it was the other way
oh
now it's blocking it and
now it's
I accidentally put
I don't know what position is supposed
to be and then I just jumped off and I
was like I'm gonna come back here later
[Music]
the fire is gone wait
it has to recharge right yeah
[Music]
okay
what
100 intention of course Ice movie
hi what
ah yeah
[Music]
tomorrow oh
yeah yeah I knew you guys would be very
excited for that
well we are doing is uh 3D thing
is the first
I gotta go in the middle right
it's the first like occasion
I think
since mummies like not really it's not
her of 3D
debut but it was her reveal woman and
Elena
revealing their Freddie at the
fourth Fest
so Louis immediately took the chance
so give you guys
what you want
um
okay I'm guessing this is it this is
what they want
what what else did the thing say
uh unite the person like to reveal the
lightning Stone and open the way
lightning Stone
the Moon it must be
more maybe underneath no wait
what
trying to look
we're not complete
huh
although that one is kind of like lower
than the other one
did I place it wrong after all that one
oh yeah
is it
because of this one
just slightly up
and that felt like everything was
perfect
because it met that one at least
damn it
damn it they got me they got me good
yeah yeah
oh wow I mean by the way
um has she has two suits
just telling you guys she has two suits
but she doesn't have um
like enough cameras really
capture also that was her first attempt
like what we did in the first stream on
Amish Channel that was her first attempt
and
um
trying to capture two people what we
were doing is we were just wearing the
tops
um and we're just gonna we were just why
is it not working we were just gonna
capture the
uh upper body yeah because
she knew I guess that because of the
lack of cameras
which by the way cost
thousands and thousands and ten
thousands of dollars so
the the suits are not the problems the
cameras
but yeah
um we're gonna just do upper body then
it was her first time trying because she
already knew like she can't really
technically do it well
but it wasn't an attempt
there it is wow
Triforce
Transformers
[Laughter]
sorry I got a little bit too excited
yeah and if it wasn't for the [\h__\h]
internet it probably probably would have
worked but then later on we just we had
to record some things and then I was
already fully suited and we just decided
to just do it the way we were in that
moment
and then yeah we had some other travels
that's why that's why am I ended up
being a little bit more scuffed than
desired but
it's fun anyway and I mean already had a
lot of like fun with her 3D Studio so it
was nice that I could always be high
quality 3D in these streams hey
because I normally don't have this
opportunity
um where was it
here
and you guys got so much good stuff so
many gifs gifts from it can you guys get
them to be like available oh
on Twitter when you look for
takanasikiara gifts please I looked for
them they're not there yet
link
who's there
did you see that link it's Zelda yeah
oh she's gone
ah
yeah can you upload them on tenor or
giphy
I think I always see it yeah on 10 or 10
or 10 or
please
upload them all all of them
close-ups too not only full body okay
close-ups are useful too
yeah
what she's gone
you know I found the the eye tracking
especially on day three of the Amaco lab
really interesting we were what the [\h__\h]
what are you doing there you freaked me
out I was like what is that
we were
um trying different apps for face
tracking throughout the
days
and they're all different ones than what
we use in the cover Studio
we have very different ways of doing it
in cover studio uh but yeah Ahmed and I
we were like using like apps that like
3D 3D YouTubers and so on use
um and the one on the third one was that
kind of cute
on the third day that I'm a stream my
eyes were like so
you're kind of cute
I've been there we're so cute so Godly
and wobbly
oh we're cute
they were like freaking out though when
I was looking elsewhere
to reload the gun and and shoot
hey yeah
the only thing it couldn't really do is
like change the expression
um we would probably have to press a
toggle or so but we were always away
from phone and PC so we couldn't press
any toggles
I guess we are ready to enter the temple
or is there even more foreplay
I saw the lights of the red pillars and
hurt here as quickly as I could
it can't be a coincidence that we've
seen someone who looked like Zelda twice
but a mystery for another time did you
solve the mirror's riddle and caused
this to appear I'm impressed thank you
for noticing that it was me
if I remember correctly the mural said
unite the pillars and light to reveal
the lightning Stone and open the way
maybe my lightning strike is the key
I think so
oh
whoa
oh wait it has that thing
let's do something about the temple
immediately because
otherwise maybe there's give those
spawning from it
your favorite Temple really well
hopefully because the last one was you
know
okay okay so no foreplay
that's fine because all of that even
though it was kind of scattered
was plenty in my opinion
all right
what a temple
I mean it was it was it was fun it was
just like kind of short and small and
didn't feel like a temple because it was
so open
lightning Temple
I liked it anyway it's just short
ah pre-tample stuff was fine too but
maybe I don't know it's been too long I
also don't really remember
I know
and go
oh
kinda cute
thank you
[Music]
look at the feathers oh
cute that is cute
okay
it's the face
right
yeah
no okay can I hit it normally now
oh [\h__\h]
once you get hit that's a lot of damage
um what can I hit it now
when I missed all my chances I'm not
giving up
oh can I fly up without them
oh wait he's not he's still white though
oh
what's going on
did I do it right
are we restarting the fight did I reset
it
are you going inside and we're gonna
play later
just like in Metroid Prime
it's light up toward the roof maybe
there's some way to go up after it
inside the structure come on link let's
look for a way in
okay
or we just climb up can we
can you
could you
what if you you can't but she can't oh
yeah
yo yo
ninja ninja
[Music]
ignore those bastards
okay
I saw you move
[Music]
uh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
okay
looks like the queen is wearing cute
little bow
say that but don't you agree you know
it's like those feathers
those Tufts on top of owls
not all owls have it but some owls
yeah
wouldn't you say you know that's what
makes those owls especially killed
um
like a mop yeah yeah yeah kind of like a
moth
[Music]
wait what now
Oh I thought the sand was already
pushing it down and releasing it was the
key
[Music]
um
thingy actually is really good to have
torches too
it's like so well prepared like what
this just literally came out of the sand
why is there things for me to like
you know yeah
work with
why it's like it wants to be solved
yeah
right
I want to go up do I want to go down
there
nah
write a smaller ones
uh-huh
couldn't pull it towards me but
wait this reminds me of um
this one like cave uh or or whatever it
was that I walked into an Elden ring
because it also had firewalls like this
and it had these paths where I would
walk around the corner and it's dark and
I wouldn't know what would expect me
around the corner but that fire that
fire
really like traumatized me
it was a trap
so can I expect there to be more traps
these Flames make it possible well we
have a different problem now lady
nice shot
yeah the desert it's not the pyramid the
pyramids have like traps right
this is not a pyramid
um
we could use those stones to block it
but weren't those kind of far away
or
is that really the intense way
come back later okay
whoa
we attacked at the same time
though Genie
[Music]
ah it's okay
um
there's a Gerudo Claymore
Noni
I thought this would continue here audio
I guess I'm going down
great Robin
oh you think that there was a person
down there
maybe maybe not anymore maybe somebody
already
robbed the person
or it's one of the gibdos and they they
give those came out of the Grave hello
[Music]
someone never helps when you actually
need him
[\h__\h]
no I don't think I will
just another weapon
garudos kimita
okay thankfully I I still have enough to
drop wait
brain
oh Tommy horn ah I feel sick
what
um
[Music]
foreign
okay a petting is in order
I'll give this movie to be a pity party
[Music]
happy cat
hi
[Music]
oh
it was so soft
[Music]
thank you
would you like to sit here
probably not right you don't wanna you
wanna go again
[Music]
I see chunkers outside the room too hi
chunky wonky looks like she just woke up
from a nap or so
ah okay
okay
I got some
some cuddles and
perfect you came at the perfect timing
didn't you
and I had a good excuse to cuddle with
her
but I'm not feeling too well
I lost track of what I was doing though
I came down here I picked that up and
now
dead handle
back up
oh I wait if I Ascend here am I on the
other side of the fire
no
okay well
whoopsie
oh no way
no I can't run when I do that I mean I
mean I could just really quickly
and I have fire protection anyway but
what about nature
maybe from the other side I'll fix it
ah okay
I didn't want to go without her she
could be scared alone
yeah
actually one one shot moment I mean do
something really quick don't worry
I'm staying
[Music]
oh
look oh
just removing a Band-Aid that I was
planning on
uh airing out
while I was streaming because like in
bed I I wanted to keep the Band-Aid on
so that like the cat hairs don't go to
where I put it on
yeah now
I'm just airing it out yeah
okay that's different kind of sand okay
what's next
huh
yeah
[Music]
placed it on the on the burning ball
they just explode there okay
why is she so negative
it's no problem girl
okay wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
we might as well also we could do it
this way too come on
maybe there's another button okay
there's buttons everywhere
that's how you did it
[Music]
is
already the fourth dungeon right oh my
God I'm like
am I pretty far into the game or what
certainly feels like I am
damn maybe you tomorrow instead of story
I should do like a
Side Story and underground exploration
part
Maybe
uh
let's eat something
why did I eat that
damn it
[Music]
I still got a decent amount of main
story okay
that is gonna turn on
soon ah huh
it's already glowing
is there like a trigger
can I take off the cable now
but wait uh it's too early anyway huh
there it is okay
straight by the six came out oh the hell
did you go to Links here yeah
it's cute it's pineapple hairstyle
pineapple hairstyle yeah yeah
we started Amber inside the base really
oh [\h__\h] wait I should open these up more
often
why do I have a speedometer because I
don't like it when there's too many of
these idiots running around because it's
actually bothering me like there's just
too many and also sedan this is I don't
know
doesn't seem so helpful
wouldn't you look great but like for
real like ideally I'd only have one
running around sometimes I really only
have two and running running around
because like I I accidentally like
activate them when I don't wanna
hmm
it's kind of irritating
you know
now
oh I mean
I'm not I don't okay I can say that you
can use unable too but I want to say I'm
like wasting my sword that's what swords
are for and I made my my sword only with
a fire breath
LaSalle boss so I can recreate that
quickly also we never looked at the map
so far it was pretty like
you know easy to go for it without
looking at it but we went here
wait seven
uh okay good luck to me but we already
now wait we ended for the first floor
then we went to the B1
okay I don't know man
I don't even want to look at this
[Music]
so even when I throw the bloom seeds
it feels like
I can barely see anything
confusing Temple
one floor four rooms
what are you talking about
one for each hearing oh no way no way
that that's
what they're trying to do
oh
is that where I came from
yeah maybe
maybe it was
oh wow
let's go
sneeze
here we go
now we go to
first floor again I guess
huh
no
what are Zona is doing here now huh
oh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
ing
feet
because of a [\h__\h] vase
huh
the [\h__\h] man
nah that makes me mad nah nah that's not
cool
that's not cool
although it is quite comedic to hit
people with a vase right
I see that sometimes in like movies or
so
that's why I didn't look critical
comedic effect oh oh oh hello oh hello
uh
sorry sometimes I get confused
I will need a new what weapon right now
did you kill him no
you guys doing your thing I'm gonna make
a new weapon
for the zunai I don't want to use the
Ground Pounder
let's use
uh yeah let's use this one
[Music]
did I put it away
foreign
[Laughter]
was that my last fairy
I think so
[Music]
fast panicking
no
um question that I was wondering about
these meals do I have to drink them and
then
like
is it like a backup fairy once I drink
it or does it not have that Reviving
option at all
oh I could change my armor yeah perhaps
oh yeah because I didn't upgrade this
one it was really weak wait
are we really in a temple because I
don't remember touching something to
teleport inside
no revive
just normal food it doesn't even heal
that much
okay
can I wear this
oh yeah okay
it's just like sometimes there's sand I
was thinking so
um
well yeah but now I definitely have a
lot more defense
the healing varies
mine is really like weak look at that
seven hearts
[Music]
anyway
uh before we proceed actually let me um
let me make another Elemental weapon
before I run out of this one soon
um
so I was a fire or electricity right
um what about those little false
thingies where are they
oh
[Music]
Electric
and fire okay I'll do fire again
[Music]
and then
oh maybe the Gerudo Claymore wow
oh la la
oh I only have one electric oh yeah I
remember fighting these ones they were
really rough
okay
start a fire today I got some good
Elemental Weapons now
what am I lightning at
that thing up there
but
angle
wait
there we go
[Music]
makes me miss that bird girl from Wind
Waker
we did the stuff in the Wind Waker
dungeon
of light and stuff
oh
there it is I was just talking about it
wait what was that on
until was it not the dungeon yet
of course that was a dungeon
why does this thing appear so late
[Music]
I believe we'll also find whoever that
voice we've been hearing belongs to
laughs
for real for real
yeah real dance in the Starts Now
huh
hey the floor starts to rise then
slammed back down yeah I know
I know what what is this
foreign
[Music]
I heard the voice very clearly just now
it's calling to me
it's sad that I should use my power to
charge the four batteries
the monster we fought outside earlier
fled to the top of this Temple and the
voice that has been speaking to us said
the platform should be able to take us
all the way up there if that's true we
could Corner The Monster at the top we
might also figure out who's talking to
us and why
okay link we need to get to the very top
to start we should do what that voice
suggested and try to find these four
battery devices all game
and what about this thing is it gonna
like make us jump
all the way up what
but okay we have uh
um
can I move that
we have a very narrow building
[Music]
for that
really I don't deserve that
oh oh we get up pretty high
let me go here
and there's nothing to do here
wait let me go oh there's something for
a mirror
right that looks like it
let's go there
oh goodbye thanks for watching
[Music]
room up light and Flame
oh wait you have the mirror
no
she asked me are you okay no no I'm not
okay
I want to have some egg pudding
mirrors
all right thanks tooling for keeping
this one busy
but I'm good now what the [\h__\h] see this
is what happens it's annoying
I should just put him away I'm not using
him actively
sorry uh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
Uno bomb
I'll call you when I need you
[Music]
one
honey
why does it have to be a shield I just
want to carry it normally
[Music]
my fancy Shields I'm gonna get it back
afterwards maybe maybe
what where is the light coming from
anyway there's light here
you catch a vulture hand
can't do that
I don't think you can do that
that's what that like place in Tarrytown
is for to detach
these kind of things
[Music]
am I too early here
I thought the lights that would go to
the mirror would come from here
okay let's just
send for now
[Music]
oh it's one of the last rooms okay
do we kind of start from the top and
work our way down actually
yo these like
this uh
vases
so often link will spawn gems
[Music]
careful not to ascend it to the final
chamber
oh what happens do you immediately start
the boss fight Plus
no way
why you gotta be so careful with that oh
there's so many mirrors here
they're all aimed at different
directions
interesting
[Music]
you need you to start the battle okay
but wait up here is also nothing really
oh
maybe one lower
I need like one light source
to get this party started
oh there's something here maybe
not
does it make sense to
turn it like this
maybe the timing was kind of above
there we have it I like sauce
[Music]
oh
I have to stop the wheels properly too
but
that was long enough however can we
actually stop it though ah wait if we
just turn it
so that it's like at the same spot
would that help
does that make sense
mine that's not quite as good
yeah aligned
that kind of a line Yay
ah
okay so this is now always
send out the light hopefully
it no but it seems like it doesn't have
to
yeah because that one's already
activated anyway
okay then something opened up but I
didn't really notice what and where
[Music]
ah just here I guess
okay
always like this
why are you like this
see no problem
just gotta climb over there okay
she sees a problem immediately she's
like nope can't do it I'm are you sure
you want to be Queen
[\h__\h]
um
foreign
no problem here no problem at all can I
fit earlier
yeah
okay anyway
go ahead please
yeah I mean I mean you know she probably
couldn't have softness on her own but
that's what she has me here for by now
she should have figured out that I can
solve every issue
it's a given now
she should know
she should know better
wait um
I'm behind the shield how am I hitting
the shield
I guess I was just glitching through it
another mirror Shield maybe I didn't
have to take the other mirror Shield
maybe that was just like for fun because
here
princess Niche thank you here I see um
afraid to take normal mirror
well do we place it uh
it's like this
[Music]
but there's light coming from below no
wait do we have to open it up
button
oh
dear
huh okay
steaks do I stop it with the sticks
again Super Taco this time thank you
how is that strong enough damn
but did I do it at the wrong spot
I guess that has to be maybe fully
visible or
right I'm not sure what I'm doing I'm
just doing things without thinking too
much about it
uh
[Music]
stop moving
wait it's not visible at all now
should I bring can I bring the mirror
thing down
what
DP what are you what are you saying what
does DP mean
true
but now I need to find that mirror again
I am
stop moving in the floor
eventually
come to me there you go
okay first we activate that I suppose
foreign
[Music]
not quite correctly
wait does this still move when I
remove the stone
I guess we'll never know
because I can't get it out
oh
[Music]
you glitched one of the sticks and it
fell into the wall
it's charging is it
was charging for a moment now it is
[Music]
with the crop
fan
wowzers
okay
wait is that one ah
wait what
[Music]
I thought I thought I thought
that would be
ah wait did you just needs to activate
there's no
[Music]
okay
all right
why did we have to do the line today
uh it seems to have absorbed my life
lightning Wellness
now okay we did one I'm afraid
was that thing always there
yeah five hours
honestly today it feels longer to me
[Music]
um after I'm done with the temple
I'm probably gonna end it we don't want
to
you know over X
x uh what's the word
excelled
excerpt yeah
[Music]
okay where's next
this I'm guessing comes last two though
there's so many mirrors that are
supposed to
redirect the light
[Music]
that's where we just came from right
still
I know it's it's the the other thing no
no no
um
we'll have a little little stomach cramp
right now
oh oh it's getting bigger
oh it's like I'm pregnant oh
[Music]
oh it hurts a little bit oh
oh
[Music]
smoothie what what do you have like a
radar for my pain
did you hear her
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
holy
what do you call this like this women
Intuition or oh my God wait that's
that's worth another belly rub
[Music]
y you don't actually care and you're
coming for other reasons
[Music]
foreign
double intuition
hey baby ah
what
this movie
[Music]
and
came with me
hey Chill on the table
it's unbelievable but I
I want to say that you know she felt my
pain but there's no way that she can
arrive within like two seconds of me
feeling pain
when she was in a different room but
that's incredible that was the second
time in a row
I no I like I scream much more in like
streams sometimes right
often like when I'm like really panicked
at a boss fight I would occasionally
scream even more and then they don't
care
they can tell when I'm screaming from uh
pain in a game like the frustration and
and when it's like pain actually coming
from my body
I I would like to give them the credit
for that but I am not going that far yet
maybe if it happens a third time
hey my pain is gone again
[Laughter]
perfect she really gets my mind off of
it oh wait a second
doctor
how did I not see this before
foreign
[Music]
kind of people say that
maybe pets in general like dogs and cats
especially dogs because that's why they
train dogs to be
um
well what do you call them like service
dogs
right
that they have like a sense like a
feeling for it yeah yeah
it's absolutely incredible though
that a dog can like feel
when your heart for example is about to
do something weird
and they will alert you of it that's
that's insane
speaking of when I was at the airport
waiting for my luggage which took
forever apparently
um there was a drug dog running around
and the dog was so pretty
and he was smelling everybody
and I was hoping he would come to me
well
I guess I don't even look worth
inspecting
because the guy who was leading the dog
just completely like ignored me
and just went elsewhere like he went to
pretty much every person but not to me
man he knew I was straight edge
oh I wanted to kill doggone to sniff
snuff
looks so fluffy I mean I wouldn't I
wouldn't feel like I could pet the dog
anyway
because the dog's working and I don't
think you're supposed to pet them
like calm
calm yourself dog crazy people
just this once which one is the next I I
don't I don't know how to open that one
over there
top floor
I don't know what that tells me but
should I go to the top floor
yeah anyway
but even just having to toggle close to
me would have been nice
speaking of airports so after
uh I arrived
you know last time I went to America
I would also because you know I was with
the other girls so we often shared an
Uber and we always relied on Ubers
um but I think
I arrived alone
and I was
um back then I arrived alone so when I
was still alone
and I had no Wi-fi outside
I was like ah there's no way I can make
it
to our Airbnb
without Wi-Fi so I took a taxi or an
Uber or whatever it was I think it was a
normal taxi actually
yeah but it was really expensive and
this time I was like yes see I'm paying
for this trip to make a not so smart for
later business situation a decision to
create a music video so I need to save
costs wherever I can so I went only
inspect around the Torches
or it's joking
I went only with public transport this
time guys
I did not take
an Uber
there's no torch
pick up
[Music]
yo how did I do it Miss This
were you okay I was quite scared and
intimidated that's why I'm like even
prouder and I didn't have internet as as
soon as I would leave the airport I
didn't have internet
and like in Europe
you know we have this like law back like
a couple years ago it wasn't like this
yet but we have this law that was and
it's actually absolutely incredible that
every internet provider back in the day
for or every phone into the provider
back in the day where this wasn't in
place yet when you would leave your
country you would have to try like pay
extra for using your internet in other
countries and for European countries it
wasn't as expensive but it was
for
eign
it was for
um wait wait wait Brain Brain Brain I
can't do two things at once
it was definitely for outside of
European countries even more expensive
and and yeah anyway so then it was
[\h__\h] epic when uh European lawmakers
I guess I don't know who decided this
but it was decided that uh every
like phone company
has to adjust
and make it so that
if you have internet in Austria on your
phone you will have internet in every
European country
[Music]
on your phone
yeah only the EU that's what I mean
full guys when I traveled to Italy when
I travel to Greece everywhere I didn't
have to think of getting a SIM card or
whatever
yeah
I had free internet everywhere and I
have quite a good data plan so I would
never run out either
yeah it's so based it's so good I guess
I saw something about Apple but I don't
give a [\h__\h] I don't care I don't know
what the [\h__\h] is up with that I saw
people were happy though but yeah Europe
when Europe standards sizes some things
it's usually pretty awesome pretty
helpful sometimes sometimes there's good
things sometimes there's lots of good
things I guess I don't know yeah but so
I have that when I travel within Europe
but I don't have that when I travel in
America
and I don't know in in Japan I always
get myself a pocket Wi-Fi
uh because that's like pretty common
there for like foreigners to get like a
little pocket Wi-Fi it's like a little
device small thing that you turn on and
then you connect to it
um
um and in Korea they have that tooth so
I did the same thing in Korea I could
just arrive at the airport and without
reservation go to a counter and take one
of these
um and they're for rent they're not free
they're a little bit expensive I guess
yeah but I
I felt like I really needed it there
and then for America I was considering
like I was looking up you know
but all I could find is like SIM cards
and I don't really like the idea of
switching out my SIM card
it's annoying like if I have to like
open that tiny thing
and and then I need I need the the
needle or something which I usually
don't have with me so how am I gonna
open it
and and yeah I don't know it's annoying
I don't want to switch off my sim card
so I don't like the option of using a
SIM card normally you know
so this time I was like okay it's like
basically what three four nights of a
stay
and I will most of the time be at Emma's
place or close to Emma's place
so I'll surely be fine
and I've been there before
so I can do it
even if I'm alone so I went to public
transport beforehand I saved the the
route I took screenshots and everything
that even when my internet would be gone
I would be okay
and and the good thing is you know
sometimes my GPS on my Google Maps when
I don't have internet I don't know
what's supposed to be normal but
sometimes it shows me it updates me on
where I am and sometimes it doesn't when
I don't have internet
um
sometimes it shows me where I am and
sometimes it does but this time it did
so that was really my save here I could
see where I was going
in real time
like you know being on a train or
something I would know at which station
to get off but then there was also like
walking Parts you know and that's what I
was really scared of
yeah but it was okay it was all okay and
I made it safely it didn't I didn't miss
any connections
I was like very concerned that I was
very bored because I couldn't use the
Wi-Fi on my phone I was just staring
outside and staring on the ground
staring but trying to not stare at
people because maybe they would try to
rob me or or assassinate me who knows
you know I'm very scared
but yeah I made it yay both ways
back and forth mm-hmm
so proud of myself to travel alone
without internet through
public transport I mean okay I'm a
[\h__\h] adult and I've done that many
times
but in some for some reason in America
it always intimidated me
um
this is always intimidated me but
nothing weird happened except for like I
mean it's that happens in other
countries too but when I when I got out
of a train
station
um
some
some guy that looked something like
maybe homeless or just I don't know
[\h__\h] up
uh like started talking to me and like
ah how are you where are you going and
I'm like
nice weather right
I tried not answering but he was like
following me for a couple
meters
and I I didn't know if I should be
completely ignoring or if that would
make him mad and I don't know I I I said
some things but I I also
uh just really quickly I didn't I didn't
even look at his face I was like looking
very focused on my phone and like the
direction of where I should be going
So eventually he gave up ah Tommy
Tommy oh man I mean
ah
let's see if she comes
um
oh but maybe she just comes because I'm
like kind of quiet and you know she
always comes when I end the stream when
I get quiet
maybe that's what's happening
it's like a weird nauseous tummy horde
it's weird
oh
um
it's like
quite up high
on the top of my tummy
[Music]
you might really have a stomach virus
it's it's definitely gotten much better
but it's still there and this is the
third day
[Music]
it's Saturday night I can't go to a
doctor
I'm okay I need to go to a doctor for
something like that
as long as I'm not like
as terrible as I was
around Christmas
no today I haven't taken any medication
not even a painkiller I want to take a
pink and look at this today I took one
okay what the [\h__\h]
what am I doing here why are there too
where do I even bring the light I don't
see it like do I have to move the mirror
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
um
um oh I can't move it
uh I can only move it away wait a second
wait a second brain activated tangent
over
brain activated
no
where is this home
should be
my head
I'm being like here
yeah and then it goes over there
well we can adjust that later on
if you say if you set up the mirror in
the room so it always shines outside
um or maybe I can use this Stone as a
podest right
baby
yeah baby
oh
okay
do I need a second mirror no
I have one mirror attached to one of my
Shields so
okay
oh no
wait
oh that could push it
oh
wait just a bit more
ah oh
oh what is that
please don't open up the boss fight run
what is that is
I supposed to do this right now anyway
what if I want to activate
where does that go
the last one that I skipped
it's not okay just a button
it's all part of the dungeon okay okay
but what about that light
um
should I try to can I even
go
let's let's check out the button
[Music]
probably where the battery is
I don't think so
ah
what where would that go
okay oh okay
oh hello
oh my
God
she's like what are you doing uh
everything is according to kikaku
somebody pushed me some [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
push me must have been you Lisa
um I need you down here though
what detail
eh
wait what what what
a button a button
CJ you're just gonna jump now
oh you did what is this the dispenser
button or what because it didn't even
stop the fire
I'm so confused
[Music]
one more
foreign
[Music]
Oh you mean she came from this store it
looked like she dropped down from the
top
oh
okay
now we're here now
which one is the last one let me see
third floor
[Music]
wait is that the first one oh
like that
[Music]
and here's the photo okay
uh
[Music]
what now now I'm before Florida ah
confusing
and but where's that opening
[Music]
you notice my different hairstyle oh
I've had that one for a while
thank you
[Music]
you're supposed to be a path
away
ah is that where that last mirror goes
okay okay okay
now that I know where it's supposed to
go
[Music]
I feel like I can aim it there
more or less
and it doesn't have to be permanently
right it just has to be
for a while so let me try to maybe
[Music]
can I
can't do it wait wait wait wait wait
wait does that one
does that work
this one
oh yeah oh yeah
huh
I've still gotta move the last one
it's almost there
[Music]
right here
okay cool
[Music]
very
satisfying indeed
[Music]
you know I felt like
um
last trip to Japan I bonded with gura a
lot right
this trip even though
like so many enemies even though it was
a pretty short time
oh yeah
wait
I shot
ah okay
I'm using this thing now
even though it was a really short time I
feel like I've bonded quite well with
almond
yeah
like
we didn't do much in terms of like
besides work that's true
but the work you know that we do
together also last time when I was
recording my pretty birthday stuff for
last year
I feel like you know that kind of
connects us
and we Bond through that till
and this time too like this time it was
only us too so
it was like focused even more on our
only our interactions you know I I
offered enough to come true I like told
her the dates and everything and what
we're doing
um I think it didn't work out for her
because maybe no time I don't know which
is totally fine it's like uh
thanks to that
I got a lot of alone time with that man
so wait am I is it are they spawning
forever
or is there an end to this
ah okay
[Music]
I was immersed in my story
yeah lots of solo bonding with Ahmed and
I really appreciated that like
as I said we were like planning on doing
some more things but I was actually
robbed up one day
by one of my flights
delayed
[Music]
um and I lost the whole day because of
that on an already short trip yeah
uh-huh
yeah
and yeah that was one thing and then you
know the other uh
stream not really working out robbing us
of like half a day
so I was planning originally for some
more like you know chill non-stream time
um but that was oops
unfortunately not quite possible
but but yeah
even then like you know when she was
baking cookies and I was like sitting
there waiting for her we were talking
and talking and talking the whole time
about all kinds of things
opinions and thoughts and recent
uh developments and all kinds of things
and and that was very even even things
like that are very
um
valuable to me
yeah private girl talk well not
necessarily girl talk but definitely
private talk
[Music]
so I don't know about almond but I felt
like you know we had some good bonding
time why is that in there
what are you doing what so you're like
trying to mess with my brain
yo I really really
on that was the problem of breaking the
pot I've really really loved ama's um
whole like PC
area she changed it quite a bit
compared to last time when I was there
she changed it like everything I was
like yeah this is so
is staring at everything it was like
also aesthetically pleasing
also cute
I'm like what the hell amen like just
this area you focus all your your
cuteness on what's going on
[Music]
I just wanted to enter dad
like everything else was like pretty
normal you know and then just her PC
area everything's like aesthetic and and
I don't know
artistic and pretty and and color coded
everything's like one color
I'm so pretty so cute so much like cute
stuff ah what's going on
back to the game amazing theater girls
knew you were coming no no no no no no
no no she did that before already just
on her own
what are we doing here
oh wait a minute
I mean there's balloons here for a
reason
right
and there's
these platforms
let me check out what's up there
why can't I move these
um
I'm gonna try the center
and multiple ways to do this puzzle okay
let me get an overview
I thought so I thought that that's where
the light goes not a little
ah easy you could probably do it with
the uh
is there a reason there for like weight
reasons that there needs to be
pots in there I don't care
we're not doing it with pots
no
hello
what
huh
someone explained what's going on there
to me
why why I was closer to that one and
couldn't even move it
am I going crazy right now
they were both the same range originally
uh Heights
anyway whatever
I don't care it's not affecting me at
all
now
uh
[Music]
wait it's not even um
no wait what
[Music]
okay wait what flipping
wow
this is using my batteries
[\h__\h] help I need time to solve this
okay but this is not high enough anyway
[Music]
is it just gonna drop it
balloon is easier
I don't want to use the balloon
why can I
knock you
oh come on he's [\h__\h] pissing me off
now
ah
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
what how do you do it with balloons
don't they go up too high but maybe
that's fine if I attach it to the bottom
of the balloon
I don't know
ah
does it need the pots though
why is there so many
is it because like once you send it up
then it's like too late
and you won't be able to reach it to get
it down anymore or what
I don't know
it's a hint like put as many as possible
there so that the player gets it that
you should use
these
so
it just goes up completely straight
then you would think
that that's
[Music]
there's torches here somebody said use
torches but look
can I
place the torch inside
there's fire
foreign
[Music]
does this work
ah
why why
[Music]
I put it completely straight but it kind
of turned didn't it
[Music]
my weight
you calling me fat
follow me back
[Music]
but it's pretty straight again
next time I'll just stand right behind
it I guess
instead of on the side of it
now it has no fire
oh behind behind behind behind behind
behind
but then doesn't it go even higher like
too high how do I stop it from going too
high
was it enough it's enough okay I thought
it would like already pass it
okay
[Music]
ah wait ah I want the um the faces okay
you're late
[Music]
Dazzle front works but you need a pawn
to go off
for the mirrors they're good yeah
[Music]
she talks so much nice
we did it last
but not least we do the boss side now
is this activated I'm kind of scared
when
um I'm Legit scared so let me prepare
some more weapons
like if I need more Elemental ones
because the other ones already this
one's already breaking
how about an ice one
I just want to make sure that I have all
the weapons that I couldn't eat before
we go into it so we have a little bit
left of fire and we have the electrical
one and we have this one I'm gonna drop
this no trash please
should be
okay and then let's heal up
coming
something
hello
anything lower than that
oh maybe this
does it it doesn't go down during cut
scenes right let me let me eat it right
away when it starts
eh Elemental sword or spare well I think
I have one
oh
yeah I made a lot of food I would have
liked it Mike even more but it stopped
me because it says full inventory yeah
link I think this platform is about to
move what did you feel it with a sense
like smoothie woman intuition huh
was the voice in your head that's
telling you that
I was thinking I should be able to
make the food inventory bigger with the
cutoff
extensions
something's shining over there
I'm scared
oh it doesn't start yet I know though
um
okay
uh
I sit here but what
oh no we don't we just wait for those to
start ah
huh oh
there's light sources up there
[Music]
I mean is that ready to be shot already
I guess it's pink enough
hi welcome back
Queen
Queen let's go no link yes
I can and there's like a funny thing
with the fingers okay he and comfy on
tonight
[Music]
um
uh yeah I was gonna heal myself let's
see what was that
oh
I don't know where that thing is
yeah my weapon is too slow
oh and like they break so easy holy [\h__\h]
can I just shoot him again
where am I supposed to fly up with those
I still don't really know
I think he did that when we were outside
and I was like
I can't I can't oh
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
okay they do hurt me now we know
I didn't jump back but um
[Music]
anything oh
oh
I mean it doesn't have to be Elemental
now so
I just front to look at if I was gonna
do the jump thing ah tummy horse
no no I'm not okay let's just keep on
repeating it is it not gonna send out
the the ketones by the way I thought
they were gonna spend like a spawn like
a lot of give those
guess not
stop that from happening
[Music]
did we hit him
I need you
halfway through I think
okay
oh now now you're calling your little
babies
I knew you would have to you okay
they are fast oh
why not
[Music]
um well who do we shoot wait
wait
ah
[Music]
yeah okay I got one down
chaos chaos but maybe I should get out
uh my other buddies to help me now I
suppose
because Tunes already shooting
[Music]
um
literally
[Music]
but it works too
he died
okay you got it ah wait ah get me out of
this mess
let me destroy all them first and then
I'll think about what to do with the
light it's like oh that's going on
[Laughter]
they're breaking I should have made more
I thought I would be okay
oh okay okay okay okay I mean what is
that what
okay okay
isn't this kind of overwhelming
oh when
wait that was uh in some way genius
let's wait
the whole time I have no idea what the
queen is doing oh oh oh oh oh oh that's
what she was doing
oh [\h__\h] no don't get in the way
you need
me
let's go one more
[Applause]
okay okay okay okay
I take care of some of these because
they're annoying oh wait I have one more
electric Reaper
okay uh now lines
do they just assume that I have a light
Shield or
or what
because I I mean I do
but
I don't even know how to aim and
probably I
I don't even know how to aim it properly
in terms of stand on it so they come to
me okay
[Music]
okay
but what about the queen
ah
I find it very difficult to aim with
this like
maybe I'm doing it wrong
[Music]
oh
my God
I can't I can't am
we were thinking it and what the [\h__\h] is
the light for just like a nice little
extra
ah [\h__\h]
Let's Get Closer on YouTube
closer ah give some Spanish
oh you just walk into the light on its
own nah what's behind right
not one I wanted but didn't get it
actually it was on fire was that still
from before what is it doing
did that even do anything
[Music]
oh
how do you dance that I always jump
hmm
[Music]
what should I eat
uh
I'm not okay okay
no
[\h__\h] it's got to learn
[Music]
the queen game though
where's the two
okay
okay this time this time
don't
coin right here
got it but it doesn't even it doesn't
even feel like it's doing that much
damage does it
foreign
I was like riding on top of it
okay
um I'm cleaning up my my fridge tonight
it looks like it
oh okay
here we go
all the food is expiring soon so it's
time to have at least a mukbang
yay Temple finished box finished fourth
um assistant
ghetto that's it
wow
your phone will actually helped me in
that moment a lot
oh yeah
we're gonna be told the same information
a fourth time
but we have a different voice over
hot container
[Music]
yeah she said something during the space
that's why I reacted to it
she was like everything that I used was
fine it's totally edible I ate it too
after all
you know
oh wait sorry I'm not taking it you're
taking it sorry I did you go ahead
I thought it was mine
that was creepy
oh
yeah
it's like a ghost
oh
these are stemmer pastors
video chemist s
I don't even see her face and I still
think it's pretty the earrings
mysterian oh wait so she's also gonna
wear it on her ear
s
[Music]
yeah sure I haven't heard that before
ever tell me tell me I'm very curious
outside
foreign
it's eight
because
we only have four
inspired
um
I never wait did I know
he has it on his forehead
um
noticed it on his forehead
foreign
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
my personal
um
foreign
[Music]
in English it was just a you know
it is
of course it is
obviously
you have to plot armor
[Music]
um
whoa
I'm speaking highly and not German yeah
yeah
hylene is just another word for German
whoa
that is so cool I want that as
merchandise for ladies or boys
[Music]
oh hot
oh wait does it happen instantly now as
as a ghost or do I still have to like
charge it again
[Music]
so [\h__\h] cool
foreign
[Music]
we cleared all the four um problems with
this too
whoa I wonder
what
PIRA will say
medicine
[Music]
oh I found the ring finger hello
isn't it on the special hand is is the
ring finger I think should be on the
left hand right wasn't it his right hand
I don't even know
oh Zelda didn't get that finger damn
damn
was it his his right hand right
depends on the handedness
really so if I'm left-handed it will be
opposite for me
really they adjust
[Music]
oh
always on the left
[Music]
the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
ing
thank you
[Music]
whoa that water was pretty
[Laughter]
um
[\h__\h] huh
[Music]
I don't sound like a goat no
wait ninja did you get smaller again
you're so tiny did you I hope you didn't
stop growing right you would be so tiny
compared to only your guards
but right now your perfect size for link
a link I'm grateful to you for helping
me save the Gerudo I've received reports
that ever since the sandshred dissipated
gypto attacks uh have almost entirely
stopped oh
it will no doubt take some time to
rebuild but it is thanks to your help
that we can live on the surface again
on behalf on behalf of all the Garuda
people thank you
oh
I'm sorry to say though that despite the
safety of Gerudo town no longer being a
prison concern we still haven't been
able to uncover any information on the
whereabouts of Princess Ella's useless
actually well actually bully Arrow I do
have a small piece of information
regarding Zelda I experienced a vision
when I took the secret Stone in my hand
the person that my ancestor referred to
as the stage of time looked identical to
Zelda
someone who just happens to look like
Zelda that doesn't explain everything
that's been going on
but it's impossible to deny that someone
resembling Zelda has been spotted across
Hyrule and that terrible events follow
her
the salad we know and the Zelda we saw
in the vision of the distant past are
incredibly similar if the Zelda in the
past is our salad and who is this other
person we must uncover her true identity
I'm sorry link although the threat of
the sand shroud and to keep those has
passed I cannot leave Garuda town at the
moment things need some time to settle
however we will take on the task of
searching this area for any signs of
Zelda
they all say that and I wonder if any of
these four people
will eventually have any information for
me or if it's just all on me
left hand is for marriage because it is
said to the closest to the heart ah
that makes sense yeah
do you guys want me to draw Liza hell
yeah
do it
I get an interesting encounter now for
the story
okay
ah yeah yeah now we will have some
Gerudo in the
the headquarters yeah
and with my newfound power assh I will
still be able to support you I swear
that I will do anything I can to help
[Music]
me wow
wow wow wow
link you said you had already visited
retail Village Goran City and Zora's
domain I'm sure Lookout Landing would
value any information you could share
why not go there and see if you can help
I hope your travels bring you back here
again link I look forward to such a
reunion
[Music]
I like how she's just like leaning there
chilling just like in breath of the wild
I feel like she had the same stance
you
all right
um
six hours
oh I started late today so it's almost
midnight
um whoa
hi juicy looking meat well overheated
body what is this the in
[Music]
nice they're selling everything outside
now
um but
wait do you have wheat I actually need
weight
[Music]
I ran out of wheat
I'll take them all
tell me when you got more
um I want to what's our next um
[Music]
what's our next memory that we need to
get
down here you shouldn't touch that thing
on until you check it oh okay well not
now
that seems like a quest for a quest and
the Quest for of course the dagger one
I have uh damn I already saw so many
on the map at least uh
dagger
daggers
I wanna watch a memory
before we ended and then tomorrow we
might not do so much story because I
want to focus on doing some you know
side stuff you know no need to rush
because we're already so far already
um ah bottom right for the dagger
damn
so really next
yeah the standing person we saw
okay
and then it's the ah I also know the
location of the next one because I have
a shrine activated there I think
okay
uh oopsie bottom right
wait I don't have that map
I was like I don't know maybe on the
tail here
I wanna see it I wanna get there launch
from the tower this one maybe or that
one maybe that one's better actually oh
wait it's a shrine what am I saying
that one
um
I think the tower is probably here
that's why I marked it
so
we'll go to the next Tower and then from
that Tower maybe we can glinder from the
lab you think so
we can go to the lab
I would recommend to what left until the
end
leave until the end but I saw in the
chat everybody's saying that I'm like
missing so much information from the
memories
so I'm like yeah I want to watch at
least one
oh
ah
okay maybe a sky island really
I only have that one
can I see the tower from here
what is that
and I already like it doesn't look so
far is that the tower
uh I think
[Music]
oh that is the Tower
and I did already mark it
um okay red and green
should we go to Tower
or to the memory
be easier to find the memory with the
tower in theory you would think so
at least
our quite far skip the tower
well
um
okay
let's see how far we get
um
I think I'll do more climbing and
running
because I'm already sinking so much
um
I'll take a speed boost because I made
some speed boosts
go
let's wear climbing armor
we'll be there in a minute guys
trust me I know all the shortcuts
horses that climb mountain mountains I
don't think so
what
oh
there's a crack
nice I I'm like so bad at finding them
and the bring me to my friend kuroks I
never do them
because I'm like
don't bother me with this now it's like
ah they're so annoying you know
wait a second I don't see anything huh
foreign
I marked some of them on the map like
just in case I
[Music]
just in case I've like really
desperately need some products [\h__\h] my
speed post has been
big
[Music]
what
don't fall down
[Music]
hey
what
[\h__\h]
I don't know ah
whatever I don't know number 10.
I don't want to lace my speed boost
what time she says
what are you wearing
what
[Music]
okay that's a silver run oh you see
where dangerous I was making out of
color I haven't seen it before
oh okay but it looks so nice with the
flower on his head
okay
we will go straight to the memory
is that for Kodak
it must be I'm right nearby are probably
down there
I can feel it
um
any better to go that way
it's for the membership and the super
tab thank you
blah blah blah
silver liners hit harder than Ganon oh
my God
oh we all know
gallon is a [\h__\h] weak ass [\h__\h]
in every game
we guess mofo
we all knew that
um I don't even know where exactly it is
but I'm hoping that it's kind of where I
put my mark oh God okay I thought there
was a Lino I thought it was a Lino
it could be anywhere
cause like he was he's on the horse and
he was like in the middle of a field
alone oh you want to fight you want to
fight little bastard
foreign
[Music]
ah because it's a dagger and it's like
shaped like that tail yeah
[Music]
that's easy to find thank God
what a bunny oh it's a bunny
for a cave
um
maybe let's quickly do the cave
get like less rupees if you shoot them
like this because I often feel like
that's the case
yeah
oh there it goes
okay
I killed it too early oh what
okay where's the cave
I feel like it was going that direction
ah
it's probably there in the water
where my drop is from the enemy what
would be 100 random
man I always feel like I get nothing
yeah
oh it's not dead
I don't know
okay we're gonna do this really quickly
because otherwise I'm gonna forget about
this cave and never come back to this
corner of this world
it dries off can you do this
oh I should just cut it all right you
can cut it
all right
foreign
I need to make more weapons I have so
many
um
combined ones
let's do a charge come on
never do that let's go
[Music]
gnarled long sticky never used that
before
this grinnald weapons
in
[Music]
royal blue
I think that's the first
Limited
oh is there Shrine in here
a bigger cave sometimes they have
shrines
no
the big boys okay
[Music]
um
you know the the fire ones you can
easily counter with ice any other way
around but what do you counter the
electric ones with water
no what do you what what could I counter
it with water really
I don't know about this
how about electricity
or did I charge you back up
huh
oh wait
um
what else is this
I have one down
oh
what's he doing
damn
good job beautiful
frenick well Anita I already have one
and my other my little eyeball also
zooms
that's unfortunate I feel like so
unsatisfied when I can't take the thing
they give to me
long fro
for
uh for like a
Tana type of weapon
I don't want to throw that
no I didn't attempt I'm not a newbie to
Zelda games I know what happens when you
attack
such a foolish thing it's not gonna
happen to me
um
they're making it extra difficult huh to
reach out there because it's like always
raining in the cave basically
thank you
oh boy wait maybe for the first time
I would have to cook
myself a sticky medicine
I've never done that before
I'm finally doing it but
um
a sand but there's
our platform I can put there no
there's water
maybe I can stand over there
I found a good spot all right I can
freeze the water I forgot about that
yo I feel like features like that
yeah they may introduce it to you like
the lava one they introduce you more to
the ice like putting ice
on water I don't know if I've even been
properly introduced to that feature or
if I just saw it on Don tando's video
but it's like not so what is this Stone
it's not so ingrained in my grain yet
you know
[Applause]
ow
does this one need bombs by any HMS
it doesn't really work always ah still
the first time yeah first time probably
did need a bomb
strong Fusion
but it's already breaking it's not worth
it
thank you
I could have rewinded it too really
[Music]
wait what plus nine
six
um
[Music]
that like like you know basically
it reminds me of
when I put on one of my mud masks on my
face
that's how my skin would look like
after a while
and then wash it off and underneath
it's beautiful
oh well I mean that's exaggerated not so
beautiful
you know
put them before
why do I let myself get hit so many
times what the last one immediately you
showed me
oh man
another one quick shot
oh did my bow break so I could the Zone
eyeball did it break
a really strong one damn it I shouldn't
have used it so much
[Music]
it's entering the shrine with
religious electricity
enchanted diamond mining pickup
rewatch run
I mean yeah I did I did some things to
reach here but
okay
I mean
not gonna turn it down I do appreciate
it saves me some time
and brain energy because like I I I I
don't know if I would have been able to
do a difficult trend
quite well right now
hmm
[Music]
yeah four again we did four today I feel
like we barely did any shrines today but
it seems like we did
thanks for the heel
being sick sucks I don't really feel
sick anymore just like yeah throughout
today
I felt I really
[\h__\h] when I was going outside to the
pet store as I said
the pet food store
but
when I I'm just inside and
sitting I'm mostly good as long like
sometimes I get these
smaller cramps still
but yeah I'm good I'm good
I perk up once I start streaming
not when I'm really sick no
that's just
[Music]
I'm not using any of these shields
oh
you guys ever lose your Shields because
mine are like with me forever
on this way right because I didn't go
there yet
[Music]
interesting
it goes them when you fight lionels
oh okay
800 hits for the highlands build really
Sapphire
[Music]
is that an opening
wait if this is a cave did we already
find the Frog
I don't remember finding the Frog but we
found a shrine
no
maybe this is so
no way ah wait here
[Music]
yeah oh yeah
that was so hard to see you know
[Music]
there's some things I shouldn't be
seeing
[Music]
me
it was a big frog ah no fortune was the
Frog for a moment
sorry you a bird
what the [\h__\h] okay a frog hello
so you can make a better version what
crafting or what
look up there was nothing there
you made me
and there's nothing here
yeah
you you made me doubt myself
oh there's like weapons stuck in here
too
one guy yeah but rad usually use
trustworthy at least when it comes to
Fire Emblem
hey maybe
that's not it's not unbreakable amount
[Music]
is that what you meant rad
ew
[Applause]
don't don't hate him in theory look I
can't really get up from here easily you
probably have to ascend from over there
red red did you know what did you just
say like oh look up maybe there's
something there if you're new
or if you didn't you either way
your honor is intact
foreign
[Music]
Funky Monkey no
no I have to go down
because that was a rare one that I don't
fight so often
If Only They would keep their ability to
pick up items that like fall far away
from you
because
um when they're not ghosts yet they do
do that
all right
rewind it
but then I have to rewind each single
thing hell no
foreign
wait that's the way out
why why did I miss the Frog
tomato
oh golden why is it up there
I don't want to throw a bomb it's gonna
fall everywhere
can I somehow
get it
from here
maybe if I throw my rock hammer right
oh oh what
you're joking right one Ruby
wasn't that a golden one
what what
wasn't there
wasn't that a golden
Corral
good job I know man I don't know
[Music]
what a shitty RNG I have
whoa
I went from here to here
but I wanted to go here
damn we backtracked not really we moved
back I don't know what is this this
place is kind of special
but I missed the Frog I have to go back
anyway
but but wow pretty
[Applause]
okay
wait how do we fight these again oh you
climb up in the middle oh hit them and
then that's a simple one wait
foreign
[Music]
does this work
maybe otherwise I have to go down and
refuse something I think I saw some
Stones let me try it I ah
I don't even it's like
what
something to fuel
I don't see anything maybe I'll just use
bombs only
works
oh I did hit him well
ah
[Music]
the position oh
it's broken it's broken
please
[Applause]
I ran out of normal food hmm
so I should get them later wait there's
no stone that I can
oh
is he focusing on
my my partners oh nice tree
ice cream
and some spam bombs now
there's no damage okay
[Music]
what could I you maybe that one that one
would probably work right
I kind of want to use it on a [\h__\h]
Palace
[Music]
good Mount why yeah yeah let's go
oh
that's pretty fast at the end
can you not
and now our problem is solved
in terms of
can I possibly mine with
because we now have the Luminous
luminous
that one wasn't luminous at all but I
guess because he wasn't in a cave
it wasn't luminous because of that way I
saw like some Amber chilling
in the ponds did I already pick that up
I don't want to waste anything
I guess I picked up everything
I feel like it was kind of like
scattered all over
but okay so that was that
doing a bit more than just getting the
memory at this point
this is typical
zelding where the [\h__\h] is that dog
foreign
did I yeah I went up there and that was
a shrine
there was a shrine there
where is the frog has someone been in
this cave before
was it in the beginning
like normally
would be
um
like more in the middle
[Music]
the Santa I thought my sensors only for
shrines I thought I can't even change it
yet like maybe they still need to teach
me how to change it
just what I assumed
the fact that I didn't mind those my
mind those two things
confuses me
normally I mind everything
and now I'm in the beginning of the cave
how
it's not the first time that I just
cannot find the Frog of okay
yeah I have to upgrade it for a snow
anyway where the [\h__\h] is this frog
[Music]
where
where are
here
that was hard to see
a little [\h__\h]
actually you deserve a bomb but you know
what by accident
[Music]
finally
okay
time to go to the memory for real for
real for real for real for real for real
and then I'll rest
oh my God
let's go I wonder what this memory will
bring for me
by the way tomorrow I want to start
earlier than today
oh
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
but we'll see how it goes I mean I'm
pretty sure I'll start earlier than
today like
at the latest 4pm
and um
as I said less story more exploring and
adventuring a little bit of a loose do
whatever
I want to do kind of part
and
yeah
and I will make a schedule for next
month
a week
wait this place there's nothing to
really look up from high up there
Brewing
spawning bananas
oh my God wait what was that what's that
I can't read
Lauren Village
is that where it is I just have to burn
this
looks like it
my eyes me too it's even brighter on my
screen I think than on my other screen
oh
it's even brighter than on my screen
than my other screen whatever makes no
sense thank you one banana oh wait you
want my banana
I guess you're a monkey
I'll give you banana
is that a carrot
no way
no is that an octurer what is that
foreign
[Music]
that looks so weird the vegetation here
is so different
it was nothing when it had like a weird
like start like bottom part you know
what I mean
cool stuff you can get here though
bananas
find no bunion this banana tree
this is banana tree right
see it doesn't that look so weird wait
look look look look look look look
is like a banana tree starting to grow
oh yeah it looks like it
it just pushed it very deep into the
ground
see you guys
I have so many bombs these days you can
have
purple
I'm a kid what's that car
what is blue
blue
my sunset
I wanna go on the beach Paradise
location look at that my God
that is just torture
[Music]
foreign
did I run away
oh
wait is that
what what was this was this color thing
this stuff is so crazy
I thought that it was showing me the
the puddle
no
I guess it's probably somewhere at the
tip
probably
this one's hard to find
whoa
[\h__\h] you probably can't kill those one
hit I'm pretty sure
but I wanna kill it
sorry dude
is he dead yeah
yeah let's see what meat you give me
already
because I set it on fire
um I would have liked it raw to be
honest but okay
so cook it into something
um
banana
I was so excited about the banana
[Music]
oh run away
for what the [\h__\h]
they look like Pokemon they look like
they have um
uh punching gloves on
they really don't but they look like
Pokemon
yeah that's so cute yeah
no didn't you also say this last time
it's for every time
oh
don't tell me it's not at the tip and
all I'm being
[Music]
I mean
you can't swim
push the white one okay I'll see what I
can do or you know what could be funny
oh
hahaha
pull it the white one into the water
oh wait I stop moving you can't even see
my happiness
diabolical
I just want to watch this
but they don't really do much damage huh
should I join them wait this is the one
in the water
foreign
[Music]
this looks like the Pikmin I think
where are you going
oh are they like he's throwing something
at me doing like a cremation
[Music]
um
not so bad not so bad not so bad just
[Music]
okay
look at that
you just changed his Focus
[Music]
all right yo it takes a lot of damage
ah
um
[Music]
did it break in my weapon yeah I
couldn't even oh God don't blame it
take the [\h__\h] weapon rip
no ocean
was about to
throw him at him okay nice oh
I got a lot of stuff on it
look like that
oh man
because I already started the app and it
kind of resets what I look like and it's
kind of bugging out right now
no I'm not moving I'm [\h__\h] hell you
know
I regret
praising you because you're in the way
YouTube
don't look at me guysukashi
behind them my head is so busy
no I can't wait let me get rid of this
keyless
kill us
better
okay
I hear
sparkly shiny light
what
what's that
is it a weapon noise
confused me
confusarino
okay turns out the memory I stopped
moving again something's happening right
now uh but
turns out the memories not at the tip
the freaking bamboozled
where is it
oh when the weapon has an effect oh
my head naked that's okay
that's okay sometimes
the product was a cook
was it close by
I don't know how I would make that
assumption because that's not always the
case
often the code up is like very far away
but maybe the color of this one on one
side of the handle of the dagger because
I assume that was the handle or so
and then the memories on the other side
of the
handle
okay
I would take another speed boost but
we're ending it right after so
whatever
come on Wawa
do me the favor and move
like that I'm on the moon Jagger
[Music]
well there should go thank you
it's difficult when you can see it from
the top
oh
finally and I went all the way to the
tip and you guys didn't say go back
man
[Music]
wait tomorrow's Sunday what am I gonna
eat for breakfast
foreign
[Music]
I need like a third thing oh well anyway
Focus
Ed third time
the world is then
dank or cone again
[Music]
was creepy oh yeah
oh [\h__\h] foreign
what did I miss something
did I not watch one memory before that
oh it's the river okay okay
oh
imposters
is that a thing he does oh [\h__\h] what
no
hey what the [\h__\h]
oh
that's where he gets the tears
[Applause]
[Laughter]
laughs
but is she dead
hopefully not oh my God
damn
wait are you guys saying what the [\h__\h]
is it with that face about me or about
his face because I was laughing the
first second because of his face
and then because of his laugh
and then because like it matched so well
with my face both his face mostly his
face huh
yeah it was kind of crazy
yeah
yeah that was definitely worth watching
it was short but okay did Ganon always
have this
puppeteering though cause [\h__\h] else
you're fired
because I I won't recall him being a
puppeteer
yeah really did I see it in any other
games I played
go away
go away go away
um
and when do I fight a big puppet
[Music]
he had a puppet
really what's she looks ridiculous
I feel like maybe I remember from like
uh one of the DS games that I saw I'm
using puppets actually
am I crazy
damn there's so many bananas here
what why
A Link to the Past
or horsies
uh
don't go into the village
I mean a sad Village over there and it
wasn't a village so what do you know
what do they mean is which part is the
village
oh it said Village when I was here okay
that's it wait why is it like what's
what's at the village
just an enemy Village or is there
something creepy going on
don't go in okay okay
because they're gonna lure me into the
Laura Lynn what no
it's not even what it says
is is its own right side quest ah okay
I'll kill again
okay okay
and I'm curious about the other stories
um
I want to watch the next one
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm going to do it tomorrow
when I want to do them now
[Music]
the Canon one yes
yeah I think I have
a teleportation point there oopsie
all right yes
see this one's fast
I I can go there immediately
nothing speaks against it
right
oh [\h__\h] it's 20 minutes past [\h__\h]
midnight how
how is that possible
good
um
there's a lot of tear-shaped Tears
on this one
there's a tear there's a tear
everywhere theater old MacDonald had a
farm
e-i-e-i-o it's probably on the other
side
hmm
there's a dragon here and a chicken
there
you're an elk hair Fox
everywhere
crack
I'm gonna [\h__\h] you up
if you don't leave me alone
yeah
you rode your horse around here
well but I don't have it right now
I promised my viewers that this one
would be quick
that's kind of sussy that the stone is
there
was there two products
here yeah wait we can fly up with this
thing and maybe see it better
foreign
[Music]
here it is
and that one's like so Random it makes
no sense it doesn't like feel like oh
that's where it should be
okay
there's somebody in the chat say that
this one will have a spoiler what does
that even mean like how can it be a
spoiler
am I not supposed to watch it because
something in the store oh
it doesn't okay
if I watch it out of order this one's a
late one
you can't I mean yeah it was fine it was
fun
I'm fine the old tears are some wood
spoilers
they have to assume that people that
really
curious and want to watch everything
immediately
there he goes
and place oh
and please
oh it turned dark
oh
what
the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs
in my name is
oh she looks so scared
oh is that where the miasma [\h__\h] starts
whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh
[Music]
so much power all the black ones
whoa
oh this hair grew too
it looks more like that zombie
oh there you go
sheesh
ah
wait that's the pass that's the first
time ever that there were these kind of
mobs on Hyrule
that's like where he spawns them
oh
yeah
because that's the first Blood Moon
[Music]
is she dead though
near me
oh
[Music]
his third eye opens
what hops
oh teleportation I guess I can do that
too with my parents sure true mm-hmm
very interesting
this one's so much longer than the other
ones
[Laughter]
[Music]
when in trouble just fast travel
and no more trouble fast trouble trouble
solution
how that connects a Skyward Sword this
is an interesting thing to think about I
guess
but Zelda timelines are
at this point just troll
lines
no more timelines there's only troll
ones there's no such thing as timelines
anymore
oh
what Japanese way of doing it is to have
it all make absolutely no sense first we
give you the hope of having a connected
story and then then we [\h__\h] you up
just to trigger you
yeah it's okay though I mean I think
it's good to enjoy this as its own story
but I was just you know I feel like it
this game did give you hopes right to be
like connected to Skyward Sword because
there's so so much happens in the sky
and I felt like there were other
references to
you know like the the workers in the
underground
um those statues they look like the the
workers from Skyward Sword um
stuff like that like this references so
are you teasing me with that what the
funk
or teasing us
um
yeah the moment
no
[Music]
free if if he shows up I mean I'm gonna
[\h__\h] lose it
we cannot show up no
anyway uh I had a mug mom is that the
German name
we are moles the mole people mugma
that's also the English name right
seven hours OMG that's just normal here
ah
[Music]
that was certainly
a lot of fun
and a lot of good progress
um I wasn't planning on streaming
for too long today
but oh well seven and a half hours it's
like
a decent stream
yeah thank you guys for watching today
and welcoming me back to Austria
I'm so sorry about you know getting sick
I was so pissed off to you you guys know
how much like pressure
I put myself under to stream regularly
and when something like
illness that I can't do anything about
comes in between makes me really mad but
I I didn't feel
like too bad this time because like I
feel like I gave you guys plenty of
really fun content during my
um stay in America and I I used every
single of those few days that I had when
I already lost one I used every moment I
could
ah
even though we had lots to do and like
for that for the dancing stream I also
like I I had to practice a lot for that
one too because I had to remember
um all the choreographies and also I had
to record I had to record because I'm
not allowed to use the original audio so
I had to record everything I couldn't do
it beforehand so I had to do it in
almonds place you know
um it was actually like a lot of
preparation for that as well and
generally all the 3D stuff always takes
preparation
with like setting everything up
there's a lot of work but I I I'm happy
that you guys enjoyed every single
stream so much I'm glad every single
stream turned out to be a hit
yeah I was very happy and I think Amber
was very happy too
um
it was a good time
definitely
yeah uh tomorrow look out for
um uh what what time is it uh jst like
eight nine or so
uh Louis is Channel
2 p.m CEST 9 pm jst
um
7am CST apparently 8 A.M EDT apparently
4 a.m PST so you might want to stay
awake maybe I don't know you can also
watch the archive
um yeah but it's gonna be the first time
that holder Tony performs together in 3D
so that's pretty [\h__\h] hype
yay
yeah
you'll see me there and then afterwards
we'll have a stream but I think I'll
wait again to put up the reservation
until tomorrow okay
I sleep first I suppose or should I I
probably should put it up though because
it's already past midnight
hey okay I'll do it now okay okay
hi I already changed my mind
[Music]
okay yeah
yeah yeah yeah
why do I have free DMs
one from Jen Ma
[Music]
[\h__\h] keyboard where's the
ah
hi smoothie
[Music]
for real
oh
wow
yeah yeah meow meow meow meow
um
[Music]
oh and she flops again
asking for belly rubs
um
[Music]
well you'll be putting up a schedule on
Monday
oh I'll definitely be putting up
schedule for the coming week but I don't
know when it's happening oh wait
I was in America uh so I didn't like I
wasn't like in the right like headspace
for it but members wallpaper [\h__\h]
um
I have the members wallpaper wait I
didn't even like see the finished
version yet I think or did I
wait I didn't even I didn't even see
them I I was sent the finished version
but I didn't download it yet
ah it's gone
wait download
um download
Mommy
in the download
time is over mommy Gemma always
downloads them though usually so let me
ask her she's not online now so you guys
have to wait one more day
um Mommy I didn't recently I called Jen
my mommy sometimes
wallpaper in time
do you have it
um
okay
I feel like there's a lot to
catch up on for me too but step by step
step by step I recorded one thing that I
had a deadline for today today but
there's was there was one more thing
I couldn't record today and I'll do that
tomorrow before the Stream
anyway more chill till TK time tomorrow
and
yeah
my brain is empty right now and
hopefully also Super Chat reading
tomorrow okay
now already late next week Diablo Tio TK
uh a collab with
a Japanese member on her Channel
and this and that
okay
[Music]
down
I know but Street Fighter not feeling it
right now
[Music]
bye bye
also members wallpaper tomorrow
oh we gotta do a member stream next week
remind me if I forget
thank you for watching
thank you
[Music]
foreign