[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
um i'm i'm a i'm a gorilla what are you
doing what is he doing what is that cat
doing
oh my god it's been like a million years
since i've last played this game
uh
i forgot to put the logo on the screen i
mean we all know what game it is the
only reason i put the logos down there
is because uh otherwise it looks like so
empty on the bottom left
[Music]
foreign
did you guys know thank you daisy did
you guys know that today is a good the
day of the good or she
good or she's only today
and i am your
your precious good oshi yours is truly
your dear oshie it is me yes
me
i am your good ocean
i love to be your good hoshi
to
explain that for people who don't
understand
in japan they like to add a lot of funny
names to random days because of the
letters the numbers
um if you pronounce them in a certain
way
you might get a word out of it and today
the uh fourth of november the the
november's two ones they become into e
something good
wait a second girl before you talk to me
wait
um
so in november you get like
suddenly a huge wave of good something
something day and
is like oh
and four can be pronounced as either yon
or she in japanese and in this case they
choose
she so they make it into e ushi
yeah
yeah yeah and you're gonna be having a
lot of those days in this month it's all
it's always the same suddenly it's like
if today is
today is good but today oh wow
uh today is good toilet day where what
what how today is good bread day
what do you mean today is good birthday
what a good
good sandwich day mmm yeah yeah maybe
that gives me a reason to get a good
sandwich hell yeah baby
yeah yeah
uh i will have a little surprise for you
guys a little really little nothing
insane but
i have a surprise for you at the end of
the stream like maybe after the stream
maybe right after it ends anyway that's
something for later i was supposed to
play uh yeah i was supposed to play
minecraft today with aqua senpai on her
channel but it got um um
uh moved to another day or for now so i
thought well um
that would mean
no stream from my side for like over 48
hours so
i didn't want you guys to go without
your
good aussie for too long so here i am
[Laughter]
fact is that animal crossings new update
is absolutely
amazing
um like even for someone like me who
doesn't really
you know i'm not i'm not a huge like
freak when it comes to animal crossing
like i'm not a i i play i enjoyed
playing it for a little while but uh i
didn't get addicted uh unfortunately but
but the new update is free and it's huge
it's absolutely huge
i did not buy the dlc no
i i will have to think about that if i
need it i probably get it but i don't
know if i need it
anyway i want to check out the new
update and i have a feeling that i will
not be the only one
and playing animal crossing
in the next couple of days because i
feel like the update is uh gonna live up
uh i'm gonna make the community hype
again
how huge are we talking about well you
should have watched the animal crossing
direct nintendo direct and animal
crossing version because that was like
oh my god when are they gonna stop are
they still really are they still [\h__\h]
going are they still going
what it's free are you [\h__\h] kidding
me it was it was shocking
so
uh it's been a while
and my island is really nothing special
but let's look into it um
good evening everyone
right now in australia it's uh 8 p.m on
thursday november 4th
eoc
i don't have any big news to share with
y'all today but i would like to touch on
one seasonal topic
this morning i couldn't help but know
these mushrooms are starting to pop up
all over the island oh
[Music]
mushroom pie i
hate it i hate it no thank you
of course they're delicious but don't
forget they can also be used in the
occasional diy project
all right as long as i don't have to eat
it speaking of
everyone on the diy recipes app should
have received my recipe for a mushroom
ref what
is it like
the round circle thing
don't fall is complete without partaking
in that classic combo for raging and
crafting thank you for the guys on the
super trottos reef
that's all for now i hope you all enjoy
the loveliest of lovely days
you're not gonna tell me anything about
like those i don't know the update no
i definitely got the update it said
2.0.0 i made a
mistake
who is this
tata
wait a second
is this really what i look like
is this really my island oh well i mean
look at the presents
yeah i guess i guess i guess uh
yeah okay it's been so long i'm just
like why do i have that hair color
why
why do i have no i never cleaned no why
do i have this hair color
no but yeah it's okay was that not all
right all right
[Music]
what if
i don't know it's kind of freaking me
out right now
you guys were on this island before
right who's this in plastic
[Laughter]
dude mama told you borrow your game no
damn girl you look like this
there will be cockroaches in your house
yeah
uh that's all right um
i'm scared to open this
mommy
oh my god
okay so good it's all good i am i am who
i think i am
today in one year elder wait when did
you
when did i receive this oh there's no
dates here
when do you think was my birthday mommy
when
i mean of course the
national fried chicken day i don't know
i'm kind of like
i'm kind of freaking out right now
something feels weird but i think
everything's fine but she has a present
for me
all right
[Laughter]
that's not my real mom
yeah i mean yeah i know
i'm scared to look at my uh like
everything oh present
oh no no no no no open open
open how do i how do i pick up items
again ah okay i literally forgot how to
play this game
open
homemade cake
and this one
beautiful statue oh i must respect the
statue of myself
please
oh yeah that's me
yeah yeah yeah that's me that's me
indeed thank you
what's that
okay
hallway hallway
what what do you mean hallway
can i place it stop drop
place the item
wait a second how do you move this again
wait a second
how do i oh this again
there we go whoa
who gave this to me that must have been
a million years ago love the thumbnail
thank you isn't it adorable
that art from chill magazine
oh that looks cool uh i kind of would
prefer it to be daytime maybe it will
change the time later anyway what do you
got to say to me uh duck
frog
that's a duck who thinks it's a frog
that's why it's green and that's why
it's wearing a frog t-shirt kiana you're
back how's your oct
octopus
yeah i was totally on the marathon i was
on the marathon of streaming as many
games as i could in the past
few
months since my last animal crossing
stream i'm sorry i had [\h__\h] to do
what you didn't want um
life is a [\h__\h] marathon scoot you
listening life is the marathon we're all
running a marathon every freaking night
yeah it's tough out there
it's freaking tough out there what does
my house look like
i don't remember what my house looks
like
[Laughter]
oh my
god okay
[Music]
i've got some practice in killing
fun oh my god no it's killing me this
game this game is so cute oh hello
weird ugly crocodile
[Laughter]
[Music]
i could have invited you to my club
crazy for peach chris
uh-huh
what kind of peaches are you and
okay i might have been the only member
but still
what ah
oh my god look at my bridge beautiful
right oh what did i have in here can i
go shopping
i probably should go to the
to the office and check out what they
have to say about the update maybe
there is a mozart wink right there in
the bath bathroom maybe i should welcome
everyone with a bathrobe
and there's slippers there too
wow
nah this outfit is the cutest i wouldn't
want to wear anything else
bye sonic yeah yeah that's sonic sonic
gotta go fast check the fitting room nah
now whatever you got better things to do
and you guys can bring me close anyway
you guys bring me the cutest clothes
please
clue clothes
oh you're singing
these ugly villagers
did i really have these villagers we're
kicking them out ah right you can't do
that animal crossing what the [\h__\h]
mushrooms
flat mushroom how can i take
is isn't veils yes
she does have
similar colors but now it's more like
orange yellow isn't it
bales is more
red and
uh black and white
anyway
can you get out of my village my city my
island
what's this doing this is new too isn't
it like i haven't played in such a long
time i haven't even tried going swimming
yet
hello
what's up
hey
[Music]
that's kelly in cat form look at her
outfit with that gold chain around her
neck to drip oh yeah
hey hey so did i hear right you're
trying to drum up some hype for
australia protein
i hope so i want to be able to brag to
everyone that i was there before
australia got big
hopping up australia sounds like a ton
of work though you really do a lot for
this place
actually i've got something that i think
might help
oh is that my current quest to get the
reputation up
can i even enjoy any of the new things
right now with my island being so behind
on everything
a sandcastle what am i staying of course
it would be cool yeah just trust me like
i trust me on this so you should do too
you can enjoy some things okay some
stuff i can what what can i not enjoy
let's place
the sand castle
here
please
cute
cute cute cute cute okay uh
i wanna get the the the
cafe going
time travel speed run
my time travel once
to go to the next day to get the cafe
going
good
what kind of voice did i give him back
in the day
um
good evening
welcome to the australian museum
how may i be of service yeah
what about
what about the cafe dude
why is it because it's not complete
is it because i'm still missing like
i did update i did what do i need to do
i need to freeze the island what
[Laughter]
what what is mummy in the chat or are
you just saying because of blabbers
what am i missing
i don't
my element is not good enough how do we
how do we speed up on this
decorating
oh god no it's a island to three stars
time to clean and play the game
it's not that easy
[Music]
like okay it i just have to put millions
of decorations okay let's see how many
stars are currently good huh
um wait if we got three stars what what
happens like can i just go back in here
and then he says okay i'll guess you're
real ready for uh
they still got pumpkins i realized i
missed out on halloween
and so many other cool things it's so
unfortunate
oh god how do i play this game
how do i what's what's the quick
i don't know how do i quickly get uh
what's what's ah no no how do i
wasn't there like a
like a shortcut to my
uh
to my tools
up error ah thank you
smart wow you were rich oh i'm gonna get
richer i need to get this place going
i'm gonna be quicker richer and
uh yep uh let's see
[Music]
no time for singing beautiful white owl
oh my god so beautiful wait what does
that mean again that means something
special
right oh beautiful
[Music]
oh my beautiful wine oh my god it looks
so fluffy
[Music]
hello
um
so i have a little problem i started to
stream in the hopes of showing people
the update but um
i see that's not happening so soon is it
can i get some help
it's you isn't
it
do i need to make paths and [\h__\h] please
tell me no
of course
as mr luke mentioned i'm leading a task
force that compares feedback related to
the image of our island
if i get if i have guests over can they
make paths
or do i have to do that
just need to clean up for starters all
right all right you guys are going to
come over to my island
okay it's just me though i have always
wanted to a task force of my very own
anyway i won't bore you with the details
now but feel free to ask me about island
evaluations anytime that's exactly what
i'm here for now then how can i help you
today
what does this mean evil's evils
what does that mean
this is old it's a bell dialogue what do
you mean
what
what does that mean the update didn't
work or what
which is just i'm so far behind with the
game that she just talks really old
stuff
uh
i heavily every evaluation i'm so
pleased that you've taken an interest in
the image of our island i'm just so far
behind all right guys get your money
ready guys
well allow me to explain how the task
force and you and cool decorations
please that's me collects and analyzes
the data for my reports reports first i
conduct random polling around the island
with residents visitors
their feedback is then wrapped used
using the well-known fraps dollar system
i just need free size just give me free
stuff can i pay you off i can give you
like i don't know how how much money can
they give me maybe like
1 billion bells or that's probably not
even a lot for animal crossing how about
10 billion bells i offer you 10 billion
bells if you can fake my rating mrs
isabelle
what yeah no no no i'm not serious no
i'm not just a joke just a joke isabel
don't worry
just a joke
no i will work hard of course
that means we need more residents and
buildings proper infrastructure and more
residents
oh i wouldn't mind getting more
residents but i'm still like oh oh right
i still need like a lot more houses as
well don't lie oh [\h__\h] wait do you need
full residence uh like all of them a
maximum amount of residents in order to
get three stars is that also
something i need
yeah sounds easy but if we can achieve
that perfect balance and welcoming
environment our ranking is about to rise
need eight for free stars okay okay okay
what do you want what do you want from
me
there's some positive buzz floating
around about our island folks are
starting to take notice
allow me to be an excerpt from the
feedback that i gathered
it's like when a snow person is built
just right sure it's a good thing to be
well made and to feel alone
you can't believe i haven't talked to
yourself is this a sign that i have
never talked to her before yeah that
might be true
but i don't know
that there's no person would get the
proper attention here that's my take
anyway
well sorry for not getting addicted like
you guys maybe i will now okay
i i am on a i'm on a journey
to better myself and for that i will
play animal crossing every day now
let's get more greenery on this island
by planting fruit and saplings okay
more trees okay when it comes to train
varieties we really should branch out
i'm sorry i'm sorry i just can't resist
such a little hat
you're talking about talking about mine
mine are not low hanging oil [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] all right back to business calm
down
wasn't talking about your little hanging
fruit i was talking about tanuki's
there's just one more thing i'd like to
mention
some of our feedback mentions that there
aren't too many items lying around oh oh
really i didn't notice
i didn't know this oh oh sorry i'll
clean up okay okay
okay
so in any case you're saying put it all
in your storage and then plant a lot of
things okay
uh
i'm good for now
let's go
[Music]
i'm sorry she's cute she's beautiful
okay and um isn't [\h__\h] something you
call a female dog anyway
so
how dare you
dare me
about calling a female dog
a female dog
what is your problem
i am not wrong
hey
i'm actually surprised i remembered that
perfect english
so we're gonna put all of that
uh
into my house and that will hopefully
already help
uh i guess we maybe shouldn't really
have too many people bringing me
presents maybe only money because
presents are gonna be lying around
everywhere again why is there still
cockroaches
[Music]
how do i put this easily
in my
storage can i choose them all at once
wasn't there a way to do this all easier
maybe like this no that wasn't it
how do one at a time are you [\h__\h]
kidding me
one at a [\h__\h] time
that's good
where are you
[Music]
i'm coming in
oh yeah where are you hello
you can help me
i was finishing up a really intense
workout and fun i'd cool off here
do what you want i'm busy i'm kind of
busy right now one by one but hey it's
good i have some perfect perfectly
adorable things here for you wait look
at look at this
okay okay
doll look at that
eh
it's rotary ducky right when you have
company
it's he came in here without me asking
for it are you kidding i told him i'm
busy
okay i will not show you
the could've been dolden and the bridge
i will not show you that either i will
not show you any of this i hope you're
happy
see i could have shown you a decoy duck
one of your friends but no you didn't
want to see it all right all right then
pom-pom pudding bed i got the cutest
things wait pom pom point
isn't that
it has nothing to do with the thing that
amelia always sings right
now is that does that have anything to
do with that
you know what i mean
yeah this is san mario right what she
was saying was an anime opening
but if ami ever starts playing this game
i'm gonna give her all of these presents
that you guys gave me everything that
says pom-pom pudding i'm gonna give to
others
it's the pudding the pudding uh mascot i
remember though i know i know what that
looks like yeah yeah
well
put away no wait i should put that in
the atm right
shamrock soda
cool cool
eat i can eat that does that make me
stronger
that must be so cute
[Music]
i wanna wear it well of course i can't
are you going to tell me i can't change
either
are you leaving well thank god i'll get
out of here
thanks for coming bye-bye
i need to change clothes
and we're not that far yet you and me
bye bye bye bye
i need you to take out dig out three say
that's what i thought okay and how do i
use this again
there we go look at my cute outfits
can i get naked
oh wow graphic
gothic uh
punk
takanawa
so now i can wear this
[Applause]
[Music]
ew ew not in my bedroom
okay how do i i want to like enhance
this outfit because it doesn't fit the
boots although the boots are pretty cool
yeah
let me make an outfit can i do one with
the one i'm currently wearing or are you
going to tell me that's not possible
wait ah
it must be possible right
i love it when they over complicate
things how do i take it off
take that off
yeah get making it
i skipped the option no no but that
would wouldn't that mean i would put all
that together um that i was just wearing
uh
edit want outfits
but that wasn't the way i wanted to look
like so okay create
so cute
oh mama i need more clothes
oh frog froggie
why does
it so cute
where's my hair i look like i don't know
i'm bald or something
[Music]
cute
i
well all right i have a kitty hat oh my
god
yes i am happy with this
do i have one tight stove
yeah
all right let's track a pose should we
wear uh those in our mouth
the orange one
oh look at that face that smug face
she's giving us she's like i know i'm
hot
outfit sticks
yes
okay
so how do i use this again
[Music]
there we go
this one
you outfit
so
uh
look in the mirror for new hat
okay
i have a mirror here
sorry i don't know how to play this game
please
[Music]
let's just put this in storage
this one to the
visual punk dress
oh i can hang it on the wall
fascinating game put this in storage
menu chalkboard and that would be so
useful if i ever get like a restaurant
going here
also okay so
now i need my wand back uh
i don't uh there we go
i do need the wand with me
[Music]
duck duck that duck
chose violence
[Music]
i need that
i didn't know i had a frog umbrella
beautiful all right i need a wand though
but but then i have to change the outfit
again right
or wait our umbrellas umbrellas are like
kind of like extra thing right yeah uh
where is it
[Music]
hold
do
this
do this
easy where's the froggit
i know i know i know i know the frog
chair i know it's like super popular and
and
famous
[Applause]
and people are asking for it to
come to this game has it finally been uh
i think it was implemented now right
can i not wear this favorite
i guess somewhere here
oh
what do i probably not need
let's do this right now
nah nah nah okay i wanna use this uh
uh
i wanna
[Music]
[Laughter]
a how about that
[Music]
what do we want to look like we got new
hairstyles
and we can have orange hair too now
all right then
i like the hairstyle
itself actually a lot
[Music]
no no i'm happy with this one still
these eyes are like
terrifying
is that all right eye color for me
something
between pink and purple i guess this
would actually be more accurate you know
what let me get that
ah
cute animal crossing eyes are so funny
[Music]
okay i want these
i look like a clown
thank you guys for all the super chats
thank you
how do you like my new look
[Music]
that's terrifying what
what
i
have am eyes it's
it's this look
[Laughter]
do i are you saying i don't look cute is
that what you're gonna tell me on my
special day the day of good or shoes
you want to tell me that i don't look
cute
you sure that's what you want to tell me
nope yeah i thought so
uh i came here to put down some money
are you guys sure you don't want to brag
from me
no
oh damn one yeah
[Music]
abd what's abd
i want to put money into the bank into
the atm
[Music]
apd
ah this
deposit
look i got eight million
bells
not bad
eh
am i paying something off right now i
wonder
anyway for now take the money
stunks
but i guess for like everyday animal
crossing players is actually not much
huh
um
maybe we should ask wait can i do i need
to pay something off boy
[Music]
because in that case i guess i'll spend
all my money here
how can i help you about my home
it is much early i have
978 million
bells what
[Music]
i've kept you waiting long enough
how can i help you uh
oh expand my storage yeah why the hell
no
can you take my money directly from the
atm please
are you gonna tell me to go to the atm
[Music]
are you gonna tell me i have no money
when are they gonna invent debit cards
in this game
like i don't know pay with your phone or
something
uh deposit no no i don't withdrawal
um
get up get up get up there we go
never
because this will be the last update
oh that would be sad don't don't think
so negatively
but i know i've heard like it took them
a long time to make this update huh
but hey you get a huge update all at
once now
no one expected it to be this big
so uh about my
home i want to expand my storage
yeah an expansion pack
i mean this is the last free one
hopefully yeah hopefully there will be
more dlcs then
let's do it
excellent okay thank you
tomorrow morning okay
okay i will in the meantime continue
cleaning
up gosh
[Music]
they said it was the last major update
not the last in general
no more dlcs either actually what
[Music]
what about these i don't have to clean
up these right these are fine i think i
do need to
uh
oopsie
we need to clean up
this shelf
hey also kind of we're hinting that i
don't have enough
uh
and i don't have enough uh uh treats
yeah i think i have enough but okay
we'll see we will see after i clean up
everything if that does the trick
i heard it's difficult
pretty difficult to get to a five-star
island but i mean
[Music]
freestyle should be manageable right
what did i just do um please
might as well also want to place some of
these items
as decoration oopsies sorry flowers
[Music]
okay i think that's actually
on this side i shouldn't have any [\h__\h]
lying around
okay okay
it's not that hard to get plastics you
were just putting a lot of furniture
outside
but what do i have right now what could
i put outside
giant teddy bear ring a throwback rocket
and a blossom viewing gun oh yeah i was
trying to collect these back when they
first came out and i was playing
privately and i had a lot of them
okay i'll just place it randomly for now
can i hire some architect
to make my island look pretty
wouldn't that be nice
if you could get someone over to design
wait that's actually
it's not part of the dlc but you can you
can only do it like for your uh
island people not for
other random players right
you have to give them your switch
i wonder if there's anyone i know
who's like super addicted
to
animal crossing in my friend's circle
okay can i place something here
cinnamon roll parasol hello kitty
planter
place item
wait let me put that next to my house
please oh
i didn't necessarily want it to be uh
there but okay
look
makes it even more obvious that i love
cats
[Music]
oh cute stuff baby chick costume
new year's noodles food so much food
cinnamon roll hats
12th grade dish
ah i can learn this
interesting
doesn't not a huddle at all
okay let me put this inside
gotta use my what my
senpai
senpai nest to make my cool eyes
ah but i would have to actually meet
them though that sounds difficult
put in storage
why can i not choose more than one at
once huh
put in storage
no
yes i thought so no
not
[Music]
i love that
one what about this one
oh cute that looks comfy
but but we gotta
be stylish put this back
[Music]
know this [\h__\h] too
i wanna get to freestyles
do you think i can do it
we gotta believe
[Music]
pirate dress pirate dress
i want to get a new villager too i want
to do i have a free house
i wonder oh
i can sell those right let's put this
away for now too
and you know what uh
this is actually i guess currently
uh
in the way
okay
[Music]
you might be there already what you mean
at three stars
you for real should we check already
kelly's been real quiet since the
freestyle no you know what before we go
back we're gonna clean up all of that
kusa
and yes i shall do it myself
no one's chilling here why not
come on over guys
i'm gonna clean up my island
and also i wonder can i already do the
the tours like aren't there like boat
tours that you can do now can i do that
or do i need to like do something
for that as well in order
to
make it possible
check the dock oh
ah
i know you don't mean the the dodo dog
the dog
you mean the other duck right
i will check it out
oh hello
look at my phoenix look at my phoenix
i mean those glasses are
looking really stupid on you but
yeah
oh my god there is so much kusa
this is considered
oh kusal right
hey but it's on the flowers
that looks like flowers
you're telling me this is bad it looks
beautiful
who saw indeed
these flowers are fine right
marshall
that counts as a flower that doesn't
right
the one with the tiny blue ones
what about that one
by the way let's equip
this
and dig up some of those fossils
i gotta do something about my museum
right i still have like
probably more than 50 percent
of museum things missing
will she ever be able to fill up her
museum
we will never know
probably
is anyone living in that house
it's dark oh my god look at all that
can i bring you guys over
oh my god that's it i'm calling you guys
over
i'm calling you guys over i need some
help bring some money while you're at it
i mean
don't drop too many things it's too much
work oops
don't drop them don't drop in front i
don't need furniture right now
no no no furniture no items only money
[Applause]
only money
you're here to come become my gardener
yeah yeah yeah
although never mind if you have
something special maybe bring me that
too
are you ready i hope you guys are
prepared i have a pinned comment so
but everyone be a good good
uh
chicken and don't do anything stupid on
my island okay how did we do this before
we just i just gave you guys the code
and that's it but i didn't
[Music]
it's gonna take so much time though
until everyone is on the island again
it's gonna stop us so often
[Music]
via online play
wasn't there something i'm supposed to
hide or was that just when i visited
other islands
um
let me just connect you if you guys come
to my island you can plant trees and
stuff right but you can't make paths
maybe i should get you guys to try to
plant some trees
um and some flowers you can plant
flowers right can you guys plant flowers
is that a thing
no
no planting
only i guess uh
digging
we can't make holes
okay
uh
okay only if marcus best friend ah
i have blue flower flowers sure if you
can get in sure please please bring
bring me blue flowers
and you know
okay wait i will show something right it
doesn't right
it won't show anything weird right
anyway i'll hide it anyway
i need a dodo code though
no i don't think i can give out the code
to members only because you know
times have changed
who do you all want to invite i want a
doll doll called but don't show it right
away
[Music]
they work for me they're kfp
they're all my friends all of them
um
here we go opening the gate now
what's gonna be my daughter
okay
you guys ready i will i will spell it
out if you wear my album before you
might wanna
hold back and give others a chance
[Music]
x
b
w
okay is it open already though
is it really open
actually i don't i don't i don't even
remember
i already forgot i hope you guys wrote
it down
come on over guys come on come on help
me
quickly
[Music]
welcome
come on over come on come on come on
catch me please help me help me help me
you can't be
one hour there we go it started uh 30
minutes later
gardening squad come on who's going to
come
do not touch
you can't tell me what to
should i do this
a toby you wish for coconut
coconuts
coconuts coconuts
[Music]
yeah you know that song that's me it's
you congratulations you made it in
i hope you're ready to get some work
done
yeah no messing around and you leave
when i say you leave
[Music]
you better not show your face to iris
like that
hello
is it christmas over there
next one please
next one please oh
how many people can come to maryland
what's the maximum
[Music]
and another one
seven uh-huh
[Music]
okay that's fine arthur arefer are you
bringing your sword as well
[Music]
why do i have to be at work right now oh
don't worry don't worry we might have
another chance
and also the other girls in the whole
live english are a lot of them i think
are excited to play animal crossing
again
[Music]
no that's my sword that's not his sword
that's my thought
my sword
welcome
welcome back uh not back welcome to the
island wow you're stylish i like what
you're wearing
oh
whoa
you got fashion sense
oh
time to look at everyone's fashion
looks fancy what's a chad
is he dressed like colonel sanders wait
a second nah he would have had white
hair then no
hello santa
hello
[Music]
what a young santa claus
all right next up we got
[Music]
it's a fan meeting with kfb
who we got
freshly delivered trash
oh don't we love the self burns you are
more than just trash don't worry jess
don't put yourself down like that what
happened who hurt you
you're beautiful
you're talented
you're sweet
you don't have to put yourself down like
that
[Music]
yeah well at least your fridge fresh
yeah
usual room attendant
no no no no no just doesn't belong into
the usual room
top shelf
i wonder what i put as my own title i
don't remember
it must have been your freaking boss
[Music]
there we go that is the third person
so
four more oh well
you do look like trash
couldn't you have put on some nicer
clothes when you come on over here or
are you telling me you had some
accidents some incidents you definitely
look like trash
what happened
this person probably doesn't even have a
home doesn't even have an island it's
all fake
oh wow you don't even need to tap
anything you don't have time to tap
anything
oh i still have the christmas tree there
wait is the last time i played around
december because i still have a
christmas tree over there
that one's on the way
quick hide quick
all right let's see who's next uh
who's next
why do you need to save every time huh
i literally didn't do anything in the
game besides walking three steps
okay
so called something or other to
that sounds
complicated what does that mean
what is the meaning
[Music]
i'm waiting for you
ovula and oval is that on purpose
[Laughter]
[Music]
which one do you guys like more uvu or
oval is so hard to say
did you guys bring money
if you said if you're gonna tell me i
forgot the money i'm gonna kick you out
just kidding
i'm waiting
[Music]
welcome to australia
oh
whoa oh okay okay i mean at least you're
not in freaking rags
i see you like the color black
very very uncolorful
very uh monochrome
[Laughter]
no way
no way is that what you were trying to
accomplish
the majima look
actually looking at this dude with the
hat he also looks like he could be a
yakuza
somehow hello
oh wow you'll change your freaking
clothes
can i bonk him with my shovel
[Music]
next up
but first let us save the game
apparently
stop being a bully
excuse me
[Laughter]
did you see maybe maybe he used up all
the money on you know giving it to me so
he he sold all his clothes so that way
he would have something to
show to me
all right next we have
joshua
you know what that stands for seashore
seashell cellar sss
in reality in reality it stands for
shiny smiley story
i understand
here we have a typical whole life simple
yes yes understandable
shiny smiley story yeah
yeah or it could mean sparks spark specs
stream sparks
[Music]
single handling
no stream sparks
[Music]
today
stream sparks sporadically what that
doesn't sound right streams probably
surely
suddenly streaming sparks successfully
series
springs bikes soon now now now
no springbok saturday no everyday
springs sparks
speedily stinky what
there's nothing stinky about sparks
you're stinky
social security stuff
stream spark sims
[Music]
all right and another one and another
one but let me bump him i want to
bargain yeah watch it with your clothes
what happened
what happened what's the excuse huh you
can't even move nobody's even moving
you're so scared of me
okay okay
okay
stream sparks on spotify ah
we got a freaking winner you are the
winner
that actually fits perfectly
indeed you shouldn't only be
be streaming it on youtube you should
also be streaming it on
spotify
why i could i choose your hair
kiana's bullying me please help
are you the one with the raggedy clothes
you should have worn proper klaus
don't blame me
for your attire nah
a variation supreme being edward
laura edwards
are you edward scissor hands wasn't
there a character like that
wasn't there wonder who looks small with
that again endpoint
and the lord
scissor hands
it's a movie
yeah you know it's the thing it's the
whole thing it's the whole thing oh
johnny depp
johnny depp is coming to how did i get
to that point how did i
[Music]
oh yeah
thank you so much it's taking so much
time
why can't they all just take the same
goddamn flight
a pirate oh are you uh are you a modern
senpai
understandable
me too who isn't who is not a fan
no one can resist maddening senpai's
charm
do we have one more
[Music]
where are the girls why is
[Laughter]
where are the girls send me a girl now
i want to see a girl right now or that
that this one also looks a little bit
the eye the eyelashes look quite
feminine and they're herself too
actually are you a girl are you a girl
never trust anyone on the internet who
says they're a girl anyway
didn't make it angela why not
i don't know i'm yawning so much i slept
enough actually i got up early like at 9
00 a.m once for actually no at 8 55 a.m
i slept
so little i was so tired but i had to
get up for uh something
work related
and then um i couldn't sleep
immediately after that when i tried
how i put it
it was funny
oh more trash great
do i look like i need more trash on my
island i'm getting you guys over here to
pick up my trash not the other way
around why are we getting more and more
trash on my island
[Music]
i was saying
i was saying yeah so i got up uh
for
something work related and then
uh
i got out of my bed and
i could really notice for the first time
that the muscle relaxant was working
because i i never felt so
my body like i could get up and i was
able to walk but i definitely noticed
that my muscle relaxant has not
worn off yet
that's how little i slept at that point
yeah i was feeling like jelly it was
interesting
[Music]
i got up too early but no i was able to
function anyway girl
that is a deadbeat that is a [\h__\h]
kelly cosplay
where's the pink hair
girl it's a girl is that the last
visitor
dead beat made it in
or i get to work
one two three four five six seven okay
get to work
go go go go
go go go it's like up up there
don't go google i'll check out how you
guys are working in a moment yeah hello
can we you're tapping something what do
you want to say what do you want to say
yay yay let's go
if you brought money please place it um
please place your money offerings
and
next to my house here
and i'm gonna be sitting here like a
queen
nah
you have to work
welcome
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
cutting cutting
[Music]
oh if you put on a suit mate oh perfect
outfit perfect outfit perfect perfect
perfect what's with this stuff
what is that oh
i'm already i already got full pockets
wait wait a second guys wait a second i
need to uh
oh my god oh my god wait a second
guys don't don't pick up the other
people's presents okay there's another
thing that you can do please do not do
that that would be uh so stupid
how unexpected yeah i didn't predict
this at all
stocks thanks strange sparks songs
songs
yes hello i would like to put down some
money
and i would like to uh yes the full
amount 1.5 million
yeah
okay
thank you
i'm coming back soon
[Laughter]
do i have anything in my inventory that
could be decoration to put down let's
see
anything
mysterious painting oh is that for the
isn't this like super precious do people
not like pay millions of bells for the
froggy chair
or is it like easy to get now
oh my god that check is going crazy
the chat is going crazy
oh
my god
froggy
there's one
froggy chair it's a froggy chair nanka
you might not use a more hotel
oh
you guys are going insane this is so
hard to get is it so hard to get
you can take this am i full already
no there we go
in front
welcome why are you guys not working
not enough room in my wallet okay okay
oh yeah yeah
hey that was fast
mr dropped item limit oh
i'm not sure i want to open the presents
what is this stuff open
cherry blossom flooring oh
[Music]
hey hey
oh yeah you go to the user room
i like your captain looks like a kfc cap
um are you guys already done all that
open
i'm talking to your villagers okay don't
steal them terrible some bonsai oh i
care for you
my outfit
red purple emperor model oh toilet
i look like i need a toilet i'm an idol
flashy hairpin
don't go into my house
now it's okay but
kind of rude not gonna lie
and i will what's wrong man yeah rag
rock person is here yeah yeah
i know i know oh i can't okay let me put
uh
some i should just be putting
taking money only um for a while but
and then the items but oh well
next time
at home
then these people come to to clean up my
island
it better be a five-star island when you
guys leave
they'll remember me later what does that
mean you scare me
i'm stuck
trying to make a kia video or what
no no you can't be stuck why are you
stuck
hi stuck
it was recess but the cluttering dropped
into one
that is very very much possible
but i
will
clean it up
in the
moment let me take some items only i
don't know what all this stuff is
that was it
wait did you already do the
i have to check up on your guys's work
are you fishing in order to put uh
to give me fish for the museum
if yes then
you're very welcome to do that
okay let me put this in my storage i
hope i have enough
the clutter trapped him what
and he can't pick it up or what
do i need to pick it up for you
[Music]
all right give me a moment i can't seem
to get into my house
sea bass no thank you
i can't get into my house
[Music]
is this a normal
well i'm stuck
what happens when the when the
host is stuck
[Laughter]
it might just be a really long leg i
mean the people are still moving
you guys
maybe
it will load really maybe the person who
got into my house first
pulled some trick on me
broke my game by destroying my house
from the inside
ah there we go
[Laughter]
we good we go don't try to get into my
house though please because it will
probably take a long time for me to
uh sort my things while you're here i
think uh
doesn't it like load every time someone
comes in so please please do not come in
please do not come in
i'm gonna have a quick
[Music]
open frame kitchen mysterious painting
cherry blossom bonsai
festival stall
is that a toilet festival float float
gold pole that's full flap
midnight
telling me to give her i literally just
came back to this game excuse me give me
some time okay we're gonna place this
froggy chair in order to flex
[Music]
oh it's the holy throne of animal
crossing players
oh my god i'm sitting on the throne
if this were game of thrones this would
be the most majestic thrones of them all
[Laughter]
[Music]
but how much is this worth how much is
that froggit with don't don't uh animal
crossing players pay good money for that
i won't sell it but
i don't know i just want to know what
it's worth
it's just out of curiosity
you know
priceless
i agree
princess peach crown cute
i want to try out that outfit later too
creepy wants us to be friends well do
whatever you want
eh five belts probably not that much to
be honest really
uh open
oops ah well i guess i'll
it doesn't matter if my house is messy
right
and
okay oh wait let me put the
wood away
and this one
okay inventory empty again
only took me
way too much time for that
it's a meme chair yeah
i got the famous chair it's so exciting
let me go grab this money
quickly before someone steals it
can't beat the house belong to me
they're here to pay their salary to me
oh no no no what do you what do you
think you're doing
what do you think you're doing
is that is that all the money nothing
i'm complaining wait this is money too i
think
buying saplings from shops sure sure
okay do what you think you need to do
what are you are you fauna
fana always says ooh doesn't mean
pick that up pick it up i can't pick up
this item
i literally can't
uh
oh
goodness
fana what are you doing on my island
bless you thank you oh thank you oh
thank you
oh this is so nice
everyone so sweet
uh
i'm gonna check up on everyone's work in
just a moment so better be prepared okay
thank you chad thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes work yes yes that's what you came
for you're just shopping in my stores
and talking to my villagers that's not
what you came here for
um
[Music]
hold on
what who is holdering the door who is
holdering
no need to hold her i want to go online
i love hodor but not right now
[Music]
please stream now
no
this is my stream
i'm waiting hello i got some stuff to do
can i start a yoga session oh i don't
know how to do yoga
i can only maybe start a stretching
session
i i know my things now
i know how to stretch
all right let's see what we got this
time open
cart banner
okay
donation box oh perfect
wait can people actually put money into
that
or is it just decoration
materials
yata
garden gnome who doesn't love garden
gnomes
money
a money
puma pudding chair
people can actually donate wait anyone
[Music]
abd
oh oh wait i can take wait wait isn't
that can i can i
uh this this deposit and withdraw money
like outside with that thing
wait why did i go outside now i should
have first put everything
in this storage
wait wait wait but i want to put these
things down wait people can like legit
donate into my donation box
and this uh
place
i can't place it down now
oh
[Music]
that's right
for ease of use thank you oh in the
future that will be very very helpful
next time i get visitors
i'll put that down and then i can uh
yeah
it doesn't go in directly into the
account
just automatically
noise
jolly painting ho ho ho
is this the festival stuff is that uh
what is what is the theme behind that
christmas or
a carnival
no
oh
oh you're right those are for like
moving around for the island right
[Music]
well my cat
can i can you move that
okay it stays here for now
chapters
put in storage
water her flowers oh yeah feel free to
water my flowers i guess
[Music]
thank you
open
open oh my god
all my money worries are gone forever
oh no no no oh my kimono stands nice
i already got a couple those are really
really pretty
okay
[Music]
okay i'm almost done i'm almost done
with putting away everyone's presents
thank you guys for bringing so much cool
stuff
oh oh
what what happened here did you plant
flowers
did you plant flowers pink
thank you
thank you yeah thank
[Music]
you can do that
push this whoa
whoa
thank you that's very helpful that will
help my rating
flowers and bushes oh
wish i wasn't at work
you're at work but you're watching my
stream but you can't play animal
crossing
yeah
i'll play it again soon next week maybe
or the week after i'll play it again
don't you worry about it
eh wait what
uh what
over 11 million
that's a cool looking number one one six
nine six one one one
[Music]
okay should we already ask no i wanna be
surprised after everything is cleaned up
i wanna know the reading of that
okay let me quickly oh
what are you dressing up as a
oh they're writing on my wall now oh
[Music]
and let me check
if they did what they actually
originally came here for
oh you're talking to my phoenix lady
go ahead oh someone's working hard up
here
i will keep you in mind oh you you're
wondering my plans thank you
i see
no kusa
oh okay well destroyed flowers that's
okay no kusa inside
[Music]
trying to get my flowers okie dokie
no kusa here either
good job
no kusa
oh good good stuff good stuff
good stuff
i'm too stupid for this yes i am
literally too stupid for this
gotta have a
good feeling in your fingertips for this
kind of stuff
[Music]
that's my first one
ew it's in right inventory
whether you're still giving dip what
what what what does that mean
what
what are they giving you
didn't you like i like i like um
caterpillars
but centipedes is a whole different
story okay
diy rice yeah what oh yes so what are
you making fun of me because i
i still have a lot to learn
plan some veggie starters oh thank you
they stop after a bit oh
oh ho ho i see
it's limited time oh yeah i haven't
talked much with them yet
okay i don't think there's any kusalas i
think you guys did a great job there
hello you're checking too i think i
think it's fine
there's something here behind no
got some pumpkins over there
i would love to have some pumpkin soup
right now that would be so
divine
let me try to see it
are you playing with my doggo
i want to see on the other side of the
island if they looked over there too
looks good
can be
kfb members you're for once not going to
the usual room i think good job
good job
that's kind of what he did
wonderful now i just have to pick up a
couple more items um off the ground and
then i think we're good
[Music]
let's go
got some good hard-working kfc employees
here on my island i will not forget you
guys
i will not forget you
here by the way uh we talked about
having a rock uh as you go pets the
other day
so if anyone wants a stone or rock as
their pet here's one you can pick it up
you can have it special uh
limited time offer are you taking it
i can sign it for you
you don't want it oh my god oh my god
so keep on changing your outfits you
want it here this is for you this is my
stone for you
ah he took it
it's a special stone
don't lose it
don't lose it okay oh oh wow
what's your cute outfit
let me look at you
wow it's a trip are you okay
it is cute the green outfit you're
adorable
oh you're right that's the thing if you
wear that mask right
then you'll keep on tripping over i've
heard of that before
oh scary mask
oh
i still became fauna oh i guess so
i don't know i mean there's something
about that outfit that's actually kind
of cute but you are trash
no i don't like that one change
i don't like it
fall autumn outfit very cute
oh oh you i got all those fancy outfits
guys it's cute
i like i like that one i like it
i'm not a friend of camouflage to be
honest oh pumpkin
cute i want that pumpkin head
do you trip with that one as well
let's make a deal did you name it your
outfit dad
aha
oh my god wait who's that again
again i know that face
you look exactly like one of those
characters from yakuza
what's that matchima oh my god
yeah they can't the caffeine uniform is
the best though can i um go through here
once i really just want to pick up my
items thank you
deadbeat's working now
all right
uh
your show what is that stuff
they started a fashion show i still
can't pick up that item whoever um put
this item down are you able to pick it
up again or is this broken forever
both dead feet and can't be thank you
k of beats is what you call that
thank you thank you
oh that's cute
ah looks like you're not able to pick it
up huh wario what are you doing here
wario you already got your own game why
are you in this one
oh oh try once more leave yeah good idea
i guess maybe restarting the game or
whatever
could probably do the trick as well
okay did i pick up everything
i think i did
something here all right game is weird
yeah sometimes
okay okay okay i'll go
wait
we're done
we're done we're done we're done
for now
i want my cafe
i want it
princess peach dress whoa oh you're
right there was this whole uh super
mario
stuff right that you could get in the
game
i've seen it but i didn't play uh the
game when that was coming out so i don't
have any of those items what are you
doing my house
what are you doing in my
basement
they just do whatever the hell they want
ice cream oh okay that's it i'm eating
ice cream today
for dinner yes that's right no one can
stop me because i live alone i don't
have like a
like a mama who can be like no kiana
you're not eating ice cream for dinner
now
i do what i want
what a sexy seashell
places i'll keep them in my inventory
what saplings are those trees
bushes didn't diner sofa
perfect for my kitchen
flower petal baskets cute is that you
are in the basement uh i think something
like that was in the basement when i
forgot what does my basin look like
i think i was trying to make it into a
usual room i was trying
oh
oh yeah yeah this is my usual room
beautiful
gorgeous
divine
who wouldn't want to live here
you know what kfp you can stay in my
house as long as you stay in the
basement
okay uh
oh we should set this centipede free
eh
shut up
god damn it okay
oh welcome to the usual room have fun
don't burn yourself or maybe do burn
yourself and good luck trying to finish
the puzzle
[Music]
bathroom use no entry
all right i think we can check
i mean if if that doesn't give me one
more star
[Laughter]
that's
that's my
super sexy naked statue can you please
not take pictures of that
it's embarrassing okay
should i put a leaf on on the boobies
over there
so please three stars come on or four
stars even eh
come on
come on it's a bell
huh
hello
okay can i do this right now when i have
people over here
[Music]
is this because i have people over i
can't ask
okay guys you gotta leave now so that
means another 30 minutes of waiting for
everyone to leave
you all can take a picture with me
before you leave all right
we can take a group picture
kick them all out oh i can kick them all
out at once can i do that then please
don't don't even start leaving
close the session good idea okay then
come come to the
uh middle of the island and let's take a
picture
i'll stand here and you take pictures
because i forgot how to do it
[Music]
or i will try as well and how do i how
do i do it
[Music]
i wait wait let me when if i wear this
it's cute yeah that's cute
[Music]
camera
okay everybody line up
everybody line up someone
we have an uneven number do we
wait shouldn't we be eight people
is there someone missing
one two three one two three
all right someone has to stand
oh yeah santa you can stand on the very
right
i am the eighth person
[Music]
i'm currently huh wait i'm confused oh
you can sit down there
all right all right all right
your hat your hat covers up my beautiful
face a little bit though
can you
actually stand over there and then
someone else sits in the front
coordinating the beautiful picture
oh you're changing all right all right
all right now you can sit down i guess
if you wanna
sit down sit down
okay
set out for camera run step out
oh okay pose everyone pause
pause
adorable thank you
oh wonderful
thank you okay now
let me kick your ass out of here
how do i do it do i have to go to the
hello i have to go to
to the airport
don't don't think about leaving on your
own i have to kick you all out don't
waste my time
thank you guys for coming i love you
[Music]
i hope it was fun for you guys to clean
up my island
please close the gate
wait does that mean if you will kick
them out as well if they did just say
mine is to
kick them out but does this kick them
out too
thank you thank you i hope for yoga
maybe next time we can have a yoga
session
oh i know it just means that no more
people can join after those sleep huh
okay
and session
bye bye
thank you
love your bus thank you well i'll help
you guys um come back to my island
someday
uh especially if i'm not at three stars
rating right now then we're gonna have a
problem
yeah that might be might be a bit of an
issue
i wanna be in stars but one thing that
we can probably do anyway is visiting a
different uh
like going on a boat trip right we
should be able to do that
no no we're not done with the stream yet
i was just saying goodbye to these
people
although it will be definitely a short
stream
uh
supposedly supposedly
make sure to place the donation box and
the aw yeah we'll do it that's really
helpful
should i place uh
both in front of my house perhaps
so four
honestly now this is just a kfp meme
whenever kiana says it's going to be a
short stream
um that means it's uh
probably something about four hours
but you guys love it don't you
don't i love it when i'm with you the
whole day whenever you want to see me
i'm here for you 24 7.
i don't want to hear any complaints
yeah i know it honestly yes
now it's the moment of truth guys
also displacement is kind of horrible
because like i will always run over them
i don't know if i want to keep that ah
my cute cat so cute look at that cute
cat look at her
yeah
oh wow it's great to see you again
i have your window this time i dropped
by your place to work for you but you
were never home oh
i was just getting some milk for you
cats like milk no
i bet you went on a secret mission
yeah to some place exotic but filled
with danger at every turn
sorry about that i've been on a kind of
adventure novel cake oh
welcome back now
i know i know you shouldn't really give
cats milk i know i know i mean when they
are young i guess you can give them a
little bit
yeah but my cats uh they don't drink
milk they drink water
yeah it's kind of a
weird thing that people
when they think of what cats drink
if they're not a cat owner they think
they drink milk but they don't really
they shouldn't really it's bad for their
stomach
uh
let's talk about my rating
bell
and i would like to remind you that i
have a basement in my house that you can
stay over
in case you don't like my island
[Music]
she didn't want to go to my basement it
seems i don't know what her problem is
but all right
yeah i don't care i don't care what the
people think i just wanted to three-star
rating
what's happening
am i hallucinating what was that
feedback signed by a chaos
yes there it is very clear
and the pendant ship is quite striking
if i do say so myself
could it be
[Music]
[Laughter]
we finally achieved our goal of bringing
our i went to the attention of the okay
sliders stop sending me friend requests
not only that but he said he's looking
for an excuse to visit
oh yeah if i log in tomorrow i beat the
game right let's do a timescape i need
to do one anyway for the
uh cafe and we finally see okay the
first ever kka concert
then what are we waiting for yes yes
let's offer him the chance to hold a
concert on our shores
strike while the iron is hot they say
all right
[Music]
pleasure of speaking with mr
k.k sliders
milk ink located on australia a week
don't forget the link oh yeah yeah so
this girl i don't know what the hell her
problem is but she
uh just now
yeah got the freestyle rating it only
took her about five
years and a lot of help from her
viewers she can't do [\h__\h] on her own
apparently but that's how it is
sometimes well at least anyway finally
you can come over to the [\h__\h] hole of an
island
and i hope you will enjoy it yeah yeah
yeah and we need a concert yes indeed
indeed a concert to save this island
from being the worst place on earth
please i beg you yes she has a lot of
money yeah she can pay you
oh i'd say one billion bells because in
the end it's not her paying that anyway
trust me trust me she won't say no she
doesn't know what's a lot of money and
what's a little money in this game
ah if i say that's like five dollars she
will have no issue with that
so what did he say
he'll do the concert
kk slider is coming here
amazing congratulations
[Music]
he could be here as soon as tomorrow but
he has to check his schedule of course
i need those one billion bells though
can you believe it believe it we finally
turned our going to a reality we'll
spread news of the concert via our allen
broadcast system i can hope you'll be in
attendance piano you simply must hear kk
play
yes yes you must
well but will he be streaming sparks
because if no then i'm not interested
what about the cafe
[Music]
more owls i'm scared to look at this uh
on stream
[Music]
[Laughter]
um okay
[Music]
okay um
guess who this is
guess who this is um
that kind of looks like someone i've
seen before i'm not sure i'm not sure
who it could be it looks familiar
[Music]
[Laughter]
goomba
and we have kiana daisuki i love you too
edward was here indeed thank you
last time i was here in january kiana
told me to take off my clothes at the
airport i'm scared please send help will
i ever get my apron back
oh and tom nook
yeah yeah yeah alrighty
now i really hope
look at my beautiful fox girl she's so
cute
now let's see let's see
will i be able to open my cafe or not
i worked hard for this okay blabbers
please
i think i just saw on the top left it
was actually open now like the the room
was like
open i think
uh might there be something with which i
can assist you
oh wait it's not open
need a time travel
after the cake i got it okay
okay okay okay
okay anything else i want to do right
now because i need to time travel for it
anyway i wonder
don't die now yes it's not time to die
i can die after
after the cafe is open
the kfp cafe
have you heard just like mcdonald's we
have decided to not only
be not only be a fast food chain we're
now opening cafes all over the world
cafe cafe
look forward to it coming close to your
local kfb
uh right next to
where your grandma lives hell yeah
hell yeah
oh
i like that that's pretty
yes i am interested eight thousand five
hundred no problem i'll buy it
kfc
kiana fried caffeine
why do we keep on going back to kfc i
don't understand
this is nice too
yeah this is actually the notes for
spikes
and table isn't that bad either
mac
we need a better name for that perhaps
before we open it for real
can i sell
some of my cousins
[Music]
mm-hmm
yeah that's all i want to sell
oh books
[Music]
i love that and especially because like
the c and the l looks like a mirrored b
and that's basically still just
starbucks
no we can't use that
we can't just use that i think that's
that might uh create some issues oh
orange umbrella
nice
yes we can no no no
spark box
spark bugs
spark clucks spark plugs spark clutch
that could be good that could be already
uh different enough
spark
spike
all right one second let me uh
oh let me how do i get out of this game
again
i guess i'll dress still
one second
let me time travel please
you don't have to save an animal
crossing right right
a minus okay
wait do you have to save save you have
to save all the saves wait why does it
say seven and if it's on saves
okay i did save an end okay
why not include konnichoke um
[Music]
it's better to end your session first
okay all the saves up every five minutes
oh
oh time traveling
sorry uh cronie um we're messing around
with the timeline a little bit i hope
you don't mind
can you imagine if cronie gets into
animal crossing
she'll probably go insane with the game
has cronie ever said if she gets if
she's like if she's an animal crossing
fan because i can imagine
she's the type of animal crossing player
that would play it every day the whole
day just like how she plays minecraft
too like she already is she's getting
ready to play she is
oh my god
oh well at least i guess that will get
her off of uh minecraft for a little
while
she already got bored of it oh really
yeah no way
i thought she would like it
oh
that's unfortunate
okay i'll make it the 5th of november
but
let's say
uh 10 a.m
my show okay
okay
that should be
good
okay
[Music]
remember remember the fifth of november
wait a second what's wait what is that
from it remember remember the 5th of
november remember remember the 5th of
november
was that from
what was that from
v from vendetta
what is that what's that
it's a british thing
and but i feel like i've heard of that
before the remember remember 5th of
november what
oh it's a movie
ah
all those memes again all of those men
that i don't understand
[Music]
look at her look at that super cute
sentai bunny
she's the cutest i love her so much
i didn't have her in the beginning i
only got her thanks to a viewer
absolute chad
what a chat i will never forget that
because when i was playing privately um
she was the first villager that i got
and i loved her so much and then
um when i started playing animal
crossing on stream i had to make a new
island and then i didn't have her and i
didn't really like get my hopes up for
getting her but then someone gave her to
me thank you for the red super chat
good morning everyone
right now in australia it's almost 10
a.m on a friday november 5th 2021 now
for today's announcements today we have
a visitor staying at the captain
which wait you only get do you only get
visitors at the campsite if you have an
empty house or even when all the houses
have filled up
now let's see to wrap up today's
broadcast i have a very special
announcement the incredible amazing
musician kkk sliders here visiting
australia
oh originally i agreed to put on a
special concert for everyone on the
island
even when houses are filled ah okay okay
okay do i have an empty house
i hope i do
they ask you if you want to kick someone
out
i thought that was impossible
oh
it's happening
hey australia it's real groovy being
here
feels like this today i once had when i
was just a scruffy pup with a shoebox
guitar
i was dreaming of hitting out on my own
wondering wherever my road would take me
dreaming of finding a magical place
where cool cats like you would come
together to see you straight like me
sorry about that
time to get your fingers snapping
oh my god i finally cleared the game
right on this one goes out to all your
cool cats in australia
[Music]
with that
this might have been my longest
playthrough of a game
we finally did it
turn it up turn it up
[Music]
thank you
i couldn't have done it without you
[Music]
that looks scary
with those eyes
[Music]
oh
yeah i know crosstalk has this ending
but you obviously can like
play for millions of hours afterwards
this is like
it just needs some kind of ending to it
ending it's not really an ending though
[Music]
oh
incredible
better than madonna
better than michael jackson
[Applause]
better than
everyone out there literally except
except uh
what
what a dog
what a hello
what did i do what did i do now
hello
[Music]
i'm
that can play music and i do hope you
enjoy it
i have some big news too
is apparently very fond of our hours now
i'm not surprised
he's going to perform a show here every
saturday evening from now on it's really
amazing
australia was once a deserted island but
now we can host important concerts i'm
so thankful to you and everyone else on
this island
speaking of which i've developed a new
app that should help you make the island
even more inviting oh
let me send it to you now what is it
what
what did i get
oh island designer
all right i'll try my best to make my
own look good
it's a special app from cooking that
gives residents the ability to take part
in bold island development ah is it uh
that can you like do terraforming ah
only took me
million years to unlock
have permission that create tabs but you
can use new mouse to access more options
like different kinds of paths and
permits for changing your clips and
rivers
once you get a taste of island design i
think you'll want more i encourage you
to obtain all the necessary permissions
yeah australia has come a long way
i think i'll leave more and more of the
future development of this island in the
hands of its residents i'm glad we had
this talk
on behalf of noking thank you for the
millions and millions of dollars you
have invested in me
[Music]
well now that kk has performed it's time
to focus on making our life better and
better i agree
that means living each day to the
fullest doing things i like and having
lots of fun
sounds good to me
what
what said l
mm-hmm do i have some
accomplishments right
i had nook mouse
i'll probably have a bunch don't i
uh
huh no
jump
thank you
doesn't it feel good to get a stamp on a
stamp card
growing collection your tongue
two thousand milk miles
next door okay mania oh my first concert
do you guys stand for every time he
comes over
island and you win
another one
i just started my island
well kind of me too i mean look at the
state of my island
who's inside here
who's in that yeah who's in that yeah
who's that who are you who are you come
on show your face yeah
you better be cute you better be cute
you know you're um
kind of cute
i don't know it's kind of
what's your problem with what's that
anime animal called again
a tap tap here aren't those the ones
that eat ants
[Music]
pink and either i don't know kind of
cute eating a donut good taste
um
but no thank you no
no no
bye bye
and now please tell me i can open up the
cafe now or i'm gonna be mad is there
any anything else you have to do in
order to get it
come on
did i not donate enough things yet
wake up wake up wake up
this is not a joke
i need you
to give me
[Music]
i need to donate more items are you
kidding me
no
travel till next day i already did i
need you guys to come over and bring me
uh fossils and [\h__\h] i don't have that
many i think i have a few in my storage
now but yeah
it's not much
i think i need a few more guests
donate the statue the statue the statue
the statue can put into the museum
oh
really
but it's my
hot knife that body why i don't want too
many people looking at that in a museum
i think you're just missing art
that really sounds like something
motivational that super senpai would be
screaming at me
our reactions to cheer folks on oh yeah
thank you encouraging thank you
snaps muscles
which which one i don't really have any
why you didn't need to point it out like
that it kind of hurts
kind of hurts
[Music]
why do i still have cockroaches
i was here yesterday okay
okay we got a seat we gotta check out
if we have like some stuff i can donate
to the museum is this
is is this for the museum
wow i got a lot of stuff yo
a lot of cool stuff
only real art this one
no
mysterious painting
maybe
what about this what about this
dynamic painting or this is a
decorational for the museum
those three go into the museum those
three count oh okay okay
but i don't even know yet if they're
fake or real right
or maybe they gave it to me because they
know it's real they wouldn't give me
fake stuff right
i like that pirate dress thank you
oh that's cute cinnamon roll hat looks
cute
okay okay is that oh my god and fossils
right some fossils
did you see anything else that i could
donate in this uh inventory probably not
probably not okay
the statue from earlier okay
sure you can i had a centipede
okay i still have that in my inventory i
think oh and a butterfly
wait a model no that's not
that's not donatable i think
it looks looks like that's it okay
oh
bugs and fish
yeah i know i know i know i don't have
many of those though i hate fishing in
animal crossing
i always get the same goddamn fish
always
i think i've donated those before maybe
i should try to catch them anyway
i'm gonna feel like yeah
probably have never mind then bye-bye
[Music]
i brought some donations please
take my donations uh maybe is it just
that i don't even have to fill it up
properly but i just have to give him at
least one painting so that he'll open up
the painting room which would that be
this one
ah statues maybe it goes up there and
then once i have at least one of those
in there maybe he will offer me the
cafe
yes yes
okay
if you have at least one piece of art
you probably have enough okay good
says fossils first
all of them please
one two three four five six seven
eight
how do you get those statues are they
also being sold with the guy who sells
the paintings
off from red
it's the same guy
oh the one in the boat how does he bring
those huge statues in that tiny ass boat
fabulous
okay so jolly painting dynamic painting
amber what did i not bring the statue
skull
painting ah statue okay and the
centipede or ronnie
what are you saying about this splatters
hmm
who gave me a fake painting will he take
it anyway
problem work has warmed its way in
amongst the donations you have presented
me
i'm terribly sorry but surely you
understand we simply cannot display
fakes you there better be one real one
in between those
[Music]
okay
what did he leave the paintings
the paintings are gone it's a statue
okay
so are they in here now
the villagers
are looking at the paintings well that's
a beautiful painting those paintings
exist in real life right as far as i
know
i want to buy
oh
the music in here is beautiful too
stop running in the museum that's so
rude
yeah it's real art right you can also
get the mona lisa right
oh
i want to buy them for my for like
you can buy copies of these real
paintings right for for your own
for your own
inventory right like in real life right
where would you where would one buy a
copy of the mona lisa is there like is
it like illegal to just buy
just just just to to just print out a
mona lisa picture and put it in the
frame is that illegal
do you have to like kind of
buy the real thing a copy of the real
thing or can you
is that is that illegal it's not illegal
yes it is no it isn't
isn't there copyright on it
yeah you're right shouldn't there be
hey i wonder what the rules on what the
laws on that kind of stuff are i
actually have no idea
you have to ask mona lisa herself oh i'm
probably gonna have a problem with that
how may i assist you yeah well i want
the freaking cafe do i have to wait
another day
i gave you paintings what else do you
want does he want the statue now
but at least there's already one thing
in the
in the painting room so
shouldn't that be enough
should i go back in
maybe he just wants me to come back
again
one more time
[Music]
the print doesn't have the texture
exactly i want a copy
of the mona lisa or anything else
[Laughter]
that's not just a printed out image like
that
how do you get that
did you talk to the dog guy not yet i
wanted to do that i didn't see him wait
are they only there uh
if it's uh daytime
that might explain why i didn't see him
yet or i just didn't look closely that
[\h__\h] looks huge
but i think it's probably just normal
size
okay
well
if we can't get the cafe i at least want
to go on the boats tour
we need a sea creature
what do you mean i haven't donated a sea
creature before you mean fish
there is no way that i have not donated
a sea creature before
why did i come here for ah
isn't it down here
i need to get the wetsuit
i think i bought one before
okay
i need to learn to swim first
and catch something in the water and
then i can go on the boats tour
oh my god
oh guys it's so complicated
[Music]
is that fortune cookies
gorgeous cookies are so yummy i don't
know what it is about them that makes
them so yummy
all right uh a wetsuit all right
[Music]
okay okay i think i had one in my
storage where could you buy it otherwise
in the
in the nooks cranny shop
i guess i'll just buy one in case i
don't want to run into my apartment and
figure out that i actually don't have a
wetsuit i'm pretty sure i have one but
still
no not my pretty shovel
i hear a present hmm
yeah i'm good
in the cupboard in the shop okay i think
i've seen it before i just never
tested it out
what is that hot plate of food
i'm hungry
i don't know how much longer i can take
it
the decoration in this place is so cute
for autumn with the pumpkins
so cute there it is it's not very cute
all kinds of different wetsuits right
three thousand bells okay no problem
oh i'm so hungry i can't stream much
longer
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
well my mom told me when i was younger
then you shouldn't go into the water
anyway right after eating something so i
have to uh hunger a little bit more
can i put the wetsuit on even when i
have a
magical stick outfit
where
of course not
that was too much to us
revert outfit
okay
and then
wet suit
i still don't know what the
problem is though
why can't i not go into the water do i
have to what
what do i have to do
wait
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
bubble gum in my mouth and a wool hat on
my
uh
head
do you have to look like look for like
specific bubbles or can you dive like
anywhere
i think it's probably you need to look
for bubbles right
safety first oh one's done i'm done
nothing
i see bubbles
bubbles bubbles bubbles bubbles oh
where's that over there
what's that over there
wait wait wait where are the bubbles
i thought they were oh there they are
come on you can do it
here no did it go away
oh no no there it is
[Music]
it's been working out
oh
that is so funny
and i was like what is that but it's
something i placed there before i guess
oh
i can see other islands in the distance
wow
seaweed couldn't help myself
can i donate that or is that just trash
of the ocean
i mean with seaweed you could make a
snack out of it right
and those bubbles are really close to
the shore
and five
yeah you can cook it hmm
wait in the game are you saying you can
cook it in the game
ew i think you could cute
cute cucumber it's a bit cumbersome
uh-huh
you know i didn't know you were involved
in creating this game
i respect that though i wish i could
come up with those jokes
and style
oh turn around
this is such a great addition to the
game though when i heard that you could
swim in the game i was like yo that's so
great i mean i don't
i don't really
feel any
urge to play the game anymore but
being able to swim and dive
it feels like it should have been a
feature from the start because like
you're literally on a freaking island in
the beautiful ocean
why would you not be able to swim around
from the get-go
why else would you move to an island
who would move to an island and for the
first one year or whatever just ignore
the ocean completely and just fish
why why would you not swim in it
it just makes no sense
you're hot
oh i swam too far
there we go
if i donate this will i get the cafe
down
we're still not oyster it's a little
shellfish haha
all right go go go go go go
plateaus
can i uh
go back on land here on the stone
no
probably not here either
or maybe on that small
part there's like that little uh
beach
uh
on the back of the map right
donate and then time travel donate to
the museum right but i just don't have
enough things
can i
stop swimming please
okay
now i'm just gonna make my way back up
here
you're going to have to find bruce on an
island after talking to blathers
yeah i know i know i know about dad but
he doesn't even like offer me
don't wait a second
[Music]
wait wait wait that was a combined thing
huh right yeah
i guess he won't offer that to me until
i even have the possibility to go on the
boats tour which i didn't have so far
so that explains that
but now i swam for the first time so
wouldn't they finally gave me the option
to take the boat tour now if i
log out
and log back in
[Music]
okay
do i have to skip another day for that i
wonder
[Music]
just need to donate one of every type
okay so these are
uh
another new type perhaps
oh he takes seaweed as well
[Music]
do i have any unassessed fossils
go out of the museum and enter again
after donating you think i will do the
trick
i would hope
yeah it's actually specifically good
aussie day but still
thank you
wait did did i donate them i think i did
right
good
oh wait i did not did i
uh he already had the other ones i guess
t-rex girl are you sure you already have
dead
i only identified wait he didn't take
him
i didn't pay attention doesn't he take
them automatically when he assesses them
and he finds out you uh
i guess not
okay sorry to wake me up again
i love blabbers
blabbers is so cute he just talks too
much
oh t-rex skull you didn't have that yet
the statue was a fake right so i don't
have to try giving that to him again
why can't is there a bad ocean today
yeah no i don't think so
okay
wait i went out but he didn't offer me
anything so i guess i'll have to skip
another day and if that doesn't do that
trick that i'm giving up for today and
i'm gonna look it up on google
and tomorrow is my day off so i will
just play and play and play
until i get
the boats tour and the cafe but i wanted
i wanted it to happen on stream
[Music]
i wanted it to happen today
oh well
i couldn't donate those
did i have
them twice
really
i already wanted this stream to be over
by now
i want it but
[Music]
sometimes life just doesn't go the way
you want it to go
no gorilla tomorrow yeah i i need to
sleep early and
if i were to do a gorilla tomorrow i
would have no day off this week so
that's probably not a good idea
save and then
all right
last try
my last try and then if this doesn't
work then we're ending it
safe completely
yeah i am coming over there in a moment
just
let me change the date because i am god
i'm gonna play a little trick on your
nintendo switch gonna bamboozle you
gorilla
yeah this stream is a gorilla stream too
no i wouldn't have strained on my
channel anyway
originally
yeah
but the aqua senpai collab fell through
today unfortunately so
and i decided i'll just stream something
on my channel and it was destiny it was
destiny that an animal crossing got its
update early it's just not destiny that
i
was so far behind with
the whole
game
yeah
uh
oh
why is it
sixth
let's do this
does it say
6th november okay thank you
thank you for the orange super champion
and then close the game and open it back
up again let's go
the moment of truth
[Music]
at least the prologue is completed now
yeah
finally we did some progress we finished
another game today i can finally put
another game
i'm actually not even finally i've been
finishing so many games i think the only
game that i've ever
um
not finished
that's supposed to be finished normally
is uh sakuna no is that the only game i
dropped
i think all other games that i've
started on this channel all jrpgs
okay outlast no i don't really count
outlast because i didn't start it with
the intention of finishing it
super mario sunshine
true although i also didn't necessarily
start zipping my ascension with the
intention of finishing an either
and mario 64.
no no no mario games in my mind are not
made
to be finished ever
they are made to be um
destroyed
no but i do want to play some mario
games again sometime either 64 and
sunshine again or a different one i
don't mind i just want to play the mario
game again i don't know why but we are
playing um
super mario
uh
sorry brain freeze super
we're playing um
party uh
superstars right yeah yeah that's what
we're playing um uh on the day after
tomorrow with gouda mummy and amelia
watson on my channel i invited
them to play it with me thankfully they
accepted
the new one the new one that has like
all the old
uh
maps and i looked at the trailer and
when i saw the trailer i got so excited
because i saw so many maps that i know
from my gamecube um
mario party times
so i'm really excited for this nostalgic
feeling of playing old maps in a
renovated look yeah
are working now which means the update
is finally working
ordinance is a great way to help improve
the everyday lives of all of our
residents
they have quite a lot of responsibility
however and anyone enacting one should
understand everyone's needs
that's why our resident why do i hear
crackling noises
[Music]
and kiara will be in charge she's in
control no matter what she does yeah i
can't help it um please trust her
i'm sure she'll take good care of you
it's probably better to not try to stop
here
[Music]
which means now if i go to the museum
or do i have to go take a boat tour
first i think it should be fine if we go
to the museum now
and then he'll tell me oh he wants to
open a a
a cafe but the guy that he needs for it
is somewhere else can you find him and
then i'll go to
yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay
oh he's lifting
show me those muscles scoot
flexing on me
first thing in the morning
is the presence on the beach oh i didn't
notice let me check in a moment
hello oh he's awake he's awake he's
awake during the day that is such a rare
occasion
you got something to tell me huh
[Music]
why did he look so in love
pardon me i'm afraid i was quite lost in
fortress now you see there is a matter
which oh
actually your timing is impeccable as
ever perhaps you could help me
see i was thinking of ways to draw more
vlogs to our museum when i hit upon the
idea of adding a cafe
you stop my ideal bladders i came up
with that idea first kfp cafe mm-hmm
unfortunately
closed up shop and nobody appears to
know where he's gone
however in my search i also caught wind
of a nearly unearthed grip of
groins
that goes positive like
over groins urines how do i say that guy
words huh you see it's in much the same
way as i do around fossils
my very things wings that brewster has
heard about these gyroids as well
naturally you can see where this is
going i would like you to take up the
search of brewster okay
you know what his name is in germany
kofi kofi maybe in japanese as well
actually
i wonder why i didn't use coffee as well
in english because it works in as a pun
in english as well
um
okay
you wasted already so much time for me
oh wait why do i why why am i still
wearing that ugly outfit
oh and i was gonna put down the atm and
stuff oopsie well i don't think i'm
having any more people over today anyway
so that's okay um but
let me
wear a cute outfit um how about this
[Music]
don't you love it oh what are you doing
here no one's listening it's so sad
daddy
oh
i see
okay we gotta go
here
what up it's a cuppa
papada
away the name
your name is captain captain the captain
wait [\h__\h] oh my god it's a joke
that doesn't only
imply that he's a captain but also a
kappa
holy [\h__\h] that is so smart
that is so smart
oh
my brain is exploding
names
what's yours
well i came here to fairy folks on tours
to various way islands in exchange for
mario
my name is
[Music]
laughing and floaties
time to sense watch your step is your
husband bird no no no no no you won't
get that no floaties here
the sharks will eat you instead
[Music]
that's so cute
kiana
[Music]
i hope this is not like zelda skyward
sword where they're gonna be like girl
you [\h__\h] messed up again you were
supposed to be in rhythm
i already knew about uh the fact that
they were gonna see sing the sea
shanties i love that i wanna learn the
lyrics according to the melody and then
be able to nail it someday
yeah we've arrived
[Applause]
this is
[Music]
if we are wanting to set sail for home
okay i'm actually just here for the cafe
guys
why am i picking this up
[Music]
big
uh phoenix uh i don't really look like a
phoenix right now but trust me i'm a
phoenix i'm a verb just like you are and
i think you're gorgeous
i think you are gorgeous cool
you out here looking for i work too
and
not necessarily i want you
oh
you're looking at him
mind if i ask what you're after
brother sent me to find you
to create the kfb cafe the first one in
the whole wide world
i see
i hear you
ah tell him that for me
oh and also
oh
take this
this is yours if you want it it's a
gyroid fragment plant it in the ground
give it some water and sometimes it will
grow up strong the next day
thyroids take fruit fast when you return
them to the ground
well then we seeing you
he doesn't
tell enough bird puns to be honest
so i'm not quite happy i should have
brought a shovel but i think i can get
one from the dudes
let me go get a shovel
can i get a shovel
i need tools
maybe he'll wing it
[Music]
absolutely cracking
me up
100 miles for that shitty shovel for
sure
all right i guess i could have created
one on my own i guess
oh well
oh well there's a crafting table
ah
never mind uh where is it don't see it
oh
look i think there's a guy right here
too
all right so are you coming over to my
island or what
i guess ladder is my best
coco all right
he's a pigeon right
patients i love how they're like
appreciating the existence of pigeons
by creating that character
because pigeons
are being treated
like [\h__\h] all over the world and they
deserve better okay they might be
shooting all over the world
so it kind of makes sense to be getting
[\h__\h] on over all over the world as well
but i mean they have to poop somewhere
okay and they're just trying to
live their life and and i mean you know
they have a hard life no one wants them
children's run after them and are like
i want to catch you
and they never
they never have like a cozy warm home
because people don't want them in their
home
it's just sad the way the pigeons are
being treated yeah they're really cute
pigeons are adorable
and yet they only get crap food
and and and and everyone yelling at them
and saying they're ugly and
carry diseases and i mean maybe they do
but it's not their fault
yeah living on the street
it's not easy
pigeons are flying rats
no
don't say that
let's go
no don't hate on pigeons you guys are
chickens you think you're like that much
better than pigeons
i think i raised you chickens
to be not so freaking
evil i raised you as better chickens
than that
to be respectful of other birds
and kind-hearted and open-minded
we've adopted other birds at kfb already
other non-chicken
people
like owls and stuff and eagles
what's your problem with pigeons now
okay we're gonna give them some love
yeah
they're tasty
just the other day we have bonded over
loving dodos and now you say no to
pigeons really
what's your problem
be kind to one another
[Music]
huh
i want to learn this
[Music]
oh
i love these songs don't they don't they
have like a like a quite the big
inventory of songs quite a big set list
of sea shanties
when you go on these boat tours these
are not the only ones you can hear right
animal crossing yeah
i want to
hear more of those sea sandy's
so charming
i love it
do i have to go back to the museum now
and then wait another day
we can do one more time skip i just want
to see the cafe and then i'm happy
happiness
okay let's talk to blathers two days for
a cafe
okay so just skip two days or do i have
to be online on each day
i found him
[Music]
so i expect he'll make his way here
hopefully
what you what mate
i don't think i must make arrangements
for his arrival straight away
i'm afraid i'll need to close the museum
to all visitors tomorrow for
construction if everything goes as
planned we shall reopen the day after
next
the day after next month cafe service oh
it sounds like he only needs one day
it is two days really
okay all right no problem
easy you might
okay
all right
if we do this then
at least we have achieved our goal
for this stream so
i feel
obligated
to do another time skip
please bear with me until the end
pigeons are useful grateful falconry
excuse me how
don't tell me the eagles eat the pigeons
don't tell me that's what it is do they
just like
do do they just like playing with
pigeons
well how are pigeons helpful
there's a bear review
help there's a bear with me
help it's gonna eat me
birds eat birds
yeah you guys do you also eat chickens
eat chickens as well apparently okay of
me
eagles fight else to death oh my god
[Music]
okay
november
days yeah yeah from six to eight
i didn't close it
and open again
[Music]
oh i'm excited
cafe opening
are you guys playing animal crossing to
have your have you already opened your
cafe
are you maybe someone who doesn't want
to do time skips that's perfectly fine
too
that's really respectable animal
crossing players you don't skip the time
i just did i just did oh i don't want to
switch oh no
you're cute okay bye don't go yet
you're cute too
i think time skips are sinful
when you have to forgive me i'm doing it
for the sake of a stream if you were to
stream animal crossing without time
skipping then there is really not much
you can do in one day
in plain entire stream too not
that's addicted
you can play animal crossing while
watching me play animal crossing it's
not even that distracting i feel like
with other games it's a little bit more
difficult to
do that but with animal crossing it's
easy
it's for the content yeah
daily one hour animal crossing stream
yeah no i don't really think that that
would be a smart idea not a good
business idea
and takanashikiyada is a
business today
as amelia called me today
we were discussing something and i i
wrote this whole ass huge paragraph
uh telling telling them what i think
about a certain topic and then amelia
was like
you're totally right kia you're such a
business tony i was like
oh thank you
thank you kind of flattering
right now in australia it's 11 51 a.m on
monday november 8th 2021
now for today's announcements today our
museum welcomes a new international
campaign called
[Music]
that's so funny again
you all know first though maybe a bird a
few words but his coffee is so good it
can say it all for him
young curator has informed me that like
the museum the cafe will be open 24
hours a day
nice i like that
sounds good
i know i can't wait to duck in for duck
for a quick coffee break was that on
purpose and i bet a lot of you can't
wait either
and of course we'll be holding a special
ceremony to celebrate the happy news
if you're interested in participating
and half the time please check with tom
knock at resident services
i hope you all have uh i hope you all
enjoy the loveliest of lovely days
i hope so too
i hope everyone is having a lovely day
it's been kind of quiet with a whole lot
of english streams this week hasn't it
uh like ina
is kind of um taking the week off and
today and yesterday i feel like barely
anyone has been streaming
right good as has been taking it easy as
well right now um it's kind of like
quiet what is your problem
i'm thinking of maybe you know moving
away from this island and i totally need
your input
no [\h__\h] way
it's not that i don't love it here it's
just i need some adventure and
excitement
please don't leave
me
no pop star makes her fast cry so that
means no moving i'm here just taking it
out yeah you better
let's have all sorts of fun together
okay um
i don't even know how you
how you got the idea of leaving that's
ridiculous
[Music]
entering your next slide and there's the
usual room
no we can't put ani there
she's a pop star
do i need to say hello to you probably
not whatever whatever blabbers there is
a new bourbon town
whoa
cute logo
[Music]
isn't there supposed to be a room on the
right too
at some point
or is that for a later update
what room would there be on the right
side
anyway
no oh
[Music]
ah
hmm
[Music]
no why do i keep on closing my eyes
she's so weird why does she look
why does he make such a weird sound when
she closes her eyes once
no she keeps on closing her eyes
it's so nice here it's so relaxing i
want to go to the cafe right now
you know you're so little
i'm sorry i don't really drink coffee
though do you have like a smoothie or an
iced tea or something like that or it
can also be a hot tea i guess
actually he should have a lower voice
huh
[Music]
thanks well
thanks thank you folks thanks for
passing that message on back on that
remote island
you will find yourself in need of a cup
of coffee to swing on by
careful
[Music]
what the hell did i come here for
what excuse me
[Music]
i will force you to drink coffee because
that's what i'm here for
you better get used to it [\h__\h]
think that you won't regret it it's the
miracle juice
here you have one cup of the house
special drink up and enjoy
i hate coffee
i hate
coffee
uh
i found the blend i want to drink for
the rest of my life if if i want to end
my life right now that is
disgusting
take it away from
down me is divine exquisite you just
don't get it
thank you very much though for the money
keep it coming keep it coming
yeah i don't know but
i think you know coffee for me it has a
nice smell and all that but the taste i
hate i wonder if i'll ever get used to
it
i heard that you can like meet villagers
in the cafe or like bring them over i
guess you can invite them right how do i
do that
that's reserved seating what
who's coming
what
hey where are the signs then you should
put one of those signs and it's reserved
on the tables it's just normal
everyone does that
in restaurants and cafes
no
no i thought
i thought i could invite people over to
hang out with me or do you need to call
them with an amiibo
will they not come otherwise yeah
well
i don't have any amiibos
no i don't even own a single one
amiibo only i thought they come in here
just like for fun as well random
like how they also walk around the
museum uh
just randomly looking at pictures and
stuff
maybe it's just a timing thing
they come they do come in at random okay
i thought so okay okay well
well well well i am satisfied we did it
thank you guys for watching today for
coming to the spontaneous
animal crossing stream it was a long
time since the last one so i hope you
guys liked it and thank you for the
people who came over to give me some
presents and help me with cleaning up
the island and i'm sure there will be
another animal crossing stream sometime
soon fairly soon so please look forward
to that
and prepare some presents
yeah i'm looking forward to maybe
hanging out with the other whole live
english girls in animal crossing
gotta see when they're planning on
playing
and i don't know i'm not sure what to do
just check out their island and they
check out my island or something
whole live english island tours no more
minecraft tours no now we do animal
crossing island tours
did you see harvey island a bit ah no
not yet no
i guess yeah that's also something new
ah
[Music]
yeah i do i always wanted to do some
more island visitings visitations
so uh yeah clean up your islands polish
them until everything sparkles
you know the easiest way to do that is
by streaming sparks
[Music]
this is so cute we we just captured a
really special moment
don't you guys now kind of want a cuckoo
clock as a takanashikiya merchandise one
day
oh my god
wouldn't that be so cute
write that down cavey write that down
write that down
a cuckoo clock i wonder if that's
possible like before when i asked like
when it was like my birthday and i was
asked what kind of merchandise you
wanted and i was i asked them like what
is possible i was told like basically
anything anything you can imagine so
hmm
how do cool clocks even work i wonder
do they need batteries
that would be awesome that would be so
original i think
very expensive nah
shouldn't be too expensive i mean it's
it's
i guess i
i don't really remember i don't recall
any other whole life members merchandise
that's actually like
functional in a way like that like it
would have an actual mechanism inside of
it and do something
like that
but
i mean come on
there has been some really cool original
merchandise before
i wouldn't say it's impossible
gotta give it a try
martin has her computer all right there
we there you go then the cuckoo clock
is
not just a dream
it lies in our hands kfb
they're quite sturdy
i think so too i don't think it would
like really
make any issues but it would be
definitely something that one has to
look into and like how to create that
and how to make it like an original
takanashikiya clock
anyway anyway anyway
uh i don't think i'll be reading super
chats because um i want to try and sleep
early and also my throat hurts um
so i will not be reading super chats
right now but
the next stream will be
um mario party superstars collab on my
channel and then on sunday would be a
little nightmare so i think i would be
able to read it after little nightmares
i think yeah
sorry
yeah
a short screen though only three hours
new record
new record you all thought it would be
four hours but here we go it's three
hours
we did it we kept it short yeah
not really a record though i think i've
had shorter streams before
yeah yeah
but this is quite special
quite a special occasion
no please we need more ah
sorry i'm i'm gonna take
the rest of the
evening off hmm whole talk is shorter
usually yeah that's true
only because you skipped super chat
reading
yeah but that's generally i keep on
saying that the streams only end up
being so long because of super chat
readings most of the times
yeah but the game portions are usually
not that long
anyway i hope you had fun today
thank you for joining
see you
in the sports festival bales will be
streaming our perspective
um
yeah
i'm gonna try my best to practice a
little bit tomorrow gotta practice
flying
and the
the
ball game as well basketball gotta dunk
those
uh snowballs
okay and in germany nothing
such a nice cafe
i'm just gonna
sit here and chill
flirt with the pigeon i guess
[Music]
superstar
see you guys good night sleep well have
a nice day whatever wherever you are
whatever time it is have some good food
treat yourself
oh
um in the next
and thank you for the reminder
in the next
let's say five minutes
i want you guys to keep an eye on my
channel
and just refresh a couple times
little surprise from
um
your attention
because it's
the day of
the good oshie
all right then bye-bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]