[Music]
bye
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
a lot of first meetings today yeah
welcome everybody to today's
international collab
international karthik phone collab hey
yo welcome
thank you
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
okay
is
[Laughter]
me
[Music]
next
how many languages have i done anyways
um
i'm sorry this is the pain of being
multi-level um
today
um i'm kind of nervous because there's
like too many beautiful girls i'll try
my best
[Music]
i heard you're really good at drawing it
really i just regularly at least in
garden phone i heard you're good in
garage when people wanted me to invite
you
[Laughter]
[Music]
really okay yeah you're looking forward
to it i have high expectations
[Music]
first generation
i've played this game a million times by
now and so
i am not addicted not at all but i'm not
important
yay
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yeah i was like oh yeah i forgot to
introduce myself in english yeah
yeah yeah
slowly
[Laughter]
m
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
i see
[Music]
[Laughter]
hi
uh
okay
okay okay okay we are just gonna explain
the rules yes explain the rules so
this is an international collab
uh and then for the first round uh for
the prompt
for the prompt uh
easy
english okay easy english okay what is
easy english
[Music]
you guys can talk to your listeners as
much as you want you can also laugh at
my drawings
if you know which one it is
and then once uh the presentation starts
you can unmute and then we can uh talk
together about you know everybody's
drawings
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's have fun
everything okay but
you said
before uh
dismember only
about yes
[Applause]
okay
you can totally understand that
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay let's start let's i'm gonna
start in three two one and when
everything starts we can mute okay got
it
okay okay
[Music]
okay uh we have to start drawing um
how was the volume by the way i had a
hard time adjusting
oh can we um
i wonder do you guys think they'll
understand this
do you think they'll understand this oh
wait wait wait let's go um
i can't believe you seduce everyone here
let's do this
when i finish my drawing i want to turn
on the air conditioner it's getting hot
in here
sorry yeah i totally forgot to introduce
myself in english
student
okay
how am i going to draw them
where everyone knows
oh wait
so apparently i'm i'm gonna be wait oh
wait maybe i should bust out my pen tab
wait
honestly it's not gonna make any
difference at all
okay there we go
pen tab time the only thing is my hand
shakes a lot
okay you know what maybe i shouldn't use
a 10 pen tab
does this look like a sailor outfit i'm
trying to draw a sailor outfit
i
this kind of looks like twin tails for a
second why i wonder why um
i'm trying to draw sailor outfit sailor
outfit
okay there we go there we go
okay
i should add color yeah you know what
okay i'm going to get rid of my pen tab
i draw better without the pen tab nope
nope nope
oh yeah i do not have stable hands
this this totally looks like a student
an energy and student
that's about it right
no team to describe this scene
uh
olly zombie hand go wild
that's really nice drawing i wonder who
drew that
you can totally tell what's going on
very nice drawing
hmm
okay nene g plus iris child
okay okay
what do you guys consider is neneji
senpai's hair color it's like a nice you
know
blonde ish pinkish blonde and it's like
a little hint of pink blonde it's kind
of hard to
write that but we'll try anyways
oh my god there's not enough time
okay you know what i wonder if it's
bad for me to be writing words
and this is supposed to be me yes
magenta hair equals
equals iris
[Laughter]
and we're like in like little bundles
little baby looking bundles
okay okay
these are the hands there we go there we
go
ah perfect okay i'm gonna go turn on the
air conditioner real quick i'll be right
back
okay
horns horns horns that's true that's
true
okay there we go there you go
okay
ah
now it's your turn to describe this
scene
uh
three eggs oh
olly mass genius
oh my god everyone's so good at drawing
and wait are they all using pen tabs i
think they are yeah
it's okay
it doesn't make a difference whether i
use pen tab or mouse or not whatever
it's all good it's all good
ollie teaches math ah it does kind of
look like that that's true
um
okay
oh my god this is hard okay
by the way justify i do still draw
better
um
with uh
just like you know not computer drawings
okay
there we go and then
i'm having a hard time drawing nina's
hair
i thought
looks like a little like sailor moon
here for some reason when i try to draw
it
okay
and then
oh wait why doesn't it look right here
i want to make them around the same
height
and then
yeah
okay that looks totally cute like kiara
right that does totally look like yara's
in five
ah
okay tiny small chiara yay happy happy
happy family ah
perfect
i draw chicken ah that was a good idea
that was a good idea it's okay
it's important that they get the whole
picture
of it
i know my feelings
i put my whole heart and soul into this
i know that they will understand my
feelings they'll understand
what i wanted to do okay
hello
yo it's done
yay
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
no more students
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah i do know that they do that yeah
okay
is anyone gonna save the gifts or the
the sorry legit
okay
okay okay i saved
yay
okay nice
oh another high school
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
there's a flat there's there's something
there's something on her chest what does
that see on her chest
[Laughter]
[Music]
can't think of any genius math problems
sorry
ollie
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
surprisingly i know exactly what you
were trying to convey thank god
baby kiara
you
that's the only way i can i can you know
show off my skills stick on yeah your
statements yeah i stick my skills
that's good you always need like when
you play garlic phone it's good to have
uh people who are good at art and people
who are better than you mix them
together for a great great moment are
you suggesting that i'm bad at art are
you suggesting good luck
yeah i'm
i'm obviously one of the one of the
better ones right yeah
obviously
okay okay next next
iris
fusion
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yes i did because they were like oh
maybe you should get rid of the the
words it's cheating so i thought
[Laughter]
oh god
[Music]
[Laughter]
next
it's very good
[Laughter]
[Music]
next
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
is
i love you guys i love you i love you
[Laughter]
in three two
i did not get approval
you can practice
[Music]
the e-cable academy
academy
do you like fishing
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you like fishing
[Music]
do you wanna be my hot wings
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
please
[Laughter]
okay three
two one
[Laughter]
hotel
[Music]
i need a funny prompt come on chad yeah
i need i need your problem too help me
help me a problem give me give me prompt
give me yeah give me a promise
i don't wanna think i just wanna ask
chad
okay okay okay
okay okay come on chad come on chad come
on okay
okay actually i didn't need to chat
oh okay you can
give me the idea then
okay then uh so we're gonna separate i'm
gonna miss you guys it's so lonely
without you guys
it is
really quiet
okay see you guys soon
[Music]
okay okay um prompt prompt prompt uh
wait wait oh wait where'd the window go
okay okay
oh we're gonna type in japanese right
um
suit
here
let's go with that
was i supposed to type in romaji was i
supposed to type in romaji i'm not so
sure anymore
um
okay
sexy
wait
can we uh how do i i'm kind of trying to
do that kauri pose that quota pose with
reina
uh
raina's hair is gray
ah let's draw short hair reina
okay there we go there we go yeah sexy
sexy radius sexy right now
aha
uh-huh
[Laughter]
from the 3.0 movie but i don't i don't
know how to draw it
i have a lot of time i can't i can't fit
something else anyway um
under the night sky
oh wait no
okay there we go
over here there we go there we go there
we go there we go
oh you know that this is gonna look
different this is gonna look different
oh it's okay
it's okay to get okay
this looks like 1688 all right 16 okay
okay
i tried to draw i tried to do the whole
um the
evangelion counter scene okay um now
it's your turn to describe this scene oh
nice
hot wings
wait
is it romaji is it romaji i'm not so
sure anymore
ah
did it did it type it in did it type it
in oh god okay um
uh me
let's draw
but six
eight eight
let's use our time wisely shall we
i'm rushing i'm rushing i'm rushing does
this look like
does this look like the lips to you guys
that's it
this is supposed to see six of us i
don't have enough time to draw every
single
even the stick figures are starting to
become very scuffed is it just me
hey
okay okay
it's okay hand count head count guys and
count
head count over
ninja
okay there we go there we go
oh wait i might have time to draw
wait
almost there almost there almost there
okay there i got the hair colors
i got the hair colors
asia
this is raining
rocket is this rain a rock yet
reyna rocket
it's nice i do like rain a rocket
it's she's supposed to be a turkey right
rain is a turkey can turkeys fly they
should be able to fly right
how do i draw this oh my god that's hard
okay um
first let's draw reina first
with the blue pin
is it okay for me to just draw the words
because this is hard it
okay let's draw
arena that's
tall and proud
uh
i wonder what the power level of the
holobirds are
i wonder what the the the the power
levels of the hollow birds are
so basically this is rayna supposed to
be like oh that was easy that was easy
that's what it means in japanese
so i'm assuming she defeated someone
easily let's do that that's a
yeah over 9 000.
there we go
i do know what i do wonder what the
power i feel like i don't know if kiara
senpai
it's okay it's okay i saw i saw words i
saw words on some people's stuff it's
over 9 000.
only number fine fine but it's like they
can find out anyways that i wrote wait
let's
9 000.
okay
there we go there we go
there we go couldn't i get it started i
hope i hope they get it with just the
number
um
[Music]
i missed you guys i'm so sorry i think i
messed one thing up because i didn't
press enter uh when i was supposed to
write the the answer to a prank
i know
i had the same problem too
ah okay yeah
okay
then they caught up close yeah mine
yeah sometimes i do that too
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
yeah sorry it didn't go through
you got it
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i
it overpowered your brains
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
we're so in sync everyone drew it like
the same way yeah even without my prompt
yeah it's
amazing
it's amazing i wasn't able to press
enter right away like in in time i guess
i did type something yeah
it was just
i understand
next one next though okay
wow
[Music]
very
[Laughter]
everyone
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
i'm trying to say i'm the weakest hollow
bird but hey i'm a phoenix i cannot be
killed in the first place that's true
it will rise up after this
yeah
how it went from energy's
it is very easy to that drawing
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
from the sky
it became space
i'm going outside yeah i'm going out to
space turkey in space
[Music]
you guys don't seem to acknowledge my
existence as a phoenix so i will do the
same thing
[Music]
uh i will acknowledge your existence as
a people okay thank you my beautiful
feelings next
[Music]
easy japanese
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
teaching the wrong
[Laughter]
[Music]
go on
[Laughter]
i know
[Music]
[Laughter]
wrote the title of today's collaboration
is
[Laughter]
he's just laughing
yes
how are we gonna mix it okay
mix
[Music]
japanese
oh
[Music]
japanese
so shitty japanese skyva okay
okay come on chad give me problems yeah
give me props
[Music]
get with the
feast
me
who would sound like they would say that
who who would sound like they would say
hontony fisto me
i feel like kiara would say that qris if
i would say that ah
kiara
okay
a lot of a lot of shipping going on a
lot of shipping going on this garcic
phone
okay wait
let's draw the usual
wait
okay so
in a nice wedding dress
okay i can draw some
some flowers
bouquet
and then
i
okay and then
there's
kiara you can mention
in a tuxedo
i'm gonna draw the tuxedo okay
is
i don't know this is starting to look
like chef kiara
steph kiara
and then we can draw
a bell
ding dong
okay
marriage
marriage okay this looks perfect perfect
perfect perfect
top that kiara i don't know i feel like
that hat just fits it fits well it's
well
okay uh
it's your turn to describe the scene
huh
ah
what is this wait wait
uh
[Music]
pokemon
i did it again i did it again ah
another blank script
[Music]
okay
i wasn't able to make the script in time
okay um
okay
olly
olly laughing like crazy let's go with
that
ah maybe i should be typing words okay
okay
hahahaha iris what
oh oh yeah i'm saying idiots
uh
okay
i know how to take i know how to do this
okay there there there there there this
is perfect this is perfect
ah this is perfect
okay
yeah this is from um the the
conversation before yeah it captures it
very well
where ollie was laughing about how iris
in indonesia means
uh
thinly sliced stuff i think
i feel so bad for not being able to
write the prompt though it just kind of
ruins everything
no not yandere or iris no no no no
uh to describe this scene ah
[Laughter]
what's it what's it the the the chest
ah
iris iris
[Music]
listening the
music
[Laughter]
let's go let's just write regular music
okay
um
irish drunk mermaid yo butter
i never get drunk i never get drunk how
would how would i draw a mermaid iris
wait
okay
because i'm doing stick
figures but i guess i'll draw a tail
wait
okay there we go there we go
wait does that
let's try that again
okay there we go there we go does that
look like a mermaid too
you know why i want to do this again
there we go there we go that looks a
little better
okay there okay okay
okay
okay how am i gonna draw that i'm that
it's drunk uh
uh
let's draw uh
alcohol looking
alcoholic drink
alcoholic drink does that look like
does that look like alcohol to you guys
it should right it looks pretty much
like alcohol
okay there we go
wait let's draw
the handle this way
okay there we go there we go there we go
this is so random
so random
by the way that is just lemon soda that
is not
that is not alcohol
um
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
we have rainy what did i write
listening
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
was the pun intended
music here
[Music]
this one is perfect yeah
excuse me
[Music]
i get it
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay nice irish drums
[Laughter]
[Music]
beautiful
[Laughter]
[Music]
i totally forgot it's okay the hair
color color hair color gives it away
that's true that's true
okay next
video
laughing laughter
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
ah
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
wtf
oh
[Laughter]
um
okay
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
no no no
already
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
that was so much fun
um
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
um
[Laughter]
oh
feelings
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign want to hear about
how you feel about the game today
yes irish classic comments please close
and comment please
one thing i know is that there are
always there are never mistakes only
happy accidents
[Laughter]
agreed
okay well i don't comment
yeah uh for everyone it was a really
really fun collab thank you so much for
having me
[Laughter]
are you aware that hot wings is my
nickname
oh no i don't oh it is oh yeah now you
know
you know
i got hot wings just another term for
like getting turned on
oh no it's a nickname that my
fans gave me a while ago ah
the organizational
part of this collaboration oh thank you
thank you dana
yes thank you
everybody is
very unique in their interactions we
have
unique interactions today i mean
um congratulations to kiara senpai too
getting punched by ninety crore congrats
a new complicated relationship is born i
don't know how to feel about this but i
am very happy to be able to organize
this collab
thank you for inviting us thank you so
much for the invite
[Music]
yes closing comments uh
first of all i'm sorry for drawing only
in an etsy position but that's not mine
i loved it it's okay
um
and um
the good thing is i came out with uh a
realization about iris
today
i found out that iris the reason she
hates santa claus so much is because she
used to be an elf for santa i mean just
look at her ears
no no no no
they're nephilim ears
irish was fired from santa claus's uh
factory because she did a bad job and
they had a lot of issues i have a very
clean resume i have a clean resume
there's no such thing as being fired no
no no no no no no santa saying that you
were never on uh
christmas elf for santa claus
no the north pole no no i would never
work under santa why would i well then i
need a proof for that i need a pro for
that proof
need proof
yeah we'll see about that so thank you
for letting me participate i had a lot
of fun today thank you thank you
thank you
yeah
today
today i enjoy this member and i'm
drawing isolation
back
internet
but
english testo
keeps
[Music]
please
go back to the hotel
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay everybody i'll see you guys later
bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
darkness will fade away
hope has descended and you are not alone
[Music]
oh
darkness
[Music]
you