​​​ ​This hot spring is ​really hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm driving my UFO right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd like to hear about​ ​​
​​ ​today's special at KFP.​ ​​
​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise Calls ​Minus the Surprise​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise​ Calls ​Minus the Surprise​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise Calls Minus the Surprise​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise​ Calls Minus the Surprise​ ​​
​​​ ​La-lion!​ ​​
​​​ ​On the main channel, la-lion!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway, good morning!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Shishiro Botan.​ ​​
​​​ ​And here I am in a video​ ​​
​​ ​on the main channel​ ​​
​​​ ​doing the opening all by myself.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is giving me a bit of anxiety here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, to explain what we're doing today,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's an official surprise call program!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​By myself, yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay yay yay yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Peace peace!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're going to surprise call​ ​​
​​ ​these three people today!​ ​​
​​​ ​From 4th Gen, Tsunomaki Watame!​ ​​
​​​ ​Next, from ID, Airani Iofifteen!​ ​​
​​​ ​And finally, from EN, Takanashi Kiara.​ ​​
​​​ ​Making surprise calls all over the world!​ ​​
​​​ ​This should be fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​A-chan​ ​​
​​​ ​But!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Actually, these aren't​ ​​
​​ ​regular surprise calls!​ ​​
​​​ ​We told these three in advance​ ​​
​​ ​that they'd get a call today!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're ready and waiting​ ​​
​​ ​to have a little fun with the call!​ ​​
​​​ ​A-chan​ ​​
​​​ ​And also!​ ​​
​​​ ​Botan has been acting like she doesn't know​ ​​
​​ ​anything about this, but she does!​ ​​
​​​ ​Basically...​ ​​
​​​ ​it's all a put-on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now then, how will these surprise calls go?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay! Who's our​ ​​
​​ ​very special first participant?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's 4th Gen's Tsunomaki Watame!​ ​​
​​​ ​Watame-senpai is first.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder what she's up to.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's give her a call!​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise call starts now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Exciting.​ ​​
​​​ ​I really do wonder what's she doing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Excitement. Excitement!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​How are you doing?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm good!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah? What are you up to right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​I was just about to get in the bath.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're gonna take a bath?​ ​​
​​​ ​Right in front of me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​You sure about that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Where are you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Getting in the bath, so at home?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I'm not.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm at a hot spring!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm naked as a jaybird right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna get in now, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're naked?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, can I?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna hop in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​Splash!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, did you rinse yourself first?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Do what now?​ ​​
​​​ ​You gotta rinse yourself before you get in!​ ​​
​​​ ​What now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bath Manners​ ​​
​​ ​Before you get in, use a bucket of hot water​ ​​
​​ ​to rinse your body of excess dirt.​ ​​
​​​ ​You gotta rinse your body to​ ​​
​​ ​get rid of dirt before you get in!​ ​​
​​​ ​This hot spring's kinda brown and murky.​ ​​
​​​ ​It says...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, one of those.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's... huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​This hot spring is ​really hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​There are green onions​ ​​
​​ ​and stuff in here! Weird!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds like a boiling issue.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is there anything else in there?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Tofu...​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirataki noodles...​ ​​
​​​ ​Shirataki noodles?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are the benefits of the hot spring written?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​- Health Benefits -​ ​​
​​​ ​Highly nutritious.​ ​​
​​​ ​Packed with protein.​ ​​
​​​ ​- Health Benefits -​ ​​
​​​ ​Highly nutritious...​ ​​
​​​ ​Weird, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​- Watame Stew -​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, ain't this a stew?!​ ​​
​​​ ​The protein they mentioned...​ ​​
​​​ ​they probably mean you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my god!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm getting out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, get out!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm outta here!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're in trouble.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I got a little bit scalded.​ ​​
​​​ ​I bet.​ ​​
​​​ ​My body's stinging a bit.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I dry my hair now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's soaking wet.​ ​​
​​​ ​The way this is going​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm expecting some sear marks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everything should be fine now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ow ow ow ow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that actually a hair dryer?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oww!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is different from​ ​​
​​ ​any hair dryer I know!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ow ow ow ow!​ ​​
​​​ ​This thing's a blowtorch!​ ​​
​​​ ​For cooking​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a blowtorch! A blowtorch!​ ​​
​​​ ​(the sound of meat sizzling)​ ​​
​​​ ​You really are getting sear marks!​ ​​
​​​ ​Blowtorch! Owwie!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anything weird with your body right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Anything weird?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's getting harder to move, I think.​ ​​
​​​ ​Crispy texture achieved.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're on the verge of becoming a meal.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a plate on this conveyor belt, so I'm​ ​​
​​ ​gonna get on that and head over your way.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really? I'll await your arrival.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​What a crazy place to be in.​ ​​
​​​ ​A food processing plant.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm back!​ ​​
​​​ ​You were at a hot spring?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure was.​ ​​
​​​ ​More like sure wasn't!​ ​​
​​​ ​And that's the end of the surprise call!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now Watame-senpai is here!​ ​​
​​​ ​How was it?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's your rating?​ ​​
​​​ ​60 out of 100, I guess?​ ​​
​​​ ​That low?​ ​​
​​​ ​Lower than I thought!​ ​​
​​​ ​A sixty, I'd say.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a tough one.​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm an idol,​ ​​
​​​ ​so having to act like a comedian​ ​​
​​ ​wasn't in my plans.​ ​​
​​​ ​What? I thought you were a meal.​ ​​
​​​ ​You went there?!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next surprise call is going to...​ ​​
​​​ ​Airani Iofifteen from hololive ID!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh! Iofi!​ ​​
​​​ ​You do a lot of collabs with​ ​​
​​ ​Iofi-senpai, don't you, Watame?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is Iofi-senpai normally like?​ ​​
​​​ ​She's cute.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder if we'll see that cuteness today,​ ​​
​​ ​when we surprise call her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see what Iofi-senpai is up to.​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise call starts now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring ring ring! Ring ring ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? Who's this?​ ​​
​​​ ​At this hour?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this Iofi-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's me, the biggest brain alien, Iofi.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whatcha need?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Shishiro Botan​ ​​
​​ ​with Tsunomaki Watame.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you two!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's been a while!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, it has!​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-senpai, what are you up to right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm taking a little drive.​ ​​
​​​ ​A drive?!​ ​​
​​​ ​A drive...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Where are you driving to?​ ​​
​​​ ​Space.​ ​​
​​​ ​Driving in space...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's very pretty.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm driving my UFO right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, that's so romantic!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you have a driver's license?​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you need a license for a UFO?​ ​​
​​​ ​I do!​ ​​
​​​ ​You need one!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you do.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you need a license!​ ​​
​​​ ​Seems so.​ ​​
​​​ ​Definitely.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd say it's harder to drive than a normal car.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, like a special heavy vehicle license?​ ​​
​​​ ​You probably don't know that.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's a special heavy vehicle license?​ ​​
​​​ ​Special Large Motor Vehicle License level?​ ​​
​​​ ​Medium​ ​​
​​ ​vehicles​ ​​
​​​ ​Heavy special​ ​​
​​​ ​There's like a special license you need​ ​​
​​ ​to drive some large vehicles.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Something like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​So it's lumped into that class.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​How far from Earth are you right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can see the constellation Leo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so pretty.​ ​​
​​​ ​Woohoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanna go there?​ ​​
​​​ ​So you're millions of light-years away right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Leo​ ​​
​​ ​A constellation 80 light-years from Earth.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right? Just how far away are you?​ ​​
​​​ ​How many years should we wait for you?​ ​​
​​​ ​How many years?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd say about twenty minu—​ ​​
​​​ ​Nah,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll just head there immediately!​ ​​
​​​ ​You can make it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I can.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're coming back? You sure?​ ​​
​​​ ​Should be right away!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just wait for me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, this is a surprise call.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now arriving​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Totally.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's here!​ ​​
​​​ ​See!​ ​​
​​​ ​She made it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fast, ain't I?​ ​​
​​​ ​And now Iofi-chan is here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Iofi-senpai, have you ever done​ ​​
​​ ​any surprise calls like this?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I don't think I've ever done any.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​I asked some pretty crazy stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​Were you okay with that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Easy-peasy!​ ​​
​​​ ​On the easy side, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, for me, every day​ ​​
​​​ ​is nothing but chaos,​ ​​
​​​ ​so this was no problem.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every day is chaos!​ ​​
​​​ ​Every day is chaos for you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, every day is just chaos upon chaos.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds rough!​ ​​
​​​ ​So this was nothing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring it!​ ​​
​​​ ​On to the next one!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the last surprise call.​ ​​
​​​ ​Last but not least is​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara from hololive EN!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thoughts?​ ​​
​​​ ​About Kiara?​ ​​
​​​ ​Fried chicken!​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanna eat Kiara?​ ​​
​​​ ​A fellow food friend?​ ​​
​​​ ​Continuing our cooking (?) special,​ ​​
​​​ ​we'll see what Kiara's up to.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's find out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Surprise call starts now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring ring ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ring ring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​The president of KFP, though​ ​​
​​ ​they call me the manager,​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive EN's Takanashi Kiara here!​ ​​
​​​ ​What can I do for you today?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello? It's Shishiro Botan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm here with Watame and Iofi.​ ​​
​​​ ​'Sup!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​My senpais!​ ​​
​​​ ​My senpais, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a little busy at the moment,​ ​​
​​​ ​but if it's you guys,​ ​​
​​​ ​I can make some time.​ ​​
​​​ ​What were you doing?​ ​​
​​​ ​Busy busy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right now,​ ​​
​​​ ​I was just chewing out my KFP employees.​ ​​
​​​ ​KFP: The fast-food chain that Kiara runs.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh? What happened?​ ​​
​​​ ​They're having a little meltdown​ ​​
​​ ​over their salary.​ ​​
​​​ ​Should you be telling us this?​ ​​
​​​ ​How much do you pay them?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh... well...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a... at-will.​ ​​
​​​ ​The paycheck is...​ ​​
​​​ ​also at-will (free).​ ​​
​​​ ​The paycheck is also at-will (free).​ ​​
​​​ ​So the people who show up​ ​​
​​ ​just really wanna work for you?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​But after that,​ ​​
​​​ ​the chickens—​ ​​
​​​ ​all my employees are chickens,​ ​​
​​ ​by the way.​ ​​
​​​ ​But chickens have a birdbrain memory.​ ​​
​​​ ​They keep complaining to me about it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right.​ ​​
​​​ ​So they forget.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really!​ ​​
​​​ ​What? What? Don't bother me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pay us​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm on the phone right now!​ ​​
​​ ​Don't bug me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm talking to my senpais right now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't touch me!​ ​​
​​​ ​N-No touchy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pay us​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, don't...​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't touch me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where are you carrying me?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Stooop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is she about to get fried?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no!​ ​​
​​​ ​Should we help her?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't touch!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's been taken away.​ ​​
​​​ ​Help me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Help me!!​ ​​
​​​ ​By the way,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd like to hear about​ ​​
​​ ​today's special at KFP.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm quite hungry, so yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you have a Kiara burger?​ ​​
​​​ ​New menu item: The Kiara Burger!​ ​​
​​​ ​New menu!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​We aim to please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to have you, uh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm exhausted.​ ​​
​​​ ​come by after this.​ ​​
​​​ ​But are you okay? Can you?​ ​​
​​​ ​If you want me there, I'll be there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. I'll come by!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, we'll be waiting.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll see you here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Freshly delivered.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fresh 'n' hot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Made to order.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's here and ready!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​She's ready!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pipin' hot Kiara?​ ​​
​​​ ​I am not!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pipin' hot!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not, seriously!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you always get fried up like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, that was the first time!​ ​​
​​​ ​First time?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​First time!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's usually the opposite!​ ​​
​​ ​The other way around!​ ​​
​​​ ​So then...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, they're tasty.​ ​​
​​​ ​You feed your employees​ ​​
​​ ​to the customers?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a lucrative business.​ ​​
​​​ ​The Dark Side of KFP​ ​​
​​ ​A cruel work environment.​ ​​
​​​ ​So-called​ ​​
​​ ​KFP president​ ​​
​​​ ​Selling your employees as food.​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you like​ ​​
​​ ​doing this in Japanese?​ ​​
​​​ ​It was fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm looking forward to more!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm happy to hear that!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna do more of these!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's have some fun again sometime!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, let's have some fun!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do a collab!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Absolutely!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do another cross-border​ ​​
​​ ​collaboration sometime!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye-bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please ​like this video and subscribe to​ ​​
​​ ​this ​channel ​and the ​talents' ​channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye-bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Byebyebye!​ ​​