[Music]
do
uh
i was just here where did i go
you guys don't see me do you
i disappeared oh there i am
what what what
what
obs what did you just hear that
i can't get it
obs what when i open that
capture window here i am going to close
it like i mean it's still like
i just want to like open the properties
and it's there but when i close the
properties it's gone
uh but when i turn it into studio mode
i'm here though
i just updated obs because there was an
update out
and interesting something is
weird something is ah wait how do you
say that
something is something something's
uh something's not cheesy not stinky
something's fishy yeah fish
sounds yummy eh
the screen froze yeah i'm moving
come on
am i moving is it frozen obs
says hello i'm moving
is it you see me okay okay
yeah really huh bro huh
that was frozen for me i'll go okay why
is the game not on the screen
oh there we go okay i don't know what's
going on
but let's
[Music]
wait let me let me turn you down a
little bit
[Music]
should i be holding my cat while doing
this huh
wait wait a second
[Laughter]
plates
something like that
oh oh
jonkers
cute cat
cat petting cat perfect
perfect
look yeah
i still didn't download the the the new
version of
smoothie so we're still petting changes
free oh
oh oh
[Music]
this cute they say perfect
me okay possum
ah it's not cute i wanted to show you
that
no i don't have three or four hands
anymore now shut up shut up
you see what i'm seeing now right it's
confusing me
everything's weird today
oh actually let me refresh them
chat on my son it's kind of like delayed
what the hell
how are you guys doing by the way
[Music]
how are you how are you
sure every time i tap out of the window
sorry the music stops
on have you guys recovered from
two 12 hour two back to back 12 hour
streams
have you guys recovered i kind of did
i'm feeling fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
as good as always how are you i'm fine
sleepy tired and what
[Music]
i'm good just ate my cat what the [\h__\h]
i don't like you that is um
a terrible joke terrible joke
kind of has some weird delay today we're
covered just fine
no it's good to hear that
and ready for another 12. no no no we're
not doing another 12 today
we're probably gonna play this game for
one hour and then
just read more of the remaining super
chat but it shouldn't be that much
left over so i think we will be fine
so this is the first time i'm playing
this i guess we have to start with
tutorial
actually there's a new remount that
version of this coming out soon but i
couldn't find anymore
i wanted to do cat things i wanted to be
a basket a bad kitty yet
so let's do it let's learn how to play
cat lateral damage okay
how long have we turned okay knock
objects
onto the floor how do i move okay knock
offs under the floor there's no objects
here uh-huh
oh jump squats right
okay okay i got it okay let's go up here
yeah oh wow those jumps
powerful jumps eat yeah
as expected from kitty cat can i can i
swatch this don't know
how how do i become stronger how do i
become strong cat
i need to get need to go to the plant
no
[Music]
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you i did it
but they still ah painting
but it's a beautiful it's a beautiful
cat
i don't want to eat that that's that's
oh that's nippy oh how why would i eat
that okay we gotta
do some acrobatics here
yourself oh
what a beautiful kitty cat
that's me apparently what else
a pot
[Music]
yes
now go make some messes easy
meowville's coke with meows did that
break
yeah if i've only gotten 12 hours of
sleep these humans will pay
stubborn humans get 170 objects
whoa okay that's a lot four minutes
okay okay what what that's a lot of
objects but okay
can we do it can we do it
what is this [\h__\h] socks they look so
so stiff what the hell where did you buy
those socks horrible socks
[Music]
these are a bit hard to move what the
hell is that [\h__\h] that
and just yeah yeah okay
quick quick quick gotta hurry
yeah i don't like this the positioning
of this doesn't sh it doesn't fit my
feng shui that's that's that
thing
i wanted to say something but i better
not say it or should i say it
[Music]
those sensitive dvds very
sensitive oh god i don't have much time
three minutes left but i'm already at
50 heated items [\h__\h] those whatever
let's find something easier
there must be something easier food
never enough always have to drink out of
somewhere else
event what's a power up has a pit
power power oh can i be strong cat
did i get it did i get it
did i get it how do i get it don't have
to go inside
what oh
yummy yeah foreign
[Music]
does it just eat everything in my way
where am i
where am i i want to make use of this
but i don't know where i am
okay okay we heated for some things i
want to go to the next room is this
where i came from here okay
let's go to that room yeah oh well i
already made a mess here
no no my first field
my first field yeah
oh it's over okay
can i go higher uh it's tough when you
don't see that much huh
what i know i was not here as [\h__\h]
i should have came here no
can we destroy tv can we destroy the tv
huh my my parents have
enough money anyway
[Music]
new upgrade oh what is that
sweat increased
maximum power did i eat those things
did i do it did i do it
[Music]
i'm such a bad kitty cat but in a
different kind of way
maybe the next room is easier
[Music]
oh no she's walking in front of me hi hi
hi hi smoothie i love you
you're watching me being a cat time's up
oh sweet oh baby
did i still like kind of like make it
leave i just
uh
favorite object
yeah did i fail
later box mode this little box
[Music]
oh orange cat that's me now
what is this
what is this what is this guys
that was me awful shut up i'm trying my
best
ah forgot slow-mo i think i thought i
had that turned on
okay
uh turn it on now that's for sure
sandbox mode well i don't understand
but i guess that's something else okay
objective no let's go
round two i still have the same room i
really not
no way there's a different room is it
but will i unlock new rooms
with time free home is pretty obvious
let's go
okay you can already start the time
eight minutes oh okay
that's a lot of time guys
i hate drugs although actually my cats
love playing with socks every once in a
while so who in the audience has cats
hmm
who owns kitty cats tell me tell me
what's what's their names what did you
name your cats
i wanted to uh show me your cat's stream
[Music]
me me me me i subbed to a kid
they mean me i have two cats sphinx cats
oh
[\h__\h] you can we make that jump yeah
[Music]
okay professor
amber pillow that's a good name
event a free upgrade has appeared we're
not coming i'm coming
okay i'm doing better than before i
think yeah
[Music]
and i sprint no no oh my father was a
rainbow
[Music]
or not i was just talking about wanting
to dash
what you upgrade whoa can i have two
upgrades at the same time
wow yeah
wait wait get that out of the way
there goes the high okay
[\h__\h] all of these things why is there
balls up here anyway huh
come on
those are all fake books anyway you
never read them do you
just want to look smart stupid humans
i'm smarter than you
it's me outer
[Music]
fubu and misty making spoon mittens cute
name
you know cats actually hate when you
call themse
just telling i heard it from the other
cats
they feel like you're making fun of them
wow wow go away
that's not an actual game is it that is
not a real game
oh upgrade scratch my nails so i
can scratch my owner's face even better
skies look cool you know makes you
stronger
sorry i actually like dogs
[Music]
but cats are superior
and who owns a doggo in the audience now
we know who owns cats but who owns dogo
ew flowers always bothered me stupid
flowers
stupid flowers always bothers me goes in
that spot
i don't like the book scene if i don't
like this picture get it
what kill the clothing right there what
i don't see it
all right
[Music]
i got it
that's cool you're special
[Music]
see those plates in those cups
wait i need to get up there
[Music]
huh
professional cat i am professional cat
what is it what is it jump oh nice nice
nice
yo holy [\h__\h] yeah that's what i wanted i
was hoping for matt's
uh jump [\h__\h]
never
[Music]
i'm a little bit of a clumsy cat
okay okay that's okay i wanted to go to
the to the one above that but we can do
it we can do it myself
two minutes maybe i shouldn't bother
with this room anymore though
what about here it was already here huh
it was here too i think so there's there
must be another room
am i spinning at my room here look at
this one oh
is my is my jump still max no i don't
think so love it
oh
candies
yes yes those are easy dolls are easy
now
clumsy chaotic cat love my chicken cat
excuse me i'm a real cat i'm a real cat
that's why my own cats love me so much
whoa yes yes
for this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] this this is too
dangerous when it's on the table it's
better if it's on the ground believe me
trust me trust me with this one
i always eat from the ground i mean like
a little little plate you
my owners put me on the ground but but i
don't even need that i can just eat from
the ground yeah you guys are stupid you
need tools for that you can just use
your hands
and your mouth actually not even your
hands who needs hands when you have a
mouth
huh think think ona
think human think think logically for
once
[Music]
we almost have it oh my god
new upgrade well i don't need that
anymore now but i'll take it
wow
did i miss a room by the way i think
there was one more over there huh
i didn't even need it wait i can still
continue
i know i go i go to the fruitful map
oh let's go
nice box nice box ooh
comfy
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] this looks dangerous
perfect let's make some things go boom
and then make all humans die yeah
that's that's the spirit let's poison
them let's have a big explosion
yeah yeah
i want them all to die cats are superior
oh it's right is that smoke on the
ground dangerous
perhaps i cannot risk
my own life
huh who ate that that was for me
can we eat that
[Laughter]
okay this one no yeah
frame rate yes for real
are we having issues with the frame rate
have seven lives wait where huh
in the game you see that
is it chad's confusing me
chad is talking nonsense
that's the anime lab you think i'mma
works here
[Music]
i wonder if there's only one room nope
it's fine okay
okay yo
let's get on the shelves parkour cats
give that to the dogs they deserve the
bones
i get the luxury meat only the best for
the
best animal in the world
[Music]
you don't know questions
should we continue here we still have
five minutes yes nice job
[Music]
can't get up there
oh whoa whoa whoa
it's getting kind of stinky in here
[Music]
can i eat those two yeah books books
easy
mess maker achievement
i think i'll go to the next room
what do we have here give me upgrade
[Music]
increase okay what can i
what can i sweat with this power
is it just swats
stronger so that i don't have to go do
it again and again
you skeleton i don't like you fine i
mean you're already dead but i'll make
you even better
whatever that means believe me it's it's
cat language just makes sense in my
language
oh next next target
this room sucks stop in here
could i go can we try to
destroy that before cats actually
accidentally get onto that table you
wouldn't want that yet
nice knife
yeah but it's a laser i want to play
with it
[Music]
oh i kind of did it it's here now
mysteriousness what the hell is that
yeah
are you alive
[\h__\h] three minutes left can we make it
200 okay
okay okay i gotta focus focus on
destroying
yourself
black what
what what we are back how did obs say
goodbye
for a moment i'm very focused on this
drawing so i didn't even notice
pretty good now okay
how long was it
[Music]
give it give it to me quick quick i
don't have time
speed okay okay where's the next room i
think i came from here didn't i
uh wait there's only one room
ah two worms i guess
this is all i get to choose from
difficult difficult difficult but not a
problem for me
i'll get i'll get to the to those books
that should help
[Music]
if anything you should get a book about
how to spoil your kitty cat even more
i'll perfectly spoil your kitty cat
how to treat your kitty cat like a god
how to join the church of the cats
and the only book you will ever have to
read in your whole goddamn stupid
empty life
i mean what does life even what's life
even wealth if you're not a kitty cat
okay we're gonna make it we have only we
need only eight more items
yeah jump increase okay where do we we
need to jump up there
[Music]
what do you mean jump increase uh
is it decrease when i'm down there
[Music]
okay okay
bonus we got bonus time get in
okay okay or bonus items okay
we destroyed the laboratory
[Music]
we did a great job let's go next one
210 objects okay it's a low one a lower
number but
[Music]
why are these pillows so heavy look at
that yeah
humans don't deserve to sleep on beds
only me i deserve to sleep everywhere
everywhere
[Music]
huh did you get that
this is a catastrophe cat apostrophe
[Music]
the stream is bouncing around bent back
in time by five seconds
what you guys are making me really worry
about the stream today
oh wow wow
is that is it okay
[Music]
is
high value object has changed what what
what are you telling me here open this
[\h__\h] door
behind ya open the [\h__\h] door
i'm good on my end seems fine
[Music]
did i activate that already
wait where's the next room oh here let's
go over here
what's what is you i need to destroy you
my raffle paper
[Music]
what do we have here
jump oh thank god okay i need to get out
there help me out here
yeah oh maybe there's something up there
whatever
uh uh wait here
[Music]
okay whatever still so many items left
oh wait here's a room oh wait is it my
[Music]
if you know what i mean yeah do you know
what i mean
[Music]
i was going a little bit to sonia i was
wasting my time in another room
yeah visual apps will do this again here
what
[Music]
no upgrade i'm getting so many upgrades
though
speed increased okay
[Music]
what's going on did i boogie
[Laughter]
daniel
[Music]
no you you are the one here
yeah i'm bored these humans will play
but
what is this am i starting over
brianna's 30.
was i in this room
anyway gotta destroy the world now vrv
i have better things to do i need to
destroy the whale i can't be burning i
can't be on fire
no time for that is this
why was it before wasn't that you have
to start all over
[Music]
who's that cat's picture who's the pig
who's the picture in the cat who's the
cat in the victim are you cheating on me
with another
[Music]
thank you
this is just perfect yeah
i need to get up there
you're making me madness yeah
wait six minutes left we don't have to
we don't have to lose our hope just yet
what is this upgrade
i'm sorry jump increase perfect okay
uh-huh
no no no more bookstores i demand no
more books
i reject books
go away go away go away you must go away
yeah okay let's go here
[Music]
are there's movies about cats no then we
don't need them in this household
in any case this house is mine it does
not belong to you human it only belongs
to me
are you aware of that if if you are
gonna
ask me to buy uh to pay the rent then
you're thinking wrong this is not how
this works
you your rent house i live in house
i own house
[Music]
[Applause]
could be better at this but no one more
higher please
no okay i need some jumping crease or
something like that
ew flowers too much color
yeah they stink
stinky
who needs that huh please
[Music]
where the hell did i just go
stay airborne for three seconds
what what is that
yeah moon gravity
[Music]
i believe i can touch the sky yeah
even if you don't take me out for a walk
[Music]
i need a few more objects
and then not carefully very good very
good that's the tactic
uh uh how do i get to the other side i
know
whatever move on moving on but can i get
up there
[Music]
you think we're done i think
or is it already heated i think it's all
ready nope
meowski oh
quick
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah
oh
[Music]
get that out of the way get that out of
the way humans
you don't need this
[Music]
get in okay
comfy it's a bit too big this box is
going to blink
you really have to start all over
[Music]
yeah obvious messed something up
hey really what this what is going on
there's i'm and there seems to really be
a lag yeah like some
chocolate but okay everyone say hello
say hello
i know how the landings
hello hello
i've been wondering if after all these
years you'd like to meet me
[Music]
no oh there we go okay it's not that bad
i see it
i see your answers it's not that bad
i'm busy being a cat i can't i can't
care about obs
now i think i got time for that
busy business cat now
does it also count if i eat it from
there there yes
things that fell from the shelf onto the
beds
[Music]
oh
ew that's the supermarket food eww
help me better food than that
oh what was that he was like feeling
like a bunny or something like that
oh bunny's bunnies are friends i want to
play with bunnies
come play with minions
[Music]
what a beautiful cat i'm falling in love
oh
oh i'm joseph very german name yeah
yeah oh i got it
hell yeah oh no that's that that's the
thing i
accidentally jumped into last time very
dangerous now
we don't want we don't want the roasted
cat no no no
[Music]
no no
let's get up onto these shelves and get
some books those are easy points
who eats nowadays huh
the only information you need is that
cats are the best
cats one day will dominate the world if
i mean if you think about it we're
already dominating the world by now
mm-hmm austrian and
you're right wait i didn't do they know
i'm playing the game did they do that on
purpose
i mean i'm australian they're not not
not those austrians
i don't know what they're talking about
yeah i wanna get up now
let's do this
never upgrade wow they really want to
give me all those upgrades what is it
oh i didn't take it speed increased
where's the never ending i didn't look
out yet is this one nope i was here
the damage has been done oh yeah
cookies oh now i really want some
chocolate chip cookies but cats cannot
keep cooking on
[Music]
i need to get those places
no
[Music]
why
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't want to start over again
fight cat what the hell why would you
give someone such a name
[Music]
senior missy cute
um and we start over on you
but what is the difference i'm hungry
time to make a mess
time to have to annoy the hell out of my
own onion
[Music]
you put that there and it's buttering
facially
yeah not sure if i'm still not sure if
that really was the
right thing but i think i think cat's
always right here
that's never wrong now let the mess
begin
yeah tell you you and me are on the same
wavelength
[Music]
fun fun
get here and then from here we got
some some magic powers are trying to
stop me from getting over there but i
did it
possible but nothing is impossible
impossible romania what even
oh this girl this
what do i do about this girl what do you
want me to do that's this
i don't like it it makes me feel crazy
what the hell
turn it out turn it out
and those are too big i want the smaller
laser
smile laser please don't have time for
this [\h__\h]
this is in the way okay yeah oh
i'm all at the top welcome to the
mountain shelf top now
welcome to the shelf top here i destroy
everything yeah
you're below me because you were human
yeah i
am above you because i'm a kitty cat
yeah
very trippy yeah
[Music]
sometimes i like to try human food you
know what i can open the fridge
no oh
milk smelling and weird
weird containers nia there's an american
house now
what the hell yeah i'm not an american
cat
i am australian cat yeah
[Music]
wow
you have to do something about the
damage you did to me in my palm
do something about it i don't know what
but do it
i wanna get your grades for folks thank
you
[Music]
where is it i've got too much power
oh speed increase okay um let's go
somewhere else
where did i come from i was here before
that is very obvious
what do we have here oh
electronic devices yeah
i told you to shut them off i hold you
so many times now
you don't listen yeah you're [\h__\h]
stupid
bag milk i mean that's also weird as
hell
no no no not back milk no no no
i'm eating honey best thing is to get
the milk
straight from the source
[Music]
oh see all those books over there
they wanna fight with me
[Music]
we have to use that let me get all the
way to the top
yeah okay
and over there that looks good oh no no
no
big big yo that's a lot of stuff here yo
yo do they also fly in moon gravity
fly faster fly your food down
okay uh
yeah oh it's over it's over yeah
and
we can do it now do you believe in cats
yeah i believe in cats
that is the only thing i i'll ever
believe in
yeah upgrade we don't have much time so
do it faster
jumping chris okay perfect yeah uh
not much stuff here but let's do it yeah
[Music]
no no no no
okay now it's a fun game
world's domination felt so close
world domination must happen another
dania
ah ah the power
the power it was so close let me do one
more time one more time one more time
but is there a difference in which cats
are strong and which
which are weak you look you look strong
kratos i mean your name is powerful
i have too much energy now let's make a
mess
free cats the cat in the game the cat on
petty
and me
now thing can stop us unstoppable
yeah books on sale
zero zero dollars because who gives a
[\h__\h] about
books can't
[Music]
if anything you only read it to yourself
silently never think about me what about
me
maybe that's the real reason why i'm
reading your books because i want you to
read them for me
dakota unlocks oh the corner
the kona sounds interesting
[Music]
they say as if it's such a simple thing
to do
ah no it's been somewhere else
[Music]
whatever [\h__\h] the glowing dog okay now i
have speed now let me go there
oh that coat is so
[Music]
is it on the top whoa and
here okay uh uh
[Music]
okay so uh what do we do with all this
power
i feel invincible let me let me get rid
of all this toilet paper
you don't need toilet paper that's how
it works uh we have three minutes left
[Music]
wait uh we need to eat those items
new home
[Music]
you're cheating on me with another cat
huh
[Music]
is he cute yeah
okay we need a place with more items
what do we have here here i was here
before
no let's get this
what
100 items you have jump increased we can
get up there right
come on come on i believe in myself only
in myself i'm the only one i can trust
them to live in
[Music]
[Applause]
oh where else can i go
[Music]
i feel like there's no items here
small things i guess michelle yeah
wait there's something there's some
stuff up here
out of the way thank you and i have a
bad feeling
what about these does this work does
this count
i think yeah let's count it uh
maybe in the bathroom there's not much
why you got no [\h__\h] in your bathroom you
broke it
up yeah poor decoration yeah
useless oh no i failed here before
didn't i
come on when she pushed down on him
[Music]
maybe we can do it maybe we can do it
maybe we can do it this all counts
how comes this all comes no
uh i can't do it
where are my sevens now to help
wow this is pretty difficult
so what do we learn from this
humans suck cats are the best
i'm just gonna stay as a cat
protect human return to
kitty cat stay kitty cat always kitty
cat
that's what i learned from that thank
you guys for watching i still have a lot
of super chats to catch up on so we're
gonna do some chitty chatty and some
super chatty reading so
uh if you wanna stay you're
[Music]
thank you all for watching if you stay
then i'll be very happy
let's move over
oh [\h__\h] there's a lot of stuff going on
here
let me put the chat in here that was fun
that was fun but i don't know why why
how do i become a better cat huh how do
i become a better cat
i need to learn by looking at my own
cats where is it chat thingy
chat there we are okay
okay perfect perfect super chat time oh
let's turn on some people
let's see what do we have today
i am
i want to play
[Music]
uh
oh you know what how about we play the
ending music
the boss and nova for a little while i
feel like we're listening to that
[Music]
two streams in a row so i think we have
to take it a little bit easy
um oh yeah but i want to say
uh tomorrow is my day off but on i hope
you saw my schedule
on the day after which is uh a friday
yeah on friday i have one collab on
raina's channel and one collab on inna's
channel
and i'll actually also be somewhere else
uh
on another channel but i don't know if
that has been announced yet probably
not it might be a surprise yeah i will
be surprised
i can't tell you really um but yeah i'll
be on
very different places except my own
place
which i realized uh because the day
after is a member's only stream
turns out that if you're not a member
then that means that for three days on
my channel there will be nothing
maybe i'll upload a little tiny video
yeah we're doing a cat's watch along on
inna's channel
and with lena we're playing um
the goose game the untitled ghost game
haven't played that one a while in a
while the last time was with super
senpai
yes yes yes
i'm zoo video yeah maybe i should have
make an mcat video because we got like
two cat related streams this week
and and we should you know get all that
katniss katniss
out there before before it's oh wait the
music isn't even playing
oh i hear that
beautiful you know tony basa nova remix
okay so let me close the game
i'm cat video i guess it's time for that
huh
her duck and win
turd duncan went good question
thank you elvis thank you that is
that is mildly considerate moderately
considerate
at some five regions and thank you
yeah hopefully we won't get sick of it
too fast i need some
i need more like bts i should get more
non non-copyright museum to play during
the super jet reading times
uh anyway where is my
exo file
with the super chats
uh super cats show my cats super cat
reading
[Music]
last time but um the archive apparently
like edited itself and cut it out even
though it was there before
like i checked the archive to see if
everything's okay
but then i mean i i listened and the
mamaloni part the last super chat
that i read it was there but then later
on it got cut out
what the hell youtube so i will i don't
know i guess i'll read it again but
the direction it's kind of fake
and that their reaction is kind of fake
sorry
foreign
[Music]
that she wants to buy the the drawing
that i did of kelly in the past part 2
stream but i told her i already sold it
to felix sal
who asked for it in the super chat
before that so
i can't do that but she can she can
medium slightly out okay she can totally
get uh like draw herself some even
better
sensitive artwork of county
or me better quality
more sensitiveness
i envy the power that she has
[Music]
okay so we are reading uh there's like
superchats to go or something like that
from the
marathon stream and then the ones from
today and that's it then we're finally
free
although we did that actually i really i
really tried my best
yesterday to read as much as possible in
12 hours
so we got really far they're not gonna
haunt us forever and ever
those super chattels
[Music]
super chat
yes i'm of chaos thank you for the pinky
you should draw tiara ah
yeah i i didn't in the past part two
stream because i still wanna think about
you know i gotta think about that deeply
what i wanted to look like i saw
a bunch of like fan-made designs
the amount of tangents giving given i
tried my best
later on in the beginning i was assuming
in some
minecraft server i guess but yeah an
effort was made yeah
uh what was i saying uh oh yeah i saw a
lot of fan-made designs and they're
so good that i somehow just want to say
this is the design i just want to be
like
i'm using this but i'm not sure
because they they all like based it off
of
me and i didn't really want to do that
not sure though they look so good i
don't know what to do
[Music]
eh for the cats
i didn't realize either what i did with
that schedule because if you're not a
member then there won't be a stream on
my channel for three days maybe i have
to like
squeeze in something i don't know maybe
tomorrow
no but tomorrow i'm also kind of busy um
and and on on the day after tomorrow i'm
especially busy with all those collabs i
don't know
i want to squeeze in something because
three days without a public
stream on my channel with a bit meh
design it yourself trust in your designs
follow your heart i don't know what my
heart says
i've seen some great art online yeah me
too
what's up
you just did two and two twelve hours
what the [\h__\h] do you mean
yeah but i don't know
i know but but but
you could do something short yeah i
could do like a one hour mario kart
stream without super chat
reading or we could do a challenge you
know like pick what happened by someone
does like
uh playing mario kart on uh until
i get placed below like rank
uh seven or something like that which
might happen after the first round
but that that at least would um
guarantee that i wouldn't
uh uh stream too long
so let's see let's see thunderbolts
thank you and thank you for the pinky
[Music]
hi do you use any upcorner when you
stream
[Music]
oh dog
do you use any up dog when you
what's up i basically asked what's up
dog
that's funny the chad is not so
impressed but i'm quite impressed now
[Music]
funny
uh
no text with it but thank you i
appreciate your support
wait no that's not it i didn't
oh wait wait oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay you get a case from a cat
kia today
thank you
[Music]
brian hitch not thank you and thank you
for the pinky i'd like to buy the county
piece pink is a great color and the
compliments orange perfectly
thank you i do think that you know
whenever i see
a tacoma fan art that it does harmonize
quite well
yeah it's not even
not even a lie can i speak japanese
[Music]
thank you for a a two-way rainbow
what okay yeah this is where i was like
what the hell are these numbers
[Music]
where do i start reading and the lowest
one i want a 995 i guess
you're dazzling like kiara not only are
you incredibly talented entertainer you
are an amazing
artist and singer too kind compassionate
and thoughtful you
are but also strong and resilient with
all the difficulties
you faced like the channel termination
and shadow bamboozle
and the many re-debuts he always writes
the occasion although the re-debuts i
mean the first time
it was a i guess like for a little
moment it was troublesome but every
every other
debut it was just fun and jokes
always overcoming these hurdles you make
them your strengths
you have an outgoing wholesome nature
and magnetic personnel you simply
being around you brings out the good
people that reminds me some
someone did a magnet fan out of takamori
and i i
i retweeted it yesterday today
i real i really want to sing that with
kelly that song is so nostalgic to me
[Music]
yeah that would be cool
yes yes yes yes i guess you guys want to
hear it too
good taste your interactions and honesty
with us has built such a close community
supportive community
you treat us not as fans or supporters
but as close friends and appreciate us
all equally which i can't help but
admire and
respect this marks my 1 000
super chat to you since debut did you
count all along
congratulations scared of 1 million
subscribers congratulations on a
thousand super chats
i am incredibly happy to see you shining
brightly as an idol
enriching the lives of people all around
the world
this is my pinky promise to always
support you
you've been my aussie since the
beginning and just like this rainbow i
will continue to follow and support you
you have confidence because you
have so many people so have confidence
because so many people
you have so many people who want you to
succeed i would like to give a shout out
to broken
yo you're here broken
[Music]
where's broken at
lurkers and dds the care of the old
barons
runs clippers and artists each one of us
million chickens is what makes caffey
strong and it wouldn't be the same about
you all
maybe too every will said to everyone
i've met and befriended you all
amazing individuals thank you canada for
bringing us all together
thank you thank you
very sweet message
yeah i talked a lot about it yesterday
in the 12 hour in the second
12 hour stream that um the lurkers are
very important i hope more likely
can come out and chat but um
even if you cannot donate anything being
there to watch the stream
is one of the most important roles if
not
the most important rule number one
[Music]
broke gang is here broken always here yo
thank you for watching thank you so
much
[Music]
so let me give you a kissy tell me
thank you for the ring below thank you
for all the support you give me
thank you for staying here for so long
and staying
part of kfp saying hashtag vocassic yolk
yeah thank you it means a lot to me
i see thank you for the pinkie pink
super just to count and balance the game
hating on cali i would totally write
those paintings
and that's that really sucks and that
game is amazing
but i don't think it's good that they um
like
have every every npc hates the color
pink so much because like it's just not
fair because you can make absolutely
beautiful
paintings love them with the color pink
as well
it just doesn't make sense so that's one
thing i wish they would
would not have in the game everything
else in that game is amazing though
it's so chill
[Music]
foreign
yeah i didn't know that i didn't
remember i didn't think about that that
maybe would help out
marines up for the drama after drawing
kelly in that game as well
yeah oh that sucks
[Music]
first need to get recognition oh really
would it would it work if you have
recognition
[Music]
thank you for the pinky ignore the art
trolls your cali paintings are always
the most passionate think pink
thank you thank you for believing in me
by your tea at least someone
[\h__\h] those [\h__\h] them they don't
understand the beauty of me i mean
i'm also not like a huge huge fan of
pink
i would prefer orange or or purple or
like pastel colors or white
um but but still hello it's not fail
she drew luna and i think it's so don't
remember yeah
oh luna is super pink
[Music]
they only like pink if they think you're
good
question mark
[Music]
thank you for continuing to motivate me
to fulfill my dreams thank you for
existing i love you mama
i love you too my child come here
no i've got kidding so plump
thank you for your support thank you for
watching my streams
and good luck of your dreams i'm sure
you can fulfill them
i fulfilled dreams that i didn't even
know i had so yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay
congratulations on 1 million subs sorry
that i haven't been able to watch a
proper live stream in a while
ever since you moved but i'll continue
to do my best to catch more livestreams
in the future i promise
love the things you do and wish you the
best thank you
is it because of the time zone i feel
like people told me though
that my my my time slots yeah didn't
actually change that much
um so maybe it's because of private
reasons
but but thank you for trying pinkie
promise pinkie promise
hopefully i'll see you live in the chat
more often thank you kenji
dankeshen colleen burgess thunderson as
the zombie dancer
[Music]
thank you oliver wright for the red
super chat blessing me because of my
sneeze
hot tea there you are
wow love thank you oliver
thank you so much
was not necessary but i appreciate it
let me drink some water and miso no more
[Music]
i saw you playing ah this is okay we've
reached the point where i started
playing
uh hi heart oh egg is broken height
still
man i got so close i'm so painful i
didn't make it
[Music]
what does that mean and it shows how
much effort
and work you've done to entertain us
what
what you deserve this one million
chickens it has been eight months but
but felt like a great phoenix life
watching your streams
[Music]
hey you feel like it felt longer than
eight months
back thank you for the pinky thank you
for watching and supporting me in this
special special special stream segment
[Music]
i have to quit after one hour so
maybe next time if i take a little bit
more time maybe we'll finally be able to
clear that level but i heard that
there's actually
more than that level i'm fine if i can
just clear that one level the first
level and i'm happy with that
please style libertas
general piccolin thank you for the red
super chat
how much we just sent you on the grand 1
million just to let you know the kfp
will
have a grand present a gift from our
hearts to you but you must wait
and wait you will until it is ready for
the glory of the king
and it's the 1 million mystery rhino
already saw that
thank you are you the one that organized
that
piccolin general pekurini was it you
thank you
wow you did a great job nah and everyone
that was involved
thank you so much for doing that you
guys are so
sweet so so so sweet
love you love you
[Music]
there's always a next time
i have a trick for you for the cat game
what
focus
[Music]
is
wow thank you
even though you're uh drunken retired
although you're not your name doesn't
say retired right now so i guess maybe
maybe you're like
on and off retired and right now you're
not
are you drunk though
like korean name let me translate
[Music]
12 hours of tantra from start to finish
wait you ah-ha-ha what do you see what
you're doing here
you capitalized some letters in that
super chat and
it already looked uh sauce to me from
the beginning
i see what you did there
12 hours of potential from start to
finish
ever since debuted you amazed our hearts
to really care for you
in the name of all of kfb those who
can't get super chat we want to say
thank you very much we will support you
forever recaps i did i did i didn't you
didn't
even even have to tell me it says stream
high challenger
the capital letters say stream high
challenger
thank you thank you i like
i like this you always think of the
important things it seems
thank you
[Music]
gargantual thank you for the red
superchatto
thank you uh congrats on writing 1
million thank you
i knew you would make it the full 12
hours now i wonder how many
hours of super chat readings it will
take uh you to get
hey i did pretty well are you proud of
me
but you'll make it through because i see
you love us misfits
as much as we love you thanks for the
full days
for for the full day showbox thank you
for watching
yeah it might be a lot uh and it takes a
lot of lot a lot of time to get through
these but you know you guys know me
i always try i always i don't only try
i always go through each and every
single super chat
and sometimes i even read the ones the
messages that
and are not pinkies and reds because i
just
want to um read as many as i can
so yeah i try even though it takes
[Music]
thank you thank you
blue cheese happy birthday 17 huh
emma sticky thank you motion one for
broke it again yesterday
but youtube says because they cut
something out of my stream
you know
i hope you get to enjoy one million
mystery project from kfp
thank you thank you thank you so much i
did enjoy it
i probably enjoyed the minecraft part a
little bit too much though
[Music]
you are not a yogurt you are a chicken
you are just a little bit confused
confused but you got the spirit
[Music]
yummy congratulations to one million and
to the record of the live stream in hell
live ian continue to do your best we'll
make
sure to support in the future thank you
i will count on you if that's okay thank
you
so much mwah i'm glad that you
are part of kfb thank you for supporting
the journey and the marathon stream
swain magnanim
oliver wright thank you another red
super chat
and we're taking the stream length title
with quality throughout yes yes
well deserved a million subs too yeah
you know i could have
i could have easily reclaimed it by
doing a movie watch along
but i did it with good content
playing lots of games and stuff thank
you
thank you on to the next record we go
thank you naked chicken thank you also
for a red super chat
and there has been so many positive
messages sent away until now it's clear
you've touched so many people's heights
since you've appeared as takana
kyara that's something to be truly proud
proud of
thank you naked chicken
put some cloves on before you fall down
here come on
there you go thank you for putting on
your uniform you've missed the panties
but okay
[Music]
thank you now you can take your clothes
off again just in front of the camera
please
please turn uh put something on
otherwise i'll get banned you know
thank you so much for your support
thank you makes me very happy and yeah
[Music]
why is there so many weird comments in
chat today
what the hell
[Music]
from brazil oh
thank you for the bottom of my heart and
so you helped me during rough times and
being a comfy place to always return to
when i was crying and things went crazy
you kept me company i will never forget
you
and how much you helped me grow as an
artist and as a person
oh i'm glad i was able to help you with
that and be by your side
i'll always be by your side wow
thank you so much thank you lena real
fighter you're a fida
[Music]
fighter chicken cute
thank you for the red super
been chat your sincere debbie and it's
been a pleasure watching all of your
streams
all of my streams oh
looking forward to many more fun streams
of you thank you
if that is true wow big
thank you big kisses
thank you for watching me and and not
giving up on me
and continuously supporting me even even
during tough times
and for believing in me mm-hmm
[Music]
i see you're probably someone who's a
part of the broken come here
come here for kissy this is you bastion
sample kiss for you good night
and i'd sleep well
[Music]
this is my first red super chat and
what's the more fitting time for it on
your biggest mouse on yet
yeah i have been watching your stream
near the beginning
and you are the one that i watched the
most oh
[Music]
did he get the kiss yeah
you did you definitely deserve this we
love you so much
thank you thank you for watching my
stream so much
call me jason
thank you thank you i'm glad that you're
enjoying my streams
i hope that will never change
i'll continue doing my best for you
i hope take it since we share names what
the hell
are these two with the same name
what's youtube funny i can trust one for
everyone
although words alone can never express
my gratitude towards you
i just want to thank you for making my
life so much better i'm fortunate enough
to have found you and be part of kfb and
you will forever be my aussie
again congrats i love you
come here come here
mom thank you that is so sweet
[Music]
thank you for letting me be your aussie
i will i will i will do my best that you
will not change your aussie
promise me kb channel thank you also for
the red super chat
one million and the new long stream
record in the in en
verb boss keeps on winning you mean cat
boss
congratulations again thank you
[Music]
hey peace out i love a kiss for you
wow loving you
cute you're a cute chicken
thank you so much for your support for
always being here
[Music]
loop question what's aussie oh she comes
from the
japanese verb called osu
it's pushing someone but in in like
um when it's like when it when it's
about like
idols or artists or whatever it's like
supporting someone so your orsi is the
one you support the most or you like the
most
you could say
that means i am supporting kiara or you
say
which means
what what was the closest english
word uh
[Music]
uh
what was that again i forgot
that was a sim yeah yeah stem
that i think that's mostly used in like
k-pop
i never saw it being used anywhere else
i think but yeah
it's pretty similar i guess no it's the
same meaning
[Music]
dubs christophe thank you and ready and
crimson thank you and baron man
um millitos thank you for the pinky
oh you sent two where's the other one
here ah
thank you for two pinkies many of your
fans know the feeling of self-doubt and
impostor syndrome
i can only recommend that you take a
leap of faith and believe in us who
believe in you
you're the 16th most subscribed youtuber
oh wow
and still climbing out of 31 million
channels
only 22 000 have reached 1 million suns
oh
it takes the average channel 22 months
to reach one k sub
keep flying to what two million and we
will be with you
thank you for our millions
thank you i'll give you a kiss because
that's because that was two pinkies
thank you
thank you for believing in me
i will continue to work hard
thank you thank you so much chaos do not
thank you
blue thank you for the thinking
[Music]
congrats to one million now you hold the
record for endurance terms as well
yep
eight months ago feels like yesterday
and now you have all made it to this
great milestone i'm glad to have
witnessed it since whole ian's debut
thank you thank you wow
that's nice that you've been there from
from the beginning supporting all of us
thank you very much
thank you
17.7 thank you for the pinky
congratula 12 hour stream one million
subs two original songs with millions of
views
all thousands of loving chicken that
watch you daily me included
and it was you who did that despite all
of the difficulties i rarely super chat
but i want you to remember this
thank you thank you so much
i love you too thank you for spending so
much time with me
uh i don't have the url right now but if
you look up
uh takanawa
remix then you should find it
i think there's only one busan over ah
no
yeah i think there's only one
[Music]
um
now that the stream is almost over thank
you for everything you've had good times
bad times and strange times and look at
how far you've come
thanks for all your hard work and may
you have more adventures in the life of
your dear friends raise a glass to kfp
thank you thank you come here for
kissing
there you are
thank you so much for supporting me
throughout all of these times
for never giving up on me never letting
me down
never deserting me you know the drill
some aka guys thank you for the red
super chat oh wait that's
two out of two ah you started out with a
smaller one
[Music]
let me read you've inspired so many
people including myself to enjoy life
and encouraged us to do things like
learn a new language or travel to new
places yeah yeah i did didn't i told you
guys to do that kind of things
continue to be yourself kiana and i
can't wait to see what future has in
store for us here kfp
love you
i i could tell you what the future has
in store
at us a story for you
here at kfc i could tell you but you
just have to look at the membership
um upgrades
[Music]
and i'll say nothing more
good luck with that thank you for your
support
[Music]
you give kisses that any bird would love
cats kissing a bird is a bit dangerous
though not sure if birds want to be
kissed by cats to be honest
[Music]
oh thank you bastiana i'm happy it made
you happy
hey i try my best to read the comments
uh but there's always so many so i'm
sorry that there's many people that i
don't know this at all sorry
[Music]
and thanks for the super fun endurance
stream
says apple and what's fun being here
since this
very cute movie they're all alone oh my
god i literally can't believe so many
were there from beginning to end wow you
guys are crazy and then
some even were there from beginning to
end for yesterday as well
thank you comrades and we're taking the
longest stream record in halloween and
once more
congress on 1 million subs thank you
thank you info
thank you thank you soon
from the bottom of my high doll
thank you wouldn't miss it for the world
thank you
[Music]
anything for you boys thank you
it's just that we love you thank you
said i missed the super chat reading
well well well you got 12 hours
to watch anytime when you've got time
when you're like bored we're already
like in a long train ride or something
already need to fall asleep to something
eden thank you for the pinky uh
conversations on one million phoenix
burgers serve that mean chickens eh what
the hell no
watching your group has been so fun when
you first dreamed of being a fast food
owner to making a cafe a worldwide chain
worldwide chain and look forward to your
continued growth
thank you me too let's
thank you for the red super chat jesus
my heart think of the vlog
come on you guys are really chickens
for freaking out so much in the last
five minutes
mwah i knew what i was doing
stop being such a chicken and be a
fighter chicken
be a chicken without fear
kritanya thank you and jimmy thank you
for the
red rest of the chat with no text but
obrigada
opening data
thank you it actually cut off the last
few minutes well that's not my fault
i was told 12 hours and i did i i did
stop before 12 hours
i don't know why i did that i mean
did it happen for both streams i
i heard it they also did it for the for
the marathon stream
i didn't check it though
it sucks
[Music]
again
what is this music from it's a bosa nova
remix of
hinotoni my original song
it cuts to ah
[Music]
that makes no sense like youtube lets
you stream
like 12 hours and saves the archive if
it's not over 12 hours but it still cuts
at
five minutes before why not just
keep those five minutes youtube wow
that makes no sense well okay we'll
remember that for next time
we know the real number okay if anyone
asks what is keanu's record
it's not 11 hours 55 minutes
let's just say [\h__\h] 12 hours or like
11 hours
57 minutes or something like that
darren wait thank you [\h__\h] maxwell
buffalo first time cushion microwave
junior dancer
spirit vet thank you nico no thank you
for the pinky
love you guys thank you
a rainbow chicken iron hood are you
making a rainbow now what
what elvis thank you
oh my god for the pinky
11 55 got it
11 58 43 seconds oh that's the exact
number okay remember dan if anyone asks
what was kiada's record let it be known
let it be known youtube sauce
[Music]
i wanted to congratulate you again for
the 1 million subs 2 million vapor world
and 12
for the 12 hours of streaming you
deserve all these achievements so
continue this wonderful person that you
are
sharing our days and inspiring us thank
you alice i'll do my best all
let me eat some chocolate dogs
oh there's one more only oreo filled
chocolate
yeah that one was a good one
[Music]
okay
yummy
[Music]
oh one hour break still counts as one
one stream recording who desired that
[Music]
hmm
so she took like one hour naps i wonder
wait you're doing a rainbow after all
[Music]
you bamboozled me i thought you weren't
doing one
oh let me eat another chocolate
[Music]
is
ah
[Music]
hmm
um
and now i'll die because i'm a cat and i
ate chocolate
[Music]
i guess that's one similarity about cats
and phoenixes
i can die another a bunch of times
before i return
to phoenix reject cat to return to
phoenix
[Music]
i just said that i used to be so
addicted to chocolate it actually is
much better now
nowadays i mean i just ate chocolate but
i really eat
chocolate so much less than before i
used to eat chocolate like
daily bars of chocolate daily
[Music]
but now it's like only every once in a
while
thankfully
so centerful writes you showed me that
the haters in life
were wrong and that it's super cool to
have emotions and passion for things
and i'll always be grateful here's a
bright long future for young carefree
thank you but who the [\h__\h] told you or
like made you
think that having emotions and passions
for things is wrong
yeah i mean
i guess
santa fe you came again oh wow
[Music]
i can't imagine that but having emotions
and passions is
very important like what the hell you
would be a robot otherwise wait
that was a pinky oh you got so many
kisses for a pinky
lucky you
oopsie
another red supercharger
don't worry about it you don't need to
send any super jets
it's not necessary at all
i love you no matter if you send money
or not
no matter thank you for everything since
you debuted
uh you've been amazing congratulations
again thank you you've been watching
this
video thank you thank you
i'm glad you still like me and want to
support me
thank you oliver
eric patrick anderson residency
the last super chat was from razidez's
five dollars
and it says made it for all 12 hours i
can't say congrats and thank you enough
for us
you always know how to keep long strums
the longest dreams entertaining
[Music]
i only have to read the ones from today
we made it
yummy
even though i take so much time but but
at least for
for these super jets i i took way less
time for each red one than i usually do
but i think you guys
understand right you understand that i
i didn't really have much
[Music]
the choice let me
get it out of the way
thank you she actually did it yeah wow
wow it only took me
13 hours
[Music]
i love that get rest after this
yeah yeah yeah we're still gonna read
the ones from today but
it should be fairly fast
[Music]
okay okay so let me get out of this
excel
file thank you thank you mena jason for
um helping me by marking all the pinks
and red ones in the excel file thank you
that was very very helpful
visual so
oh my god why does this stream also have
so many super chats
[Music]
is this the people who couldn't super
chat during the marathon stream and
kept it for today
[Music]
you guys work in mysterious ways
thank you for the support guys
i mean at some point i had to open it
back up again
can't keep it closed for too long
okay so what do we got okay
starting yeah oh yeah that was the first
one
don't spam super jets and there they go
there they [\h__\h] go
yeah thank you mr caspian
at least there's not so many red ones
huh i said
but who knows what comes after this film
adios
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
must be ready to retribution for not
being able to switch out for two whole
days
oh my god i have taken a leader right
from you guys to super chat
unbelievable unforgivable
unforgettable how dare she
[Music]
take away the opportunity for you guys
to send me money
two days
[Music]
uh you guys are too supportive you have
to spoil yourself someone
for real
[Music]
do you guys not know how to spoil
yourself
you could buy yourself bath bombs from
lush
you could buy yourself um
playstation 5 or a new pc or a new
laptop
you could buy yourself a new
mattress a 9 000 mattress
you could buy yourself some luxury
dinner
go to a restaurant you could uh
you could take the money for a vacation
a super amazing vacation sometime soon
when you when you're able to travel
actually here we can already travel to
certain countries so that's
pretty dope um
[Music]
here they go again spoil the phoenix
live
five five yank
will you spy last time so well the only
thing i can do is give you
streams and and and
songs and my love
[Music]
can't afford that ah
well i mean some people say that the kfb
sells
luxury dinner and all the employees get
free food at kfp so i guess yeah just
eat at kfp
that seems like the only logical thing
to do anyway
99 000 199 000
the one that coco had is nine thousand
and it's already way too much like
i i i i don't see why i i i don't want
to spend so much money on the back i got
a new bed when i moved
and it actually ended up being pretty
cheap i wanted to get something
better but then nothing was available so
fast i would have to wait
weeks and weeks and weeks for some
reason so
i was like well whatever i should take
what's available
i was able to buy it uh for like
it cost like uh 900
euro something like that like a it was a
what's it called again
box box spring bed
[Music]
yeah but it's super comfy i'm i'm happy
with it
my cats are happy with it
i'm satisfied thank you for the
membership welcome
oh nine thousand dollar cat bed that
sounds
like a reasonable process no
they're not gonna use it they're not
gonna use it
unless it's like a real bad if it's a
real bad like a human bed then they
would probably use it
as long as it's not made for cats the
cats will use it
no but actually uh i need to i was
thinking about
buying that cat's race that i told you
guys before about
was it remember the only stream though
think it was public
was it oh no i'm not sure
but i don't know that
i still have this this this mindset
i don't know if i really want to buy i
kind of want it because it looks so cute
i don't know i still have to think about
it
my amazing bed was only 400 total so you
can totally get something good for that
money but i wonder
i should have tested out the 9 000
mattress from coco senpai
i should have tested it out yeah but i
think cali also
got an amazing new mattress didn't she
did she tell you guys
i feel i think she even or was she just
thinking about it
i talked with her about it for a little
bit
but i'm not sure if she actually did it
i should have next time next time i
visit
callie i'll test out her bed
[Music]
and see how how comfy it is
wow that's still that's so amazing bold
strategy
she she has a five thousand dollar bed
mattress yeah
i'm gonna test it out and if i if it's
really that good then i need to
i guess upgrade my bed
[Music]
so okay that was enough of a tangent
and where was i big swing thank you
elvis thank you for the red superchat
thank you for another 12 hour stream you
are amazing for being able to keep your
energy up and chat with us for so long i
managed to stay until the end and it was
so much fun
i look forward to seeing what this cat
game is like over the counter
she would ask here
oh we were having some top level
top secret uh portuguese conversations
here
uh only only we understand
no no surprise you guys can't understand
it but this was totally legit
[Laughter]
[Music]
portuguese
um
[Music]
bonita
ah
[Music]
are you casting spells look at harry
potter
what um
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
having a good time
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
meow
portuguese version
[Music]
i actually have a um a sweater a parka
uh that's really tacky um
i have i have it from a tourism shop
in brazil and it's like in in like
those tacky brazilian colors and yellow
and green
and it says brazil on it i wore i wear
it sometimes
yeah brazil vodka
it's quite comfy
yes okay back to business
jeff the phoenix hello thank you
this is not a red or a pinky but we have
time to read uh
smaller ones as well again so let's go
thanks for another 12 hour stream you
are amazing for being able to keep your
energy up
no wait i
looked below that was elvis
oh holy one we have heard tales and
rumors from visitors to our village that
your divine legion
of followers now number one million
that's right that's right
the villagers have gathered what they
can for this offering of congratulations
oh i love the phoenix tony and they're
so good
the people of phoenix time humbly pray
for your continued success and that you
will continue to become more powerful
may you continue to provide us blessed
protection and bring
further prosperity to our village yo
jeff i love you you're the best
trevor g thank you for the two red zu
potatoes
sasuke attention beating the longest em
stream worker twice in a week also be
sometimes for all the sneezes
the following super jet is my missing
number five ah
from my one pair 100k
subs super test oh that
that's what you were trying to do oh
yeah oh because it was 10
you sent 10 indeed you wanted to and
one million not a huddle i understand
completely now
oh
as i blocked as i've locked it up
it's now late and you don't need to read
it i just wanted to make sure it was
sent
number five you've shown your naturally
hatched comedian
with the m2 series with your performance
in the waiting for ina stream
always makes me go
you can take moments others may break
out over and calmly turn them into gold
your first three w for example
you're kind of right there aren't you
you're
kind of right i am quite the
professional comedian
oh sorry
[Music]
thank you trevor
thank you trevor that was great i loved
all your messages thank you so much
travelty
your messages always always make me
smile
[Music]
the crazy matter from supported foiled
support foiled my plot to leave
propaganda advocating ditching takamori
in favor of
kokoliope
in a place where you couldn't bug me
from you leave me no alternative
but to go pink in order to spread the
word from a safe
i'll [\h__\h] burn you i'll [\h__\h]
burn you and everything that's precious
to you
holy [\h__\h] you have some nerves my friend
[Music]
looks at it again with the velcros
where's ship name i kind of like the
ship name but you shouldn't ship them
uh it it's get a boxer cat i don't know
because i just started her life it
really
i'm never this is just an accessory i'm
actually a phoenix
[Music]
nice to meet you
just finished watching your super chat
reading archive oh my god you
you did you did that to yourself you mad
lad
must have been painful i'll try to watch
your live streams as much as i can
unless i control me uncontrollably pass
out on bed
also make sure you have enough rest that
was two twelve hours almost streams
pretty much back to back
make sure you rest well thank you i mean
i had one free day in between
one day off so oh fine today also
since the stream started somewhat late
um
i was i had enough time to rest and
and uh chill with my kitty cats yeah
[Music]
it's all good i'm feeling fine um but
i even though i feel fine i'm also being
careful to like
like not
overwork myself without like me noticing
you know because i might feel fine but i
might not actually
be fine play that play that thing in the
background
they say you're fine but you're not
really fine
um because uh yeah sometimes you don't
notice when you're like burning out so
that's why today
like even though i feel fine i'm going
for a shorter stream
yeah and tomorrow i'm also taking
the day off so two days off this week
don't worry don't worry but thank you
for watching
thank you feelings come here you
sweetheart
no come back here come come come back
sorry okay there you go
so sorry so sorry to scare you i would
never send you to the usual room you've
always been so sweet and kind to me
you'll never tease me or hurt me
or desert me oh my god stop stop
safety margin is always good yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
i do need to also just take some more
time for myself to take care of
real life things and and um
you know there's some things that i've
been neglecting a lot
yeah shorter five hours
hey we're still in 12 and a half hours
mark we can do this below
below four hours for sure today
[Music]
and thank you for writing it as well
because i
wouldn't probably have really known i
really wish that youtube would just
actually can someone make a formula from
for for excel where it marks all pinkies
of all currencies and marks all red ones
of all currencies
so that i can just always copy and paste
them into an exo file and then
just it just works that would be nice
[Music]
how's your back been horrible but that's
for like many many years so
not much of a as difference
usual also i finished uh
watching re re-watching game of thrones
yesterday
[Music]
oh yeah this is a google spreadsheet
someone already did probably oh i can
imagine it must be
somewhat easy definitely possible
for people who know how to use uh excel
slash google
spreadsheets thingy whatever
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah we never shut up about
the time you mean
i'm going there eventually any at least
maybe this month
[Music]
you fought on the last season i mean
it's not the first time i watched it uh
it's yeah stuff like
the dothrakis being there again
just makes no sense uh
her forgetting about you know a certain
fleet
makes no sense yeah many things that
make no sense
but still um i don't want to hate too
much on it because
still the rest of the series is really
good
yeah you need to okay
you can't just convert everything to usd
the value of red varies yeah
yeah yeah yeah exactly so it must just
be there must be a formula for each
common currency that are used in super
chats
that would work i would say anyway
anyways
thank you for the pinky i'm the busy i'm
a ranger of the compilation video ah
the journey and i'm glad you enjoyed it
it was really good damn
i also made a bgm only video for you as
a gift
and i tweeted it is it on youtube
well let me play it let me let's change
the pgm
timo halos uh journey
piano maybe
oh that must be it that must be it
oh but this was
uh piano right
[Music]
oh
uh that that's just and
again that hits me
holy [\h__\h] that sounds sounds like all
right all right let's listen to some
piano yeah
thank you for making that you're very
talented did you play that like on an
actual
piano or did you do it on the pc
probably on the pc huh
so cool john v bear
and john v berg john v bear thank you
[Music]
so much as a promise you didn't have
stream on my birthday
but you said happy birthday to me so i
sent super chat now
oh i didn't see white cannon in your new
outfit with cat ears can you do it now
how did you know that i would be oh
because this is from today's stream
[Music]
uh
happy birthday join me
[Music]
hope you're happy hope you're
oh i didn't transition oh for [\h__\h]
sake
youtube
happy birthday
hope you're happy and uh yeah again i
haven't been here for a while house is
going guys how's it going
how are you doing yo what up you
you guys really uh gotten older
and yeah you changed you changed but you
still look beautiful
not as beautiful as me that is beautiful
as me
and no one can reach this beauty
obviously
look at me oh you know what i forgot why
they're my boys
[Music]
can we go find another please
i shall wait and then
i totally ruined this beautiful music
[Music]
much better
jeffery jeffery thank you thank you
slavic fellow thank you for two pinkies
and one yellow thank you thank you
i'm sorry about that awkward one million
celebration celebrate to celebrate the
rebels
celebrity reach this episode of mine i
generally meant it as a price for your
hard work don't worry there were so many
[\h__\h] super jets that i don't remember
um six to seven months back when i first
fell into the rabbit hole i didn't know
what to think as previously i've only
ever seen some kison
ants popping up here and there oh but as
i kept watching a certain majestic
phoenix
i began to understand and became amazed
mesmerized even
whole life is a big family bringing
smiles and joy to people yes yes that is
true
and you're an example example idol and
my oc
thank you sorry for being a cylindric
intention now i'll go out
the back dig a hole and hide in it
before i say no no no no
no don't you're wonderful the way you
are you didn't say anything wrong
because i don't remember it anyway it's
all good come here
i love you wow thank you for supporting
me
thank you so much you are so sweet
thank you for letting me be your aussie
who beat him for mod 2021
i love that
not nice
oh wait that's a rainbow isn't it no
wait oh my god no
it's a one two three four four red
silver jacks oh god
king crimson one of the five five one
two three four
is this is this you teasing me waiting
for the
fifth one i don't see it anyway
okay so sorry this is late damn youtube
wouldn't
[\h__\h] let me send super chat last
sunday oh isn't it
is it also not letting you sense the
fifth one
hope you got a good rest after two 12
hours dreams anyways tantra
congratulations on one million
in all seriousness never ever doubt you
would reach
never had any doubt you would reach this
milestone you're amazing thank you
gotta say you weren't the first video i
saw pikami
who was the first one who you weren't
the youtuber that introduced me to whole
live ian
kelly in trash test thank you dad but
you're the one that's making me stay
i love you for that thank you for all
your hard work for the community company
that you built
camp is the best and the people
around you hope support it can win with
you all this time you've touched and
inspired so many it's a testament to
your success so proud of you bus
knowing you're gonna say something like
it
was a variety of factors like audience
and whole events around and yes those
may
be true but it's also definitely just
cause it's you
you're a talented wonderful
straightforward and extremely
entertaining
[Music]
but thank you so much it was a super
sweet message
[Music]
i'm gonna be so hyped every time that
part plays
[Music]
thank you for staying not ness i'm i'm
so happy that i made you stay
and that you are you decided to support
me out of everyone
thank you so much for that i hope you
will never regret it and continue
supporting me
and we'll we'll have lots
[Music]
let me put the link for this
let me pin it
if you're wondering about the pgm it's
in the
it is a pin yeah on it
it should be pinned now
not sure if i really can't play this but
yeah
well no risk no fun huh wifi yes thank
you for the
red super chat text to avoid getting
bonked
cory doesn't want me to listen thank you
either yes thank you
thank you thank you so much
come here i won't bonk you don't be
scared
and you i punk headbutt book
oh you'll still like it huh
bye bye thank you for your support wi-fi
yes i saw you in this chat as well when
you were watching
[Music]
if i don't know if you're watching but
if you have like this the
single tracks
maybe you can send them to me and i can
like uh
exclude the ones that might be
problematic like the
the pokorano asean one
maybe
love you too thank you for supporting me
thank you thank you love you too
cocoon thank you for the pinky i don't
have a cat movie and i don't plan on
buying it so sadly i have to miss that
stream
wait do you have netflix i think it's on
netflix
but i wish you in and out of the
takatori folks a fun time really looking
forward to your members stream though
whatever it is
thank you yeah i still don't know what
to do there's
a lot of things we could do still
thinking about it
i'll inform you guys as soon as i know
thank you
[Music]
oh what is this sparkly beautiful sound
the phoenix will go on orchestral
arrangement of pinot noir
oh you're coming here to make me cry
huh
someone said in the chat i didn't read
their super chat but i
just checked and i don't see anything
here i don't think i missed it
this is so epic yeah
[Music]
you send yourself to the usual room
uh was that when i was in the in the
oven
what the hell was it that was a bug
right it must have been a bug
i couldn't get out i just squeezed
myself in there cat's a liquid i get it
but then i must have been able to get
out as well but i couldn't
so much for being liquid cats are ashes
it turns out
thank you
for watching today's stream again you're
always here
yeah it was a bug i thought so when that
[\h__\h] up my run i was
doing so well
this oh [\h__\h] this is so epic
this gives me that that part just gave
me super smash brother
vibes i think i don't know why
[Music]
the rainbow okay
good evening story time congratulations
on 1 million subscribers this is a late
1 million rainbow thank you
nice to see rainbows today too beautiful
outside
i didn't watch the 12-hour stream the
day of the event because i had worked
the next day but it will take i'll take
my time to finish watching the 12 hour
live stream file
this is a reward for your efforts enjoy
it
thank you thank you i guess so you
didn't watch it yet you're still working
on it
thank you for doing that
it was um it was very oh
fun i think even though it was 12 hours
i don't think it was tedious
or anything so
thank you i hope you will enjoy it thank
you for supporting me
i appreciate it archive watchers are
uh very important too mm-hmm
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
converts on a million this is late but
because of work i couldn't send one even
now i can't stick around because of it
oh damn you're not here right now
but congratulations on such an
accomplishment and will always be there
for you boss as long as you want us to
be around we
love you kiara thank you love you too
i hope you will watch this in the
archive
ryan you said you're not here but there
you are
thank you for the support
and good luck at work fight all
men having a job is tough isn't it
neat life is best life just kidding
no no no no go get yourself a job
work at kfp this look area
this look really dangerous
i've
congratulations on one million mama
thank you for everything i was sad in
the past few days but watching you can
always cheer me up oh
thank you for being you and so amazing
it's my birthday today oh
thank you for everyone who says happy
birthday to you i love you all
happy birthday
[Music]
no need to be sad mama is here i hope
you can celebrate
and eat some cake and and i don't know
drink your favorite drink
maybe be with a friend oh
happy birthday um
[Music]
kuala
uh
[Music]
patrick batman bateman
that was hard to read you turned the
other way around
[Music]
back soon
it looks like the obs update reset your
life latency settings to normal latency
of course
but that setting is in youtube not in
obs
um but i'll i'll check if something
changed in obvious
people around action this looker thank
you for the thinking
it breaks my ever-loving cat heart but
i'll have to catch most of this on vod
no peace thank you
oh man that that is sad fun it's at
least not a long vod
so should should be um
oh it's a reference oh was that a
reference
it shouldn't be too long this longer i
hope you enjoyed the rev with the
archive hey
archive this one yo yo what's up
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
i'm a good cat meow i didn't do anything
bad meow
i believe you i believe you
by the way congrats on one million subs
again thank you for everything and thank
you for being part of my life
love you love you tunia
donna thank you
thank you for supporting me thank you
for enjoying my streams and following me
thank you soon sophie vivian dankeshen
albedo dankeshen sophie vivian dankeshen
eddie elf thank you yeah
[Music]
i love how i have this honest background
noise right now and it sounds like pure
chaos
i literally died from nafta when you
went full young cat
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
sorry i um i i went crazy there for a
second who am i where am i
blacked out
[Music]
oh
now where's my headphone i want to crack
my neck
damn it i can't reach it because i still
have that weird cramp there
don't confuse me
sorry but that is just such a good song
i cannot resist
it hypes me up
[Music]
thank you for a rainbow
wow
[Music]
such a meme
that guitar shallow man sounds good in
piano as well hi thanks for all the fun
here's a rainbow i've been an avid
avent avid fan since the start and we
can't remember because of all the fun
watching you enjoy games and streaming
it truly is a blast thank you i only
just found out about
whole life when ian debuted but you were
the first one i truly became a fan of
thank you thank you
i am honored
uh it's safe to say you yanked me into
the rabbit hole and made me part of the
kfp
kfkpf canopy community funny story ever
since the band of darkness ah
i like how you ride around it my main
channel has been bugged
apparently preventing you from seeing my
supersets what
[Music]
what do we have to blow them up or
something
huh a [\h__\h]
that sounds sauce apparently preventing
you from seeing my superheroes i only
realized that when you didn't read my
pink and red supers at one point
what the [\h__\h] you've been sending them
all along and but then
did they really go through did youtube
also charge you because if they charge
you and it still doesn't show up neither
in my chat nor in my
um like super chat history
that is uh not very nice
um but that won't stop me from showing
support i'm so sorry that i missed so
many then
i love the energy you bring to your
streams the smells you bring to
everyone's lives including mine
and the awesome community community you
created for kfp
what the [\h__\h] man i'm so mad about the
super chats
a big chicken thanks for all the hard
work you put in
too close i think what did it for me was
your genuine side
not many that don't stick around see it
but underneath the onion peel are you
calling me an onion now
it's a genuine personality that says it
like it is and isn't afraid to share
your feelings
your true feelings you deserve the one
million and many more to come
[Music]
mr kyle brown that is such a sweet
message
and i am so mad that i missed out on
many other sweet messages apparently
are you here in the chat now
alberto that's [\h__\h]
that songs electric piano sent me to pc
tweaking mistakes and articulations
uh interesting
i don't see him in the chat at least now
but
come here kisses for you
there you are there you are all the
kinds do the trick okay
yeah i i guess i have to visit the
youtube office again and bring amma and
callie along with me and show them who's
boss
show them who the tantra is
they want to put up a fight huh thank
you for your kind words they touched my
heart
thank you mr kyle brown
i hope that um you you enjoy
being out of the shadows you were
forcefully put into the shadows but no
more of that
let's have some fun times together thank
you for the rainbow
jessie ling dankesh and tony tony dungan
black christian duncan penguin dancing
pokemon
[Music]
you deserve it if you still doubt
yourself then i can remind you one
million chicken times
[Music]
chat i'm sending this super chat for the
days you won't be streaming on the
channel
thank you i'm sending this case for you
for the days where i won't be streaming
on my channel
[Music]
foreign
what do i read that as
[Music]
899 is a red one i won't remember that
will i
dkk 899 is the red one okay remember
remember remember
thank you kiana thinking
this is too hard i can't use this spgm
too often because i
i just can't stop myself from from
vibing with it
it's a bit um it's too high up here and
there
jesse lingard
w2
[Music]
thank you for the pinky late congrats to
one million subscription
on behalf of your filipino fans thank
you so much
thank you i appreciate it thank you
genie
love you hi romanian
random
[Music]
i love you you are so cute i love you
too so much love
love is in the air come here
[Music]
thank you
blue sets now so thank you for the red
super chat as well
no words but only
red but there you are
thank you blue
what can i say what i can say is that
i'm really glad that i started
watching this i started watching you i
didn't have a dream to follow and it was
kind of painful but you mother motivated
me to look for one
for me you're an idol in the true
meaning of the word
thank you did you find it yet i wonder
if not that's okay take your time with
it
okay let me stop the music here
[Music]
shaping sweet how do i read that call me
shape oh thank god
the beginning of your super chat says
shape copy shape as if you knew that i
wouldn't be able to read that
thank you shape thank you for the rest
of the chat
hi ken i really enjoy your streams i l
and i love your rise out
one to two streams oh really
thank you i got my fiance hooked on you
and she loves you i love fiance
you're looking hot i lost my dad when we
started dating oh my god and she's
helped a lot oh
what a great girlfriend of your fiance
your streams bring me joy keep it up
tantra you're doing great oh that sounds
like a very wholesome dynamic that you
got there
yeah let me kiss your girlfriend instead
your fiance
[Music]
she can give those kisses to you if she
if she wants to
i i i don't wanna i don't wanna be in
any trouble so
[Music]
hey i'm happy that you were saying you
enjoyed the rhizome stream so that makes
me really happy
some appreciation for the riser stream
said the game itself is underappreciated
so
um really really glad to hear that
thank you soon
[Music]
they're very hungry singularity thank
you you have to cure this tale and hold
my finger it's really fluffy isn't it
does that make a dancer a rice also
reduction
now that i have spent 24 hours in here i
would like to write a formal complaint
that the usual room does not live up to
my expectation
if anything you're not giving me a peck
on the head hurts a lot more
eh we have to make the usual room more
painful
nice thing i see i'll think about
something
[Music]
thank you korean thank you for the pinky
think motion super chat reading got cut
out from archives by youtube
[Music]
but mama only was the last one
motion is too clear why to bring it up
me not so much
[Music]
which one
do i have to read it again
i thought it stopped at mamaloni
it wasn't cut off it got missed oh
[\h__\h] which one did you only send one
in uh the whole stream because then it
might be easy to find
let's see motion i see
uh 13 which one did i miss
this this is not it
this probably not it
uh wait oh no it's just people who write
emotional and stuff like that
this one the red one probably huh
feels like yesterday i was celebrating
the 300k stream i hope this
accomplishment will be
enough proof that you are extremely
talented and make amazing content
while also stealing your heart thank you
for being my ocean congrats on getting
the love you deserve
thank you sorry for missing out on it
ocean i love you thank you
so sorry about that
did you join around the 400k stream
and that's also a long long long long
time ago
thank you very much for supporting me so
long motion it was fun playing like
rhizo when you helped me so much
i'll never forget that i was here from
the start oh oh okay okay
i guess you just for some reason
mentioned differently
celebration
i i i really need to go to an idle
meeting really quick
[Music]
you want to come with me
you have to announce yourself
baby let's go let's go idle meeting
come baby baby
but first pet pet pet pet pet
yeah and you are you i'm baby let's go
let's go together
[Music]
do
me and jonkers are back
[Music]
i'm holding her right now
okay she left
[Music]
okay i think we're closer for this new
super jets from today
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah maybe i need to clean it again
today
[Music]
no problem i mean i know that you're in
a time zone that's probably
most of the time in the middle of the
night when i stream like
in the very early morning i am
sorry for that i do try though to like
start a lot of streams at least at an
okay
time so that you guys at least can see
the beginning
often um i do try that but
i also you know you know me i try to
serve every time zone because we are kfp
a worldwide fast food restaurant
we have to serve them all gotta serve
them all
[Music]
telling me about that when motion wasn't
able to tell me
[Laughter]
wow
you are a gentleman
[Music]
thank you
it's been so long since i've joined
never realizing i became a full chicken
oh
it's been such an enjoyable ride and i
look forward to my bucket time
thank you so much i promise not to like
so much please
not the usual
um uh
i mean at least you're looking forward
to the future resume but
i'm being like positive about it so okay
okay that's that's a good attitude to
have
i'll not send you to the usual room it's
okay but don't call me henry anymore
don't you guys already have enough ways
to tease me
iron hat thank you for the red super
chat can i miss your 1 million
subscribers i couldn't watch your other
streams but i
want to tell you congratulations now i
couldn't catch your order streams which
streams all of them
i don't know you missed it i hope you're
watching the archive
thank you for the rainbow the slow
[Music]
slow um
did you send me out to me wow okay i
mean
if you say so oops no
no no no no no no i'm not kissing you
who are you anyway
everything you hear before
[Music]
probably from jfp that was probably lb
though
[Music]
just joined what the [\h__\h] is going on
just a normal day at kfp
you sound so good thank you
feels like a fever tree
[Music]
bleep
this gives me like happiness and energy
[Music]
my
it's you hyping every museum f stream
[Music]
what why obvious what
why why are two people saying something
about the stream
did something happen
[Music]
epic epic cello phone is that a cell
phone
[Music]
i want to commission cell phone music
from me
no no this is not a gift museum no no
fine for me okay what the hell okay
[Music]
elvis thanks for the red super chat on
the kiara oh
hey that's your life model elvis nice
one
thank you
black rich and thank you also for the
red super chat would
much rather spoil the phoenix wife
there you are thank you i love you i
love you
i'll i'll okay i'll i'll spawn myself in
the name of black friction
i will go to lush and buy a new stock
full stock of um bath bombs and [\h__\h]
also i
want a new um mask i've been using a
mask from lush
and but it's running out and also those
like
they use like some fresh ingredients i
guess so they have this
um quite early uh expire
expiration date and i don't know if i
should still use it because mine is
actually
expired but i still have it's like half
full
so i guess i have to buy a new one
go to lunch to buy stock not those kind
of stonks
different kind of stunts
[Music]
what's your favorite burger or a meal
at kfp huh you know i wanna i wanna
there's a bunch of backgrounds i wanna
commission new backgrounds
like especially today when i saw piccolo
senpai's
background um she's been using like
she's been using like like free material
like really basic uh microphone and
background for
ages but now she's finally upgraded and
has like this super
awesome background i want something like
that for karaoke too like a stage that
is like
a little bit animated here and there and
then also
um the whole talk stage and then also i
wanna
um commission maybe an image of the
usual room
that would be dope and
also what i wanna commission is like an
office of kfb or like the inside
of kfp not necessarily the office just
like you know the the inside of the
store
of the restaurant with the counter but
like not in
nothing you know 2d pixel but like
um which is great for the loading screen
it looks so cute but i mean like you
know
like a proper uh background that i can
use for the stream
[Music]
however i'm not sure who to go to for
all these commissions
for the whole talk stage i want to go to
the
same person who made the whole talk
background um
yeah i still uh damn it there's so many
things i need to do
some of the things i have to get back to
right now to my manager for certain
things that are
somewhere in the near future maybe in
july
[Music]
yeah i have to work on those things
well i don't know if i have time this
week
[Music]
but what do you think is a cool idea to
get like a background
of the kfb restaurant yeah
that would be dope the same artist that
it did on his background
for the stage i would love it if it had
some kind of animation though and i'm
not sure who draws really good
backgrounds and can
animate it a little bit not sure who
is who has those skills
yeah the streams are going to become a
visual novel now that you say it kind of
sounds like it
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
okay i need to read to the chat stay
lord
mrs fortune junior have been attraction
uh it probably is larry dankeshen iron
hot duncan thank you for the rest of the
chat
by the way denzel you know requires more
test subjects from the usual room
the cult calendar indicates you're
lacking oh wait you know said to not say
this
what is what i don't even know about
this what
obviously i'm taking talking about test
subjects as in game testers
[Music]
no actually what the hell are we talking
about i need to be
filled in about this you know didn't
tell me neither what the hell what are
you guys doing behind my back
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
wait did i miss that red super chat
where i told myself to not miss it
did i already miss it no it's all the
way up there okay
phoenix oh phoenix why are so so lovely
in this tough and cruel world your smile
warms and supports me
is it too much to ask for a chew when
confronted by a beauty
like you ignore this common fool
foolish enough to want to be with you
from ceiling fan oh that's not from you
okay ceiling
[Music]
very charming big flirt
very very much charm flirtation
don't worry about it i have to wear it
i have to worry about it cocoon thank
you for the pinky
you are very strong woman you have tons
of endurance breaking workouts every
other day like it's nothing
also i'm finally from the free from the
24 hour usual room just want to let you
know
it's weak i don't regret calling your
chicken on low
[Music]
since one day was apparently not enough
for you i sentenced you to
one month in the usual room
and i'm sending you to the special usual
room that i keep for people like you
[Music]
have fun there i guess
i'll show you who is weak i'll show you
who is weak
it's you by the way
freaking rude cocoon
[Music]
i've been watching since your debut and
have always been impressed by your fun
presence and professionalism oh i'm not
sure if i'm so professional though
your wonderful entertainers have cheered
us all for eight joyous moms congrats
and take pride in your success
thank you so much i am pretty proud of
it yeah
thank you
i'm so proud i would love to go outside
and then and then yell
[Music]
[Applause]
fast
[Music]
that's what i would like yeah but
unfortunately
uh that's probably not so smart
[Music]
that would probably um be dangerous so
i just yell it to myself in my mind and
in my height
and yeah that must be enough for now
i'll be the vanishing cookie magazine a
random crab duncan
mama and schneider a rainbow and reagan
boogie
i originally want to send this during
the milestone stream but sadly
it wasn't possible so it's coming now i
wanted to express just how much your
streams mean to me
i've been watching you since the mario
since the full stream before the
the cake i look and you've grown so much
the way you engage with your community
and your enthusiasm is unmatched by
anyone
i love your selection of games though
i'd love if you tried to play some
genres that you aren't uh familiar with
as well whether it's shooters fighting
game or horror
i'm really looking forward to what
you'll be able to achieve in the future
especially with your upcoming songs
i'm looking forward to the next annika
of karaoke as well
i love if you would stay in the way of
the world from the near endings or
the bart song by blind guardian no idea
can't wait for the ttip to collapse as
well and i hope you'll have a great time
flushing out this tiana
as well as playing and drawing her and
the end
at the end i just hope that you stay the
way you are you help me getting
through the final part of uni and i love
for
you love you from the bottom of my heart
i love you too thank you
[Music]
thank you more professional in your work
ethic and preserver and
pursue thank you
yeah um well i mean i did try horror i
played
phasmophobia again just recently and
that was my decision that we played that
so
i was i was really [\h__\h] scared by the
way that me screaming
in that uh stream was not acting i was
really scared i was really freaking out
i'm i'm
[Music]
i'm not a chicken though
um however um
horror games i'm like
i just don't want to be in pain when i
stream
but i guess it will probably at some
point
you know i might do something like that
in 3d
maybe or so i feel like that would be
interesting
and um yeah
when i do shout out for the bug bug book
what i do want to try again or when i do
when it's right
scary the cat oh yeah that that fits too
well i don't want to try again it's a
cooking stream
[Music]
now that i have the laptop it arrived by
the way i didn't open it yet but
it did arrive now that i have the laptop
i um can easily stream from the kitchen
so i do want to try that out and that's
also a good way to test out the laptop
if it actually works well
let's
[Music]
going to have a heart attack yeah
i'll be very careful very very careful
don't worry it didn't go like nothing
happened last time either
it all went well and and the first time
was always the most difficult time now i
won't mess up again
i'll make one for stringing the jammy
phone then mango demo hello that just
saw that super chat thank you that would
be cool
send anything over a twitter i guess
i'll find it thank you adam nobody
thank is thank you is this a red super
chat because you say you can read this
quickly
[Music]
thank you for supporting me
it's on the red one huf1212
[Music]
i brought an alien away
can i get since the usual room
yeah why
[Music]
okay i'll give you a little tour i'll
i'll just wait wait for me there
okay i'll give you a tour
in like uh 20 minutes okay
thank you for the pinky you liked the
crack didn't you
me too
[Music]
it never ends the pain never ends
ginger ranger 13 duncan
really was that easy well he asked
nicely
eating mike tyson's balanced
breakfast you changed it because i
didn't want to read it
[Music]
thank you i didn't forget thank god next
time you send one it would be safer to
um add the text uh
uh uh like um in in in those um
uh
[Music]
what's that in english
i think that i don't know every word in
english
i mean i'm sure i've heard of it before
brackets okay
put red in brackets that would help me a
lot
hello kid i just wanted to say that you
are an amazing person with an amazing
personality
love the energy you give from you and
thanks to you it's actually fun to learn
german
ooh thousand thanks kiara thank you
no no no no no i stopped it
[Music]
don't be scared
wow my reflex there was on point
oh my god
[Music]
nice safe yeah
uh oh oh ah it's still showing it on the
screen
because i'm in studio will i still
disappear if i undo it
oh no i'm here oh okay okay that was
weird obvious
lpnt thank you for the pinky my boss
kissed me yesterday she cradled me with
both of her hands and kissed the back of
my head like three times i haven't
showered since
if it was just yesterday that's so fun i
guess i'm here forever now anyway can
you please give us a sample of how
flirty german sounds like
a fl how flirty german sounds like
[Music]
no i don't want to
even if you ask about pinky i'm sorry i
have to say i have to say
no nine nine
nine it's embarrassing
[Music]
maybe maybe on a different day i feel a
bit more flirty
nine
[Music]
maybe i do a german lesson again
sometimes
[Music]
okay forgive me now
yeah understandable have a nice day
yay that was not the same person but
i'll take it
[Music]
why did you ride the same thing almost
my boss kissed me why are you faking him
my boss kissed me yesterday she touched
my booty without consenting forcefully
kissed the back of my head a bunch of
time i showered instantly
oh [\h__\h] you anyways can you please show
me the way to the campus hdr department
to fill a second however
but of course of course of course let me
show you the way
let me show you that way
one more fusion room for you looking for
the top you have been a little bit
too shiny no i don't know how to say
that in english
you're you're uh you're being a bit too
playful thinking you can get away with
stuff like that
it's okay oh for [\h__\h] sake why are you
happy about it
[Music]
shut up he's just talking [\h__\h]
i did not it's actually harassed you
guys when when i
i just hold you gently and give you some
smooches
[Music]
i try my best to make you happy
all of you but you guys are so
ungrateful sometimes
you want to report me you want to make
me disappear
i don't understand you consent
you consented the moment you sent the
red super chat you know that
you know that
[Music]
so sunny into your
i'm gonna grind you
[Music]
you have a girlfriend and gloria i
thought it killed her
huh have you have you had received any
contact
from her in the past weeks
she must be long gone by now that's the
reason why she's not answering your
calls
she is not really a girlfriend anymore
anyway um
would you be in charge of angel oh my
gosh
oh i put someone in charge of hr but i
don't quite remember
who it was wasn't it one of the members
of what was it
[Music]
now
that was just you that was just you
imagining it
freaking desperate she's gone give up
[Music]
okay i'm gonna skip those flush chats
thank you for the red super chat thank
you mama i love you very very much i'm
so happy you said happy birthday to me
in chinese how can you remember
it's my best birthday ever sorry that's
that all
i always missed your stream but i will
try my best to watch it live continue to
support you
thank you
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for your support don't be
scared don't be scared
i got you i got you i wouldn't let you
go there
you don't deserve it in a good way
[Music]
duncan
what is that mysterious super chat vibe
is that the code no that does that's not
the code
[Music]
oh my god what
hey i said we can make it on the four
hours and there we go we're pretty much
done yeah i gotta do thank you for the
pinky
spoil yourself now imagine this you
could buy the quality out
i know exactly what are you going to
talk
[Music]
about you for the membership welcome
i don't know which one to buy give me
recommendations and then i'll think
about it
i'll fake it thank you sir and hello
duncan thank you for the pinky
i hope you don't mind a 28 year old
woman simp no what the hell why would i
mind
i mean employee i hope you and the wife
are doing well
this way this is for y'all in the chat
who can't donate okay gotcha homies
thank you you are 28 years young
so very young and fresh oh wait no no
kiss but i just told you
[Music]
thank
not sure if i understand your super jet
correctly
if it is
[Music]
you can't send the moment you join
carefully that's right that's right
you joined us by looking at the contract
and
all action taken by kiada is just it's
just spoiling us and the babies exactly
the contract is ironclad you want to go
these talons already
thai friend you are you deserve to be a
uh cafe employee of the month at some
point
not eating dude you don't even have to
mod you don't even have to moderate the
chat you just
be be a employee of the month
you deserve it
i think that's it now yeah okay we did
it okay guys thank you so much for
watching today
just a chill little stream where i was a
cat
a dream dream come true
i want to be a cat again i will be when
we're watching
cats on inna's channel and
the day after tomorrow so i'll see you
there also
on reyna's channel don't miss it uh
watch
uh follow my twitter if you don't want
to miss out on stuff like that on
notifications like that
or just subscribe to every single whole
life member
but that might actually make you miss
out on things if your subscription box
is so freaking full of everything
[Music]
well then well then thank you guys
and in german we say i'll be that then
i'll go get some
uh dinner now i think um very hungry
hungry bye bye love you all so much i
would not thank you for the pinky
really really let me just say because
the rest got cut off yesterday and the
day before yesterday but
[Music]
i i don't know like honestly
yeah maybe i deserve the 1 million subs
but i don't deserve so many
freaking super chats holy [\h__\h] you guys
are crazy
thank you for supporting me like this
this is insane alex thank you
thank you so much and also thank you for
subscribing
and watching my streams following me on
twitter and everywhere
i hope um i don't care about reaching 2
million or anything like that but i just
hope we can spend
a lot of wholesome moments fun moments
together
in the future cry together laugh
and just you know make memories
use this time that we have together as
much
as possible as wisely as possible
and grow together evolve together
into cats into frogs into crowds into
anything el canal river
[Music]
foreign
can i just read it as crackers that
would be much easier
thank you for toughing function typhoon
[Music]
i love you too you're the best
albert's good oh my god
thank you for the rental
[Music]
thank you
bye
[Music]
oh cats thanks hello nice one
good job
[Music]
is