[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
KY key
[Laughter]
k m
rooster yeah farmer or Gardener wa is
back in the house that's s that's
me okay
today once again we're going to be
playing stard Valley sorry I'm a little
bit out of breath I was once again
trying to eat as fast as possible and
made some
tea cuz yesterday I was feeling like
kind of dry in my throat but now I have
tea and I'm using the super expensive
Manuka Honey today cuz I ran out of all
my other honey so that should be
good hello very fancy mhm but just one
spoon one spoon for the first cup any
following cups because I made a big
Theros bottle of tea any following cups
will not be blessed by the Manuka Honey
unless I feel like maybe maybe I want
some after all but for now it's
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
ah first of all
[Music]
reached 1 million thank you so
much thank you it happened soon after I
woke up yeah woohoo
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah let's go thank you so much it means
a lot to me well we did it it didn't
even take that much time overall just
like 3 weeks yeah yeah yeah I didn't I
didn't uh you know know think if we
could do
it in the beginning before I released it
but now yeah we did it thank you so much
for listening to it on YouTube or
wherever else you're listening to it now
that the MV has reached 1
million uh don't like I don't know if
anybody was purposefully like watching
it on YouTube because they wanted to
help me out with the views uh but now
don't feel pressured to do it anymore in
that case and maybe let's stream it
normally on the streaming services
whenever you feel like it no
pressure oh sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry ah thank
you is also is also listening to it she
showed me proof even not that I was
doubting it but damn I'm really in her
top five of
spotify and the rest is just like K-pop
groups let's go I am on the same level
for her as like famous K-pop groups oh
I knew she would like this song I knew
it I hope she will continue to like my
music yeah it's nice it's nice to be uh
appreciated directly from like a
coworker like this so
openly someone who expresses their
support so openly openly it really you
know makes me feel
appreciated and just overall that
support and and you guys everything
makes me feel very validated thank you
so much all too of course
yeah MAA also like she left a comment on
the MV too a while ago so but Mauna is
also one of those people who are really
into K-pop just like
me so it tickles her
fancy I
[Music]
suppose K pop K pop let's
go okay so today we'll play more stario
Valley I cooked yesterday so today I
don't have to cook cuz I have
leftovers that is good news let me tell
you
that but but I'm still going to end
around midnight
nonetheless but yeah and here we
go what are these pink birds flamingos
or some other that's not flamingos right
they don't have that weird
red thing on their
head no thinking what to eat tonight
exactly I was really thinking of like
making lazy ass frozen pizza last night
but then I checked the meat like I told
you and the expiration date was indeed
yesterday so didn't want to waste it
especially cuz the recipe was freaking
schnitzel they may have given me random
recipes that were kind of me for the
most part but I mean a schnitzel oh
yeah schnitzel is not a bad recipe
that's a the best I can hope
for uh when it's
randomized r randomizer this it's like a
randomizer mod for
hellofresh nah not really a
mod dony
wony yeah oh it's raining by the way as
we know
tomorrow is clear and sunny all day
amazing
oops um our luck is
oh the spirits are very happy they will
do their best to shower everyone with a
good fortune oh the queen of sauce what
it is I the queen of sauce here to teach
you a new mouth watering recipe from my
secret cookbook this week's dish COA
envisioning BL
Bland moons of Limp cabbage you're not
alone but a great Co Sal can be so much
more make sure you have juicy fresh
cabbage for this one toss of a little
vinegar and mayonnaise and you're all
set Ah that's
crisp oh so that's how you learn recipes
you have to watch the TV ah okay then I
got to do that every day
now yeah I guess we got to go to the
mines but I don't think I have that much
oh
oh finally some
cauliflower also why are these dead
or are they not dead they're fine right
some more beans oopsie sorry a so I want
the
beans I think that's it nice so we got
to keep oh we have a special green bean
we got to keep one of the cauliflowers
probably so I need some stuff to eat
right if I go to the mines M this is not
it's not that
much it's not that much do I do you
think I need one of the special ones
probably not right ah because like it
blinks for both of them but I don't
think I specifically need a a special
one I don't think so you can make the
can
I
uh
uh you mean this one this one I can't
make I don't have
acorns I have pine
cones I don't think I have the stuff
check for onions in the
forest but then we
again we need to be ready in the morning
right away we again like going to be
late need acorns where the hell do I get
acorns
oh uhoh oh I can shake the
trees I didn't know
that I guess only sometimes something
falls
out Hey where's my luck
now or should I chop trees for the acons
oh no you can shake them for okay okay
that was my intuition
now but no gain no pain no gain oh I
found food at
least okay we're going to gather some
food and then I guess we'll go into the
mines and then now I'm going to give
myself the habit of shaking all the
trees
nothing
nothing is there a certain amount of
times I need to shake it
shake it shake shake shake shake it
shake it shake it shake it shake shake
shake it like i b a ro picture or it's
maybe not the right tree because these
are different trees maybe there's a a
specific
one I left my gear yeah no I'm not going
directly I
guess it's
okay just once okay
I have to wait until the weather is
cooler than being
cool ice
cold I'm not going to wait until the
weather is ice cold I don't want to go
outside at all when that's the case can
I shake this one
no this
one
oh oh I thought something fell down and
I can't see it uh
man didn't my snitel look delicious on
Twitter I'm always like
so nervous when I fry something with
like so much
oil that's really why I should be using
my air fryer
obviously come
on why are they so rare
but yeah it went fine just once like I I
washed some tongs I I I rinsed them
really quickly and then I forgot there
was still like a few water droplets on
there and then I put them to touch the
Schnitzel I wanted I wanted to turn it
around so I put them into the cooking
oil and then it it went
like and I was like ah but it was all
okay it was only only that one
moment is it the wrong season wait my
mommy wrote
something okay my mom says this is a
waste of
time uh okay I I don't know I I really
don't know how to spend my
time I'm at the same time I'm looking
for food oh there's a
flower I'm just looking for food at the
same same
time cuz I want to go into the minds of
Moria get seeds on your
farm they're on the ground mostly what
get seeds on your
farm
what what what
what
what the what fishing is an
option fishing he
that thing is
moving what the [\h__\h] is
that I'm just you know doing everything
uh Slowly by Pace still have to get to
know this game but yeah the the shaking
the trees really seems like a waste of
time so
far man
[Music]
I guess I'm going to go to the mines I
don't know if this will be enough food I
feel like it won't be and i' I'd like
also to have food that doesn't take up
several slots in my inventory you know
is it open right now can I buy some food
I don't really want
to sorry for spilling water
m nah he doesn't really
it doesn't really sell what I would
want Saloon sells food oh
okay don't mind me does she have a
lesser opinion of me
now yo cookies why why is it oh is this
because of the good luck day the trash
is giving me more
stuff than
ever hey yo
shees if you take a and yeah oh yes she
has a lesser opinion now
[\h__\h] wait this not the
saloon trash cookies they they were
packaged don't
worry they were totally
packaged did you finish find the trash
book yet trash book
no ooh that is expensive oh but they
have recipes
oh
potato
oil egg
milk I think I have milk eggs are okay
wheat flour I need to be able to make
wheat
flour need to learn how to make that
need to learn how to make any of these
so I can make my own
food oh I oh I need a kitchen anyway
oh you can't just cook like like you're
crafting okay okay okay
okay just really quick
oh wait go around the corner go go go go
go
go okay nothing that's fine I got some
things
H okay I'm going to go back I'm going to
go to the
mines even though it's already
4m. I'm not going
to endure that much anyway because of
lack of food
so
uh
[Music]
I'm going to
keep none none of this oh I'm going to
bring some of
it sell
this and then this
and I wish I had some more seats for
this okay do I even have
space sword and pickaxe is all I need
right do I I don't need a normal axe
right
[Music]
I'm just going to bring the leak now
too for eating oh I could bring the eggs
no no I'm keeping the egg I'm keeping
the egg right I'm keeping it oh the
chickens I forgot about the chickens ah
I'm such a bad chicken
mother good morning sunshine sorry I'm a
bit late but you slept in anyway did you
large egg large egg
amazing they are as cute and fluffy as
ever the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] was
that I'm just going
to put this in I think these two I
need mhm and then this one I can sell or
eat right I'm going to sell
it safe from the
butcher it was a close call my oh oh
yeah right I started the day with like
energy level on like
zero what well
that's a kind of shitty
start cuz then I have to heal myself all
the way up and then I'm going to have no
food left for in the mines anyway yeah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] the mines today I'm not going
there let's maybe fish let's just go
fishing let's just go fishing
M fishing it
is I mean the day is almost over already
anyway time passes so
fast oh yeah okay well I guess I needed
some
food oh they need energy too fishing
need energy too you
[Music]
what how much do I
get
barely oh that was good cookies were
good cookies we a good CH wait fishing
uh where should I go for
[Music]
fishing is there a good spot up here too
or do I need
[Music]
to beach H
okay [\h__\h] I can't breathe so well did
you guys see EDF Ed e f
EDF GAA Iris and me are going to be
like um
early early order bonus can I fish
here for the game if you pre-order it
from either na or Europe and we look so
cute okay it's trash again EDF EDF
EDF at early purchase not PR oh okay
early purchase bonus
is I think all of us not just one of us
right Iris can't get the
DLC that's maybe there's a way around
it maybe there's a way around it for
her it would be cool if we could all
play it together I mean I'm not I wasn't
planning on buying it either I was
hoping I would get a code to download it
so uh maybe
Iris somehow will be able to obtain it
that way as well I forgot what a beach
is I think it's over here and then
down yeah it's the the sixth game of its
kind was it
the
sixth what was it the sixth
oopsie yeah already so
[Music]
many yo I
actually I got the offer ages ago it's
been so
long and now it was so sudden just felt
so spontaneous like oh
oh oh oh oh
oh this fish hates me already okay I
hate you too I got to get lucky with a
good
fish yeah it's been ages like I
I got the offer ages ago I recorded my
lines ages ago like sometime last year
oh oh oh no don't fall off now don't
fall off now we've been doing so well
come on come on yeah yeah rice rice
woohoo a hering
okay I'm going to keep all the fish now
for the collection
thingy oh that's so fast oh my God
they're so excited they're so
excited oh oh oh oh interesting
interesting you just want to stay in one
spot which is also a little bit
difficult but okay oh oh better than
going up and down and up and down H
boot nice
ooh grilling some sausages and stuff
yummy
amazing already having Grill parties
it's already that time of the
year I need to buy a
grill need to get a grill and then some
grills as
well maybe there's a a set bonus getting
a grill and some grills
for this Grill
girl oh there's
treasure can I ditch the fish and then
go for the treasure should I have done
that hot grills hot grills in your
area I can do both treasure is hard but
it doesn't seem to be moving it's just
like there
don't wor if you can't get treasure okay
fish is more important
okay I
understand what was I talking about oh
yeah grills but also
EDF
oh yeah so I I'm looking kind of crazy
maybe you guys saw the preview that
video I retweeted it on Twitter so check
it out or like you can look it up up on
YouTube Ed
F6 PlayStation 5 announcement trailer or
something like that so that's the thing
it's only for PlayStation 5 right now
right oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] only for PlayStation 5 oh the day
is almost over let's
go so if you want Wawa in this game you
have to have a PlayStation 5 and be from
na or Europe oh on Steam too yeah but is
the purchase bonus
for not only for PlayStation I read
something about that but I don't even
know the
details oh oh please please please
please please please I'm getting better
at this but I keep on getting the same
[\h__\h] fish is it the
area I need to go
anyway we don't want to wake
up uh with zero energy
again so we better hurry back quickly
wait what is the fastest path y
y can I I don't know I don't know I
don't know I don't know I'm just going
to go the one that I
know wait I can't I don't think I'll
make it
no wait no I can't make
it no no no no no no no no
no [\h__\h] but I leveled up oh I got a
crafting recipe for the mayonnaise
machine can make mayonnaise yay and a
sprinkler well at least we have
something to do
then [\h__\h] second day in a
row man I'm I I
[\h__\h] so basically just like
IRL with me streaming like when I see
it's hitting midnight it's time to
go I should oh it's not always the
recipes I should remember that though
midnight is time to
go wait oh because I leveled up oh
y welcome to living off the land we're
back again with another tip for yall now
listen up it's salmonberry SE oh okay
what the [\h__\h] is that all across the
countryside bushes are teaming with
Juicy little berries and they're free
for the taking ooh harvesting them is a
great way to earn some extra cash okay
I'll be keeping an eye
out uh this please today today so I'm
not going into the mines
today tomorrow is clear and sunny
okay today oh d where the berries it's
already oh oh wait those are not salmon
berries those are
raspberries butterflies I think it's
summer now is it is this
summer let's go to the
chickens
wait
uh still spring
[Music]
mhm
um do I need to keep the clams for
something and the the fish I'm keeping
for now but not all of them right I can
get rid of like
[Music]
two you can sell the clowns okay oh yeah
I should just check uh but you say you
say oh for crafting
M can I get one back
thanks I like the music music music now
I think it changed from the usual
one it's
fun MH
[Music]
check mail yeah told there's so much to
do okay EDF announcement Chima 1
million and I have a
personal thank you for you guys because
froggy wa merch sales ended yesterday
right
oh now they're growing like a
lot take take them ah you can't why
not or or the day before yesterday I
don't know so they
ended
and I was told by
staff that and I I was shown of course
the the
statistics I was shown that it's sold so
well thank you so
much it has done so well especially the
plushy yeah things are going really
well and the merch sold a lot better
even than my last Anniversary
merchandise
a lot better
sheesh and that really made me think you
guys love froggy Wawa so much huh was a
a good idea for me to make froggy waa
merchandise oh my God I'm such a
business woman
wao and there may have been someone and
I have a feeling I know
who someone purchased like 70 of the
froggy W
plushies who could have
thank you so much what the [\h__\h] right
what the [\h__\h]
man
oh but very much appreciate even without
those 70 FR ra plushies uh there we
still insanely good sales so thank you
so much I really appreciate
it thanks to you guys no no no no no
that yeah we all know who that is thanks
to you guys it went so well and and I
can I can uh feel relieved now I did a
good job promoting and I did a good job
making froggy waa
popular
yeah was it you Jindo I'm definitely
thinking of Jindo Jindo are you
here yeah
and Dear Mrs Wawa or Miss I don't know
last night a Georgia team member found
you incapacitate
Oh I
thought when I read this I think of
decapitated like no head you made me
worry for a
moment medical team was dispatched to
bring you home safely we're glad you're
okay you've been build nine gold Ah
that's okay that's not that
much crabby waa crabby waa is really
something I I've been thinking of oh oh
oh okay now 19 gold oh [\h__\h] does it like
double every time I know you're just
getting started as a garden so I wanted
to give you a little tip most crops only
grow in one season when summer arrives
your spring crops will all die out so
plan ahead oh
[\h__\h] guys you have to warn me when that
happens
oopsie open it up oh my God sometimes I
just the only reason I I keep on
pressing the wrong button then is
because I first tried the right click
button it's not working so I'm like oh
maybe it was the left button and then I
tried a left button and it's wrong and I
tried a right button again and it just
doesn't work so I try the left button
again okay what I do with all this can I
bring
[Music]
something this needs to go to the to a
collection the large egg number Uno
large egg egg number
do this can although does this also is
this also affected by my luck the
geod oh you guys played with controllers
sheesh that won't finish growing before
fortive hey how the [\h__\h] should I know
how the [\h__\h] do I know when they are
done
growing I have no idea the fishies are
for the museum I guess right
geot are not affective
okay seat says how long it takes
well
well okay one one green bean only right
one green bean one cauliflower one
potato which I don't have anymore I need
to plant potatoes [\h__\h] and a
parsnip one parsnip parip parip [\h__\h]
okay I really need to
grow is any of this
a potato or a parsnip how do I
know
mhm I have one of each in here I don't
see one you mean in the field right cuz
I don't see anything
here I really need more space I really
need that stupid bag I'm running out of
space
those are random yeah yeah I know there
like a lot of them are random so we
won't know on for a
while
where aha okay this is the one for the
eggs
where's the one for the ah here for the
wood and stuff right is over
here yeah
9999 10 99 wood actually twice 99 Stone
I don't think I can do that yet can
I 99 Stone I can do
[Music]
and is there a way to take a certain
amount I'll just take it
all take oyster too I have I have no
wait which one is the
oyster oyster oyster o o oyster
oyster you see an oyster
here that is a [\h__\h]
oyster I don't I
I those
space oh wait oh those are still
available
okay uh okay H I don't know let's go uh
okay I'm going to do some things uh did
I check out the chickens yet I think I
did right I did I did everything I did
all the the
watering
okay
daffodil not now
this game is a little
bit overwhelming and underwhelming at
the same time for me at the
moment 36 months thank
you
uh what did I come here for again oh
yeah it's just whelming yeah
like I like there's moments where I have
no idea what to do at
all and then now it's like and I got to
go here and there and here and
there but under the ring is the wrong
word I guess because I just feel like
wait let's go to the museum first I just
feel like I don't
know what's the right thing to
do and how to do things and then the
time is
stressful the time is so
stressful eh what you don't want the
fish who wants the fish I thought I
thought thought we needed to give them
fish huh am I not going to give anybody
the
fish Community Center the community
center what the okay okay because it
didn't go like bling bling
bling see that's that's the that's the
problem right now that's the [\h__\h]
problem
okay I feel like my mom is probably
molding while watching my
stream she's
like back seating me on Discord but
she's probably like if you know a game
so well I've had this before watching
someone
else and they're just not getting it
yet feel like my mom's absolutely
like all right
now hello ah okay this broken ass fish
tank are we sure it's safe to put some
fish in here
now
ah there you go and the clam
nice and the
fish oh
maybe maybe in like the next level oh no
they're not here
or or right those okay I I don't need
those
actually oops
see so how do I give you the right
amount okay there we
go
nice those ones don't go in there you
can just sell them ah huh all right
okay now I we can go get the
geod bnie
bird
berries
M so what's the best thing to do with
the salmon berries also just sell them
whenever I get
them I'll talk to
you I know you're mocking me girl I know
you're Army digging in the trash and now
you think I'm I'm just a just a I don't
know dirty dirty
woman very cheap better to eat it m okay
okay I would love to do
[Music]
that ah already have that so what do I
do with these that I already
have nice ne ne ne ne
cat
Stone cell do I not need them for
crafting Museum or cell okay but Museum
already has
it this one looks so
[Music]
special wow it's pink and so
pretty okay no crafting then all right
all right we're just going to sell I'm I
I will gladly do that
H it is my unlucky day makes
sense ah yeah oh yeah I was talking
about the
merchandise so yeah and thank you so
much for your support and please look
forward to everything
arriving Jemma told me she also bought
one froggy waa plushy and then I said oh
okay so I guess I'm never visiting you
ever again I'm not going to a place that
has froggy waha
inside you are frogy
supporter I see how it
is I see how it is do I need to buy more
seats guys what do you think should I
buy more
seats wait I didn't get the eggs
I forgot about the
eggs I forgot about the
eggs he'll never visit my house I guess
I'm not visiting a lot of your
places parsnips Lots
parsnips
lots and
potatoes I'm selling this
right wait
wait mommy don't don't caps block
me I'm I'm Don what do you mean I'm
donating this is selling
right oh you mean I should take that
green bean and donate it yeah that's
also what I originally wanted to do
yeah uh you need five gold quality
prices for and they grow okay
so well I don't have that much money so
I don't think I can buy that much
today but I'll try to buy if it's even
open right now 5:20
[Music]
p.m. my mom's like stressing me to make
the Mayo
machine don't stress for onee completion
of the community yeah that's probably
what my mom is trying to make me
do she's m maxing
me cuz she played the game several times
like several saves right so she wants
to she wants to do everything
quickly where where where do the bean
go what where do the bean go how do I
know where the bean go I already checked
this where do the bean go where do the
egg
go maybe up
here
Bean stupid bean egg
what okay it had to be large okay
good sheesh sheesh
okay yeah I'm not getting anything done
in the first year at this rate which is
okay I wouldn't even know that that's
like a thing you want to try to do I
wouldn't even know that that is an
aspiration to have
get the berry get the berry get the
berry what what did I not get the
berry also can I not go faster is this
like the maximum is there not a dash a
running oh that's stupid
Berry stupid
Berry how dare
you you're not supposed to okay it's
okay if you're a bit confused from a
start that that I am you know what will
that happened today me falling asleep on
the
streets I will go back home on time
sorry was not trying to chop off your
head just trying to talk to
you just want to socialize a little bit
because I think that is important in
this game
right have I told you Haley and I
sisters who's
haey this going to get you anything
no wait I should give a flower to
someone do you want a flower oh wait you
[Music]
Pam uh a
wait there we go she's feeling a
positive energy from this
gift I I don't know you why are you
talking to me we know each other by now
why do you forget about me my father was
also blacksmith not
hold good to know thanks for the random
information really
random I love blueh haired lady she's a
hippie
hippie a happy hippie a happy
hippo happy hippo happy hippie on a
hippo
[Music]
Emily best girl Emily's great there's I
see there's certain girls that are more
popular than others and I have observed
that you guys those per popular girls
are mostly just you know the
prettiest I am
disappointed disappointed but not
surprised
all the girls are
pretty yeah yeah they're not not
pretty all the El eligible girls are
pretty in this game oh oh you think
so the [\h__\h]
fiber Bon Bonk just trying to clean up a
little bit and get these mats because I
need them right I need the
wood what about the
boys the
boys so far I'm not really interested in
any of them
surprise surprise surprise you should
not be surprised by that oh oh I'm my
energy I want to finish the tree but
okay I'm going to bed
now but first do I have something else
to
sell what can I
sell all of these things
maybe
nothing who did Mama told he marry mommy
who who did you
marry my cat is sleeping on my
bed I'm so
blessed okay this game is winning wait
oh oh zero gold because I I
I did I give all my eggs to did I forget
to pick up the eggs or did I bring all
my eggs
elsewhere I think I brought all my eggs
to the museum or Community Center thingy
mommy says she always lives with
cobus don't know who that
is ex donate okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
this Bas is a good
choice oh I don't know him yet who the
[\h__\h] is
K hi baby where's your
sister where is she is she still inside
why is she always awake so late oh why
you working hard on these
eggs one large egg another large why did
you give me double eggs why what's going
on you crazy crazy chicken you just
really had to push some more out huh
was feeling like there was no space in
your tummy I get it so many eggs good
morning so can I sell them right away is
that okay should I keep them I'm selling
them hello T I hope you're feeling
settled in your new home I am now I'm
wunning to let you know that Pierre's
store is now selling fertilizers why
don't you swing by
no forgot one thing
um neutral today should I still go to
the mines [\h__\h] I
should tomorrow today partially cloudy
with a light Breeze or is that
tomorrow H wait uh mommy said okay wait
mommy said Mayo
machine I need 15 Wood 15 Stone ah I
think I can make every can make it
except because of the copper bar I'm
guessing the copper bar I need to make
separately out of my little
coppers do I bring it to the
blacksmith is 22
enough oh I need a furnace okay I can
make it then okay
uh
furnace 20 copper or okay 25 stone I can
make it but then I don't think I can
make the m machine
anymore which means we should go to the
mine to get more copper
ore
so uh
okay and this I just put it
outside nice do I need to put fire in
how do I use
it requires one coal
aha okay
then it is time to go to the mines
chicken have no hay
okay I'mma eat
those I'mma keep one cuz I that's still
necessary
okay okay this is what I'm
bringing this is what I'm bringing
mhm mhm mm okay water the
pl I'm already so low on energy how the
[\h__\h] because of me making the furnace
huh I must have drained a little bit of
energy [\h__\h] is there no way like maybe
taking a little nap or so to regain some
more
[Music]
energy relaxing game they say Yeah
ironic isn't
it oh we should make sprinklers as well
soon cuz we already have the
recipe o beans
ready for the
taking the beans
are pretty
great I have to say they they took a
long time to
grow oh wait the cauliflower is ready
too I need to put something else
here but yeah we we're getting uh
parsnip and potato seeds right
bck need more
water need more
water Chad that just forget about
it
[Music]
um are we
back hello
OBS died for 1
second no need to panic no need to
[Music]
panic is this
watered
yeah it we're back I was asking you guys
why did the music stop is this a bug why
the [\h__\h] am I out of
energy crunch
goodbye no keep
keep okay and I'm going to check out the
shop and then I'm going to
go no BG I'm no but the game has see
there it is it's
back y free
berries more berries
please can you make a food bar yet no I
don't think so I'm missing
something so sad
[Music]
please while set up your Twitch no I
asked jenma to set it up I think she did
but she forgot to tell me that it's
finished but I saw I got the email that
the account was created
and uh one person somehow already found
it and uh like followed
[Music]
it how did you find it huh how did you
know that's
[Music]
me come and get it folks coupons for 50%
off your purchase at JoJo mod really
give me
50% well I want I want I want I want I
want I want
[Music]
two you searched today and you didn't
find it
well don't worry once I get it started
you will find
it but I can't match those prices I'd be
selling at a
loss sometimes you have to do that to
get people interested in your business
and then you go to the normal prices you
know it must be so difficult for you to
lose your loyal customers like that but
can you blame them JoJo corporations Le
the superior Choice soon the whole town
will realize
that yeah well at Le Georgia Market
seems to be always open unlike
you did you did you just gr me with its
farmer waa that's right that's me okay
uh you guys said I need many many right
and uh like not many potatoes right just
one is okay
right not much how much oh more parsnips
one
[Music]
potato maybe two to be safe two
potato see yeah
okay the walking
sounds oh man already 12:00 p.m.
okay I'm going to bring these seeds back
I'm going to uh plant them and then
we'll go into the mines for real for
real my energy
man
crunch is it is it really that crunchy
[Music]
no go
away got to fix
this okay let put them right here oh
wait I actually I don't have that much
space guess I'm going to make another
row still have some space face or I'll
like add on onto here
nah
no okay that will do for
now
perfect why is there no music
if the whole game was with no music okay
then I could bring my
own but this is so
awkward okay I'm done I'm
done I'm done with the groundwork we are
going going to go
now got to bring this to to
eat right away
okay yeah I mean generally like I
wouldn't mind a whole game with no music
because I like the ambience
only it's
nice okay
crunch ber nice this is the perfect
season season for mining because I can
get all these yummy Berry Stacks did you
guys see my strawberries not all of them
are oh wait I need I need to pick them
up not all of them are so red though
most of them are still like green and
small but there were like two or so that
looked already almost edible they looked
more red on the picture than they really
were so I wouldn't eat them yet it's
still a little bit too early and most of
them are still very green so not quite
ready but they're
growing ah you you
guys you guys follow my Twitch account
now I have 80 followers are you sure
it's the right one it's something with
like whole life Ian at the
end probably because uh Taki Kar only
was already taken or
so wait can I not uh go
[Music]
directly what the
[\h__\h] what the
hell why YouTube why
H OBS
actually not doing so good today
[Music]
this one
more oh today today you're kind of in a
weird mood my OBS I was going to ask you
guys is lauan do you guys no is she
still actively streaming on
Twitch cuz today I saw her stream on
YouTube uh singing K stream maybe she
only streams games on Twitch and then
anything else she streams on
YouTube time to time she should just do
dual
streaming
oh like what I'm trying to
do
nice okay fight fight fight
will that slime be
useful
oh then what the hell are you I still
don't know but you look like a crap to
me Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum they dropped like
nothing oh oh he wants to poison me oh I
dodged oh that one that one has red eyes
the other one
doesn't the fighting in this game is so
weird oh
wow
again
again what the hell sorry I don't know
what's wrong with uh OBS today I didn't
change any settings
uh guys don't leave
me don't leave me alone in this dark
dark mine
Y what the
[\h__\h] yeah you're back right I don't know
what's wrong with obs
yes get a hold of yourself I am working
and I need you to work as
well oh [\h__\h] inventory
full let me eat some
stuff get it together OBS for
real okay
I need this quartz it looks so pretty
I'm not going to leave it
behind oh yeah this time this time I
want to I want to try
mining oh but I guess it takes more
energy
then let me finish this slime first it's
so evil it's so
evil why does this one have red
eyes okay now the the crab is a little
bit scared so it's like at least staying
in place okay okay now I can focus on
you
oh what you going to do but I didn't get
any different kind of uh loot did I do
it
wrong I can
Parry I don't like
parrying in any kind of
game oh
nice 9:00 p.m. warning [\h__\h] already so
late
huh oh wait wait wait wait wait
oh they all saw me I'm pulling the
argro can I attack from here no okay
bring it on little slime
people Bring It On fight
me I may have a midnight bedtime but I'm
still a fierce Warrior trust
me one coal might as well get rid of the
coal I don't know if that was a worthy
exchange I found is that normal or or
Hardwood
hidewood I have yet to obtain I
literally I I mean I know but I have
some I have
some I probably should go
soon what what what what was that what
was that
sound level up or something
but I'm looking if there's any more like
special
things down here Quest complete
oh was it the slimes that I killed or
the blood that I've
shed oh is it a circle does it go in a
circle coal uh okay I I want to take the
coal
[Music]
but I really have to go
damn this is so
clutch why already have to
go I should go I'm going to
go okay but this time I'm I'm going to
make it at
least going early means at least I will
not wait there's a cat here
I will not fall asleep and lose money
and lose
energy I have 200 followers
now damn we're growing fast on Twitch
twitch is going to ban me has there ever
been incidents like that like with
YouTube where oh no was that Twitter
guess that was just Twitter not
YouTube when like somebody somebody gets
followed too much
M I wouldn't know what to
sell ah that okay okay should go to the
mines on a rainy day cuz then you don't
have to spend so much energy
on uh on working on your garden YouTu
just takes the subs away yeah ha it
happened to narissa switch what getting
banned for getting too many subscribers
right away although I always say
subscribers but subscribers on Twitch
are different from YouTube subscribers
on Twitch are like members on YouTube
it's so
confusing okay let's just put everything
here in here for
now
yeah but you guys know what I mean
probably most of the
time new crafting recipe charcoal kid
can I make new charcoal with that by
burning wood probably oo lots of money
from the eggs eat ay
M check Journal yeah yeah yeah
yeah
K enter The Adventurous Guild because I
killed 10 slimes yeah use your furnace
to smell a copper bar I do want to do
that reach level 40 find Robin's lost
axe wherever that is feeding animals
build a silo Silo is also um one thing
W beautiful
he wow look at the growth
here
okay
uh let me think I don't think I can make
mayo machine yet I don't
know let's see uh wait you need
coal so how does this
work well take the [\h__\h] coal then
what do you want from me oh
okay did it it took the coal like
automatically from my inventory and now
it's working on it
okay let's wait and pick up some nice
fresh chicken eggs pet and pet no don't
worry you're not going to the butcher
today not
today maybe tomorrow what's this huge
egg small egg hey who was slacking today
it must have been you the white eggs
come from you right
I would assume oh wait that looks like
gold oh it's copper
okay wait did it say how many I need
just
one one okay I think I can make
it uh wood Stone Earth
crystal wood Stone Earth
crystal wao let's
go I'm made the egg mayonnaise
machine we can make make egg cream now
no why are you standing there no no I
want to
no no why is it
here can I move
it how do I move it he it with the
pickaxe
okay oh
[Music]
oh there you go so what now do I just
never sell my eggs again but just make
Mayon all the time
[Music]
now may better
money h
no okay oh all right all right uh okay
okay
nice nice to
this I can make instruments now okay I'm
not interested right now oh we're having
one machine per
chicken oh okay mommy also says I should
make another
one does it take so
long uh
uh wait
[Music]
no
mhm game is overwhelming me
you want to buy this game it's a
classic if you like these kind of
farming games but also have a little bit
of
fighting then it's great but be ready to
be overwhelmed just like me and be ready
to read the wiky every single page of it
if you're not getting back seated by a
whole chat and by your mother like me
then you don't have nobody to help you
then you need the wiki the wiki is your
only hope
maybe I should read the wiki but I'm not
I'm not that like I'm not feeling like
getting that hardcoree about this game
yet I take and then I make one
more oh right next to it and then the
other
stuff can go
in I like how it's
breathing squeezing the
egg yeah
normally I don't know normally you
wouldn't just immediately go for the
wiki if you start a new game
right like any game not just this in
particular your first thought wouldn't
be um okay first let me read through a
whole
Wiki if anything you'd want to play it
blind but this game seems to be a bit
different this one I've been I feel like
it's always so easy to miss it I don't
think I've missed it so far but maybe I
should get rid of the
tree also the color difference in like
what I've watered and what I haven't
watered is not so clear not as clear as
I'd wish it to be so it's was like got
to be really careful and remember where
you have watered
before it's so subtle yeah
H this is like Terraria I don't know is
it I haven't played Terraria and we got
the
Mayo oh I love
mayonnaise and I guess I'm selling it
now goodbye
mayonnaise what
now what
now oh yeah oh I played it yeah for one
test but I I don't even remember what I
[Music]
did clear your farm what what what oh
you mean get rid of the trees and stuff
here oh
coal have you seen the cave on your pH
I've seen it yeah but I didn't go in
yet should I
go this one down here
right sto too big can't pass
through there's nothing there right now
oh
okay m
[Music]
oh my God so hard to get
through what am I growing down there
weren't all of those random and then
they turned out to be like apparently
all the
same I should plant the carrot seeds
[Music]
I'm
sorry star berries oh this I right they
do look like my
strawberries they do look exactly like
that oh that makes so much
sense okay perfect just enough water for
that
and more mayonnaise to sell yay I love
eating potatoes um like baked oven or
fried potatoes anything with mayonnaise
yesterday I mixed it with sour
cream and that actually I feel like I
love
that it makes the mayonnaise a little
bit less intense a little bit more
fresh it was kind of an
accident but it was a very happy
accident
oh it wasn't supposed to happen but it
happened because it wanted to happen
okay we should go I don't know talk to
the adventurer Guild dude maybe I don't
know if I can find him where is
he
guys where's where is that
dude ah ah near the mines okay
okay hi how you all doing do you have
everything you need for the
farm if not we might be able to help you
out I think right now I can't
complain
berries more more ber BET's
Coble I need to start a Berry Farm so
that I can call myself Betty's coal my
favorite Idol group that doesn't exist
anymore on Tuesdays and Thursdays I work
at Harvest Clinic he says he likes
having me around in his in case his
medical equipment goes
Haywire what business would I have in
the hospital or in the clinic right
now anymore yeah they've like retired
pretty much a long time
ago and cobal means like Factory so it's
Betty's Factory that was the name of the
group good times man good times hey
there Wawa I was just daydreaming about
some new carpentry projects oh what
pattern are you thinking of huh you're
probably growing a lot of interesting
plants on your new Farm
huh oopsie are you doing okay that your
place how's the woodwork what do you
care about the woodwork are you want to
cover it up with a carpet if it's too
like
ugly thank you for thinking of
me c boy Factory no no no no no no no no
no no no no okay okay wait you have to
there's different
writings depends on the Kani kuo is not
always Factory but so not that you think
automatically KU can do means Factory
no wait
over
here cooy Cobo Coboy b
[Music]
ball
uh
[Music]
oh how do I
join I've come to join your guild
[Music]
I'm already in I just did it just by
walking
in 1,000 Monsters Just
Lay yeah I'm already in just by walking
in that's so weird so
confusing pretty low bar yeah I mean at
kfb it's kind of the
same you walk into my stream you're part
of kfp it's over and it has only just
begun at the same
[Music]
time you have signed the waiver the
moment you join the moment you enter my
stream you might call it a scam you
might also call it just like really
quick
procedure really convenient you know
don't you love it when things go really
fast and you don't have to wait
forever don't remember signing anything
exactly just your present was
enough oh so many berries let's
go let's go they're going to be so
useful for mining maybe tomorrow I
wonder what weather we have tomorrow oh
also there's a berry bush over there
too let me set it free
NE chop chop chop
chop ta actually let me get rid of the
tree it won't grow back
right so this way it's easier to
access the berries
[Music]
nice go away
F there goes froggy W while running away
with my
money okay
uh can I sell
something should I sell something the
eggs are turned into Mayon I sold
that this maybe I'll keep I think I'm
good I think I'm
good does taking
water uh take energy let's see cuz then
I'd rather do it now before I go to
sleep no it
didn't I'm about to steal wow wow wow
wow I am just taking
some money to make up for the damage she
has
done in my
home cat is always sleeping on my bed
now is it because we like grew closer so
[Music]
cute okay okay Mayon brought in some
good
money day 18 of
[Music]
refreshing rain a farmer's best friend
when it rains you don't have to water
your crops use this to your advantage oh
my God it's the same in real life
[\h__\h] the spirits feel neutral today
[\h__\h] beautiful sunny day tomorrow h M
okay uh oh
sheesh okay we have a lot of oh
flowers the [\h__\h] what what's of all the
[\h__\h]
flowers a
lot what
happened I guess a lot of the random
ones were
flowers I would have expected like some
more like veggie stuff
[Music]
what
happened no don't
eat no don't I want to
[Music]
huh oh am
I no
space lesson learned I guess I mean what
was there a lesson to learn to not plant
the
random why
not I mean I I I'll sell all of
this I don't know if I maybe should keep
some of these for
snacking but the
flowers I'll sell I
guess free money and then level up your
foraging they're they're worth doing
okay there you
[Music]
go Mommy says I can craft Wild
seeds
[Music]
ah flowers make good gifts mhm I'll
probably have some left
over h so
many that's it
50 uh okay oh but mommy says to sell
them mommy says I should sell them a
papa there it goes I sold them all two
golden D gone well yeah oh well it is
what it
[Music]
is keeping the rest
sell the seed yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah um I sold
them okay now I shall start the watering
and by the way let me check my phone
really quick because I feel
like I
should bring out a tangent if I can find
one m i [\h__\h] stop stop
stop m
that's my dream
tangent let me delete
that
oh oh yeah ooh yeah I just reminded
myself of a
tangent oh
oh where how do I start where ooh do I
remember this
well
sheesh okay so it's about my
kitchen as you know by
now I have moved recently and then I got
myself a kitchen right and we're
skipping we're skipping the whole
getting a kitchen
process really quickly for another time
but
um I okay this is uh about what's
installat in
English what do you call the dudes who
like do the water
stuff I mean these dudes they did both
they did the water stuff and the the
like the water Behind the Walls they
like moved it around
yeah yeah but they were I guess they
were I don't know they were plumbers
and electricians at the same time they
did
both yeah so my my my kitchen lady I
went to a kitchen studio right and uh
like we made the kitchen together and
then she
organized uh people for me because I
didn't know anyone she was like oh do
you want to like do you have anyone in
particular
that You' want to hire for moving around
the uh St stom the strong
electricity uh cuz we had to do that and
then I think besides that I don't know
there was just some something some work
to be
[Music]
done yeah they um they got me some some
contractors m
wait before I continue Tangen thing what
should I
do I mean I'm going to put the eggs in
there but
then what now should I get some more
seeds did I the the caulif
[Music]
cauliflower yeah I think that was
watered what about these ones ah I
forgot these
cauliflower cauliflower is
watered and
now see I'm like so lost like what the
[\h__\h] visit
Carpenter
why can I make a
silo which one's the silo
Silo Silo Silo Silo Silo I don't see a
silo it tells me to build a silo and
then it doesn't even give me the
freaking
[Music]
recipe the carpenter okay where's the
carpenter
[Music]
wait I love her
up
north ah I can't reach it
scam
scam how the [\h__\h] am I supposed to reach
[Music]
it okay up north in the City north
or and do I need to bring materials or
just
money in the mountains here North up
here
okay near the lake
okay bring materials well take my wood
okay see see see 10 clay I don't have
Clay so I shouldn't even
go then let's go to the geod guy
since I don't have
Clay no okay um okay so back to my
kitchen thing it's going to be hard to
tell the story uh my brain is so
useless uh why do I even I don't even
know I don't even know
anything okay so it was the day of the
kitchen building I think we had two
days and they arrived early in the
morning and it was two people one was
like
uh the seemingly the the not the
supervisor but like the main dude who
was like leading the
operation uh and the other one was like
his helper but yeah um his German wasn't
so good the other yeah it's like an
apprentice and the Forman yeah the
German wasn't so good of that one guy
and the other guy is like yeah typical
Austrian older
dude I think I'm just going to tell you
the story while I'm uh pausing the
screen cuz I'm I I can't I'm going to
lose my train of f so [\h__\h] many
times I'm so going to lose it wait
should I buy
seeds should I buy
seeds mommy should I buy more
seeds I have money should I get kale or
so what's Jazz what the
[\h__\h] parsnips more parsnips says
chat something we can grow in 10 days or
less
o
cute hey Y what the [\h__\h] provides
unlimited access to all wall wallpapers
and Floors from the conven of your home
cool about 30,000
gold 28 days 28 days 28 days 28 days
[Music]
no okay mommy says now I should save the
money for the Silo and for the backpack
upgrade okay I'm fine with that okay
okay okay
okay okay let's just go back home I want
to tell
you the
story maybe then I'll get
the
the fishing rod and maybe fish a little
bit I don't know for the rest of the day
I don't
know oh can I go over to the other side
I didn't
realize oh the chicken crossed the road
but why not earlier why did the chicken
not cross the road earlier guys because
the chicken didn't know that it could do
that
she well I I totally looked both sides
of course I did oh that reminds me I was
thinking about how I
totally
um
I I I've noticed that I when I cross the
road on red
lights like I only do it like obviously
when it's like really really empty
there's no car you know but then when
there's a child around I don't do it cuz
I feel like the mom there's usually a
mom with the child and they're totally
going to judge me so I don't want to be
a bad influencer it'll be like the one
bad adult who's walking right in front
of a child who's waiting for the lights
and I'm walking over it even though
there's absolutely no traffic isn't that
EDI in in in Japanese we say
II yeah I am so wow respect respectable
I don't
know now that's what I call being an
influenc yeah good role model mhm
mhm thank you yeah I don't want children
to be like Mommy to their parents
because then they're going to be like to
their parents they're going to be like
Mommy why why why don't we have to wait
when there's no cars but this other girl
she just walked over the street right in
front of us why can't she do it and why
can we not do
it and then I don't want to I don't want
to be the reason why the mom has to have
this conversation with the child and be
like no we will not jwalk
no I want to make the parenting even
more difficult for
them that's because the other girl is
the devil
yeah yeah yeah or a kid like just
running because they saw me do
it not even asking their parents yeah
I'm so considerate thank you
okay so let me try to recall this it's
been a while since this happened um but
okay I told you two people came to build
uh to ah they didn't come to build the
kitchen they came to like first do the
stuff behind the walls right they made
holes into the walls really big
holes really loud drills and
[\h__\h] and then it did some stuff there
okay okay and uh I I just let them in
and then I let them do the work
basically I didn't really I didn't
really say anything I didn't watch them
I just like went into a different room
and waited for them to finish because
what was I supposed to do so also
because there was not really much space
anyway because at this time I was like
still somewhat freshly moved in and I
had a lot of boxes all over the place so
I was already pretty like you know
packed no stuff no no place cuz too much
stuff so I was just waiting and then uh
at some point this like austan dude he
takes a break and the other dude who
remains uh oh on he didn't take a break
I think he was just on the phone and the
other dude who remains he like comes
over to my room and he's like hey sorry
can I talk to you for a moment in like
somewhat broken German I'm like yeah
okay no problem I come over and he like
points at the whole work they've done so
far it's been a few hours by now and and
they're like getting done soon and he
tries to tell me
that uh apparently this is kind of lazy
work and they're just doing it this way
like not his choice but they're just
doing it this way because they don't
have that much time or so I don't know
and I should not be charged too much for
this work and I'm like okay like it was
a little bit hard to understand what
he's trying to say I'm just like telling
you a bit more clearer now because I
already know you know what happened but
yeah he's being honest he's trying he
waited for the moment that his Superior
was gone just to tell me this and he
also told me that I should not tell the
superior that he told me that you know
obviously he's going to be in trouble or
something but he was just telling me
that this is kind of lazy work and maybe
r or so and he showed like for example
they're like really really those thick
cables right from the electricity and
whatever from moving the high voltage
[\h__\h] uh from one place to another that
stuff uh it was like not completely
going through the walls like parts were
like just hanging around because they
can be covered up by the kitchen I guess
probably that's what uh wasn't done so
properly in the end I don't really know
but um this really made me feel insecure
because I was like okay what do I do
with this
information so they were done eventually
and I I had to like I I couldn't say
something yet at the at that point
because like it
was difficult um cuz I didn't have I was
alone I didn't have any second opinion
and didn't I didn't I couldn't you know
it's a problem as always like with me
not being able to assert dominance um
um and I didn't want to question it
right there because what reason did I
have with no expertise to question it I
still was also like not sure because I
wouldn't even know what to say because
the Dude the way he phrased everything
just confused me a lot I would I didn't
even know like what exactly was wrong
with it so I couldn't even complain
about it at the spot you know what I
mean so I wanted to maybe ask around a
little bit it before I would complain to
them if there was anything to complain
but if if the dude himself tells me that
this is not so properly done then it
gives me the feeling that I should
probably complain about it if even he is
saying
so yeah but like if I were to I have I
it was like this kind of atmosphere that
like if I were to question it right
there and then then it would would have
been pretty obvious that the colleague
said something to me
cuz I otherwise would have had no idea
that there could be anything wrong with
this
but it was all functional you know so
whatever so they leave and I show a
picture of this to um you know that uh
couple the the that I have as friends
like quite far away that sometimes I
hang out with them the ones that are big
fans of
me one of them is quite the handy person
yeah
and he has a friend who works also for a
company like
that uh is quite high up there in that
field and so the friend yeah the shirt
couple mhm the friend already said when
he saw a picture even though he's not a
professional in that regard but he
thought okay this looks weird and then
he sent it to his friend and his friend
said yeah this is totally [\h__\h] up
looks like [\h__\h] and I'm like okay so now
I have two
opinions uh the different opinion and
the guy who is actually working on this
are telling me this is [\h__\h] but okay
what do I do now but then I um um I
wrote to the company because they I
think they already sent me an invoice at
this
point and I I wrote to them hey I don't
know maybe this should be lowered
because uh I've been getting some input
from others and I could not say that one
of this input was from one of their own
workers but I feel like that would have
been very important information to say
that even you know getting an opinion
from others might always be kind of
biased but if your own worker is saying
this then it's not
biased but I couldn't say that I wanted
to protect that person
yeah and I didn't want to rat yeah so I
just said yeah I got some input from
several people and this
doesn't like something's like kind
of looks rash I don't know I so can we
talk about the price again maybe or no I
think I even said I I really tried to
sound confident in the email I said so
either you lower the price or you come
here and then you know fix it before the
kitchen is coming in the next few
days and then I don't think I get an
answer so then I called and I was told
by the
freaking uh phone desk lady
assistant that the boss is not in for a
few days and I should tell her what's
up and I'm like O Okay so I start
telling her the
situation and then she's also asking for
pictures and then she's like okay I'll
get back to you and uh I sent her a
picture and then I guess she talked with
the workers who worked on it on that day
I guess probably just the Austrian guy
and the Austrian guy probably told her
this is how it is and then she called me
back and then that's why I got really
nervous because she basically just
called me and like stomped me into the
ground you know I was like this is this
is fine this is you know exactly what
was discussed this is what was in the
order uh if you look at the order BL
blah blue this is how it's supposed to
be and there's nothing wrong with it and
I'm like um uh yeah uh
uh um well okay
I
guess then then I was like yeah well
but I don't
know then I didn't know what to say
anymore and I was just
like trying to stay cool but I really
couldn't and she just basically
destroyed me and made me feel like [\h__\h]
and she was kind of yeah not even giving
it the benefit of the doubt and of
course I still couldn't tell I I feel
like if I I would have told at that
moment that the only reason I brought
all of this up was because one of your
workers told me it's not good
work then that would have helped my
case
yeah so yeah I I I was destroyed and
then I just paid the normal price
and it it it was uh done and the kitchen
was put in and everything and it all
works and so on but it's like apparently
it could have been nicer but it's not
like it was ever not functional but I
think the concern was like the
friend uh of the friend brought up the
concern that possibly if I ever have
like water damage then maybe that could
uh
affect be affected by how they worked on
those like cables or whatever
crushing customer descent yeah she's
good at her job I guess but she the
moment she came back with all those
statements she she was like
so rude mean not rude but mean and I was
like confidence is crashed no confidence
yeah watering cable doesn't sound good
right
yeah that was the
concern I don't know if that's I really
don't know the details because because
I'm not a professional so I don't really
know what to
say and then especially when it turns
into a discussion where there should be
a back and forth I cannot handle this
like
maybe maybe if the that friend and that
lady would have communicated directly
with one with each
other you know then this would have
maybe gone down a little bit differently
but it's you know just me once again one
of those times where I felt really
like lost
and alone and [\h__\h]
because I am just smer smarter
WWA let me talk to
you small small
Wawa cannot do anything on her
own I have no
Integrity what is
this
Cole
oh what the [\h__\h] the game
crashed give me my cocko I was about to
make a joke like
[\h__\h] the cocko crashed my
game wait what the [\h__\h] do I have to
restart the day from the beginning what
did I do what did I
do you think I remember what I did I was
Tangen thing
what the
G have to restart the day we couldn't
handle my tangent I tanged it for too
long the game was like all right I'm
out
what we we we're at the beginning of the
last day we just played
right yeah that sounds familiar
[Music]
mhm day
18 I think so I think we shot it at day
13 or something oh
yeah so that's
[Music]
there then I'll make wild seed thingies
out of
this and then I'll sell them then I'll
Water everything
then
I'll get the eggs make some
mayonnaise we'll we'll get back on
track no
worries
uh you guys complained that I
made wild seeds out of some of these
like the the golden star ones should I
just sell them separately
are they worth more on their
own I can understand caving if this was
an apartment but this is your home I
could potentially be with you forever it
could pot I could potentially be with
you
forever I would want my home to be the
best could be shot well well well well
it doesn't look shoty at all now that
the kitchen is in and and I wouldn't
have known in the first place if that
dude never said
anything oh where the [\h__\h] did the
lantern come
from uh and I don't know no it it it
it's not I mean in the end the lady you
know she destroyed me but I felt
like it was fine in the end fix it
myself no [\h__\h] way how am I going to
do that it's like going into really
really thick concrete walls and [\h__\h] I'm
not a professional I'm not going to
touch
that uh but yeah anyway well should I
not should I not make this into seat
packs where am I where am I where am I
where are my
professionals it's okay now it's over
it's fine everything's fine I just
wanted to tell you the story there's no
need to like fix anything now it's it's
not something that needs to be fixed I
think yeah at least I tried but I'm
getting sick of trying these kind of
situ like to fix these kind of
situations because I always just like
end up in this position where I'm like
ah oh oh okay never mind then sorry
ha sell them
normally sell them like this only these
or you
guys I don't know what I'm doing
[Music]
I'm going just do it like
this give me give me those berries this
time don't scam
me I got it I got it
[Music]
I didn't think like I was in the right
anymore at the end of it all
because a check
[Music]
I hate that happen so much to me
accidentally I was
saying uh upon
checking what she pointed out that the
offer originally the way it was
phrased does make it seem like this is
okay upon her saying that I didn't feel
like
I I didn't feel like I was in the right
anymore but then I was so confused
because I was like you're yeah you may
be right and I may be wrong but then why
did your coworker tell me all of this
now I feel really [\h__\h]
weird for complaining in the first
place no
[Music]
yeah I was just in a really weird
spot
man but I still appreciate the honesty
of the dude he maybe maybe he just
didn't know what the offer was he maybe
thought that the work was supposed to be
[Music]
different
yeah he didn't have the details because
he was just there working for the older
dude yeah I still think he was
trustworthy I still
think that he has good
intentions
Yow where's my fishing rod oh
somewhere
why what did I go in here for nothing
nothing here it is
don't worry me you make me think I lost
it I'm losing my
mind yeah and they basically were saying
this is this is what you paid
for this is what we discussed
beforehand but if I have known that the
friend of my
friend has a a job like this then I
would have maybe hired them although
they were I think in a different region
or I would have hired them or I would
have gotten their opinion when I got the
offer before they even started working
on it but you never
know you never know about the friends of
your
friends what am I going to do ask all of
my friends if their friends or their
friends' friends work in this are kind
of a
branch what a pain in the
ass never hire a friends but hire my
friend friends is that
okay but yeah um never hire why do you
say that why do you say never hire your
friends because I have
recently hired a friend for something
else is that a bad thing because like
when you're unhappy with something you
can't say it clearly or something like
that or you feel like you
can't I think I watered it all I think I
did business can get Missy
yeah well so far it's it's okay I
think some friends are lazy when working
for a
friend yeah I can see that
mhm think so badly it might hurt the
Friendship no it's going to be fine I
don't think that will be the case
[Music]
but well I am not paying friendship
price like that's a that's a discussion
we had like I was basically told okay so
if you pay me like the professional
price then I'm going to do professional
work and you know I'm like oh okay I
mean French of price would have been
nice too
but but uh okay let's uh yeah that's
fine that's fine even the professional
price was acceptable so we're good we
good how good could the frener prise
have been
manut them we have even more berries
here
amazing this cat is so late
wow mayonnaise is
[Music]
ready who is wild going after I have no
idea no one really speaks to me just yet
I don't really care about anyone that
much yet so now have I done already all
the things that I did before the game
crashed I think I did so I can go
fishing
now I feel like yes
right 100 Wood ooh I'm going to wait
until I have the 200
wood oh the five wait the five the five
the it just needs one let's let's just
uh I don't know I can do it at anytime
so
whatever R up
Robin Robin was who
again we not even remembering them
properly tells you something wait did I
go to The Adventurous Guild the previous
day I think I already did it I'm part of
the adventurous Guild now I
[Music]
think carpet lady who's who's
she carpet lady I need to see their
faces otherwise I can't
really tell who they are I think that's
Pam
right no that's Jody's pretty Penny's a
sweet girl she's been Vincent's teacher
for a while now and he really loves
her okay I guess uh Penny's taken but
what about
you oh she's she's
taken I mean what even what what do I
even get out
of marrying
someone I'm scared to pick this
up what if it crashes the game
again then I might rage
quit I don't want to do all of this
again do you think it's will crash
again Crash and
Burn Eternal Bliss tax benefits that
just sounds like you're joking you do
get a tangible thing but it's mainly for
the story oh okay okay Penny single jod
is taken oh
sorry okay we're
good made me feel really nervous there
for a
moment okay this is like deep blue do I
get something else out of here although
actually this all deep
blue catch an eel well I'd love to catch
an eel it's not really on me is it
come on
[Applause]
fishy oh
treasure but I'm I'mma stay with the
fish this one's
easy if only all fish were that easy
sardine I think sardine yeah first catch
y
sard fish the bubbles yeah I want to go
there can I even reach though shut the M
I'll go there
in a
moment right up oh wait are they
disappearing oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh no no no no oh please why is it so
bouncy
[Music]
antoi with an Tois I'm always like that
sounds like a vegetable how is that a
fish do you guys feel the same or is it
just because English isn't my first
language it just sounds like a
[Music]
vegetable no I I know artist chalks are
something else I know
that why are they all staying on the
ground oh
wait why the hell staying on the ground
for
me I'm not complaining it's just me
doesn't sound like a fish thank you I
think anybody who's English isn't their
first language would would agree with me
thank
you
uh can I eat it
already full inventory guys I could uh
sell the fish that I already
brought and in before I think I can sell
one sardine right maybe the golden
one I guess I can sell the
clams the [\h__\h] and the ovy and the
Sardine are going to go into
the museum probably
not the museum the community center both
both are collecting things for me it's
the same thing
wait I can fish a bit more now actually
do I get something over here
too that is the wrong
direction please cook the
fish it's a behavior it's a sinker you
sound like someone who goes fishing iron
well underneath the the six dark blue
spots has the best
loot six dark blue
spots ah oh
[Music]
there here
ooh it's a little bit deeper than
everywhere else but I can't reach over
[Applause]
there you didn't know you didn't
know you didn't read the
wiki should have read the wiki but I'm
not getting anything right now what the
hell
fishy fishy fishy fishy seems like he
doesn't know either he didn't read the
wiki
either hello what the
[\h__\h]
Max I missed it
really no way that I would miss
that a [\h__\h] Stay Stay chill chill chill
chill
chill y what's this Herring I had it
before I always get the same
Fish N I didn't miss it you guys are
hallucinating take some
pills I would never miss the sound oh my
God okay okay
oh oh God damn it don't those are so
impossible those are impossible
[Applause]
please stay
yes that's right baby
oh why do you do why why
why I had this one before
too Mama
Mia I worked so hard for
it this is how you treat
me okay I'm going to
quickly go to the community center just
very
quickly oh no
space no
[Music]
space looks like an old school
building why do you always leave
me Dam there we
go where's the other
ones
sardine oh that's
it oh what
about the an tropies that that was a
first
catch maybe in the
future oh why not
[Music]
enies not everything is
required
okay anything
here no I think I I can
go yeah they're really small right don't
they come in like
uh uh those glasses
I
sard you you you
you I wouldn't eat
it
oh not really appetizing to me oh or is
it cans not
glasses or both
tints have you guys had that before how
do you eat it just like straight from
the tin or do you cook with
it they go great on pizza or salad
[Music]
M I don't know somehow something about
that is just not appetizing to
me Blended for sauces e fish fish sauce
Blended fish
[Music]
sauce I don't know tuna tuna from the
tin or can or whatever sounds fine to me
you know but for some reason because
tuna that's already just the meat of the
tuna anything besides that just doesn't
doesn't no doesn't speak to
me yeah tuna I love
tuna allergic to
Seafood well me too me too me
too we're the
same
whoa whoa that was big I don't think
could we have made this much money
otherwise selling them as singles oh
3,000 Gold
Guys hating something is an allergy too
yeah please have mercy on
[Music]
me how much do you think a tuna can get
I know from Dave the diver that they get
huge huge
[Music]
huge they get so
huge this is true Big
Tuna what are we doing today let me ask
what what my luck is
[Music]
today very happy
beautiful sunny day tomorrow very happy
but I have
to uh use up all my energy for my stuff
here
[Music]
H buy the backpack yes shush open
open I need fresh cauliflower for recipe
yeah I I mean it's not going to be Super
Fresh
it's been in my storage for a while is
that
[Music]
okay some kfps hate fake my allergy you
know how many times I've done that
once it's not a big deal one time I have
said to a
restaurant because the food was just a
little bit too crazy for me that I have
an allergy for seafood okay even if I
would have said I just don't want it not
that it's an allergy they would have
still done something about
it because that that was a fancy
restaurant they would have still changed
everything up for me I just wanted to
sound a little bit more reasonable by
saying it's an
allergy wow I light people died yeah I
don't think it's that dramatic
really I did that once yeah they would
have still accommodated me even if it
wasn't an allergy but just a personal
preference I just said it because I
wanted to sound less like a
[\h__\h]
yeah oh because they have to like wash
all the utensils and stuff uh I don't
know if they really did that I don't
know did I really do
that cuz like I said like normal fish is
fine just like uh uh I think I think did
I I don't know I don't remember the
details
anymore but yeah I mean it was once okay
it was one
[Music]
time what what did I not water this part
well I mean washing your
utensils and all that I mean come on
it's not going
to ah Maybe
no whatever this this is this is a
really
really annoying conversation right now
so I'm not going to have it I'm not
going to have
it
um
um what do I
do am I going to go
mining
uh am I going to go mining what am I
going to do
are we going to have any wallpaper a I
forgot I had it ready I have it ready
just need to upload it uh check out the
traveling cart where is
that go south from here and then left
okay is that worth it the traveling card
is it the the the the thing uh South
from
here south from
here from my
backyard okay oh down
here uh is it I thought it was I thought
you were talking about maybe the wizard
place where are we going to end up at a
and then left no where
uh
[Music]
mhm am I going too far down
probably ah
[Music]
H
here here's the tower and then I think
up there is
the
[Music]
cart what do I I
want they have rare seats but I'm saving
oh yeah I need to get the bag why you
guys don't tell me to get the
bag what these summer
spangle rare seeds is very
good are is this shop here
always yeah backpack is 2,000
so I can still afford it only on some
[Music]
days the rest is not worth it now okay
okay I'm going to get it that's
okay funny
pig pig is so pink never seen a Pinker
pig ever
before so pink I can't believe it's real
who said by that some of you guys mommy
says I can only use it in Fall that's
okay I'll keep it until
then okay we're finally going to buy the
backpack
oh
hallelu
Hallelujah yeah oh that looks like so
much
better now that would be a good time to
go mining as
well with all this
space hell yeah but it's already so late
[Music]
M and I didn't bring my
things
10,000 well I think 10,000 it will get
easier and easier soon have this feeling
cuz now I made in one night I made 3,000
bucks that's pretty amazing but most of
it came also from the the wild seed
packages that I
made m but yeah I think it still should
become
easier you're going to leave this in
here for a while until fall it's going
to be a long time what do we do
now this is like my problem with this
game is like I'm in the middle of the
day going to the mine I'm not going to
get
anywhere and also low
energy this just like what what the [\h__\h]
do I do
I can go fishing again but no let me
bring the cauliflower or is it too late
I don't
know one cauliflower probably right to
Jodie okay let's find
her you just explore the South
usually south from your home
[Music]
uh yeah jod where's
Jodie Jodie Jodie Jodie you guys know
where Jodie is Jody maybe one of these
houses are you
Jodie
[\h__\h] I gave it by accident give it back
why don't they ask you to like confirm
it or
so [\h__\h] Leah
you're not Jodie right Haley's ignoring
you and she's blocking my way oh my God
why is she why is she ignoring me what's
her problem it's that Barbie girl that I
talked to
before what did I do before she was
friendly to
me well she never talk to me ever again
maybe I have to give her
flowers oh Mommy
says left the last okay then I was
really close to it I had the right
feeling but
I I
failed let's put something else in my
hand so I don't accidentally give the
cauliflower to someone
[Music]
else maybe she's in a bad mood never
talk to EP with something in your hands
at least not something you can gift to
them
right
man you're not Jodie
Jodie
uh no one in here maybe she's in the
saloon you saw her work walking north of
me ah jie no that's Leah is
it a
jie let go
found you perfect for my yellow
curry yeah um yellow curry sounds
amazing but with coliflower no John fre
50 gold
oh more requests like this please where
is the Lost axe she was cutting wood
south of Mar's Ranch the ranch is that
where the cows
are so if I oh
[Music]
okay so south of here maybe I find the
axe that would be
nice cutting wood was the hint so maybe
I have to cut some wood as
well or the hint is that it's going to
be somewhere in the
woods wait is it on the
islands or is it more like here near the
SE South right of the hor
very south and then
right on the
islands across the
bridges
um 800
p.m. ah the sewer what was with the
sewer what you say about the
sewer oh I found it I found it I found
it
yay we're turned to Robin who's
Robin am I the only one who just doesn't
remember like put the faces and the
names together that
easily am I the only one did you guys
remember everything right away you
probably just had your the carp the
carpenter okay where is she but I'm
going to go home for now but you guys
probably just had the wikii open the old
time in the north carpenter is in the
north the north of the city or north of
me oh where the mines are says my mommy
my mom's faster than you guys with the
back seating
first person you meet in the game well I
don't remember
that uh are we all good to sleep soon
wait spring onion that was a
first
[Music]
nice H wait the the spring onion IRL
meta tells me that I could take this
spring onion and grow my own I don't
need the
seeds but in this game I don't think
that
works damn
it I didn't feed the chicken what
they're feeding themselves don't worry
about
it they're okay I
think those only grow wild oh okay I
can't grow them then I was lucky to find
them I guess
I guess am I ready to sleep it's kind of
early mommy says to open my
map
oh ah not a
hoodle not a
hoodle oh I mean I've had the map open
before but I didn't really like look at
it properly cuz I didn't know what I'm
looking at this just looks like a big
cookie okay
[Laughter]
that's why she makes
carpets
mhm ah okay I don't know I guess I guess
I'll
sleep guess I'll die I don't know guess
[Music]
sleep or I'll chop some more wood
I need more
wood oh butterflies sorry for disturbing
you isn't this a normal thing to do at
11:00
p.m. I think this is totally normal
right having this feeling that you need
to chop some wood right now right
here man all there I made them
[Music]
homeless it's all my fault
oh oh thank you for the raid that
reminds
me yesterday I had a big Pawn moment
huh but I swear so I noticed like okay I
I was looking for Kon senpai's
stream at the end of my stream I wanted
to rate Kon Senpai so I was looking for
her stream and I couldn't find it so I
typed in Kon in English and then I found
like
something that my brain first thought
was her stream then I clicked on it and
then a moment later I realized wait wait
wait wait that might be wrong uh and
then I open it up again the window and I
realized yeah that was wrong she's not
playing Cod on the box right now
obviously so I thought okay let me check
again let me look up let me copy paste
her stream title cuz sometimes it
doesn't doesn't show it right away you
have to like I don't know look for it
with more detail then I looked it up
with the exact stream title then her
stream show up in the list but it was
grade out which means I can't rate her
she doesn't have the permissions uh
on so I was like okay whatever let me at
least remove the other one and I swear
to God I clicked and I confirmed to
remove the other stream which was just
like some random his chat was even
closed
oh it was just some yeah some random
dude who was playing qu on the box to
like I don't know 10 viewers or so uh
but I I removed it but YouTube just kept
it you know YouTube's like when I try to
raid people it doesn't work sometimes
like for half of the people it works for
half it dozen and then I don't know it's
just like always messed up right and
this one time I remove it and
then it stayed in there apparently and
then you guys went over there some of
you guys apparently
and I feel so
embarrassed uh uh I didn't see his
reaction though though though did he
react like oh my God like why the [\h__\h]
is the real
takii raiding me with several hundreds
he didn't even
notice oh well maybe it's better that
[Laughter]
way his viewers went up to over a
thousand from under
10 and I guess you can't noce cuz you
have the chat closed but like
dude oh I was so embarrassed
[Music]
man oh
man oh he want a p Clipper oh made a
happy day well I don't know like when he
doesn't even notice was it really made
into a Happ happy
day his analytics yeah for that one
stream I'm going to be
wild well I mean not everybody
necessarily wants to be raid and uh the
ens have opened up their perms and all
that but I think on the Japanese side
you know it's just not really something
they're familiar with so they probably
didn't even talk about it they probably
don't even know about the feature
partially so they just kept it all
closed you know so that's okay like I I
get it I was just trying to see if maybe
maybe maybe maybe it works but yeah it's
not yeah the culture but I mean it
wasn't YouTube culture overall but then
we got it and a lot of people know it
from twitch and so on so we just kind of
went with it and yeah although they
turned it on for that like Koka relay uh
that was like New Year's or Christmas or
something
they turned it on even the Japanese
members and we like raided each other
but then only the ones who participated
did that and I guess maybe they turned
it off again as
well but that's like the first time some
of these members found out about the F
feature in the first
place I think it makes so much sense to
do it for relays at least so yeah for
relays it's genius
yeah the managers yeah I think the
managers turned it on or yeah but anyway
uh watering can proficiency hope
proficiency bee house beeh house speed
grow farmer launch
yummy
okay mommy says when I have time I
should just chop some trees yeah I I I
was doing that cuz I need more wood
anyway 99 wood time two and then 99
Stones I think and some hardwood k
key oh the I think the parsnips are
ready nice plop plop the carrots too
plop
plop P plop plop plop
plop beans I don't have space wait I do
have
space I do have space oopsie oh my God I
almost destroyed it
again I hate this so much
um
or or the one golden one is what I need
right no five golden ones one normal
one uh where is it five golden okay okay
okay okay we're keeping the golden
one
and uh we're selling one normal one and
this one we're keeping the five ones no
no the other way around no it's so
confusing we're we're keeping one we're
selling the rest we're keeping this one
to get up to a five oh my God it's so
confusing uh and then the carrots are
not necessary but maybe I'll keep them
for cooking I don't
know um I'll sell this
Bean
yeah five golden one normal five gold
why is it not the other way around that
would be so much
easier
mommy mommy is sending me some good
advice one of the things we got to do
today though
is give the axe to its rightful
owner then make maybe they give us a
better axe or maybe not we'll find out
my
Fields my fields are broken because I
have nothing to
grow oh
well
plop yeah that's what I
thought you go to blacksmith with copper
inot to upgrade ah okay but I I mean
I've a few times encountered The Prompt
that says you need a better axe or
so but so
far I don't think it's that urgent
right large egg lar
egg okay mommy says a few more parsnips
maybe
okay I'll buy some seeds oh yeah because
of the golden oh okay ah we only got one
golden one out of those like 15 parsnips
or
so okay okay okay okay okay ah wait
mayonnaise mayonnaise mayonnaise
mayonnaise
[Music]
Mayon and done and done and
done bring my hoe I
think um
[Music]
no
mhm me did I water
it think not
yeah almost
forgot if you don't water it one day do
the plants die right away
it's
rhed oh they have a high chance of dying
oh no okay okay par
snip par par
wait is the shop open
anyway plans don't die but they won't oh
okay I got one guy oh my God why does it
keep on
happening so mommy says there's places
where there's like little worms and
that's where I need to do something with
my
whole little worms I feel like I've seen
that
before feel like I've seen it so I feel
like I know what you're talking about uh
wait uh Robin house was like h no no no
wrong wrong
sorry uh it's up up in the north sorry
got lost a little
bit and seeds let's buy
[Music]
seeds question
20 I don't
know 33 is the number I'm going
with no this board do you have you do
you know this
spard K do you know this sport it
doesn't seem like you know this sport
because you always want past
[Applause]
it fresh seaweeds a
paste if you find one I could put it to
good use what you want the the seaweed
only makes Harvey
happy seaweed I might have or I've
already eaten it but I can probably get
it again
[Music]
thanks for the membership see someone
really liked my
joke how the [\h__\h] do I get
there can I go around here
[Music]
here
yeah hello I got your axe you better be
home right now is is are you the
one [\h__\h] yeah could I have accidentally
gifted that to someone
else uh hey you found my axe would I
relief I almost chopped my toe off with
the other one I was just like my mom
[Music]
just like wait what did I get for
that 250 H
okay wait two
days oh it's just seaweed okay awesome
just seaweed I can
do hey hey
hey then let me plant the parsnips and
then bring him some seaweed oh we have a
plan talk about Silo yeah but I don't
have the clay
anyway but mommy said I can get the clay
from the worms in the
ground
uh Coupe
no what about ah Barn well
Silo well not really there's not really
anything to talk about it seems
you can dig normally dig normally I
don't have
a was
there something
weird I don't have a
shovel ah no that's just grass I it was
moving so I thought it was maybe a worm
a worms
[Music]
worms oh digging is with the
hole where are the
worms okay anyway let me do my my field
I've got some farming to do wait I was
using the wrong thing
anyway those are the worms okay that's
just moving grass wait wait wait wait
wait are they still there
I was using an axe you guys didn't even
point it
out oh I thought I need the shovel this
whole time I thought for digging I'd
need a freaking
shovel big freaking bamboozle right
there
guys I was just
naive it's either moving free worms or
free moving grass aha okay so there's
both okay
oh you are
disturbing my
land
uh we got some
carrots let's go I love
carrots oh yeah I think on the beach I
saw
a lot of
wormies let me got rid of the tree once
and for all it's so over for you get out
of here I don't want to see you
anymore I want to be
[Music]
free free
Acorn acor AK o n acor
[Music]
um I don't really have a joke for that
I'm just
um bringing in bringing it up just you
know hope you're enjoying the
reference uh
okay please bring me many many golden
par Snips or just four what do you think
my chances are guys
what the hell is a parsnip I thought
this was a
carrot
okay okay there were like white carrots
ah oh like more like yellowish carrots
right or is that just
carrots oh I just became the treasure
chest I wasn't even trying to uh seaweed
nice wood zp
Acorn okay uh
water water in the farming
why yeah carrots come in a lot of colors
right I even had uh purple carrots
before a few
times is it like with apples that they
taste different I feel like apples have
very more like distinct different
flavors depending on their color with
carrots I feel like maybe I've noticed a
slight difference but not as strong as
of apples what do you think guys
one thing I can say is with bell peppers
it's very different
though people hate green bell
peppers but I love yellow ones and
orange and red bell
peppers never noticed that blame the
Dutch green yellow appet seem to be more
sour than red ones apparently but for
apples I don't really care I I'll eat
any
Apple oh it might be too late for the
seaweed maybe they're already going to
bed bell peppers taste the same to me
what I
mean all the bell peppers besides the
green ones yeah I would agree they kind
of taste the sameish
you guys all talk about the pink lady
apples I don't think we get those in
Austria do we oh 500 gold what the [\h__\h]
thank you Dad have you settled into your
new life yet I can't believe you're all
grown up now time sure flies now that
you're gone I have all this extra money
laying around so I include this little
what let's go dear from I'd like to
apologize for joking about your
grandpa's old College when we first met
it's really a nice little house however
you might need some more space someday
that's where I can help oh my God we're
going Animal
Crossing oh no no no no no no no no
no okay let's
spend wait let's sell the
Mayo almost forgot about the Mayo no no
no
okay then I'll chop some more trees and
maybe I'll scy that stupid grass away
scyth do I I hope I don't accidentally
Scythe my beans
[Music]
away could that happen o dangerous
territory
there
okay you can't okay
good I saw this video the other day uh
like a YouTube short was recommended to
me maybe you guys saw it too I feel like
it was recommended to a lot of people at
that moment of some
Austrian dude like there was like a
competition on the countryside and like
a big field of grass oh
there okay
goodbye a big field of grass really high
high high grass and this dude he had
like a huge SI like a Reaper side like
huge really impressive
and they were like counting down and
then he started swinging his side really
professionally really
energetically oh oh the cat was just
inside a moment
ago and uh yeah people in the comments
like it was even though this was an
Austrian video it's most of the English
comments and everybody was like so
impressed and people were talking about
how this is a skill that people nowadays
don't have anymore this was like yeah
Scythe grass cutting was a thing back in
the day but nowadays it's not really
nobody knows how to do it and it takes a
lot of lot of strength and uh energy and
power to do it like that everybody was
respecting the Austrian uh dude for
going so hard pretty sure it was
Austrian because I I heard the the
accent and the
dialect he was so
fast yeah had to think of C when I saw
that
yeah it looked so cool it looks so
satisfying seeing all the
grass just disappear with the Scythe in
one
swoosh yeah Callie can't do that c can't
do it like that oh you is it raining oh
sorry is it
raining it seems like it's
raining how's my luck though uh Al a
recipe Rish salad there's nothing like a
fresh peppery radish it reminds me of
the late spring my mother would slice up
our fresh radishes BL blah
blue radish salad let's go what's with
the decorative
Lantern mildly perturbed today luck will
not be on your
side uh I guess I'll mine
[Music]
anyway what the [\h__\h]
F I took it from the table oh
no should I go
anyway okay mommy says go anyway hi they
so cute
[Music]
I'm so
cute my game
crashed
oh
again no well at least the day just
started I malfunctioned that's why the
game
crashed the cuteness of the chickens was
too much for me and the
[Music]
game it's a lot of crashes yeah
weird
weird new update maybe that's
why
H yesterday I didn't crash I think
still not on my
side I have to learn this recipe
again tomorrow is beautiful sunny day
okay the strawberries already some of
them oh they look so good they look like
big
hearts big red heart mama big red heart
mama big red
heart
y
beautiful wait the plant doesn't
disappear so they're going to grow
more
yo yo I want to make some strawberry
rard
pie how's that sound
guys they'll grow
more one more time before summer
let's go oh look at
them and I don't need this for anything
else just selling mommy says sell sell
sell sell sell I'm sell this too sell
this
too let's go I'm looking forward to that
money did I get the eggs yet I don't
think so that's when my game
crashed please don't crash now oh
they're inside of each other Lo ah
what have I
witnessed yeah you love me but you seem
to love each other very much as
well don't act so innocent
now they're missing a
rooster
[Music]
okay Harvey hary
do Haley
har har Harvest
Clinic is he going to be there at 9:00
a.m. or can I go there
[Music]
now cuz it's too early now so many
flowers oops
well oh uh the time is so fast that it
might be 9:00 a.m. by the time I am
there almost almost
almost just going to look for some spots
to
dig D D D D D no nothing nothing here
maybe here
and it's 9:00
a.m. hot balloon hot
balloon I want to go on a hot balloon
have you guys been on a hot air balloon
before there you
go is this not
Harvey how do
I I have to go around
that's so
dumb I do want to name them after you
guys yeah can I not name the current
ones like rename them no what sounds
awesome no no no yes oh going around the
corner I think haven't yet the height
would make me
nervous Yes actually they have a
festival at my Lo local
park
cool I want to go sounds awesome yeah I
think so I think maybe it would be a
really nice
dating
activity I heard you're now part of EDF
EDF
[Music]
EDF how's the melody go
again I think that was a different
Melody Maybe
uh there's a little something for your
trouble thank
you [\h__\h] 60 Gold nothing I'm going to
leave your doors open for that
one especially this
one and even more not this
one but
still yeah how you like that
huh okay I will go back get my stuff and
then go
mine what a rebel I sure showed him yeah
60 Gold is not enough for my services
how dare
you R
Rouge okay
um I will
take I guess I'll take the whole
two and food oh that's maybe 21 berries
will be
enough ooh
[Music]
wow oh 25 energy oh actually they heal a
lot more energy well this this oh no
never mind I was looking at this now oh
maybe the cauliflowers do I don't know
it's probably going to be enough though
okay uh let's
go hopefully we'll get pretty far this a
I'll do it later I'll do it
later that was American national anthem
or
[Music]
something sounds very familiar to me
but it's also not EDF is
it the president's theme
song why does the president have a theme
song what and that's kind of a dumb
themee song
too
what okay here we go um
plop he's a president why wouldn't
he but it's just
so it's like a
March like it should be
more
epic doesn't sound very Epic
ew no special Stones
here just need to find the stairs
please [\h__\h] you yeah what you going to
do now man what you going to do
now die is what you going to do and now
you can't fight
me yummy
crab what the [\h__\h] I'm already out of
energy cuz I can't find the godamn
stairs Mama
Mia is this also to do with my luck
Here Comes achievements played during
presidential procession so yes it's
supposed to sound like a
March where are the
stairs there oh my God right in front of
the elevator are you kidding me
is the I wonder how it's coded is the is
the stair I see those by the way is the
stair uh position already decided the
moment you enter the level or is it
like like not decided yet and the more
Stones like it's just like every time
you hit a stone the game
decides with a certain percentage if
this will be a stair or not you know
what I mean you know what I mean how
would you know it my luck infl to it are
you
sure oh so that's why it took me 5 years
to freaking find the stairs oh it's
going to be a pain in the
[Music]
ass I think it's dead of where they are
when you enter the
floor then it might not have to do with
my luck on the
day
nice is it worth fighting all the
monsters
[Music]
what are you doing
here Mommy says
yes not all of
them M mommy says
yes this is the
circle level I think that goes in a
[Music]
circle nice relaxing music
here it is 4pm in
[Music]
game if I again don't find the
stairs until much
later then I think it may actually be
decided like not when I enter but you
know like kind decided by my luck yes
but it will decide okay you will find
the
stairs after you get rid of like 20
stones so then the location is not
decided the moment I enter okay does any
of this make sense are you able to read
like what's in my
brain do you understand what I'm getting
at
yeah cuz I guess and it seems like I'm
having a hard time finding the stairs
this is kind of
sus yeah DC's pretty
sus oh my God what a waste of my time
but at least I'm getting a [\h__\h] ton of
stones
[Music]
yay there it is there it
is Mommy says I need copper I agree and
oh
maybe
H now we got it right
away sometimes do you get them by
killing monsters that's true yeah this
time this time it was because I broke a
stone
though came pretty
easily oh no monsters in here I think
okay got all the Copper got all the
quartz let's
go I was lucky for
once oh I don't think we've ever been so
deep
before how deep is your love is it like
the
ocean oh
yeah how de
[Music]
How Deep Is Your
Love Hit me hard oh
yeah can we get much
deeper what's this face here why why is
it blue
it farted it found
disgusting my luck is so
bad there's nothing interesting in the
chests whoa what who whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa what was
that on the ground in the sand little
funny worms
do I need to use my
hole how do I fight that come here come
here come and get me
try I got
you I got you I got you got to keep on
moving yeah I got
him a
wacka wack oh oh wait wait okay yeah you
guys can come over
first a whole
party I feel like this would
be quite the heaven for Dungeon
meshy especially that
crab that crab would be a feast
oh my God anime reference from takanashi
Ki what is going on oh I think I need to
go home soon do I maybe get an elevator
dough soon please before I
go two cherry
bombs yeah I need to go to the next
level maybe elevator
elevator and
Boots okay so next time we can start
from this level level
10 armor do you always get the same item
here one defense one
immunity
one is that going to make a big
difference yeah always the
same have a nice IE to find stairs
faster ooh okay okay did I get them oh
did they did the enemies drop
them I did not
see
anything
lucky every 10th you get some goodies
[Music]
oh nice okay maybe next rainy day we can
go to level 20 and then 40 isn't so far
anymore h
H okay
mayonnaise and think I can sell the do
you think I can sell that should I or do
I need
it I've already used it for something
but maybe I need it for something else
too keep up oh oh making more Mayo
machines oh but mommy says I could sell
it well I'll keep it for
now
and some GE going to put this
back tomorrow we can go to the GE
guy and probably do some more farming
and I don't know what else but it's time
to sleep for now and think about it
tomorrow good night o
uh oh maybe we should make some sprink
maybe we can work on making some
sprinklers iron fence preserve preserves
jar
nice okay
okay speaking of tomorrow anything
planned oh yeah actually yeah
o bug steak
ew actually yeah I have something
planned for tomorrow for streaming oo
[Music]
3,440 than
soon I was realizing that I actually
forgot that I wanted to play
this so tomorrow we're playing Dragon's
[Laughter]
[Music]
Dogma mhm that's cool are you happy
about that I think it will be
interesting yeah probably going to spend
actually no I don't think I'll spend too
long in the Character Creator cuz it's
just like whatever yeah you can spend a
lot of time in it but I don't have to I
didn't spend that much time in character
creators and other games either except
for Sims and even there not that
much get your hands on a fishing pole
and sell your cats fishing is a great
way B blah blah blue blue blue
[Music]
okay somewhat annoyed today luck will
not be on your side okay I'm not going
going mining anyway tomorrow is going to
be clear and sunny all day or is that
today I think it's
tomorrow
tomorrow St B St
strawberry strawberry
oh
potato
potatoes
okay I got it I got it I got it I got it
Pi pick where's the other
one you're so good at hiding in this
grass how's the how's the hay doing uh
oh wait the grass too uh the eggs too
but wait I'll I'll bring some more
hay don't walk out yeah that's you guys
that's you
[Music]
guys okay
wait wait efficiency wind
maxing this music is giving me like part
of it not this part the other part
giving me lowkey Fly for Fun soundtrack
by
oh my God I want to play f for fun so
bad but they I I requested permissions
like twice and it doesn't seem like they
get back to
us I think they just don't get the email
they don't see the email or they don't
they don't want to answer or I don't
know what's
wrong for like one of
those I think I think it's like a I
don't
know maybe it's a fan server cuz
officially they don't don't have a
server anymore like an official one but
it's the most official one you can be
on but yeah I requested PRS several
times so maybe I'll just play it on my
own without you guys I was really trying
to stream it even though it might not be
a good streaming game or so but you know
it's just you know cuz I want to play
something that's nostalgic to me and I
want to play
MMOs but it's summer soon and summer
soon
means blue new protocol
uhoh this tree needs to
go it was popular in SCA ages ago yeah
yeah yeah in Europe too I think
especially in the German speaking
countries I don't know why but Germany
just had some kind of desire for anime
mm
RPGs thanks for the membership
gifts blue protocol blue protocol
the protocol let's
go you spend so much on on Fly for Fun
me too I spent hours and hours and hours
and then when Fly for Fun wasn't wasn't
the most popular anymore I was uh moving
on to the next one like there were new
ones coming out all the time now days
there's like
nothing but back then there was a new
one coming out like every every half a
year
maybe in the even in the German speaking
Market MMO genre it's literally dying
yeah like at least PC
MMO genre is
dying or like yeah M RPG specifically
MOS no but mm RPGs yeah I think I
watered it all
think I did it's hard to
see oh my God why you do this to
[Music]
me only one potato
right as far as I
remember you like my farm it looks
organized right I
agree I'm I tried my best to make it
look
organized the miracle Stella blade perms
well
currently currently I can't request
perms cuz I'm logged out and I don't
know how to log back in and I asked JMA
about it and she's like okay I'll check
and then I never heard back so I should
probably ask her again
[Music]
[\h__\h] I can't
move what oh oh okay uh what's I doing I
am let's make
[Music]
mayonnaise perms please there's a booty
game I can get behind Stella blade yeah
me too me
too that's a horny game that I want to
[Music]
play okay one potato one
potato one tomato one tomato
[Music]
Stellar blade perms ju it's a Korean
game
right perms
[Music]
CH what am I doing what am I doing what
am I going to do what am I going to do
what what am I
doing build a silo I need clay should we
just go look everywhere for clay for uh
I'm just going to hoe everything
down maybe at the
Beach what else was I going to do I
think I'm done
here would you play it in Korean if you
did get the perms uh you mean if it's if
the only BMS I got were Korean
BMS dig in the beach yeah I will do okay
but
also let's bring the geod as I said and
let's bring one flower to give to
someone and
and I'm almost done with the
wood almost got all the
wood add the potato let's bring the
potato to bring it to you know
where okay
[Music]
got the part snip too ah
the this one
yeah
oh
no oh I can repair with 200 well now I
don't have that not quite so close
should I repair it now
then I can get some wood
here Mommy says there's a bridge there
that I have to repair for 200
wood the carrot no I think the carrot is
not necessary for the community center
it wasn't
blinking access to good forageable loot
all right
do I just go straight to the
bridge I think it was 300 300 wood oh
Mommy I think it was 300 several people
are saying it was 300 after
all even that should
be no
issue I think I can get there
oh wait my
energy
uh uh
food uh food
food
oh drink the make no I have to sell it
no it's too
valuable I have to sell it I would
rather
eat
this I can make the field snack now oh
oh because of the
acorns well I wouldn't eat it now I
would eat it in the in the mines I
think these are so yummy so crunchy you
love a good
crunch
crunch oh by the way the molding stuff
was not actually molding it was just
really not smelling Pleasant anymore and
it was kind of like creating juice
around the plate even though it was
covered which was what was concerning me
the most but it was not molding and I
got rid of everything
now I was cleaning the apartment me and
my little little Roomba we're cleaning
the
apartment
yeah everything's clean now
yeah don't worry about
it it's all taken care
of do your cats like the Roomba they
don't mind it they sometimes look at it
a little bit curiously for a
moment but no they actually don't
really they don't get upset or anything
by it you know they're
chill the first time I turned it on they
were
like uh observing it oh sorry
butterflies but now they don't care
really they just uh chill around
me as per
usual no they don't jump on the
Roomba I'm so happy that you had your
first Grown star I I already talked
about it yeah I said um on the picture
it looks more grown than it actually is
um oh [\h__\h] my energy they still need
um I
I don't appreciate
that I don't appreciate
that but but I already watered
everything
right I
didn't I thought you just get slow I
didn't know you could actually fall
asleep I thought you only get you you
only fall asleep automatically when it's
2:00 a.m.
I was just having fun cutting some trees
I was about to
eat the
[\h__\h] no I'm I don't appreciate that I do
not appreciate
that come
on oh I start with half my energy
now h
yeah now I know that
[Music]
too I need to better watch my energy why
am I so low energy
anyway I'm not that tired today I didn't
take a nap today and somehow I'm more
energetic today than yesterday at the
moment at
least maybe it's cuz of the green tea
I've been drinking I don't know or maybe
it is because I did not take a
nap uh the spirits are very displeased
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with the
spirits what's there is why am I even
believing a fortune teller why am I
leing a letting a fortune teller like
control my life and my daily life
choices clear and sunny what flower
[Music]
dance why are they so grumpy what's
their issue what do they want from
me so if the if the strawberries are
harvestable
twice does that mean
IRL the same or I guess it's not
harvestable twice but just like some
late bloomer little buds on the plant
are blooming
later maybe that's it it's not that the
same spot where I picked a strawberry
will grow another one right right mommy
I'm going to wait for my mommy to answer
that one
it's not the same
spot that gives no strawberry it's just
other little buds that give me more
strawberries later on right cuz some are
really tiny now oh yeah that's what I
was talking about the strawberries so on
the photo it looks pretty red but it's
uh not that
red not edible yet but we're getting
there and 90% of the plant is still tiny
and green baby strawberries
yeah okay it is how I said it is how I
assumed it is okay W are you lucky I
found you last night oh shut up I have
no idea how much money they
took well I I have 7,000 bucks right now
so I I don't know how much I had
before they ran away as soon as I be
more careful
H tomorrow we're all getting together
for the flower dance if you can find a
partner you might even want want to
participate in the dance yourself
there's a little clearing Beyond the
Forest west of town where we hold a
dance arrive at 9:00 a.m. and 2:
p.m. oh between if you're
interested am I
[Music]
interested am
I
interested uh am I
interested do I need to invite someone
today for energy you need a certain late
game food and for now getting proficient
in different work will lower a bit of
your energy
use is worth checking out you'll invite
at the dance oh okay okay okay okay okay
um was I going to do something with
these
carrots maybe I'll sell this
one I'll sell I'll sell the ones with
the
Stars ah I can talk with everybody okay
so it's another like so socializing
opportunity 342 wood we are going to
take this wood and going to repair the
bridge we're going to give the potato to
the community center as well as the
parsnip and the beans are just for
snacking we're going to sell this we're
going to give the flour to someone we're
going to go give the geod to the geode
guy and I have to water everything
first does that sound like a plan or
what
so much to do guys so much to
do mommy is praising
me reaching low energy gives you a pity
on the next day yeah yeah I saw I saw
but today we started with half
previously we started with zero I guess
wories
cool not what you would like to receive
on Christmas but but currently I'm okay
with
it
oopsie really want to make sprinklers
though it just bucks wait let me sell
the carrots first he just randomly goes
like
B cute so cute
[Music]
uh as they do it's just what you
do this is what you
do mommy you really need to get chickens
this
summer mommy keeps on talking about
needing to get chickens but she also
needs to build a coup first
that's the
problem why do they make such funny
sounds that like actually oh my God I
need to learn about this I need to look
this up because like birds they all have
like these chirpy
sounds like we hear now maybe maybe you
faintly hear it in the
background right why why are chickens
like they sound more oaba than other
birds why do you guys go
like what's wrong with
you what's wrong with
[Music]
you why do you go like that why are you
not sounding more sophisticated
like make like bird songs nobody calls
your sounds like a bird song have you
noticed
other birds get praised for their
beautiful bird songs I'm just like
roasting
you and you just go
like you sound so
funny you're
trying [\h__\h] it's like two more I I
watered the same place a few times
one of our o is waking up in the morning
that's that's that's also not very
elegant we weren't made for singing we
speak more words and when B do trick why
speak more words when B do trick ah yeah
I
guess it's not about more words it's
about more beautiful sophisticated
words reject chicken go back to Dinosaur
wow
it's a speech
impediment
understandable I I believe that what a
struggle oh my God I have a question
have people try to recreate their stardo
Valley I had to check what game I'm
playing cuz in my mind it was a harvest
moon and people tried to create their
Harvest Moon
like place here in Animal Crossing
because I feel like you could totally
recreate it in Animal
Crossing and
dinosaur is my oh I was wondering if my
stuff was still down there the ones I
didn't pick up it
is now she call no no I mean Animal
Crossing I mean can you rebuild
this this whole thing an anmal Crossing
like with these levels this this looks
like it would totally like recreate this
an animal crossing with the tree
placements and the fence here I actually
mean Animal
Crossing but then I called this Harvest
Moon no I didn't really I said I was
about
to what was I going to do
[Music]
it'll be gone on Sunday
n yeah people made pretty much
everything wait cat needs
water water is the Cat
Why by the way can I this looks like
something I can
unearth it's
acorns
guys were they there all
[Music]
along you guys what about
this
OMG
acorns well that's not an corn
but
yo why were you hiding this power from
me hey
yo you guys are holding me
back you didn't
know ah if I leave them there they'll
grow into trees uhhuh
okay I said uh community center
community center geod guy bridge I think
that's it and flower for
somebody oh my God it's already 400 p.m.
holy [\h__\h] I was working on my farm
[Music]
Mommy I was working now we're
flower okay we'll just give it to
somebody random like
granny granny
wait there you go you're
welcome uh where is this bridge I need
to repair like around the beach or what
was it where was
it here
Pam you're welcome Hey I can recognize
Pam
now going to GE guy
first uh on the beach right on the beach
ah okay okay okay okay
no I'm too
late can I be too late for the bridge
too just [\h__\h] closed
man I hate my
life okay beach beach always
open got some new no got some new
stuff which one though which
[Music]
one let's try this
one
yeah wait I could have brought a c do I
still have cauliflower I think I do
could have brought that one over
too tomorrow
tomorrow
tomorrow today
is M
okay is she okay like I know it's
allergies but like is it okay when your
throat gets like that with allergies to
like strain it even
further it doesn't sound like it's
getting any worse at
least is she okay she sounds funny it's
cute but she should rest I don't know
there the the good thing is there to two
people there're two people with one
channel she can just let fuava stream
this is so
convenient it's so
convenient I can fish here [\h__\h] I didn't
bring
my didn't bring my
thingy she sounded better today
okay oh
wormies hi
[Music]
wow you found an artifact an artifact
okay
cool nice
lucky any more wormies
no doing a lot better now almost back to
normal but higher higher pitch than
usual is that what allergies do to you
you open your inventory there's a tree
Ion on the top of you I know I know that
already
what the birds
do what the birds
doing
wormies gotum me worms Oh book
sheesh you found a lost book the
library's collection has expanded
actually the seagulls also don't have
quite the
sophisticated call do they but a bit a
bit more sophisticated than yours guys
uh yes [\h__\h]
yeah I
am M fix it all let's go I fixed
it oh sea
urchin mine mine mine
mine mine mine mine mine mine mine mine
mine mine mine mine mine mine what what
I can't go to the mine so so
late it's already 9:00 p.m. guys we're
going to the mine whenever it rains okay
not today I know what you mean though I
know what you
mean I need to bring my fishing
rod that's it that's all I get
here that's
it can I chop the
trees
no uh hering frenzy has begun at the
beach oh my God and I didn't bring my I
didn't bring my
[Applause]
thingy um more forage will show up every
day
okay all right I'll be back as a famous
Austrian once
said yeah okay guess I'll go
home then tomorrow I'll bring the
cauliflower and I'll do the geod
and I'll bring the spoon also to the
museum and the Sea Orin looks like
something
that is wanted in the community center
but apparently
not where am I is this Pap shorter right
now there may also be a certain someone
that's shows up there I certain
someone interesting sea urchin mommy
says I can sell the sea
urchin
okay sounds
good I'm going for the jungle it's okay
I still have enough time and enough
energy this is my jungle
Welcome to the Jungle
Mayon I love
[Music]
Mayon see cell
Coral coron also
sell apparently
think I can go
sleep
cute
cats
oh good good money
[Music]
400 for the sea urchins and the coral
noise cauliflower cauliflower yeah I
know I know I know
K rerun so I don't get a new recipe oh
no it is a new recipe stir
fry n thank you fortune teller M neutral
today okay but I'm not mining I need a
day where it rains and I have good luck
is that too much ask WEA for tomorrow
it's going to be clear and sunny
[Music]
okay oh we having a little bit of a
harvest please give me some golden
ones
silver oh God oh
God
silver
gold we have struck gold officially
[Music]
come
on
[Music]
more how the [\h__\h] did I do
that is this safe
coming I guess it
is didn't get very far it's
okay I left click I left clicked all of
them and it was fine should I generally
right click
though
[Music]
oops time honored
tradition you mean for you too not just
for
me ah
I already have two golden ones does it
roll the
[Music]
odds I mean I don't know I didn't pick
those I think yet
previously
free that's not why I did it though okay
I think we can do it cuz we have one
already so we need just one
more one and one and three is five just
so you know
wait maybe I
didn't maybe did I really destroy that
plant now that I think about maybe I
didn't destroy
it come on come
on come on oh no
[Music]
no my lucky spoon didn't help me I'm
missing
one I'm missing one on can I still make
more within the
time sheesh so many parsnips I think
yeah we have one more round uh we have
time for one more I'm not going to
reload no no no no no no this is fine
okay uh so we're going to
buy some more seeds we're going to sell
these
Well for now also I'm going to bring
my the thing fishing uh Pole from now
on making me a little bit nervous about
Miss fishing opportunities today's a ah
today is a
festival a can't buy can I go to the
museum though
into the geod guy or is it all
closed damn
it everything's close except
[Music]
joa Amazon is always
open okay then we'll buy a joa but what
what about my geod I guess the geod are
not so important not so urgent the spoon
isn't urgent
either
oh
oh no refill necessary
[Music]
today k
me sell hats okay poke come to old old
old house poke bring coins coin
is you sound like
by old house small small house because
Mouse you are hot Mouse Hot Mouse in
small small house
why
oopsie
o oh Dad thank you for 500 gold So
based dopet super
based more small house for smaller
smaller
Mouse where's the other one wait you're
you're together
again where are my eggs doing small and
big okay that's
okay tomorrow I want large eggs from
both of you
understand no no
excuses mhm I don't want to hear no buck
from
you you made the small
egg shame on you
Shame
Shame okay those can be done another day
okay then I'll just uh go to the
Festival e
time e
time that's all I'm doing right wait I'm
I'm actually going to uh go to Amazon
first
maybe and buy or should I I don't know
is okay to go now we have enough time
right get speed grow too
okay speed
grow got to go fast
I thought you guys were at the
festival it's closed why why why you're
losing a customer right here right
[Music]
now no no no no
no why
why I thought this one was
open huh bamboozle
okay but then we buy it tomorrow close
Okay uh we buy it tomorrow and then
maybe we buy speed grow too uh Festival
they said like
somewhere somewhere there
is I wish I could just follow them I
don't know where they're
going south of my house
[Music]
okay oh
I think I'm
[Music]
in I think I'm
in oh yeah I'm so
in I can't use my
items okay what do you
[Music]
sell seasonal plants seasonal
decor flowers flowers flowers I brought
my own rare
Crow collect them all five of eight
what I'm happy with my
own ceiling leaves oh these are cute if
you have like lots of money to waste
what should I get seasonal plants
[Music]
Maybe Mommy says no need to buy the rare
Crown some of those are new to this
update oh
[Music]
oh wait SE wait I thought I could plant
them never mind I guess plants are not
for planting
huh these are just for decoration are
they then I don't know just going to
talk to everybody
now oh I'm stuffed hey have you tried
the red jelly yet red jelly oh it's
bouncing on its
own can I
[Music]
eat I'm not a big jelly fan though got
to be honest I really hate dancing in
front of everybody it's so embarrassing
for real I get
[Music]
it you know what I admited I really like
flowers oh you
do frog season is really starting to
pick up I fought it just ended a while
ago don't tell me froggy waa is coming
out again she wants that
money now this is the life H Kid sweet
wine a babbling brck warm air did I
mention
wine oh
Pam I should have brought my fishing
pole that's what I was saying yesterday
and I did bring my fishing pole but they
won't let me use my
[Music]
items I wore my best shirt for the dads
this sort of thing doesn't happen very
often hi Wawa glad to see you here
oh that's how I asked them okay
[Music]
mhm the air smells so sweet with all
these
flowers are you going to be dancing
today M why why why is she why is she
laughing at the like like this at me
like she's mocking
me the springtime dances can't be traced
back to ancient fertility rual
rituals fertility rituals meeting dance
I wish Pier would spend this time with
the
family this is like very Pokmon
likee them walking around after each
other like that in a
circle that's not fair why can't I be
the flower
Queen yes slay
Queen someday I'm going to be the flower
Queen and now you're just the princess
are you still ignoring me I'm practicing
my dance moves it needs to be perfect
she not ignoring me
interesting I've been flower Queen for
the past 5 years and I'm not readyy to
step off the front just
yet I'm just enjoying the scenery or
like this Barbie girl over
there but are you K enough is the
question huh love is in the air and I'm
still
single Marney looks lovely today oh I
feel the love is this like Valentine no
well previously was Easter is this
supposed to be
something I'm
nervous I like dancing but this one is a
little stilted uh the old times really
love it though I'm working up the court
to ask someone to dance with
me oh it's saw trash
guy hell there it's nice of you to talk
to me spring is almost over what a
shame a
[Music]
lenus it's sort of like
Valentine's wasn't Valentine's before
Easter flowers I can hardly see
them I've been working on these flower
arrangements for a week do you lik
[Music]
him okay almost I think I talked to
everybody actually
I think I
did excellent saw slurp you okay I talk
to everybody who should I dance with
[Music]
M don't say names say hair colors
I don't know which one's
which pick me I'd love to dance with you
where the
[Music]
chickens I need any orange hair
girl but aren't some of them taken she
looks like me she has purple
eyes Leah Leah saw
me no was was it Leah was Leah the one
who saw me with the trash no I think
Leah was the one that accidentally gave
a flower I think or something
else a cauliflower think Abigail saw me
okay then I don't want to talk to her
anyway can I go with
[Music]
Leah can I go with Lea is she taken with
the guy next to
[Music]
her I will totally dance with three of
you in uh stacked in the trench
code I did it before I'll do it again
again I'll be honest I don't want to
dance with you
[Music]
I can't recover from
this I'm
leaving I'm going to cry myself to sleep
bye just kidding just kidding but that
was emotional
damage can I actually leave before
dancing with someone or is the game
forcing me you know what I'm over orange
haired girls I'm going for green eh I
can't [\h__\h] okay then I'm going for
[Music]
blue why am I even
here why what why am I even here just to
[Music]
suffer I mean this Abigail she's saw me
in the
trash but she's
cute mom makes me do it yeah
but not I don't know I guess I'll go
with you
[Applause]
[Music]
I want to go
home I want to go
[Music]
home
no
lenos please I can't talk to
him wait I don't think I talk to him at
all he Blended in oh oh I can dance
alone negative R
wait one of the
guys he really wanted uh no he liked
flowers right I don't know Sam no no we
need cute
girl I said I I'm I said I I said I'm
critting orange but
oh yeah I'm still creating orange I
can't click on her what what what about
you
[Laughter]
Penny Penny
please please
[Music]
Penny what the [\h__\h] why do they all hate
me
what what is it because I didn't talk
enough of them until
now she ignored me before she's not
going to say yes is
[Music]
she are they all going to say no to me
and you guys trolled me to do this to
get all the emotional damage I could
possibly take is it even possible to
have someone say yes to me once it just
never chance to begin
with
[Music]
correct no yeah I need free hearts of
them I don't think I have free hearts of
[Music]
anybody I'll dance alone
when okay I see how it
[Music]
is where am I
where am
[Music]
I where am
I this is me sorry the brown hair didn't
look like
me
[Music]
what I wanted to wear cute white what
the [\h__\h] I want
[Music]
that was not
fun what the
hell what was
that you guys were like oh you can ask
someone out for a dance you guys knew I
never had a chance to begin with
I wasn't socializing that little with
everybody I have to I gave flowers here
and
there I I hate them I want to move
somewhere else I don't like these
people I'm going to sleep early tonight
[Music]
K risen and shine [\h__\h] today
I'm going to burn the whole village down
oh yes I will I will take revenge on all
of you you will let a phoenix be
rejected on our day oh oh regretti
spaghetti big mistake big big mistake
you have played with the wrong birn in
down I will burn all of this place down
all of it you'll regret rejecting
[Music]
me first pet the
chickens then I'll burn everything down
[Music]
Str
Sparks and then if that actually maybe
first I I'll unleash a
Chima on on on the
village and then everybody who the
Chimera didn't
get i'll will burn down
personally but the Chima will do the
ground work
so this in
[Music]
there I will burn the spirits down too
I can get it done today I just need to
water everything first but the the
strawberry plants they're still there
even though I harvested them for the
second
time oh before next season okay so I'll
just leave them be now
[Music]
okay chicken frog Chima we need a thir
animal for that is there anything
besides strawberries here
no did really all of them carry twice
now I feel like in the first harvest I
didn't get all of them at once but H
maybe the following day I got like two
on the it own like
individually yeah yeah I probably should
should have been at all of
them I'll wa
cat don't
worry I would never forget the
cat you know she's the most important to
me
okay guess I'll go
and face my
enemies and my
haters my denters is that the right word
it's one of the
[Music]
words why would I marry any of these
[\h__\h] that's what you get that's what
you get it starts like that it's starts
like that and you think you think that's
going to be it no no F you Penny F
you it starts with me rumaging in your
trash you're welcome Louis you seem more
appreciative of it than penny at
least Abigail was nice even if she
rejected you I only heard a few that's
all I
heard maybe my
ears were hearing what they wanted to
hear but all I heard is what they said
is f
you that's all I
heard what's
this it's like a
bell oh
Diamond no alamite
okay that's fine that's
cool ew no yeah what the [\h__\h] how is
that nice
H oh I was like why can't I get in I was
checking a time five times I was looking
at the time and at that time and at that
time and at that time I'm like
why you won't let me in what am I
[Music]
misunderstanding
yooo new
reward
what what why is there two places
now a book missing a book missing what
do you mean a what does that
mean where's my reward
a more Lost Books to
[Music]
find I talk to him
okay
ah
califlower what
califlower
califlower the moment it's like I was
hit by a car lost all my memories
somebody says something to me and I'm
like what W wo wo wo wo
wo califl
cellie
CI sounds familiar to
me wait parsnip seats
pareps Callie
pareps
F cuz I need one more golden one right
15 should be enough right otherwise I'll
save
scum is that for one
single
plant maybe I they take four days you
have free oh okay one
per OMG
she so well CIF flowers will also not
grow anymore will
they keep the seeds for next Seas no I'm
going to get the parsnips I already
bought the speed grows but I'm going to
keep the cauliflower seeds I
[Music]
guess um but wait I still have one right
to
give to Community Center pretty sure I
still have one
can't get the seats for next season now
oh I would lose money using speed yeah
but I just want the gold whatever I
already bought it it's too
late if I use the speed grow it's going
to be fine
right like 10% at
least maybe
more it depends
[Music]
really I was so
close one day too long man just because
of their stupid Festival yesterday where
I just
cried was that necessary they could have
had their festival today
instead they're so
selfish m
I don't know should I do
[Music]
it Wiki says it's fine
let's give it a try
I feel like I'm more in a Groove now at
least I have some stuff to
do I'm
feeling
less goal less and less disoriented than
in the beginning of the
stream
but I think I'll end
anyway after I bring this cauliflower in
and end the day
because it's getting
late yeah I mean they just Ru everything
with that Festival
now I would play more if it wasn't for
that can I dig
this
no they ruined it
themselves hi Bary hi
Ken I have decided I'm going to organize
my clothes today I'll have to throw out
all of last year's styles to make room
for the new
ones
understandable I mean
maybe it wouldn't maybe you don't have
to throw away like
everything maybe at least donate them
[Music]
but maybe some items can be
reworn but I understand wanting to have
a completely new wardrobe but you
probably do that all the time
girl ooh it's so windy in here
woo fin
could have finished it earlier but here
we
are we did
it who whoa whoa
whoa I get speed
grow I just bought a [\h__\h] ton of
that hm
good for next season H I see you I see
you what's this new
one let's check it
out only
free ooh
okay a bar of each metal quartz o okay I
can these ones I
can give you probably time okay the rest
I've never seen before
not not h g
Mas
G and you get pumpkins plant them in a
free free grid so you get giant pumpkins
which
is I feel like that was a thing in
another game too
[Music]
was it Minecraft or was
it an
[Music]
Crossing if you need to give a present
to the person you like once per day
[Music]
oh uh can you never miss a day if you
want to be
like if you want to marry them are you
never allowed to miss a single
day
o
o o o o o the library has been
expanded o o o o
o twice a week ah I can miss it twice a
[Music]
week nice rolloo
oh oh oh no no no no
[Music]
[Applause]
no
okay why do you hate me why does the
ocean hate me so much what did I
do
trash okay the game really hates
me improve your I can't improve my rod
maybe I will but I just got gold ore oh
my god let's go oh wait I should check
out the
island
loot loot Goblin loot Goblin
moment now's fossil let's go that's
cool I think that's it oh wait I didn't
go down here before did I maybe I did
no no
bubbles gold on the beach let's
go the sand is taunting
me sand is making fun of me it's
probably just fake gold I'm going to
proudly bring it to the blacksmith and
he's just going to laugh at me
like you
fool you uneducated fool you big this is
gold it's literally just chocolate
wrapped in Golden foil here rip it off
and you can see and then eat
it
[Laughter]
ridiculous that's what I'll hear from
them this whole game is just out to get
me
I'm home says Wawa to
nobody nobody cares nobody
answers except for my cat I guess
actually my cat cares my cat cares and I
love my cat I can sell all of this right
even this no wait this is this has to be
donated
trash
yeah that's all I need yeah so
true
okay
yum oh daffs alone are not good enough
either apparently oh my God what if I
don't want to be married with these
people because they're so picky and so
selfish
and make no effort on their own why do I
have to put in all the effort why is it
always me why is it always me who has to
like invite people and socialize with
people and talk to people start a
conversation and give them gifts why is
it always me yeah I want to marry lenus
give me lenus he appreciates
me as a human being even though I'm a
phoenix cuz they're EMP
PCS
well
well there's cases where it's not NPCs
and it's the same situation just kidding
I'm not that I'm just making
jokes uh oo level five farming hey
y Rancher oh I have to choose animal
products worth 20% more ooh eggs eggs
eggs eggs but even are they still 20%
worth more after I put them into mayones
choose tiller mommy says
tiller even though it's a smaller
percentage well you guys also say tiller
okay okay level three foring we cookout
kit Moss
soup thanks for the recipe I will cook
it for
am it's been a long time since the last
am Mansion huh o good
money good money
[Music]
hone e m soup is that a real
soup that people used to make maybe
K it's so over guys I have a lot of
money though and it's almost the end of
spring uh apparently by the way I
checked um apparently uh this is
also uh streamable for members only so
that's a possibility in the future
H if you guys would like that then I
don't spam my channel publicly with this
not that I'm planning
to yeah no uh oh yeah regarding members
I don't think I can do a member stream
this week I'm sorry but you guys have
been getting weekly member streams
anyway for for months now so I think
you're okay with that thank you next
week I'll be back with maybe a short
Shrine Wawa Shrine review if you guys
can prepare some Wawa shrines I would
appreciate it now we're going to read
Super Chat so feel free to stay and
listen stay while and
listen need to clean my place yeah or
just the area where the wa Shrine
goes Shrine RW
[Music]
I'll consolidate all of my stuff to one
area yeah that'll be your Shrine make
sure to place some candles to make it
more Shrine
like candles or what else could maybe
flowers if you want want to make it look
really nice and pretty flowers
candles M maybe a
cat plushies or plushies belong to the
merchandise I guess maybe some nice like
uh like you can place them on like some
stairs or so and maybe some some other
like something like plates and bowls
maybe if that helps just giving you some
ideas right now
beautify the W yeah
cookies food
offering oh yeah good night Mommy good
night food offer you could offer me some
food yeah maybe like a crispy chicken
from Burger
King or uh strawberries or cookies
chocolate cookies
or uh something like that I don't know
you know you know what I like you know
what I
eat [\h__\h] Burger
King I love crispy chicken from Burger
King I had it the other day when I came
back uh from cologne and uh I had my
friend try
to for the first time my friend was
delighted by it the Tomato in there with
the crispiness the special crispiness of
the crispy chicken wo it's so fresh and
juicy and um and then the salad there's
always plenty of salad in there I don't
mind it with uh cheese either by the way
usually I get the no cheese version
though sometimes I get with cheese but
that's just because they decide to put
cheese in there but normally it's
without cheese oh yeah the Oreo sh Shake
M crispy chicken with the Oreo shake
usually that's I I don't order that
because it's not included in the set an
Oreo shake but uh it would be great but
it's a little bit too much it feels like
a little bit too unhealthy I usually
just get the items individually
separately on different days like I
wouldn't get both the Oreo shake and the
crispy chicken at once what are we
talking about right
now um
yeah press multiple times the green
leaves w a the little apple
guys cute they're dancing
oh I didn't know they could do
this oh that's cute I love interactive
screens like
this
wow that's so
pretty it's
SK who
h
a
[Music]
did you recognize that
I made the
[Music]
melody how did you not recognize
it I I didn't do it all the time I did
it at the very end
[Music]
there you didn't hear it what the
[\h__\h] are you real kfp are you even real
kfp one more time
okay
huh are you hear it now
I mean they all kind of sound the same
but it's the Rhythm It's the
[Laughter]
[Music]
Rhythm Bravo
[Applause]
oh
oh come back to us I'm here don't worry
that was a an error in The Matrix
it's me like an hour exactly that's why
we got to read super
chats oh she's a ghost no that's me
doto who apparently oh she's me oh my
God
stop wow why am I so popular with
girls why am I so popular with girls how
come oh my God no way oh my
gosh yeah I'm her o o
oi I don't know what it means but I'm
her
o wow it must be that
special this voice makes you bless
really oh you're one of the few ones who
can tolerate it
then most are like please shut the [\h__\h]
up k please shut
up well the we real k please shut up
please shut up please shut up with the
real k please shut
up early in the
morning I'm mixing some things
here okay Super Chat time it's super
chat reading time super CH reading time
super CH reading time super CH reading
super reading super reading super
reading Super Chat reading Super Chat
reading Super Chat reading
wooo what's next part
eight you just said what we all want
admit really you think
so why won't you why won't
[Music]
you w w w w
cor okay Cor
I love that uh thumbnail art is so cute
oh my god I've been using so much froggy
waa art now I'm running out of it soon
don't just because froggy waa week is
over does not mean you guys cannot draw
more froggy wa uh uh hoodie art by the
way not hoodie whatever that is uh
Poncho why is rain on the menu you're
late with that question nobody questions
that nowaday
it is what it is long long long long
tradition that is called
Thanksgiving I kind of need to go on an
idle meeting but I also think I can hold
it in for another
hour
easily the other day the other day on
like Monday was
it
I went to an idle meeting at around
11: and then it was like uh
past uh next time I went was uh past
11:00 p.m. no past midnight I
think but for most of most of it I
didn't feel like I I had to go until
maybe the very end I think on that day I
probably used up a lot of the liquid by
sweating during the day and I didn't
drink that much either in general but
yeah just saying I can hold it
in all the discussions I need to do in
idle meetings I can hold it in to the
next meeting easily
okay I was okay I didn't feel like I had
to go don't worry don't worry don't
worry I wasn't like holding it in
because I you know felt like oh my God I
need to go no no no no no I just didn't
feel like I had to go but then thinking
about it I was like huh it's been such a
long
time I was just busy but maybe I'll go
now I shall go
idle meeting time maybe petting a cat a
little bit as well see you in a
moment
e
e e
woohoo
okay
sorry
I I am
healed I went to go to Idol meeting and
on my
way I saw smovie I saw
smoovie and she
was lying on
[Laughter]
and she was lying
on my waa
blanket
because the usual blanket that I usually
use as a spread over my bed so that
smoothie can make cookies out of
it uh she threw up on it like 3 days ago
so I've
been I've been washing and drying it
right now
um so as a replacement because there has
to be something to make cookies out of I
put the waa blanket on there just this
once as an
exception don't want to use it too much
you
know um and now it's cute because she
was lying there and then she was like
kind of lying diagonally to where
smoothie in the illustration is on my
legs so so there was two smoothies there
was two smoothies and the moment I saw
her she's like she was like she was
sleeping but she woke up and she was
like and she stretched her H her arms
towards me and then I went up to her and
I gave her one pet and the moment I gave
her one pet she started buring
aggressively so I gave her more pets and
more and more and more and more and then
I brought her
over yeah she might go back to the waa
blanket but it's smoothie seption
smoothie next to
Smoothie let's
go it's a good blanket very good blanket
you this movie doing the Spiderman
pointing me kind of congratulations on
the 1 million views of C yay thank you
so much I'm so happy I wanted to say
this like just uh once again say um like
me doing well with my music within Holo
like being able to kind of lowy a little
bit keep up with the how do you say the
hard
hitters the the ones that are more even
more active in terms of music and have a
big label me being able to keep up with
that wow it really uh makes me feel very
very honored and
validated
sheesh shees
[Music]
yeah the merch sales too oh my God it's
good stuff good stuff happening at the
moment good
stuff the non Envy yeah that one also
has like a lot of views was surprised it
wasn't like completely combined I guess
no that does just doesn't happen I'm
going to upload the Acappella of Kima
like Saturday
or uh or Friday I don't know what are
those days and then there will be a
cader broadcast on I think
Sunday uh Early Morning Europe time so
night time Na and
good afternoon time
sea oh maybe no maybe I'll do it on
Saturday I'm pretty spontane uh flexible
when it comes to that maybe I'll do it
on
[Music]
Saturday but Acappella on Friday I
think hopefully my internet will work
this time and I can enjoy the K I hope
so too for you I hope so too cuz it was
really good people really liked it the
clips were so funny
48 hour
loop no I'll put it up as like a b not a
stream so that I don't have to be there
to like keep OBS open or so the only
thing that has to be done is JMA
privatizing it afterwards privating
privatizing
[Music]
privating but otherwise you know I'd
have to start the stream in OBS and end
the stream in OBS and on YouTube studio
and I think I think I I I can't do that
with uh the VOD if I put put it up as a
v then I just have to make the
reservation like one or two days before
or so and then it's hands off for me
just somebody has to private
it it's
easier don't have to keep something
running all the
time just let it run all weekend no it's
okay no I mean
nah nah let's not do that cuz I I don't
know I don't know no no no need to do
that
unless I don't know should
I should I no but then then I have to
keep the PC on no if I would do
that I have to keep my PC on the whole
no I
can't also because I think
um you know whoever's taking care of my
cats will be using my PC
too
so then someone else like JMA would have
to do it but I don't think it's very
convenient for her to keep it on like
endlessly
too she have
to keep it on for hours and hours
depending on how long you want me to
have it 24 hours that that's that's
electricity
bills and all that I'm not going to ask
Gemma to do that
no that's
crazy and I don't think she would be
there monitoring it the whole time what
if what if something happens what if
like some
some like something breaks down I don't
know no I'll just do it
[Music]
normally okay that's right the w
w super chats great game by the way
ah yeah it's golden week yeah I think
they might be working
anyway hi my comments on the last four
yaka streams have been Shadow banned and
some kfp suggest me to ask you about it
maybe you can help this apparently
hasn't happened before to a kfp I don't
know what to do this hasn't happened
before to a
[Music]
kfp
uh it
hasn't I mean there were times
where comments yeah in the in the live
chat
where oh it was just his comment he
could chat talk in chat F you mean so
the VA
comments what well maybe you wrote some
keywords that uh uh were like NG I don't
know or it was like taken a Spam which
is weird in itself is it still like
this is is it also in other YouTube
channels comment section can you comment
[Music]
there it usually gets fixed after a few
days wait I I guess you're not here now
but maybe answer these questions in the
kfp hashtag
tweet and I can send it to JMA a
screenshot kept on coming up as era
couldn't send yeah for super chats it's
like you know you just can't send a
super chat then
[Music]
mhm jaob 47 d mp53 g
d philipo
[Music]
Dan
SP monkey na for the pinky is this the
start of your keyan Arc
[Music]
or
who some joke I'm not getting
again what is this
[Music]
about K it says k i that's me and then j
u a n
y Spanish
bit vamos Amigos oh yeah I I was saying
a little bit of Amigos and stuff I
think oh I want to learn Spanish please
teach
[Music]
me
Shin
sha did I read it correctly come thank
you oh this is the one that said they
collected more than
4,900 boxes oh my
God np15 free garlic d n d eating my
Tyson as
than Jes py m d Lou thanks for the red
chat and K just got home right on time
for the chw w wow how you doing kiaha I
hope you're having an amazing day I'd
say as amazing as you but getting to
your level of amazingness is is quite
possible for a simple day wow flattering
aren't you what's going
on
woohoo thank
you P
maker black d h d Legion D motion danuki
Sky
ER tiny
Del looking for
[Music]
the go the pink
thank you for using my arst the
thumbnail for today it really made me so
happy love W you're welcome I'm glad I
can give you some Joy from that because
honestly it's just I'm just really
grateful for getting cute art you know
for my thumbnails really easy to turn
into a thumbnail too some some some
artworks are a little bit difficult even
if they're really good and I want to use
them they just don't work quite well
with the comp position and
everything uh so this one was really
easy to use and really cute and really
eye-catching so thank you so much it
turned out great please more please
more action in thanks for the red chat
Bing Bong mother Cluckers I hit my third
year in my service to Kiana and you know
what that means that's right I get my
combat armor and get sent to the front
LS to fight the taco Menace fight or
friy chickens PS can you bring back the
KP mea PSS Kima banga thank you that's
right it's funny how
the the not the Lord what's the word
again that I forgot about
previously the cannon is that our
enemies are the
tacos so I feel kind of bad about it but
but but we we all know we we don't
really have a issue with them or
anything I wonder do they ever bring up
something like this in their own
Community like we have to fight the
chickens or is this like a really
one-sided
[Music]
thing if if yes and that's kind of
awkward if it's just us making up these
things Ro playing and and talking to
ourself are you this one-sided oh that's
that's kind of embarrassing
[Music]
it's like we just want to play and they
just don't indulge in it
oh it's okay chickens we can play with
each other even if they don't want to
play with you if they don't want to
share toys that's okay we have each
[Music]
other
uh or that one person in the
[Music]
corner I just needed some random enemy
and remembered that was a thing for a
bit I mean for a bit it's always been
kind of a
thing I don't think Ena even
knows I guess maybe she
doesn't she's just existing you know she
wouldn't know about these things
she's just
[Music]
vibing the feeling of that one person no
one wanted to dance with yeah it feels
very
[Music]
familiar anyway moving on thank you
action
it
congratulations for the armor and thank
you for supporting me for so
long you are the best thank
I think I'm going to read the super
chats from the
K the trucker
okay trucker
okay
now so
good so good if only it could be
archived
[Music]
man would have been great would have
been legendary it was legendary but
people that's how I guess that's how
Legends that's how Legends work if it
was archived maybe it couldn't have been
a
legend then it's just
history a Legend doesn't have this like
Clear Proof this way it's a
legend because like this mysterious
thing that people talk about it happened
but you can't really look back on it you
just have to trust what the people tell
through generations
[Music]
wow so
philosoph philosop philosoph Phil Phil
philosophical
[Music]
thanks I got it figured it
out okay Super Chat time reading time
for TR just as soon as his red light
changes it's cute I like the uh
emojis stupid red
lights red light not going to tell me
what to do no no no
no what if I'm color blind huh what you
going to do then huh what can I do about
it
huh no my truck I still have my license
I still have my online
license they're in order you look at
sometimes sometimes they're a little bit
different sometimes they're kind of
weird sometimes they're sideways
especially the icon is also
sideways and and sometimes sometimes
it's four sometimes it's two you
know sometimes it's different and it's
like what what does this
mean what does this mean
well maybe I would know if I had a
license right well anyway I don't need
one I truck in my lands of Austria I
have a right to truck in my lands of
Austria it is my land it is my country I
shall truck where I like to
truck no one can hold me back it's my
country he thank you Jay's
WB
[Music]
oh that reminds me
guys or maybe I'll bring this up um in
in the next Euro Truck Simulator stream
can you remind me uh keywords are friend
and
inbook I'll I'll keep it for the next
stream if we drive to inbook or so
I Stumble over your name I
[Music]
always Studio r faceks with Pinky
Cruz d m arcade d m thanks for the pinky
last thing I expected to see today was K
singing ACDC but I'm very happy I did
thank you for the rock also kudos for
not totally crashing it yet thank you I
was also going to sing like one more
ACDC song but I thought well I might
just keep it for next time I need some
good songs tracking songs for next time
too and uh this one I didn't have time
to practice but yeah you're welcome was
it yeah it was going to be TNT I mean
the chorus is very easy obviously I knew
it but then I realized the rest of the
song I didn't
know and I didn't have time to practice
anymore
so next time there always next
time you're welcome ACDC Rocky Wawa came
out finally on that
day Jackson FB thank you for the pink
Super Chat this is unironically the mix
of music I listen to on my road trips 10
out of 10 realism thank you all you're
welcome it's so funny because like as I
said a couple days ago when me and my
friend were like driving around and had
the radio on they were playing a lot of
these songs too and I'm I'm like I I
don't know again I felt validated
because I was like yep when I was
shooting these songs I was like yep yep
this this would possibly
fit to you driving this is maybe
something that would feel nice while
[Music]
driving yeah
so feel free to next time not turn on
the radio but play the VA of my K just
got to download it
somewhere got to record it when it's
rebroadcasting nightfall dun TX dun Dori
dun M HT D Dori dun seon thanks pinky
just appreciating the multitasking going
on here between driving singing when she
might have to glance at lycs plus maning
the 3D dancing with her arms but that's
exactly why this will be so silly and
alltime Stream in the making for real
thank you for pointing it out I mean
maybe it was obvious I hope you guys all
appreciated it but I was obviously
moving more than I
wanted to because of the 3D to make it
look more interesting but that means
even less control over the wheel and
then I was also looking away cuz I was
reading the
lyrics and then you guys didn't even
know until I told you but the music was
really quiet in my ears I barely heard
it it was all a hot mess and it felt so
stressful for me but then you guys still
really enjoyed it so
actually you guys didn't really feel any
of the hot mess if anything it was
entertaining to you so mission
accomplished yeah
[Music]
nice no no I think this is how I want to
play the game um but
yeah hopefully next time it can hold at
least a full
hour the fry tracking
I think it really can it's just maybe
one tracker wasn't charging properly
I'll check I'll double check next time
when I put everything on because once
the the stupid thing is I can only see
the status of the batteries of
everything when I have everything on and
the program open and like every tracker
has to be turned
on so that it shows the batteries of
everything so if one tracker is dead
already it won't turn on and it won't
show me which which one has a that oh my
God it's so ridiculous actually if you
think about it like say say the
batteries are like one is off one out of
like I don't know 20 trackers is off so
it won't show me in the
program if they're all on then it will
show me the battery level of each
tracker also like the location like on
which body part but if one is dead
everything will shut
down it seems and then I have have to
find out which one it is but the way I
can know is I can look at every single
tracker and uh they're like um they have
a l LED that's like
blinking but I have to it's still a
little bit annoying I can't do it with
one look because they are wrapped
around and like they are like for
example on the arm but the whole thing
is like wrapped in a strap like maybe
one or two layers of strap so
I can't just look I have to look under
the strap so that I see the
LED and they're wrapped really
tightly and some are tucked in the in
the shirt like in the shoulders and on
the
back it's a bit inconvenient all over uh
but
yeah I've been getting more and more
used to it actually I need to really
check the the
um map data like chy has been putting
them together for me and something about
them just looked kind of off to me and
funny to me it's just really hard to
explain what it
is something just looked weird which is
why I didn't upload them but anyway it
will be good to upload them while I'm
gone
anyway so they don't have to be ready
just
[Music]
yet yeah I'll check it after the stream
because chy sent
something again something
new I'll be checking it I'll be checking
the
[Music]
chy checking the
checky another word with ch checking the
Chey
[Music]
uh
CH chat yeah yeah so easy and it makes
sense I'll be checking the Chey chat
I'll be checking the Chey chat checking
the Chey CH checking the Chey chat
checking the Chey chat checking the Chey
chat checking the checky chat checking
the Chey chat checking the chck chat oh
[Music]
checky
Channel check in the checky chat check
into check chat check into check
chat check
chat this is actually a really good
practice for
your sounds because it's
checking the
checky slightly different chat then
again different similar but different
now if you want to use this tongue
twister that I just created you have to
say everything very clearly
yeah checking the chagy
chat checking the chick
CH checking the chicky chat checking the
chck
[Music]
chat okay okay okay okay okay sorry
sorry sorry
sorry return to Super
[Music]
chats samai
KY stamps bear D cish thanks for Pinky
the singing the German the bunks pure
Cinema what bun me bunking
against everything on the
streets thank you very much glad you
enjoyed it little bit of German here and
there sprinkled in I'm glad you liked it
I think um obviously there were there
was like at least Loof ballon that you
know but there were some that may feel
very new to you
right what the [\h__\h] is this in my
tea I see some weird stuff in my
tea what is this
[Music]
uh okay I'm not drinking this tea
anymore uh no not the honey I think I
don't know what it is oh well it's
okay not the fly
no I bonked a fly today one of the fat
ones and it fell down on the ground and
it looked dead for a moment and I'm like
I didn't even hit it that hard but I
guess that worked but I looked at it for
a moment and then it started moving and
started walking around I'm like oh did
you play dead or were you actually just
I don't know feeling like you were
bonked but not like deaf Bonk and then I
let it out into the freedom because at
least it didn't fly away anymore
uncontrollably it was just
walking so I I let to
[Music]
outside it didn't bleed don't
worry maybe it bled internally though I
don't
know spider D Che your channel
D do Moonlight thanks for red Super Chat
got home just in time for the true
Halloween Classic Country Roads Country
Roads yeah
yeah now time to relax and enjoy some
amazing kiok special your amazing
tension never please never doubt that K
be love
forever thank you thank you Country
Road take me
home to the
place where she
Serv and she
slays singing and
dancing Country
Roads Take Me Home
y you're
welcome tripod D Richard G D seven s d
Jin d h thank you for the rest of CH
this set list is a is Banger after
Banger after Banger after Banger after
Banger best Koka to date couldn't stop
smiling all the time it was so much fun
actually want to see how how would you
fair on a racetrack after today
what do you mean thank you for today
much love thank you but what do you mean
I've been playing Mario Kart several
times in my time in all Al that is a RAC
trck excuse me very serious one at
that racing against you guys and other
whole life members and random people is
really serious
business do not underestimate what goes
into that
[Music]
oh yeah I played F thank you thank you
if you're not happy with Mario Kart what
about me playing fzero
huhuh
huh
huh said that a racing game to you
you guys will never be satisfied I see I
see I offer you so much so many
options you're never
[Music]
satisfied God damn it these chickens so
picky so picky thank you
hokan LBX D Star Command D somber APO d
gy d for the pinky I love your song CH
in every K you do W it's always so much
thank
you I hope you can also do more of these
fun kok ideas because watching you drive
and sing is way more enjoyable than I
thought it would be thank
you yeah I I do want to like I want to
do like like you know like more like
standing up and lowkey dancing just like
I did back in the day with the like the
shitty uh home 3D
but
man bre
Doo bre Doo
Desa well I might do it eventually
[Music]
anyway no I never played with those DDR
mats never
[Music]
hey if only I had a treadmill H if only
ha funny H
funny check 47 G for the pinky love love
love the bangless I had to hold myself
I'm singing out loud at 6:00 in the
morning enjoying this immensely reminds
me whenever I go on long drives
listening and singing to my favorite
songs kopia thank
you yeah those are good vibes even if
you don't have a license yourself just
by
I mean everybody probably has been in a
car before with someone else then just
enjoying the radio while the cars are
going by and you are zooming around too
it's just a nice feeling that we can all
relate to yeah I think people are more
like even if you don't normally listen
to mainstream music I think people are
more tolerant of mainstream music if
it's in the radio in the car why
why D you tolerate it
[Music]
huh I don't mind it generally
but I feel like you guys were more
tolerating
too I mean I sang you know some songs
you that maybe I mean those were all
kind of
mainstream but more genres that you like
but still there were also some some
different ones like shine up and drive
drive drive which is not mainstream now
anymore but it used to be back in the
day it wasn't that different from my
usual kok song Choices if you think
about
it just a bit more variety but I mean
there were some older songs you know
like foot
loose but that's pretty much you know
that K I did back then the the' 7s 8s
themed K that's pretty much
that if you want more of that foot loose
was so fun man Foot
[Music]
Loose yeah the boom C I really really
really like that one too I need to do it
again that was a good
one Boomer or we should call it the
classics karoke don't call it the Boomer
karoke it's the classics
Kar from 70s and 80s m
or was it more 80s and 90s I don't
know or all of
it yeah g d again you're welcome for Rip
Tide I love that song Lou M again thank
you for the red super chat I've waited
for this forever thank you kiaha you're
the best context you saying you're King
cover from all
ah I've say that one a few times already
though in KZ
but yeah thank you it's made a comeback
a nice
one appreciate it thank
you salubri be z d for the pinky this
was so freaking fun you come up with
some crazy ideas awesome sist too thanks
for singing for us W you're the best
thank you thank you soon yeah I try to
still you know have some nice UniQue
Ideas every once in a while bring some
creativity onto my channel still trying
my best can't do it every day we need
some normal streams in between but I'm
I'm here I'm using my brain and my
creative side as much as I
can thank you very much I'm a beep dang
unending arrogance dang for the
pinky oo some you seem like a
lurker I can't believe we got two backto
back Alzheimer and I actually got to
watch them live I'm glad you got to
watch them live thank
you thank you for being there thank you
for watching my stream thank you for
supporting me and having good time with
[Music]
me
H Jim Tracy D for the pinky this was
such a cool stream so much fun and the
sist was sick we even got German bangers
and H thanks for coming up with such a
neat idea thank you I I'm glad you
enjoyed it I thought we need some German
even if it's
risky and yeah H know was unplanned but
you know when it comes to Europe beat I
always have hinotori at
hand my beloved yab beat hinotori so
many memories with that one
too
[Music]
Christina SP blaz and or Titus
t t thank you
up by up and also belated happy birthday
to Christina mananita I don't know if I
already said it but just in case happy
belated
[Music]
birthday I'm going to read like a dragon
part seven or is it not part
seven part nine
but seven fits the ribbon
[Music]
better
Christina starting to catch
up kind of but at least I mean most of
these have pretty smaller smaller amount
of super chats
yeah uh here we
go did I
never
take thank you for
pink na cotton thanks for the pinky the
moment when your favorite streamer gets
the same feeling you yearn for when
their chat gets
[Music]
read was this what did I what did I talk
about aord I reading my chat I thought
it must have been like yeah me being in
someone else's stream and recently that
was mostly coron his
empai and not don't tendo I don't think
so don't tendo and me chatting and being
recognized by don't tendo it's been a
long time
ago he's been streaming a lot these days
but I'm I'm too shy I don't really want
to I don't really I don't know I try to
avoid
it I don't want to bring attention upon
myself in his
chat at least not on Main
[Music]
yeah except except for palor because in
palor he really seemed like he needed
some back seating urgently like the rest
of his chat was so useless oh my God
it's so it's like so different from
here it's mostly it's the age difference
it's crazy what it does to one's
[Music]
chat
yeah all all kids
mostly kids under
15 but there's some other adults too I
think but I don't know somehow the chat
is
just zooming with
Zoomers we got these those here too
really I don't really ever see maybe
really rarely but that's maybe not even
the age but just weirdo
weird people being
[Music]
weird anyway I got to
hurry yeah thank you
na I was happy when Kon read my my my
chat
but today was it today
yesterday I also showed up for the the
other stream no maybe it was yesterday I
think h and and she you know the thing
is like she gets so focused like she
misses a lot of my messages too
which it's okay I
guess it's it's okay like she will ask a
question and I'll answer but then she
won't see
it it's okay I can't be helped she's
locked in yeah they can't be help it's
not like I it's not like I had anything
important to say
anyway it's okay her viewers are having
a conversation with me
instead yeah she stays pretty focused
she'll miss
like 60% of my
messages it's
okay it's not it's not so important but
I'm just happy she notices me at
all I love
her spank thank you for the r thanks for
the recommendation I must check into
this Taki I need another
oi you don't know her yet in what year
were you born on born under what rock
were you living how have you not known
her until now especially if you're other
oi obviously is Celly how can you oi
Kelly and not have heard about
me crazy crazy
crazy yeah keep up with the times man
thank you I hope you're aing me now
properly as you should I am a beep D Jim
Tracy D motion d j d CG o I like your
name dun Yu or oos oos you even you even
put like a proper Katakana pronunciation
there next to the you know Ro romanized
letters and I still read it how I want
to read
it for the pinky too much enemies no
more enemies please Yakuza less enemies
okay
careful that was what I was thinking all
that time
same
same I love this
meme hu for the pinky I went to K collab
Cafe yesterday I am at this super chat
it's not that there was a collab Cafe
yet I just thought about k at the cafe
in fact I didn't go to a cafe I just
drank coffee at home in fact I didn't
even drink coffee my state just k
I think this is one of the best super
chats of all time on this
channel this has to be go onto like a
wall of best super
chats has to become
history honestly we should we should put
this
somewhere I love this it's up there it's
so up
there genius Super Chat delusional and
hallucinating but absolutely
winning and so
[Music]
right let's go
[Applause]
Honolulu oh my God it hit Super
Chat so
true slay Unity chat D the monster Envy
D Anthony W the pinky kiaha did you know
New Jersey has the most diners in the
United States why do all these sounds
are familiar I guess I was just actively
reading super chats when they came
in we talked about this I think on
stream na
SP new
Joy some people seemed to be offended by
that I don't know what's going
[Music]
on feel like I'm missing ah some
something it's only the accent in the
northern half of the state New Jersey
took that personally yeah I did
yeah they
did ah fridge oh that's a cute
idea pinning all the the funniest super
chats it doesn't even have to be on the
fridge it could be on that that cork
thingy cork board over there I got to go
now thank you Richard thank you thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you wait
hold what it this time I went to KI kabu
Cafe last week this time I really went
oh the kabu menu was kfp fries and
potatoes it just fries and potatoes wait
wait that's the same thing it was
heartbreaking for Oh you mean probably
chicken fried chicken right it was
heartbreaking for eight the friend but
it was quite delicious I was sad that K
didn't appear in any of the random Goods
a you got to go
again one more one more one more one
more more one more go again go again go
again go again go again go again one
more one
more let's go let's go
vamos that's the only choice that's the
only option that's the only reasonable
thing to
do yeah Jacob 47 D Lou Moonlight thanks
for chat I won't be home for the stream
but I still hope you have an amazing
time Kiwa and kfp also from the stream
title I guess I should say once again
doubt this to the frer even if they're
right I'll catch up as soon as I can I
swear I like the way you
think this is the ideal
way even if you're doubting it even if
you're going to be right you you should
still be cheering for me not be Doom
posting
[Music]
no doubt yet yes yes no
doubt don't speak I just want
[Music]
your don't tell
me don't speak
[Music]
no
D it's such a good song right ah they
made great
songs motion Santiago Santiago Martin
thank you for the red chat dear K on the
second week in the usual room I've been
forced to hear your little [\h__\h] every
single day the fact W doesn't know it
was my dream been called like that by
her is amazing but I have to act like
I'm in pain suffering and dying two
weeks more to leave this place
[Music]
sorry I think I'm too exhausted to like
role play with you right now
[Music]
uh to fight against you I hate it
actually okay I strongly dislike it when
people are like turning this thing
around on me and saying I enjoy the
usual room so much no you hate the usual
room it is set up to be whatever the
most painful setting is for you you
enter the usual room everybody gets
their own Dimension it doesn't work like
that you cannot be enjoying the usual
room
[Music]
understand it is not possible I create
this world
[Music]
that's what I told him too thank you
he's delusional from his
stay if you say
so you like the robot well then there's
no robot in your usual
room if you like it then it's not there
does that mean in new room there's no
Kiwa if that's what you if that's what's
the most painful for you
yeah
[Music]
yeah well then you better be good once
you get out of the usual room again if
you don't want that to
happen oh don't cry to me now don't come
crying to me now you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
don't have energy for
this stop
crying stop crying
[Music]
wait
motion is motion
[Music]
here
motion
who what's
up what do you mean if I start you into
bed we start what my stream started 5
hours 42 minutes ago I'm not starting
[Music]
anything wait are you mad are you
angry are you angry are you angry
[Music]
he gone
did motion motion his way to the
bed oh you're here oh are you
[Music]
laughing okay I still want that story
though still need that
story whenever you
ready take your time I mean you have
your whole life in front of you in the
usual room so
you can take your time it's like on you
you memory hold all your worst ones
it'll come to you because that's will
that will be all that you thinking about
in the usual
room you have nothing else to think
about there is nothing
else you have plenty of
[Laughter]
[Music]
time what could it be what could it be
maybe ask a friend or ask your family
members you don't have to tell me like
publicly in the super chat or so either
you can send me a letter which will
arrive 6 months to one year later which
will of
course yeah your usual Rim sentence will
take as long as it takes until the
letter comes to
me and I have to still Jud it but it was
good
enough I'm so so
[Music]
evil oh that's
delicious Michael H Dan white boy Dan
Thomas D stry thank you for the wet
Super
Chat wow it's my birthday it's my third
year sending a birthday Super Chat been
watching since the first near stream oh
and wanted to thank you for always being
amazing I'm happy to call you one of my
osies
# Tony good choice good choice good
taste all I wish for is if you can maybe
sing me Happy
Birthday h happy birthday to
you
m
[Music]
in I hope the satisfi you
satisfy happy birthday to
[Music]
[Applause]
you happy birthday thank you for your
support I'm glad you're still here after
three years I'm glad you joined on that
faithful day we're meant to be together
you know it you know it you and me dear
chicken you and
[Music]
me so don't leave ever don't leave pinky
swear pinky swear you're not here I
think right now but pinky swear yes yes
yes yes I know you're going to say yes
you have to you have to m
don't have those true
but I'm just going to dye your feathers
pink and then you swear and then it's a
pinky swear
easy looking for the top dang R dang
Lord D Anthony web D did you guys know
flush chats used to be way more common
in my streams back back in the day I
completely stopped mostly stopped going
away so you mostly stopped
flushing it feels like nostalgic for me
to see several blue super chats in a
row H silly strawberry d space
wonderful for
fun
L and and space water
[Music]
and I used to skip them when there were
too many nowadays I don't skip them
necessarily and it shouldn't be about
that flushing has a a
deeper more important meaning than just
being read out
[Music]
loud you should understand that there's
a bigger
Mission a bigger
purpose ah flushing is more than just
being read out loud and it's more than
just
flushing it's
about
making or what's the word bring
[Music]
it it's yeah it's a way of
life
and making a statement yeah yeah
yeah
and
believing
period yeah it's about
sanitizing no not really sanitizing
[Music]
but it's important for all of us
yeah H I am feeling
like I am turning into Cinderella
soon but I caught up a little bit in
super chats maybe tomorrow a little bit
more maybe even finish them Dragon's
Dogma tomorrow will be the last stream
for a few days Asa
Dragon tomorrow Dragon
Dogma yeah I know I I'll start I don't
know what I'll decide when I wake
up but yeah probably going to start a
little bit earlier then
[Music]
today
and yeah tomorrow is Thursday
right okay yeah and the MERS
wallpaper maybe I'll put it up
tomorrow we'll
see
Thursday thanks for the chill stream
thank you for watching hope you had a
good time everybody see you again
soon thank you for
watching
and I'm going to eat the rest of my
now I made two of
course as always minimum two
[Music]
servings
byebye thank you for coming
by and talking to
me I'm just a smaller smaller YouTuber
on the screen on the
T thank you for giving me an a audience
AUD
[Music]
million yeah