[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
y k
frog
W where's your
camera do they see me I'm
so I could see
you really this is this is my little
sister today oh you're
so you're so
[Music]
cute we're not that far yet okay oh
sorry sorry we just met know each other
okay yeah we just met
hi hi Chad hi welcome to the stream this
is our first date because we met on
Tinder for frogs right Tinder for frogs
yeah yeah yeah yeah what what could it
be called what could Tinder for frogs be
called
[Music]
um uh Tad tadpole uh uh I I was thinking
of tatter
like T Frogger ER uhoh Frogger right
that's a game though that I love that's
kind of ruining my childhood right now
stop it guys
ruining I don't want to think that like
I mean Tinder has like a pretty like you
know it's pretty scandalous you know
Frogger Frogger is just a cute guy oh so
what we're doing is scandalous too are
we no I don't think now
[Music]
no come on
St come on you guys stop get your minds
out of the gutter was what was um what
was so interesting about my profile that
made you swipe to whatever side it is um
whatever side it is um I think
definitely the gun is really
attractive really oh you like guns
yeah
it's attract good gun it's a good gun
good gun M can you see it has a little
frog sticker on it yeah it's so
cute well also I can I can even though
you should be the one protecting me but
I can protect you with this uh fly sweat
sweater oh are you catching our dinner
tonight yeah I guess I could do
that
okay so we are going to go on a date
this is the the uh winter World Of The
Well of us like whole live English that
we used for the first time last year or
last last year I can't even I don't even
understand time anymore me neither I
think it was last
year was it I think so I want to show
you guys there have been some updates
made for this date specifically and
there once again more than I could have
ever imagined first of
all uh how do I angle the camera like oh
yeah
look wait this is it this look at the
nor I'll show you guys
too wait how do I angle it stop looking
at me wait is this sideways oh sorry
guys um we're sideways now it's so
pretty there we go
wow oh my gosh wait it's the Big Dipper
or Big Dipper the Big Dipper Little
Dipper
Dipper blue Dipper Dipper what dip what
is that BL Dipper it's a dip oh gosh I
can't let go oh my hand so
shaky you guys oh gosh the camera's
stuck are they shaky because it's so
cold I don't really think this is an
environment where frogs should be
normally anyways no I'm I'm nervous
that's why they're so
shaky
understandable
well right am I more beautiful than
these Norr lights oh yes so much more
really yeah I'm going to put mine there
too
I
oh oh why is it sideways
again why is it sideway you guys this is
so
scuffed oh my God booty I'm upside down
oh my God there we go wait I want to
look I want to look between your legs
let me I mean I mean I mean I mean I
don't in a weird way yeah okay yeah yeah
yeah okay oh it's like um it's like
a oop oop oop oop hey yay I passed I
passed yay
y go through properly I don't think go
for my
I can try probably hold on let me okay
I'm I'm willing to try anything close
the
ground okay here I go here I go
everybody um I can my B like this every
kfp is probably screaming at me right
now that's
okay I'm dring I'm crawling I'm crawling
I'm crawling is is it working is it
working
[Music]
oh
nice nice nice nice okay I think that is
a weird start to our date I feel like it
shouldn't be like this but maybe
yeah uh well anyway this is by the way
in case you guys don't recognize her
this is p rain puff hello
first
wave and this
is frogy AKA Tak I guess but that's a
secret don't don't tell anyone oh yeah
don't tell anyone or else you have two
choices of weapons to be dealt with was
oh I think I'll take
the on your butt let me spank your butt
like show me your butt okay okay
wa there's literally no butt you're so
flat hey that's not very kind of
me look at my butt that is Rous I can
twerk she
can
who look at her
girl actually but but frog bird where is
your frog bird voice I was just about to
say I don't I don't know will you love
me even as a frog
Bird that's exactly why I brought you
over
[Laughter]
here yeah hello everybody my name is
frog um I'm a pretty uh swell guy I'm
ready to take this
lovely froggy lady on a a spicy
don't you let's
go oh my God I love your voice so much
Canada oh we're in Canada it's pretty
seems
like I don't know I don't think it's
Canada I think it's Finland girl oh
maybe yeah so uneducated Mama Mia I
didn't P geography or biology
see one of the charmes you have besides
um being tall because knowledge doesn't
seem to be one of your charms
so um let's
see
um uh I a tall dark you wrong mic what
do you mean I'm using the wrong mic I'm
using the right mic I think wait wait
wait wait wait sorry I don't notice the
comments that much oh [\h__\h] no oh yeah I
was using the wrong what you
are that's why it is that why you were
so quiet that's why it was yeah that's
why oh my God sorry it took me a while
and fixed now and fixed how loud is it
now pretty loud okay you sound okay I
think it was fine in VR chat so yeah it
definitely
was yay
SC froggy waa hasn't streamed for a
while so I'm not used to it anymore true
oh yeah the last time you used frog
birt um I think frog birt had like a
comedy special um used it yeah frog
Bird's a really sought after
guy the ladies are like knocking they're
punching they're kicking everybody to
get to him actually so oh oh yeah well
but you don't want anyone but this cute
froggy lady right yeah it's it's funny
cuz they like punch and kick I can't
tell um I can't tell if they're like
trying to get to me or run away it's a
little I remember that one stream where
you were like doing a dating show like
you were participating in a dating show
yeah and I was
thinking these ladies are not rightful
this frog man she needs he needs someone
like
me yes so we're going to go on this
State now and we're going to show you
guys this beautiful winter World which
is now updated for these cute
frogs go let's go hold on I'm going to
grab the
camera me
too oh hello everybody I'm going to move
you up a little bit then I'm going to do
this activate
wait I need to set it to follow me I'm
so Terri ifying next to
you okay oh it's a little bit low wait
wait one more one more try yeah
oh good good that's good and then T
let's go I will follow you oh but then
it's behind me wait wait how oh my God
po froggy waa is leading you on the date
okay come with
me so
cute follow me okay I'm
following beautiful man oop sorry I
don't want to get in your camera away
guys oh it's
fine following
you hold my hand oh okay I don't hope
you don't mind
Cheetos
can I stick your Thum in my
mouth yum wow this the first time
anyone's volunteer to do
that okay come on come on come on this
is the main area with the tree the tree
oh hold on everybody almost Christmas
yay
Christmas do you know what Christmas is
frog bird uh yeah it's the time when uh
the world is a
blaze the trees are all on fire and it's
a beautiful oh yeah [\h__\h] yeah I love
that kind of
Christmas that's the best kind of
Christmas oh my God this this girl knows
how to have a good
time I know or two of our good
time especially frog related games on
Steam detective my favorite game wait
you are you gamer too did you play frog
detective yeah I did yeah it's so
fun frogs bonding over
frog I didn't play two or three though
only
one what well you you need to get up to
my level which is this High she's a real
gamer amazing I'm a real gamer M so if
you want to you know if you want to get
with me you need to be you know a good
gamer can you can you do that can you
get good at gaming I'll be good for you
girl she's so cute oh my
God
froggy look at me I'm not cute I'm
dashingly
handsome yeah okay truth sorry sorry of
course you're really handsome like I
I've never seen such a long frog like
this especially someone who can stand on
two legs besides me I've never seen some
some frog that can stand on two
legs yeah it's pretty rare actually I
think maybe we're freaks of
nature I think I think everybody else is
a freak to be honest so true not to us
not us I almost fell okay let me
check is everything okay besides the the
thing in the beginning I think
everything is okay now okay are we all
good so I want you I have an idea for
your first quest to impress this frog
lady okay follow me
oh all right guys we're going this
way this way this way this area is um
already familiar to the viewers of me I
think yeah this is not new but I want
you there's these pens right we we used
to use them to draw on the on on top of
the Snowman oh yeah these pens okay and
if you like um uh if you if you push the
right button then you can draw oh yeah
like this but I want you to draw me like
one of your French frogs with this pen
okay with the pen all right any of these
pens oh wait where's the other pen
there's this one catch oh I see there
just one catch you can only use uh 30
Strokes then it will start to disappear
you can do 30 strokes and then get
another pen and continue the art with
that pen okay oh okay okay just use
several pens okay what do you want to
draw maybe uh like against the the nice
scenery you can draw in the air you
don't have to draw on the St oh okay
okay let's see um I think let me check
test oh yeah I can draw in the
air hold on let's get rid of
[Music]
it but everything will only disappear
slowly pumu just take a new a new pen oh
okay I made a mess here you go Taco how
do I show
it okay I'm going to draw her
likeness wait where should I stand so
you can watch me um uh right there right
there I wait I'll put the camera here
okay I guess we good everybody everybody
can say I'll do sexy pose sexy pose me
like one of your friends
frogs sounds like a french
fry French frog excuse me don't turn me
into a french fry and more than that
okay let's
see well are you an artist
yes oh
really
yeah I'm also quite an artist myself
sometimes so I have a best friend his
name is the pomy he's pretty well py
yeah the
pomy the pum the
p is that just the Vinci uh AKA pain po
uh no that'd be ridiculous are you
counting those Strokes by the
way 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 okay okay I'll
draw the rest in one
stroke okay wait let me put that here oh
oh that that's good that's good
oh
oh what's what the [\h__\h] is that it's you
doing
this okay my arms are not that long hold
on I forgot the
bow
okay I drew you a little bit more froggy
like cuz that's kind of my style but and
I'll give you some long fingers too just
like
me it looks like a
monkey what do you think guys does it
look like does it look like me come here
come here
guys
I'm going to turn the
dramatic entrance what you think it
doesn't it's it's it's it's pretty nice
it's pretty nice yeah I mean we maybe
have to work on that on those artistic
skills okay but as long as long as you
have passion for it I guess I guess I
can see room for
improvement well if you're looking for
an artist maybe you should be at a
museum not on
Frogger um excuse me wow wow you even
want to be here you should be fighting
for my love you're right sorry I am an
artist my craft is my [\h__\h]
cute it so cute I love your froge voice
it honestly turns me on like
wow oh my guys I think I'm
in don't say that I can hear that okay I
can hear that sorry I can hear
everything okay frog uh drawing mission
complete
compl for that you get one hug come here
come here big
boy I can't even touch her I got I have
to hover hand I'm too
sweaty cuz I didn't change shirts before
the that's what you should have done why
did you not you stinky stinky
frog they think they can imagine the
smell can't imagine the
smell okay next uh wait let me move the
camera again okay
can I reach the
button your arms are so
small so
small but that doesn't mean that I don't
have a a big
ego
okay she I like that in a lady a lady
who knows her worth
yeah that's
attractive
I I have so much worth I'm worth I'm
worth more than your whole frog uh a
pond what my pond I have six ponds by
the way six
ponds whoa I think I'm marrying into
royalty okay yeah now now I can reach it
uh so it's so pretty
wait I cracked the Cod let's go a frog
bird let's go
okay we're going this
way this way
okay so starting from here there will be
a new
area here oh my gosh wait yeah okay cuz
this this is this is existed before it
was a nice place where you can Grill
some marshmallows o yeah like with this
did I show you this area
before I think so sausage
really maybe I explored it myself yeah
really
wait I actually I thought it's actually
getting um darker just now but it was
just the Shadow the
[Music]
contrast very filling
indeed wow holy
[\h__\h] I don't want to I don't want to say
anything about that but that was kind of
spicy
wow sor is really
delicious wait the
camera uh why does it not turn with
meou what are you do ouch
ouch sorry I was just trying to protect
you my
lady no no no we don't want grilled frog
tonight maybe another night can you kiss
my feet to make them feel
better I'm going to blow at
them did they feel better now frog birth
much
better really okay good then you follow
me I'll make you feel even
better wait hold on I'm going to zoom in
a little bit there we go guys this C is
new guys wait I'm going to do it from
behind so you guys
can
see oh wait hold on oh I messed up there
we
go wow on the ball no I'm as tall as you
give me
a oh wait I'm on the
ball oh I'm on the oh I'm on the why are
you trying why you always trying to be
I'm not trying to
[Music]
be right that seems to be a solution to
for our height problem yeah now you're
actually taller than
me how does that feel huh finally a lady
that's frog taller than you wow oh my
god get your crotch out of my
face uhoh I'm not trying to harass you
or anything it's a sorry I just was
really excited about the
ball one
leg let me carry
this okay stop doing stupid stunts how
did that
happen there I don't know what
happened be careful you going to destroy
the snow okay we're not going to destroy
okay me this this New
Path oh wait uh I got to do this there
we go now you guys will
[Music]
follow it's so beautiful in this winter
wonderland wow oh my God running through
the snow with a frog by my side Will he
win the love a froggy W oh my God and
she's a lyrical
genius yeah and now surprise turn
around Christmas
Market
W this is so
cute
[Music]
AKA and V not marked in German it's a
Christmas part game it's my first time
ever both going to Christmas Market
really yeah really
yeah come come here at the at the
entrance I want to let's take a picture
more like you guys will have to take the
picture though
uh oh oh nice nice this is good this is
good yay welcome to the Christmas
Market frog date look at look look at me
frog frog bird Look At Me Hold My Hand
this is a beautiful
moment like our prom
photos
cute so cute
okay okay let's go in I I heard that
it's not officially open yet so there's
no people actually doing anything there
but oh perfect we can still go anyway
yay oh hold
on uh
Anor beh anchor local there we go sorry
guys frog take a picture with me
[Laughter]
here can you fit
um wait I think uh hold on let me move
it cuz uh the your camera there we
go oh there we go there we go yeah yeah
okay Crouch yeah yeah yeah am I
in uh yeah pretty much
[Music]
yay so
cute what are we oh we Santa a what do
you want for Christmas we we're holding
a
reindeer what what I want for Christmas
all I want for Christmas is
you
baby I watched your video about the
Christmas Market
tles oh really yeah my Advent calendar
video yeah I watched
it whoa you're so interested me are you
you could say I'm a little
obsessed oh I like that I kind of like
that on
you see the CL let's go through the
market I don't know what they will be
selling not looking at me we'll look at
the market don't look at me look at the
market you don't need to look at
me oh my God creepy dos and one of them
oh hello I didn't notice that hello can
I go
in wait I can't go in why is it why do
they look like
[Music]
that they I think they want to be
adopted but they got to try a little bit
harder than that oh I've seen that clip
of like the doll from Resident Evil that
sounds like her
yeah yeah it totally sounds like her
does maybe that's why crazy I would I
would like to purchas oh there is
yeah Boop you you would like to purchase
one yes
please I think you're a little bit
delusional because there's no one
actually selling them right now D
they're right there what are you talking
about wow right there yeah just take him
just take him you don't have to buy you
can just take him take him
yeah you're so
close so close are you just grouping
them
no oh that'll be
mine oh this is a atie anti- theft
policy this is how you just make the
merchandise fake and then you can't
steal it perfect for frog bir and froggy
waa
prevention trust me trust me you don't
want to take this doll home it's going
to turn into a horror doll that's going
to H
you oh oh sorry guys how how do you like
horror games by the way frog bird I a
big fan of horror games if I do say so
myself really yeah I don't really like
them but yeah maybe you can can hold
me while playing
them and protect me so that I'm not
scared yeah with my if you don't mind a
little bit of slime I mean I'll win I'm
also slimy slimy that's why we're
together wait what's here oh there's a
microwave and I think you can get uh
like punch and mold wine here
o and coffee coffee I want some I want
some the good juice the hot Christmas
juice give me give
me I want why is there no one serving
the frog
princess uh um I can serve you uh give
me one
moment oh
oh my arm's really long
actually reach
amazing you're the man for
me I love him I love this
guy just get you guy a really lanky arms
and you'll forever be
okay that's kind of hot that's pretty
sexy no the beverages are served hot
but you also pretty hot it's it's cuz
it's a really a
here are you okay so far like are you
not freezing from the cold cuz it's like
minus 10 cius here I'm stuck in the
building but I think I'm all
right get out of there come down here be
careful you're going to Bunk your head
you beautiful head you're so
cute the more I look at you the more
Charming I find you how did you think
when you first saw
[Music]
me I let's just say
that might just ruin our relationship so
far so let's stop froggy wow you hopped
right on Frogger so you
know I do be hopping on Frogger
hoing and
twerking that's what got me for the
right
man okay frt come follow
me I'm scared is
that let's go let's go this way first
okay oh I think I have to turn around
there's another little section here with
another
Bridge oh I left you guys hold on I left
my chat behind sorry guys oh no okay now
they're following you know where it is
yeah yeah okay I reserved a private uh
Hut just for
us wow she moves
fast whoa there's a hot you don't move
faster yeah there's a hot tub and oh
yeah here here is the hot Tob look with
candles
oh let's
enter we do a swim in the hot tub and we
don't even have to take a clothes off
because we're already
naked you're it's kind of cozy in here
I'm feeling really self-conscious
now why are you already naked before
yeah but there's something about being
in a tub and
then getting even more slimy huh my chat
has like the stalker looking around the
corner view yeah
don't look where are they right over
that
one I can't hi oh there we
go how's it going oh I keep on standing
up let me sit
down look
cute it's so so warm in here maybe we
can lay our first eggs in here this is a
perfect place for
eggs right I think they will be well
protected and you don't drink it no no
drink the water where I will birth our
children sorry I just wanted to also get
a little we need a good
amount I'm going to get my camera real
quick come you guys it'll go right
here that should be good there we go
yeah I got something for you if you were
so thirsty
uh you can either have me or this hot
chocolate preferably the hot chocolate
oh
okay I'll also take
one you
nous everybody
come
I can drink
handsfree she's so
talented thank you I'm glitching in the
water me too me too you know I think
frogs are meant to be
glitching that's just our Natural State
it's true
I think actually the funny thing is I
think in German slimy M kind of uh you
you do say is uh slimy is glitching oh
which is like
glitching yeah wait I just realized that
holy [\h__\h]
what so it is real it's F yeah would you
like a marshmallow m'am I'll feed it to
you it's so big wao wow
actually like in oh my
God Crossing some boundaries here but
okay slow slower please can we take it
more slow Mr Frog bird I'm kind of shy
sorry I didn't mean to frighten you
glitching we're both
glitching so frog tell me a little bit
about your your frog family do you have
have any frog family that I I have to
like know about um I don't know I was
born in a tub similar to this I
okay I think I was the last guy to be
born I'm a bit of a slow Bloomer but uh
you know um by the time I woke up
everybody was
gone oh oh that's really sad wow
but I think that's what made you so
strong to be such a such a strong
independent frog bird today it's true I
had to learn how to fend for myself and
that's when I created
fire you created fire yeah how um I just
uh I
uh and somehow it just you know there
was also a lighter that was close to
where I was born
so okay a close to where you were born
yeah interesting can you teach me how to
create the fire another time oh yeah
I'll show you every one of my techniques
even how not to get detected by the
cops that sounds exciting I I I want to
destroy more things you know and fire
seems like an element that could be
really helpful in
that I think you have your priorities in
order I think you've got a good head on
your
shoulders a big head at yeah I know no I
said did I say big a good
head yeah but also a big one I'm proud
of my big head that's fine you can say
it very round has a good shape oh thank
you wonder what that skull looks like in
there my skull my skull I I think my
skull should
be pretty similar to yours but we can
figure it out sometime maybe if you open
me up like they do in the schools I'm
going to look right
now no no I'm not ready yet no sorry not
for not for
television yeah actually never mind
because one of my one of my family
members they died because the they were
um taken apart in the school by some
children those [\h__\h] humans yeah they
spliced up like my whole family it's
kind of like I don't know I that's what
the day when I decided I have to be a
menace to society and teach them a
lesson yeah with this water gun
yeah it's a water gun how dare they kill
my whole family how dare they how dare
they
stupid ass kids what did they learn from
that anyway frogs rise up help them at
all yeah frog let's go unite together
against the
schools yeah rule the world rule the
world rule the
world I like your I like your political
Ambitions yeah I'm goingon to you should
run for president honestly
me only if you're my vice president baby
oh froggy waha and frog President and
Vice President of the
world sounds good okay follow me okay
follow me we're going to go to the next
we're going to go inside a little bit
and warm up oh we're going to go inside
scooting you over guys we're going to go
in
here W where's my chair there oh my
god oh it's so nice it's so cozy I legit
want to um sleep in here oh what the
this looks really cozy ceiling and
everything the windows are so pretty
this is actually so
cute can I lay down right here or I'll
lay right here can I actually lay down
you
could there I go um you're
disappearing are you still
there come come back
up I'm drown is this just are you just
trying to see my under skirt but I'm not
even wearing a skirt I'm already you
don't have to do these kind of things
just say more you caught
me wow frogy waa sit
down can you sit do you know those
videos of like whole Live members in
Fredy just sitting down cuz that's so
special wait just sitting
down yeah like some people clip the
moments of home life members in freie
just sitting down oh CU that like
sometimes they sit down in a really cute
way oh probably just a normal way yeah
no the one thing froggy while I sitting
down
oh my God so cute wait I can't hold on
trying to capture it on mine so I can
show everybody don't look at me look at
her look at her where she's
sitting no the clip I'm obsessed with
right
now yeah you tell me oh I was going to
say the one where M son is going to the
bathroom
I love that one
too oh on stream it's so funny yeah that
was really funny I'm obsessed with it
disasters okay let me let me tell you
something yeah the this this um building
that we're in right now is called
aota it was originally a six sided tent
used by the Sami people of lab land but
nowadays these are often built out of
wood for outdoor recreation it's a it's
it's also good uh to go there when
you're going skiing uh on natur nature
trail and then you take a rest at a
public Kota yeah there you go hitting
you with the Kota lore wow where did you
read
[Laughter]
that no I totally knew that on the top
of my head oh
I'm very knowledgeable I can share a lot
of knowledge with you you know she's so
knowledgeable
realiz if you show this
window wait oh God this is difficult you
see the norn lights for this
window yeah like this both of them yeah
yeah wow both of them pretty so
beautiful so pretty this place yeah it
looks pretty uh
flammable
[Laughter]
don't evention get out of
here think about it don't destroy the
beauty just yet maybe another
time no no no no no I'm watching
you we have to we have to you know be
careful because they built this just for
us we can't burn it just yet it's so
true it's so beautiful there's a lot of
candles though
what's over here maybe maybe in
summertime maybe we can jump into the
water from here actually wait you can't
go into the water here there's an
opening wait where's my
camera [\h__\h] do you know how to
swim no help
me help me oh um I'm coming I think hold
on give me a
moment oh she's going to
drown hold on I have to film you're
drowning give me a
second what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] generation
of YouTube they need to film everything
on Tik toks and [\h__\h] man I'm dying just
filming a Tik
Tok
hi
that's so cute I like a [\h__\h]
baby wait how do I get out of here wait
how do you jump uh I think it's a yeah
okay okay here you
go I stole your thing from you oh you
can take it nice okay okay I got it I
got it I'm back out okay danger danger
zone this is the danger zone oh you're
doing a swim oh you're a good
swimmer
ouch who how did you get so good at
swimming uh you know just uh having to
escape one too many times from the
backwards swimming Alat can you teach me
Alat I went I went skateboarding in
alcat once what
skateboarding
yeah I we skateboarding in alcatra have
you never been skateboarding in Alcatraz
I can't say that I have that's really
impressive I think there this game was
it a GameCube
game yeah Pro Skater Pro Skater 4
Something Something Tony Hawk Tony Haw
Tony
Hawk
yes yes so this there okay follow me I
have I think one more spot to
show uh sorry
guys um I got to move you up a little
bit more enough swimming thanks for
being patient enough swimm he likes
me does he like
me I'm going to crawl after her okay
look at this watch watch I'm going to
crawl after
her what are you
doing
um
don't okay I'm gonna
crawl what did you say
nothing nothing I'm embarrassed now
there we go
okay come here what she saying all the
[Laughter]
time okay oh oh oh look here frog bird
there there is a cozy area for us to sit
in and oh what is this water botle doing
here on the ground oo I don't know what
it could it be
before
oh we we'll have to find out maybe come
sit down here
okay um next to me
okay yeah
yep we're both on the
ground nice oh wait I have to move my
camera I'm
sorry no problem oh [\h__\h] is it because I
moved my camera there it's okay though
don't worry I'll just put it right in
front Okay
okay okay I think maybe I should spin
the bottle or you should spin the bottle
and wouldn't it be so funny if if if it
points to one of us we we should do
truth or there
oh yeah sorry hold on this is so
SC okay there we go truth or dear all
right then you you know I spin it first
okay okay you spin it no you spin it no
you spin it oh okay I'll spin
[Applause]
it well
um what do we do about
that I guess you have to ask yourself
Truth or Dare and you have to choose
truth or dare I dare frog bir
to to yes
yes burn the whole building down oh oh
wait no
no I know it's our our inner inner
voices you have to turn down your inner
voices just for a little while longer
okay okay my bad I dare you I dare you
to uh run in a cir won turn in spin in a
circle uh 10 Rounds 10 turns spin for 10
turns no not like
that
two three that
no
okay I'll stand up I'm scared of
actually hitting my head he's messing
with me oh yeah this spacious enough
yeah this is okay all right spin spin
frog spin spin spin the
frog is there a cable yes there's a
cable
four oh five okay I'm going to go the
other way
[Music]
six no accident please no we're okay uh
what was that eight
uh something like that nine
n
[Music]
10 W I'm actually dizzy how dizzy are
you I'm really yeah actually I think
like VR makes you even dizer
than I think so
[Music]
too okay all right that was good you can
sit down again okay and I guess because
you spin it last I'll spin it now okay
[Music]
spin will it be oh it's on
me no
way
you can uh you can you can ask me truth
or
there um TR Truth or
Dare truth
truth
um what's your favorite way of world
domination favorite method
oh favorite favorite way of world
domination using
takiki as my puppet
making her think that she is in
control because she is quite a strong
lady I will admit so I let her do all
the the ground work and then then once
she is close to dominating the world my
plan is to shoot her down
yeah and then take come with the
world I've seen you invade her
straight yeah yeah yeah I've invaded her
once but I I thought she wasn't quite
ready to like finish with her work that
I have planned out for her so then I
backed down but I will be coming back I
will be coming back watch your watch
Tak you I'll be back yeah she'll be back
not copyrighted trademark phrase from
movie you can't get rid of me just yet
nope okay you spin you spin the B
[Music]
okay it's not meant to really do this
all the time wait spin it again spin it
[Laughter]
[Music]
again oh my God
it's on me truth for dare frog bir um
we'll go
truth do you is there someone that you
love
oh
Mark
um
um my
m
I love my I like my
mom and
uh was it something I
said I'm going to spin the bottle
now why do you just spit it you just
ignored it after do you not care do you
notet about my feelings you just bring
volum alone here anyway what's going to
happen are you going to ask yourself TR
there again H what the hell you know how
to treat the
lady I um I was going to say truth or
dare dare I I dare frog BT to propose to
miss frog
you I'm going to get on one
knee done
oh oh wait that reminds me I
actually there's something missing here
okay whoa is that a
come do you oh
maybe do you take these Cheeto
fingers as your L I will take
them oh I'm getting sucked in oh take
you
a how are you doing
that wait wait and then I trth or dare I
dare myself I dare myself to kiss you
okay I can't close my eyes um hold on me
neither hold on I'm just going to die
real
quick oh what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] no F you have to kiss
I was about to kiss you kiss me to wake
me
up but that didn't change anything about
your eyes so I don't quite understand
why you did that a I I don't
know okay I'll kiss you I guess you're a
little bit submissive
[Music]
huh how do I get up one for you guys how
do I get up wait how do I get
up use your legs what do you got them
for I can't get
up wait that's how this ends oh there we
go again Romeo and Juliet all over again
oh okay um
woohoo we're married we're
married you a
backflip at least we're engaged now yeah
we're engaged maybe next time we can
have a wedding a
wedding what do you think about that now
that we're engaged we can have a wedding
next time wedding yeah yeah yeah we can
we'll we'll find a really toasty place
next time nothing too cold
okay oh oh really well I kind of like it
here
though okay we can find some we can go
to the desert next time the desert yeah
go to the
deser well then everybody congratulate
us for our engagement please let me hear
you say congratulations
congratulations
W okay congrats on the engagement thanks
I finally found love in this lovely frog
you
did I almost I almost ruined I didn't
think I would meet someone like you I
thought I would be alone forever in my
world domination plans but I found
someone who understands me and and my
hate for the world truly from the
deepest of their heart so let's let's
destroy the world together power frog
power frog power what's up with frogs
and wanting to destroy the world that's
a
little well don't ask me I this is how I
feel I can't help it
I can't I can't really move my hands cuz
I'm always holding
something your hands are so small I need
to be prepared I need to be prepared for
for for destroying you guys if you cross
me or even
you okay y so with that I I I guess
that's we're going to have our secret
alone time now because you know engaged
people do what engaged people do maybe
we'll go back to that hot bathtub and
lay some Tad PES oh my god um yeah yeah
we better get some good baby shower uh
uh
presents yeah baby shower send the check
to
here me I'll take the money gold bars
gold bars Please gold
bars only gold bars that's the only baby
shower gift that we accept yeah okay
let's let's uh take a cute picture uh at
the end come here come put your arm
around my head like it's my
shoulder y yay p peace thank you guys PE
peace oh
peace Yay
byebye see you next time when the frogs
are ready to either dominate the world
or get married for one of those things
one something's going to happen
byebye byee
byee oh and and w w
w can I can I say this girl that's doing
the world termination for me Takara on
Sunday she has oh she has a 3ed uh
birthday concert half a year late and
and and um well froggy wa won't be in
her in there Pomo won't be in there
either because your model wasn't
ready but yeah I hope you guys can check
it out I'll be dancing a and fumu will
be watching too right yeah fumu will
probably be watching
yeah all right then thank you guys thank
you so much bye-bye byebye
check out P's Channel if you haven't yet
it's in my description
than K you have to check out kiaha so
that all right my computer is over here
byebye
[Music]
byebye where is everything
going to turn
[Music]
over