​​​ ​Some “once upon a time”​ ​​
​​ ​is not where our myth belongs​ ​​
​​​ ​Through the faded lines​ ​​
​​ ​of words and rhyme is a hidden song​ ​​
​​​ ​Though fractured deeply,​ ​​
​​ ​worn by sorrows from time and time again​ ​​
​​​ ​Take my hand and enter our… “pretend.”​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Myth - Non-Fiction​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics and Direction: Mori Calliope​ ​​
​​​ ​Composition and Music: Elliot Hsu​ ​​
​​​ ​Art and Illustration: Dino​ ​​
​​​ ​Animation and Music Video: Echo Motion​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Mori Calliope, Takanashi Kiara,​ ​​
​​ ​Ninomae Ina'nis, Gawr Gura, Amelia Watson​ ​​
​​​ ​Special Thanks: Our Loving Fans​ ​​
​​​ ​By star-lit skies​ ​​
​​​ ​Endlessly writing​ ​​
​​​ ​Inviting those along​ ​​
​​​ ​Lost souls who hear our song when gone astray​ ​​
​​​ ​Though strife’s part of life​ ​​
​​​ ​Stay unafraid, now​ ​​
​​​ ​When forces say “behave”​ ​​
​​​ ​We say instead,​ ​​
​​​ ​“Be brave.”​ ​​
​​​ ​In a desperate shout, our souls reach out​ ​​
​​​ ​With pen toward every page​ ​​
​​​ ​We ignite, come alive​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a starry night​ ​​
​​​ ​With a fire no doubts can take away​ ​​
​​​ ​Got no fairy tale​ ​​
​​​ ​Where “love prevails”​ ​​
​​​ ​Though painful, now we move endlessly on​ ​​
​​​ ​By the light- your spark​ ​​
​​​ ​Head first, into the dark​ ​​
​​​ ​Some “once upon a time”​ ​​
​​ ​is not where a voice gets heard​ ​​
​​​ ​Will the faded lines​ ​​
​​ ​of speeding time make us flightless birds?​ ​​
​​​ ​When pen is running dry, a soul on fire​ ​​
​​​ ​Is driven to react​ ​​
​​​ ​And when burning flames attack​ ​​
​​​ ​We will never fade to black​ ​​
​​​ ​Though fake, it seems​ ​​
​​​ ​Not a dream​ ​​
​​​ ​Or a trick of light​ ​​
​​​ ​Always vacancy,​ ​​
​​​ ​Take a seat​ ​​
​​​ ​It’s our story’s time​ ​​
​​​ ​A world is brought to life, through voices five​ ​​
​​​ ​And as “real” as they say​ ​​
​​​ ​Pen as sword, we’re choosing fate​ ​​
​​​ ​We can never lose our way​ ​​
​​​ ​By star-lit skies​ ​​
​​​ ​Endlessly writing​ ​​
​​​ ​Inviting those along​ ​​
​​​ ​Lost souls who hear our song when gone astray​ ​​
​​​ ​Though strife’s part of life​ ​​
​​​ ​Stay unafraid, now​ ​​
​​​ ​When forces say “behave”​ ​​
​​​ ​We say instead,​ ​​
​​​ ​“Be brave.”​ ​​
​​​ ​Defiant ‘til the end, I’ll stay killing​ ​​
​​​ ​To sing​ ​​
​​​ ​I’ll dance in burning embers unyielding​ ​​
​​​ ​Your love’s given me wings​ ​​
​​​ ​While learning to remember the good times​ ​​
​​​ ​We bring​ ​​
​​​ ​Our ocean’s finally full of life​ ​​
​​​ ​Set every vital piece in motion​ ​​
​​​ ​Now we write​ ​​
​​​ ​In a desperate shout, our souls reach out​ ​​
​​​ ​With pen toward every page​ ​​
​​​ ​We ignite, come alive​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a starry night​ ​​
​​​ ​With a fire no doubts can take away​ ​​
​​​ ​Write a fairy tale​ ​​
​​​ ​Where “love prevails”​ ​​
​​​ ​Cliched, maybe, we move joyfully on​ ​​
​​​ ​By the light- your spark​ ​​
​​​ ​Hopeless days are just a part of being free​ ​​
​​​ ​We wrote it all by heart.​ ​​
​​​ ​And smile, side by side among the stars…​ ​​