[Music]
how do i r do it
today
G
gin
g
j I'm ready for Le
lean I'm ready for Leo
Le and then Path of Exile to came out
today did you see kiaha I was going to
play that but then I you know the the
queue isn't looking very good with over
a million and um just didn't seem very
likely that I was going to play anything
today so goodby everybody's invite came
at a good time yeah over a million it's
really bad the server is down too so
right
now yeah it's down and it's an hour in
and people in KY are not in but I didn't
expect anything else it's not running
the game is not
oh yeah the game is not up so there is
no
quue
okay so good luck gy later all right I
was like should I be logging in right
now to get through but if not even up
then n you can't can't even get in path
of X out we should we should
play yeah I'm I'm
I I would
yipp yippe and let's play When the
servers calm down
more yes all right yeah I was thinking
so too maybe like next
week yeah definitely want to be
safer are you girls showing your like
this the screen like the where the names
are yes
okay wow I'll even show them my DMs with
you what the 1
pm. I just opened my Steam and it's
redownloading all 80 gigs of Path of
Exile so I hope I lag in of
Legends
amazing amazing be
great this will be hello hello hello
come back okay
hello hello
what are we
airing what what what what happena wants
to steal my cats even though she has her
own now messed up no no M up mess up
de get yourself more then don't take
mine away Ste them steal them you should
have gotten to minimum anyway narissa I
could have told you that no
why know you just want to steal are you
a kleptomaniac are we ready to play some
Le can we can we an audio check can we
do yeah everyone introduce yourselves
[Music]
ohood amazing G moodin leag of
Legends Cecilia
spin League of
Legends don't think that what's the game
name Elizabeth oh League of
[Music]
Legends narissa Raven cross SP wind Le
of it sound like nerve nerva as if
you're nervous I am she
is uh Top Lane uh and and Heimerdinger
checking my ass out
W Legends
what what is he doing ready to find a
match thumbnail he's checking my ass out
I
am CeCe you ready aren't we matching am
I ready uh yeah so match
found so loud it is very
loud we I have to switch to window
anyway is do I choose a character here
yeah I can choose VI
exciting yeah yeah whoever you
want okay H
H I'm going to start
off with uh uh uh uh rats rats rats we
the rats rats rats top yeah don't
question it we are the rats rats rats
rats rats ooh we said choosing sarapen I
see I see I'm your support wait I'm I
didn't pick
yet uh you got to click lock in I think
you have already locked in haven't you
oh it says
you're
uh uh uh select your runes oh
God I have no runes okay there we go get
the
ruins okay H I think
I think it's good now okay okay sorry
guys I'm I'm struggling with uh audio
balancing my biggest
weakness it's okay okay window
switch oh my God I love your AR
skin wow hot KDA K thank you
KD down down down down down down down
down
[Music]
down down should I buy this world
atlas good luck welcome do you girls not
buy items yeah I buy it starting pack
yeah buy the little red potion K I think
what what what sorry what buy the little
red potion I think that's a nice
starting item oh okay why is the camera
so weird
so oh you click the camera at the click
the camera at the bottom and it will
follow you oh thank you you hit Y and
it'll follow and unfollow you you'll
have to answer a lot of beginner
questions it's okay ask as much you want
while Senpai um thank
you so well in the shop W West Senpai it
does give you suggestions so I mean I
buy the little starter that it pops up
with it the at the the start when you
open it initially okay I did that
Gigi and narissa are the peeps like that
know it inside out yeah careful with the
tower who you say that and kill
everyone and and and and kill the
minions and and don't don't die I don't
have a a distance attack more arranged
attack I like the way you said minions
you see minions oh wa let me change my
thing I'm gonna make fet out of
them oh God thank goodbye you goodbye oh
god oh goodbye and I click and then oh
and click and click click the things and
press the buttons yes yes yes I'm here
for you my queen I have fed the Enemy No
it's okay don't do that they're Bots oh
what what would be oh what would be do
B is to go back to base to go home like
teleportation yeah yeah
oh it has a channel time and people can
cancel it by hitting
you
oh
uhoh am
IA your your your skin keeps making me
think I've accidentally got dmca music
on or something no I'm I'm sorry like
I'm always like did I leave a tab on no
you're listening to L of
Legends L of
Legends the most with in the game is
like the camera to just like have to
hold it down and I keep
forgetting I die snake hates me like
space
oh you don't have to if you don't want
to you can press y to keep it
fixed really yeah
oh let's go let's go oh shop oopsie uhoh
I'm dead it's
okay press y to lock H oh
interesting going she was waiting for me
even even
now here I'll come
Thank You Are You The Bard yes I pressed
the wrong button please avenge me that
snake lady has been bullying
me thank you that was a
Gooding why did the they have a
jungler is that a jungle character okay
they have a
jungler why you leave her I thought she
was doing fine
I guess not rat rat rat and you must
live
rat I am
rat hey turn get
her okay okay are you ready getting
better
CeCe see see right here right here yes
oh you want me to okay yes she is so
confused she has no I thank you yay
she's dead we did it transfer
buff chat what in in short words because
I can't look at the the text what does w
do in this
[Laughter]
case it's a passive it breaks armor okay
wait now I can
read the
same I don't have to do anything it's
just always working
what's always
working my passive yes
nice we got her okay yeah yeah yeah yeah
reset rats rats we are the rats we are
the rats we are the rat world of
atas uhoh was it not
good yeah I think the way Vice works is
you hit something three times and then
they take more damage and then her que
goes through to rain and walls but you
can charge it
up and she has one more skill forgot
what it does
something it like does AOE
stuffs Sor it's a bit much right now I
don't understand anything snake there's
a snake that's okay yeah why's a snake
here snake void grubs ouch grub grub I
don't understand void that mean we get
to eat oh the grubs she shot my
[Music]
booty too late
okay did I not sell it did I sell the
wrong
thing what' you sell I don't
know an item
that I didn't need I guess but uh
whatever
sold and I bought
okay skin why is
she what she up
[Music]
to to see if I can take GRS me alone
where's mid ler what how where are
they yeah where are they hold Q to fly
longer
the mid Lina is here it's a woman
Misfortune jungle bot takes void
grubs
ew why rubs this an objective I just
can't believe the bot in this people
objetives they're
annoying hey what did I steping uh-oh
n so how what how many times have you
girls played this as a collab already
first time yeah wow hey you in bottom
Lane mother trucker I remember you I'm
dead I'm dead don't die don't die help
me don't help me Liz kill them li no no
wait come back don't do it oh the deer
is here the deer is here oh dear oh dear
oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
dear thank you she's being really mean
yeah to fly
longer oh oh you got this this that is a
deer is
it was a little
deer it's okay I'm back Liz I'll support
you she's chared she's chared kill her
I'm a run from
Power what get away from
me what oops I ran too late I uh oh I'm
sorry ow ow ow where are my minions
there minions they're dead that's messed
up power don't worry I'm here to take
run out of minions why would you do that
to me I'll
leave I'm coming back Nissa are kind of
crazy all the things they're
doing what is
this don't be afraid go my little
minions go minions go cute cute
cute oh no Cecilia is GRE
now how do I buy that
Pur
just no whatever it's time probably oh
there's another one I didn't even see
that one uhoh watch out if you see that
white thing around her it means the next
spell she hits you with you'll get
stunned oh
okay I see I see level eight two go
blood flame go blood
flame uh she's a
queen you fool
walked into a tower what an idiot true
what an
idiot
fool uhoh is there like did you set
these Bots to a high difficulty or so
they're
normal could they be easier
yes I'm a bad
matchup no you're okay
so
there is it
normal it's normal why is the horse on
our side horse kill the horse oh she's
running away what is that uh she's like
um oh the the dragon I still don't know
I'm going to
die she just explained like a million I
still don't understand explain what what
the what the
um the is Drake what was that um gives
us gold and gives us some passive stuff
so it's a good objective to get wow it's
an enemy we have to kill or yeah it's a
jungle mob don't worry usually in like
actual games people fight around this
and then you have to be aware but we're
just playing bot doesn't matter too much
I I got this
you sound like you totally got this i
got this she's got I'm going go top a
little
bit you going to be good down here
M did I cannot tell the one can't tell
these games it's winning or not evil
jungler just took my my my
Raptors your Raptors yeah I can't
believe that b counter jungle
you I just can't believe it it's weird
it's weird right yeah it's so strange
that that bot will counter jungle
you so should I CH choose someone that's
far away chat
probably yes run after me you
fool go get out of there
nice thank you all
before ma'am get out of here what the
freak are you doing in here a little
girl in the forest careful
careful get a B I'm
running oh that completely missed that
was nowhere near her where did she go
wait where is she KAIT yeah maybe I want
r
o Caitlyn is the BL one I think one G is
not
little- I said blue no blue yeah blue
blue blue blue did you watch Arcane did
everybody watch Arcane no the second
season yet but I've seen the first
one I watch both finished my Twitter
feed has seen all of the second season
of a Kane I loved it although the second
season was a bit rushed yeah a lot of
things that they were she's trying she's
trying down mhm nice thank you copia is
going back so you should be able to get
the tower pretty much undisturbed mhm
okay another one charm she's Charmed
she's Charmed oops she did not run why I
wanted her to run ow ow good
job I'm turning I'm
[Music]
turning ow let me K you she stunned she
stunned ow
yeah andk gosh damn you're having a
party there are you a
DJ yeah it's a it's a it's a
party a the snake is back that's okay
snake oh careful back up a little
bit I wanted to use my Alti
yeah did I use it oh my God leave me
alone all right let's yes come here
mother trucker did you want to come here
there two if they stay we can kill them
okay okay okay let's just kill
her watch out she knows how to
combo oops that's that's a minion
oh you
here careful careful she Charmed she's
Charmed she
careful I'm dead wow kill her kill her
kill her G
yay I'll kill her for you thank you good
job I shouldn't have gone in there I
didn't see the second
enemy RS R how do I do the she's
jungling again Annie's G back to Jungle
ah no she no okay I've got it back good
luck
Kiara I get
this
no Ari has nine tails huh is she related
to Nar back off buddy no she's a gho
well she is a niled fox so yeah the
question oh ghole like the Korean yeah
oh no regret she says uhoh no no no no
no thank
you yay we got her come back come back
come
nice
loser you're getting toxic you're
learning the ways of League of Legends
yes it's true I'm I shouldn't I
shouldn't I mean no you got this enemy
bot you you go come here Lilia come here
wonderful
bot let's go out of
range I don't need I'm going to try a
different character guess I get
that all right
oops what boots no which boots
there's so many boots which boots should
I
buy I'm sorry I didn't have my heal up
get the
mer I can't afford I need cheap boots
basic boots yay minion you are Gucci I
was being
pery oh there's three why are there's
three people in mid that's not this is
not fair guys this is not fair obsessed
with you yeah they they just you just
are very intimidating
[Music]
watch your
step on my way oh on my way mid never
mind everyone left you yeah I she one
died
league league of
leged okay
I really like um like I don't know if
this is like the character always does
it or if it's just the skin but when she
teleports home she like creates uh oh
that's the how does this work yeah it's
really
cool she creates an invisible stairs and
then she sits on the throne that's so
Throne of legal
leggings Throne of legal
leggings LS
of my favorite top Champion was always
Riven
she's voiced by Christina V
yeah I can't F her suffering sounds
great got this o I pressed the wrong
button dang it oh what's that what's
that what the infernal blazes what does
it mean they took the dragon so now
there's things that'll pop up on this
map oh
okay nice nice nice job
yay God I'm zoning
out like mentally or in the game in oh
my brain I wish I could zone out but I
can't even Zone
in just chilling playing league with the
ladies we
vibing you got this you got this you got
this ah yes yes aome C look at you oh
God so
good thanks to
Nissa she had it's all because of
narissa I'm going to die no you're
not I I'm I'm going to back got this no
you're not you got this you're so
strong oh my god let's push the tower
yeah
yeah get the tower we
winning I guess I'll push a tower too
she's behind
you
teamy don't worry oh oh oh you're you're
going crazy you're going crazy you crazy
you're crazy you're crazy you're crazy
and and because of that yes in a good
way and we have a friend and I'm going
to bring you a friend and then oh don't
worry where am I going why am I running
this way that's a cute friend he's also
crazy oh no oh no well I sacrificed
myself for a good purpose yeah yeah yeah
yeah I'm going to go crazy again my
first
[Music]
successful I dived
wow without my diving license can't
believe it hey you're doing really good
no I'm not don't
lie you got this you got
this sure first time is V this is great
I sucked as by when I first played by
oh V looks
difficult let's
go okay can I one shot these now
no
no V is really hard yeah she's really
really difficult I thought she was GNA
people were saying she's like one of the
easier ones no they lied to you li she's
a pretty simple jungler
[Music]
yeah yay a tower is
destroyed unfortunate oh speed for a
moment
wow I'm here no no I missed it's okay I
shouldn't let's scatter her let's
scatter her you got this yeah get the
kill get the
kill nice so good look at
you
sure you you doing
it
[Music]
work oh you got this you got this you're
crazy you're crazy she sleeping you oh
oh no oh
no I was trying to figure how to make my
how to make my LT work but I think I
have to stand still to use it or I don't
think you have to stand still I was
pressing it the whole time you have to
press and then click
again on the person you want to use it
on or if you press um in the settings oh
and um there's like these little arrows
that you can if you just hover over a
person you can use them instead of
having to click on
them
okay hey if if someone can help me just
get the inhibitor
bottom we'll have mega creeps and we can
abandon
Lane I Le thank you
hello oh is it thank
you everything seems to be right click
in this game is it left
click it's it's left click
actually don't remember I just do it by
muscle memory I have no
clue
[Music]
Yayo uh-oh huh
okay let's try again
[Music]
no w w w w w w
let's go mid every time
I'm but it worked this
time oh
the okay it's fine no it's just
me how dare you kill narissa how dare
mother away from
us nice Li how do I
breath here uh you're
dead Okay what are we doing
team um what do I buy when I'm out of
stuff on the list what do you mean
whatever whatever makes you happy I
always like to go for a rabadon's death
cat a a hat rabadon's death C
okay if your ability power yeah mid
I
forgot oh recommend there's a recommend
list
okay
you don't don't um no I ran out of the
things on that one list that you sent me
like the three main items you lived by
this and then I
did that's
amazing
hello nice welcome I thought the deare
was going to kill me she's charm she's
charm no
okay get her too get her too get her get
her get her she's so
fast don't worry we're here get her get
her awesome nice nice nice nice get the
tower
okay
that get the inh
him what is that called what did you
call it inhib it's an inhibitor okay
you my flee now
what here oh behind behind two behind us
ah oh oh I'm
dead no you're not thank
you kill
her so Kara if you attack
uh if you attack them over
when when there's not Creeps in front of
you or if you attack someone over a
tower like the the tower will start
attacking you so if you're in the tow
vicinity don't attack one of the enemy
Champions
okay and if there's no creep don't don't
go up by the
tower no creep yeah what's the creep the
little gu fighting for you oh minions
yeah okay
[Music]
live live live it's okay our are going
to
end it's
fine okay I'll end the game don't
worry
woo
won yay easy easiest game of our lives
so easy
easy easyest game easy easy winners
we're winning we are winner winner
winner winner dinner
easy
yay first win of the day amazing our
first win of our
lives so easy so
easy do you guys want to do intro Bots
or let's do real people oh actually Ki
should pick what pick what do you want
to or you want to do bots are the real
people going to be easier than the
Bots
just also there might be a chance that
if we go with real people we still get
bots like I'll be right back you guys
talk about what you want and then tell
me when I get back crazy
Bots I mean I I I don't mind either way
I like playing against real people I'm
not sure if we can play against real
people yet since Ki is on a new account
we might have to do a few
more before but we can see if we can go
into Quick
Play
yeah maybe we should do bots first and
then uh well right now we did M medium
Bots and we won uh so either we should
do maybe we should do hard Bots to see
if we can keep up against hard Bots
before real people mhm
mhm maybe maybe can I do Caitlyn and Top
Lane you can play yeah whoever
wherever yeah okay be whoever you want
to be just have just yeah just mix it up
okay I want to try her Caitlyn KAIT
Kaitlyn's fun that's the blue
one Kaitlyn and VI perfect
match
yeah all these discounted skins
purchase purchase I'm
back welcome back thank you okay what
did we decide on what are we up
to and Bots okay Bots and do you just
want to do beginner Bots I'm not sure
what was the
conclusion we'll do
oh I feel like we can handle the same
level of bots you did really well yeah
we didner Bots we were playing beginner
Bots oh we W playing beginner Bots oh
we'll continue doing middle Bots okay
okay okay I'll intermediate I'll do
whatever continue are we all ready
mhm we're W on okay I'm pressing buttons
okay let's play you're already perfect
at the game except I don't like how that
is Kaitlyn let's go lock in our
relationship yeah let I try she's like a
narissa but with a gun what if we all
made a star Guardian team who I that do
I need to buy a skin for that I have
star Guardian there's star Guardian
Ari how much
cost like I think star Guardian skin
would be around
$15 oh 15 15
15 I get to use
my if I want to invest into this game by
giving it money I will decide after this
stream okay that is
fair I do want to look pretty in a star
Guardian skin why are you Sona wait
let's talk real quick what's What's
Happening Here for
funsies okay we'll win yeah is it a
problema or both supports is the only
one you can build
AP go carry yeah you can be anyone
anything okay
so anything you want
okay what do we
have are we already
running yeah can we do the thing G where
we like kill them in the in the in the
bushes yeah we can we'll have to go over
here I'm so fast okay I'm fast as fudge
boy yeah I'm
speeding let's
go
hi I like like your hat thank you I like
your ball
orb oh no not the snake again why do we
get same characters everyone here they
killed my ward no messed up we can try
killing them still I'm normally rata
just she's not even
running kill her kill her is it a her I
can't tell yes yes get her get her she's
almost dead kill her get her get her get
her
First Blood get him oh yeah uhoh I'm
dead I'm dead no no no help me help me
help me help me yay thank
you nice too okay
y baby Tower isn't it I'll take this
this is mine
now the minions are here you guys can
[Music]
go goodbye
you're welcome thank you it was all it
was all us yes
yes oh we killed them through that wall
Sona can't believe you're here with
us yay
IIA okay I am running for I am low in
health where are you running yeah you
better what do you mean you
better you sound like you're directly
out of the game like I wasn't sure if
that was a game Voice or
not she should voice all the characters
let's mute the game and just have how do
it yeah can you make the noises Bard
makes I don't know what you make
my he sounds like
windsh her scream when she dies Yoo
[Music]
crazy
anyway oh
beautiful pushing her
[Laughter]
oh always missed the last hit on this
stupid minions no you're so
[Music]
good not bad though not bad I don't know
how to ad carry seraphine you don't have
to ad carry just a
carry I don't know what that means oh
just just build like normal AP items I
don't know how to AP Carrie your
abdons RAB I just get my rabadons yeah
you can build your R why she running
away where is she
going she's a coward she's a coward kill
her she's Charmed she's Charmed be to
heal as normal okay what she
doing I'm out of
Mana if we can just keep getting them to
back even it's not too bad because then
they they don't get to level I need
healing thank
you no Mana no Mana I'm out of Mana
can't do anything she's so low but I
can't do it I'm out of man no
Mana guess I shouldn't have used all the
Mana on the minions
[Music]
minions seriously
what the oh you can hide in the bushes
too like in the in the Pokmon game too
like you disappear when you're in the
bushes what's happening here you can
become stealth what's going on an
assassin the night
dragon dragon dragon
is Dragon where Dragon
where where are you draging us
is happening
here are we still on beginner Bots [\h__\h]
yeah they're very strange
oopsie she keeps like zooming behind me
it's so
frustrating what if I what if I what if
I what have you want what have you want
what have you want nothing nothing
nothing nothing nothing nothing
what do you what what you what
though rest in
peace ma'am stop it ma'am stop it ma'am
stop upgrade let us kill
you good
kill what so if I don't get the kill if
the tala gets the kill I don't get any
like experience work on leveling
oh you're only level never mind I'll
stay you
back out of
here
oh how does she know I'm
here I don't know oh no secret
Ward yeah I'm just trying to hit this
how does she have the knowledge that I'm
here these Bots are cheating nice of
course of course they are they're
cheating are always
Cheating Who they're stream sniping I
heal I heal I heal I heal
yay how could they stream snipe that's
so rude I know it's so cringe of these
BX to stream
[Music]
snip minions minions minions minions bye
minions
I heal and then I go back into the
bushes thank you thank
you thank you for the assist
NE nus n should I go back for it
really I'm I mean Nissa I'm fighting
your mirror match miror match killer
it's a dou
ganger a double ganger yeah do that
nah nice one thanks you're the best
you're the best
music
[Music]
oo what why are they getting
these how do the Bots know to get
this it's
over no it's not over it's over I died
reset over there somebody in the bushes
BF sword what sorry BF big [\h__\h] sword
I didn't know what is is that what I got
oh I did get the BF sword nothing wrong
with the BF sword
mhm best friend sword oh okay okay
it's takes a moment to channel and line
up the perfect shot then
fires oh
no oh no Okay can intercept
it all
right no no she's running away I ha her
that's not where I want to flash
oops
big big large
wall big very large wall
oops I don't like
AEL no she keeps like she keeps like I'm
about to charm her then she teleports
behind me and she goes nothing personal
appreciate
that yay I got her
yay Oh My Stream died my bad how does
that happen because I'm I'm connected to
League internet so what your stream died
y yeah oh my God that's really weird
what your stream died yeah rest in peace
OBS issue it's okay it's back it's back
but yay who she welcome back from the
dead ow ow ow ow
rooted back sorry woo well you missed me
killing 20 enemies yeah all of them that
happened all of them
killed every single one of
them don't kill me this is
mine whoopsie I forgot if you hit
someone it was
okay he's confused he lacks critical
knowledge
oh God what in fool outplayed her
yeah I went into Caitlyn I sent Caitlyn
back into her closet she was invisible
oh come on you what come
on you heard her yeah you heard
me you mother trer let me kill you let
me kill you I don't think we should do
that no I got her oh God
let's go
minions oh my god let's eat more Snake
flesh snake for dinner snake
sausage snake sausage I already ate six
sausages
today six yeah pretty impressive uhoh
impressive impressive display I
impressive display of it's very unlike
of Caitlyn oops I should have done the
uhoh what's
this woven into everything I he
back
okay we have a Like A League of Legends
voice pack from Elizabeth yeah we need
one oh oh God she's going into the
bushes you're not going to escape me ha
imagine running away from a Healer
imagine running have to be ignite what
come back how close do I have to before
ignite I feel like often I press it and
nothing happen come here come here come
here come here over it you can see the
range no there's another one
FR and another one you'll be fine you're
son another one okay okay okay I need to
go oh no we
running not it's one
maybe
not so many unactivated traps so
sad what do I do okay don't die the way
that goast me on a hover blood okay
okay oh God how low are you very oh my
God I at 26 HP I died to saraph
oh she aled me she how could she do this
messed up the seraphine though I know
how could she I have a
skin yes get hit by the turret yes
fool yay these Bots are awesome I like
yeah I like when they run into the
turrets because it's like I would do
that but mother tra you would do
that yeah
but I haven't today oh yeah I remember
last I kept getting confused which one
which which which Towers were ours so I
kept running into
Towers I think I think we Riot gave me
free RP so I did buy more sarine skins I
want stuff too right we can we can
ask there's two of them why are there
two what am I going to do okay one run
away no she's back next
time how did I not hit her Riot give me
free stuff or I'm a I'm going to
Riot I'm going to
Riot yeah before we start
rioting just kidding just kidding I'm
sorry Riot I have so much respect for
you sorry Mr Riot sorry we already are
RI get away from
me good trade it's good if I if I die
and I say good trade is that like does
it nullify any negativity I created yeah
yeah cre space good trade good trade
good trade creates space for my skill TR
TR good trade good trade TR good trade
good trade
oh nice go team finally nice turret is
gone we can now move on with our lives
yeah we move on next turret and then the
next
turret Target the
Aurelia level 10 why would you come here
Alia I'm trying to get this Rift
Herald yes my Rift I work so hard
on I'm a little bit too happy when I uh
kill a champion as you should be that's
good that's your life blood
uh oh forgot over here Al walk over here
I'm so
low your little bot brain wants me so
bad I'm so
low o walk over here just walk over
here delicious yeah come get me
come on here I keep pressing D and
nothing happens so annoying I don't get
it may me look
closer you also have it quick
casted oh
yes walk up
here like I'll her I'll her I'll her
I'll charm her oops I pressed the wrong
button she's Charmed she's Charmed yay
that will show her for trying to take my
Rift
heral Rift heral wonder if I can get it
now it's okay it's okay my 3,000 gold
it's
okay
uh-oh I do this one got to get a
needlessly large
Rod needlessly large yeah need so
needlessly large huh that's why I need
it h okay cute necessary necessarily
large
Rod yeah uhoh uhoh I slowed okay I'm
fine live live 11 I'm live I live
totally ignored me no
respect
oh no yes come here sarap yes you want
me you want to eat oh she ran away yes
walk over here you want us yes come on
over
damn okay Retreat tactical Retreat
tactical
retreating leaving my minions
behind for a better time and I'm going
to buy boots boots boots
boots boots
maybe can I buy a potion
tooy here we
go killing oh
nice get get you get her you get her I'm
letting you get yay crazy you guys are
really
pushing right into their base we to get
the inhibitor
shall we go and help
M
sure inhibitor I thought you said that
an inhibitor does okay an inhibitor an
inhibitor an inhib has help destroy an
inhibitor goodbye ohud don't die dude
stop following me dude dude
St D them oh yeah I keep forgetting
about my old oops see oh hi hi n hi I'm
here to
help
hi hi everyone ow I'm standing in it how
am I standing in it help help thank you
oh o what's everyone screaming
about okay okay okay okay wow she just
jumped on she's charm she's Charmed kill
her crazy
yay yay yay
yipp you're on a rampage kiaha you're
crazy
crazy that's fine I'll avenge you it's
nice to have I won't let them get away
with
this Char uh oh uh oh uhoh uhoh okay oh
why did you run over
here yes yes you're crazy
feel this uhoh oops I didn't mean to do
that run away run away run
away no I'll avenge you
too I meant to go here but I clicked I
clicked on the oh my God let me out let
me out let me
out am I clicking I think the hardest
part is like the moving with the mouse
because like I you you you click because
you're trying to get away but your mouse
is completely in a different place than
you thought it was G and then you always
walk into wrong
areas
hi hi
no hi thanks for
the GG you got
this I don't think I do but like
scrolled over to you and I just see like
four enemies in front of you walk up why
if I had more if I had more Mana I could
have done it you can do it you got this
you can still do it nice nice nice
is
yeah POS music is because
we what music think so I hear positive
music maybe it's the star
Guardian it's so pretty
oh God
like come back over
here yeah don't be a coward Bots come on
yeah come on walk over here we're just
beginners just beginner bot now
we
healing get them okay now we're winning
[Applause]
healing
victory
victory e game of Our Lives so
easy I think we're ready for
intermediate Bots
you I need get water okay okay me too
actually sorry I'm like since I'm sick
I'm drinking so much water that's good
drink more drink more water thirsty
girl I am so thirsty do I still not have
this skin oh I just need the
icon I was about to kill myself okay
I'll be right back don't do it
okay I'll be or B um yeah I'll be or B M
you guys are still on my stream water
KDA
KDA KD it is around again what do it
mean k
a what does it
mean look
[Music]
with
doggy animals
oh so they saying it's killed def assist
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wow you got
that way faster than me and Cecilia did
really really I don't know if that's
really fast yeah yeah yeah I didn't
notice until Cecilia brought up she was
like oh kill death like assist and I was
like why is this why is this yellow are
they telling me I did bad for what my
character could do potentially
or is it just because that's me what's
yellow my damage dealt to Champions is
it just because it's me okay yeah yeah
yeah I thought they were dissing
me can you get skins with the blue stuff
or not um there's the they sometimes
bring back like a blue Essence store but
it's usually a lot of blue Essence it
was here recently h H I don't know where
it went I don't know if it's still here
what are these mystery boxes oh it's
here oh the mystery which
one what one what you need I want can
you explain them to me like these loot
Loot Crate Box thingies are the on in
your
inventory inventory is it in your
inventory ones in my inventory sometimes
you get these like chest that you can
use and it give you character shards or
skin shards or um Wards and stuff but
you have to unlock it
with this other currency that you get
from breaking down what you get from
boxes
a I maybe
see so none of these loot boxes have
skins the loot boxes have skins if you
buy a loot box you can get a
skin M there will gold too right no well
there's these
blue b City mystery mini icon
icons how are we doing
gers good good yeah are we ready do we
want to up the bot
difficulty sure by one maybe there's
only one more to go let's go nice okay
let's SE we got this we got this we got
it let's search let's search for Bots
that want to play against us yeah I hope
we find I seeking
BS let's change the
world okay KDA skin time yay woo for me
I mean you're flexing so
hard bro I had to play to unlock this
I'm not
flexing still a flex no I had to play so
much to unlock lock her we we'll get you
a pretty skin too K don't worry next
time I know who pretty I don't know who
this guy is but he reminds me of like
someone from Myspace so I'm going to try
he looks beautifully sad yeah yeah he
looks like a MySpace guy why oh sorry I
don't
know pool party Kaitlyn p p po party
party pool party po pool party I want
pool party
you
sure yay no snake this time oh there's a
cow cute oh there a CO
guy fair fair quart Lux oh it's Lux oh
no I hate l oh it's over oh yeah I feel
like I heard some bad things about Lux
but did not understand the context what
do you mean she's evil she's she's pure
evil do you
um her bot AI is really good because
she's really good at aiming skill shots
because
robot
yeah can we kill them all in the bushes
again yeah over here P it thank
you oh this guy has a big paintbrush
let's
go okay I'll wait for everyone to get
here o Nissa you look so cute thank you
we matched now ready we're both sparkly
yeah I'm ready I'm ready to press the
one button I have I just going to look
up this guy
uh I'm
in he got got why did he
flash don't
flash oh you thank you for the heal yeah
you're welcome nice thank you everyone
goodbye
goodbye not here I'll just go back to my
uhoh oh no look Lux is in the middle
it's over she's in the middle she's
always there she's a LX and she's in the
middle I hate her she's Lux and she's
it's okay I'm not the same person I was
two weeks ago Lux in the I will not lose
to this spot this time yeah you are not
the same person what did I do he's like
the guy
from uh from
Naruto which one
saigh his name s I love you drew that's
right was he he drew stuff yes Artist
Artist Artist yeah how does he see me in
the bushes if you hit him and then the
minions aggro you they'll reveal your
location in the bush oh yeah so if
you're aggroed by something it'll show
yourself
no he's so
cool
yeah yeah cannot outrun your crimes is
what I want to say to Walter
White are you planning on watching saw
after yeah
totally my I'm so excited it's good I'm
like halfway through the last season of
Breaking Bad you're so good I think I'm
going to finish it tonight maybe
oo also I saw I saw I was in a museum
yesterday and um I saw a painting that
really looked like Walter White I took a
picture of it I need to show it to you
guys later to anybody who understands
what he looks like in the first place it
looks so much like him bald and and
glasses and everything
and depressed fa not really depressed
flash push me in he pushed me in just
like his face just says she's got issues
wow I agree he kicked me into the the
thing he's
rude
wow I'm a cute mypace boy that
draws yeah come
on I never us my space yeah even though
it was popular when I was
smaller uh-oh uhoh Fair my space was too
cool for me you run into our
Tower no but I I should have gone home
like ages ago and I kept thinking I
should use my Mana before going home and
then I
didn't oops wrong
button
oh a pot of
tea a ble water bottle of
water bottle of water bottle of water
bottle of water here I'm ready for
you are you back oh really yeah I'm here
I'm here she's St charm her charm she's
Charmed she's charm she's all right I'm
on her I'm on her I'm on top of her I'm
on top of her
okay thanks
GG I feel like when it's two versus one
it becomes a little bit unfair why come
here little cow what what do you do when
you're
not ideally in the game you're not you
have like a better understanding or like
you you know where the jungler is and
you know when to not overextend so she
wouldn't have been in that position in
the first place if she
was watching a map or she wor it when
I'm in the middle should I and you are
close to the middle should I tell you
um when I'm about to engage it's up to
the jungler because it's like um they
usually evalu the kill potential if you
like if they went mid would you guys be
able to get a kill mhm or if just's like
other objectives cuz even though you
might engage they'll be like oh it's not
worth it cuz I have to go to this other
place right now and it would waste too
much time here I wanted
to in a game though but since this a
black game I can just come
in I wonder what skins he
[Music]
has oh you're so Mana poor good thing
she's not level six
yet oh I'm dead nope I got her don't
worry don't wor wor okay I'm going home
I'm going home go home go
home go home yes go home
uh zigs is missing any minute now oh
there we
go can you believe that
airplane and the night sky are like
shooting stars I can't believe
it nice nice an airplane in back good J
oh Li you sound very roboty right
now
guys you intentional nice I'm almost
there I'm almost
must is it the ping okay charm charm
charm yeah yeah
aome I'll fix it in a moment
okay am I Wally am I
[Applause]
Wally oh wait I need really
good
him good yeah you just sound really good
is there no Mana
potions in the shop no oh in the shop I
actually don't
know there's like a refillable potion
but
people don't usually get it or it
depends on what Champion you're
playing I can't buy it oh nice why is it
locked they used to be but removed yeah
cookies give Mana
uhhuh I love
cookies have you girls had some
Christmas cookies yet oh it's evil I
thought it was no not yet been to some
Christmas markets yet not yet no I did
in a voice pack not yeah yeah right it's
so it's all just a lie I did in a voice
pack in the last 3 days I went to like
six Christmas markets that's awesome wow
speed running Christmas markets I
totally did repetitive Christmas mark
and it made it even more obvious like I
never noticed how like all the shops are
so repetitive in the Christmas markets
but it's still nice it's still nice it's
really nice what's your favorite
Christmas Market uh snack this will
decide
everything y
[Music]
okay Germans are talking about German
[Laughter]
things Yumm
yeah
yummy those are like candied almonds
they're like they're like um roasted
candied almonds caramelized roasted yeah
they're really good they bought they
sell them at the Christmas markets I
Leta eat them and she was so fascinated
she was like oh my God this is the [\h__\h]
in a good way it's really good it's like
just the right amount of super sweet you
know mhm and crunchy and crunchy yeah
uhoh
he pushed me away thank
goodness I'm going to heal up o y go
ahead uh level eight I'm strut
away a he's
[Applause]
painting he's
painting he's a
painter he's a
[Music]
painter don't attack me do I still sound
like a robot you Ed
no oh it fixed itself cool nice you
didn't even have to do anything I didn't
even touch
it Elizabeth Rose blood
flame
oh did I flash and my fire switch oh
that's why I keep flashing why would
they why would the game do that to me
that's M up why would they yeah why
would they do that to you I had it I had
it rebound and it it reset itself
oh my God Darius is not interested in me
anymore he realized I am uh not
interested in him
either good good go somewhere else
Darius stay
away he go what oh you channeled so fast
oh I lost gu included him whoops
uhoh an oh my
God okay there
damn my aim is so bad man come
back stay
here I know F should be flash flash okay
I got a B be
careful flash
flash can't give up I can't give up for
the Lash no for Flash for the Lash
no oh why they all let's go for pilt
over pilt
over
y oh my God everyone's crunchy
uh-oh everyone
crunchy how about
now oh I got boots I fix it
[Music]
good now okay okay see if I can get this
guy with this this time f f launches a
vision ofair that sticks to an enemy
Champion for 3 seconds
oh top like a boss I've had this real
weird issue recently it happened like
started a week ago where my audio just
becomes like really roboty but I can't
hear like it hears sounds normal in my
my ears audio jungle audio jungle you
came to the wrong neighborhood how you
jle you cow come here jle come here come
here you cow nice let's get this mid
turret yes this game is teaching me
restraint
wow he's so good he's scripting this SP
ising yeah kill him kill him kill him
kill him kill him kill him so fast you
got him y he died from me ni y I'm going
home oh should I stay with you I don't
know no I'm afraid of this
L I should have gone home G maybe should
have got home I should have gone home I
never bought this huh oops just run
alls let's go Tower
two have gone
home I'm here no there is let's get the
rumble Rumble come
what no no no
no please darus please have mercy let me
go let me go
let me go little hi hi hinger that's
zigs Dragon SP he does look like Hing
her though I F the same when I was
watching the show I was like is this
character going to turn into digs or
what no no they they're their own people
oh
un
y are they
related no they're just little they just
the same they're just are they y yeah
yort oh that's what I meant are they the
same species oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah his crazy
[Laughter]
cousin there's another guy down here
Rumble it's who is ready to Rum whatever
Dom wow you're Dom back
up get let's finally get someone with
this let's go ah yay
finally my y I'm like no
no oh whoops get out
of my death they're cheating up there
celebrating your death yeah
yay wa dies let's go it's okay cuz she's
a phoenix she'll be back yeah he'll be
back
BRB
see I just wanted to go shopping anyway
get
her I could no you're not we'll get her
we'll get her flash for her oh I don't
do enough damage
okay we got him we got him we got him we
got him we got him oh he flashed oh my
God so annoying come back come back oh
God come back okay we got him we got him
we got
him
yay wow shut down shut down you know we
were ambitious yeah I mean we have three
people against us yeah yeah yeah yeah we
did really well yeah what is that
it's no issue oops we still
beautiful I'm beautiful my space boy so
she came back and then killed you that's
rude kind of mean yeah very that was
like this giant arrow on the map and I
was like what could that be but it was
on top of an enemy so I thought the
enemy was doing something but it was her
teleporting I understand now Lee now I
know what it looks like you get it you
get it what I get it now I get it now
does your guy have a Santa skin I feel
like he suit one I don't think he has a
Santa skin this is his winter one right
now M he would look really cool as Santa
yeah he'd be really
cute please have
mercy I'm on my way I'm on my way okay
okay okay don't let almost there Top
Lane is so
depressing you got
be
careful me ieng you she knows
it I presson again yes yes crazy yes I
did well she's dead so
that's it's on the wrong butt no it's
not my fault you did
it you're
crazy
yo snippity snipe no no let me kill you
please let me kill you give me that
satisfaction whoops you scared
me
please kill
the you
coward
no oh
no I'm weak again who is this Rumble
where did he come from he the jungle can
you come kill this
Rumble Rumble can you come control your
jungle he's just chilling he lost his
jungle he has no idea what's going on
you know oh oh is that a
Teleport that is a Teleport okay I I see
it now I see it now
no uhoh uhoh there he is there he is
please let me go should have done
anything when there two it's a lesson I
have to learn when there's more than one
enemy full health I should not tickle
them cuz they me and kill me pickle them
you out play
them no I died no no next timeck they me
and use her don't know okay okay I see
yeah yeah see what of you what if youall
play them for next time oh that's a good
Destin actually maybe I didn't think of
it about it that way okay okay thanks
teacher
darus get away from
me we got them yeah we got
this get away from Oh wait we're winning
are we I can't
tell there just one okay I can take on
one
[Music]
y took me long
enough he's too
strong it's
over she's a singer she's a
singer she's working there singer she's
a
singer listen topress up now on Spotify
thank you Chase working L listen to
Blackbird out now on Spotify Co out now
on
Spotify I'm on a roll look at you Kiara
you're slaying crazy all alone all alone
baby all
alone
no all alone it's okay it's like it's
it's a character development for your my
character about it it's like the Ang
probably what's that why is that a red
circle around me what does that mean oh
no no no it's a buff it's a buff you
have a bu en okay okay okay it's good
good okay okay yeah good good good good
good okay okay you got red buff from
Jungle
good if you have a blue I'll protect you
I'll protect you thank you ow
oh they're all up here oh there's so
many of them leave leave uh
uhoh wa I was about to dodge that but
that came fast it just happened she just
got the both of us I'm glad we died
together yeah at least we're here
together she dang it
uhoh oo thank you oh there's three of
them um get okay okay he's he's Charmed
he's not charm never mind I
lied what else I flashed again damn it
you're
okay every
time oh the music cute you character
makes cute music thank
you she's a singer she's a singer she's
working
late uh oh there's two left left
destroy he's Charmed he's
Charmed nice he's dead he's dead kill
him kill him I'm trying a it's okay it's
okay I'm running oh I'm dead you're all
alone it's
okay
over ooh nice dominating
dominating
dominating um
yeah
yeah and this
one and this
one
yeah are
[Music]
crazy oh I'm going to
die that damn
LS damn it l annoying all her
fault she's tearing
H play in the cloud Drake nice honestly
when we played her against the ls the
first time I thought she would be like
super toxic character like you know like
no no the way her character is like her
characteristics and then I played her
she like yeah she's like super positive
peace in Love Somehow that makes it
worse I don't know why someone that's
like peace and love stuns you and then
like old in a line nothing
personal
yeah nothing personal at all yeah she
doesn't mean it he's just
joking I see I see come minions be my
wall go g go kill her kill it Rumble L
get LS oh there there there's like the
five of
them go CH
go wait no run run
are those the flowers from the show
no no those look at the co wheel I got
it I got it I got
it ooh I can just figure out how to
drive this
thing I'll hit there I'll hit it I'll
hit it this way what I'm driving I'm
driving here okay goodbye did you become
the thing yeah you can drive it
I didn't look like driving it seemed
like you possessed it no you're driving
[Music]
it what is
this only the spawn was closer that's
confusing
we can end yeah you guys can end right
now do
it the game we're
winning y we're so
good
y the party easy easy easy easy easy
easy
easy well your first time playing that
guy Liz how did you like him I love I
thought he was really
cool nice I'm going to see if he has
skins oh
yeah can you be part of pup
Stars skin
time I get more more gold all of a
sudden malfunction describes it
well I got more RP too yeah how do we
huh yeah yay we're R thank
you R thank you r i can get my mypace
boy skins I can buy more sarap
skins Myspace boy skin they also get
stuff I don't know how did they give me
stuff yeah we need to we need to submit
to them your username and stuff but I
got some stuff how did I know oh well
you did like you got some Arles oh wait
how how can I well wait I also got okay
it's time for a new skin what do I buy
thank you Le how
[Music]
do uh cuz they can probably see it on my
stream
oh oh it's here thank you Ryan I guess I
won't Riot then you you get away SC
free lucky
has a winter
skin I'm going to get it yay how much is
that like the the how much is 3,600 is
that a lot it's it's quite a bit you can
buy a skin where do I buy skin go go to
the right by the RP there's like coins
stacked up you click
there uh uhuh uhhuh and then you you buy
stuff there okay
o short ha I think he only has one skin
and it's winter I love winter oh oh we
Qui Champion I don't have Caitlyn yet
even though I'm playing her she's she's
probably free this week get her with
your your blue stuff my blue stuff yeah
the in-game in go buy her if you like
her
okay I do like her m
you know sarapen has a skin called
graceful Phoenix
ooh is it red orange
ory it's nice perf oops don't have a lot
of SK a littleit annoyed AR doesn't have
a single green type skin yeah believe it
can believe it messed
up am I still in your party I can't tell
yeah uh probably
maybe I'm not in it right
now I'm buying things you're buying
things oh you're not in here I'll invite
you to the game
thanks pressed something wrong hi guys
okay money is gone Riot thank you thank
you Riot thank
you got I had a billion dollars but I I
spent it all
billion dollars wow very based
billion what is chroma what does that
mean it's different color variations so
if you go to chroma and you look up the
champion you like they might have
different variation like color
variations for the Skins you already
have oh so it's like in skins chroma oh
chroma yeah oh Ari so for example yeah
if you go into chroma and go Ari me she
has green here
yeah then you can buy the chroma and
then you can use that
one instead you
[Music]
know oh this is
green yeah she has literally an emerald
KDA skin that's nice yeah purchase it
byy bye bye bye byy now byy now wait I
have to pick I'm going to get the the
the oama it's time to go toed
time to go to bed it's time to go to bed
it's time to go to
bed so end the no what everybody saying
bye to go to bed
byebye to play League of
[Music]
Legends Jo summer so if I I should
always prioritize using the blue ones
right since those are in game
mhm yeah that was something I did wrong
when I first like got got characters and
stuff okay I got a green
one are we going to try real people now
or can we still not what do you want to
do what is this Gwen looks cool cissors
can we play
against sure I'm so ready I feel
extremely prepared for the
challeng I
believe nothing can stop me nothing can
stop I'm ready you uh I'm going to
change my thing Cara you need to select
uh Top
Lane Cosmetics winter he has multiple
apparently everyone wants me to tell you
about
aniva I've been seeing it in my chat too
I don't care I just invested in hot
outfits for for Caitlyn play Caitlyn
where do
I where do I select top L I don't know
uh right under your character icon C's
character icon there's like a little
square that you
can and then oh you click on the
character and then you okay got it okay
okay is it possible to change the skin
now no in cosmetics yes yes okay
okay hot cute hell yeah hell yeah how do
I change the color of my skin oh uh you
hit the little chroma button you can use
the blue stuff wo I got it I got it I
got it let me know when we're all ready
flash to F I
[Music]
did flash flash flash
buttoms blue stuff use the blue blue
stuff M the blue
stuff 99%
Purity flash
flash use the blue stuff female dog
you're ready W everyone ready I'm ready
I'm
ready I'll take yes Mr we're looking
we're going to play people we're going
to play people I'm so scared don't worri
they might be you you think I I I'm just
the like five years we're five years old
with how bad I'm playing no we're all
bading so good you're pushing top you're
getting it's okay because we're together
with you so you're not going to get
reported oh okay yeah that's what
matters it's okay even if they reported
me I have Riot on my side what can they
do a
lot it's
fine a party
Ka and lock no
locks no that might this seems like a
bot team you know oh okay okay that's
good yeah yeah I bet I bet they're I bet
they're
bot I'm a star Guardian look I'm green
and gold my or is gold the
[Music]
green I'll charm them with my swim green
with like beish hair
[Music]
oh do we do the bush thing doesn't work
I don't
know wait people or are they not real
people should I walk in if I walk in and
I see them maybe they are not real
people check this out everyone I'm about
to face check to see if they're real
people do it they might be
Bots that's
fine oops I hope they're Bots
who's pinging me yeah who's pinging us
what someone's oh the
robot oh who's that I even know oh no
are the is the robot intentional this is
robot
again how do you even do
that robot maybe it is intentional we
don't know no I don't think so Robo Liz
in the house Robo Liz my back there a
robot again yeah yes you're a
robot terminate oh go exterminate
exterminate oo it's red
now scared
exterminate forgot for a moment cuz I'm
nervous there's a
die come here
[Music]
exterminate can't tell if this is a bot
or not I've been
rooted you've been don't worry she's a
bot she's a bot maybe she will walk into
the thingy then that's good all right
all right you ready for this get her get
her get her ah okay she flashed I'm
leaving goodbye I'll take some of this
while I leave they're so nice take this
while I leave M goodbye no don't eat
them I'm going to
die believe
it oh oh nice First Blood oh you're back
thank
God
uhoh I Avenged you don't
worry nice good job
okay CeCe in in about
um in about 10 seconds I will come to
you 10 okay okay
yes no more no
less all right all right make her come
back make her come
back okay she will never never expect
this she will never expect this she's
not expecting this one what is that my
snowball goodbye nice thank you wait who
are
you
noo and oh sorry sorry you two people
and will yes and will okay okay oh no
oh no no I'm so scared I'm in back
scared you're beautiful
I am
retreating that's a jungle okay oh no
how do you know don't hurt me I am just
a Noo-noo and
will
noo oh Liz what are you doing by the
tower I'm
reading okay that's I'm reading uh some
bits to do with um this skin makes my
weapon like super super visible compared
to before it's crazy super visible yeah
it's it's nice it's kind of nice
actually Super
Chat super visible so
slow I am so
slow oh
God help minions
super
visible super
visible I'm going
home oh let's see what animation she has
here I'm going to run it down bot Lane
are you
ready have fun okay well I hope you're
ready for me to run it down bot
Lane woo oo take him
down come back well done
huz thank you thank you I did how did
you know she how did she know I want her
to come
back
goodbye Hi
Li hello I'll help you with this guy for
a moment thank you okay okay okay okay
okay
okay oh I love playing people or totally
people and not I love playing against
people yeah these people I love playing
against
them I get it oh I
believe oh she's
here ymer there two of them uhoh uhoh
uhoh
M why is there uh Hey High heal there go
is it yours oh cool oh she's nice oh no
my guy's not a Healer I just had that on
me okay I might have to retweet here
retweet Retreat
retweet retweet get oh I just ran to the
wall never mind rooted I know what oh no
oh no oh no I need to run run run run
run run run run run run run
okay we going going home we're going
home yeah I'm going
home I'm done this skin is like she
hearts and stuff it's kind of like an
astrolog kind of
cool poo is freaking out leave me alone
a little
Don I'm a some might be
outside today is my first time you'll be
fine you're doing nice don't worry yeah
you're doing great yeah is it easy to
stream snipe in this
game we're probably against bot right
now mm yeah but is it easy to stream
snipe no you look
likeus
ow oh Nissa you look like sa V thank you
I am a magical girl
higher
LS oh there's a guy there's a guy
here kill him no I'm not worried about
it if anything I would have welcomed it
getting stream sniped may maybe they
would be nicer to
me you're
like I'll ban you and they'll just kiss
my feet my beautiful bare
feet please stream snipe us oh God I
die I'm so sorry it's
okay it's okay I died too in solidarity
sh down
solidarity yeah I'm slowly but surely
overcoming greed that's good no you
should keep Being Greedy oh really yes
continue your greed okay okay continue
your greed be
greedy okay oh they're they're right
here why are they right here okay wow
I'm coming top oh you're welcome to come
as long as you don't steal my kill okay
I'll let you have it I'm going to set it
up so you can get him where's he going
why is he leaving okay okay
he's never going to expect this if he
just walks up okay okay okay snowball
get him get him get him get him really
I'm not ready get get him get him get
him I'm trying I'm
trying I took it oh it's okay it feels
like I did it oh okay we did that
together y there's like four of them
what three three just three oh that's
just
okay so you're telling me if there's two
people I should still attack them kill
them okay you got this
okay I'm
rooted oh there's someone else
teleporting in so three people should I
still yes you should kill them yes I
should still go okay okay okay don't be
a coward kill
them out of my way nocturn got a blue
buff to get an En yay I killed her I'm
running home green is
good who's pinging what did I say I
don't know I don't know it's not me
unless I it's not us it's not me I
didn't even know how to P what the heck
I don't know how to Ping either which
means maybe is us what's
ping I didn't I didn't click anywhere
there so uh anything else I should
buy ow come back H me under
Tower okay okay are you ready are you
ready go in I mean go okay he's charm
he's
charm he's charm he's Charmed he's charm
crazy he's
dead okay I'm going home I will also go
home I
suppose Focus un completing one
G doesn't work I was writing to my chat
because they were like poo box I'm like
he's a
parrot
actually well he's a type of par he is a
Kakao so like and parrots can like you
know mimic a lot of animals can mimic a
dog sound very impressive if dogs really
do sound like
that an nice hey I got kill
[Music]
nice
thanks oh
nine
yes I let out an alt and it did
absolutely nothing it was so bad hey the
thought is what counts yeah yeah my aim
is so [\h__\h]
man you spooked
him what
what is that what is that what is that
why are they all doing the apocalypse is
upon
us no turns thing ow why are they why
are they all
here is they Wen you and they what
they're
crazy oh my God BS are crazy I want to
take it I walk up is it dead is it
gone oh [\h__\h] oh reset okay I'll
leave the adventure
continu you got this it's two of
them
yummy no come
back where is she R where is she come
here no that didn't hit
her
ooh I can do this oh that doesn't go
over there y y Yum Yum Yum y
yum okay yum yum yum
yum I'm going home
okay going home uhoh will they hit
[Music]
me
yay uh
woo turret kill her kill her y the the
to killed her nice walk up to me walk up
to me okay you you don't need you don't
need you don't need to do that
Liz oh what's that oh we got a mountain
Drake
ow ow well I got
Dragon the CH plants bloom so it's worth
it I did the thing wrong
what does it
mean what does it mean what does it all
mean what she doing what
the what WAOW what was that he does a
little
dance run he was teleporting uh-huh into
the
minion sometimes that's just what you
have to
do uhoh
biscuits heal you oh these I didn't even
realize I had biscuits in my inventory
oh yeah
biscuits oh that's why you guys
ah I didn't realize I had any
[Laughter]
biscuits I thought you guys were cuz you
guys like cookies that's what I thought
cookies
cookie sometimes you just wait why did I
leave I can buy more stuff oh my
God
yay you got
her y yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum um if if okay so I I'm spending a
lot of time barely killing the the Bots
and then going home should I rather play
it safe so I don't go home and push the
lane
instead n n you should kill them yeah
kill them okay oh what is that that's
the nocturn
old are you dead no I'm
alive I came to help you oh oh no I
killed him he's di now don't worry okay
did what chat told
me
moments oh she's singing why she
singing okay okay I'm I'm roll I'm
rolling I'm rolling okay okay she's
Charmed she's
Charmed
okay
yay thanks
so my
Hero level 12 is this
one I'm just a
girl I don't know
the I'm going to go I don't know if I'll
survive a dive you're not just a girl
hello welcome
Lane hello please assist me get away
from
her oh oh
oh oh oh
wa what happened push power down you're
so crazy the
hell can you just
Mor I mean nothing kind of worked you
should morb more often almost dead she's
almost dead she's almost
dead is it the power of women that
compelled you to do this the power of
woman that really pushed me into doing
that that's so strong I also believe in
the power of s side it was very powerful
here okay I'll charm her she's Charmed
oh I'm inside it's okay we're fine it's
okay she's Charmed yeah kill kill you
got this I don't have any
heals it's okay you got her you got her
kill her kill
her no you got no it's okay it's okay
it's okay
uh keep chasing me sarapen come on what
are you doing
yeah nice try Lux you're aim is as bad
as mine all right I'm here for you I'm
here for you I'm rolling I'm rolling it
down I'm rolling it down go go go get
get
him R to the
wall oh nice nice you got it
nice y
double double kill
um now I buy this guy oh yeah oh yeah oh
not
wo windows I don't know what that means
I you wi you win them you know you
Windows
oh no minion don't kill me yeah you wi
you
Windows oh
God Windows window you windows and you
lose window that's okay sometimes you
have to lose in order to get a Windows
activation key does he have the same
skill as me oh I knew right behind
you he's trying he's trying he's going
to come out from come
out nice nice nice nice nice nice he's
low smoking he's low there's another one
coming from Top jungle I guess okay did
not in in fact come why not Chas oh here
he's there he's there oh more friendly
people oh
hi I'm
going behind yes I brought them over
sorry about that it's okay it's okay
Charmed
Nice kill kill kill kill kill
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
teleport into the
thingy oh finally
I want
kill
oo let's get this Tower let me kill
you y nice Tower oh forgot about
him you have your old
kiaha yes if you use it it's like a
sniping if I can get him low enough
maybe you can can kill him
get in
in I don't know why I I I I don't know I
I'm
sorry she just walked into
it but she's she's showing me her pretty
butt get her get her get
him goodbye
come back come back he's
dead come here saraph be Charmed Yum Yum
Yum oops I'm in there I've got I've got
to back walked into their
home you walked into their home and died
you know
yeah oopsie press
okay guys guys kill them all it's fine
planted my ass there worth yeah yeah
yeah worth worth worth
oo we're so good at this game yay not
bad not bad you're
slaying no right now I'm just running
because I died I have been slayed though
you're slay you were slaying so good
though
that is
questionable why am I here I don't know
where is
everybody mother trucker no we're on our
way there's two away away will I die to
this no nice I did a
thing I got rooted I did a thing H
guys's right behind you
don't die
Kiara an ambush a
stampede I
was we were here we
won we're
winners winner winners
win this was us huh does honor players
just never show yourself
or yeah you can't honor yourself it's
just the other this oh oh this is a
screen where you
choose why would you honor yourself ke
no no I thought this was showing the the
good players of the game already no no
no you get to pick oh I haven't seen
that window do I skip it by accident I
don't know
um I just want to go get the drink be
right back
okay we're doing it wow we're so good
yeah we're doing it we're doing a League
of Legends with the with the
professionals um quick say like some
terms that only professionals would
know I think I need to restart my League
of Legends oh what that is what a
professional would say
restart my League of Legends yeah I see
I see I'm going to yeah I'm going to I'm
going to restart League G I'm going to
Lane Swap and then I'll I'll midgap and
then I'll wave state and split push and
then and then I'll uhuh Tower tower
Tower to Tower tower Tower I agree with
everything solo Baron solo Baron uh um
um um um flash yes what what about your
micros oh all of them
yeah I I got it I understood did you get
what I meant yeah I I got it I I
understood that solo bolo jungle un
install un jungle un install that is
what League of Legends Pros would say
proxy proxy I am just very confused
about all the words that are being
thrown around um um they're good words
jungle jungle diff What does diff mean
difference diff diff yeah basically if
you say it to someone it's like you're
complimenting
them if you go into a normal game you
should say that and you're complimenting
them you're lying to me I can hear from
your tone of voice don't try gasing me
don't even try you're gapped it's a
compliment G oh you gapped yeah oh oh I
see I see so make sure to use that in
your next League of Legends game teach
me more what else should I say so yeah
just because I want to be a good player
a positive mindset what should I say
okay okay okay so next time you go into
a normal game just go just say like pick
any role and say like I don't know mid
Canyon mhm yeah and can someone tell me
why I got promoted to bronze they're in
the game yay she's
bronze you're BR okay I'll do that
thanks for the for oh you've invited me
Y game I just checked their
streams they made it for the
queue damn how did they do that did they
cheat what they cheat the poe girls got
for the like biboo and Kyla got into
they did nice yeah I'm trying to get in
and it's telling me that I need to
purchase a code but I purchased a
code so what does it want from me why is
it lying more
codes codes what's more of it that's all
you had to do wait
damn it's okay this this is wor right no
it's okay it took them it took them
three hours they waited three hours
that's crazy okay that is crazy I'm glad
I didn't do
that hello I'm glad I'm please welcome
back can play uh P Exile too or I have
partially regrets but mostly no regrets
no regrets no regrets even yes no
regret absolutely no none
regrets no regrets allowed in this
household none of that
no n no that no
Cecilia yes the jump scared me are we in
are we ready for you yeah how yeah how I
haven't said anything in like a while
you did you did something oh getting
ready for C I'm
sorry I'm sorry oh I in oh okay okay
okay we're queuing we're queuing we're
going to queue six people I see I see
that's fun except are we doing yeah we
we'll do real people yes yes yes yes I
believe
I like real people me oh heart
throb Warwick oh
heart
[Music]
Warwick real I am a hard
Fring at
theend you love her be on that one
remember darling
you you'll love her be on that one
k yeah does she do something
special
yep you'll see I won't spoil
it I'm so fast do we go into the
bushes we can check we can see if
they're real people I'm big how do we
know if they're real people um
Instinct yeah okay I think they're
Bots that's a
bot I'm I don't have any PC I didn't
start with it I'm leav embarrassed
myself oh thank
you if it's a bot they won't judge me
too
hard
damn Warick you're on my Lane hello no
you look so different I could you I
should have started running at that
part should have start AV you double
you oh the music's cute he's inviting me
okay never mind get them get them he's
so
stupid go Nissa it's worth it I can't
get
anymore
annoying trash man oh nice that looks
cool Liz yeah pain
goodu goodbye
didn't even heal up I miss you oh really
really really come on you little [\h__\h]
they're low there's two that are low
here
guys I'm
running worry
not
I'm oh there are okay I'm here for to
harass her
jungle okay okay okay
okay nice nice
nice good that was totally worth it I'm
going to die from the leave leave run
away run
[Music]
away it's okay the minions are keeping
everything up I don't even have to do
anything
yay yay you can go home you should go
home I'm going
home she's going
home a woman who's beautiful she's a
woman wao wo I said she's a woman who's
beautiful she's going she's a woman what
are you trying to say huh oh my
God know we were like that I didn't know
we were that kind of League of Legends
team I oh sorry that's the league
experience that I was looking forward
to wow she has to
heal uh what's that what's what's his
name
uh GA
Gallo mm
galloo Gallo I hate that guy you hate
him okay he has a chicken costume and
I'm aware of it kfp I'm aware she's
aware there everybody told me to look at
it I've seen
it come
back nice where are you running Charmed
Charmed charm where are you running
[Music]
to he gave me a kill for free he's so
nice paid
actor all
right he working
L my head forever it's hard to get
out cuz she's a
singer beautiful woman
singer I'll switch the order
now cuz he's himer
Dinger oh my
god oh there was a sparkle in the
world wait why are there two of them
that's not fair that's a bot you know
she just doesn't know what's going
on I'm going to
die you're not going going to die not
today not today
uhoh at this guy he keep what are you
doing he keeps going back and forth what
is
that they're doing their best their best
is not good enough they're trying really
hard back up the Bots are going to kill
you or the
minions it's mine to dis oh God I'm
going to die no okay now so you're going
to Flame the
bot are you saying I deserve this yes
you deserved that you deserved what was
coming for you for flaming the
Bots don't Flame the poor Bots just once
yeah once maybe I shouldn't have Flame
the weird moving B this is what you get
for being toxic and this is a lesson we
should
allly okay
oh the that's so cute bigest snowball
bigger bigger I
learned okay okay okay I did it right
he's charm he's charm he's charm I'm
killing this
G flash o kill him yay we did it get the
other one get the other one
okay down okay I she's Charmed it's
Charmed it's Charmed okay okay okay no
don't go
in no did you get him I did oh no wait
there's another one behind I'm going to
get this dragon
now get
it he could have killed me if he wanted
to I think he's in love with me I think
so too that's the only logical yeah
makes
sense I have my ult now I'm unkillable
because I can run
away oh I will just wa I'm leaving
obviously Sor wait there's two there's
three it's over I'm doing my
best I'm doing greata you're fastic
you're doing great I lost my lane and
it's it's 100% because of the jungler oh
yeah yeah so because of GG way wow GG
yeah my bad it's just how it is
sometimes what is that I'm going man
okay we I'm out of Mana I I mean I could
charm him I'm going I'm I'm okay okay
okay okay charm charm
okay that's all I can do now I have to
leave okay I'm running away to again
he's confused wait wait he's coming in
hit him
awesome okay hold on he's Charmed he's
Charmed I anymore kill him kill him kill
him go in yay it's it's easy good job e
easy easiest game okay now I'm going
home
nice
yay
yeah did you use your ult
already yes you're not asking me know
who you asking no one talk no of course
oh really you sure because I know I'm
alone here so no one's talking to me
it's okay I I watch I'm looking I'm
watching you
yeah if he's really low like that and
he's far away you can save your ult for
last and you should be able to kill him
you actually talked to
me I I have my eye on you you watching
me I'm watching you I'm
Charmed W I'm dying you thank
you
damn uhoh do you do you have my stream
open in the second screen or
I click on the map and I look at
you why I why you even have time for
that she's a I'm losing my Lane because
of you you should focus on your lane you
don't want to you don't want to watch
Pros they they're like crazy with doing
that
yeah I can imagine they got their eyes
everywhere ow there's one guy here up
here G
okay there there okay okay I'm Charming
him he's
Charmed okay let's get get him get
him oh oh no they regret
[Music]
living no okay okay there's another one
there's another one right here Warwick
Warwick wait okay never mind dying I'm
going to kill that Warwick no don't
steal my kill don't die don't die steal
her kill I'm going into my locker bye no
no no here I'll start this kill for you
I'll start this kill for you I'm already
gone I'll get this kill I I'll avenge
you okay oh my God he feared
me he
knew are you seeing what she takes out
of the locker what does she take out of
the locker it's a picture of VI oh the
ball I'm rolling the ball he has no idea
what's going on oh wait don't spoil it's
fine I haven't seen yeah don't spoil
please it's fine it's what I don't know
anything what it's the animation in the
The Bee no no no I didn't mean that I
was asking follow-up questions and then
I I took it back don't
worry fool you stand no chance I killed
him what is that I see dead you you did
did that because I said that I lost my
Lane because of you previously huh I I
had to get rid of him for you I I really
got it
back they don't care
chat we care no no no no
uh I I don't mean you
it's okay of course we care about you no
no no no we love you we care I'll come
back and kill him again no don't do that
I'll make him regret being up he's to
kill oh someone's
teleporting who who's teleporting God
tell him not to
okay I'll do that next time oh yeah I
eat the eat the cookies eat the cookies
eat the cookies geky my ALT is ready
okay and I'm like lowy dying though my B
I don't know what he's doing over
here stop fearing me I keep forgetting
to eat my
biscuits at least you have
biscuits goodbye
Unstoppable double kill
my
tower y there's some people up here but
I don't think they're coming up here yet
all not mean the flash back finger
that right here help right here it's
okay don't die to her I can do an
ALT
yay okay okay
oh God oh God we can do this maybe yeah
yeah got
this give me the kill give me the kill
get it get it get it oh
no
no I'm I'm going to leave right here
right here
to let's look picture time this
one oh oh no
yay was close that was
close PE PE oh just a little bit of
Tower so none of my letter abilities
work on the
tower what the hell was that that
sucks oh he has a lot of Health no weird
he's a tanky Champion he's tanky don't
appreciate it why thank
you wow what's she doing over there I'm
going
home yeah J the tower the tower starts
walking towards you yeah like
uproots oh buy stuff I forgot where'd he
go there he is I came for you Warwick
I'm getting my kill one way or another
yes grows legs and then he starts
walking towards you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] be
cute
oops
ow we got him good job I need more
damage I need more damage cuz are
good it doesn't matter who gets them as
long as he dies
right oh I mean no I me I me I don't
know how I got
him
good oh back I I didn't mind to get
tower Tower tower
Tower kill
Hima no come back come back come back
come back ride come back come back oh
no get
her all right all right I'm here he has
no Mana he has no Mana get the tower get
the tower going keep going yay more
minions
thanks oh he's behind me he's behind me
who's behind you oh there a toad why is
the toad
attack I mean just kill
him why are you attacking us Mr Toad
that's not very nice
toad a
toad oh I'm coming jungle coming
jungle I'm welcome what is that what was
that oh is that a buff okay
yes hi Liz thank
you okay okay okay let's go get him I'm
leaving oh wait this K I'm stupid
I last time
so I was like oh kick oh down down he's
Charmed he's Charmed
oh I'm dying it's okay run it's fine
it's fine I'll stop them oh waa who he's
still running he's I missed him he's not
Charmed I'm wrong I'm
lying ooh oops I didn't mean to attack
him oh
oh
no running at me oh we all here though
come back mid we're all
here
nice nice nice nice nice nice get the
turret okay
awesome
nice oh
oh what oh I died from the tower my
bad my
[Music]
bad oops if we stay really still we be
you think he'll walk out over here yeah
yeah he's coming your way go over here
come
back no he's not I think he's so scared
he's too scared of you what is he scared
of oh he's coming
back don't be scared nice nice nice go
nice G man this suck no you got him
you're two people and there's Gigi right
behind you
n what is that is that an elephant no
tiger no a boar I'm not sure an animal
play time is never over chunky wonky
welcome to the table I guess hello
fluffy
monster a boar she wants to play
league she is she only she thinks I'm
done streaming cuz I'm so
quiet cute girl I'm still streaming
let's get top Tower oh guess I should
talk more this is my more it's okay
we're all locked in we're we're all
locked in so hard ah ah locked in but
not not protecting the
waa goodbye chunky
wonky okay
uh
is I am here but I am low ah
shoot okay we did get two it was worse
it was worse was worse worse
what's
worth
worth okay he's almost dead do you see
him yes on the right yes oh it's
you nice nice nice
nice
legendary charm Charmed nice go nice
going back
she's going back where's my mouse oh I'm
[Laughter]
coming I'm B not again not
again almost died I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine get him get him goodbye everyone
good job destroy destroy
yeah I'm coming com
in you got him nice uhoh uhoh I'm
dead it's fine you guys can finish it
course you got this nice protect
last a triple kill
[Music]
no live she's weak you can get her nice
you you you got a triple kill you you
got triple kill look at you
Kara
yay thanks to the question marks League
of Legends
Pro League of leing
pro g
g g g
good
work
GW oh my God I can honor more than one
person I can just honor all of you yeah
oh
oops not biased do you
think would would okay going top does w
want a bot Lane oh yeah you want to
support what the hell is bot she can
still play
Kaitlyn I don't mind doing
whatever okay don't bother me I mean I
love I I love
youa but I don't mind switching up oh
bottom L I thought everywhere is bot
linge cuz the Bots are everywhere no
oh okay what so should I go bottom yeah
go
bottom oh I I'll see a different scenery
for once mhm okay
okay yeah and then narissa will set up
all the kills for
you okay okay okay oh she will steal
them all is that what I hear from that
giggle I I nothing
intentional I believe okay one second
I'm just getting water up but I'm still
like here okay she will steal them it's
okay like if I don't she can't steal
anything that doesn't exist there are no
kills in the first place with me no she
she's going to set them up and then
you're going to kill steal her it's
probably more like she's setting them up
and she's killing
them they for you both I'm just there
for mental support we have to do it
together
okay can't play play again okay I'm here
okay let's go I'm baby
I'm
baby I'm
sorry are
you we need you mine's still mine's
still
loading yeah mine's still loading back
into the thing yeah now it's doing it
well I've recently met a baby so I think
I'm pretty good with you know you
recently met a baby the mystical
creature
and I I I I uh it it pulled my hair it
was pretty fascinated with me I gave it
an elephant like the elephant yeah I
think it was in love with
[Music]
me H
baby baby do I need to click something
different now no you can just swap you
can go
top baby was cute top of the thingy
you pulled my hair
yeah and I
didn't I would like to go back bottom
after this game though
okay it's just a test
yeah with
great so I'm going to go Bottom now yeah
go B Yes Yes W fairy CT this looks
like I know it's so pretty the
guy oh we on the oh no we on the other
side oh no oh no it's oh no is that
bad confus me personally it doesn't
change anything but it gets really
confusing for no it is confusing yeah
let's see if they're real people so is
my bottom the top now because we're the
other way around yeah go this way
right uh wait wait wait why is the view
always so weird in the beginning why do
I always have to change it I don't know
are we going into the into the into the
bushes G we can see if they're real I'll
poke my head over what they start I
follow you are we going into the
bush yeah we might die I don't see that
they might be starting
blue blue should I walk over there just
to look
yeah behind you I'm behind you okay oh
are are you guys real are you guys BS
guys are you real are you B real people
where you going s where are they are you
they're no trying to be my individual
own person wait there's someone there
are they real are they real get them I'm
too used to being there's another one
behind oh no that's that's okay well
come hurry we'll just go to Lane are
yay he's dead it's okay oh they're here
hey wait that's a real person that's
really yeah they're they're definitely
real where okay I'm running
away back to the tower back to the tower
wow okay I'm at the tower you're playing
against a real
person who the Lux is real the Lux is
real no pot Lane is definitely real
people
it's okay I got this we've trained for
this
guys no we haven't yes we what yes we
have sorry sorry hey what ELO are you
playing against what's happening what
the
hell what's the best thing to do
now bro
wow
um you just are supposed to kill kill
the minions last hit them so you get
money so when you die or go back you can
um you know buy things to get stronger
yeah I meant more like she's running
away from me why she running away from
me Retreat or scared h i mean there is
no retreat we just have to keep doing it
if you're struggling you can come back
by the
tower
[Music]
okay I carry the Legacy blah blah Ari
blah blah blah blah telling us she's
telling us her entire life story blah
blah blah blah blah
blah
okay is careful whoops what the hell
must come here
CeCe where is here up up yeah where I am
I'm
coming okay Charmed good good kill him
kill him kill him I don't have a ward
I'm afraid of walking in I'm very
low no I have to eat this okay he
there's two now I can't do it
on I die to this oh I die to this
cookie
[Music]
owie the music is so peaceful it has to
go
peaceful ow ow ow ow
ow I prefer playing against bots no no
it'll be okay I like I like people I
feel more fulfilled when it's a real
person than a bot yeah it's a learning
it's how you learn it's how you actually
get
better from BS I mean from like minions
oh I'll use all my money and then I'll
leave yummy yum yum yum no no I'm going
to die have confidence nope goodbye have
confidence oh she's a high oh no oh no
oh no I am dead oh no oh no no no
no all right I will come smack him soon
Liz maybe let me kill all these little
tiny
babies you leaving they're pretty good
they're pretty good
bot that's a little good luck GG you're
going to have to carry
I'm I KN new okay okay I'm here Li I'm
here cookie okay I'm going
to I didn't get closer to be able to do
what I want to do oh no where did he go
no he healed oh I shouldn't have
flashed oh I don't know where they are
well damn nice
try there they are
okay she has no Mana I'm running
up okay go go go go
go nice ping she FL can I blame the Ping
have 170 ping blame the Ping thank you
though
okay it's that goddamn
every time maybe I can maybe if I charm
her ow ow he's hurting
me I'm going to go back let's go I can
walk
bottom wow he's ice sking with himself
it's so cute I'm going for the Draven or
the
Jin go on okay well I HIIT them but I
have to leave my minions go they're
leaving back up back up
I want to go get grubs so careful b side
okay grubs
grubs grss just back up we're really
[Music]
low nice
thanks go my minions
gos oh
uh-oh what was that does this music come
from you I don't know oh H yeah the
music comes from nissa's
uh it's so calming ouch double kill uhoh
ouch
oh uh oh gotch you [\h__\h] female dog uh
fale
dog help
me jilbert please save us I can't I
can't fight this 10 no no she's level
seven okay I can't fight
Warick where are
you he's
ons can't really can't do anything here
o
I got you
biscuit no Lux leave leave my tower
alone you
fiend leave it
alone I take my jumper off it's
hot we can go kill Warwick if you want I
don't think we can kill Warwick oh we
two people two versus one should we win
oh he's just standing there we can walk
towards him I don't think we'll make it
there in time it's the only problem by
the time he leaves he's very fast oh
they're already level six we're screwed
oh he's right there I see him they have
alts we don't I'm coming it's okay wait
there's two of them there's two of them
I'm dead I'm so dead I'm walking to you
oh no dang
it Go the wall I'm too behind to do much
it's okay it's okay sorry it's okay
let me grab
this please stop pinging
randomly ma'am um I've been told it's a
polite thing to do if you do it
correctly oh I think retreating was the
correct thing to do it was just too
late would you agree chat
no she rooted me she always Roots me no
you rolled at
you that's rude I hate
her
goodbye what the
heck oh my
God okay so that one is like a is that
the St I can't
tell take eight LEL eight
okay oh he's just walking pastes care
okay I'm coming from behind the Warwick
might come back back oh I'm dead I'm
dead I'm I'm running away I missed I
missed don't worry I scared her I scar
why you
ballar oh no oh no oh no
I'm going to be more careful o it's good
go go go go you got
him ow O okay never
mind okay it's okay no you got
this I was trying to W the bush
no wait that's messed up only the bear
dies and the girl still lives and then
she just like lays next to him on the
floor what do you mean the bear which
bear Noo-noo and W which one I don't
know the Y animal your pets yeah and
then the and she's fine and then she
just lays down on the floor she's living
that's messed up she dies of
grief a oh it's a ye Yeti a Yeti a bear
if you think about
itent okay we can still turn this right
guys yes we can still turn this
around
no yeah we can around we can do it duh
I should have just played
Teo I'm a we're getting melted
bottom oh my God okay what Strat do we
do quick do this Strat number seven I
number and then got this we do seven I
think we got this so can you tell me cuz
it's my first day
was yeah of course I can tell you
everybody else knows but you got to
explain it to me yeah so the man on the
strats oh there coming behind me's
coming up behind me he's behind me he's
behind me oh behind you okay I'll charm
him he here yeah he's over here
somewhere by myself he was behind me
okay I'm running away again L okay to my
minions destroyed
uh-oh that's not good
oh he's here oh where okay okay
okay he's Charmed he's
Charmed coming Mondo's on his way
Mundo's on his way try coming back we're
both dead okay okay yeah I need helpy
that was a try oh he
flashed I mean I need help top I'm not
bottom
anymore you need help top
okay yeah I need help top for a moment
watch out for this Warick let's get in
whoa what is
oh actually as M
Mundo what is this what is all this fire
everywhere fire fire light the fire we
lighting the
fire fire high as you desire very
collector wow no not legendary fine he
got executed he was greedy nice what a
what a fool what a loser fool just
kidding he's kicking our asses no no
he's he's a Los the
fool I hit by that okay I have to learn
how to dodge
that let's go where am I to
go we're getting
stomped no we're not it's okay we're
fine we're fine yeah we can turn this
around I don't know I don't know can we
just has to come up with some Strat and
tell us what to do that like really conf
they have 21 kills and we have two are
you
sure uhoh uhoh uhoh oh God that they're
all here the war and the freaking M got
me am I
can you come up with like a cool strp no
don't die we going to bite
them okay that's a good idea I
think that is my plan mhm going to bite
B we bite them okay what if we just went
next you know like a
reset okay okay where what like like we
go to the next game
[Music]
what if
we what if we went to the next game that
sounds like surrendering not winning
that feels like the opposite of winning
no it's winning it's
winning I can't get this ow they're all
here I'm coming I'm coming I'm coming
bring them mid uhoh there's so oh my
God your dead body and the dead child oh
my so messed up the dead child too
we can we can go next to reset and maybe
we'll get worse people you know they're
going they're going mid I think they're
all going mid
hooray
surrender
what dang
it who did
no wait I know
eend how many people have to have to
vote it has to be unanimous for early
surrender animous a
man oh if only that was if only we knew
who that was too bad we can't figur it
it out oh it is unanimous I
suppose that's the first time I see that
today it's very depressing I know no
it's okay the d stands for done well
done yeah f e a t yeah yeah I finished
my second liter of water give me a sec I
need to grab more more what let's
do I'll BRB okay
brbs okay you are still not muted on my
screen you know
okay I'm muting myself hello chat for
the first time how do I get on Path of
Exile
if I didn't redeem myy cuz now the ks
from that
cloudy am I supposed to do what do I
do oh speaking of Jester I want to try
shako shako shako shako what uh let's
see do I even have him
yet have to wait until the website goes
back up bug
was I am a fast food restaurant quiet I
don't here to feed people no I'm as loud
as I can be unfortunately my thing is on
M feed them you so
hungry I would be evil if I would let
people hunger just got to wait so we
have to wait for the redeemed to
back I I I do like to receive too but
this is because everyone saying Discord
was too quiet early on so I just base
boosted it m
yeah yeah is this better your love
language or is this better what's my
love language
uh this better uh okay yes I bought it
on
Steam we should all take one of these
quizzes yeah I feel like the only person
who didn't take this like Omega quiz
thing oh I haven't done it yet you oh so
it's is it that short I bought it on
stream I don't know we can we can still
look at it afterwards after stream after
after stream cuz every posting the
results while I was busy with and fixed
it it still says your account does not
have access redeem key on website very I
purchased it so I do have to it has 40
questions oh that shouldn't be too long
turned
it I have cont you take make a quiz to I
have to wait no not yet
youen yet if I spam log I should I have
what's your excuse I forgot about it I
saw it and I was I should do
this I'm about it when it's been going
on for
like kiaha is saying that but her and me
haven't done it yet so yeah I see I see
excuse okay what is your excuse yeah
what Vis the past 3 days with ladies in
my in my house should I pick that one
ladies did you have ladies in your house
I'm a
lady I mean mom's l
exive l my mom's the lady have you been
having a nice time yeah me and the
ladies or and the ladies me and the L we
had we a nice time very nice time and
magnificent marous time so
beautiful they love
Austria everyone loves austa two out of
five of us here have taken the O
Omega I will
say how much longer do you girls want to
play because one person in this room has
a uh thing to do I can't even get on
don't even worry I want to to apply uh
not pressure but I want to remind a who
is it who has the thing to do
oh someone sounds very
guilty I
see it's practically done it's just I
whether I whether I want to add a cherry
on top you should you
should okay you know yeah sure I'll add
the cherry on top add the cherry on top
and I will eat it should we play another
one yeah yeah we can play one how long
does the Cherry take
last um shouldn't take too long all
right if we do one more then yeah I'll
have I'll have time all
right let's go hold on are my runes
correct okay finding m Comfort Pi
Teo oh you're doing Teo this time okay
Comfort Teo I oh I want to change my
catak
everybody Discord room has participated
in the Advent calendar already for one
person I declin that you can switch your
character thank you sorry I can try try
Lilia actal
[Music]
herb oh my God Teo with the be skin is
called we're playing Le that's so cute
beo I love
beo beo beo wait who are you Arcanist
Shack ah can I go top again bottom was
stressful yeah you're going
top why would you say that like you want
to get
R you are not a good
goodbye how do I learn then how will I
ever learn you're to read you need to
read how to play it read how to play it
and then try
again w w w hey I I am sensing some
hostility is this the to I hovering over
the report
[Laughter]
button I'm I'm ready now I don't care
either way but you up before you broke
up with me I already said I'm going back
up good she already said a letter before
good fine then good I hope you'll have
fun down there being bottom I love bot
yeah I already
have who's who's joining you down there
H herb me
[Music]
a I said off I said before the last game
I want to go
you want to go oh okay I wish you
happiness I see I've seen this coming in
the past weeks and months anyway the
signs all mama called me she was like
you knew that that we would be likeing
in
the and then I'm like I have to see and
she's like actually you have to do I'm
just call beginning seen the Synergy in
your colors and your designs yes I have
to well she's monitoring me you know
yeah I mean I'm monitoring yeah I mean
Cecilia and Gigi also monitor Thea too
so
yeah oh I'm ready I don't
see oh
there are we checking if they're real
people again they're real people I'm
sure wa I hear KDA music
[Music]
[Laughter]
are we going into the bushes or not
nah that's the most fun part
of I'm fine on my
own me and my minions we're going to
guys you want to you want to go you want
to see this oh my God you're clown
you're clown my goodness who are you
playing against is that lux okay no Lux
it's okay my goodness now what is
this have smolder smolder is
that what do I need to know G quick I
know nothing about him I I I think it
takes him a really long time to ramp up
he needs a lot of
farm and his oldest this big line and he
flies around and he's
like and he throws a ball at
you smolder from a okay
hello
yes that's crazy wa turn turn on your
screen question mark
someone you can't tell me what to do
okay okay do whatever makes you happy
that's fine I have to I have to task
manager my way out of it why is it not
Window mode anymore what happened
actually wait why is he doing more
damage than me messed
up he's going to farm
huh oh W
wake so nice to see you you thought I
was alone did you
oh you are wrong yes you are wrong I
think bot is real people I'm pretty sure
they're real people that's still yeah
uh Warwick behaves just the way I like
it so I think he's a bot mhm can the
team be like half bot half real people
not sure yes I think that's what
happened last the first time we played
yeah I think if they don't have like a
full
team and there's like not a good amount
of people who can join with them they'll
just like supplement with Bots that
would be
evil oh
it's okay she's
backed is it like common that the Top
Lane is always played a load and the
bottom is always double yeah
yeah
o Bottom's not as aggressive as last
time which is good maybe maybe they are
Bots maybe they are Bots you shouldn't
have you shouldn't have judged Me by One
game against Real I'm not judging you
I'm not judging you I would do better
now perhaps
I'm not judging you just bot bot all the
lanes in all the different areas are
played differently oh they all Bots
they're Bots for reals is mine bot guys
yeah they're all Bots
[Music]
yay the jokes on I'm getting very
conflicting information come to where I
am you yeah me
yeah okay I'm coming
oh guys you're going to going want to
come see this oh don't run up to him
though he's melee don't run up to him
he's he's a melee range
champ too late Miss Sor I wasn't I
wasn't looking at my HP but you got him
you got him you got him he has he
got I don't know anything about this
Champion messed up
no his life
steal well an it's okay they're
Bots it's okay nothing wrong with a
little
feeding I see right through you oh she's
so close so close to death I'm dead why'
you die all right I thought she was
going to die awkward she's so weird I
thought she was going to die
Nissa oh God now I'm going to die wa
he's going home wait wait wait yeah kill
him kill the bot kill the bot oh he just
left yeah he teleported away oh he went
bot mhm oh what that's a skill Oh I
thought he was going home if it's purple
it's
teleport I think it was
gold don't
remember wow if it's blue it's the back
oh I see
[Music]
okay get her get her get
her oh
minions one
more thanks
Gigi that was very very productive no
problem uh uh uh uh
thanks no problem thanks just doing my
part thanks
oh I'm out of
man
ow bye my go back
home I'm living my best life she says
actually I'll leave one of these byebye
okay
goodbye oh I can zoom in
I'm
coming oh God oh God looks
funny jungle
attacks is that what you is that what
you
need was that what it was GG jungle
attacks yeah yeah just is that part of
League yeah it's part of League you know
it's normal you should should get used
to it yeah all right it's a normal thing
that everyone does all right all right
all right I understand now
mhm here I don't think so I don't think
the Bots are intelligent enough for that
oh stop him oh stop him oh wait there's
so many of them there's three people in
the jungle HH ah GG it's okay you justra
I'm sure that they won't get the last
grub they're going to go to k though
okay I'm running oh my God they killed
my guy you got him kill him kill him
kill him jungle tax jungle tax jungle
tax jungle ta jle ta jungle ta jle
jungle I'm getting the jungler the
jungle tags a
owie he's Charmed okay you're crazy do
it
again uh give me like 5 Seconds change
my mind nice okay bye goodbye do you
have like a heal or something nah it is
what it is that's fine that's fine so
when they do damage to the to the Jungle
jungle animals don't die can you like
kill kill them and then steal the kill
yeah you can steal the the jungle
animal M that's a
strat that's how you always want to
fight objectives and take it from them
a the
name let me have your let me have this
no
please let me have your
blue oh where is he oh he's right there
hit hit it take
it take your
blue they're weak we'll fight it
together Vol bear
we we'll
together okay chunky wonky oh SMY is
also here sleeping oh hi
hi my cats are
here oh he's he's flying he's flying oh
he's
[Music]
flying did you hear that so cute cute
she just jumped up
burping home oops don't press buttons
thank
you she wants me to watch the
enemy she's the enemy oh oh
the everybody want
to she's an Arcane hater don't be a
hater Arcane from L League of Legends
yeah from League of Legends League of
Legends you know they made a game based
off Arcane from League of Legend
that's it feels to
me you're fake fan fake League fan they
made they made a game based off of our
play this game before joining you guys
of course we fake fans what do you
think I'm an Arcane fan oh what's that
sorry
Ryan it's my well you're playing league
so wrong one
so come here you little bot get him
clone get
him aim
do
weak whoa what he killed you going to
take away my skins yeah that was like a
wave let's run oh that's as old okay uh
level eight I love taking your farm AR I
appreciate that you know someone should
take it I never hit the last hit
anyway I was B might as well are you
dead I'm running
down oh they leaving oh what is he oh no
oh no you don't you don't see me I I see
you I'm helping I'm helping I'm helping
helping you're crazy I'm helping I'm
helping you're
crazy oh oh nice nice nice you guys are
so strong oh there's two oh
no no but Gigi said engage even if it's
two at full healthid do not be afraid
always always greet I'm not hitting any
of my shots that's fine come be here now
okay okay okay okay ow ow I'm just
cleaning up yeah it's my job perfectly
planned get him almost oh my God nice
nice nice nice nice who the heck is
that worth G you wor did you do
War let him die he's a bear
now what really is that still Warwick
yeah that that's still him no it's a
bear why is he a bear it's Vol Bear
right yeah Voli bear that's not war
rck they're Botho
same you know are are they yeah they're
basically the same ow
Boozled oh okay I see Warwick and Vol
bear at the same time now so I think a
she's so low you bamboozled me no I
would not lie to you I'm fine I'm fine
I'm
fine I'll scare him away from your
lane help thank you please continue
doing so ow trying I'm freaking
en
bye
okay is it
fixed ma'am stop
it I don't know why that is I have no
idea are we sure they're Bots yeah we're
I'm sure they're
Bots I'm not sure if B
pretty
flowers
a what that
do
okay sorry about the audio
stuff maybe I should reinstall like all
my audio drivers or something yeah every
every single one Mak
them what's your audio problem oh in a
while since like last week every once in
a while my audio just becomes like super
crunchy but I can't hear it only chat
can hear it for some reason it's like
what is you know it must be OBS I don't
know interesting oh go go get him get
him get him he'll walk back to
us now is as good time as nice
[Music]
so now GG when I have like this much
health should I happening to my p hold
on something is going on with my
computer something very terrible is
happening uhoh I admitted something bad
my I think what is happening my second
monitor is
flickering oh God everybody's got maybe
the C loose crunch it's it's like flick
let me take a video of this so you can
see how cursed this is it would be so
funny if you would like screen
record I'm going to start screen
recording huh what no that's not going
to work if it's the monitor okay let me
send this to you uhoh what what is
happening computer you killed her
the USB is has problems with connection
let me upload and then send
this oops what speed it up can't believe
he's at my
[Music]
tower there he
goes where'd it go the jokes on you
oh my my goodness what is going Onis yay
to Broken
finally ooh I don't have boots yet I'm
slow put it here and then I'll also send
to kiaha so you can see thank
you check after the game I I did have a
lot of uh flickering issues so yeah do
you see that like what is what is
happening that's fine just hit it once
I'm sure it's fine o I'm sure you're
okay o yeah
yeah yeah it's fine it's fine don't
worry don't worry you think it's fine
you think it's okay yeah I think it's
fine I'm pretty sure it's
fine we're winning I'm glad it's okay
and nothing is bad bad is happening no
no it's
fine I don't even like what are these
circles and question marks and x's on my
screen let me know if it turns into a
blue screen I had that
before I can make it through this League
of Legends game
yeah we'll we'll make it to this I bet
it's Path of Exile it's mad at me oh you
are you do you have Roblox on in the
side as well no I don't have Roblox on
today I'm believe you very
surprising it became dark what's going
on my greed I will die now oh my
God I deserved
it I deserved it for my greed what is
that oh that's his Sal that's pretty
bad
die I accidentally flashed I'm already
in the middle I no longer have second
monitor
like at all no it's still flickering but
I it's I just can't use it you know oh
that's okay you don't need a second
aitor you feel it you know what doing I
feel it I don't need to read
chat
yo all
right what is we're doing well is that
TW that's flickering on my page what is
oh my God takes another video he's a sh
pu what is
happen oh what's that oh Char this
enemy hey looks
funny what do we want to do we're all
we're all doing pretty
well whatever you want to do beautiful
lady do we want to all go and push mid
we want to push bottom what do we want
to do oh this wait they're all here here
all mid I'm here let's go let's go let's
go let's go okay okay okay I'm going let
go go
in okay I'll I'm get
him I'm not get
nice this one too get this GG I'm dead
you got this though you got it good
job qura kill goodbye the P the panta
anything left over what the hell what
what's going on what he run to wait guys
oh yeah you you got I'm run running you
all running behind no he keeps going oh
nice
shot I'm too far I'm too slow are you
still running he's just fting you
goodbye
my War
well very nice you guys are just in
their base destroying things that's
amazing that's
beautiful would it make sense like if
you just kill one lane and then ignore
the other turrets and then you go into
the base you could do that but um why
don't people do that that should be a
thing the more people that are in a lane
the you have to split XP with them
I put that on the outside so if everyone
went mid and tried to push
mid and Theory it sounds like a great
idea sounds like a great idea yeah but
if you're all level
one oh the the the single person in that
lane on their side is going to level
faster than you and everyone else is
getting lots of exp free Farm me
yeah
wow good job
my poor poor
computer oh no I did my thing chat it's
okay
we yes Oh's this it's
fine my homework will I ever hit an
ignite wait
how
uhoh W she's singing oh that's you right
I was like am might walk back she's the
singer he's Charmed he's Charmed he's
Charmed yay she's the
singer hey
SN she's a singer himer
Dinger nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice
nice this is so nice we're so
good we an end y
Y come out twin she's a
Seer we
[Applause]
[Music]
woni twin was hit to see it
too my
clone good job y good work everyone one
good keep up the good work all right I
got a
dash I'm awaiting your
[Music]
DM by byebye bye
bye is everybody just oh that's the same
one for everybody what yeah I think I
need to restart my computer I really
don't know what is going on it really is
not having a good
time I mean you played really well all
things considered yeah just this is my
second monitor something's happening to
it I can't explain your
problem I can't either I can't explain
my problem either have you tried turning
it off and on again I will after this
turn to help you've got it good job
today yay
thanks thanks for joining you saved the
day thanks k for joining thank you for
playing with us yeah yeah you did we had
she like coma she wakes up what did I
do I mean it would have just been a bot
otherwise right no no it would have been
a random person
yeah this it was very nice I love
playing with you yeah join us again
sometime sure I will joining we can play
Bot game I can hold your hand and I can
teach you yeah
sure sure okay bye everyone thanks
fore my computer byebye
byee okay everyone since it's just hold
on let me see if this
is doible I just took a video of my
screen I will show you what's going on
it's
really really not good let me see that I
don't I'm not showing anything I show
you
this hold
on okay let me take another video so you
can see a fraction of my
screen okay take
that video and let me upload
this it it's pretty bad whatever is
happening it it is pretty
bad it's honestly it's
awful ah why is I playing
okay this yeah I just took another video
to make sure that nothing is on
it here let me show
you me
[Music]
look
okay just do you see this that's what's
happening to my screen right
now I I don't I don't know what's going
on I I need to restart my C
computer it it is very worrying and
that's only a portion of my
screen so yeah I would have loved to
play more League of Legends I wanted to
play solo Cube but I think um I think I
should solve this I think I should
figure out if this monitor is dead and
what's like maybe a simple restart will
work yeah but but I will see you
guys I don't know it looks like Path of
Exile is still having login problems or
like I can't get in because um the
redeem key side is down and I purchased
it off of steam and then people are like
but if you buy it off steam you can play
but it wasn't working it was not working
it kept telling me to purchase key but I
purchased it off of steam so we will see
if I am able to get into Path of Exile
in any capacity I will stream and then
um but if I am unable to then I will not
stream but we will have a stream for p x
eventually another time
but so my priority list is figure out
second Monitor and then path the
vile and if I can't figure out second
monitor if like everything fails while
I'm trying to solve the second monitor
then um I'm not going to do anything
I'm going to go restart my computer
goodbye everyone thanks for
joining here I'll play it one more time
for whoever missed
it how do I replay
it
properties Loop that's what it looks
like here's here's my
monitor
[Laughter]
that okay bye everyone
fwell League of Legends
[Music]