foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hi guys
I forgot to take my throw candy before
the stream so I'm sorry if I sound like
[\h__\h] come in there hi
hello hello hello hello
Hello whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you did
not just do that you did not just do the
whole
[Music]
wait I muted myself oopsies
[Applause]
my alerts are gonna be going off for a
while now
thank you for the 50 memberships thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you
[Music]
who came in oh God I don't know how I'm
gonna really say thank you and welcome
to all of you uh 50 [\h__\h] people yes
holy [\h__\h]
you didn't you did not you
don't have to do that we just start Ed
we just [\h__\h] started wait did I get
raided okay okay wow wow this one we're
not even like two minutes in
oh God thank you for the rain thank you
okay I really cannot I cannot keep track
of 50 different people
um hi
hello
hello wow The Burbs are all coming to my
streams wow wow started off with
takanashikiara and then yesterday I had
Ezra on my street now we have okay
reading the holy I am surrounded by
Burbs
oh
ah thank you Anonymous thank you for the
donuts
you see me on Twitter before I I would
hope so yes if you haven't that'd be
kind of sad why are you here
hi wow YouTube is telling me now would
be a good time to insert ads
it just popped up on my screen it just
popped up here I'm gonna show you just
look at this [\h__\h] you see that just
yes yes YouTube yes because now would be
a great time
I'm just gonna close that
yeah I don't know YouTube weird like
that oh gosh
thank you for the don't know again
whoever it was has a hammer is flat as a
I'm not gonna say that out loud because
that would be admitting it but yes thank
you
oh my God service thank you thank you so
much for the for the five the 50 not 550
freaking gifted memberships and I know
they're not cheap so even bigger thank
you I appreciate you this thing is
really good I keep going for a while
okay so today's stream I think you all
can tell what it is by now I don't need
to elaborate
um I have a lot of things that I'd like
to talk to and I also don't want to
waste your time so
um
I hope you'll be patient with me as I
try and answer every single question
everybody has asked but I have I have a
list of stuff that I wrote down
beforehand uh which I hope you guys
uh I the thing is I tried to think of
questions and like topics that I think
the majority of you would all ask me
that way we can eliminate any repeat
stuff
um and all that oh bye okay thank you
for reading me again
if you guys don't know okay you really
should know okay just saying
but yeah I um
I came up with stuff already I like I
said don't want to waste your times and
and Moonies because time is Moonies so
um
beef before before I actually start
talking about stuff
oh Spanish thank you for the demo let's
start the donation fun to get me a third
monitor I just got my second it is not
even done yet
it's not even done yet I haven't even
set it up yet I'm still streaming on one
monitor right now I'm sorry
I need the cables okay I don't have it
yet uh hopefully this doesn't kill my
ears oh gosh
um let's turn that on oh yes you got
some nice cozy bgm
uh let me set this up for myself first
I'm sorry I'm not as organized as I
usually am today woman
I'll make it really really quiet make it
really really really quiet to the point
that even I can't hear it okay okay
anyway uh I hope you all had a good day
first of all
um I certainly had
a time
so uh okay I I'm gonna just tell you a
quick recap of my day because I need to
rant about it a little bit before I can
even talk about anything else so
uh yesterday my bank account almost got
hacked so
my my not credit card I don't have a
credit card yet my debit card got
deactivated and three thousand dollars
were gone from my account so I went to
the bank today to get a new debit card
and uh the people there were just like
so your old card is still under
investigation we don't know if we're
gonna be able to get back your three
thousand dollars and you're gonna learn
later today uh in the Stream because I
will talk about this but three thousand
dollars
is about the same amount that I it's
honestly
I hate to say it but three thousand
dollars
is about three to four months worth of
streaming income okay you're gonna learn
more about that later I'm I'm gonna show
you guys my analytics but three to four
months of streaming with how often I
stream
is a pain in the ass to have to think of
losing and it's I've been really anxious
about it
but I hope I will get it back I really
don't know when that will be but I'm
just gonna pray with my life that I will
get it back
otherwise I'ma cry
and it is a big chunk of money and you
know people can earn that really fast
sometimes but for me no for me no though
that was my hard earned three thousand
dollars over three to four months okay I
will talk about more about income that's
one of the topics that's on my list of
stuff but okay yeah I just had to rant
about it and I got hit on by a high
schooler today okay I got hit on by a
high school and I was trying to get my
Starbucks drink when I went to the bank
and I went to the mall that was next to
the bank and then for lunch I wanted
Starbucks and then the freaking high
schooler who was working at Starbucks
tried to hit on me and they yeah okay
I've had a day
what kind of day guys
I just it's been it's been a day
when you have my full-time salary oh God
I don't know yeah bye
by the Christmas shows okay also I have
um what's it called slow no not slow
mode I have uh uh ultra low latency so
Chad should be relatively fast today
uh I'll try and keep up with it but like
I said there's a lot of things that I'd
like to get through and I I'm trying to
make sure I save questions for the end
but
um I'll also have the question thing up
and I'll try to answer any uh as we go
uh so I'm not I don't think I'll be able
to get through any of the first ones at
the moment considering how I'm pretty
sure that some of the questions that are
here is something I'm gonna answer
because uh looking at it all yeah Ray
Lewis why why are you so cute that's
your question because I Was Born This
Way
okay
um
me
change this
let's change that uh to how I started
because I think that's pretty important
how you even become a full-time YouTuber
like more
um let's see here
so I guess I'm pretty sure there's a lot
of new people in my chat today and hello
hello nice to welcome you to the chat
you are now in minodachi and you're not
leaving okay
uh but hello if you don't already know
me I Amino you can call me me uh I am a
Immortal human uh angel in training and
I uh
have a big hammer yes okay
okay are the alerts done now no it's
good that that took a long time holy
[\h__\h]
also this is incented and it's bothering
me I'm sorry this is nice to meet you
nice to meet you too anybody who's new
here hello and everyone who's been
around for a while also hello any luck
into it here also hello hi fix one
bedroom you can't fix a pet then fix but
you don't need to fix a pet and pet on
his life Monk
Punk
no wrong one [\h__\h] okay
okay hello folk hello I usually like to
say hello to everybody at the beginning
of the stream but Chad's kind of been
going too fast for me to say every
single name uh but yes hello hello to my
Lakers to the Chatters to other
YouTubers who want to know what it's
like to be me
this is a real fast chat usually my chat
rate is like a two now it's 12.
you're like okay Unicode hello
think
thank you for the donut though
still readable I'm trying I'm trying
okay so
um
I started streaming not full time last
year when I was still in University so
um last year January in March that's
when I decided that I would become a
YouTuber and at the time I was in fourth
year finishing off University
um and that was my fourth year so me
um what else I was studying Healthcare
I have a degree in something healthcare
related I don't really want to explain
what it is for privacy reasons oh yeah
thank everybody distraction
thank you thank you that is a
distraction noodle what the [\h__\h] because
I I do have a degree in something
healthcare related if you don't already
know by now and
um to give you a better idea my minor is
in physiology
so yes I was on the path to become a
healthcare practitioner and during
finals I got really stressed out
and I was like I need an outlet so I
actually ended up getting into V tubing
so
um
for I started PNG tubing around
April May early May early May oh
[Music]
Dr me I'm not a doctorate I can't be
called a doctor that would be illegal
um yeah that's how I got interview
tubing is I needed an outlet and if you
don't already know my backstory and my
history and
the shitty uh Health uh condition I have
well
that's okay but that's also part of the
reason why I went into V tubing in the
first place
so
in the beginning PNG and then about a
month later I became a cheap baby tuber
and then I was a cheap YouTuber up until
last year November 2020.
and I debuted a full big model uh a bit
lower quality and cheaper than the one I
currently have by like three times but
um I use that model for a very long time
up until this year in April I believe
I think
maybe less
I think it was less
I don't know somewhere around there I'm
getting times a bit mixed up because
it's been so long uh but I got monetized
uh this year
I reached 1K also this year
so when we look at analytics later you
will see the time frame and how long it
took for me to get to 1K
and uh the amount of subscribers I had
the type of uh like the growth that I
had in the audience that I had well
we'll look into that a lot later so
don't worry I'm just trying to give you
like a very quick summary of my
streaming career so far so it doesn't I
don't look like someone who doesn't know
what she's doing
okay
so uh this year in June so June 4th that
is when I debuted this model
uh we'll talk about model pricing and
stuff as well when I talk about income
uh and then
I've been streaming since yeah
around last year in November that is
when I went completely full time
so for about
I'd say
from
April till November I was working as a
research assistant
and the November onwards I was full-time
youtubing
oh cozy congrats for packing
congratulations please fly safe and text
me when you land okay I love you too
mwah
yes
yeah so um
I guess
it was really strange to go from working
at a clinic and then going into research
in healthcare like healthcare stuff was
that was my life I grew up around it and
then I dropped it all for vetubing in
November when uh I actually don't I
don't think I hit 1 000 subscribers yet
at the time but I dropped it anyway
which is honestly very sketchy very very
not well planned of me but again part of
The Learning Experience you can't be a
full-time YouTuber right off the bat
okay but uh yeah that is how I started
uh
uh I guess what can we talk about after
that
um you dropped your job this summer it
is a very scary thing if you don't if
you're not a YouTuber you may not know
what it's like to have that like okay
it's all or nothing you know it's very
scary to have to drop something that you
worked so hard for I went four years
University never took a break even in
the summer I took summer school all four
months also worked the job I had my
clinic job and you know I was on the
path to get my Master's Degree
but no no I did not apply to go to my
master's last year because I decided to
go full-time youtubing and uh
I know a lot of people are very worried
about telling their family that they're
streamers or that they're a YouTuber in
any capacity
I ended up telling my parents uh that I
was a YouTuber
uh when I got monetized this year I
think that was around March I believe
that was in March if it wasn't March
then it was probably the month after
yeah
and I will talk about my experience with
telling my parents with uh the whole
experience of getting monetized how that
influenced everything and how I saw my
youtubeing career I will say that when I
started I did not view V2 being the same
way that I as I do now
and it's taken a very long time for me
to develop the habits that I have
developed the community that I have
developed everyone has different values
and niches when it comes to youtubing so
maybe what I'm about to say
is not going to be your thing and you're
not going to want to do it or you don't
want to learn from it and that's okay I
am just gonna impart hell I became a
YouTuber
I don't expect anyone to do the exact
same because everyone's journey is
different
and you know it's it's all about
learning I guess I'm still learning
there's still things I don't know if I
should do or not but yeah okay
let's let's get into the nitty gritty
okay
so
hi that mother I think models are
probably one of the biggest things you
notice about Victory so let's start with
that
praising to budgeting
money in this world sadly is very
important
oh hey Rosa hello hello what you doing
here hi
I hope you're having a fun time
it's okay so if you want to be a
full-time YouTuber well it will be
you're gonna need a bottle
and um I was still in school at the time
and when I started so money was tight
money still is tight
but
um I decided to design my model and not
pay a lot of money for it
so I drew my own PNG to start
that cost me no money because I had my
iPad already and I have a background in
art so I was able to design my own stuff
was able to draw my own emotes was able
to draw my own Badges and other stuff
like that if I ever had to I also Drew
my own overlays at some point so
girls done everything
and I wasn't good at digital art at the
time I was horrible at it
but that was no excuse for me I was like
I have the tool in front of me
I can do it if I want to
I just didn't really bother beforehand
to really learn more about digital art
um and it's very difficult to try and
learn something
off from the beginning because I'm a
traditional artist originally I did
watercolor and uh painting stuff I never
really did
uh digital and that's a completely
different
uh type of art medium
so
starting off I designed my own model
with a sketch and it was very hard I
tried to draw a live 2D model but it was
just something I couldn't grasp I was I
had a lot of trouble it was making me
really frustrated so I decided to
commission somebody
and that person
took over
six months
to give me my model
the person I commissioned was the one
that that model that I got I debuted in
November last year it was like the big
had oppai model
and I was getting really impatient
already a month in because they were
just still not doing anything I was just
like did I get ripped off
so I found someone else to make me a
chibi model for the time being
which was honestly improv it was
probably a better idea for me because
it meant that I could be very very chill
and I had a feeling that uh with my
background and how I grew up
that's kind of cute
that's the vibe I wanted to go for so I
never swore on stream I never
yeah I never swore on stream but I never
did anything on say so I just had a fun
time
and uh my family had no idea that I was
streaming they would just assume that
every night I would be
playing games with my friends until 4am
in the morning
and it was it was really awkward to
explain like yeah I have to be awake at
that time you know totally not strange
yeah all right let me show you the GP
model
since I'm talking about it
I'll I'll take the time to show you guys
what it was uh pretty sure it was this
one
this was a this costed me like
less than a hundred and fifty dollars
pretty cheap model but very cute very
cute yeah this is this was a long time
ago this is how I started
yay
it was a while ago
I haven't used this model since last
year so yeah look at all look at all
this uh I've had over time I had the
multiple
outfits
how do I get rid of this I wish I could
get rid of that that's another one and
then I had uh this one
a lot of different outfits thanks to
very generous donations that my viewers
gave me
yes uh and then after that I had this
one I'm just zooming through these
really fast this is the one that took
six months but I designed the outfit
myself okay yeah bake it make it and
then uh in June I got this one which is
a big upgrade very big upgrade takes
forever to load because it's so big
yes that is how this is my journey of
how many models I've had and the types
of models I've had okay
so
um I know what it's like to be a PNG a
chibi and a cheap model Nano and
expensive bottle I've had experience
with all of those
which I think is a lot I think it's
quite a lot of experience so yeah
PNG model oh uh
uh let me show you guys that hold on I
gotta go through my files
give me a second I saved it in this like
a folder behind all of the other things
uh reactive PNG
listen
yeah I started out with this
this is how I started I think it's best
master with the mega expensive model yes
and I I agree very much very very much
I also have a closed mouth version and
like an O shaped mouth version but yeah
that's that is my Beginnings
um
first time seeing it really
description oh it was you're right
yeah
little thing I still have the Fang that
is something that I never got rid of
ah you see it
[Music]
yeah I I kept it because I really
enjoyed it it was the kusogaki vibe and
I know I have the kusagaki vibe very
educational
okay so blue purple all the way yeah and
yellow and yellow
and that's how that's how I started so I
know what it's like to be all of those I
know what it's like to be very small
with only 50 subscribers for a long time
again we'll go through analytics later I
promise
um but that was those are my those are
my beginnings and I cherish the
experiences that I had during that time
a lot because I cannot imagine
like what it would be like to just shoot
up the Fame with no experience I'm so
glad that I decided to go with the root
of
slowly growing and not instantly just
trying to take off and spend all my
money it was incredibly difficult to
learn everything
yeah I think it's a mistake that a lot
of people make is they throw in money to
get the best model they possibly can and
it goes down the drain because maybe
they want to Rebrand or they have to
restart and a good thing
oh welcome goodie
yeah I've had a very slow growth again
you will see in uh when I talk about
analytics and I'll show you my analytics
too I found out some settings I'd like
to show you guys
yeah
you're here hi I saw your question
I'll talk about my daily schedule in a
bit I I have I have that as a topic
after this uh but yeah that was my model
that was my model uh
uh history yeah I think it takes time
not money even the biggest blue plus you
have been streaming videos exactly
exactly it takes so long to get the
algorithm to love you forever it takes
forever and ever and um I kept streaming
very frequently I'll tell you guys about
my how frequent I streamed last year and
how it went forward from there okay
so uh when I was still working in
research last year I didn't stream every
single day like I do now
I used to stream every Monday Wednesday
and um either Friday Saturday I think uh
definitely throughout the weekend
but I didn't do uh streams every day
which I feel like I could have done but
didn't do uh because I was trying to
learn a lot of art behind the scenes and
uh getting emote commissions and stuff
started
yeah I don't like those abnormal
expectations I went in knowing that I
was gonna start out small and I expected
to start out small
going and thinking that you're gonna
make it right away and you're gonna earn
a [\h__\h] ton of money is not the way to go
about it
I think a lot of my chat can tell by now
I don't stream for the money if I stream
for the money I would have quit a long
time ago it's okay
once you look at my income you will see
okay I don't earn a lot I do not earn a
lot I stream as often as a full-time job
but no I do not earn a lot
and yeah we'll we'll talk more about
that later I promise
Okay so if you don't go into V tubing
genuinely wanting to just have fun make
content
you're not gonna last you're gonna like
fall off the edge of a cliff and just be
like nope this ain't for me goodbye you
know so I would highly suggest not not
doing it for namuni and if you don't
have fun youtubing your chat's not gonna
have fun watching you and it's just you
know yeah
but over the time like
finding what I loved and how I wanted to
structure my content took so much
experimentation
like last year I was so Zazzle and I
didn't swear on stream I would always
say shoot instead of [\h__\h] like I tried
so hard to be as safe so as possible and
family friendly
Look At Me Now
I I swear on stream I make sex joke I am
unsay so and if I wasn't unsafe so I
wouldn't have had commissioned different
outfits that have more skin show me okay
now you talk about too much Piggy finger
exactly if you know you know
okay so uh originally I I really was
just I knew to go into vtubing thinking
that it was just a hobby and I'm not
gonna earn much from it it's just a way
to kill time while I'm working
and um slowly took off I was getting a
little bit more income I was earning
maybe like a hundred per month when I
started not through super chats and
anything obviously but it was through
stream elements because that's I'm gonna
talk about income again later but uh
that's how I started earning income
first
then I got a little bit of Arc missions
which boosted me up a bit and obviously
my real-time like real life job was
earning me more money than
being a YouTuber but I hated it I hated
being in research I hated doing clinical
research because it was boring as heck I
was reading scientific journal articles
every single day doing APA format
referencing and
my gosh I hated it so much reading every
intro and summary and Method section
stats and conclusions P values and
I just I I was not having fun
I loved being able to work in healthcare
but my God I hated it so much I remember
like
being told that I look too young to be a
healthcare practitioner that people are
going to mistake me as a kid they're not
going to take me seriously if I ever
been to become a doctor
uh when I worked in a clinic and I was
actually you know working with patients
a lot of them would question me if I was
old enough to be doing the examinations
I was doing on them like if I was
allowed to be handling the technology
that I was working around and
sucked ass man
okay it
being told that while I'm working and
earning money like
that I should not be here
trying to gain experience to become some
kind of doctor in the future
I was like I hate this I don't care how
much money it's gonna give me I hate
this
so
when I turned to youtubing and I noticed
how like I was genuinely having fun with
it and I could earn at least some income
from it
I was like okay I'm gonna drop the
healthcare stuff there was there's no
way that I'm gonna stay here
at least for now
there's a lot of emotional fatigue so
much fatigue oh God my hours were [\h__\h]
as well okay I sometimes woke up at four
in the morning sometimes I had to wake
up at 5 pm to get to work for a night
shift it was
really damn hard
oh Rosie buns I see your question I will
answer that when I get to the section
when I talk about it trust I'll get
there
yeah I
I don't want to get into that too much
because it's honestly makes me triggered
but yeah
and you're just like awesome what a
great start right the emergency room
the ER was just it was hell and they say
to be in healthcare you need to have a
very strong mental
capacity and you can withstand a lot of
the you know you have to think on your
feet and I could do that I'm not gonna
lie I was pretty good at it
but I did not like it I couldn't say
that I want to do this for the rest of
my life no I can say I would want to be
a YouTuber for the rest of my life yeah
but I couldn't save that for healthcare
stuff no
so I came into Healthcare I came out of
healthcare and I came into V tubing
instead because V2 being genuinely felt
like something I wanted to do and I
could earn money from it and I felt that
if I genuinely worked hard enough for it
I would be able to make it a full-time
job
and I guess
when like last year uh when I worked a
full-time real person job and then
also part-time streaming on the side I
was like okay no I'd rather I'd rather
not do the the full-time gig I'd rather
just be full-time YouTuber
YouTube's slow on the notifications
today huh rip I hope that's okay though
okay so I talked about the model
I talked about how I thought about going
into it I didn't think I'd go into V2
being I become full-time no I went in
thinking that I was gonna be part-time
forever and ever
yeah oh thank you I'm honestly skipping
over a lot of things because this is
just a summary of stuff on how I started
we still have more to get through trying
to be fast
I talked about my Healthcare stuff oh uh
social media quick briefing on that I
guess we can do uh I started Twitter
last year and no I started Twitter
November 2020 when I wanted to play
Animal Crossing and I posted a lot of
Animal Crossing stuff
I turned that account into a v tubing
account
uh I started off with
50. maybe even less like 20 20 followers
did not have a YouTube account yet
join the Discord server
met a [\h__\h] ton of great people
only ended up staying friends with about
10 of them which is now the higamana
Familia which is also kind of like a
mini YouTuber group that's not official
in any way whatsoever
yeah
they're still my best friends in the
vitamin Community to the till this very
day
and
I think I gained about 100 followers
from that
was that the one I met you on yes yes it
was you're one of the 10 friends
and then um yeah I've known Toto for a
very long time when I didn't even have a
YouTube channel yet
although I am sure that you are one of
the first like 20 subscribers I had on
YouTube Trust
and um
I had I think it's all on my phone I
think but I gained a thousand
subscribers sometime earlier Maybe
like around winter time last year I
think yeah question mark and until now I
only just gained up to two thousand so
I used to really worry about my Twitter
following count
but then my YouTube number started
increasing and that's when I was just
like hmm maybe I should focus on the
numbers on my actual mainstreaming
platform not Twitter because so many
people I see on Twitter have like 10K
20K followers and then their streaming
platform is like 8K 2K I'm like
so you're more of a v Tweeter than like
a streamer
it
it made me
concerned about
what to prioritize
if I should be networking and posting
stuff on Twitter to gain more viewers or
am I supposed to be streaming more often
and posting more stuff or you know
making shorts and other stuff on YouTube
like I did not know it made me hella
confused
but then I ended up
doing what I thought was correct and
focusing more on my mainstreaming
platform which shot me up from 1K to 2K
and then now we're at 3K oh there I
think your principal champion thank you
thank you but yeah that's how Twitter
was for me I ended up seeing Twitter as
just like a [\h__\h] post dump place for me
now it's where I post my going live
tweets to connect with other YouTubers
I rarely follow viewers on Twitter
because I see Twitter as a vetoing
Network platform not a
me to viewer platform it's more of if I
want to interact with my viewers I will
do that on YouTube primarily
4K soon no way there's no display we
just got to 3K like a month ago you're
funny
but okay that was that let me talk about
my daily schedule I'm gonna change the
this
day in the life of a full-time YouTuber
because I think that sums it up about
how I got here
uh through a lot of hard work but
there's there's my daily you know daily
schedule first we'll talk about weekly
after
my Twitter before you should
3.99 oh holy [\h__\h]
holy book okay let me know when it hits
4K we'll celebrate together yeah
okay okay
uh daily schedule daily schedule okay so
um
obviously every day
is different I have a life outside be
tubing too you know this is like the
same if you work with real-time job you
have a life outside of your real-time
job too I am the same I'm the same I
have a life
so
um
my day starts at around 10 to 11 A.M in
the morning
I wake up
I
wake up with my dogs I pet them I cuddle
them
uh I go wake up brush my teeth wash my
face do skin care
and then I carry my doggos downstairs
for breakfast
and I watched some TV with them you know
just chilling just slow easy morning
that's how I usually am
and then I have lunch eat
you know be
be healthy uh make different food every
day but I do not make instant noodles
okay
I'm more cultured and healthy than that
so for about I guess I eat lunch up
until like one to two p.m I take my time
all right
and then
um I draw for a majority of the
afternoon I either draw or I come up
with streaming ideas or I
uh go and help out my family because uh
some family members that are within my
neighborhood we all kind of live close
together uh
some of them need rides to go to places
they need help translating stuff
so I end up being the one oh okay guys
thank you forgetting yeah I end up being
the one to help my family out driving
them to Banks or something like that
yeah
uh especially my grandparents because I
mean my grandparents they can drive and
stuff on their own but if they're doing
things that might need some help with
translation uh like Bank stuff for
example
that's when I would go with them or if
they're meeting I don't know like
lawyers for stuff or uh they want to go
traveling and things like that like I
will I will help my grandparents or my
aunts and uncles and stuff sometimes I
even pick up my cousins from school if
my aunts and uncles can't make it oh hi
Carla
uh but yeah that that's what I do in the
afternoon
sometimes I might meet up with a friend
so that we can do art together at a cafe
or uh just to catch up with them and
stuff so I have a social life I have a
family too
look after and
care for okay
and then
um I sometime in the afternoon I will go
work out typically between four ish
starting four to five about an hour
grocery
yeah that's me
and hello
I do touch grass I know I but why do you
think I haven't burnt out I have I
haven't stopped streaming like at all I
think I've been streaming every single
day since November
I haven't taken a break
okay yes I've gone traveling but that
was less than three days and three days
is sometimes a regular part-time
streamer schedule all right I stream
every [\h__\h] day
e
so
um after I work out and stuff I go make
dinner I make the rice and I shower
after I made the voice I have a workout
thing in my basement so we ate
wait did I get the 4K we got the 4K bye
[Music]
thank you guys for 4K we'll celebrate
another day I promise now is not the
time but thank you
again
[Music]
ah you guys are so sweet
mama
oh bongola thank you for the sofa
thank you
[Music]
thank you guys
Neil thank you for the super 495
Japan
oh wait I don't think I made a Discord
hold on did I make a Discord
I mean Discord
to command that's the word right let me
let me add a Discord command for you
because because I feel like I should I'm
sorry that I didn't do that
I'll make a disco thing for you please
no limit never expired coffee
uh
[Music]
hold on I'm trying to be fast
okay I made a Discord command this
should work now oh [\h__\h] welcome to the
membership thank you
last night thank you for the super four
kilometers
we go in we're going places
hello
goodbye you're a copia member
yes I am the copium
I I need copy
wait a minute
[Music]
okay okay where was I where was I oh
anyway thank you for joining the
membership thank you thank you
okay I gotta get back to telling this
stuff I'll never stop otherwise oh gosh
uh okay okay so I make I I work out from
four o'clock to around six
okay I do not know what that says button
button something
[Music]
yes I did
laughs
oh thank you also welcome anybody who
just subscribed and became a member
again thank you thank you
uh okay where was I oh yeah yeah so so
uh uh
what was it oh yeah workout from four
until six ish I make rice around 6 30.
and then I shower uh by the time I come
down my parents are home so we make
dinner together
then we eat together
and I spent some time with my family
um
sometimes not a lot of time though
because I've been starting streams at
9pm EST
so uh I only get to see my family like
my my direct family like mom dad sister
I only get to see them for about
two hours if they come home at seven
I get to see them for about two hours
and then I have to stream so
even though we live in the same house I
hardly see my family which kind of sucks
uh there are some days though where I
don't stream at night uh some other
alternatives to that daily schedule
would be wake up at 9 50.
brush my teeth and get ready for the day
and stuff I stream at 10. up until I
have to go make lunch I make lunch I eat
uh do the same things in the afternoon
like helping out my family doing art
um planning streams
and then a workout or chill even more
and be a potato uh make dinner a bit
earlier so that when my parents come
home it's all done and uh you know they
don't have to work too hard and stuff
I get to spend the night with my family
and then I will either talk to some
friends so that I maintain my you know
outside of youtubing relationships or I
will talk to some YouTuber friends and I
try and maintain those relationships
around too because I am very bad at
interaction I'm a big introvert so
I like to make sure I set some time in
my day to talk to people
it is very important for your mental
well-being being even if you don't think
it is like some people are like oh no I
don't need I don't want to talk to
people I like being an introvert we
don't need to go out like I I want to
just stream and be on my own and work
and stream be on my own and work but no
I think it's I genuinely think if you
don't want to burn out you need to rent
to somebody you need to be able to find
people that you can talk to about that
kind of thing like it's very difficult
otherwise oh great thank you for being a
member for a month depending willing
thanks for being willing to share
details about you to me of course of
course of course
I feel like it's very rare to find the
small ndv tuber like myself that does it
full time
uh I've been very blessed with like you
know
being able to do it because I don't not
everybody has that privilege to be able
to do something like this full-time and
be supported by their family for it
I'll talk more about like my family
being involved and stuff like when I get
to it but yeah okay that's the daily
schedule
but if I talk about what I do during the
week
uh sometimes I'll be like uh I'll make
my my weekly like some weekly stuff that
I do I should say something I don't do
every day would be making a schedule to
post out I've only started doing that
recently uh for the majority of this
year I've just been streaming every
single day
at a specific time oh minutes thank you
for the planning
Victoria it is I'm trying to be as real
as I can I'm not giving you guys like
the fairy tale version of how to be a
full-time YouTuber there's no such thing
there's no such thing you gotta work for
it man
um
there's there's really no way to just
suddenly grow and be big it's it's not
like that you can't do that that's fake
whoever tells you that you could just
dream and grow
by streaming like once a month no no
that's fake no I'm giving you realism
maybe I'll get it yeah thank you thank
you schedules can be hard they can be
very hard I think you're very they're
very difficult to stick to sometimes
especially when things kind of just get
thrown in your face out of the way and
you're just like oh no I did not plan
that I get really anxious uh when
something doesn't go my way or something
happens that I don't expect like my bank
account being hacked that's something
that made me very anxious
but
um
I'm making a schedule for the past year
uh up until like three weeks ago or four
weeks ago I was streaming every single
day
starting stream between 9 and 10 pm
within that hour bracket I would
schedule the stream 15 to 20 minutes
before the stream started
and I I would just do I I wouldn't
schedule the stream a week in advance
because my schedule was kind of uh like
unpredictable at night sometimes my
family would come home late we would
have dinner a lot later than usual
sometimes we'd have it a lot earlier
than usual sometimes uh maybe we'd go to
like the drugstore to get some stuff and
then come back you know it's very wasn't
stable schedule but my viewers
were it was very clear to them that I
would stream between that time bracket I
would start streaming within that time
bracket so despite not having a schedule
I was able to have a very consistent
viewer average viewer count like it was
always I think uh in the beginning it
was
uh
in the like underneath five on average
last year
and then it went up to 10 uh in November
on average and then earlier this year
around March that's when it went up to
like 15. and then about sometime in the
summer it was in the 20s and then more
recently it's been the high 20s and 30s
but I think this particular month has
increased it to like 50 which is kind of
insane so yeah
consistency definitely printed and and
oh Andrew thank you thank you for the
dinner how much was that 20. oh nice
thank you thank you uh it feels like no
time at all since you debuted the new
model and hit monetization really the
type wait time really does fly when
you're having a great time 5K here we go
thank you Andrew thank you thank you
thank you thank you
because this is a dreamy time very
viewer friendly yeah like I didn't even
have to say that I would be streaming
they just my viewers just knew
thank you I've been trying hard man I've
been trying hard for a long time
welcome party here
okay thank you Olga
congratsun 4K thank you thank you you're
one of the most dangerous I've had the
pleasure of being introduced to Rosa
thank you I appreciate that you're one
of the most hilarious Mimi persons I've
ever met as well
thank you me I uh I've only grown
recently all right it hasn't
if I if I grew this fast like right away
I would not be calm streaming to 70
people at the same time all right that's
scary [\h__\h] imagine like okay you know
when you give class presentations
I'm the type to freak out and cold sweat
just speaking in front of my class
now I can speak to seven of you at the
same time and not break a sweat
shirt
[Music]
I mean I knew I knew I had the talents I
just needed the time to be able to hone
them and somehow show them
somehow show them not seeing faces helps
oh it helps so much and I guess like if
you just don't look at the number and
you look at chat talking it feels like
there's less people so you don't stress
out as much just I know a lot of people
are like oh I want to see I want to see
more people come to my streams but I'm
not gonna lie that's a lot of pressure
okay anyway anyway
um so I now make weekly schedules I make
my streams well this week I've done a
lot of morning streams and I think I'm
gonna keep it up because I found out
that I still get very high viewerships
in the morning so I will stream in the
morning more frequently nowadays I know
I don't normally do because I like to
take my mornings very slow but for some
reason you guys like it when I stream in
the morning so I will stream in the
morning for you
it's so much sweat we sweat so much but
the mornings change they're nice for
Europe
that is that is very nice to know very
nice to know I won't be able to do them
every day but I will try my best to do
more I promise I promise
I'm not a certainly at night though
everything else Asian friendly yeah I
can't wait till daylight savings isn't a
thing so I can do them more often
but yeah weekly weekly I make my
schedules
um
I also think of shorts that I can make I
sometimes might even take the entire
afternoon just making it short because
those take time to make very good I edit
all my shorts myself I've never
commissioned anybody to edit for me or
hired anyone to edit for me like I
learned how to edit videos all on my own
just for youtubing I never did much
video editing prior to that
um what else
let us
okay Fred bye-bye thank you for coming
thank you for coming
[Music]
okay so that's the weekly scheduled
one of your morning shoes
mom Packer you're a few hours behind me
so it does it's okay if you can't make
it but if you can't make it I will
always welcome you
okay now uh is there a particular topic
you guys might want to talk about after
this I have a list of stuff uh I'm gonna
check the
uh
questions here to see if I can
uh enter any of these
uh okay some of them are a bit different
let's see
um networking stuff
stuff uh day-to-day stuff I already
talked about that call that many
YouTubers oh that comes after I'll talk
about that more later
um
find yourself neglecting exercise more
easily as a YouTuber no because I still
exercise regularly I exercise at least
four times to five times a week I have
apps
um let's see
[Music]
all right okay
I think the next one's income looking at
the questions I think
I think we can talk about income and how
I decided to spend my income
uh
and then how it came into V tubing so to
stream
you need a PC
it is very difficult to stream on a Mac
very difficult okay
so uh let me change this to oh oh maybe
a better word is budgeting
but is that how you spell budgeting guys
I don't know how to English anymore
I think this is the right way to spell
it
budgeting budgeting
budgeting
Mac yeah so all my life I have been a
Mac User
I got into V tubing when I still had a
MacBook Pro and no other laptop or
computer that was not Apple
I did spell it right right okay so
it's what I wanted to become a YouTuber
I was like oh no
oh no
and I told my parents Mom Dad
can I have a PC can I have a desktop
computer and they were like why do you
need one and I'm like well
my laptop is slowly breaking down
because the screen had like a black line
across it when I dropped it
and they're like okay well if we get you
that then we're not gonna get you
another laptop but I was like
that's okay with me and they're like
wouldn't it be easier if you just bought
a pre-built PC and I was like no no I'm
gonna make my own PC so I went online to
find out what kind of PC specs Hollow
I've had
and there's this one the Minecraft
streams like it shows the the thing and
there's like a screenshot of it I looked
at all of it and I was just like okay if
they have those specs then maybe I can
have this and this and this and this and
I'll be okay you know
that's that's how I that's how I decided
yeah
I didn't look at like okay only until
after I decided exactly what I wanted
did I look at if it was compatible or
not I went on to like the PC part picker
thing and
um I you know I just wasn't sure how
much power I needed to be a YouTuber at
the time considering I only ever had Mac
knowledge prior to it
I didn't know where to begin I also
didn't know who to ask because all of my
friends also did not have anything else
but Mac
yeah they were so expensive
I have a story about that oh my God
but um I had a budget for my PC
uh it was
underneath the price of a Macbook laptop
which is about 2 000 Canadian dollars
in U.S I think that's a thousand eight
hundred one thousand five hundred ish I
think just for the PC
so I uh
tonight okay so I went on to the PC part
Baker went on to Amazon went on to
Newegg and Best Buy and all of that I do
live in Canada so we have Canada
Computers which is actually very nice
and my parents paid for it they paid for
the PC itself they didn't pay for the
monitor
they didn't pay for a keyboard or Mouse
they didn't pay for any of the mic stuff
my XLR stuff stream deck they did not
pay for any of that no they only paid
for the PC parts like the case
motherboard CPU GPU
and power supply
they didn't pay for anything else
I had to pay for all of that stuff
from my own pocket which was another
chunk of money go bye-bye but at the
time please remember I was still working
so I had the money and I knew it
wouldn't make a dent in my account so it
was safe to do that
and someone asked me what my PC specs
are it is a well CPU is 3600 uh the AMD
thing
um graphics card is a RX 5600 XT my case
is I think it's a Vietnamese one it's
white with like the nice RGB on the
front
uh power supply 750 watts from I think
it's something Sonic yeah I don't
remember uh my motherboard is the Asus
tough gaming one that has Wi-Fi but I
never use the Wi-Fi which was kind of
dumb to get it but yeah at the time
actually no when I started streaming I
didn't have an Ethernet cable so
uh I had to get the Wi-Fi now I use any
ethernet cables don't worry I have
better wi-fi now but those are my PC's
bags uh and then
my mouse is the Razer Viper thingy
that's why everyone in Wireless I have a
an echo
keyboard no the one I got before what
was it I just remember the keyboard I
had before was less than a hundred
dollars hot swappable with
uh gather on Brown switches it was white
and pink and green very small
[Music]
um
yeah it was all really cheap
and then my mic
I knew I wanted good audio
and I wanted the best that I would never
have to upgrade if I ever wanted to
upgrade from USB to to a
XLR I could so I got the shore MP7 and
in Canada that is very expensive but I
bought it anyway
and I used all USB functions first
because I got a better keyboard I have
an echo keyboard now it's acrylic and
it's got jelly white switches and
cinnamon roll keycaps and it's very cute
yes so
um
I yeah I started with USB mic mode first
and then earlier so I think no like last
year ish maybe or earlier this year I
got gifted the wave XLR and the stream
deck by very very nice mods thank you
thank you
uh so yeah it's not the sure sm7b no no
because I needed the USB function first
so
um
yeah I
I only changed the XLR earlier this year
I admire this year every day it is so
nice it's
awesome
oh thank you thank you thank you yeah uh
that's how my my setup got upgraded yes
yes okay uh
so I didn't spend too much my PC was at
the underneath a thousand eight hundred
dollars uh
the mic I didn't want to have to keep
buying new mics to save myself the time
and money so I bought a really nice mic
from the beginning
uh Mouse and stuff I was already I
already knew I had to spend a lot for it
so didn't matter to me I knew it wasn't
an FPS gamer or anything so I didn't
need something that was like 200 yeah
um monitor well you guys know I have one
big monitor it is 31.5 inches from Asus
and it is curved I don't remember how
much it was but I have that monitor
and then I bought a new one recently
which I haven't set up yet
uh yes I know okay audio is very
important you're right as I hit so so
important
I don't know how to pronounce that thank
you for subscribing
I uh
how do you put this like
models are models they have they can
either have really you know subpar
rigging to really nice rigging that
costs a lot of money
and the other thing is
your voice
streaming is a lot of audio that goes
into your computer and out to someone
else's ears it's basically what
streaming is you know as a YouTuber you
may not have subtitles on or like the
the voice to text thing for everybody to
see like captions right so
to me my voice being captured was very
important to me I also knew I wanted to
record like covers and stuff so yeah
both media thank you for subscribing
thank you
uh so that's yeah that's that's how
that's how I decided to choose my parts
and streaming gear
uh who I think one of the questions was
who inspired me to be a YouTuber it was
at first gura then Kiara so Kiara is
like my Kami Oishi and my cubby oh she
gave it to my tree so I'm very happy my
life goal has been complete okay anyway
um
okay
uh let me change the theme
so that's how I bought stuff my first
model I will run through this really
fast
because this I don't think I need to
spend too much time on everybody has
their own ideas of how much is expensive
and how much is considered cheap so um I
will just give you guys as much
bass line stuff uh I can as for price of
models okay
yeah I came into my stream she chatted
in my chat
yeah anyway that's that's that's
something for later that's not that's
not the topic we did but yes
okay
um chibi model you saw earlier as I said
it was around 150 dollars
in the US all of this is going to be USD
um and then the uh
other outfits after that were fifty
dollars each outfit rigging was slowly
increasing in price because it got more
complex and my usual rigor increased her
pricing so uh it went from
I think based from 50 to like 150 and
yeah so it's slowly increasing
increasingly got expensive
but that's kind of to be expected when
people upgrade their skills and stuff
right yes you should be patient and nice
to your artists and rigors when you're
commissioning models as always okay
it's very hard to be an artist art blogs
happen and wrist starts to get in pain
when you draw a lot always be respectful
and give your artist as many references
and preferably a color palette when
you're commissioning them because it
makes their life a lot easier okay
yeah
so uh all my TV models were under 200
dollars
yeah each okay uh and then
I made a rule for myself
I had to be able to spend like
I I how do I even put this
however much I earned
in a month was how much in half I was
allowed to spend on youtubeing
activities because I wanted to profit
from vtubing not have a net loss of
negative something something something
okay
oh the wandering Helms man thank you for
subscribing
if you guys like it they often do more
than answers yes they do they really do
I do as an artist myself I will do more
can you enables it's not fun not fun for
your wallet it's fun for you not your
wallet
so um
if I earned a hundred within a month
cut that in half that's fifty dollars I
was allowed to spend on streaming
whether it be at games or saving up for
a model or saving up for new overlays or
like
yeah
but then once I became full-time that
rule became much harder to commit to
because if I only earned 100 within a
month I had 50 to spend on daily
expenses as well so if I had to get a
full tank of gas
which is around fifty dollars for me
I'm done for the month I'm not allowed
to spend it on anything else I cannot
buy any new games cannot buy any new
snacks to eat you know I couldn't buy
new clothes I couldn't buy like new
glasses if I wanted to couldn't buy
makeup couldn't buy skin care none of
that
none of that I was very frugal very very
very very very very very very very very
frugal all right
and I had to be to survive otherwise I
would die
I mean obviously I had
if I earned 100 and I only use the 50.
if I went over that limit
I would be very strict with myself the
next month
and because I was also you know as a
full-time YouTuber I don't really have
to drive out often I was saving up on a
lot of gas
and that left me some spending room for
games or like other necessities like my
skincare shampoo conditioner you know
skincare hygiene yeah very important
so I
I was very strict with myself and how I
spent money and if my friends asked me
to go out I'm not gonna lie I typically
would say no because I'd be like let's
just play games together online so I
don't have to go out and spend money I
don't have to go out and you know buy
food that's way more expensive plus tax
which is 13
I was very strict and while it did help
my content it did it did make me lose
some close friendships and it slowly
feet slowly dwindled down but I was able
to keep a lot of the good ones at the
very least the neat shed in life yes I
had to be a niche and to be able to pay
for my models yes so
um overall over the course of streaming
before okay so to get this particular
model which is very expensive one I
think that's the one most people tend to
be curious about
I'll give you more details about this
one
last year in November december-ish I was
already planning this new model
I sketched it out
I colored it
I took about two weeks to find an artist
that I genuinely really loved the art
style of
I asked them how much it would be to
commission them for a model that had
this design and these expressions and
this hairstyle these outfits because I
knew I wanted to more than one outfit
and I also wanted
my hammer so I knew oh wait uh there's
also the the microphone that was
designed by then
I already knew that it was going to be a
lot more expensive than my original
models so I asked and it was about a
thousand six hundred to seven hundred
dollars a thousand six hundred seven
hundred just for the art alone
and when I thought about it that was the
amount of money that I had saved up
through streaming
for that duration of time that I was
streaming
and I was like okay
that's probably all right
and um actually no a bit less I'd say
it's half of it because then when I
calculated the price plus rigging which
was all about it was about the same uh
but because I was example a of being
good to your rigors and artists okay I
was very understanding towards my rigor
he had a lot of family problems going at
the time and I was like it's okay if you
delay it like it's okay it is fine
they gave me a discount
I didn't have to pay as much as it
originally was I had to pay only I had
to pay 200 I was allowed to pay 200 less
because of me being a very understanding
and nice client to my rigor okay
they're they're so good I love them
but um yeah my rigging was 1400 500 yen
my art was for the model was a thousand
six hundred seven hundred and
uh no I mean not yet USD what am I
saying so in total my model in its
entirety this particular model was about
3 000 US dollars
but again because I'm in Canada it's
actually a lot more expensive than that
it's probably like 3200 for me but yeah
that is how much my model cost and
the reason why I was willing to spend
that much is because I saved up that
much money
and then I also had some left over
because
I saved money
I set myself a budget goal and I kept at
it so even though I spent that much
money I had a net gain of some amount
remember this no
[Music]
yeah it does I didn't even ask for the I
didn't ask for any of that like the fact
that I can do this the fact that I can
make this fish
like I didn't ask for that I didn't ask
for the Jake Paul no but they gave it to
me anyway
there's so many things that I was given
just because I was a nice person all
right being nice goes a long way
the face is how it's this high quality
yeah
[Music]
um for me uh for other stuff that
involves
um streaming like assets and stuff
for the intro and ending screen I spent
two months drawing and animating it
myself the logo and background like
overlays gaming and chatting overlays
were gifted to me
my cuddle Orchestra screen was also
gifted to me by huffeny wonderful
wonderful graphic designer please go
commission and he is wonderful
um
and bgm I found online by myself it took
me three days of constantly just
listening to music trying to find the
one that suited the vibe that I thought
I vibed with the most
a lot of research a lot of time a lot of
research
at the time I was already full-time when
I was planning this model though and the
debut of this model so
it wasn't didn't like it felt
worth it you know
the other thing I animated was my lore
video made that by myself so I didn't
have to commission any art or like
someone to animate it for me I did it
myself
I need the art trades for human to
change they're not completely free okay
but like The Archers
he he gave me more than I gave him so it
wasn't a fair trade
but I'd like to say that it was a fair
trade
he gave me a logo for dancing he gave me
the logo he gave me the backgrounds like
I gave him like three pieces of Art
yeah I was able to trade because of that
um so that's the model pricing and
budgeting for Stuff where's your lure
video at in my debut
I never posted it separately because I
was embarrassed
it's very cute though it's I drew
everything right so it's very cute
uh okay so the next thing I should talk
about different types of income and how
much I earned
crash okay
um how long has it been oh gosh it's
already been over an hour I am so sorry
I thought it would have gotten farther
than that
uh I'm trying to get through all the
factual things first before I talk about
like building relationships with people
collabs and how to treat your job and
stuff and how more of like the
discussion type topics I'm gonna try and
leave till the end and get all the
factual stuff out there first so that
you will see my point of views on things
when I talk about it later I hope the
way I structure the stream makes sense
and if possible please time stamp it for
me so I can go back and add the channel
the chapters I mean for the islands
alone okay so uh I earned income income
from art not a lot I earned about a
hundred dollars in art income per month
if I even get the commissions okay do
not earn a lot from it it's a very like
small portion of my income because first
and foremost I am a full-time YouTuber
not full-time artist okay
I don't prioritize my art as much as I
prioritize streaming and I have my own
Theory where if you want to be a
YouTuber
streaming is your primary content shorts
highlight videos clips are secondary
peoples have it the other way around
sometimes where they make the clips and
the highlights their primary and
streaming is their secondary content but
my theory for me to grow and be as
successful as I am at the moment was to
stream primarily over all the other
stuff I do make the other stuff just not
as much
it is my way of doing things it will
everybody
it might work for you it might not like
that is how I did it
okay so that's the art part
um streaming income let me go to my
analytics so that I can show you all the
stuff
uh but I'm gonna be very careful about
it because I don't want to accidentally
dogs myself or something like that so
let me let me find that for you I didn't
pull it up beforehand uh here
uh
analytics there we go
okay
uh uh all right we're gonna just look at
it how do you guys we're gonna look at
this better be safe than sorry exactly I
don't want to give away things that I
don't want to give away you know I'm
gonna be careful about it uh
let me just double check the stoof real
quick honestly I might not really know
exactly what everything means but I will
show you
what I feel comfortable showing you okay
and that is probably just the main page
of income which is honestly what you
need oh lifetime
uh
oh this one
last seven days no that's not it last
month uh we can go through lifetime
first which is I guess when I got
monetized which was
April 13th
I think yeah okay we'll start we'll
start from there I'm gonna show you the
lifetime one I'm not gonna go through
too much I I feel like that'd be a waste
of time otherwise and let's do it over
here
oh look at Chad oh would not be able to
keep it keep up if it was actually that
fast why am I so tiny oh it's because I
was in the box yesterday that's why
they're here
uh
is that better I wanna be able to show
you guys stuff I don't want to get in
your way so okay I think that would do
it uh window capture
there we go
alrighty
this should be
a decent amount for you guys to see
I believe question mark
hope that's okay I'm gonna refresh this
holy
crap
please keep in mind I'm still doing it
on a uh you know one monitor setup all
right so uh there we have my income in
the Life in my lifetime that I've been a
streamer uh but because I didn't get
monetized on YouTube until this year in
April it's not actually the whole entire
time I've been streaming
okay I haven't earned this much uh this
is how much I've earned since April
April April April May what day is it
today I guess it's almost December so
April
April May June July August September
October November it's been nine months
so in nine months I earned five thousand
six hundred and eighty two dollars in
super chats this does not include
extreme elements uh Donuts because
that's my other stream of income I'm not
gonna show you that one today because
I'd like to keep that to myself but I'm
willingly showing you guys this okay
um
you guys want to know what that is
uh this one
yeah okay okay
so
um
I earned the most on certain streams but
yeah they they they're different oh he's
different
don't know stream elements don't knows I
uh let me think
oh
terrible
[Music]
thank you for the big dodo thank you
thank you get a second monitor hi
hi
honey
thank you thank you
I have one though I just got one I just
got one so this will this will recover
my bank account from having to spend
money on that second Monitor and all the
stuff that comes with it
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
okay oh my gosh uh yeah so I actually
prefer stream elements dodos over super
chats but I know super chats get shown
up on stream which make people feel
happy that they see themselves on the
stream so
like at the top of the the chat so like
I'm honestly okay with both
uh super Chads
I only get 70 like everybody else even
with memberships only get 70 of that
unfortunately but it is what it is and I
could I can't change that
okay those include memberships I think
so because if we scroll down
[Music]
top earning content in my life
yeah they're very specific to some
um so in the past months this is how
much I earn and it varies clearly
they're not all the same okay this is
only in the last six months and in the
last six months I've done decent this is
a lot to me okay for someone who was a
full-time YouTuber last year earning a
hundred dollars per month only to me
this is a lot this is
very very very very very much
so if I split this in half like
at least per month I have about like 200
300 to spend
this is a lot for me in my opinion
I know for some it might not seem like a
lot
but to me it's a lot for for being a
full-time YouTuber
uh and an indie at that to me this is a
lot more than I ever expected to earn
from Genie so now that we're here I get
to say thank you for letting me live my
best life
because streaming is my only income I
don't I don't have any other income
besides this clearly although if you
think about how much this is per month
it is not enough for me to live on for
the rest of my life
it is not enough for me to move out on
my own pay my own rent pay for insurance
pay for phone bills pay for everything
that I need to survive on my own
and I'm very lucky and happy that my
family let me live with them and they
still pay for groceries I don't pay for
groceries they still pay for a lot of
things for me to survive like water
bills electric bills
um electricity bills
a lot of bills
they still pay for all of that I only
pay for my car insurance and phone bills
uh but my family ends up paying for the
rest so I get to keep a lot of this
money
I don't have to pay for a lot of things
so I am in a position where I get to
save money
but it's I am doing good I am doing very
well I don't have a high viewer account
on average
not until this month
I've always had on average about 30
viewers
20 30 viewers
per stream
okay and I don't get a lot of super
chats I get a lot of P supers and got a
lot of water supers
but I don't get a lot of super jets and
I'm still able to earn this much which
is very surprising to me but I'm also
very thankful
it's only beginning yet I
I'm still a very humble person and I've
been told that it is a good and a bad
thing at the same time because to some
people it might not look like I'm
thankful enough for what I have or I
think that what I'm earning isn't a lot
but I think what I'm earning is a lot
a lot more than what other streamers who
have 30 viewers on average will earn
so I'm very proud of my community being
the community it is being very
supportive of me being very
understanding of me
or supporting what I do like it is
something that I
I don't think I'll I'll ever want to let
go of ever
that's how you're gonna call your
mentions because yeah this is what I
that's why I chose YouTube is because of
that particular reason is that
everything gets documented
that's quite a bit of money for this
number of concurrent views exactly and
it's actually very rare for me to get
viewership counts you'll see when I
click audience later uh that it's just
rare for me to get more than 30 viewers
on average so in this past month where
I've you know grown a lot I've been able
to earn
in bed I don't know why I earned so much
last month like nothing special happened
last month so I really don't know where
that came from
yeah
there's two holes
the fact that with 30 viewers on average
they're though within the 30 viewers I
am able to earn this much per month like
I can't imagine what it's gonna be like
when I grow I I don't I cannot predict
the future but this is how much I earn
per month okay in within my lifetime I
guess we can change it to like oh 2021
does it show anything okay nothing
I wasn't monetized until this year
yeah
maybe some other people were sent during
the same period I would hope so yeah we
can actually check that uh let's see but
yeah within this year alone this is how
much I've earned
uh you're a transaction Revenue within a
lifetime but this year technically
YouTube premium if you have YouTube
premium good for you because you don't
have to watch ads which I'm gonna start
putting on my streams after today
I've been told so much I need to do that
okay
um let's see estimated ad Revenue it's
not a lot not a lot please have YouTube
premium
it will give you more benefits
I don't have ads mostly but yeah there's
still some of those okay there we go
this is what you guys wanted to see
right how much I get from memberships
how much I get you know from gifted
memberships
cerebos must have
been a lot of that okay
he's gonna be there next month
um super thanks which is the comment
stuff super stickers and like the tiny
little super chants cannot believe I can
earn This Much from stickers alone what
the heck
interesting but that's like for the
entire year please remember that this is
not monthly this is not monthly this is
within the entire year that I've had
monetization on my channel okay
yeah yeah
I wasn't monetized last year so there's
no point in looking at 2021
but this is up until November which was
yesterday
yeah
you guys giving me a lot of gifted stuff
over the past year that I've been
monetized well a few months I've been
monetized and
if you want to look at the month we can
look at the month
this is this is November the breakdown
of November
but yeah I hope that gives you a better
idea of what I've earned uh we can check
a little October
I got a lot of super chats in October I
do not know why but cool
uh September got more Channel
memberships in September not as many
super chats see things are very very
inconsistent and I think that's to be
expected considering I am still very
small Indie vichuba with less than 10K
subscribers okay I am still tiny I do
not know how many how much money
corporate YouTubers make but this is how
much I make and at least I get to keep
the 70 I don't have to split my money
with anybody which is nice
3K in October
yeah
just in Super Chat and Jupiter alone uh
and uh okay so that's that's my income
okay I've given you a pretty good idea
of what that looks like I think I'm
being very open and honest about it I
don't think that I don't know how to use
advanced mode very well
sometimes they don't make that much by
the Indies I know I've been told that
but like I'm not 100 sure because
everybody's different times
I have to hit this average the average
amount of viewers like what is it 70 is
it 70 average viewers per screen that's
a [\h__\h] ton of viewers how many are
watching me now
oh holy [\h__\h]
that's the reason I make quickly use it
oh thank you thank you
thank you thank you I don't earn enough
to sustain myself if I lived alone so
yeah
yeah okay but this is my lifetime
earnings on YouTube all right
I've been very honest about it if you
want to know what it's like to be me
then
in terms of my financial stability it's
a lot so
going back to what happened to me
yesterday of my account being my bank
account being hacked and me almost
losing three thousand dollars and I'm
actually not sure if those three
thousand dollars are going to come back
into my bank account
you can see why that's about to make me
cry
three thousand dollars
is a lot of money to me
so when I went to the bank today and
they told me yeah we can get you a new
debit card uh and I asked them
what's happening to those three thousand
dollars that were about to be taken out
of my account
they said your card is still under
investigation we cannot guarantee you'll
get those three thousand dollars back so
obviously my heart is breaking
they said there's a great chance that it
will come back to me but it's not a
hundred percent certain
so
yeah yeah okay
I don't feel great about it I don't
think anybody would
but to me that is over half of the
amount of money that I've earned in the
past
time that I have had monetization which
is very scary
it's very scary
so let's just pray let's just pray that
the bank gives me my three thousand
dollars
and uh I I don't have to lose three
thousand dollars cross my fingers
no thank you guys I appreciate you
worrying about my bank account
that's a really weird thing to say
they stole from all of us yeah
technically that's all your money that
you've given to me
so I was I'm very scared
that's all my super chats and
memberships and super stickers and
YouTube premium and Moonies cries man
and it's a very good idea you get it
back but until they did an event you
gotta wait until yeah I have to wait to
know I really have to wait to know
yeah yeah it could be it really could be
but it is what it is it happened I can't
go back the only thing I can do is wait
and pray so
go in
okay uh we can check the audience stuff
oh wait you guys wanted to see my growth
right so see you live count
oh wow
hello the the extra what how many 120 of
you hello
um
hi welcome to my channel
thank you thank you thank you
that was not a sippy that was a few
gulps oh gosh I'm gonna put lip balm on
I've been talking a lot how you guys
feeling does this feel intimidating to
you yet does this look does this look
like a full-time YouTuber does this feel
good does it feel nice to be watching
are you learning things
I haven't even gotten to like the more
discussion type topics yet we're still
like on my first page of notes Here
very informative nice have you been
wondering where your money's been going
Starlight every time you give me a super
the girl maybe hey we're going places
let's go
anything with thunder for sure I haven't
even talked about what I have to work on
oh this did this go up
did this go up I feel like it went up
okay bye-bye
oh
I was like I swear I saw a different
number
thank you for whoever got me that extra
number thank you but okay this is in the
last 28 days and thank you Kiana for
doing this to my channel
are you Japanese
oh oh what's this oh Frozen is it thank
you for the super I mean not super don't
know it's a Dono thank you buttons for
lost Ones
thank you thank you I appreciate you
trying to hydrate my bank again
is it better
if you want you could try
you're here because of Kiana hands up if
you're a fellow kfp
maybe if you're ready I don't know how
someone could do it to me I've been so
careful with my bank account like it
happened out of nowhere I didn't even
like log into anything and yet it still
happened
hi Moon
I'm ready thank you kfbkp hey
[Music]
hello my fellow kfb champions
please tell me that Kiara's you're
coming or she because she's my Kami Oshi
do you know why I say I didn't do what
it's like being a full-time voice
actorship no go ahead take it go go do
it do it do it I want to know what it's
like being a voice actor I don't know
what it's like being a voice actor
I have no idea oh oh the number went oh
oh the number changed
thank you it's very expensive
oh
[Music]
thank you for subscribing me
okay okay why is this just keep going up
M confusion
okay okay
yeah I don't know what it's like being a
voice actor so go ahead do the stream
let me know when it is I will be there
okay this is only in 28 days
we're gonna look at lifetime
do you see how sad that is
do you see
do you see how sad the beginning is
I persevered
through this I persevered through all of
this I did not stop I did not stop
I didn't stop streaming I kept I kept
streaming bruh I didn't stop no matter
how much I did not see any growth I did
not stop
your father's like oh thank you
it's the crazy thing called something
man are you a sub
are you what's up
that's what you said
starting a slow Soul slow but it is what
it is
mm-hmm
okay are some of your first Chatters
still here
should we check that out
do you guys want to test this out okay
okay I'm gonna do something real mean to
chat okay
okay let's test we're gonna test the
theory out okay you guys wanted to see
so we're gonna see I'm gonna change my
settings for chat to be uh subscribers
who have been subbed
for I'll only do this for like a few
seconds okay we're gonna change it we're
gonna change it
uh let's say
should we do six months we can do six
months
is that liquid thank you for subscribing
wait I'm not subscribe that's don't know
isn't it oh thank you for the donut did
you have a message with that no oh gosh
no no message why didn't you send me a
message you should have sent me a
message
okay we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna
check this for six months all right I
know a lot of you are new to my channel
I know
but I wanna I wanna know I wanna see
okay we're gonna do six months and see
and see if you're able to chat if chat
doesn't move that's okay
all right okay I'm only I'm gonna I'm
only gonna do this for like a few
seconds so make it count
all right it's been done it's been done
is Chad gonna move
hello
is that it is that it it's only YouTube
wow I Cry
well
oh Joker oh my God you're still here
okay okay I'm gonna be nice I'm gonna
change it back oh Alex wait you're a mod
can you bypass the system hold on I'm
gonna change it back to anyone okay okay
I'm changing it back I'm changing it
back I'm changing it back
okay okay so I guess there's still
people here wow
oh man oh yeah I know you're one for
sure
oh gosh
okay we're back we're back right
everyone back everyone's back okay
you're in five months ah only for five
weeks hey you know what it feels like
five months
yes you're free you're free
was happy birthday many churchy and
other mods oh I know Tracy's been here
for over like a year now so yeah we've
been amazed
yes you're all babies but I'm okay with
that I'm happy you guys are here thank
you for being in here
okay okay wait let's talk about this
though we should talk we should talk
about this I love being able to do that
though now I can test that out oh okay
I'm sorry also I know I know you guys
have questions for me in the Q a tab I
promise I'll answer all of them if like
if I have not answered them already
after we finish talking about the things
I plan to talk about okay so if you have
any more questions while I'm talking
just send them there and I'll like go
back to it after I'm done talking about
what I need to talk about
and there's been again next month okay
let's do it next month let's do the next
one again
for like three months I don't have to oh
I see you're new you're a baby YouTube
Buffet aren't you
no they're just the old subscribers
aren't here tonight as well that's true
that's true they already know my history
you guys are new so you don't know my
history
I forgot if you could bypass that missed
the opportunity ah you're right
you could do 30 days I could talk then
true meet you guys for a bit okay have
fun touching grass all right
we're gonna talk about this I think this
is very important for people who do not
know how to persevere or feel like they
cannot persevere through this slow
growth because if we look at the numbers
okay this this left side here I'm gonna
try lean a bit so you guys can see the
the uh y-axis I wish this was on the
left side God damn it uh so we look over
here
I made my channel April 9th I do not
count this as my anniversary that would
be the wrong date
uh I did PNG streaming
I debuted a chibi model I think June
24th
I think it was around June 24th or some
sometime here sometime here
and let's take a day we should take a
day June 27th okay
it's 134. we go to the next month
let's go to the next one June's June
24th 231 that's about 100 subscribers I
gained and let's see we can do let's do
August let's do it for the first of
every month I think that makes it easier
August 1st 2 55. September 1st September
September
first
so I didn't gain exactly 100 subscribers
but
I gained a bit less 99
.
[Music]
that's good enough for me Kiana's word
he had his word is something you should
trust man
hello I must go into me oh thank you
have a good time bye bye
thank you for coming
not like that but you know what I mean
okay uh so let me skip to when I
was actually full time so November
November 1st 493
December 1st
567. that's not a hundred that's less
than that it's a five six seven
January
608 that's only 40 something
it got really math quick
so clearly every month I wasn't earning
or gaining
that many subscribers
I gained less than 100 subscribers per
month
just as I was growing here I think it
increased a bit I don't know why
uh but yeah
I think it's because I got monetized
somewhere around here
oh spooky addict thank you for being a
memory thank you thank you welcome epic
math thank you
70 to 100 per month is pretty good
though yeah for a small YouTuber who
didn't exactly have like you know the
best rigging I wasn't really sure what I
was doing with my life like
you know
it was I was still trying to find
myself as a YouTuber I wasn't really
sure what personality I wanted
um but yeah I did get monetized sometime
around here so I got to 1K let's see
okay trying to hit
between the 10 and the 11.
let's say let's say 10 because it's
closer
so
I made my account on April 9th
so I guess within less than a year of
streaming I made it to 1K a little bit
maybe like 11 months
I'd say 11 months I made it to 1K which
was nice
uh and then this was the debut of my new
model
which is this model
when I debuted this model it was one
thousand 300 and then I think I got
close to 2K within the month or so
within a month or so I mean like yeah I
gained about 1K Within
the span of a month for sure somewhere
around a month
where's the 2K line the freaking thing
here is so weird
yeah okay people think models don't make
a difference they're like oh we stay for
the personality not the model we don't
we stay for the voice and the
personality not the model it doesn't
matter how expensive it is no we care
about you
I'm not gonna lie it's a [\h__\h] lie
cause
I get I get
personality
Talent and voice
matters
but
visuals
Aesthetics
the way that you structure your content
the thumbnails that you make
it [\h__\h] matters
you love the models when you think about
v-tubing and it's fundamental thing what
it is it's a character talking to you on
the internet if you don't look like a
visually appealing character
would people be able would people feel
compelled to click on your content maybe
not
oh
Mama's finished with it shiny fluid must
become memorable exactly
you could have the greatest design ever
and be a PNG YouTuber
but if you're not talking to them like
move in with them and
if you're you know
if you don't have the aesthetic that
people are looking for then
unfortunately
you're not gonna grow much
it is kind of sad people think
Aesthetics don't matter but they really
do
they really do I am trying to be as
honest with you as possible I'm giving
you a hit of reality it matters
people click for the Mother's Day for
the personality
[Music]
visual it's a thumbnail a video exactly
showed you to me and your thumbnail
model cut my eye really does make a
difference
yep yep yep
it sucks that that is the case
you can tell
it it just shows okay in the numbers
it is a very factual thing
that
if you have
not so great model
your growth is going to be very slow
because people do not feel compelled
to look at a model that's not very
expressive and is very stiff where they
don't like the way it looks or they just
you know they don't like it
your first impressions matter
the way you look matters
obviously I had people that stayed for
me for the content for my voice for my
personality which I'm very thankful for
because otherwise this would not have
gone up in any way it would have just
stayed flat
all right
and once I have new model it has gone up
a lot steeper of a slope since which I
am also very thankful for it's not like
I'm gonna go like would you like there's
no there's no way it's just gonna go
straight up like that no
oh
suddenly having a blip here thanks to
all the wonderful things that happened
this month but I can't expect this with
the way that the trend has been on my
own without without that like
it's just gonna I feel like it's just
gonna keep split
good mod how you get people to come
personalize how you get people to stay
exactly but the thing is you can't get
people to stay if they don't come to you
so
there's only one way
there's only one way the thing is I was
very confident in myself I have the
skills I have the talent I know I'm not
an [\h__\h] like I was very well aware of
that it was just the question of how do
I get people to find me how do I get
people to to come to my stream and just
hear me for a second
just listen to my voice for one second
please
and I guess the model was what it what
did it
that's what did it I feel like
Kiara did ask me to join Holo live but
I'm not gonna lie I kind of like my
community I don't really know if I Wanna
Give it up yet I'm still growing I'm
still learning I'm still learning about
myself as a content creator I didn't
really have a history of any content
creation until I started youtubing which
is sad
but
if I could get into Hall of life I'd be
very happy if I don't that's okay
because I wanna I wanna gain more
experience before I shoot myself into
hollow life if possible like obviously
if I audition for hola life and get
through to it like I would take it but
if I don't get there then that's okay
because I know I still have a lot to
like
I'm going back
that is true yeah I agree the mug is
Showcase the personality
somewhere you'll go I just thank you I
like being able to occasionally chat
with you James shoes but I love her
chatting is hard there it is hard I
agree it's very hard
because chats go fast I like being able
to talk to you guys
you've been to hola so well but I swear
so much
I'm also very open about things like now
because
I think whatever oh thank you being
interviewed seems like you have way more
freedom yeah way more freedom it I love
I love that I have a lot of freedom I'm
not gonna lie I really do
yes she does smell like a sandwich
I'm trying
not you're getting good okay have fun
Palmer I'll see you later is there
anything is out there playing games yeah
I play a lot of Nintendo it makes up a
lot of my content
uh but I have a feeling with joining
companies it gets kind of difficult
doing that
uh but yeah that's just a personal thing
I like being Indie I have a full-time
Indie and I will be a full-time Indie
probably for a long time in the
foreseeable future so it is what it is
just being in a company in general might
limit you in any way I do not know what
it's like it's only from what I've heard
do not quote me on that
okay
um
uh is that all I wanted to talk about in
terms of the growth stuff
let me check I have my notes right here
okay okay we can go back to the other
screen I think
I think
uh
uh are there any other things you want
me to look at in the analytics before I
leave this page
oh you know it'd be fun to look at my
audience
I can expose all you other channels your
audience watches
of course all said burned
um
[Music]
oh yeah yeah of course of course of
course
Rosalie
I'm not surprised I'm not surprised
definitely not definitely not surprised
okay this is funny to me because when I
was talking to some YouTuber friends
about this particular section of
Analytics
almost none of them had corporate
YouTubers almost all of them were other
Indie YouTubers or small company
YouTubers when I showed them mine they
were like
why are they all corporate big ass being
too fans
and I was like I don't know I don't know
what to tell you
because this is I'm exposing you all
other videos your audience watched
a lot of outfit reveals huh yes a lot of
the outfit reveals yes yes yes
more outfit reviews
uh-huh uh lots of lots of etherea oh
yeah okay lots of hollow life also I get
to see when you guys are awake which is
nice
most of you are awake during these hours
I guess I'm getting more people in the
afternoon which is strange because I
usually stream like
here I've been doing morning streams
lately so maybe this is why this is more
colorful now
what are you guys doing at 3 P.M
on a weekday what the heck this is also
my time zone which is EST uh whatever
this is for you guys I don't I don't
know what that is
scary info for all
yeah also there's more
all of you are in the US
United Kingdom
it's part of Europe okay see more
cities
boosting
then where the heck is a Conor
yeah okay okay what does this mean
oh
I don't know what that means lifetime
yeah this is a lifetime
maybe we can do the last 28 days
last month way off oh
Denver still who the heck is from Denver
in my chat
cool
huh
nanny
New York huh Melbourne
where the heck is this London
[Music]
rental where I'm from
Miami
I have a friend from there woohoo
okay that's enough of that that's enough
oh wait wait wait research your viewers
searches explore search tires relevant
to your channel based on what your
viewers and viewers of channels like
yours are looking for on YouTube
please be something good
that's it
that's all I get
that
content gaps
none
all searches
really
really do you guys not look up anything
else
what are you doing
you don't Google me
question mark
nah
what are you
my
what do you mean you could explain
you can explain
we count as ASMR
me
I'm
never done ASMR before
ever
new gentian character
oh no wonder
can you see what everyone does not
really Search oh
I don't
I don't Genji until Saturday
or is it Friday I think Friday I think I
think my Gentry stream is Friday I don't
know what you guys are looking up but I
do not do ASMR videos I guess because I
don't do ASMR videos you guys want more
ASMR to watch so you click on ASMR and
search ASMR videos I think that's what
it is you whisper from time to time
Anita
do I like singing yeah I do I love
singing I'm a singer I've made covers
I'm surprised that there are more of the
small YouTuber stuff in your stats just
only from your college recently say hey
I don't know why I don't know why
they're not here I don't know where they
went overview
lifetime
watch time hours I managed to hit the 4K
account for monetization earlier than I
hit the 1K for Subs
is still my most watched content
and then my debut
then my debut short
oh total it's huge
you're my you're my fourth most top
thing well
oh I liked this short this is very funny
it took me an hour to make
all my covers after that when did it hit
2500 views that doesn't use to me oh
these are my old stuff
uh genshin is my top one of my top wow
okay okay well then
I see content
content
2.5 billion
2.5
you're telling me 2.5 million people
I've seen my [\h__\h]
what
but there's no way
how many times
when did I
[Music]
did I get a hundred thousand just a few
weeks ago
I
wow
I'm not attention impact streamer I just
started doing and like I just started
playing attention last week or two
oh
average view duration you guys only stay
for less than 10 minutes on average are
you kidding me you stay for less than 10
minutes on average
and yet I stream for like three four
hours huh you're telling me you only
stay for those 10 minutes wow
wow
let's see how you guys find me browse
features Channel Pages suggested videos
huh
all right then
I guess the YouTube algorithm really
does like me lately if 48 of it gets
sent just through browsing
that's kind of cool it's kind of cool
definitely not obsessively watching
videos
oh that is true
how long do you guys usually stay in the
Stream of mine
telling me I'd like to know
I want to know
oh we can do this
and then in my lifetime we get to see we
get to see some really cool things
like this
we talked about this last time
till the end if possible
all of it oh darling I know you try I
know you try
it
oh
my Becca I'm glad you stayed thank you
for staying these guys don't believe
portray the true reality keep in mind
um I know I know I know I know
this is just an overview of stuff
I still have a lot of other things I
need to talk about oh Alexis thank you
for the super
I just found you right now like 30
seconds ago and you already gave me a
super
oh that is fast
thank you though I appreciate it Liz you
found me today
wow
wow this stream is getting views isn't
it
thank you for coming
that's fair
well oh thank you Liz you don't have to
please take care of your wallet first
before mine
speed running
I'm just I'm concerned by these numbers
I'm so concerned
you've had a great spiking reviews
recently love to see it thank you Mom
thank you I'm not gonna lie I don't
expect the viewer average concurrent
viewer thing I don't expect that to stay
for like another month I'm expecting it
to drop to like back to the 50s
because I know only recently like
there's a lot of hype around me right
now which I'm very thankful for like I I
rated Kelly which some people noticed I
rated Kiara which a lot of people
noticed and Leo from face connect rated
me and I've done a lot of really cool
collabs and like I just don't really
know how long that's gonna stay around
so
while the hype around me now gets me a
lot of viewership
the chances of them staying may just
drew up once the hype around me has died
so I am not expecting to stay at like a
70 80 consistent concurrent viewer
account I am not expecting that to me
that is incredibly unrealistic so I'm
being very realistic with myself so I
don't get my expectations up
yeah it's what I've learned over being a
full-time YouTuber again we'll talk more
about that once we get to the facts once
we get through the facts still don't
know why this is the case
let's check this
oh
okay
okay I'm kind of glad I don't get any
younger people considering the type of
content I create
I'm here this island from The Starlight
thank you
it should stick at least to 70 of it oh
thank you thank you thank you yes I am
up to the 50s lately
[Music]
that's a secret
maybe you can see me there again
I actually okay my mom watches my
streams and I'm pretty sure she's in
this bracket here
I know my dad sometimes goes and watch
my stream so he's also within this 1.3
percent
uh again we'll talk about my family
after we checked the analytics for the
numbers because I know all of you guys
like the numbers and I'm trying to give
you the numbers
uh this is
this is honestly pretty normal for V
tubing fans and stuff it's pretty pretty
normal pretty normal
uh is there anything else traffic Source
we can see where you all come from
uh view traffic source
uh what episode is this
oh this is way too much I cannot I hate
looking at that I know it's very very
common for people to look at it but I
cannot look at it it makes me confused
most of my views come from browsing
Channel pages to just video shorts feed
YouTube search why can't I click on
these
what does that mean
home subscriptions watch History watch
later I get put on people's watch later
list oh kazoo thank you for subscribing
kazoo
you should definitely do ads
I'm being told to put ads on right now
I'm being told Again YouTube is telling
me to do it again look look I'm gonna
here look it just keeps showing me this
freaking thing hold on oh you see that
it keeps telling me to put ads in and I
just I keep having to click close so if
you hear me clicking around it's because
it keeps telling me to put freaking ads
on my stream and I don't want to
you're in the higher racket that's fine
be in the higher bracket no one's
telling you no
I should tell you something because
you're live with me do you think oh
that's nice YouTube smells your recent
popularity yeah you want an ad you want
to you want to click add oh snowy
sweetie thank you for subscribing you're
a YouTuber too hello
maybe it'll stop no no no I don't want
to click it I don't want to click it
oh I
thank you for subscribing
the ads work same like twitch yeah you
just get pushed it it gets pushed
it's pushed in drop me a dance now we
can talk traffic sources please I don't
really understand traffic sources so
that would be very I'd be very thankful
for that I don't really know how to look
at all this
when I look at my analytics I stick to
looking at the very basic stuff per
month
like let's do the last 28 days
the last 20 days
hello
whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa no no no hold on
compared to October
there's no way
no no way
September
load
mode
it's usually 200 or so why is it
what
no let me click on you let me stop it
okay
custom all right let's go back in time
January last year I didn't even stream
yet December 2020
December
all right
about
let's check January March April May June
July
oh seven
oh one no no wrong is it what goes first
can I just type in July
8th 2021
and then
we'll do
July August
eight 20 21.
oh is that not
let's try this
okay
okay in U.S month date year that's weird
to me it's always date month year
wow
okay let's try let's try some other
random dates we can scroll November to
here it's a month
it
went down
uh
let's go up
to May when I was what PNG
oh goodbye thank you for just gaming
uh this is earlier
so there
to here here
March 1st the 31st yep
oh nothing yet
nothing yet I went to Burbank I went too
far back
um June June is when I actually started
but I can't scroll properly because
there's a lag for some reason
oh this is February no no no may may
let's do May
hello
let's try this
yeah okay it was really small if we do
September
September was what 210 ish
October was 290
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] happened in November
what the [\h__\h] happened in November what
okay okay
I'm sorry I just I got too into it I was
I was concerned
okay uh I think that's all for the
analytics you guys know my income now at
least in terms of super chats everything
else I'm Gonna Keep private to myself
like my stream elements and my uh art
Revenue stuff I'll keep that more
private to myself but at least you know
you you know what you get after you get
monetized okay at the very least now you
know someone at my level of youtubing
how much you get when you get monetized
there although all the details are there
for you
okay so there you go there you go
uh you can always go back in the Stream
later when I time stamp it and make
Channel stuff on a chapter stuff on it
so
there you go
we'll go back now
oh my
let's just
there we go
there you go
also I'm to the side now because I
didn't change the thing okay
what's up let's change outfits because
why not
there we go
[Music]
okay uh we talked about the income we
talked about the analytics that is
basically all I wanted to show you for
that portion of the stream uh because
those were more factual things that I
felt like I needed to show you evidence
of otherwise
I wouldn't be convincing in any capacity
when I talk about some other things
later
um the other thing is
let's see hold on I'm scrolling
okay uh community building stuff
how how did the growth happen all of the
numbers how did they increase we need to
talk about that
this is more of like my opinion stuff
starting not too much factual things
anymore but I'm giving
some insight to my opinions and
personality and behaviors according to
those numbers okay
the way I act and stuff the way that
I've structured my channel the way that
I've created my content what I've
structured it around
and what I see in chat all of those are
going to be kind of related to the
numbers you all saw I would say
I always say that's also interesting
numbers behind this is interesting and
no and it would do be it's something
very personal I know a lot a lot of
people aren't willing to share it
especially if you're carpool you're
actually not allowed to share it most of
the time
uh but I feel like currently where I am
right now I am comfortable sharing it
don't download yourself your community
building is unique to the community it
feels it's still sexual it is still
factually you're right you're right I
was right
I'll try I'll try okay so
um
in the beginning
uh I would say around the like PNG days
and uh my
chibi days of streaming where I was
still part-time uh streaming and
full-time working as a researcher in
clinical stuff
um
I
spent a lot of my time
talking in Discord
and the Discord server that I currently
still have where everyone else
originated from in the beginning
still the same server
and I shared it with someone uh that
person is Sakura himegi me she is one of
my best friends in the vitamin Community
she is the person that knew me before I
even started youtubing she was there
when I had zero followers on Twitter and
on YouTube she was my very one of my
very first subscribers and we still
shared the Discord server to this very
day
so
um I will openly admit though a lot of
the channel uh because my channel has
grown quite a bit that Discord is
flooded with a lot of my peoples but we
do still share the server it has not
changed she has like another server too
uh besides the one that we share but
um I enjoy sharing it with her because
not only is it a place for my members
and my regulars and my chat in general
is a place for other YouTubers for us to
chat and you know it's it's a very nice
place it's a very nice place for me and
I I wouldn't change it for anything and
I love being able to like you know
interact and stuff in that chat and in
that particular server of mine so yeah
if you want to talk to me off stream I
am actually quite
active in the Discord server I don't
talk in other Discord servers and I will
share with you my reasons why I do not
later
but uh so the community building stuff
again I spent a lot of time in Discord
uh when I had the time at least
and I think by doing that I was actually
able to uh keep hold of a lot of
regulars and a lot of YouTuber friends
would come and watch my streams
but that didn't last very long because
YouTubers have their own life they you
know
they have to do their own streams they
have their own families they have their
own jobs they cannot be watching me all
the time so
I wasn't like
I couldn't focus on just finding more
YouTubers to watch my streams I had to
find a way
to get new YouTuber fans and Sims into
my streams which is very difficult to do
when I feel like I wasn't good enough I
did not think that I was
like the best that I could be as a
YouTuber yet no one starts off being a
great streamer right off the bat no one
does it's a learning process so I
couldn't have expected to grow right
away from the beginning
does the does the Discord command work
let's try it
let's try it I'm very active in the
members Discord because I feel obligated
but it's also very fun I will try to
talk more in like the general chat too
uh because I
tried my best to build my community that
way by talking a lot in Discord
to get to know my viewers more and I
also talked a lot in voice chat uh I
don't do that very much anymore
I will say my reasons why later uh once
I get to it but again in the very
beginning I was in there a lot I was
trying to talk to my YouTubers trying to
talk to my viewers and every time I went
live I would always announce it on
Twitter it's a very good habit to have
especially at the time when I had more
Twitter followers than YouTube
subscribers
so
um I did that for a very very long time
about six months and then
uh come November of 2021
that's when I had no choice but to
be in Discord less because I was focused
on trying to be the full-time YouTuber
that I currently am
so that would mean streaming more often
having a set time for streams so that it
was consistent where I would
um always stream like start stream
between at the time my sleep schedule
was horrible and I had stuff to do in
the afternoon still because my family
just immigrated which meant I had a lot
more driving and meetings to go to I was
also in the middle of moving houses
it was a rough time
um but I would stream I started stream
every day 11 p.m EST I would stream up
until 2 A.M sometimes even 4 a.m in the
morning
so that was bad on my part but I had a
very very solid uh
audience it was always the same people
but I felt kind of sad that I rarely saw
new people come
and come the new year I started making
more shorts started making uh more art
stuff for myself
and I tried my best to be more active in
Discord didn't really work out which
also kind of sad uh but I also was
planning my new model which took some
time
to get things sorted and to do all the
research I did and to animate every
single part of that lore video to come
out with a cover
also very difficult
um especially for my first one
I was drawing emotes drawing new badges
drawing a lot of things anything I could
possibly draw my by myself I would draw
by myself
so
um
my community was generally built through
talking to my chat as much as I possibly
could I had to develop a very strong
just chatting skill my throat would die
an hour into a stream when I started
now
it doesn't die if I stream for six hours
which I don't know if it's a good thing
or not because what if I lose my voice
one day then I pretty much lose my job
which I'm kind of sad that'd be really
sad
I also need to drink more water
okay
so um
oh I bought throw candy so I'm gonna eat
throat candy after the stream for sure
The Voice questions
yeah let's just hope it doesn't happen I
will take it easier in the coming weeks
because I do have a tiny sore throat
uh it got better because I took a took a
throat candy today like the super color
stuff but I won't push myself I promise
I promise I am a singer so it does worry
me
[Music]
in
the house exactly
it's very smart it's a very smart thing
so um yeah I couldn't last very long I
did train myself to talk a lot can you
sing good yes I can I have almost
perfect [\h__\h]
uh because I'm a musician as well I grew
up playing the piano uh the guitars I
love seeing guitars not guitar
I play Electric bass and acoustic guitar
I don't play the bass anymore though
oh you like my singing thank you thank
you thank you you can check out my
guitar stream that was fun that was fun
and piano streams and then you'll get to
see my hands even more
but yeah that's how I built my community
is by talking to chat a lot originally I
was not a very good
person to talk to on stream I feel like
I would only comment on like
you know
stuff in games that I played and if I
sang songs I just didn't know what to
talk about I also didn't really want to
brag too much about skills that I have
because they weren't very good yet they
I hadn't honed them very well yet like
calling myself a digital artist I didn't
feel comfortable doing that I didn't
think I was good enough to call myself a
digital artist yet
calling myself a singer also didn't feel
comfortable saying that oh yeah I played
the piano I uh play the guitar but I
never did that on stream I didn't feel
comfortable saying that I'm a musician
like
there yeah I didn't think that I had the
right I didn't feel like I had the right
to do that
so I spent a lot of time uh showcasing
progress where I would do just chatting
streams maybe once a month and then they
increased up until at least two to three
every week
I think I've done like four already in
the past week
so I'm very good at talking to chat now
I feel like you're with me with
confidence about yourself not exactly
why do you think I am
it's because I tried really hard to
become confident about it
like I
didn't start digital art until last year
in May I didn't
you know I didn't really play the piano
or guitar very much until last year
where I practiced a lot more until I
felt comfortable to stream myself
playing the guitar or singing on stream
I'm a dancer I used to be a
dance instructor when I was in
university but I don't have a 3D model I
don't have tracking I don't have a I
don't have a VR headset I cannot I could
never showcase the talents that I
currently have with a 2d model I have a
figure skater I'm a dance instructor I
ride horses I have a medal for it
I also didn't want to do a hand review
and I couldn't do a hand reveal because
I didn't have a webcam at the time I
didn't have an adapter for my iPad to be
able to do that and I didn't really
figure that out until a lot later
I know how to swim I can't exactly swim
on stream
like
there's I was very restricted in what I
could showcase to you so I had to think
of other talents that I could improve on
myself
to say that like you know
I I am confident about it was I this
fluent in Japanese when I started hell
no
it's because I kept doing like Duolingo
streams and I kept studying Japanese
that I was able to confidently say I
speak Japanese
when I started in May with your artistic
art skills like oh thank you I love your
art by the way I retweeted it I hope it
gained some traction because you deserve
it
you know the number one really thing we
did don't be afraid to be a dragon I
haven't done that yet I'm talking about
my factual things
hi
so yeah I
when I started youtubing I said that I
was a polyglot
but I never boasted about it because I
only ever streamed in English and a
little bit of Japanese
even then like I didn't feel comfortable
speaking Cantonese on stream because I
thought that I wasn't
fluent enough even though I definitely
was
speaking Mandarin in Korean and she was
definitely a no I didn't feel like I was
there yet
but because I kept doing it because I
kept making myself feel kind of out of
my comfort zone and I practiced and I
put the effort into learning the
languages that I do I can confidently
tell everybody when they first meet me
I'm a polyglot I speak five languages
I'm an artist I do digital art I'm a
musician I play five instruments
I am many many things I'm a singer I'm
you know I just
I have a lot of talent and I can say
that now because I genuinely feel like
I put the effort into being those things
so
the reason why I would mention that as
well is because my community
helped me feel motivated to keep
learning to keep trying and they always
told me hey I told this friend about you
because you are a something something
like you are a polyglot you know this
language and they know that language too
or you play this instrument so I told my
friend about you you know or like oh
they liked your art from this so I told
them about blah blah or all my friends
liked that game that you played so I
told them about you
I felt the need to keep trying because
my community shared things about me that
were related to said skills oh
my sister's calling my dogs and I can
hear her she's so loud
yeah
like if if my viewers hadn't told me oh
yeah we shared you on Reddit doing this
or we clipped you doing that I told said
friend that you're singing this and this
today like
had no one told me that I wouldn't
wouldn't have tried my hardest to get
good
oh
welcome to copium second tier knives
give me copium thank you
but yeah that is thanks to my community
whenever they saw me and proven
something
they were very happy for me
and they always said we love watching
you grow we love watching you get better
and seeing you improve so until today
until this very day I will continue to
strive for that that's not gonna change
and I think by actually showing progress
that I did something that I worked hard
for something
my community grew stronger they got
together more like you guys hang out
with each other in Discord I see you
I see you guys talking with each other I
know I know I'm not blind I see you
yeah that that's how I built my
community it's because I had talents to
show for it I suppose and I talked to
them a lot I do so many chatting streams
that they ended up they ended up wanting
to talk to each other they ended up
wanting to you know get to know me
getting to know everybody
I know exactly how this twice on girl
even against other size and I was born
yeah yeah apparently it gets people in
the fields so
you're welcome let me give you thank you
thank you thank you there was a little
blip in it though because when I started
right I was very say so very uh no
swearing allowed type YouTuber
changing it from that to where I am now
where all you guys like to bully me
where you all stay on pit then where you
all swear and stuff in chat or you make
them weird pickup line jokes at me like
yeah it's it took a while to convert you
guys just to like to let you know that
it's okay it's okay to swear in my chat
it is okay to be unsay so sometimes
within reason
you know it's okay
but yeah that's that that's how I built
my community
some people build their community in
another way where they just they
primarily stick to only talking on with
with their chat in streams they don't
really do Discord maybe they do it
through Twitter
I do it mostly through my streaming
stuff now I do not do community building
as much through Discord anymore I feel
like
the community I've built here on YouTube
moves into Discord and I just
keep you there it doesn't build per se
it's more like I keep you there you
cannot escape from me
oh yeah YouTube does censor it sometimes
but at the very least like I'm okay with
it
but yeah if YouTube's answered then I
guess you kind of really don't have a
choice
it's on Supremacy and Supremacy
bedtime Supremacy do you guys have any
idea how many how many times I said that
yeah when I got my new model and I saw
the progress of it and I realized that
my art mama was gonna make me bet then
I had to say it every stream at the end
of every stream I was just like and
don't forget guys but that's a privacy
and then I went in the Stream
it took forever to convert you guys okay
I felt I felt the change it took a long
time it took me four to five months of
saying that at the end of every stream
before all of you guys accepted it
I decided in the beginning that I
wouldn't talk too much about my personal
life because I was worried that I would
dogs myself and then I realized like
you can't find me unless I I share
certain parts of myself so
I just got very open about it and I know
some people don't do that where as a
YouTuber they want to stick to being
like they want to follow their lore very
closely they want to be quote-unquote in
character all the time
uh but for me
I'm in between both
like my lore isn't anything too special
it the video took me forever to make but
the story itself is very simple my
background is very simple
and like I don't talk about it much
uh I guess for me I like to talk about
my life stories what I do during the day
sometimes I just talk about random stuff
like my preferences and food
or how
my sister made me bring her white
colored nail polish today you know
things like that weird things
how I don't care about pineapple being
on Pizza even though I really hate it
like
I like to talk about whatever it is I
want to talk about
if I feel like there's a point that I'm
going like like if I'm saying something
where I feel like I'm about to dox
myself I'll stop it but
otherwise I will continue
I even showed you how much income I earn
all right like that that is a lot of
personal information already
don't break my immersion type thing yeah
but for me this is my immersion this is
my immersion I live in a house with two
dogs and like my sister and my parents
that that is my life I can't really hide
from that it is what it is my parents or
my sister may come into the stream at
any point in time like
yeah yeah
it's a this is as immersephone as it's
gonna get I can't give you more than
that I'm sorry
oh
gender
is that you
is that the semi
is that my BL top who came in is did I
read that correctly oh oh
no hi Daddy hello hello
hi Shannon oh my God thank you for
liking the thing that I made today I was
thinking of making one for Xander
actually
hi hi hi hi hi hi
yeah hello
this is the top hello why did I say that
in a Chinese accent
hi oh my God hi Luciana
hi
hi welcome please okay fine I'll make
one presented
Sandy thank you for coming
hello hello
Johanna hello again hello oh my gosh hi
okay thank you
what are you making uh check my Twitter
you'll see you'll see
hi thank you for the raid I hope you had
a good stream hello hello hello hello
hello
[Music]
were you really cute you think so thank
you
I already know that I'm cute
is that a good thing I hope that's a
good thing oh gosh what am I gonna time
stamp this
oh I have an idea I'll just mark this
down
all right before before I forget okay
that way I can time stamp this properly
later ever heard of Pico Park oh yeah oh
yeah I played Pico Park you know what I
collabed Pico Park a while ago with some
YouTubers and it took us 40 minutes to
get over you like one level which is
kinda Sage
but yeah that was a time that was a time
was that bot
is that bot
did we kill the butt
did the bot get killed
the bike got killed yet
no
did the bike get killed yet
are they done
all right guys there's no choice I need
to put it in sub only mode for one
minute
I got no time did we get the butt
I gotta put it for at least one minute
now is about God
it didn't bypass the sub the sub did it
bypass the sub
barrier
make sure okay I'll blur it later I'll
blur it later
don't worry about it I'll blur it later
it does make me sad they can't bypass
the one minute sub
this is what I like about YouTube thank
you YouTube for having this option
how do people do that I don't know I
don't know but they can't bypass the one
minute sub
but the point in the I don't know
there's a lot of bots like this so I
think that was the first time I've seen
about like that usually it's a sex buds
Let's Go Subs there's no there's no
other way I have to do this for the butt
if someone comes in be like hey why am I
locked out for a minute is because of
the butt which is sad but yes let's
protect you guys and the Stream
can the Bobby band we we can ban it and
it was banned multiple times but it came
it kept coming back so you kind of have
to
yeah
sorry pre minute pre one minute Subs yep
I am so sorry but it had to happen it
had to happen otherwise the bot would
keep coming
yeah I hope that's understandable but
okay anyway Landon thank you again for
the read I'm so sorry that had to happen
right when you came in I cry but thank
you thank you thank you I hope you had
fun with work
we will wait for you if you wanted to
see that we'll wait for you
wait for you
because I know if I just made it subbed
like you have to be subscribed only then
um
the the bot would just it can subscribe
and uh come back so it has to be at
least a minute oh you saw it do you like
it I can make you one
it takes like
20 to 30 minutes only if I if I speed
run it because I already have the
template I just color it and stuff and I
draw the little uh thing on the side I
just look at someone's model be like
I'll just draw this on the side and then
you guys you can have like a chat
running on the left of the drawing yeah
thank you for making one for the year
too they use my Oshi all right he's like
my whack door boys I felt the need
but yes and if you want I can make you
one too
was hoping for the five dollar
commission was still open for this so I
uh didn't open it because not many
people asked me for it but I think this
one I might get commissions for if I do
it often enough and I'm like yeah you
know what
I think at this point it comes for it
that until then but like for now I just
want to make some for friends and like
other people that I I love and I'm close
to you know
yeah you're roshi
yes yes
yes I am sorry Xander but I still see
you as the BL pup it it it's the hands
I'm sorry
I'm sorry it's it's your hands
don't blame me please don't blame me you
gotta accept it
I'm sorry it it'd be like that okay I'm
sorry
you you must accept that you must also
uh
I'm just gonna make this for now
all right I made a command for you
let's try it
did I hear real yes I love BL
ah what is um
it's true
[Laughter]
I'll change it later I can't think of a
better one right now
I can't think of a better when I'm sorry
it's kind of not yeah yeah it's Canada
I'm sorry if your chat ends up calling
you that
but you have to admit it's true
blue log yeah yeah sure sure
yeah because Xander totally plays
football
right
[Laughter]
okay what was I talking about
what was I talked about guys I feel like
I was on a topic or something
um
let me see let me see
uh I talked about community building I
talked about
how I don't really have too many
boundaries for string and what I talk
about on the stream for just chatting
stuff
[Music]
um
let's do oh
telling my parents
you know what maybe I should make this
coming out to my parents no no I won't
do that that's a different thing uh okay
we're into that good part this is this
is a part that many people have had
questions about in the Q a thing I think
uh so I think
this is a very good topic to start out
with for the discussion portion where I
look at chat and then after this I will
look at the questions and answer any
that I haven't already answered so
let me drink my water before this
it's time to stream at nine it's almost
midnight oh gosh I'm so sorry I took up
so much time okay
okay so how I told my parents
uh when I got monetized earlier this
year
um
I felt like it was time
so uh last year when I was still very
baby YouTuber I only had like 500
subscribers or so I made it I made a
promise to myself that when I got
monetized I would tell my parents that
I'm a YouTuber and I'd like to be a
YouTuber for a very very long time
and the reason why I waited up until
monetization was for a very logical
reason
if you're a streamer and you're not
having any form of income that looks
stable
your parents will likely
not let you be a streamer because
they're gonna think it's a waste of time
you're not earning income from it
and
there's no point you're wasting you're
just wasting your gun yeah you're
wasting your time
so when I got monetized
I uh did all the tax stuff
and I honestly ran into a wall with it
because I didn't understand a lot of
things I never had to do my own taxes I
just had to give any information that I
got from the government or from my
parents to my mom who would give to an
accountant and they would do all this
stuff for us so I panicked I was like
there's no way I can keep this to myself
any longer I need help
so I told my sister first we were in
this room where I am right now
and I told her so uh I'm a streamer and
she's like my sister was like what's a
streamer I'm like oh God we have to
start from there because my sister's a
huge ignore me she doesn't know anything
about Beethoven she doesn't know
anything about streaming her life has
always been surrounded by more Western
like TV uh she's a nurse so she doesn't
really have much of a life uh and she
was also in school longer than I am
but yeah so I had to explain to her from
the beginning this is my channel this is
uh what I have to do now I'm stuck on
monetization here can you help me
and she's like you could just do your
own taxes and I'm like no
what
and anyway we talked it out and that's
how she found out and she's like well
you're earning income from it you're
having fun as long as you don't spend
all your time on it and you still work a
full-time job outside of YouTube being
in healthcare you're good
and I was like hmm yeah that's what
that's what I think Mom would say
so a few days maybe even a week later I
told my mom
but I'm assuming I was shaking I was on
the couch uh just sitting next to her
and I had my channel open on my phone
I had about 1
200 subscribers or so at the time so
obviously you know just getting
monetized didn't have too much
so
um
I was on the couch just watching TV with
my mom I don't remember what we were
watching and I was like hey Mom
can I talk to you for a sec and she came
over I was like hey what's up you know
and I was like so um
I have something to tell you and she's
like okay yeah what is it and I was like
so uh uh you know how I've been awake
really late for like the past couple
months and stuff and she's like yeah
you've been playing games with your
friends right I'm like well not not
exactly
um
I yell I've been up in the Stream and
she's like a streamer yeah yeah I've
been I've been streaming
and she's like
okay
uh how's that going for you she's honest
I'm surprised she even knew what it was
and I was like it's been going great I
get like 10 viewers per stream
and she's like is that a lot I'm like um
Maybe
for for my standing at the moment yeah
10 10 viewers yeah yeah it's just enough
it looks quite a bit uh and she's like
so people watch you do what what do you
do I'm like I uh game
and I talk to them
and I uh sometimes draw
uh I
I uh I talk to other streamers sometimes
question mark
and she's like oh is it is on YouTube
I'm like yeah yeah so I saw on YouTube
and uh I I just recently started being
able to earn more money from it because
obviously I had stream elements
beforehand like YouTube monetization is
totally different than stream elements
so I was like yeah I uh been earning
more money from it recently and she's
like oh you get you get paid how much do
you get paid uh that's not much or
anything it's very very little
because at the time I think in super
chats it was less than about a hundred
or less than 100 per month and I was
like yeah it's just just 100 or so per
month
and then
um she was like
I asked you do you want to see the
channel
and I showed it the channel
and she's like oh it's kind of cute
oh yeah yeah at the time I was still
using my old model not this one
and uh I guess at that time she was like
kind of shocked I think because I don't
think she expected me to have this
anime type model per se like she wanted
I guess she expected to see me having
like a webcam or something
and
uh sticking back on it kind of hits me
in the fields but I remember her saying
like it's good that you found a hobby
that you genuinely like spending your
time on but like you know like she said
the exact same thing my sister said
where she was like I hope
you don't spend all your time on
youtubing and that you will
you know you'll still job hunt in the
healthcare field and you'll use your
degree
and that I will
you know
end up not streaming someday
it has been a long time since but she
accepted it
and that was enough for me at the time I
did not care if
she was hoping that I would drop it one
day the fact that she was okay with me
continuing to stream at least four now
that was good enough for me and
considering my family is quite you know
they
we could just saw my life growing up
like
I was
honestly expecting her to tell me to
stop but she didn't tell me to so I was
like okay because at the time
if she had told me to not stream anymore
and don't let this grow any further and
focus your entire life on Healthcare and
getting a proper job out in the world if
she told me that then
I would have dropped it I would have
dropped youtubing entirely but no she
said she would support me and that I was
free to keep doing it as long as I would
still keep trying to find
a full-time job outside of it
yeah
inside of the reliable includes
important but at the same time you can't
really buy happiness important too
exactly like I understand my mom's point
of view how she
didn't you know how she wanted me to
still have like a full-time job outside
of streaming but she also wanted me to
be happy and she was you know
when she heard that I was monetized and
that I was earning income
she was like okay you can keep doing it
just make sure you keep trying to find a
health care job and yes she still does
mention it she's like how's your job
hunting going how's like have you had
any interviews lately
and I can say yes or no all most of the
time I'm just like nope I haven't
uh but
I still I still job hunt I still I still
try and even though it's hard I am very
thankful for my mom for letting me keep
streaming and let me do what I love
ah mom is that you always I can mod you
now
Mommy hi
hi Mommy hi Mommy
your mother's amazing thank you yes my
mom is amazing I know
because I love you yeah I know thank you
Mommy
amazing you're gonna make money tonight
oh thank you
that's your mother yeah that's my mom
hi Mommy
oh man I want to cry
no I don't I'm not I'm not gonna cry now
that was not the time
your daddy super talented
oh okay
[Music]
thank you
amazing
mom Alicia thank you
thank you Mommy thank you for letting me
stream I love you
oh
good night mommy sleep well I'll see you
tomorrow
bye bye
I didn't expect to see my mom tonight I
got I teared up oh my gosh
[Music]
you teach the name of me
my mom is in the room next to me
actually no she's two rooms over and
take the bike
just everything baby that's so true
bye bye Mommy
yeah it's very I think Mom pack is right
it's actually very rare to see another
mom like biological mom
in the chat one who's willing to say you
know hi and good night and slowly
thank you thank you guys for being so
nice to my mom I had to change her name
on our YouTube channel
because she didn't know how
I love I love my mom
it was very hard to tell my mom uh when
it was like
how it's like
this is the first time another videos
I'm glad I'm glad you're able to at
least say hi I know she's she's actually
usually asleep by now
um she only she usually sleeps at like
10 or 11 p.m EST and it's midnight now
so I'm surprised she was here I didn't
think she'd come in today of all streams
no that that's my real mom that's my
real mom my biological mom who raised me
who carried me in her belly
you got another purpose
I've been told I'm really good when it
becomes you know comes to a uh you know
being introduced to parents I'm a very
good friend to introduce to parents
well good night Alexis thank you for
coming and being a member today thank
you
I've asked her if she wanted to come on
stream and she said no
but yeah I'm I'm very thankful for my
mom letting me
be a streamer it's been very like I
still I still look for jobs uh sometimes
when I can uh to not so that I don't let
my family down I know they still want me
to uh work as a healthcare professional
and I want to try B1 as much as I can
too it's still an ambition I have I
can't forget that like I spent four
years for my degree trying to become one
so
I I genuinely do like that field that I
study but at the same time I love
youtubing too so
I was very scared having to pick between
either one and I don't want to have to
pick I want to be able to do both if I
can
because
I'm a group chat no
yo what you know what maybe one day
like
I'll ask my mom if she's down to talk to
Mom Pekka so that she can learn more
about the V tubing community and how
it's like because I feel like no matter
what I tell my mom she's not gonna
understand some things like she's never
really been into content Creation in
general she's never been uh into
like streams she's never been into Tech
she's not really into games either I
never grew up playing games because my
family wasn't into that so
that would be nice
if if maybe you could
I don't want to put you on the spot here
a month ago but like it'd be cool
if you could maybe tell my mom some
stuff about youtubing from my mother's
perspective
it's midnight for me right now it's time
for those oh thank you thank you thank
you
Avant date
I don't know I'll I'll see I'll think
about it if my mom is even willing
okay okay if I'm still awake after
stream my gosh that was emotional for me
I really did tear up oh God
oh gosh okay that's how I that's how I
told my parents uh I
was very very timid about it
I was a streamer for over like about a
year until I was willing to tell my mom
that I was a streamer
because I wanted to work hard for it to
show her that I put the time and effort
into something that's totally different
from what I normally do I didn't want to
spring it on her out of nowhere like hey
Mom I'm gonna become a streamer look at
this because then she would definitely
say okay you're wasting your time don't
do that you're starting something that
you totally don't know anything about
why would you do that
so
the fact that I spent the time to build
it up before telling her was probably
one of the best decisions I ever made
music
yeah I guess so it would be like hey so
your son and daughter did this today
cozy is amazing I love cozy she's one of
my best YouTuber friends
yeah that's how I told my parents and I
told my cousins before I told my sister
or
my mom and dad my cousins who are only
like 15 and 13 years old and I still
told them first because they seemed like
they'd be cool about it
thank you
I changed the description didn't I
remember in front of me oh thank you Mom
Pekka thank you thank you I'm glad that
you're proud of me
yeah I love I love my parents so much
because they've never told me
don't stream don't be a YouTuber they've
never said that to my face they've never
told me that and yes I know they hope
and dream that I'll still be you know in
the healthcare field and I wish for that
for myself too but right now
and I'm also just genuinely happy being
a YouTuber so
it's nice it's nice
okay
I think that was one of the big ones you
guys wanted me to talk about so if you
have any questions about it and uh let
me know in the Q a and I'll get back to
it later uh for now I'll keep talking
about some other stuff
uh one that is also very sensitive topic
to some people but
I'm touching on a lot of sensitive
topics today so if you get uncomfortable
just hearing about it feel free to step
away for a bit I don't mind I get it it
could be triggering
oh that's fine then don't worry about it
don't worry about it people get busy
it's okay it's okay do not do not feel
bad
if you look in the description I wrote
some stuff you can read that it might
give you a better idea of what I'm okay
with you saying and what you're not
honestly I did say in general like to
sum it up ask whatever it is you want to
ask in the Q a and I will go through it
if I don't feel comfortable answering it
I will just simply say I don't feel
comfortable answering that question and
move on so ask whatever it is you want
to ask no matter how personal it is I'll
if I feel comfortable as like answering
it I will take take the opportunity to
ask whatever question it is you want
because
there's probably I'm probably not going
to talk about this for a long time after
so yeah take take advantage of the
situation
I'm not gonna tell you no unless I
genuinely feel uncomfortable doing it
please please feel free to ask whatever
it is you want and after I finish going
through the rest of the topics I have
listed on my notes Here
I'll go look at the questions and Q a
and uh stuff for all of that okay
I really appreciate open stuff that
might be difficult for you I feel like
it's helping a lot of people oh thank
you I'm trying I'm trying I'm trying
very hard seeing my mom come into chat
was probably my breaking point I started
tearing up
I've been I've been extremely real and
vulnerable this entire stream so yeah
oh tonight
[Music]
we'll go I've never seen
much love you're doing well you know I'm
glad I got to stop by for the treatment
and ah welcome welcome thank you for
coming I watched your Kawa uh thingy it
was it was such a good thing I loved
watching it thank you thank you for
making that dream it was so informative
I loved it
yeah I was tearing up I was cheering up
I get emotional easily I'm sorry
it was a really really good cover stream
why did I just call it color thing well
English
me uh because boundaries
uh when I started streaming last year I
did not know what those were I knew what
it meant to be giving consent and how to
say no
but at the same time I was not sure how
boundaries were set as a YouTuber
I have no idea
it was such a good stream it was so good
you gave such good advice and I don't
have any challenges many people should
say even though I'm just so many things
oh you're not just someone in chat you
are a nice friend minodachi
it's great seeing you
little girl yes I uh I'm touching on a
lot of sensitive topics today so like I
said if you have questions ask them now
or forever withhold your peace uh and if
you feel uncomfortable don't worry if
like you don't feel comfortable with it
just step away and come back later okay
I don't mind it's okay
Okay so
there are many boundaries as a YouTuber
um
in the beginning when I started
streaming I
like I said did not know what those were
because I wasn't sure if for collabs
should I collab with everybody
should I only collab with some people
should I collab to like
only with
a certain age group a certain number of
people who only had a certain number of
numbers like do you have this many
YouTube or twitch subscribers or
followers or whatever like I did not
know I did not understand
I did not know how close I had to be
with somebody before it was okay for me
to be like hey can we collapse each
other
and in the beginning
whenever someone asked me for a collab
no matter who it was
I said yes I would agree because
at the time I wanted to get my name out
there as much as possible
and it was hard because number one I did
not look like every other YouTuber I had
a chibi model
I did not have like the anime type model
like now
and it was
I suppose because I didn't really know
myself yet and what kind of content I
wanted to make
I wasn't able to get across my Niche and
like what I was focusing on as a content
creator I wasn't able to
you know introduce myself to everybody's
chat and be like hey I am Mia I am this
type of content creator I make this kind
of content I did not know how to say
that I would just say my lore a little
bit and like who I was as a person be
like I am that's it
I didn't I didn't know who I was
basically I I just wasn't sure because
there were so many times I wanted to be
unsatial
but then someone told me you're a chibi
you can't be that people are gonna think
you're a kid trying to do sexual things
on the internet so I was like oh okay
guess I won't be that I'll just be Hazel
forever
and
um
whenever someone told me that I would
get triggered
mm-hmm
hope it doesn't hurt to hear myself this
okay okay
right that's why I rebranded because I
spent so much time
about a year learning who I was as a
streamer learning about what kind of
content I like learning about what I'm
comfortable with what I'm not
comfortable with learning how my chat
likes to react to stuff to what I do
like the things I do or
um like what streams I do get the most
traction
I it took a long time for me to find
what was working and what wasn't working
but I also had to balance out what the
internet wanted to see versus who I am
I
wanted to be someone that was more
unhinged I hated being so locked up
and that I couldn't express myself as I
as I wanted to because
I built up so much being Ojos
I won't swear I'll stream I built that
up so much that I felt really really
locked in
so I decided that when I rebranded to be
having this model and stuff that I would
make it so that I was more unhinged and
was allowed to stream I mean it was
allowed to swear on stream I'm allowed
to talk about more personal things like
this on stream I am you know I wanted to
be more genuine with everybody I was
genuine before don't get me wrong
it's just that there are more things I
can say on stream now like I can swear
when I get angry
um I can my mom is in chat number one
like if someone comes into my room
that's okay
like I just wanted to be I wanted to
have more freedom I don't know why I
gave myself such little freedom
okay honey
[Music]
yeah I was able to look at other
YouTubers and understand a lot of
different content which kind of helped I
don't want to be very much different
before yes I was very say so
yes I am a lot safer now
so last year when I kept collabing with
everybody
I got pulled into some some collabs that
I was not comfortable with
now I know to say no to those
is there any advice you'd give to those
who are trying to find this out to the
streamer yes
try out things that you didn't think
that you would ever do
uh for me it was like
I think it was playing
the playing I don't remember which game
it was
it Kirby or Pokemon
I think it was both
it was both I was so against playing
Pokemon until someone bought it for me
and
I tried it I was just like oh damn
that's cute
and
your voice that's another thing if
you're trying to come off with a certain
accent or a certain tone of voice
it is very difficult to keep it up for a
very long time
I used to get I used to keep trying to
not scream not be chaotic be calm and
comfy streamer and
even though that's I realize that even
though that's the type of content I
enjoy consuming
that doesn't mean I am that person
so
rather okay V2 being people think that
it's
you get to be someone you that you're
not IRL as a human being
breaking fourth wall here but you kind
of have to at times like this
people think that a lot where vitaming
is
is something that you wish you were
but
I feel like that's the wrong way to look
at it you need to see V tubing as an
extension of yourself
you're like enhancing parts of you as a
human
and giving it more life
so
like IRL I've had many different hair
colors I've bleached my hair like a few
times it's very very healthy hair though
um and
these three colors that I have are
probably my favorite uh some of my IRL
not Ira some of my YouTuber friends who
I've face revealed to and done video
calls with they know that I've had hair
colors like this before
uh and visually my model is very similar
to how I look like IRL probably even
cuter actually because it's an anime
style version of myself
and
the way that
I dress on my model is very cute
is the kind of outfit that I wish I
could wear like IRL too but like I can't
really step out of the house looking
like this so that's why I also have uh
this outfit where it's the dress I
actually have a dress that kind of looks
like this but it's not as cute
like I I had to make adjustments
um the way that I found my myself as a
YouTuber is
stop faking it just enhance what I
already have
YouTuber clothes are never practical
ity
I'm about the same as my model really
okay
without everything else everything
exactly
it's very hard to force yourself to
sound and look like something
so if anybody work exactly
like I I get that this is I'm I'm
breaking your immersions and I'm
breaking your hopes and dreams at the
moment but I am being very realistic
this one stream and this one stream only
so I'll never bring this up again but
if you're like to find yourself well
trial endeavor
but say your personality in real life is
like a very chaotic person then
and you want to tone it down for your
streams and be comfy go ahead and do it
and have your chaotic moments
occasionally if you really feel like
that's who you are
but just because you consume a type of
content and you want to be something
doesn't mean that when you're streaming
that you can't like you're gonna be able
to pull it off the same way other people
do
if you're not genuinely you on stream
then
it it comes off you'll you'll be able to
notice oh I'm Monica thank you for being
immediate hello welcome to the
membership
so that also makes me appreciate people
I agree I agree
more like an OCR Persona no no
I say that me as a YouTuber is still me
off stream I get called Mia off stream
more than I do with like IRL legal name
really hard yeah I'll talk about more
with that later but um yeah finding
myself was difficult finding where
like I my boundary I set for myself with
my models and personality on stream were
so tight
I made it too tight
I had to loosen it
and that came with the model my other
models were very monotone color they
were very colorful they were very like
calm looking
but
um me right now more colorful have more
expressions
the way I talk is also a bit different
where I don't try and sound like a calm
person I just I just talk
I just I say what I want to say it comes
out of my mouth and I don't change my
voice I don't try to be something I'm
not
because that's very difficult and
keeping that up for four hours straight
is impossible
okay so yeah I also learned that
accepting every collab invite is a bad
idea
because it'll take you into some collabs
you're not comfortable in so many people
when I say okay
I I have this in like descriptions and
stuff I do not play horror games
but so many people the second I tell
them I don't play horror games they're
like we need to drag you into a horror
game collab and play horror games
together
I will immediately say no
it doesn't matter who you are how big of
a YouTuber you are if if Kiana if
takanashikiara asked me to play a horror
game with her as our first collab I will
say no
it doesn't matter who you are I will say
no
is the fact that so many people try to
push that boundary of mine
that I instantly said no I'm not gonna
collab with you
I cannot do that I cannot do that I will
I won't push myself out of that comfort
zone I can try so many things
I can try like RPG games MMOs open World
stuff like turn-based games like Pokemon
I tried Splatoon I don't ever play
shooting games I tried valorant recently
I also tried gentian which is also
another game that I don't typically play
I'm usually a very big Nintendo streamer
but I'm willing to try things
those things I'm fine with but when
people ask me horror game you're scared
of horror games we're gonna play a
horror game
I I don't know what's going through
people's heads but why would you
personally try and put yourself in a
position that makes me feel
uncomfortable like why are you trying to
push yourself
into Myspace and drag me out of my
bubble and make me feel uncomfortable we
like even with people I just met they're
like oh my God you're afraid of horror
games I like that I'm afraid of horror
games I don't stream horror games
because I don't even know what you
stream so I'm like hey what do you
stream they're like oh I stream this and
this and this and they're like oh what
do you stream me I'm like oh I see
really cute comfy games I just never
play horror games because that's a
boundary I have to set right in the
beginning when I talk to somebody who
may want to ask me for a collab I'm like
no I don't play horror games but no
every time I tell them I don't play
horror games they're like let's play a
horror game together
in a way I find that rude
because
you're you're saying something that
purposefully makes me feel uncomfortable
right off the bat why can't people just
be respectful and say oh that's okay
that you don't play horror games like
why why
people do the same thing cozy oh gosh
yeah yeah I get that I remember someone
told me that she couldn't do it and then
she just she couldn't get through the
the beginning of the street like the
beginning loading screen I think
okay like if you're not making sense to
kick the verb yeah thank you Phil thank
you yeah
uh I think to me it's both psychological
and demonic stuff I'm okay with gory
things but like um everything else now
I don't like horror content I really
don't I don't watch it if someone's
playing it I don't watch it
[Music]
the thing is if I'm not having fun
Chad's gonna look at me they'll either
be one of two things
they're gonna make fun of me for being
scared as [\h__\h]
or they're just gonna tell me don't
stream to stop it you're hurting
yourself
so
I would prefer to just stay away from it
but that's a boundary I had to set and
many people have tried to cross it
many many many many many people have
tried to cross it
and
it
in the beginning I felt compelled to
agree
to
to say okay I'll play a horror game with
you
but I cannot stress this enough
if you're a small streamer who's looking
to grow
don't do anything you're not comfortable
with
and always make sure you know what
you're getting yourself into
probably get this guy just kind of
entertain right
right
I feel that tonight when you're so
scared you kind of just start sweating
and you don't want to you can't look at
chat you can't talk to chat it's just
pain
battleclaw compels you yeah it did it
did compel me
but then people are looking at me for
cloud now which I will talk about later
when I talk about social media stuff
we're still on the boundaries man
yeah I know some people like watching
others get scared but I'm not gonna lie
I just don't think of it as a joke I get
that it's funny for other people but
it's not fun for me I don't like getting
scared I will have nightmares for months
[Music]
exactly it is genuine fear
oh
that's so sweet though that you brought
her cocoa at the end like I think most
people will have the same reaction as
you montpaka where they're like she's
scared and then once they realize that
okay this is like she's not having a
good time because some people like to
get scared they love the adrenaline they
love the suspense but once you realize
that they genuinely hate it that they're
terrified
you're like oh God if you're a good
person you would tell them
please stop are you okay please take a
break look away can you calm down are
you all right please breathe
like
I just don't want to ever have to
experience that
some advice videos someone who doesn't
like these together is not so fun
exactly if you don't like it then your
chat's not gonna like it so don't do
something you don't like simple as that
set that boundary straight away do not
be me and accept every collab that you
could possibly accept I got pulled into
a collab with 10 other people for like
crab game once I did not know
like 50 of the people there and the
other 50 within that 50 maybe I only
knew like 10 of the people and genuinely
would talk to them so
don't don't force yourself into
situations like that it would
it would hurt you
and it would
kick you in the guts in your social
anxiety
it will make your chat
feel uncomfortable if you're
uncomfortable
so simply put do not put yourself in a
situation where you don't feel
comfortable
I wish I learned that sooner if I could
tell that to my younger self I really
would you can tell with the people I
collab nowadays I will only collab with
people I genuinely feel comfortable
talking to offstream if I my rule of
thumb all right is if I cannot hold a
conversation with you in a voice call
for an hour
We're Not Gonna collab
simple as that
if I can't talk to you and have fun with
you for a long time then
we're not collabing there's been some
exceptions uh like satako satako is a
YouTuber who I've known for a very long
time she comes and goes in my chat uh
but we've started talking a lot recently
in like Discord so
like I may may or may not
go out with her one day I have a feeling
we will to be honest because we have
very similar personalities I've been in
her chat and she's been in mine
so like yeah me and cozy we got along
very well really quickly I think you
guys may have noticed if you've been in
my chat for a while
um but we we talked a bit in DMS and
then there was one night we got in a
call together it was me cozy and Frey
and we talked for like five hours
straight and that's when I knew that is
when I knew
but we are gonna be really really good
friends
because it's not easy to find someone
that I can talk to so quickly like that
Rey also made it incredibly easy
yeah protective and sticks
cuteness aggression what the heck is
this
real yeah
our our
twin roomba's named Bob
our like we watch cage dramas we started
youtubing around the same time we're
both kind of purple we both have ribbons
of some sort
we're like into the same things we're
both scared of horror games like
like come on you gotta tell me where
that's okay
yeah
the thing is I knew cozy for a while
beforehand she didn't know me but like
I knew her because I have a simping
account
oh thank you tonight
thank you thank you I'll tell her you
said that
me I um
setting the boundary was very difficult
and setting a boundary for chat was also
very difficult telling Chad to stop
because sometimes sometimes you guys can
go off and you guys get off topic
sometimes and I understand it's the flow
of the Stream
but learning to be like okay we need to
bend this person we need to bend that
person we need to time out this person
like it took my mods a very long time to
figure things out so yeah holy crap cozy
you're still here wait I thought you
said you were on a plane no you're not
no I was no what you're not being
replaced oh my God cozy you missed
seeing my mom oh you just got off the
plane
oh wait I started streaming when you got
on the plane you're now off the plane
we've been we've been streaming for a
while guys eventually no no no no you
haven't been replaced you haven't been
replaced oh wait I forgot realize I need
to mod you that way I notice when you're
here
where's the where's the mod button
there we go
Wireless now has moderates
I need to be able to notice you
okay
um uh the boundaries the chat took my
mods a very long time to be able to set
so
um
I trust them a lot
I trust them a lot with their judgment
and I appreciate them a lot so never
complain about something my mods do
that is something I will not tolerate
because they work very hard for me
considering how often I stream and how
often I stream recently and all the
reason growth and like all the the chats
going faster and like Bots coming in
like you got you gotta appreciate the
mods appreciate the mods
and only when there wasn't custom chat
laughs
you guys gonna be more blue than green
or gray no it's not noise
I trust I trust everybody to keep chat
looking nice although obviously just
modding my friends doesn't mean that I
expect them to mod I mean I I just
turned them blue because I trust them
and I want to be able to notice when my
friends are coming in okay
that's that's my main reason is like if
if you're coming into my stream I want
to be able to see you
I like colors
yes I appreciate the mods I know they're
always watching uh it's kind of Uncle
Taco story from last year uh I used to
get a [\h__\h] ton of bots and I used to get
a lot of people being like are you a kid
are you a child or what's your age
what's your real age you sound like a
kid
or uh people were like hey you single
trying to ask me out hit on me on stream
like will you marry me I love you Mia
even though I don't even know who you
are like
I had to my mods and I it was it was
more like my YouTuber group friend group
at the time that was like okay because
Mia doesn't have mods yet one of us
within this friend group has to be in
Mia's chat at all times until she gets
mods
yeah that's how important it was because
I was also the only one on YouTube and
YouTube has a lot of weirdos
very social relationships yeah a pair of
social relationships I had to cut one of
those
but all good uh oh this is really
important in my opinion I am willing to
talk about this now because I feel like
it's very important and I used to cry
about it before but now I am okay with
talking about it so I will
uh last year before I debuted as a TB
YouTuber
I was sexually harassed by someone
uh they
like the whole grooming type where uh
that was a grooming type maybe uh but he
was a bigger YouTuber than I was also on
Twitch and YouTube on both platforms
and he came to me when I still had like
100 Twitter followers and 50 Subs on
YouTube
and he was like hey you're starting out
as a YouTuber
let me help you with that
and I got roped into it because I was
like desperate for the help I wanted to
know what it was like and to like ask
questions and stuff
I was naive I know that now willingly
admit that now
but uh an example of what made me feel
incredibly uncomfortable uh besides all
the sexual harassment stuff oh okay sure
thank you for subscribing yeah besides
all the sexual harassment stuff was
he forced me to be in a Discord call
with him
even though I said no and he kept
calling me he wouldn't stop and I was
like okay what's up
and uh I was still in school at the time
it was April for finals I was studying
and he's like just study with me on the
phone I'm like
okay I don't mind that and I tried
muting myself whenever family came and
he's like why'd you meet yourself I'm
like well
I don't like him and don't want to dox
myself or anything
and he also kept trying to ask me out I
said no
um I wanted to hang up a call and he's
like no don't hang up
don't hang up and I was like why not
he's like just fall asleep with me on
the phone and like fall asleep in a
Discord call is that a thing he's like
yeah it's a normal thing I'm like oh
okay well I don't care I don't really do
anything at night so
I just
left the phone call on I guess while my
phone was charging
next to my head I woke up and he's like
oh you're moving
I'm like oh hi good morning I'm gonna
brush my teeth now
and he's like okay take me with you I'm
like wait what
and he's like yeah just take me with you
I know okay
strange
the phone call had gone on for over 12
hours
I have a screenshot of that I kept it
saved
and by the time I was like hey I need to
go eat breakfast with my family now
please keep in mind that this is when
there was covet going on so my whole
family was stuck at home and my family
from Hong Kong who came to visit was
also stuck in Canada because they could
not leave which meant there was around
12 people living in a house made for
four people at the time which meant that
a lot of people could hear what I was
saying on the phone or they maybe you
know hearing me be on the phone with
somebody or talking into the phone
and I was very scared
so when I was like I need to go down and
eat breakfast with everybody he was like
take me with you just put me on mute or
something
and I was like okay this is creepy as
[\h__\h]
because originally like I know people in
Discord calls like voice calls they end
up falling asleep
and especially if it's late at night for
them they just end up falling asleep in
this group calls and then you move them
or you disconnect them right because
you're nice like that
it'll disturb them while they're
sleeping
but
this was really really creepy yeah not
intentionally you don't intentionally
fall asleep no but this was just like
hey nope fall asleep with me on the
phone
it was very creepy yeah what a creep
right what a creep was he awake the
whole time I don't think so
but I'm just saying that was one
instance
that happened with all the other sexual
harassment things that happened next to
that
there was yeah there was nothing okay
about it but please remember at the time
I was naive I was never into content
creation I had never met anybody online
I'd never had online friends all my
friends were in person and I thought
that these things were normal especially
with how much I was told oh yeah the
internet's weird nowadays but those
things are normalized now like how
people send snapchats throughout the day
about what they're doing and pictures
and stuff
and I was like oh it's normal that he's
sending me pictures of things
okay then and I didn't bat an eye at it
until it got to a certain point and I
was like okay bye
but
that is why I'm very careful with who I
talked to on the internet and who I
follow
[Music]
so you're trying to get things yeah
yeah it was very bad
it was very very bad
but at the time I did not know that it
was bad
so
um I will say now that this particular
YouTuber
uh quit his previous like he quote
unquote graduated
but then he came back with a model that
looks very similar and the name that is
also very similar
to
uh model he used to have
he when I got a little bit bigger as a
YouTuber
he uh messaged me
on Twitter
and I never responded
but that YouTuber who did that to me is
still around
he has like an account and everything
um
I haven't said his name this entire time
because
I don't want to ruin someone's career
I would feel incredibly guilty no matter
how bad of a person he was
he's just another person on the internet
that I don't like I don't want to think
about
oh tuna fish thank you
it's okay
thank you for this thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
oh yeah I know I know it is
disheartening when someone doesn't
believe but
um
it happens it happens very glad I think
everything it's okay it's okay I've
learned from it now I'm sad that it had
to happen that way that I learned it the
hard way but at least I learned
mm-hmm
they can just do others exactly they had
to Rebrand Quantico Rebrand with and
like change and stuff and create new
accounts because they had done something
bad in that span of time
that he was sexually harassing me next
to upon other things
so yeah
[Music]
I don't I just I don't like calling
people out
I actually really admire that you don't
come up here because it's not just
curious my job and you don't need that
in your life exactly that's something I
was going to touch on after this
yeah they were canceled before once
yeah I left it behind because
it happened last year and you I am very
mentally strong I guess I've been told
that I am mentally strong I mean when
you think about what I've been through
if you guys know my history and from
that q a if you were there
you would know what I've been through
lasting like two weeks of that sexual
maybe a month actually of that sexual
harassment was nothing
it was nothing
okay okay you can you can guess all you
want but I will never say this person's
name
they're still making content they still
have a twitch and a YouTube and the
Twitter and the Discord but no I will
never call anybody out
when I think about calling someone out I
also think about
they may be like this on the internet
but maybe in real life
they have a job they have kids maybe
they have a wife or a husband or a
partner
maybe they're really poor and all they
have is streaming because some people
are dumb like that where they spend all
they have on streaming and hope that
they make it and hope they get a lot of
money
or
you know maybe they just don't have any
friends on in real life and they just
wanted some attention even though it was
very wrong of them like I
I don't I don't like calling people out
if it ruins their chances of having a
better life then no if they wanted to be
a YouTuber to escape all the shitty
things that are happening in their life
I don't want to take that away from them
that would be mean of me
so if I can just leave it behind and
avoid it
and just make sure they never come into
my life ever again and that they don't
go near my friends people that I love
and Trust
then we're good
no just leave it
they're gonna be friends oh thank you
that'll be colors yeah
I've definitely grown way more than they
have now
and I bet they're jealous as [\h__\h]
bye bye it's okay it's okay good have
fun doing your work
best
um
you're gonna take it thank you
thank you thank you I know it is like so
many people see a need to call out
somebody because something happened to
them the thing is I don't know if
anybody else was treated the same way
if I called them out
it would be very one-sided it would be
me against them
and I don't want to draw it draw it out
I don't want to have to pull out
screenshots of screenshots of
screenshots and
try and make people see my side just so
that they
go down in flames and get canceled it is
a waste of time for me
it is emotional strain I don't want to
put onto myself
and
I feel like it's just best to deal with
these kind of things off stream offline
not on Twitter not in public
it'd be best if that person would just
leave quietly so that they can keep
doing what they want to do
not really benefits from it exactly
I think one of the key reasons to said
success quote-unquote success of mine
is that I've never been involved in
drama I really really hate it there's
YouTuber channels out there that thrive
off it and good for them
good for them
but I do not want to get involved in any
of it
I really really don't
it seems like it can grow really out of
hand and among V tubers I feel like it's
even bigger because there's sometimes
there is idle uh what do you call it
like Idol culture where they're like
you're not allowed to date this person
you're not allowed to say this kind of
thing you're not allowed to do that kind
of thing
one thing you say on stream can get you
canceled instantly
and I just don't want that to happen to
me I don't want like
someone like especially with collabs if
I bring someone onto my channel if they
say something
that I'm not comfortable with that
collab would end instantly
it's very very scary to think that like
if I collab with someone I don't feel
collabing with I don't feel comfortable
collabing with if I if they come on my
stream
and they say something I could get
canceled because of what they did which
is why I'm very careful with collabs now
[Music]
the bigger you get the easier it is for
drama to come find you
like so many people could go back into
my streams pull out some things that I
said in the past
and try and cancel me for it
it's very scary being like having all of
that on the internet
so the bigger you grow the more streams
you do
the more dirt there is on you
the more chances you'll get pulled into
something get dragged into drama
oh this is a really good segue into
clout
but yeah I've uh
I'm being very real with you that
drama's not gonna get you anywhere
I know a lot of people think that any
pre like any publicity is good publicity
but
I'm so tired of hearing that
so tired
oh good night rainbow truck good night
I hope you enjoyed stream
bye bye bye bye rainbow trout bye bye
I don't think the drama channels are
cringe I think they're doing good at
summarizing stuff because the drama
channels don't only talk about drama
they talk about genuine news like VTS
updates and they talk about like you
know new models coming out new YouTubers
coming out there's an indie section in
some of them which I think is really
cool like they're actually really
interesting it helps me find out what
trends are going on in the YouTuber
community so I don't think they're
cringe Journey they're actually very
helpful
it helps me you know figure out what's
happening in the world that's the kind
of news I watch I don't watch the news
on TV like CP24 no I watch I watch
YouTuber news
[Music]
yeah if it's all based on drama then no
but like I'll take fall side I really
like watching fall side he has a very
like unbiased opinion about a lot of
things which is good
there he's also just a very interesting
person to watch
but okay like uh I think that's enough
about boundaries let's move on to Cloud
very very important topic
again also very sensitive to some people
but
it needs to be said it needs to be
talked about especially on a day like
this because there is no other time I
will talk about it
yeah they're they're more reporting they
felt like they feel like genuine news
channels like good good reports and
stuff not all of them are dramatic and
start drama or spread it you know
foreign
I'm gonna start like I like I do with
all these topics that come up I'll
always start from the when I was a small
view smaller YouTuber up until now
oh boy oh boy
I love your old boys
okay
you can tell what to say
you can tell the size all good okay
you got some tea yeah we got tea mom
pack and you were there for all of it
do you guys mind if I just go pee before
we get into this I've been sitting here
for almost five hours and I haven't cut
to the washroom
can I go pee
I need to pee
five hours
I always hold back on peeing because I
feel bad when people give me super chats
for peeing sometimes now but I need to
pee so
um I know it's it's it's been five hours
I think all of us need to stand up and
go pee and get a drink all right so I'ma
go pee
I need to
I should try so hard not to say that but
I have to pee
I'm a copy okay okay okay
break no I do not have a be right back
screen this is my be right back screen I
will confidently say I'm in the washroom
and not be like oh yeah I'm just getting
food no I need a Pete
okay I'm gonna go now I'll see you in a
bit
me
foreign
oh gosh Andrew thank you for the pee
dodo
CCO started
thank you for the pee no nose thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
I I pay P get paid to pee guys
also also
I ran to the bathroom and then I ran to
my to my bedroom to grab me
reciprocal
talking forever and I actually have a
sore throat so
I'm gonna take one of these
you're gonna have to hear me talk with
this little candy in my mouth so I can
continue talking
thank you cipical
oh the little flap oh there you go
okay
all right we gotta talk about clout now
all right
I hope you guys all went to P2
and you scratched and you stood up
good night Russell
good night eight point
here we go yeah here we go
okay so close out
would I even begin
you know on Twitter
it always starts with Twitter because
when you're
when you're a YouTuber and you're trying
to
get your name out there you have to
network with other other YouTubers to
kind of like co-requote I mean quote
retweet retweet quote quote retweet your
[\h__\h]
to comment on your stuff
you know
you kind of have to be on Twitter
there's no other place to get your name
out there which is very sad and that's
also where all the YouTuber drama
happens which I think is really funny
because you know normies like to use
Instagram
YouTubers like to use Twitter
very strange
kind of sad Snapchat doesn't exist for
YouTubers but anyway anyway
small YouTuber days smaller of YouTuber
days I should always say that because I
still think I'm pretty small
I around the time I had a hundred
followers or so on Twitter meaning I had
typically before I hit 1K
the numbers on Twitter were always more
than what I had on YouTube
sadly that is how it was which is why I
focused a lot of my going live tweets
and like other random posting [\h__\h] I
always did that on Twitter I hardly used
my YouTube Community Channel which I
think was dumb because I should have
focused on the community Channel learn
from that mistake guys if you're trying
to be a YouTuber full-time like me
thanks for the sister yes
so um
[Music]
did YouTube not want me to talk about
clout
YouTube didn't want me to talk about
oh my God YouTube knows he took notes
I'm trying to share the secrets
[Music]
no
meow
oh I cried oh I Cry
you deleted
that makes me so sad
sad
oh yeah refresh the screen on the guy
okay well
are we backable is everybody okay
send me send me a sign
I'm glad I'm back though I'll be back
we're back
are you back can I talk about clout now
well will student block me again or do I
have to block her
in then
then
is it time to Bonk back
is it time
do I need to bring out the guns
[Laughter]
do I need do I need to Bonk back or are
we good we're good good are we
definitely good
for good good can I talk about cloud and
peace
no I think it was fun I was still able
to chat for some reason but
YouTube was like no your stream is
offline and I was like wait a second
though I get it okay okay
all right
I guess uh now would be time to talk
about the cloud scope happens yeah scuff
happens
this girl that happens full-time
YouTuber but scuff still happens
I believe it's super crap what's true
I've noticed
you didn't know that yeah but that's
okay we'll make do we'll make do I know
YouTube uh I can see it going from
excellent excellent connection to no
data which is strange but hopefully
it'll still be consistent enough later
it's showing me I have 41 concurrent
viewers on the big number and the
smaller number shows me 84 so I don't
really know what it's doing
foreign
okay you know what I'm gonna rant about
Cloud now while we're connected before
it disconnects me
you see 84
I see 64.82
YouTube analytics are [\h__\h]
um
thinking but yeah yeah it did
which I'm not surprised because the
disconnect makes people leave which is
why good internet is so important
anyway anyway we can we can talk about
stuff now we can talk about the cloud
now we don't have to worry about it okay
what do I begin
there's so much stuff you can talk about
regarding clout
okay
we need to we need to take this with a
very professional and and a very uh not
biased opinion
but again I am going to speak from
experience and how being a full-time
YouTuber has influenced said clout
alright
first and foremost last year when I was
a tiny tiny tiny tiny only 50
subscribers YouTuber I was the type of
person who uh was getting roped into
doing clout stuff Cloud seeking stuff
you know how like I said the YouTuber
versus IRL Trend the like for this
retweet for this follow for that comment
for this
those kind of those kind of tweaks
you've seen them you've seen them I
don't need to tell you you've seen them
there's a lot of those I think lately
there's been that striptease game which
is also kind of cute though uh so yeah
so those those exist and
um I was roped into them as a tiny tiny
YouTuber hoping that people would see me
more and I would use a [\h__\h] ton of
hashtags maximum four
just to try and make sure that my name
got out there and like people would do
the whole follow like and retweet thing
for me
those are useless
those are very useless yes they help in
making your numbers higher but you will
never talk to the people that do that
like you'll never you'll never really
get to know the people who only follow
you for said clout
and
getting bigger I was like I don't got
time for this [\h__\h] I would rather spend
time streaming and getting to know my
chat and actually talking to them
instead of only commenting on Twitter
not really doing much except
uh you know
[\h__\h] posting
you found me too far that's nice that's
nice
hi vid yeah YouTube right now um
that's how it was in the beginning for
me is
just to get the numbers
you gotta it's how I started you know
you shouldn't do it I don't think I feel
like you can do it to get the clout but
don't expect that they're gonna stick
around and purposefully go to your shoot
to check out your content nope don't
expect that
I used to also follow back a lot of
people uh even though I hardly knew them
I would always
are you back now
uh
we gotta get to the Cloud topic fast so
this is gonna keep happening
oh my God
academy part two yeah okay okay let's
Zoom through the cloud topic Susan
doesn't like it Susan doesn't like it
that's the case it's okay okay
we're gonna make it through we're gonna
make it through
I need to tell you everything
no I hate guys clown any presents at
school
okay yeah so um follow the trends if you
want to have some clout on your Twitter
account but like I said don't expect it
to take you anywhere don't expect your
viewer account to increase the same
amount that you gained followers and the
people commenting and stuff don't expect
your chat to go any faster no don't do
any of that just know that your follower
account's gonna go up and nothing more
okay Speed Run let's go I'm a rapper
um by the time I got to like a thousand
followers My growth in on Twitter went
uh paletto and my subscriber count on
YouTube did not Plateau it kept going up
so focused a lot on YouTuber
now
um smaller YouTuber me was never willing
to talk to anybody bigger than me never
willing to follow people who were much
much bigger than me
um I only did that because I was very
worried
that they would think I was looking uh
at their content and trying to reach out
to them for the clout
I refused I never did that
if anything I follow like Corporal
YouTubers that I was interested in but
I never followed anybody who's like
Indie YouTuber but kind of big I was
very scared of doing that
and then I eventually just went like you
know if I like you for your content then
I will follow you doesn't matter I
shouldn't look at it too much
uh about
I think
I'm trying to remember exact timing
uh
maybe maybe
[Music]
six months ago so right when I debuted
that's when I gave myself this new rule
I told myself
that once I debuted this new model
I would stop doing the whole follow-back
anybody who follows me stop
uh trying to put that boundary on
yourself and following people you don't
think you're good enough to talk to
and
only follow the people you genuinely
like for their content
the reason why is because
following someone because they followed
you will not get you anywhere you're not
gonna really interact with them much
honestly just the follow for follow
thing is never
never wake
and
I realized that
if I don't like your content
and I
I see that you haven't really put effort
into it
I won't follow you because I only want
to follow the people that
I think are very passionate about
vtubing as a YouTuber okay from a
YouTuber a very professional YouTuber
perspective
I would only follow the people that I
genuinely think are trying to take V2
being seriously they're not gonna start
drama and [\h__\h] they're not going to be a
part of that they're here for a good
time not a dramatic time like me
I would only follow people like that
people I think the content is something
I'm going to genuinely genuinely be
interested in
I need to go back into my account and
unfollow a lot of people who either have
graduated or aren't around anymore
because I feel like that just clogs up
stuff like
I'd rather follow less with quality than
more for quantity
I don't this is just my rule like
everybody again has different opinions
about it
I'm the same with YouTube if I don't
like the content you're posting on
YouTube I won't subscribe to you
and uh
don't get me wrong here
I may follow you on like I may subscribe
to you on YouTube but that does not
necessarily mean I am going to follow
you on Twitter
because
I want to be there for your content on
the platform that you stream on that you
make content on
Twitter is a place where you network
with somebody
and if I don't really want to
if I don't want to talk to you or
anything I don't think we have anything
in common but I want to be there to
support your your content then I will
subscribe to you on YouTube or or follow
you on Twitch and just not follow you on
Twitter because Twitter is not the place
that I'm going to be seeing you
that is my personal take unconscious
candy
yeah I uh rather
follow people who I am going to interact
with on Twitter who I will comment on
like posts and stuff who I will like and
retweet stuff I honestly don't I don't
retweet much to be honest because I like
to keep my profile on Twitter very clean
of things
uh besides today where I tweeted like 13
different things
like
um
like I said full-time YouTuber I don't
have the time for a lot of things uh
social media is my job
but not just it doesn't matter how many
people I follow if I don't
see you if I don't see you post things
if I don't see you
streaming if I don't see her going live
posts and I'm probably never gonna see
you which sucks
so
I'd rather follow less like I don't
follow viewers I will follow other
YouTubers I hope that doesn't hurt
anyone's feelings and
there's a thing with unfollowing that I
think a lot of people have
misconceptions about
uh if I had follow you it means I'm
either not interested in your content
anymore or I don't see you being active
and I don't even know you have never
talked to you in my life maybe I
followed you because I liked your model
but maybe I just haven't seen your
content or
I saw your content once and I just
didn't like it so I've never seen you
around like I just don't want people to
misunderstand when I unfollow them
I am not unfollowing you because I hate
you or because I don't think you're
giving me clouds I will unfollow you if
I don't see you if I don't know you if I
don't like your content
okay as simple as that don't take that
personally this is just me being me if I
don't like your content then there's
probably someone else out there in the
world who does
it's just not me
I think you can tell but what content I
create
that's the kind of content I watch so I
rarely follow like very dark type scary
spooky uh spooky ghosty uh YouTubers
for streamers I like to follow the cute
ones like me
yeah it's not a personal attack no no
it's not
oh
thank you for subscribing
yeah it's not a personal attack it's not
oh like that Doom thank you for
subscribing
yeah I don't I just hope people don't
misunderstand that please please it's
it's I don't want to start [\h__\h] I really
don't how long did you stream for an
empty chat about
four months
or four months
there would be zero people in the
waiting room when I started stream
there'd be one person or two people
waiting with the interest rate intro
screen
um
and then
overall industry they'd be maximum five
watching
and then uh at the end of this stream
probably only like three
and now there's 93 holy
these pictures was very well because
even though we're taking this the wrong
way thank you whoever comes back in the
Stream yeah just please understand me
I'm I'm not it's not a personal attack
I'm not trying to attack you
[Music]
um
talking to no one is very difficult I'll
talk more about that when we get to the
Q a for sure
okay so
um more about the cloud though this is
just unfollowing following and who I
follow who I subscribe to but
b-tubing is not a it's not a lonely
process it should never be if you are
lonely as a YouTuber then you're
probably doing something wrong uh Vito
being involves talking to chat
it involves talking to other YouTubers
to learn from them to get to know them
you have if you have a chat then you're
talking to somebody you're not lonely
maybe you don't like their company but
you're not lonely
and
I feel like people who say they're
lonely
it's that
they're not accepting the company that
they have and making the best of it
that it might be very very insensitive
but this is just my personal opinion
again please don't take it the wrong way
oh my gosh I'm always scared I'm gonna
get canceled for anything I say today
because it's such a sensitive topic
I understand but uh when I was a small
YouTuber I
looking for cloud searching for cloud
posting things and trying to be like
people notice me I have no friends
um that is that is one way to go about
things
but will you have genuine friends that
way just just because you're asking
someone to give you attention
I don't think so I've never heard of
anybody
say that they've made a very great
friend just because they've posted on
Twitter Hey I'm lonely I need friends
can you follow me let's talk in Diaz no
I've never heard of anybody making a
genuine long-lasting relationship that
way
kind of sad but
it's very true
and there was one time I made a tweet
like that because
I thought that's what everybody did
I thought it like again I last year I
was very very new to social media so I
thought that's just what everybody did
so I did the same thing
wasn't a good idea
no that was it wasn't a very good idea
so I ended up
um growing on my own Merit
and
it's something that I'm very very
proud of
that I'm able to talk about
like
how I did it on my own quote unquote
like yes I had a lot of friends and I
had a lot of people encouraging me and
motivating me even though I felt like
quitting
it's
I tried very hard to make sure I
streamed consistently and that I brought
in new viewers on my own
I never rated anybody could not do that
at the time re-rating people is new
and no one raided me because all my
friends were on Twitch and you'd have to
manual raid which is kind of weird very
difficult to do to make people click on
links for some reason
so
I never I don't think I Grew From clout
I feel like it's very hard to grow from
Cloud to make people safe with cloud
uh so I never sought for cloud
but
as I got bigger maybe once I hit the 1K
Mark that's when I started meeting a lot
of other people
and a lot of other YouTubers
those being who were smaller than me and
bigger than me
uh some smaller ones who like people who
were smaller than me as a YouTuber some
of them are nice some of them I could
tell were looking for clout because the
second they slipped into DMS they'd be
like hey I saw you stream this would you
like to collab together
that is clear clear sign
you only found me and you you just want
to collab with me so that
my 10 viewers can give you something
to give you a little boost from your
five
which I used to have
and I can understand the desperation of
wanting to grow
I I totally get it I was very desperate
to go to why do you think I streamed so
much it's because I wanted to grow too I
tried very hard
but
I can't
I can't just send my viewers to you
they're not gonna stay just because I
told them to
so why would you try why are you trying
to steal my viewership
and
when you're a small YouTuber like that
you can get very sensitive
about those things
uh you can tell I'm talking slower
because I'm thinking things through in
my head before I say it
[Music]
um
like when you're small you want to grow
faster so you have more chat to interact
with you have other YouTubers who are
noticing you and I get it I've been
through it
I still have like stream elements
notifications and emails about my uh
what's it called my
viewer average viewer account Peak Peak
content uh Peak viewer average thing I
still have all of those emails from way
way way back when
I'm gonna see if I can find it
uh don't select all how do I filter
these how do I filter my mail guys
what is this
how do you do that oh was it this button
Mark all is red no that's not it that oh
wait no I can just search up stream
elements
uh stream elements report let's go for
oh wow
this was this is a while ago I'll just
screenshot it for you guys
uh right there I'm Gonna Save this
[Music]
um
turkey let's see
it's right here
back when I had still had my Japanese
name up there
this was October 24th
average viewer amount was 11.
and stream elements Revenue was only 10
bucks
yeah for a stream that probably lasted
like three or four hours
I don't even earn minimum wage guys
I'm pretty different she hasn't coming
out about the state for you yeah yeah
um I agree I agree yes yes
[Music]
one dollar per person yeah that was that
was a good thing that was a really good
thing
but
um
being of that size at that time in
October people were coming to me for
clothes like what cloud can I give you
still happened and I met some bigger
YouTubers than myself who were getting
around like 30 viewers on average at the
time
and they
they didn't treat me too differently
some of them
some of them were very high on their
horses like
they'd be like you're tiny I'm like
thank you
so I've learned to avoid people like
that
I've met a lot of egotistical people who
are just like I'm a full-time streamer
and I get like 30 per screen what do you
get like 10 oh my God you know I've
heard yeah I've actually heard people
talk like that and uh it gets on my
nerves
it's my nerves
but
um
yeah yeah
I don't know I don't know
I don't think I know what it's like to
be egotistical besides saying yeah I'm
cute yes I have these talents
but like
I I still think I'm a very humble person
if you follow me
if you follow me I can give you so many
viewers
follow my channel and like collab with
me once I got you
laughs
and I've actually talked to people like
that before in the vitamin Community
which is very very sad
but yeah
[Laughter]
I'm so glad I don't talk to them anymore
but my God I know they're still out
there I know they're still out there but
I'm not gonna say who it is because
that's my morals I'm not gonna go
against it
laughs
so basically
um I did beat some good and some bad
bigger YouTubers than me at the time
and I learned that not everybody who is
a big YouTuber
is a good person they may be a very good
v-tweeter they may be
a very opinionated streamer
that does not always mean that they're a
good one and that's okay because if
people like their content then they like
their content I cannot stop them I am
not in control of what they do with
their time their body their money
so let them be let the egotistical
viewers and and streamers be because
they're just living their life what can
you do
that Divine act like a celebrity
that's so strange
what do you think I'm trying to be some
Mall
I only want to know if they do something
because yeah some of them did yes I'm
genuinely they did some of them like two
of them that I met yeah
love the colors and they're very cute
can you do a British rally girl accent
maybe I'll try that one day
the other people say to never meet your
Heroes I would die if I found out my
Patriot was an [\h__\h] or something yeah
see I don't think I don't think Kiana
would be I think she's genuinely a good
person
but at the same time I would die if she
was an [\h__\h] and I I swear to God
she's not but like if like if I had a
0.00
you're one chance that she is I would
die
hi
not all Valley girls are [\h__\h] okay
some of them are really nice like cozy
I'm kidding cozy I love you
I love you cozy
um I might be starving at least my head
works exactly exactly
yeah
I never did exactly exactly like you
know you know you you can you can tell
when you talk to somebody for so long
when you've watched them stream for so
long you can't keep up the Goody
Two-Shoes act forever if you're
genuinely a good person it'll come off
that way if you're genuinely an
egotistical like bastard then
you're ill ill show ill show
especially in games because there are
things on games in games I mean that
bring out things that trigger you
so you can't hide it forever
just gotta avoid those people
and I've learned to avoid them I've kept
my
thankfully I've kept my circle of
friends quite small and trusted people
so like they're only full of trusted
people which is a good thing
why do you think I love her so much
another blind I don't still says exactly
exactly like I can be slow and careful
with my words so I don't say something
that's shitty but
I cannot lie
that is my rule of thumb streams is I
cannot lie if I'm genuinely having a
hard time I will tell you kind of like
what happened with my bank account you
know like it hurt me and I was almost
about to cry or like the stories of how
I told you about my parents and how I
told them that I was a full-time
streamer I can't lie about that no
especially if my mom is gonna come into
the stream okay like I can't lie
there's no way to lie at least not for
me and not from the kind of content that
I that I create I'm too genuine for that
thank you
exactly so
is I'm gonna backtrack about a month ago
um
gradually more people
are seeking me for clout especially what
happened in November
so some big things that happened in
November are that
um I'm gonna have to bring this back up
again but
uh I started talking to more Kawa
entertainment people
I know tsunati was around when that all
happened
uh servos you were there when that
happened montpaka you were also there
when that happened a lot of you who are
here were there when that all happened
so
um uh I guess summarize for the new
viewers in chat uh last month or was it
even the month before I don't really
remember uh
when I started collabing with cozy more
often
a lot of people
uh not a lot I mean honestly it's zero
is already considered considered good
enough but like even one is just like
why and then four was
ugh yeah anyway
I started collabing with cozy a lot last
month and we became very close as
friends
and I also started collabing with Frey
who was introducing me to a lot of his
really good friends he knows the lost
city for God's sake and if you don't
know who they are they're hollow life
reacts are very nice
um and he also introduced me to Nick who
is a very very big musician
um who also knows some prison project
people I uh also talked to more kava
talents which is one of the biggest
things that happened
yeah service I saw what happened with
you in Quota I was just like what the
[\h__\h]
let the boys be boys please
anyway
uh because I started talking to pretty
much all of the Kawa entertainment
talents
um
they I got four DMS at me saying
something along the lines of urakawa
cloud chaser you just want to get
through to their auditions because they
opened auditions that week
um that you're just going to them for
clout
um stop talking to these people
things like that so
um
I never mentioned it on stream when it
happened
only a few days after did I mention it
on stream because I was over all the
emotional pain from it
uh I talked about it on stream very
briefly I just said oh yeah some people
dm'd me calling me a college cloud
chaser and I just moved on but no
because because he got angry for me
on stream she was just like what the
[\h__\h] why why are people doing that to
you and then she went on Twitter on a
rant going like hey
some people called in I hear some people
are calling my friend me a cloud chaser
she's not a cloud chaser we're not dumb
she was livid she was she was very angry
on my behalf which made me very happy
but also sorry that
she was angry because I felt like I was
the cause of it
oh no form thank you for subscribing
this is whatever you want do whatever
yeah thank you I hope more people think
that people were acting trashy I was so
glad that the comments were all really
like supportive about it
um
[Music]
talents have no say in auditions and
people don't really have the facts
straight when I hit 3K
four out of six Kawa talents ended up
coming into my chat and they were
congratulating me we had many
conversations in chat it was sunny Kota
cozy and pfp I remember that very
clearly because that was a very
wonderful day for me I was sipping for
them real hard with the debuted okay
impressive Ranch so impressive
and
um that's right you can do it yes you
did I remember that
you stayed the longest
and so so before auditions came out they
already knew me I already knew them I
talked to Cozy a lot but people still
called me a cloud chaser when auditions
came out even though we had already
collabed a few times
so I guess
um
this is what scared me is that I was
afraid I would get dragged into
something like this when I was a smaller
YouTuber but people would call me cloud
chaser that I was only talking to
someone for their viewers for their
numbers
I really really wanted to avoid it but I
guess it's unavoidable it's inevitable
and I'm glad it blew over people were
very understanding about it the Kawa
management were also really good about
it they asked me for names but it is
against my morals to give said names I
don't want to ruin people's careers so
I just told the kala management people
they have nothing to worry about
especially for auditions
uh there's like I'm being very
transparent about it I told them details
about who these people were that they
did not have to worry about them getting
through
so it blew over which I'm very happy
about it's just the fact that it
happened which makes me kind of sad
um and that was one thing the second
thing that happened last month that made
me blow up was Leah from FaZe connect
rating me
he remembers that
I think I hardly even she'd like a bit
about it yeah I know
you were there for that too [\h__\h]
you were you were you
that was a big day it was a big day
Boston you remember it too um
I like that you hear a lot though
you see him all the time you make
connections I stream daily I take like a
day or two off sometimes but there was
like a month I just streamed every day
and I didn't take a break I feel so
sorry for my mods mods if you guys want
to go to bed please go to bed it's okay
I can watch chat I can watch chat it's
okay
yeah someone from face connect rated me
if you do not know who they are it is
um I've been a member of her channel on
my private account for a long time too
but I recently became a member on this
youtubing account on her channel so I
lost my badges but that's okay
uh she's she's a dork but I love her
um when I saw my stream elements uh
report for the stream my Peak viewership
was
414. on average that stream was
130 I believe in viewership
so
I I was very surprised I was very
surprised it was a big number my numbers
are normally double digits underneath
30.
so I'm scared Zale thank you so much
you've been here since the beginning too
since I met hifuni I know I've known you
and you're that 90 now which is very
scary to me
it's very scary to me I'm trying not to
think about it because I want to be as
genuine as possible when explaining
things today this is the only time I'm
gonna say it like I said I'm not
probably never gonna bring this these
things up again unless unless people
really ask me to
he's in Destin for bigger numbers people
like you all thank you I don't know if
I'm ready for that
many currencies I've seen
so what you don't need to remember that
the fanfic streams are fun but okay okay
back on track here
um
Leah raided me with that many people and
I panicked real hard but
it was my first time streaming to
upwards of 50 viewers consistently which
meant
but I I felt the need to try harder to
stream
very very very very very very very very
very very often
remember the day you had that random
money for years I gotta know it yeah I
think those are Bots but that's okay
yes I will I will knowing me yeah I'm
also gonna talk a bit quieter so I don't
strain my voice too much okay I hope
that's all right
[Music]
um
so after that day my numbers shot up a
lot and thanks to Leah who I've known
for like seven months now
she's I feel like being around cozy
and having those collabs with her
talking with her being happier in
general and then Leo's raid
it set my channel flying in the
algorithm
because of the uh I ended up gaining
about 200 subscribers which was amazing
I was at the low end of three thousand
at the start of the month now we're at 4
000 something like what the [\h__\h]
but yeah uh I have I have to thank Leah
a lot for that
I don't want to the thing is raids are
great
but it's very hard to make people stay
after the raid which is why I tried very
hard to just say everything that was
positive about myself the second I get
raided
I tried very very very very very hard
you kept about 100 people yeah I did
because I know after the raid people
instantly leave but 150 people stayed
I never thought that I could keep 150
people entertained for four hours I
think that stream was four hours
so
after the raid
my viewership went back to normal of
about you know 30 40. it was no longer
20 30. I haven't seen the number 20 in a
very long time
but it's always been within 30 40.
and for a while it was it was very nice
it was very nice I thank Leah for that
for boosting my average viewer account
by like 10 which is a lot okay it's a
lot
and then
yeah good retention very good retention
so then
I rated Kelly
which again boosted Me by maybe a
hundred because it wasn't so it wasn't
like too big of a deal she didn't talk
about me too much she kept focusing on
Pokemon which I'm also very thankful for
it's like she could keep her chat
entertained and mine because I had to
leave I had to dip
and then
um yeah I gained about 100 from that
it was amazing the fact that I I was
confident enough to read
Kelly and then I also had the option to
she thought that was nice
I love you guys there's nobody's clear
how much work you put into YouTube
Because all these girls are so dessert
so freaking happy for you thank you
tonight thank you thank you you're hard
working too I see you I see you out
there
we should talk sometime
yeah that um
thanks to Kelly
I I did grow I don't know if any of her
viewers
stayed in my chat or anything but they
came and they subscribed to me which I'm
very thankful for
and then two streams later
I had a morning stream out of nowhere
and I rated uh Kiara because that's her
typical streaming time I don't normally
stream in the morning because I like to
watch Kiana in the morning
uh and then
around
that's when she was just like me
okay Lars made a tiny little clip of
Kiara uh talking about me very briefly I
hope it's okay if I show it
um I don't I don't know if it's okay if
I show it but
um it's it's a rough draft I hope I hope
it's okay I hope it's okay if I show it
um
I'm just gonna okay I'm gonna mute all
the bgm stuff for now let me just see if
it's it's okay it's still an unlisted
thing
it's not up anywhere yet uh but I feel
like
this will give you an idea of why I'm so
happy that
she rated me uh I'm just gonna make this
smaller
the English
okay okay we're gonna I'm gonna stop bgm
real quick
okay wait I gotta
let me hide this real quick so I can get
the audio at the right point
oh
hold on
okay
it's not gonna be too loud
uh
but it should be loud enough for you
guys to hear
okay
we'll just watch this and relish in the
moment together yeah okay I hope it's
okay that I show this if not I'll just
blur it out later and mute it okay
another red this time who
hi again hello
[Music]
that's so funny because just yesterday
it just yesterday I was watching some of
her stream archive
and I was thinking yo that voice is so
cute why is she not in whole life
English
[Laughter]
just yesterday I was thinking then
hey I knew it sounded familiar to me
yeah
I don't know I think I I found
ah
if you're on Twitter or YouTube
algorithm I don't know then I was
curious because his design was kind of
cute
no no problem
you killed please audition for hollow
life English
yeah okay that's what happened there you
go well that's my stream Beats
that's that's what happened
that's what happened that is what that
is what made
a lot of things happen
uh I hope I hope it is now
understandable why this is my Kami Oishi
okay she's my Connie Lucy
she is my cumulation I was freaking out
it's freaking the [\h__\h] out okay
I would have died I I am dead inside but
also very happy happy happy
really
[Music]
it was so nice I didn't expect her to
like shout me out like that because I
know Cali didn't she didn't she didn't
know me but
yeah she knows me and then she followed
me back on Twitter and then when I
streamed later that day in the afternoon
she she
said
she said that I was very skilled and
talented if you go into my just chatting
stream that has the thumbnail with the
word the two kanji on the left I think
it just said
and the title is just like I'm surviving
on a really good day
she was in that chat oh my God I burped
she was she was in nightstream she was
chatting
and you'll be able to see her talk in my
chat which was even bigger like I was
like
thank you
she was there she was there I have
screenshots of every single thing she
said because I really really needed
yeah that doesn't no it wasn't a fan cat
she came in when I was making the
hangout face of all things
I was combusting I couldn't sit still I
was shaking I wanted to nap that day
because I only had four hours of sleep
but I was so excited I just had to
stream and then she came into my stream
for like an hour like she stayed for an
hour and then I ended the Stream
I had to prepare for a collab that night
so I streamed three times that day but
yes okay back to the cloud thing
everybody from Kiana's dream who was
there that day I think because Kiana
knew me that she said she watches my
archives and she thought I was cute she
said my voice was cute another thing
that's the main reason why a lot of
people came to find me and I did post on
Twitter too I gained like 200 followers
on Twitter because of that one little
one little thing she said about me oh my
God
and
um about
I think it's still going to this day
but
she she wants me to audition for
Halloween
I'm a bit scared of doing that because I
don't think I'm ready for that I also
auditioned for Kala so if I get into
Kawa
I would I would stick with color I'm not
gonna lie at least for a year so I can
build myself up more
I feel like it'd be better for me as
like a streamer I know a lot of you will
be like no just go for it but um
nah I'd rather solidify my place in the
world first make my mark
ERS thank you
I'm not gonna lie I really wish I could
collab with Kiara one day that'd be
that'd be a dream come true but I don't
think I have the power yet
again to add me confident thank you I
will try if I get into color I'd like to
do like
conventions and stuff but overseas if
possible because I I have multilingual
Talent I'll expand color
but okay anyway
we had to talk about the cloud all the
drama that comes with it
um
did I even begin with this one too uh
because of the things that happened with
Kiara
uh I've had some people ask me like
is this is this fake
is this true
uh and
a day later
four or five I think five five
[Music]
yeah five people slipped into my DMs and
was like Hey Mia
it's been a while
would you like to collab again would you
like to start talking again would you
like to uh hang out off stream sometime
and you know what one or two of them
were genuine good friends who I had
before we just fell apart
but some of them
were uh not
one of them was just like do you want to
collab again and in my head I'm like
have I ever collapsed with you so I went
through my entire like uh streaming list
of stuff
like you know how in your YouTube Studio
thing you can see all the past streams
you've done in the lifetime uh
don't never collapse with this person
yeah oh no oh dear
yeah it was um
it wasn't enough
just because of that and uh I I said no
to all of them just two of them I was
like yeah let's let's get back to
talking I miss talking to you
but since then they haven't messaged me
once so I was like oh okay I guess that
bridge is burned
not by choice it just fell apart the
bridge stopped Midway oh the yeah thank
you for subscribing
the the bridge stopped mid-construction
because they run out of budget you know
budget meaning time and care
did you try it together into thinking
you collect Brian I was just like did I
actually
they're talking about nothing
yeah it was uh
I I understand that like I got a lot of
new followers and I got a lot of
um like new viewers thanks to Kiara
which like I keep saying
please keep supporting Kiana you don't
have to come to me it's okay I
appreciate the sentiment but it's okay I
understand wanting to talk and being
chiada's dreams I get in I'm a kfp too
it's she's my cubby horsey
okay
Saturday yeah
okay [\h__\h] fine fine
you like me though thank you
yeah they uh they kind of just fell off
the edge of the Earth again never to be
seen and that's okay that's on them they
missed out on a good ass friendship that
we could have had
this sucks for them I know I'm great
okay but yeah that's the kind of clap
that I've had to experience uh people
asking me for collabs uh people wanting
me for my numbers and
back when I had a hundred subscribers I
used to think people who had 1 000
subscribers as an indiev tuber were huge
now like since then I've learned that
there are ndv tubers who have upwards of
200 000 then a million and
it is scary to think about that but
at the same time
I'm
very happy that even with this number as
a subscriber count whatever it is now
I can hold a stream with an average
number of viewers that are upwards of
30.
because it's very rare most people when
they look at uh this is like another
typical rule or just Trend I should say
not rule
the average number of viewers you get is
typically one percent of your subscriber
count
one to ten percent Maybe
yeah
something if you have three thousand uh
subscribers people will they might say
you have 30 viewers on average
sometimes that is true sometimes that is
not
like if I had 1 000 subscribers I would
have 10 viewers which was very true when
I had 2 000 subscribers I had 20 viewers
on average also very true 3 000
subscribers I had 30 viewers on average
again another truth so
I I feel like it's only recently because
of all the things that have happened
that it is not true anymore now that I
have four thousand well I have 20 I
think it's 20 to 30 percent
yeah yeah
High sub counts though yeah it's
typically true when you're small but
I guess now that I have 4 000 that's not
true anymore you guys broke the system
you broke my pattern
thank you for that though
so yeah I I never expected to have
more than 30 at this point in time
and my growth was so steady you guys are
ruining the growth pattern thank you
though
I think he's like a teacher talking to a
whole class also somebody talking about
p and clout um
go to play but no no let's let's aim for
the silver let's aim for silver play
button I would like the silver play
button give me the silver play but give
me all the clout
that's not how it works but at least let
me say it once
that's under one percent is how many are
seven guys that's true I've seen that
but honestly like if you're a fan then
I feel like
that's good enough
in case that would be happening so what
do you mean estimated you're funny look
at that gnome
silver is a hundred thousand 100 100k
yeah
I predict you achieving that silver play
button who knows who knows I can't
predict the future
there's how the 100 cases I kind of get
more than 100 live yeah yeah
okay good night Carlos goodbye
everybody
I hope you get one education thank you
again I do not want to hop on Cloud for
it I need to make that very clear I know
very well that just getting clout from
other people will not get me there I
know that very well because just because
I have numbers does not mean I have
loyal fevers does not mean I'm gonna get
more income
it's not true it's not true the only way
I feel like the only way
that I would feel satisfied with my
growth is if I worked hard to get there
and I have evidence and streams and
content to show for it
so I feel like I deserve
the subscriber count that I have
um
I need to make more covers actually but
my throat is like shot dead because I've
been streaming so much and it's our pain
yeah
but I I genuinely feel like I would only
be satisfied
with streaming as often as I do like
that I get my numbers through my hard
work if I get my numbers through Cloud I
know that people aren't genuinely gonna
want to be here that they're not gonna
stay unless they somehow end up liking
me for some reason
[Music]
yeah it is common it is very common
maybe I might be that outlier who knows
I do not know I just hope that whatever
it is I do or say on stream makes
someone's day
mm-hmm
[Music]
I think the initial Panic is to be
expected
but
but at the same time
if you can't continue with that number
then I don't think you're ready
same that's how it was for me I didn't
think I was ready to handle a hundred
viewers at once but I did so it makes me
feel like I'm ready and if it ever
happens I'll be prepared for it
but at the same time I wanted to be from
my own hard work and it was earned
I'm sorry if I mumble out your messages
I'm just trying to make sure I read them
fast before it gets sent up into the
void
if I don't want to jump on no I okay I
want to apply to hololive because well
but also because
um I actually auditioned once a long
time ago
and I wasn't ready I wasn't prepared but
I had the experience of doing it
and I've applied to other agencies
before
but I didn't make it into any like any
of them so I didn't feel like I was
ready and I decided to put my effort
into my own channel before I started
applying to anything again
oh probably then thank you for the donut
the long stream rolled out like a
pancake hey let's go
so
um
I want to try I also feel like I have
more freedom being on my own
the other thing is I I like hard work
seeing you know I like seeing results
from my hard work it comes it comes from
my mom my mom and I are very result
oriented people we don't look at the
process as much as we look at the the
results so
the only way we get the result is if we
do something in something and something
right like step one two three
and yeah I I care about how
I get to a certain point it comes with a
perfectionism thing like it is what it
is
was there any big difference between
handling 100 plus three to the yeah I
think with 20 to 30
I didn't have to look at chat as much
because it was going slower but with 100
I kept
being like gender
because I pride myself on being able to
read Jet
actually interacting with you and
commenting and replying to things you
say
so it was very chaotic for me to have to
go back and forth
but I did it I think I pulled it off
thank God I have a really fast reading
speed this is what I get for reading fan
fictions when I was younger bless the
fanfiction
okay that becomes a different sorts of
trade-offs that's why I'm very careful
with the agencies I apply to I applied
for Kala for that reason
you have failures never a funner it's
just not the difference exactly like if
I see all this Cloud die down I know
this particular stream is getting me a
lot of viewership because of the content
that I'm creating the stuff I'm talking
about today
isn't common it's something people don't
typically like to talk about it puts
streamers in a very vulnerable and very
easily doxed position
which I totally understand like why
people would be coming to see me today
and they might not come back ever again
and that's okay
I just hope that whatever I did today
has helped somebody out there and you
can maybe refer them back to this stream
if they ever want to know about stuff
why am I still awake because it's only 2
A.M this is fine this is normal
are you awake
but okay that's that's the cloud section
guys I still have q a to get through
so
um that's me and clout I get that it's
very nice to have
and people will seek me out for it and I
will never seek people out for it
simple as that
great papers oh gosh I hope you're okay
oh no that'll sound fun do people come
into that one they don't even watch so
sometimes they try search on the
internet for stuff if I accidentally do
something yeah
uh okay where is the other stuff that
I'm looking for
oh understanding numbers I guess is also
part of cloud
[Music]
um
I wasn't able to tell what a big and a
small YouTuber was when I started and I
think a lot of people are like that me
you're hard not to like thank you
I feel like my voice is not exactly High
nor low
uh it's not
particularly very very cute or very very
only I'm just kind of mean it
somewhere in the middle
this isn't a condensed torture so this
has been nice to me oh you're welcome
outside
again I'll answer questions in the Q a
thing that I have set up at the end of
the stream because I might answer some
of them as I talk about stuff yeah okay
uh
so yeah if you have any questions go
ahead and ask it I will try and get to
it and leave it for the Q one day at the
end of the Stream
uh okay yeah noon Bridge
thank you I've been told that when I
speak because I raise my voice and it
doesn't sound monotone that it's
interesting how are you going to go to
wait how long are you going to go
probably for like another hour I try
I'll try and get all of this other stuff
I have in my notes for an hour
oh thank you
your voice is extremely recognizable
though that's a huge plus is it
was that recognizable
oh good night X bye-bye
you'd say so wow
you don't extremely recognize leaving
when you babble
what if I tried to sound like Animal
Crossing
[Music]
does it still sound like me
when did you learn
then you have a meeting
he's making cookies
that was exactly easy
no no no no no no no no no
still be it [\h__\h]
that means if I ever go into hololive
and they give me a new model you're
still gonna know it's me
still recognizable oatmeal
and I guess if I ever debut in Hell
alive and I have you know I speak this
many languages oh there's no way there's
no way I can get away with it laughs
there's no way
my mumbling was like easy was it oh no
that
we'll know what the energies right away
[Music]
just look for the grandma and I don't
okay
immediately yeah look at your Secret
Safe Keep all the unsafe so things I've
done safe
checking for your next gen no no don't
check on me for next that's a little too
soon I don't think I'm ready
I had your power level a bit
novel that's true
okay fine fine all the stuff that my
voice is unique all right fine fine
okay okay yeah I didn't know what being
do you guys know about this the whole
big number small Number issue where are
you allowed to talk to Big YouTubers are
you allowed to talk to small YouTubers
and you're staying in your lane thing
you guys know about that right you guys
know about that right
staying in your lane have you ever heard
that among these two words because I'm
pretty pretty sure if you're into Indies
that you would have heard something like
that before
I was like gatekeeping the one that
you've all been curious about you don't
know about it all right we're gonna
educate and all the other people who
don't know about it
so
um
in the victory community
uh
uh yeah I yeah I heard it but it doesn't
mean it has any validity exactly it
doesn't have any validity it is a social
construct that is made up from people
who are trying to gatekeep you from
making friends
uh basically if you have a hundred
subscribers you're only allowed to you
know talk to other people who are just
as small as you
if you have a thousand followers on
Twitter you're only allowed to talk to
others who also have a thousand
subscribers as you I mean followers as
you
you're allowed to follow bigger people
on Twitter but you're not allowed to
physically go into their DMS and be like
hey you know
you if you have like 10K you are
suddenly in the Limelight you are you
are a bigger YouTuber as an indie as an
indie that is big to have 10 day all
right Apparently that is that is how it
is
and if you have if you have 10K you're
allowed to talk to other people who have
10K be it 10K to 19k right that's the
range you're allowed to talk to those
people and if if you talk to smaller
people you're being very very generous
now if you have anything upwards of 100
to like 3 or 500 you're in the like
Elite of of the uh of the uh individ
tubing scene and or like even the small
company vegetable scene okay and uh
sometimes you'll see the people who are
underneath a hundred okay followers on
Twitter collab with those who have
upwards of 100K and they that's like the
the very cool people who are slowly
slipping into the DMS and taking the
risk of stepping outside of their Lanes
now if you have upwards of 500 000 your
freaking celebrity you are the [\h__\h] and
then if you're in Hollow live me design
TV Shoujo or any other bigger company
that's the same standard as that then
you are just a God above all gods those
are the lens those are the numbers that
uh was taught to me that uh
the the community has shown me which I
think is dumb as a [\h__\h] because that
doesn't mean [\h__\h]
and to people who buy with each other
really good attitude
[Music]
I agree it is very gatekeeping type
attitude
it is not worth
anything
in my opinion
and when you're in the thousands like
beneath 10K
speaking to somebody who has a thousand
more than you is already a big deal
apparently I do not think that is true
but I'm just imparting to you knowledge
that has come from other YouTubers
oh good night Nate thank you for coming
good night bye-bye
they'll be super police don't don't do
that
don't arrest me I'm innocent
people think about numbers so much to
get something making Daniel Francis
sometimes it's sad it is so sad it is so
sad like of course I'm happy when a
bigger YouTuber follows me because if
other people notice that they follow me
they're like oh maybe I'll check you out
and it makes me happy
but at the same time
the numbers in general I feel like don't
matter to me if I see a 10K like
followed YouTuber on Twitter I don't
click follow right away
I will always check your content
before I follow you or subscribe to you
or follow you on Twitch
and
it saddens me that these lanes were
created as like they're socially
constructed this there is no harsh line
here there's no document stating that
this is all true
it's Jets just a social construct that
people make so that people are afraid to
reach out or some [\h__\h]
staying in these guys preventing growth
don't jug up yeah I don't like judging
people just off their numbers and what
they've done on Twitter you gotta look
at what
the content they're making is as okay
like I said I am doing V2 being
full-time I am very careful with who I
interact with
so
I always do a little background check on
people before I either follow or
subscribe to them
[Music]
exactly
frustrates me so much when people tell
me that I'm too small for this I'm too
small for that even though I know I say
that where I'm too small to be doing
this not too small to be doing but like
I always say I'm too small to be I'm not
I'm not on the same level as no Corporal
I'm an indie and unfortunately yes
Indies haven't
they're like in a different world
sometimes because carpals do have some
support and they get to go to events and
stuff and they get nice models and you
know they get merch and all of that they
get a lot of resources and a lot of help
but they do work really hard
Indies on the other hand have other
things they have to worry about like
making their own stuff a lot of the time
and networking a lot of networking
networking is more like
I guess this goes into the networking
part now
[Music]
uh
I don't think networking should be
something people shy away from even
though I did I mean you guys know I was
sexually harassed at the beginning of my
V tipping career which made it very
scary for me to talk to other people
so I grew my channel by streaming a lot
by talking to my chat a lot
and when I slowly got more comfortable I
talked to more people and I debuted new
models which gathered more people's
attention and so I ended up being able
to talk to bigger YouTubers than I was
and I eventually grew and sometimes I
even surpassed then
no no no what does India need to worry
about game parents and stuff like that
sometimes but not often no
[Music]
exactly you have to work hard if you're
a YouTuber and you want to get out there
and make it then yes
no it's okay Jacob I've gotten over it
it's all right but thank you though
uh I feel like networking is very
different for your personality if you're
an extrovert easy if you're an introvert
hard
uh even for extrovert sometimes it might
be difficult because you don't know
where to draw the line and I've heard
that from Frey
uh he knows a lot of Corpus so yeah
um as an indie who's extra who's very
introverted
I feel like
the way that I networked was uh if they
came if a YouTuber came into my stream I
would reach out be like thank you for
coming and if they want to keep talking
then we'll keep talking if they don't
then we don't
um and
sometimes uh I'll go and watch their
content before I reach out first and be
like hey uh I like the stream of yours
good job I hope you have a good night
things like that I'll always be
very polite very surface level uh
because if they don't reply to that
that's okay but if they do then
wonderful I said Thank you to Leah and
DMS for the raid and she replied which
was very nice and I just wished her a
good night which is cute
so it hasn't gone further than that and
I don't expect it to I really don't I
just wanted to thank her genuinely
uh so yeah
um
[Music]
right back
obvious please hold on
are you okay
okay
are you alive
are you alive OBS please
did we hold it we held it nice good job
guys
oh I needed the water oh gosh let me
drink more
no I am not like most streamers I do not
drink out of a water bottle I drink out
of a mug
thank you for the welcome back
we will hold the line
thank you for holding the line I have so
much stuff I need to talk about I didn't
even get to the Q a yet
okay okay okay okay let me get my notes
back out
oh
okay well what were you talking about
again
this is thank you for the welcome back
[Music]
okay have a good have a good rest
of our kingdom
don't chase me like this no my God so
much fun
so much fun
so much fun oh yeah technical
difficulties full-time beat to break I
don't know actually any YouTubers should
know how to do it Lanes right
well I mean I think I think I finished
talking about it
uh oh yeah okay introverted YouTuber
you can tell I don't call that with too
many people if you've been on my channel
you've uh looked at the other live
streams I've done I do not collab with
many people
that is not my thing I do not do that
I'm very picky with who comes up to my
channel now but networking is still very
important it's important to keep up your
relationships with people outside of
stream and on stream I actually have an
IRL friend who wants to become a
streamer a YouTuber so I'm planning on
helping him do that I think he said he
also wants to be on YouTube so I'm
gathering more YouTube I indie YouTubers
let's go
um
yeah I've been reaching out a lot more
recently because I now feel comfortable
doing it and you know I'm not gonna lie
having the higher numbers makes me feel
more confident about it
it sucks to say
but uh it does it really really does it
makes me think that me reaching out to
people is an okay thing
nice introduce us sometimes I'll try I
will definitely try I I rate the people
that I'm friends with typically because
I know they're gonna treat my chat well
so I care about you guys okay I care
about your well-being I will never bring
you to somebody who's not gonna take
care of you while I have to leave
but I think like recently I've been
talking to like statical Frey uh Leo
came into my stream which is cool
um I even saw Xander the other day for
the like he he rated me today uh he
hated Ezra yesterday
and
um I've always I've been talking to Ezra
sometimes
um I've been I've still been talking to
my gigamara familia I do not want people
to think I don't talk to them anymore
because I don't mention them as much but
the only reason why I don't mention them
as much if you don't know who they are
it's basically the people who uh I'm I
was in a friend group with in the
Discord server and
um
we all kind of bended together to make a
mini mini very unofficial uh
YouTuber group
our main rule is we do not we we do not
start drama with anybody and we're all
friends okay bye tonight
I hope you have a good night and thank
you for coming
I will answer
let's be friends
yeah have a good night tonight thank you
for being here for honestly a long time
wow
but yeah uh
I I've been reaching out I've been
getting noticed and I feel like the
numbers are helping uh for me to get
over my introvertedness
and it all started with cozy so I
I love cozy so much for that
YouTube tonight bye bye have a good
night
that definitely so creepy I know right I
know right thank you thank you I'm
trying really hard not to sound like a
creep right now
laughs
okay I think that's enough if you have
questions about how I talk to people as
an introvert and a YouTuber you know
shoot them shoot them at me uh thing is
uh I'm an introvert who's also
apparently a public figure
so I think that's something I need to
talk about uh
let's just let's just talk about it in
streaming I'm being a streamer being on
the internet as you all know the
internet is a scary place where people
talk to you where people try and find
out personal information and fraud
happens you know it's a scary place but
at the same time
you are if you're a streamer you are
trying to become famous you cannot deny
that you're trying to become famous you
are trying to get people to know who you
are and give you attention why do you
think people want higher viewer accounts
is because they want more people to
watch them they want more subscribers
because that means that they have a
loyal audience who will come and watch
them you cannot deny that if you're a
YouTuber you're kinda kind of an
attention seeker
so at least a tiny capacity you have to
admit that okay you have to there is no
way you can deny that you don't want
attention you you that you want
attention at me like you you cannot deny
you want attention there's no way there
is no way
really
okay that's a good thing I take that as
a good thing
sounds like me
I I do like attention I'm not gonna lie
I like attention but at the same time
and I'm I'm an introvert I don't talk to
people I know what it's like to be an
extrovert because I used to be one when
I was in high school I would go around a
lot and talk to a lot of friends I had a
big friend group a lot of people liked
me in high school I was popular in high
school
yeah I was one of those anime girls who
people asked for like notes and oh my
God you're so pretty what do you do with
your hair and be like hey you want to go
shopping after school you want to go
shopping this weekend I was one of those
people would ask me for [\h__\h] people
would ask me what makeup I used I was
one of them I was one of them
I'm like um
that's basically me I'm a gremlin at
home my gosh but in school I was I was
that I was that person
oh goodnight ladies I know it's getting
late for a lot of you so don't worry
about it go to bed go to bed if you need
to it's okay
this is
but yeah you have to admit that as a
streamer you are going into the public
eye and things you say and do are kept
on the internet
they are kept
iCal squats while you're around no no no
they didn't follow me or anything we
were just a friend group all right
it is late but that's okay
um so I know what it's like to be an
extrovert but I became an introvert in
University
and after University it kind of just
stuck
uh and also if you know about my health
problems that is also another reason why
so being a streamer being being put into
uh
the light of public eye is very scary I
did not think that that is what it was I
thought that it was just plain I want to
stream for fun you know that's what I
thought it was gonna be
uh but then I started growing and I was
like this is actually genuinely fun and
I'm earning income so time to make it a
full-time job obviously it wasn't that
quick but
that was my thought process
oh Sarah
[Music]
I'm talking as fast as I can without
sounding too fast
yeah I um
the streaming content I already talked
about but it's just knowing that you're
putting yourself in the public eye be
aware that uh
things you say and do are going to be
very important and they are going to be
recorded in history people may clip you
people will screenshot you
and if you manage to Garner even more
attention than you currently have and
you grow and you grow and you grow like
I have
you gotta have to be more careful I feel
like that's the only way you gotta be
more careful
so yeah just
from my perspective I treat V2 being as
my career now I don't treat it as
flooding games anymore even though it is
fun and games I don't I sometimes don't
treat it that way because I don't want
to get canceled I am
like it is working hours for me
so yeah I know I'm having fun while I'm
working at the very least
but you have to keep in mind that I have
to stream
and I'm not on stream
I need a break too
a life balance very important
Indianapolis
exactly which is why you know doing the
stream today
was a big risk but I felt like there was
a lot of good things that could be said
my phone's very important
that's why I'm saying my daily schedule
you guys know it I I do have a life
outside stream do not worry I am living
my life did we get the less control you
have over the kind of people in your
audience which is why I'm very grateful
for my mods
mods if you need to sleep please go to
sleep do not worry about me chat's going
a little slower now I can handle it it's
okay
yeah I'm I'm glad I'm glad that uh the
way that I've been streaming nowadays
has been going very well my chat has
also been pretty decent uh not too many
bad things happening besides a couple
Bots I just feel bad that uh whoever's
modding the day that I stream
um and I stream for six hours I am so
sorry
like I will block anybody that needs
bonking it's okay
it's okay
I know today is a big big topic stream
but uh I think I please sleep if you
must okay okay
um I think
that is it
um I feel like some other things like
branding and you know
how you want to structure your content
and where to put your content
that is all very subjective opinion
so the only thing I can say about that
is stream where you're comfortable
create com create content that you're
happy with
don't let money stop you and try to do
everything that you can possibly do
yourself if you think that you can to
save yourself some money
because being a full-time streamer
you're not gonna get much money
okay
and you would know how much money you're
earn because I showed you my stats all
my analytics so yeah budget wisely
stream and spend your time wisely
this is why you mod your oh she's you
don't mind
yeah yeah I would never mud Kiara though
because I don't want to put that on her
and anyway when she when she's in chat
the the little Banner thing will pop up
which is nice so I'll notice her anyway
but okay I think that's it for all the
things I wanted to talk about
and if I missed anything it's probably
in the Q a so let's go through those
um
oh uh if you wanted to know more about
my streaming setup uh
brief thing about it is that
um
Mike is short mv7 plugged into a wave
XLR from Elgato
uh the game and stuff well that depends
on what you have but my mic is like
at one o'clock for gained
and I don't know what that is in numbers
unfortunately because I don't have my
wave link software up uh I have some
filters on through OBS and it goes in a
specific order
um it's gain which is at 12 DB
compressor is
ratio four to one thresholds negative 16
attack 10 milliseconds release 60
seconds output gain is zero limiter
all limiter is good negative 0.1
decibels releases 60 milliseconds I have
a plug-in for
um
uh Reverb stuff
that's like its own thing though
everyone has their own way of doing it
the Noise Gate I have is negative 41
DBS for a closed threshold open
threshold is negative 26 attack time 25
hold time 200 milliseconds release time
150 milliseconds I don't really know
what all this means but that's how I
have my mic set up so
whoever whoever asked me about my mic
set up and uh stuff like that well there
you go I gave you everything I could
possibly give you for it
okay okay and obviously because I have
link wavelength software that's how I
control my audio
uh I don't know how you would control
yours so I can't really tell you
I also have a stream deck it's the 15
button one so
uh let's go through the cube and hey I'm
gonna try Zoom through these because I
know there's a ton
there's a ton of questions
oh no oh no okay let me scroll
uh this one's really softwares that I
use to record and stream I record stuff
on my OBS as well but I do it in like a
different profile uh so it's vertical
that way it keeps all the uh pixels and
quality stuff PC specs already talked
about
uh
uh Holo live specifically gura but Kiara
made me stay and want to really become a
YouTuber
oh okay next one how different is it uh
to be a full-time statement and other
forms FaceCam in nocam I don't know what
it's like to be a face cam streamer so I
can't exactly say unfortunately but I
have a feeling you'd be more careful
about what you wear and
um your hand gestures because uh for me
I sit in really weird positions
sometimes like I cross my legs I put my
legs up on my table and yeah I think
that's one thing I also would put on
makeup every stream if I was if I were a
face cam streamer yeah do you like the
other so I like hearing it I can't do it
so every time someone asks me I will
always say no I cannot do it but I like
it
good night inspirational being on
Facebook and then a YouTuber yeah it's
in my opinion yes because you really
have to be careful about you know what
you're doing maybe even the clothes you
wear matters like what if it says
something that's offensive to somebody
very very scary
hello
[Music]
what is my backdrop what kind of
backdrop
it's just Oh you mean oh wait I'm dumb I
looked behind me I'm like what's my back
job
[Music]
it's a white wall
not even Kitty
I don't think I can do like a voice
acting type thing that's more of a
cerebrus's thing it's not my thing
okay uh
uh okay
so this one
I mean I hope you have a nice day I have
a question which part of become a
full-time interview YouTuber that you
think is the best thank you oh uh my
favorite part of being an indie YouTuber
is that I have complete control over
what it is I want to stream so if I want
to do games I'm allowed to do games
whatever time I want to stream I'm
allowed to stream it no one tells me I
stream too often or too little and I get
to play whatever game I want without
having to worry about copyright to a
certain extent that Persona 5 was a bit
like do I have to worry about it just in
case you know but yeah
uh that's my favorite part
I mean obviously that's only in terms of
like my full-time stuff like I actually
get to control every single second I
stream and every single thing I say and
every single stream I get to choose what
I do some carpools don't get that choice
some people get totally strain too often
are too little so yeah
uh
uh uh
let me see
[Music]
thingy
uh
uh okay I talked about
you asked me about networking stuff I
think I answered that one package
question I answered
uh this one did you ever find it hard to
find people to collab with or make
friends with other YouTubers I feel like
if I leave you to I'd be scared oh I
didn't think it was hard per se
to find people like the word is fine
here which is why I clicked on it I
never talked about finding people it
wasn't hard because of Twitter
some people would notice me they would
slide into my DMs and with Discord
servers I did join a community of
YouTubers so it wasn't too difficult to
find some people to talk to but this
moment that I found out like I found
myself as a YouTuber in my place as a
YouTuber I ended up
not collabing as much
and I focused a lot on making my content
very solidified and making sure that
whoever came into my channel knew what I
streamed and what my content was about
so I guess yeah I would be scared and
nervous too
it's just you have to put yourself out
there if you're gonna meet anybody it's
it's you can't expect someone to make
the first move all the time I learned
the hard way
uh find yourself neglecting exercise
because of being a YouTuber no no
I do not because I work out every day
almost every day
uh at what point did you feel you could
do this as a full-time job and what
advice would you give to others wanting
to make it full time so I think I gave
plenty of advice at this point where
make sure you have the right budget and
I know everyone has a different
background so if you're not in a
position to be able to do it full-time
do not do not take that risk and
um I thought that it was okay to go full
time for me because I
I have my family supporting me and they
were okay with me doing it
um the other stuff would be
the income was more than what I was
expecting
so if you think the income you're
getting is also enough to sustain you
then I think that's okay again don't
expect to be doing this for until you're
like 70. but
you know just keep it in mind keep it in
mind
uh let's see I already said that oh this
one
what software do you use to edit videos
by the way nice to meet you nice to meet
you too Unicode you're probably asleep
by now but that's okay
um
I use OBS to record stuff and then
DaVinci to edit yes I've got the entire
blade flight transport back to the fire
getting ready for Avengers list oh hi
cozy
[Laughter]
I I know I'm about to hit the six hour
mark I'm trying really hard to get
through the questions really fast I get
some good rest cozy plane flights are
tiring
uh where was I
uh
okay this one I'm sure you get this
question a lot but how does it feel to
be a YouTuber it feels fun
it is very fun it can be quite stressful
if uh because
streaming in general is a very social
job you kind of have to talk to chat and
networking with other people is
inevitable it's kind of something you
really need to do otherwise you won't
have other people to collab with and
that's also very common space among
YouTubers and streamers
exactly it's too new you'll never know
it's very up and coming especially with
like 3D tracking getting bigger who
knows
guys I'm always around I'm becoming free
Okay
um
rayless asked this oh what made you
decide to focus on streaming instead of
videos well I was never much of a video
editor uh I never grew up around media I
only grew up around watching episodes on
Disney Channel and Nickelodeon and
Cartoon Network so
um
I was always more into long-term long
form content and editing was just never
on my radar uh even nowadays when I
stream and stuff I rarely edit Clips or
make shorts because I'm very slow
I'm still learning how to do it it's
very new to me still but I'm waiting I'm
trying uh it's just that because I never
had a background in editing and I had to
learn everything from scratch that
uh I became more into streaming and was
like I would I also like the live
interaction more
that's like you know personal preference
though
me as a turtle I'm always a thing I'll
be forever and ever and ever
uh but yeah thank you for asking
railways
uh okay
this question where did you look for bgm
there's this uh site it's a Japanese
site I feel like what's it called
I forgot what it's called was it Dover
syndrome
it's somewhere in my credits if you
scroll down to my credit section you'll
probably find it
uh all right this question hi Mia what
are you feeling about being a full-time
Indie YouTuber as opposed to being part
of an organization well being in an
organization of any sort means that I
have to put the company name or
something in my name
uh sounds very official which I think is
really cool uh but then I don't have the
I don't have the Indie V2 brush stat
anymore I'm no longer an ndv super
otherwise and sometimes I feel like
being in Indie
um
you people will definitely just be like
you grew on your own you got to where
you are on your own no one helped you
get there it's all your hard work and
that's what I love hearing I love
hearing that I was able to accomplish
something based on my own merits
and I think that's just me being Asian
as me being Asian I don't like getting
help
I get told I have a problem I'll fix it
on my own don't you dare touch me I will
do it myself
that's just that's just Asian in me how
I how I grew up being independent and
all that but no okay that's just a joke
please don't take it seriously I'll ask
for help if I need it I promise
but um no I just feel prideful it makes
me feel happy to see the hard work come
to fruitin you know
so if I was in an organization I don't
like I said I don't think I would feel
as uh accomplished like I'm grateful for
it and all like but I don't think I
would feel that
I wouldn't feel as accomplished
mindset of not
want to bother us yeah Asians
I'm still Asian though okay
um
okay we talked about ad Revenue already
so I won't do that
uh this one this being a YouTuber make
doing your taxes a complicated affair
so I'm on YouTube right so I I'm not in
the US there are some things that are
different from us and Canadians so uh it
was a bit of a different process the tax
forms are different and so whenever
people talk about taxes on Twitter I'm
like it's not my time yet though
and the
I guess
I haven't had to do anything regarding
taxes just yet because when I got
monetized it was just past everything to
do with Texas so I'm gonna find out next
year when tax time comes and I'm not
ready for it but now that my parents
know that I'm a v tuber
they can help me out
okay uh let me think
so here we go do you think you would
ever have any small initial sides of
income whether like self-employed
related or not so I'm currently
self-employed being a full-time streamer
is self-employment especially as an
indie you're not employed by anybody you
are your own bus you control everything
but um for side income I'm not gonna lie
if I went back into the healthcare field
as of right now and I you know managed
to find job
then
um it would make my v-tubing life a lot
easier because I could pay for stuff
like full body tracking getting a 3D
model
and all of that merch as a side Hustle
I don't have the resources to do that
which is the benefits of joining a
company like Kawa because they help you
do that nudge nudge please if you're a
YouTuber
go audition for color
uh but yeah I um
don't have the ability to do it by
myself I know some YouTubers who are a
bit bigger than me or even sometimes
smaller than me they find ways to get
merch by partnering up with certain
people and companies and all that but
I'm also not in the US which makes it
twice as hard
we don't if I was in the US and I'd be
able to ship stuff out so easily because
most of my audience 41 of you are in the
US
but no I am
I am in Canada which is why when people
ask for me for Merch I don't really know
what to do
I've wanted merch for a long time
but I've never been able to make a
connection to make merch especially
because I'm Canadian and shipping
what the heck am I gonna do about
shipping
yeah okay so the answer to that question
is yes
okay
uh
um
oh I answered the breaking question
uh V tuber income versus past jobs
income which higher well I used to be
earning 22 to 24 dollars per hour
now
every hour I stream I earn sometimes
zero
sometimes I earn five sometimes I earn
10 and on random weird ass occasions I
will earn a hundred so really I cannot
count my income by the hour as a
YouTuber so the comparison is really
difficult
are you even making minimum wage on
average no
think about it how long have I been
streaming now six hours six hours
I've earned 83.42 in Super Chat Revenue
I haven't counted the stream elements
stuff I mean servers obviously
gave me a hundred for the don't know but
like again rare random occasion that
this happens okay and the membership
stuff very random occasion that someone
would do that for me
typically on average I earn like 10 to
20 dollars per stream
but then again please think about how
often I stream
if you don't stream as often as either
you wouldn't get the amount of money
that I'm earning
when you're an hourly wage exactly it's
two variables so
hard to say hard to say
like
I mean last year
yeah I had a I had a higher I was
earning way more money
I said that when I was a research
assistant I was earning way more money
than I was a YouTuber but I am like five
to ten times as happy
as a YouTuber so
like what's the trade off there
you get 10 to 20. sometimes sometimes
it's five
sometimes it's just one from the P
supers thank you bee supers you make you
give me five bucks you give me five
bucks for stream every time I pee thank
you
because before I used to be it used to
be two super chats for the pay to pee
because I always forget to drink water
and pee
on streams particularly so but then you
also have to remember I get 70 of that
so
it's not the whole two dollars but now
at least five people will send me uh
will send me blue super chats so I get I
get like five bucks every time I pee
which is weird because that means you're
paying me to not be on stream even
though it should be the opposite
bless you super snow I've never gotten
any of those I don't think my sneezes
are that cute
cozy you should pay the P2 you should do
pay to pee it'll earn you a little bit
of money we're talking about income like
genuinely pay to P is the way just
drinking [\h__\h] to the water let's change
obviously it's not gonna earn you a lot
but it's gonna earn you something
I guess it's time to start yeah it's
time to start I barely pee on street two
I I didn't pee for the first five hours
of stream okay I tried really hard to
hold it in but then Chad told me not to
hold it in so yeah
things I appreciate anything about how
much you'll make
it
it's a very consistent way to earn like
a dollar you could just pee
but okay okay
where was I
okay can you sort of go into how your
model commission and everything okay so
I researched a bunch of people
Japanese artists in particular because I
like Japanese art styles and I found
tinted in mama
I had to email so I went on to her
website I put in a request in English
and Japanese so I put Japanese at the
top and then had a little section where
I had a translated version of what I
said in English that way afterwards I
could just you know I could look at it
and not have to read the Japanese
because my Japanese isn't that good yet
I'm good enough to make sure I can
notice grammar mistakes and so that my
point gets across that's about it oh I
also know the difference between Kegel
and you know like basically um
uh casual speech and formal speech
so that's how it started mama got back
to me within a day or two very quick and
we hashed out the details uh it was very
organized way very professional way of
doing things like uh she gave me a list
of questions like four questions to
answer some of it would be like I've
never gotten a commission from someone
in a foreign country before like how
would paying work like is it PayPal or
something and I was like yeah PayPal is
typically the way to go uh she asked me
about the amount of Expressions I wanted
and
um the general pricing if this was okay
things like that very
structured stuff that professional
artists would need to ask like give me
any references you have color palettes
all of that stuff
um she gave me updates every month or so
about the progress and there I gave her
a lot of creative freedom I'd be like
you can design this outfit make any
changes you like
um and
during the sketching phase I was just
like oh damn this is cute and then uh
during the base coloring stuff
uh
uh she gave me even more options which I
had to choose from and it would always
be like a b c d e or like one a one b
and then two a two B that kind of thing
um by the end of it she's just like
here's the final thing if you have any
questions just let me know and you can
send this to the rigor I actually had to
ask tender de mama who she recommended
for a rigor because I didn't know any
and it was very hard to find one that I
genuinely liked so she introduced me to
no no
also very professional Arigato I didn't
do any of that English translation
though I don't know why maybe because
when I emailed Papa I didn't actually
do that myself which is kind of dumb but
I should have uh like also really fast
got a lot of updates and when I received
the model
uh I thought the leg movement was kind
of strange so I asked Nana Papa to fix
it because it looked like my leg was
getting
snapped into like my knee joint was not
moving right and I asked some friends
how it looked and they're like okay it's
weird
uh I also had to ask an update for the
rigging after debut because these shorts
um I could see the back of my thigh
peeking through like the shorts
and it was not in the right spot
so um that had to be updated but was
very very generous he's like I had to
make so many adjustments for you you
were also really kind about my time and
how like I have
stuff personal stuff going on so I'm
giving you a discount and I was very
thankful for it Nana Papa also gave me
so many Expressions I did not ask for
the Yahoo face it was given to me and I
decided to take advantage of it okay
all right so that is that
um
there you go do you ever feel lonely
since you aren't working in an
environment around people I know you
have online friends but I mean like
physically around people going to a job
Etc so yes sometimes I do feel lonely
because I have a lot of online people
friends and you have you guys in chat
which is amazing but yeah I do I do get
lonely sometimes sometimes and it's not
because I don't think it's because
um
I have a remote job
but it's because
I like being lonely
and when I put it out loud like that
I genuinely like being by myself I love
spending time by myself it's it's one of
the things I love okay
so
um
honestly When My Friends Ask me to go
out I say no
I'm like sorry I'm busy actually I'm not
I'm just playing with my dogs at home uh
some friends will be like let's go out
drinking this weekend then I'm like
sorry I have a stream planned when
really I don't so
um I just like being alone
[Music]
but I get it thank you for understanding
me thank you also I just fixed my
glasses and my tracking is weird oh good
thank you thank you for coming I'm glad
you enjoyed the stream come back yeah
everyone feels in Animal Crossing
[Music]
come on
there you go
[Music]
I hope you're doing nothing I planned
today is that's me that's me that's me
that's me that's me I plan to do nothing
to me
okay okay
um so yes I feel lonely but okay I do
have IRL friends I do go out I will have
I will I will see other people
I have IRL friends okay
you know how to speak Splatoon no I do
not I did not know how to speak speak
Splatoon unfortunately
but uh yeah I do have IRL friends that I
hang out with so
uh not often I see them like once every
two months question mark
I only have like two friends that live
around me and we met in Middle School
one of them I met in middle school she
actually came onto my stream once by
accident uh and then I have a second
friend who I met in high school and she
lives about 10 to 15 minute drive away
from me which is very close and we both
drive so that's another bonus so um I
see her fairly often like once or twice
um every two months like once per month
baby yeah she sometimes just comes over
randomly be like hey you want to chill
but yeah uh once it gets to winter time
it's even less so
not that live near me I cry cozy if you
ever want to come to Canada
uh let's see next question
[Music]
I know you're a variety sure but what do
you do when you get addicted to a
particular game I stream it
instrument
do you guys not realize this by now
whenever a new game comes out and I get
a dick that I stream it like heck
because it's probably one of those games
that like you know will get me some
Cloud subtraction let's go expose me on
YouTube algorithm yes push me push me
that's what it does
hi Dolly hello make sense in a minute
you want to go to Canada someday come
come to Toronto there's stuff
here
oh I sound so convincing right now
okay uh let's see
oh this one's a good one have you had
anyone recognize it in public IRL easy
from your voice Easy by your friends or
so
there's still here
okay oh this is actually kind of funny
um
I was going through the uh wait you know
how earlier we were going through the
geography cities and stuff I recognized
some cities on the top of the list which
is kind of concerning but uh hopefully I
don't know anyway
um
foreign
yes and no so someone in my chat a long
time ago they were we were talking about
like places in Canada
they happened to say
uh one of the places that I go to
frequently
and I was just like oh [\h__\h]
I know where that is
and um one of my friends Amai who I feel
so bad for not being able to talk to
more often uh
he lives within my vicinity and I found
out on stream and we talked to DMS and I
ended up meeting him IRL we played
basketball together of all things
and uh so I actually have met someone
because they've come to my stream and
he's also another content creator he
does a lot of ASMR stuff
so um that was kind of cool but I've had
I haven't had anybody recognize me in
public which is a good thing I also okay
when I'm in public I try to lower my
voice a bit so I don't sound like a kid
uh my height is that of a child I'm 148
centimeters Okay so
I try and lower my voice when I'm in
public so I yeah I I try to be like hi
my name is Mia nice to meet you
foreign
[Music]
next one
are you scared about collab with new
people I'm an anxious person in general
and I feel like it's hard to collab with
new people yes the way to curb the
anxiety is to talk to them in voice call
off stream first and then you call up
with them on stream
good rule of thumb talk to people off
stream first before you decide to call
that but then that way you know you can
actually hold a conversation
did you lose the game of basketball no I
actually won I shot more Hoops than than
um I did
hey
what skills do you need to be a YouTuber
many many many but uh key ones is
talking ability
uh technical difficulty problem solving
skills and networking marketing slash
social media
those are the top things I I would say
uh
uh okay
I'm gonna guess this question means how
did you come about with uh creating the
name or for channel for vtubing uh I
looked up the meaning of the name
Miracle which meant a beautiful blessed
child
and uh it was
something that I would hope that I am
and lucky I think it also met me
yeah yeah pretty it is like me yeah yeah
pretty blessed child
and uh last name was just very random I
don't really remember where it came from
uh and then with the Rebrand into Mino
Michael uh
there was really no reason besides I
didn't want to change my name too much
and that uh Mino kind of sounds like a
pun with
you know me Echo
[Music]
which is that was really cute
uh next one
uh
[Music]
nope okay answered that one
um
oh gosh oh gosh wait I lost it here we
go it's that's cozy it's a butt
did you not know it was a pun I'm so
sorry did I just break your brain no you
don't hate
we did play Splatoon for two and a half
hours
that was really fun I loved it
this is so much better than we thank you
mompaca you understand me educate your
check
on how wonderful it is to have a pun in
your name
and I think of a small fan why what okay
fine I'm not a fish
is there some mobile app that can do
rigging from just PNG no you have to get
the PNG cut and rigged unfortunately
which means you still have to uh go
through live 2D and then get YouTube
Studio
let me try to teach you the joy of the
punch for you're still filling out that
lesson oh man
no worries cozy you learn you learn one
day the joys
okay uh
she
um
oh this one's different
I'm so sorry if I missed you discussing
this I'll go back and look if you did
how did you go about actualizing your
aesthetic design those things so
um in the beginning I stuck with very
ojosama type things and purple is a very
Royal Color Purple in fact is not my
favorite color I like blue
specifically teal
but um I just thought that it fit the
aesthetic and it was a very cute thing I
also love contrasting colors so purple
and yellow were the ones I went with in
the beginning
slowly when I became more into like I
want to use my favorite color I also
dyed my hair exactly these three colors
so
um
when I debuted uh with this model I was
like I need I need an aesthetic that is
very me
and I also had to think about what what
kind of appearance I have that would fit
my voice
so um
yeah that's that's how I came about it
and uh
I have a very specific aesthetic when it
comes to the overlays too thanks to
hifuni it's kind of rounded and
simplistic which I love I've been
meaning to get like a background room
thing but when he's I just I just
potentially lost three thousand dollars
so I'm not gonna spend money on anything
for a very long time
but yeah uh I just chose my favorite
colors and I thought about my
personality
how it was kind of cute and my voice is
also kind of cute and the type of
content I like is going to be the type
of content I want to create is also very
cute so I went with cute stuff cute
rounded stuff
I gave hifuni complete control over the
logo I had no say in it besides asking
him to add the hammer in it everything
else was I didn't design any of that
Barney you want me to be Barney
okay
uh here we go this is a weird question
I've never seen someone ask me this are
there any adjacent Industries you're
interested in that your V2 base skill
set easily translates to
um
can you guys think of any
uh I feel like
maybe art stuff I'd like to teach more
art skills for for beginners especially
because that memory to me is still
really fresh like making pngs layers
just how layers work because some people
get confused like very basic things like
clipping and Alpha locking and um
very basics of choosing brushes and
smudging stuff or
the different layer types like the
multiply layer and the add layer are
some of my
the blushing layers I call them they're
like the best layers to use
excavated type jobs
I mean yeah I guess I just don't know
where
I'm not very good at talking to people
IRL versus on stream
even in collabs I get to hear people
through my ears I don't have to see
their facial expressions
okay so I guess there are some like
media things I feel like if I could get
into the media industry that'd be nice
um other than that
yeah podcasting I think that'd be cool
interviews and stuff
I'd like I'd like
to to host interviews one day but
I don't know if I'm
I'm in the position to be doing that
which is why I have the podcast it's
great because Frey is very extroverted
and I do not have to worry about
reaching out but I'd like to do
interviews I'd love to be I'd love to be
interviewed or be an interviewer I think
that would be great I think I could be
good at both
yeah like hosting stuff I just want to
be able to host stuff I don't know if my
PC can handle it but I'd like to be able
to one day he knows
okay let's see
so are you staying as an indie for now
yes yes
how does one gain the ability to talk
for five plus hours straight without
taking a break and without running out
of things to talk about
you got to be a small streamer to know
the struggle
when you have oh gosh when you have an
empty chat and you're talking to it for
hours and hours you're basically talking
to thin air and it feels like you're
talking to thin air even though there's
people licking you have to appreciate
the lurkers that will be there even
during the tiniest times of your life
when I was when I was very very small
at five viewers Max
I would keep talking no matter what I
learned that by
just pulling things out of my ass bruh
what you gotta do
no I wasn't an extrovert no
I just rant about things that I was
angry about or that I was happy about
like you guys like eating pineapple on
pizza
and um give yourself things to talk
about it's
you need life experiences I sometimes
would talk about my childhood
I talked about when I was baby
uh and I went to kindergarten
I uh during Chinese class
I would take my school bag put it on the
floor grab my cardigan from inside the
bag and take a nap at the back of the
class and then my mom had to get called
to the school and be like why am I
getting called in the principal would
get angry at me and tell my mom that I
was taking naps in class
or um how during my first to Canada as a
baby I ended up pooping so much in a
waiter's hand because they wanted to
carry me but I was like having a
stomachache problem I I pooped so much
in their hand that I went through the
diaper and my grandma didn't know what
to do because they ran out of diapers
and my mom wasn't there so they uh put
me in this plastic bag as a makeshift
diaper yeah
just come up with the weirdest [\h__\h] to
talk about your experiences in life
might seem really ordinary to you but
they could be incredibly interesting for
someone else
that is the way and also you have to
keep doing it train your vocal cords
train it
I remember when I started streaming I
tried to lower my voice so I sounded
younger but um
I learned the hard way that it's not me
yes very shitty XP
do you like very effective emergency
diaper exactly
I mean as long as you don't get a rash
from it because it's not really
breathable
but yes in a plastic bag do you ever
feel like a plastic bag
I know what it's like to be in one
deeper to sound younger no deeper to
sound less like a kid
but yeah I trained myself to talk a lot
and um to talk about any life
experiences that I had and with my
upbringing kind of ojosama type
upbringing
uh there were a lot of things that not
many people
experience like I traveled the world
when I was a baby I went to Malaysia
Singapore I couldn't stay there very
long though uh Japan Korea China
and everywhere in Asia so yeah
three years old good night
back oh my God if it's midnight for you
and you need to sleep please go to sleep
oh I need that okay
so yeah I don't run out of things to
talk about because
I always talk about the past and there's
a lot to talk about in the past it might
not seem interesting to people but I
mean it might not seem interesting to
you like I said but it may be
interesting for somebody else
that's that's where you get the stuff to
talk about
um
oh we're finally at the end
would you recommend starting as a PNG
tuber yes because then you get to know
if you actually like doing it and you
get to learn
in real time how to deal with OBS being
shitty or if you have any technical
difficulties or how you want to organize
yourself
for me I have one monitor so it took a
really long time for me to learn how to
you know organize things but yeah I do
recommend it and it helps you save the
money because if you end up not liking
it then you didn't waste your money
yeah
okay uh
uh what a number two baby is poop no no
why no
does wearing glasses impact your eye
tracking in any capacity well I've been
wearing glasses the entire time
I have not stopped wearing my glasses I
also wear blue light glasses which might
make it even harder for it to track if
anything
but no I think it's pretty decent
um
yeah
the left right down up
I think it's decent
I also have an iPhone it's better than
webcam tracking
Rose Colored Glasses no
as long as you don't have a ring light
or something that makes your glasses
you're effective it should be okay yeah
I don't have that I do blink no the
thing is I blink a ton I do blink a ton
I have really dry eyes Okay so yeah it's
it's not it's not the tracking being bad
it's just me blinking it done I do blink
a ton
and please remember I've been staring at
a monitor for six hours my eyes are
tired even with blue light glasses
located I fatigue I blink and I also
meant squinting it's 3am I'm getting
tired
uh but I'm almost at the end I want to
get through these
oh wait I think
Disney that is the end oh that was the
last question I was willing to answer
cool
alrighty alrighty we're done the Q a oh
we're done the Q a oh we made it to the
end guys
holy okay okay we're done I'm closing
that speak now or forever behold your
peace if anything you can ask them in
the chat I'll read those
oh my God
there's gonna be so much to timestamp
I'm gonna make them really generic
Chapters at first so I get the big
things in and then maybe I'll re-watch
this stream if you guys watch the stream
and you have any time stamps you want to
give me to put in the the chapters let
me know either in Discord or at the
comment section
uh like say say you find a part
and you want someone to be able to hear
it like say I talked about a specific
thing maybe the cloud stuff or
um all the
all the uh the beginning stuff like my
history how I became a YouTuber in the
first place and maybe the analytics
specific parts of the analytics like
like Muni when he's a big one like if
you end up finding that particular time
stamp let me know in the comments I'll
add that into the chapter so it's easy
for people to find uh I want I know this
shame is really long and thank you guys
for sticking throughout almost all of it
uh
I just hope that this dream helped
somebody somewhere
because I know it's a lot it was a lot
of information to take in it got
emotional for me okay uh especially the
whole parent thing so
um I just hope I just hope that it was
it was useful to somebody
[Music]
yeah that's all I wanted
it was a pleasure too as a pleasure
oh thank you Mom Becca
someone wait uh
the thing is I don't like Sonic very
much so either way no matter who it was
I would say no
you stick to the end outside I see that
what's up but it was entertaining
everyone nonetheless you're welcome
you're welcome
getting free thank you you're welcome
the thing is like even if you're a
viewer you might not know all the
details about what goes into V tubing
and I I did go quite deep into it today
but there are things that I left out
there's still things I left out
so yeah
uh
those are more that those are things for
me to keep to my shelf note
thank you
[Music]
I know
it's a lot I'm sorry it took me so long
to get through everything I tried I
tried really hard to get it all with all
the things that I plan to talk about I
tried to structure it as well as I could
there's no need of everything in my soup
I'm not available yeah there's way too
much to get through
way way way way way way
too much to get to
so unfortunately I can only talk about
so much
available you're welcome you're welcome
I hope that it was helpful to viewers as
much as it was to other YouTubers
because
like
other YouTubers would know it's not easy
and it takes a big
big
risk
to do it full time
especially when you only earn so much
um
and not everyone has the same support
that I do not everyone lives as well as
I do I know I have a very privileged
life
again I know not every YouTuber will
have that not every streamer will have
that
but um I just hope I hope I gave some
insight into what I have done it's just
my experience everyone will have
different experiences
enough for me as a fever I'm glad with
another shoe like this again I mean it
might be more centered on a specific
topic just so that we can have a more
like
dense not dense like deeper discussion
about a certain topic
but yeah I might maybe not in a while
though because
this one took a lot out of me guys
so much out of here I've been talking
really quietly because my voice is
getting shut
it's just dying on the inside I've had a
sore throat for a long time
um
it's been getting better but I think
today it might have uh
aggravated it again
that offers a perspective yeah yeah
definitely does
he has awesome Chinese shoes I'm glad
I'm glad you like it oh okay
I'm running out of water this whole
entire six hours I've only had one cup
of water because I didn't bring more
water I didn't know how long the stream
was gonna last
oh
I'm gonna have another throat candy
I need it I need the throw candy
oh no I opened the wrong end
no I hate when I do that oh my
perfectionist tendency
to this side
can you can you tell me like yeah what
tea it is can you send that to me
somehow
I will
um you you can you can DM me mom back I
give you the purse
uh like a link or a recipe or something
that'd be nice
it doesn't matter to me up to you Mom
Becca it is up to you I do not mind
my mom doesn't even have Discord
it doesn't have Twitter either I just
realized that my mom's not into social
medias I can't blame her you're a cool
mom
ah yeah I just I hope
that the stream was good for you guys
and it would help me out a lot if you
could time stamp some things please uh
at least a little stuff the big things I
can probably spend tomorrow doing but uh
for now like just a little stuff you
guys can just drop me some random funny
parts of anything
enjoy it thank you I'm glad you liked it
well thank you thank you
um
anything really
anything that you want to clip clip it I
okay when I stream I don't so so many
people say this for twitch streamers uh
always have a segment of a stream you
are willing to turn into a a short or a
highlight but for me I just stream
because I never turned those things into
short form content on YouTube
twitch streamers do that so that they
have a YouTube channel but I already
have one it's my mainstreaming platform
so I never had to do that and never had
to worry about that
you did
I didn't see that okay cool thank you
Mom Becca I will check I will check my
DMs after the stream I know I have like
how many okay let me check
kind of 20 plus
freaking notifications on Twitter that
is more than I've seen I usually am
really good at checking notifications
because I hate seeing the Little Numbers
I'll check after the dream I will I'll
definitely check out the stream oh God
um but thank you guys for coming today
do we have time to raid somebody it's
3am in the morning is anybody streaming
you know what if I rate someone now
I'm not going to be able to stay up so
let's just not rate anyone today I'm so
tired
I spent all day planning the stream I
think it's time to just we're calling it
we're calling it you guys have also been
here for like six hours so you know
we're calling it a night
oh God thank you for the No-No thank you
thank you
didn't expect that it's free streaming
all right he's doing his
Donut oh God you know I'll just I'll
read them tomorrow I can't I'm so tired
my throat needs a break
it is in pain
I'm streaming tomorrow anyway
if you guys want to wish him good luck
with his donut please go ahead and do it
support him I I cannot do that right now
I am
tired I'm so tired I gotta I need to I
want to go to bed
that's all the mods who were up until
this time thank you but please also go
to bed go rest on the guys with us
I know I also spoke a lot of English
today because I didn't really know how
to explain stuff in other in other
languages
um but I hope that's okay
I'll definitely keep eating these
typical candy thingies oh
good actually thank you for the Super
Bowl did you change experience
entertaining also you guys once again on
4K all right guys thank you again for 4K
I honestly did not expect to get to 4K
today that was
I almost I think I gained 100
subscribers today again
and it's only the 2nd of December
and
I'm so shocked
it hasn't said in yet you know it'll set
in tomorrow maybe who knows who knows
okay let me just get out of this thing
we'll have regular bgm
as I end the stream
um
I don't think you know what the next
time I do this stream if you guys really
want
if you guys really want me to do this
stream
tell me in my marshmallows
I think there's a link to that
somewhere but tell me in the
marshmallows if you really really want
me to I will check them or you know just
tell me a Discord if you'd like
or if I do it if I make a poll on
Twitter like do you want one next month
then
I'll make sure I do something for next
month you know just let me know I'll
plan something if you want
takes so much energy to do these kinds
of streams I rarely stream for more than
three or four hours so okay
um I do have a stream tomorrow scheduled
it'll probably be shorter than
this one because I have all my throat
hopefully I get to set up I want to set
up my second monitor tomorrow if my
cable comes in time and my mount comes
in time but
oh I have a morning stream
[Laughter]
okay well then I'll see you guys at 10
o'clock in the morning tomorrow
I was dreaming five and a half hours
okay okay good night guys
I streaming five and a half hours [\h__\h]
okay
guys
okay so what maybe cancel it no I'm not
gonna cancel the stream I I I I set
myself a goal I'm Gonna Keep to it
foreign
I'll push it to 11 A.M
you guys are watching out for me all
right fine today was a really good
stream though so I'll push it too I'll
push it to uh 11AM
oh I am so sorry for that oh gosh
okay
I have two streams tomorrow Pokemon
Violet and persona 5.
I'll see you then I'm gonna take a nap
tomorrow afternoon holy [\h__\h]
good night good night everyone
uh let me make sure the ending screen is
set
I just I don't know if I did that
uh
uh no it wasn't set oopsies okay well
then I am gonna go now
uh I
I am
hope you guys again enjoyed the Stream
it did take a very long time to plan it
to even do it
so um
I hope you have a good time
you had a good time that you'll help me
time stamp the video the VOD because it
was six hours and 23 minutes
a lot of information
and it would help
a lot of other new viewers finding me
and a lot of other YouTubers watching
the VOD so
please please help me timestamp it I'm
asking I'm begging thank you
um but yeah I'm gonna go thank you again
for coming I appreciate all of you and I
hope you learned something yeah okay
good night good night good night thank
you thanks oh wait wrong buttons
[Music]
um I'll leave it to you I'll do the big
work myself though
see you tomorrow or in six hours bye
bye bye Mommy and Daddy
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign