[Music]
do
is it working is the stream back okay
my tablet is working with it
[Music]
how we good youtube
stinky
hello
[Music]
and wealthy today hello
i don't know i felt i felt like going
for a while fiona today
hope that's okay for you we i mean
i don't use it that often so
no daddy
and we'll play garlic no gotta take
phone
today for the first time
yay i've seen other
members in her life japan play it
and it looks so much fun uh
i want to try it with you guys
um it won't be a super long stream maybe
one to two hours
and so let's have some fun together
the uh the thing is
um part so everyone can watch the stream
but participation
is for members only sorry we'll test it
out like this
see if everyone's nice shut up java
update
i don't want to update my java i don't
wanna
yeah so i will like i will copy
the link and then post it into the
members uh
community board so keep it open and
refresh refresh refresh refresh
keep in mind that my stream has a few
seconds lag so
yeah okay and i think we'll start with i
don't know nine players
and we'll just do normal now but i wanna
try out some other stuff to like
um i want to know what this is
i really like the drawings like the
clock gets knocked off
yeah i don't know maybe we'll we can
find something
else what is secret all the actions are
mystery drawings and sentences are
getting
hidden during the game yeah we should
try out some other modes too but i want
to try the normal one first of all
yeah okay so
uh i guess let's start wait the link
copied uh let's try this out please
um be nice be cool
if if if
anything inappropriate or
[Music]
bad happens then i will end the session
immediately and open up a new one and
we'll act as if nothing happened
okay we'll act as if nothing
happened and we'll just move on which
this is unfortunate for everyone who
made it into the session
but yeah it is what it is so good luck
to everyone
trying to enter mangan
i posted it let's see how fast they are
oh one that was fast man
oh oh oh oh
yeah well i can't squirrel
there we go oh
hello welcome some of these names seem
familiar so i think
i think we could i think we have
probably hopefully
a good
i mean generally the game has no sound
besides right now the entering thing i
think
but one second uh
how do we do this turn off
this and then you shoot yourself okay
generally i think it has no sound i
can't see the link
i posted in the members only they found
it so
what do you mean it should be in members
members uh a member's only post wait
wait that's so weird i it only has like
seven
thumbs up did it did the post
wait i think it might have gotten shadow
banned but how did they find it then
interesting yeah because i only posted
the link maybe it's got shadow band
that's why it also took so long for some
people to come in i'll try to
ah in the memphis is there a chat what
was that poop sound oh someone left
someone left someone can try to
there we go welcome it's in the
membership tab not the
okay there you go for the next round you
guys can check check in the membership
tab
apparently there's a difference there
membership tab and community tab
i didn't know that that there is a
difference
for me both shows up in the community
tab all right
let's play this game
[Music]
still don't see it they show up in
community
i don't know i still think it might have
been shadow band or something so next
time i post a link i'll just add some
text to it or so
i think okay let's go hey i'm nervous
write a sentence okay um
oh everyone who's what i was
participating maybe don't listen to the
stream now
okay uh another
yay i think that's a good prompt i
wonder what you guys come up with
you don't have to come up with like a
uh it doesn't have to be a like a piano
related prompt
but maybe whole live related prompts
would be fun
doesn't also doesn't have to be dead
either though
eh why you guys why is everything so
yummy
why why are you guys saying your bed
what's your buy about it
going going to the beach is that the
prompt
okay okay
uh so how does this work is the first
time i do this
is does it make it smaller or what is
that
yeah okay
let's draw while fiona
my my pen is kind of
slow it has some some some stabilization
going on or something weird
but then they think it's kiana well it's
okay i guess they can
they can change it into kiana going to
the beach
how much time do i have ah still enough
time okay
okay so i'm going to the beach
maybe with like a bag and ah maybe with
a bikini oh yeah
that probably makes it uh
somewhat obvious
[Music]
beach blue are you blue blue blue color
blue color
[Music]
okay but i'm already at the beach here
oh well
and then some sand color
how does how does my bikini look like
let's give it some color
how about green green is a little bit
underappreciated
[Laughter]
that's dirt no that's sand and
some orange we're running out of time
but i think
i think this is pretty uh good i think
it's obvious
i am at the beach close enough
okay okay okay okay uh
wait wait it already rained but i still
have time
i'm done
at the beach
how clear can i possibly make it oh what
the [\h__\h] is that
and was that an onion an onion
being held by a hand
someone strangling an onion is it
someone's
[Music]
triangled onion
i don't know that's what it looks like
to me
eh that doesn't look like a croissant
at all okay okay okay i'm done with that
yeah i'm answering a banana phone easy
should be should be manageable
i just do love piano the whole time
what's a banana from literally just a
banana right
yeah eat your eat your bananas get
vitamins
everyone should have chosen a better a
bigger
one but what is a banana phone
it's just a banana right
[Music]
but it doesn't look like me yet we're
just gonna make the hair orange i guess
and then it looks like me
i mean that's probably going to be
obvious anyway that everyone makes
prompts about takanawa
half the time is up
okay okay okay does it look like a
banana
i think think about the shape and the
color of it makes it pretty obvious but
let's add some some
detail like that
[Music]
and
okay okay looking good time almost up
eh okay okay i'm i'm ready
uh i think i'm yeah
i'm ready i'm ready you know zombie
telling me taking my stuff
okay okay
detail okay beautiful add rings
ah uh uh
is that is that is that what you mean
isn't that literally supposed to be
me hatching eggs
i mean i'm obviously i'm i'm a human
okay
i mean partially human like i look like
a human i don't look like this but i get
what you're trying to do
eh that looks like the same idea is is
that a friend eh
but i look happy if that's a frying pan
why am i happy
am i not in the front or is it
i don't
[Laughter]
oh
frog suit
is there oh there is a filling too
[\h__\h]
close no close it here close it close it
and then fill it
and then uh
no i don't want to turn into a cheeto
okay okay
okay okay okay cute and frog quack quack
quack quack quack
quack quack gotta love it gotta love the
m frog meme right
legendary the first the first center one
that
made every other m2 video possible
does that i think that's that i think
that's all you need
i think this explains it
very well
yeah let me make you
let me give you some frog noises
it's me i am i am your frog friend
please please feed me what do frogs eat
flies now maybe it's a stink maybe
gonna make the next one into stinky frog
or something
bugs oh should i make a long tongue no
better not better not like
got the fly
ready next one
and bro yeah needs a bath no the [\h__\h] is
that
you're not supposed to write something
huh watch only kiara hashtag
you're not supposed to you're supposed
to draw
you're supposed to draw not right
is it has to
wait where's my hashtag where's my
where's where's the hashtag
[\h__\h] i said
hashtag woke hashtag
my keyboard is in german and i'm
actually not used to it because i always
have it in japanese
all right what is this holding a bnw
plant what is that with orange eyebrow
bunnies
that sounds way too specific what the
hell what is a bmw planned anyway
with orange eyebrow bunnies this is just
someone
who didn't know what the hell the other
person drew
and what does piccolo look like again
okay we're just gonna make the these
ones so this always works this
always works
this always works
holding what is a bmw plant
they probably originally they were
probably just drawing pickle down and
that's it
oh so
but okay i'll i'll draw
i'll draw something that i think you
mean
well holding a plant
i i guess
why i don't know
some kind of plant and then orange
eyebrowed
bunnies
orange now that's probably just eyes but
okay
what does that mean what do you mean
oh the black and white plant
that probably the person probably just
didn't have any color left
well any time to color anything don't be
so specific what the hell
okay
maybe she's maybe she's um gardening and
planting carrots for her bunnies
ah well it's me
and i'm my hair is made out of straw
that person i use the the tools the line
tools i think for this
yeah what is this is this what is this
me me in love or you in love of me
bread oh that's supposed to be a bread
oh a baguette kiara
loves bread
um
okay oh we're already done okay so i
think uh
display mode shows choose how the
drawings and sentences will
be shown to the players um
manual i guess
voice over uh
uh off exhibition four shows if the
other was drawn from the beginning
from the beginning okay okay
let's go okay
i start with kiana hatching egg okay
okay okay
ozone came up with i'm so scared
that's so accurate
i like the expression it's like really
serious oh i think the hand is supposed
to be like
like me looking at the watch on my on my
wrist and like what the [\h__\h] how long
does this [\h__\h] take
oh it's kind of like a finger too yeah
what
how are you [\h__\h] around chalet
how that doesn't look like pekula senpai
do you understand this game
you don't understand the game
of course it's gonna be peculiar next
record is very happy yeah yeah it makes
sense
she looked happier before
happy rabbit anime girl
so are you going to throw a pickle or
you're going to draw someone else
he throws pickle down
that looks so cursed
i got a smiling heart heart wait
your your uh automatic
thingy avatar is a chicken
you're a chicken anyway so that
that ended up in a different direction
next doll ozone what's your idea
duck or rabbit season holo edition
what does that mean
what i wouldn't even know what to write
what does that mean okay charlene
a bug's bunny reference oh i wouldn't
have understood that good that i didn't
get that
prompt i mean i didn't but i got it in a
different form
okay pecora scolding a naughty carefree
employee
oh that's supposed to be a chicken maybe
oh i didn't even see that i wouldn't
have known what the hell that is
oh i see okay
[Laughter]
oh
is she is she whipping
supposedly a chicken with a whip
oh michael i'm disciplining okay but you
didn't get it at the cave that's okay
because that doesn't look like a chicken
so it's more like an orange human
with a kfb cap okay okay okay okay okay
no one would understand that
it's just pekona and her bunnies but
when is that supposed to be
what it looks like a spoon looks like a
flower i don't know
ah ah
that's where that came from okay
okay paco holding a ah black and white
plant
yeah okay with orange eyebrows those are
not eyebrows those are supposed to be
the carrots you cut you probably
it's okay i don't blame you but you
probably have never seen piccola's uh
emotes and emojis and how her how her
mascot basically
looks like i don't blame you hashtag
vocation yolk after all
let's see that was my drawing kind of
cute i gotta say
it's pretty cute but what
what did erica think of that when she
saw that
echo gardening okay hey that's kind of
what i thought they would
think of it
nice cute hi tuggy next stop
charlene you have been kind of stuff
charlene your your drawings have been
lacking
let's see can't open that oh that was
your idea i like the idea
oh wait that has been uh
that seems to have been um understood
well
because that's the second time you're
answering a banana phone
okay okay okay again that that's me
that's me
answering banana phone by takana
let's see if they got it is this a fine
okay okay not so far off though oh
kiara's gone oh [\h__\h] no kiana is gone
kiana is out of the picture
oh that's where kiana left the chat
we are derailing now someone questioning
you for now
it's a different kind of questioning
because
because here's like is this a banana but
here it's like
yo [\h__\h] banana you didn't you did it
didn't you you killed you killed the
apple didn't ya
i'll i'll get you into prison
random pink banana
oh man okay not so bad though
it didn't derail too much what do we
have casper is that frog girl
is the best rifle on the block
interesting idea interesting interesting
prompt
is it like it's like a whole sentence
it's just uh
you stating a fact
what what is that what
p what it i don't understand what this
is here but
okay cute drawing though kiana is a frog
yeah
even though kiana wasn't mentioned in
the beginning you kind of drew it as
me so i think there was some telepathy
going on there
wait i don't i know some legs or
or for
or i don't want to know
i guess it's probably legs
kawaii it's kind of cute and frog yeah
what did what's next me yes
and frog and frog
and frankie yes very clear i think
although isn't allowed to write
something uh additionally
[Laughter]
wow we have we we do understand each
other quite well i think we need a bit
more chaos
is it going to happen now is the chaos
going to happen now
raw for kiana we can't feed oh
[Music]
oh it does kind of look like waffle
kiara yeah yeah yeah but people would
probably just think you drew a normal
kiara
kiana loving her family oh
kawaii challenge what you got uh oh
oh well let me explain to me what is
what what is this thing the black
thing why is that
see it wasn't cooking after all i know
it but i got i didn't know what else to
write so i went with the chats up in
here
got a cookie i'm sorry
well there we go there's the chaos my
soap
[Laughter]
oh zone your stick fake your drawings
are
so good why am i on the floor
why am i on the floor
eh i didn't cook my family no no
hot tummy cooking uh well yeah it's so
tiny that it's kind of hard to see
i would probably still assume it's me
because of the
red part here and then this looks like a
crown somehow but yeah you should you
should always assume it's me
hot i'm a cooking or maybe it's me
who ate hachima's cooking and died
afterwards
and cosmetics goes for ah
that's gonna be
misunderstood i think or like not
understood at all
i i don't think they're gonna get that
ah
what
what is it with you two are you married
or what
you don't underestimate
us holy [\h__\h] i would have i wouldn't
have understood that i would be like
what the hell is that is that amelia
maybe i would have gone for amelia and
me are eating cereals
probably that's probably what i would
have written
next up coffee is hot
okay
[Music]
that reminds me of a prompt that pecora
got
yeah you didn't have enough time did you
is that a hand and it's like like like
burning because it's too hot okay
i get it what do you empty
oh [\h__\h]
ah wait when it's empty do you get the
previous prompt or
what do you see do you see mr casper
did you see the drawing or did you see
the text
i guess you just
what it's all coffee is hot
ah so you got the you got the actual
text ah okay okay
kiana eating toast and not hurting it's
real
i like that yeah i guess it can look
like hot
uh like like toast and maybe i i can say
that
but i like how you implemented that not
hurting its feelings because that's kind
of the thing
yeah oh wait that's cute
oh that's how it turned into the bread
love thingy
wait that looks like a baby kiara so
cute
holding bread wait you shouldn't write
you shouldn't write one of these that's
kind of cheating
if you didn't write that they probably
wouldn't have known but
kiana really likes bread
i mean i guess i do i do like bread yeah
hey we got that right i think
kiana loves bread
wait where did we start coffee is hot
i like that
in the end it's it's always about kiara
even when she wasn't mentioned first all
right next one kfc's on fire
okay of co then that's okay i thought
kfp for a second
no if it's kfc done okay
sorry oh my god oh my god
can't be on fire oh dear
no it's a c it's not kfb it's kfc
can you not read
oh okay [\h__\h] it can't be
on fire [\h__\h] wait is this understandable
charlene did you get it okay if you're
not a cult
she did not get it oh yeah
i said volcano
[Music]
i see well there it would be difficult
to to put that into a picture
i get that okay i said what kind of yolk
[\h__\h]
now we're just writing things yeah okay
how's it going
okay next
my name is saradin let's go onion being
higher said oh
oh okay wait what did i write
i think i was overthinking it it really
isn't being strangled it's just being
harvested
i was overthinking but it wasn't
supposed to be aquila
there we go it's supposed to be an onion
oh i like the drawing
it has emotion it has feelings it
conveys
so much yo i'ma choke out this creepy
face having onion
what the hell caspegs
but okay the theme kind of stays the
same why am i why am i
choking it now i didn't do anything i
would never choke it on you
i wouldn't do that he understand
the pumpkin oh it turned into a pumpkin
and i'm just staring at it i'm holding
it obviously but i'm very angry at it i
like the angry eyebrows here
good detail
wait that's so cute that's so cute
i'm like hmm you look like me somehow i
don't know what it is
but you do look like me
are you my family what's dom toretto
what does that mean what does that mean
but okay yeah um the the thing that i
just
said about this is kind of fitting to
what charlene wrote
family and family family
emily and diesel uh-huh
something again that i don't understand
all right we have another one that's the
last one
going to the beach aha wasn't it me who
got that
yeah cute
cute i think i think 10 out of 10.
what do you got from that papercut at
the beach
yay kind of yeah i was drawing wealthy
out i am
sexy body yo
yo
yeah i'm chilling on the beach yay yo
guys we are understanding each other too
well
there is no chaos
okay okay no you you probably got that
as
i mean some of times that that will
misunderstand that that that i think
will not reach
saradin
um is that is that me flying over
sunset around the mountain
yeah that went off topic now tony ninata
i
became i became a phoenix oh god hooker
papa is gonna be mad at me
yabby don't show her
a beautiful island on fire it does that
look
you mean maybe this part does it look
like the islanders oh [\h__\h]
all right okay this is fun
can i if i do that do i download all of
them
i want to download all of them ah wait
no i think it's one by one
was there anything anything twitter
twitter post worthy
let's see
um
i am wrong i want the improv
one
i got i don't know i don't want to show
any i don't wait
don't wanna like can you guys download
it for me
participants i don't wanna open anything
weird now i don't know what comes
okay you guys download them send them to
me newton
okay um i will have to kick everyone out
i guess
and join again i'll make a new room eh
yeah i want to make a new one how do i
make a new one
oh you can change this here actually how
do i make a new one
just go to the main page again okay
okay maybe let's do templates
one more should we do normal again or
should we go with something else
um start writing and keep drawing until
the end
finally describe the last drawing
you guys you knock off keep yourself
focused try to replicate the drawings
while the clock gets faster
i think the normal is fine too maybe one
more normal and then one knockoff
afterwards what do you think about that
let's do it that's the normal one
animation i've seen so uh i think martin
said by doing animation that was pretty
difficult
oh so if you got into the first round
please do not try to get into the second
round
i would appreciate that i will throw the
link
to the members
oh
sorry i just checked something okay uh
yeah animation is really really
difficult
okay uh maybe maybe
if i choose this setting maybe
it will reach you guys better hello
mushy mushy garlic phone
and there is the url
come in come in everyone did you guys
see the link
oh oh that was way faster i think this
time
okay okay welcome welcome
welcome no link for me what the hell
yeah it's members only but yeah not yet
no link
oh maybe
maybe next time i do a i do a normal
post
make sure you all see it and then in the
comment
section you i'll post the link in the
comment section how about that
i but the other link i think is about
like
shows up for everyone yeah it takes a
while to appear
yeah okay the next link i will post in
the comment section
of one of those posts and then i think
then i think it will be a bit
easier for you guys okay first link
appeared yeah yeah i don't know why for
some people it takes no time though
okay so we do another round normal let
me drink some iced tea slurp
um
this is fun i think i think i want to do
this more often
but actually um sprinkle one actually
though
like halloween we were kind of planning
to do a group collab on this without
audience just of us but yeah
a write a sentence um something
something funny something interesting
um chat throw me an idea maybe
there's no time
something about someone else not about
me
something with good on ame uh
[Music]
i don't know i don't know
good oh good at taking a bath that would
be cool
somebody doing it ain't at a cafe oh
[\h__\h] hey i gotta draw so many people you
kidding me
um okay we start with the table
and we put
some cups here and maybe
a piece of cake
and a fork okay and then we um
draw us
oh god oh god oh god
god no time for detail but
okay [\h__\h] so uh somebody so
i don't send fine [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
okay okay
does that look like someone was saying
bye
and okay i still have some time
i think in general the scene is set
it does it's kind of smug
okay and then um
[Music]
wait but with those recombined i think
it would be easy to
understand
that um it's it's horotodi
at a cafe
okay
i think you get it it works it works it
works
okay wait
lucky one chair
well white doesn't really show okay okay
there we go
okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay so much time
okay okay i see lucia
lucia has no phone no
lucia
this is okay i mean
this joke is in every every garlic phone
um stream that i have seen
it at least shows up once something
about russia being
boing boing or not being boing boing you
guys gonna come up with better ideas
it's always there i mean i know it's
difficult to think of something
but this is just overused
staring deep into your soul oh
but it doesn't say who it does not say
who
sorry it's gonna be me
how do i get that acrosto staring deep
into your soul
you so yourself
um how do i
maybe like some kind of
now that looks like i'm crying some kind
of energy like
that looks like a bean dog
[Music]
that looks like a killing so that's
gonna be interesting you know what let's
just go with that
this is a person and i'm staring into
you
deep into yourself very deep
[Music]
i don't know how else to do it
staring deep into your soul so
i don't want to write anything down but
like
yeah that's all i can do i think
[Laughter]
this this this has to do
let's add some details
okay
detail always always have some time to
add some detail
noise i'm done
stream spikes watch only me what the
frick is that
uh what does that even say it's sleep
what is that is that a grape for a fish
is that good as grape
good good r.i.p
[Music]
um
um takamori let's go okay
and holding loon
i can't draw
uh okay callie catty cali cali
cali
that obviously looks like cali i think
it really does
that looks like a kitchen knife
okay okay well that definitely looks
like takamori especially if i add some
color
but the let's go part i don't know about
that one
let's go we're going we're walking
we're walking we're going
walking over across i mean this is going
to be confusing but that's okay we gotta
add more chaos to it
purposefully adding chaos tacoma money
walking over a crossroad
and yeah um
okay we're kind of naked though
taco money crossing the world make space
for us
make white peasants sakamoto is
crossing through passing through i'm
done i don't need any more done
just says it all
glory to taka buddy
tt has arrived looking forward to
what what whoever is going to look at
that
thinks of it i hope that people are
participating are not listening or
watching the stream right now
otherwise you're cheating don't cheat
[Music]
oh oh this is killing small ammo
easy
i mean killing small women i think
that's pretty obvious
to you rest in peace mommy why is there
so much death
why is there so much death right now we
saw good as
uh good as grave as well
what's going on
uh stick figure tuck
you you uh saw someone drawing takamori
and stick figure but that's probably
just because they couldn't draw it in
any other way hmm
well i will do as you say
i will do as you say
[Music]
um should have maybe done it bigger
maybe do handholding again
when given the opportunity
we shall hold hands yes
stick figure why does it have to be
stick figure
hmm
this looks like hen there wasn't even a
pot on
on purpose that uh pissed off face but
okay it fits cali push
this reminds me of henry the stickman
collection thingy does that look like
her wait we can add some color
that will help color
is the mvp of this game
we're walking again wait it's the same
drawing that i did before
just a little bit less detailed
[Laughter]
kelly is not impressed kelly ain't happy
that's okay callie i don't know i know
deep in your heart you're very happy
about what's going on
well now
yesterday two of us
wow so in love wow
it's the same drawing that i did before
it's okay can't help it
that is that is uh maybe her
wedding veil boing boing
i mean they're stick figures i don't
know do stick figures have boing boing
well now they do
rtx off talk hello
oh is that me streaming why is
everything around me
orange and yellow
um wait am i okay with me is this is
this me
at my office in kfp
yeah at their fb
office ah this is is this this is fine
meme oh
is it though wouldn't he have used red
oh well
it looks like carrots chia has a gun and
is not afraid to use it
oh
ah okay let's
is this how you hold the gun totally
does that look like a gun you cute
all right i am not afraid to use it
i will shoot you i'll shoot you
you challenged me i am tiata not
kiara you thought you were meeting up
with takanasi kiana tonight well that's
where you were wrong my friend
but behold
actually takanashi kiana
and tiara are the same person
you didn't think that huh surprise beach
it doesn't look like a gun though [\h__\h]
i don't know if it will get the message
across though
i think it looks like a looks like a
microphone no
ah the angle of it
maybe maybe that oh
you wait how do you hold a gun
how do you hold a gun
okay never mind i'm not too out after
all because i don't know how to hold a
gun
but uh yeah ah
[Music]
cute pew pew pew pew pew
if we're lucky
if we're lucky they understand
no don't do that okay
we're already done okay
uh let's go start
i started good at putting amex to sleep
that's going to be taken it's going to
be wholesale let's go
yeah very simplistic very small
but i think you can see that yeah i'm
gonna tell him go to a bedtime story oh
yeah yeah yeah
pretty close almost the same round
oh [\h__\h] that is
maybe a bit too simplistic
oh is is thunderheart going to
understand this or not
oh wait it's backwards oh
oh yeah i actually did it the other way
but okay i like it this way too
i i guess i guess it kind of fits better
the other way
it kind of does maybe they like
something inside them told them like
this is
well your uh yeah i'll unconsciously
they switched it around because it fits
better i can't blame them
it does ah how the hell did you get that
ah would i get that
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is that what this what is that
what is that
empty okay did you
did you run out of time or what
oh but you got that okay okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah
looks good i'm reading bedtime story to
guna
and again uh no this this uh good good
that it ended here because
there is no bed it just looks like a
toddler gouda
is being taught how to read by amit
a little bit of parenting involved here
good that it ended at windows drawing
[Music]
that was difficult but i think we nailed
it
look at this masterpiece cute
i don't know why reina has the psycho
eyes though i should have given her the
same eyes
eh j king that's the second time he's uh
he has an empty i think
i don't know something's not working
within
oh well one less participant that's okay
uh yeah i guess
i guess that i guess that works
poor toy tea party that
actually sounds like a good stream idea
ah he disconnected oh ah that's why you
see that uh
wait another person disconnected maybe
maybe
but that person wrote something before
so maybe he just disconnected
uh
is it why
why is it taco dachi why did horatori
turn into a taco daddy are you trying to
create
chaos on purpose that is not horritory
that is obviously a taco that
the taco dances have infiltrated the
system
unbelievable they're manipulating this
show they're trying to manipulate my my
no way strength hell anything like that
makes you think it's about taco that
is a spy
taco tea type of [\h__\h] right now
[Music]
why does he have the measles why does he
have the chickenpox
hey but that's what you get that's what
you get for stealing my tea party
taco taco
taco
[Music]
oh coffee oh and you'd
you thought it was the thief that they
pale whatever
oh there's a there's a big
misunderstanding here
cute i like it but what the hell
happened to toro tony
oh man this is fun
when when when
oh
what the hell don't take over away from
me
no
i think the next person will still think
that this is amado
even though this person probably tried
to draw it as freya
also what the hell is that huge hat
ah chanting okay okay ah so the next
person will only get the text
okay okay ah
what is it with these low effort stick
figures guys
ah eh that's not kelly
blonde hair what's going on
ah
[Music]
talking about your wedding all right
that is so cute
[Music]
it does look like we're at a wedding
oh kawaii
oh oh wait he actually did left
leave a prompt can't be burning himself
you just wanted to start a fire today
and then leave
is this one
that's so cute
[Applause]
all the cursed chicken chimkin on fire
and it's fine
oh man
this is fine this is fine but it's kiara
oh that is well drawn yo
this is fine kiana version yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah and then we go to this
one
that i saw oh it was really supposed to
be
oh wow okay
for a while we really went in one
direction
again nice
yeah well it's different from the
beginning but
only
next name kiana flipping over the uno
table
okay that's finally something
interesting and original
i like it oh j king participated in that
one
it oh no it could have been so
good it could have been so good
[Music]
hello
okay i'm interested in what what they're
going to think of that
kind of laser eyes okay i cannot blame
you for that
that was it was it was kind of obvious
that that was gonna happen
yeah yeah maybe his app crashed yeah
cause after that i guess he was gone
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
i like that the first thing i do with my
new uh
skill is burning jfp yeah kaiju
kind of cause i'm so big yeah right
burns down jfp with laser eyes
and
i like this one this is one of my
favorites
it could have been even better maybe if
we went through the uno uh theme
but this is fine too i like this one
ransom piece jfp
no more no rivals accepted
so let's see what you got keanu with a
gun
i like your art style
chiata holding a gun okay this is too
easy
why is everyone so so so understanding
so in sync and this will be
yeah cause i love a gun there's no cat
ears but okay
this looks like an apple on my head
oh can't do it again
and empty okay okay
yeah there we go
chad has gotten another friend to use it
okay
and that's where i come in
oh no one had to guess it oh nice i
guess
but i think it still looks like a gun
yeah i think i think it
it came across anyway
next dog glory to taco morning
oh
it works it it works
i
why does she have a mustache a pink
mustache or is that her blush i guess
it's supposed to be blush but it looks
like she has a pink mustache
tacoma let's go very motivated friend
let's go
it stays the same very stable
very stable drawings very stable theme
callie does not look happy here okay
jating had nothing to say about that
unfortunately so
thunderhill jumps in
sweet grey's album let's go
scout kicking a final oh yeah we can
have some ttrpg
theme because tonight that i didn't make
the reservation yet but the ttrpg stream
will be on my channel
in five hours from now just to let you
know i'll make the reservation once this
stream is over
yeah yeah good that we got some titty
rpg uh prompts going here wait a second
let me drink
that's gonna be good scout kicking
although it must be difficult for
whoever is up next
to remember and draw the designs of
scout and ratato
so well that you would understand
let's see
oh that's why i tried it too big almond
kicking small
oh i mean scout is blonde
my total i guess is blonde
too yeah
um we need more skilled strawberries in
here
i'm a kicking small album
yeah that wasn't bad abandoned quickly
it's okay qjinku it's okay it's okay
don't
don't feel bad or anything huh
but what happens then you get you got
that prompt okay
okay two of them uh left early huh
this is where russia bebe left
i'm a killing small almond
and okay these are too simple
the eyebrow ah
yeah okay yeah
i messed up paint [\h__\h]
it's okay that was the end anyway
okay europe you are i'm thinking
saying your name you're probably the one
that came up with the lucia prompt
yes i am not surprised not surprised at
all
okay yeah eh
boy and
nice boing boings
yup that's that's how it is
i like how you started out drawing the
boobs in the beginning
there's your bling bling okay
it's great that uh we are all in sync
but
oh wait that gives me an idea for the
next prompt
let's see i probably spent was probably
spread
what spell spelled wrong probably what
was i reading
okay you spell to the right though
congratulations
okay next up banana
sauce that just looks sus to me
good i'm stuck in the popsicle
ah it kind of looks like a popsicle
somehow yeah that doesn't that does not
look like a banana
okay this one must have been the most
derailed one yet
good i did
wait what did that say though so ah wait
i guess
yeah it does say sorry because he
probably didn't know how to draw it
good on that that's how that happened
a fish popsicle oh
you looked at dad so my oh
ew looking brown green green and blue
oh my god
if that's supposed to be a tongue you
you you can't be happy
then it ended here because i think
someone would have thought that it's
even throwing up
fish or it's like burning fish with fire
coming out of your mouth all right okay
this was interesting um i'll make a new
round
yep and this time we'll set it to knock
up i guess i don't really know what it
is you try
you try to replicate the drugs when the
clock gets faster
okay but you don't have to guess what
something is right
but that's just gonna be replicating
stick figures
that's just gonna be replicating stick
figures most of the time with your
guys's drawing scales
it's not even even gonna be that
difficult
let's do 10 normal is funny huh
yeah i do i do i guess so
secret is good one all the actions are a
mystery drawings and sentences are
hidden
during the game then
then how how does that even work
try animation animation is so difficult
sandwich start writing and keep drawing
until the end finally describe the last
one i want
it sounds interesting i can't really
imagine what it is but i guess i want to
try that out
okay guys should i should i bring in a
good artist
like should i snuggle in one good artist
what do you think about that
just one and the rest will be members
yeah yeah okay wait a second
we can we can add uh we can make it 11
then
or oh 12. i guess let's make it 12 i
guess
since it's gonna be the last round
probably no no i don't think ina is
available right now
um okay
well if it's 12 then i'm getting into
get
in here
i think this message failed to send
why why you think that's a
okay i think it worked i think it worked
what about
me
there we go jolly is in
maybe wealthy welfia are you here are
you watching this probably not
but wait let me let me be in wealthy
maybe waffle will see that dm
hey are you here
do you wanna join now or never
what time zone i don't don't answer
answer me but i wonder
where there is over capacity please wait
if you look what the
frick what the freak
i tried standing again no twitter
doesn't like it when i send garlic phone
uh messages what buddies replying oh my
god
he said oh yes get in here
please
twitter let me send these messages
it keeps on failing to send the message
wait let me try to uh
get in here please maybe separate the
link
um dot
com there you go how about that that's
true that should work
it's gonna join us
i think wealthy might join us exciting
yeah we got the gold in here
can i just can i add one more
this
just get all the mvp artists in here
okay i invited one more
one more that seems to be active right
now
where where are my artists where are my
artists set
should i uh
is inna is inna up ethan no i don't
think so
you know isn't online so i i don't want
to disturb mama rooney
wait who else could i invite dakuma
are you watching akuma
akuma
okay that's a bunch of
bunch of good artists yeah i tried i
sent
i sent christina manzanita a link too
but i don't know if she saw it she i saw
her being active on twitter
christina check your dms i slid into
them
smoothly
join
i think yoona is probably not not
available
probably all star rounds what's your
sense
what you said
i never i never had a conversation with
torchy sensei before
for the people who don't know christina
montanita recently drew new
um memory modes for me
let's see uh who else is a
is a good or decent artist
in kfp
i can try wait oh you not replied but
she rides she fell asleep are you
streaming already
do you wanna join kusa
you can join on the phone too right this
game
or if you wanna holy [\h__\h] this is gonna
be such an amazing
legendary [\h__\h] round yo
sorry guys i hope you're not mad but i
think this will be amazing
and let's see how about you
are you here trying to
message another one
uh let me also let me try
might take a while for my pc to turn on
i can give you six minutes
hey okay
what about what about i'll give it a try
i'm scared but
i will not mention because i don't want
to give any pressure
i mean
making a mvp team
wait i'm writing a polite message right
now
okay also how about how about how about
you how about you
uh one of the artists i messaged says i
still have no idea what garlic phone is
it kind of comes naturally should we try
one more normal round though if we're
going with all these amazing artists i
want to do a nomination
it comes natural come on
give it a try
oh my god
this is gonna be so good this is gonna
be so good i'm getting the best people
in here
holy guy
ah this one artist is currently naked
and in the bathtub
guess who we're just kidding okay okay
this one is joining okay okay um
how about how about you uh
how about you what's up
me
okay i invited another one okay it might
be difficult to get
uh twelve so let's make ten after all
hey some of you guys said that person so
i'm gonna try
is that person active right now
hello moshi moshi this is kiara
from hello ian would you like to join
a spontaneous round of
uh garlic phone
oh [\h__\h] i copy pasted something oh [\h__\h]
that was the wrong copy paste
look uh wait
here is the link it sounds like an egg
okay okay okay
okay okay
okay um
callie now he's really awake
oh we got we got a big one we got a big
one i think
callie's probably busy what i can ask
callie
is you busy or
do you want to join a spontaneous round
of
garlic phone
i am streaming right now you
can say no though i know you
probably busy
oh
the one who drew the usual room
six out of ten okay four more come on
four more ah
i have a good idea i think i ah
this is this is the best garlic phone
round
ever
[Music]
i think that person is probably not here
right now
okay let's see
um we're almost there guys
all-star round yeah who else
he's probably able to join
all right wait dude
ah kelly i think is busy she's not
replying ah
how about you are you are you
are you here right now by any chance
why not join us from david scott this
sounds so weird
garlic phone round i am streaming
right now by the way you can say no
joke i mean
if you who why would you want to say no
ah how about this person are you
around right now
if yes wanna join no pressure
though but i am streaming
please join
come on come on guys come on
and probably if even if these people
join i need one more person
how about you are you are you
that would be crazy are you by any
chance
available for a 10 minute round
of i don't know if it's gonna take 10
minutes but garlic phone
i am streaming right now you can say
no no i did not say i was inviting you
but we are are doing kfb
artists round okay yes go
come on someone answer me
ah that's also a good idea thank you
chad
let me ask that person
wait wait wait wait wait
wait uh
i should i'm messing up
all the people that i've been messaging
seem to not
be around huh or they're trying to
assess the situation
okay i message one more
[Music]
come on
yeah axel seems to be active yo yo yo yo
[\h__\h] mushy this is a link to
garlic phone please join
[Music]
joy
give me the link okay sorry to keep
everyone waiting
my my high profile guess i'm sorry to
keep you waiting we're almost there
i will be the worst artist in this group
oh wait that one person that i messaged
is
uh is is is awake and has just
tweeted something so she might see my
message
and think about it
ah eyes in bed okay okay
no problem good night
[Music]
who joined
ah we could honestly just go with eight
now i think
we'll still get like good good stuff
there uh
unless how about this person
oh this is kind of i feel i feel shy
asking this person
but i'll i'll give it a try
quite a big artist another another big
artist
yeah we got some insane people
all of them all of them
i think have drawn takanashi kiara
before
hey thank you everyone for drawing me
thank you very much should i try navi
i never talked with her either though
not really
[Music]
she also i think in her time zone
she's probably sleeping
now
yeah i don't i don't want to wake her up
myself
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
you can not run you have
been chosen
another kfp artist
you don't have a choice i mean you do
you don't have to but please join
can we do nine let's do nine come on
who is the last one who takes the chance
where's the last one i know you'll be
the one i know you'll be the one
there we go let's [\h__\h] go
the best garlic phone round ever
icky myself
write a sentence okay um
okay we gotta we gotta get some good
ones holo ian
holo holo myth um
uh uh fight to death
will it censor the word do you think it
will censor the word
probably not right
i wanted to write something about the
cute but i'm not sure what i would write
there
so go
that's my that's my part that's my part
and my just sleep who wrote that
oh wait are you telling emma to just
sleep
well i will just draw emma asleep uh how
does
emma look like oh god i don't think
i can draw this in a way that
oh it would look like oh my god i have
to have to look it up
quick and
[Music]
apparently emma wears glasses
uh in sleep and and mine is very
troubled
because uh obvious
reasons and i cannot sleep at night
because we do so much [\h__\h]
in our streams
does it even look like end model
it doesn't it doesn't add some red to it
here
hardcore fans maybe recognize it
and then who is the most troublesome
let's just do a taco because
is that how a taco looks like because
that might give it away that it's enema
that might help a little bit
oh [\h__\h] that might help oh my god i'm
i'm running out of time
but it's it's troubled and my thinking
about
the takodachis that are being bonked by
yeah that are being bonked by inna with
a crowd crowbar
okay we kind of went off topic there
the flaps uh are the flaps the flaps the
flaps okay
there we go thank you i know i knew it
was missing something
alrighty but as we can see the taco
dashies are enjoying it
good stuff okay okay i'm done i think
that's that's pretty cute
oh is this is this uh cali giving me
headphones
cali um petting
kiara i think that's what it is
okay thank you for this gorgeous piece
of art wealthy
we have to save every animation that
comes
out of it out of this round
because this is gonna be the real good
stuff
i'm so excited for everyone's eyes oh my
god garfield it's
me
okay i'm gonna draw
[Music]
me on a cat's body
oh my god it's already so cursed
i am orange cat
i'm cat
okay
this is lasagna
i'm changing the topics here to get more
chaos
i'm taking my artistic freedom okay
does it look like me what do you guys
think ah wait are people forgetting to
draw my
feathers
that would probably really help
okay done
garfield it's me it's always been me
bamboozle
surprise m garfield video
when i mean my
mcat video was basically that it was
just me exposing myself
cat ear color yep yep okay there we go
i think it's pretty clear i'm done black
stripes
[\h__\h] ah i can still do it okay
now i look like bread probably music
don't done
cheese i'm garfield
and bread actually i am now bread i have
turned into a baguette
next up oh my god what's going on just
[\h__\h] help
uh my turn to describe this scene
how good i can't
guna can't swim
without floaties though
being attacked by shark
it's ah i guess it's just drowning gouda
no let's make it more dramatic
more drama baby let's go
hallie being awesome as always what the
hell is that prompt
okay um callie callie
how do you draw someone being awesome
just her standing there
already is her being awesome right
my hand was covering up when i was
drawing so
that kind of ended up looking weird
again bigger they have to be bigger the
shades
i think i think the shade kinda
make her look being awesome
okay
we'll get the calliope detail in there
yeah okay and some
beautiful flowing hair
and her being absolutely stunning
sparkling beautiful
queen hello
okay and uh
[Music]
spikes always wondered if those don't
hurt her
you know this i mean i think it already
looks like kelly let's add some color
i mean that's just cali being smug
though
yeah they're running all the time
i mean it definitely looks like cali at
least so they're not going to
misunderstand dad
okay oh
thumbs up
that's just smug dad yeah
did waffy draw that too it's waffy style
can't be on fire ah this is the it's
fine meme again it's no wait that's not
the it's fine
that's the one with the child looking
back to the camera and being like
[Music]
hmm
on fire because
they misbehaved
well that's what happens starter fire
dude oh i should have just written
spikes
this should have just written stream
sparks kiana with samu
who who is are they asking for
sam stannis sam
who well who is
samuel samus
samus from metroid
sally sammy chiara
okay okay okay uh
uh
okay
no time
[Music]
my hats always important the hats
oh god this is the looking bad but they
will understand
i mean the hat kind of gives it away i
would say
make it blue make it blue make it blue
peace
peas and um
[Music]
good eyes closed what what what exactly
they look like again
damn i forgot it's okay she already
looks like gouda
add some orange and we good
okay
missing yeah that that stuff was the
thing
all right i'm done thanks
so much tony hi 670
club when
the hat what was the hat that was fine
oh my god
is that's me driving a bus is that
supposed to be
cali but the red hair
why not pink hair
[Music]
is that middle baby it's ami
is that olivia oh oh sh
oh cuz oh then that's amit driving over
olivia
oh olivia
oliver
oh that that's true yeah because that's
oh we're already done
so sad let's go
okay we started out with holoman finance
and dev i'm really interested for what
oh [\h__\h] yes this is the best
person to start off with to to draw that
definitely wait a second that
that's that's that's not all of wait
that's good huh no
is it gonna it's inna that's me
is that cali
is that kelly where is amit
there's one person missing his tablet
broke
no no not the worst time
is this drama of mouse or what damn it
kiana punch is good i will take that she
bleeds the bag
you forgot about this dude though who is
that who's that
[Music]
cute
oh my goodness looks so cute
wait since since the taco bell is
already bleeding in the background that
means i already killed the taco daddy
didn't i let's go
chiana bullying her children
no what the hell that's not my child
that's good i mean i guess
some people say it
[Laughter]
interesting hello
hey hey
kiana preferring the new cave we my
oh yeah okay
you didn't kind of drew me in a more
kind-hearted light thank you i'm not
killing
chickens anymore i would never i would
never do that in the first place
yeah looking at the cafe menu okay and
those two are understanding one another
let's go then charlie's idea was
the anchors are getting the girl yeah
okay let me take a sip though
sipping sipping
this is so this is such a genius idea i
think you know how
a lot of girls did garlic phone with
fans like random fans and a lot of
people do it with
uh holo members but has anyone ever done
it with
kfp artists like their own artists
before has anyone ever done that
yakuza getting the girls yeah i like the
i like the suits and all that that
really gives off the yakuza vibes or
like the
the smug
[Music]
let's [\h__\h] go let's go
cute cute
ah i am in heaven
can you guys save the gifts can someone
save the gifts besides me
i'm scared of saving them i don't know
what pops up when i do it
cats canada with sunglasses and a katana
oh cool cool cool cool
i've seen that somewhere before you and
i kind of drew that in in the
in the uh uh goodbye declaration
music video there was a yakuza
appearance there as well
yeah with samuel
wait i still i still don't understand
i guess it wasn't about i guess it
wasn't about kuda
but
[Laughter]
[Music]
well yeah oh well we derailed we have
been derailed
samurai sword ah
i say i see i see i see okay
kiana driving a car oh
with my feet of course with my feet what
else
and there's a panicking chicken there
that chicken is so cute
is that why the chicken panicking my
driving skills would be
aaa plus last plus plus plugs
got a forcing kfb too what
hi what's going on
you are
you are creating chaos here not for the
first time
i i i'm not sure if it was a good idea
to bring you in just kidding
i'm just kidding just kidding oh that's
cute though
it is not that different from that image
there's just no
car next doll
teaching employees to work
cute his brows are crashed and
[\h__\h]
hey hey what
that's just two chickens oh wait i guess
manzanita didn't clarify that it's kiara
teaching
but is one of them supposed to be me
axel is one of them supposed to be me
delivery failed ah
is this a ah cause like um
okay you got some fantasy narada
[Laughter]
wait this was never wait i don't
i wanna know what jolly was thinking
what where are you actually thinking of
the ahmed olivia
i'm i'm a i'm the only scene
oh i'm driving over olivia
wait that's the end [\h__\h] i wanted to see
someone draw that
oopsie
[Laughter]
[Music]
i wasn't watching the stream it's okay
it's okay this is interesting i
i like where we're going with this
[Music]
wow that is a real good drawing of
garfield but
did you just say garfield and oh my god
it's obviously kiara garfield okay not
not not that obvious i see it on the
fluffy hair though i say it i see it
oh wait and that's my blouse that's my
blouse my white blouse and then it just
turned into garfield but don't worry i
got your fam
i understand completely i know that this
is supposed to be
kiara garfield
i understand everything katya are
getting feet
yes yes yes lasagna that's what i'm
gonna eat tonight
pizza i ate pizza last night how the
[\h__\h] did you know
how did you know
i'm being stalked help katya
eating pizza cute
yes looks like me
looks like me ralphie must be copying
my looks right now charlie kiya wow
eat pizza oh my god it's so cute
the munch the munch is so cute i love it
yes what's your idea say so cali ah
okay okay i i guess that's where i drew
the
cali being awesome one right
it's difficult to draw that because
kelly is actually
always kind of stay so like that's just
her default
she's kind of the most say so in in
normal
live english yeah that being beautiful
whoa jolly let's go
that is indeed a beautiful beautiful dad
wow
let's go cali being awesome as well
that's the one that i got yeah
i mean we're all doing the sparkle thing
we're all doing the sparkle thing
because we don't know what else to do
how else to show
what we're trying to draw who is that in
the world let's go
it's so similar dad is that me
no wait is that clara is that supposed
to be clara or someone this is so cute
cute wealthy
challenging best dad featuring kiana in
the background
could be me could be clara we don't know
but good job
good job nice round nice round next one
and i just sleep that's the one i got
yeah
i think that turned out pretty good
emma do bonking the taco dashi a dream
bonking
ah but that dr is not gonna not gonna
come across
but okay yeah yeah yeah
yes and we're taking care of
taking care yeah in in her own way
oh that's cute oh cuddling
and we're cuddling with taco touches
oh and my baby said taco duchess
oh cute
not bad i when you if you're drawing
that with mouse then i have to say
not bad the the hair the detail good job
how cool does your wit what
did you run out of time
you know promoting sparks
yo i love that kiana said you can find
it elsa it's even in my in my spice
outfit
yes i'm standing on fire today
i love it i love it so much
can't be on fire as usual oh that's how
that happened
[Music]
because they misbehaved ah
oh these are all so good
this is like chiada is in control
yes that's can't be on fire that's right
i did
nice is this the last one not yet i
don't want this to end
i don't want this to ever end
callie given kiara headsets oh
yeah that's actually exactly what i uh
wrote
basically hell you're patting kiara come
on
turn me into a cat do it
okay
[Laughter]
it's it's uh still i think very clear
cali takes care of kiara okay okay okay
okay
yo and baby
this is precious
so cute help me help
calibrating bathing kiana
oh
[Music]
wait she turned it around kiana feeding
baby kelly
yonah are you drunk
wait that's cute too i i i like to
imagine that
that is pretty cute
yeah avengers style i like it too
we'll play this again with the audience
again don't worry
uh next time next time piano feed the
baby kelly
oh we need to switch at roo
reading comprehension goku
drawings are the [\h__\h] best
it's so cute could i can't swim
[Music]
yeah just [\h__\h] help i love that one
too
but i can't talk so being attacked by
shark sorry i have to improvise a little
bit there i wanted to
add in some spices
ah he's being attacked by a shark
nice noise you did your best with mouse
good job good to be attacked by a shark
in the water
[Laughter]
the shark's face too oh my god
shark eating gouda yeah bit no
it's the end no
[Music]
no this was so good
thank you everyone this was so good
thank you everyone for participating so
spontaneously
my dear artist um you know this was so
much fun i might want to do this again
um mixing audience and actual artists
together and but but next time i'll
i'll i'll message everyone ahead of time
and then i'll give you a time and you
will know
when i'll be streaming thank you though
for
joining in so spontaneously i wish it
was so much fun we'll have to play this
again
um i'll keep the stream rather short
because we have ttrpg later and i gotta
set it up and now
and so this is a short stream but i
think i'll go read some super chats
quickly
and then the stream will end so yes yes
yes yes yes
thank you for participating
thank you i'll save i'll save these i'll
go into super chat
uh intermission screen and i'll save
these and then
i'll see you in the other screen to read
some super chats okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah this was so much fun
thank you see you in three minutes
[Music]
oh my god what's going on here
what's happening what's going on
what's happening
oh my god
[Laughter]
what are those chickens doing
oh dear lord oh god
wait i'll make myself a little bit
smaller
and so chicken you're on wildfioner's
lab today
please enjoy we'll read the super jets
quickly
shouldn't take too long also i saved all
the gifs i saved them all
they're in safe hands now
making new employees
that was so much fun i hope i don't get
bunked by management
let's see
did i did i get any bunks i don't see
any bunks
yeah yeah okay i don't
i don't see any bunks okay okay
yeah i don't know before for like i
don't know inviting so many people
like uh that i don't know uh for like
kind of a collaboration
it's like low-key low-key collaboration
but at the same time not but i i know i
i've never been bugged before
and it will never happen in the future
either we good
for pronouncing
wait now that you did did i say the
three letter word
g-i-f uh unconsciously i said it
correctly i don't actually know now that
i
want to say it consciously i don't know
how to say it
did i say it did i say gif
did i say gif or jeff
jeff was correct is it though is it
though
is it though thank you for the
membership
i said i said i said did i did i say
jefford
gif well in german we say not afrida
saying we say gif
gif gif is the right one jesus
well i don't know whatever they're both
fine
now let me write this up actually
ah some people answered me now i'm so
sorry
gummy mata kondo kara
i actually also asked um akira the one
who drew
for example my ending screen background
the most gorgeous art ever
[Laughter]
thank you so much for participating
please join again next time
sorry for your broken tablet
gotta say thank you to everyone eh i was
doing something else
ah sorry i will invite
you again next time
also said sorry it's okay your
turn next no more
escape next time
thank you everyone sorry about that
please ign
some people who didn't answer um
will be confused once they see the
message
let me quickly write something
ah i'm so happy that i could have all
these uh
cool artists dope ass artists here that
was so much fun
oh man oh man i want to upload one right
now
which one should i upload
[Music]
which one do i upload holdem if fighting
to death
[Music]
which one was the best one which one did
you like the most started fire today
that one was good yeah which one was
that
this one this one
oh yeah i'm gonna upload that one
so much fun
stream sparks
thanks artists for joining
they were all so good i love them all
i uploaded one on twitter
okay
[Music]
let me get my exo file
garlic foam golly by the way i don't
know if you guys have realized yet but
it's actually not called garlic phone
it is indeed called garcic phone yes yes
yes
i already uh i am i am aware of that
but i still i still went for
garlic because garlic is better i love
garlic who doesn't love garlic
garlic baguette best thing ever
[Music]
vampires oh well
then i guess mega senpai was not
watching the stream that's for sure
i'm sorry magnum senpai
oh okay i made sure to get the correct
axle
sheet this time
i keep on messing up and getting the
wrong one i think
couple couple
ah wait sorry i i don't know is it hyde
or hede
he's a vampire [\h__\h]
he's a vampire no bgm oh [\h__\h] oh let me
turn on the good boss and
bosa nova boss music
dun uh downloads
i guess he is kind of like a vampire it
is hida isn't it
i wasn't i was uh i didn't want to
mispronounce his name so i tried to
not say it at all
the good bgm is back
please enjoy old live songs
bosa nova version
is it hide he it he did he did it
he didn't he did
oh wait it's hide
wait wait what why now i'm confused
okay is it number one here or number two
pronoun what brain
or number two hide
number two hi oh [\h__\h] oh
it's it's hide oh okay
excuse me i will never mispronounce ever
again
like old cartridges from nintendo 64.
[Music]
there you go now they work okay let's go
mr casper kristoff duncan looking for
the top dungeon
crispy chicken dankesh and petruchen
dangestion
[Music]
version
i have so many questions about kiana
burning kfp what
what what do you question about that
isn't it clear
isn't it clear why that happened
tantra i have no idea what this cream is
so i'm eager to find out also what do
you think of garlic chicken i think the
flavor would be great
will be great garlic chicken i probably
have eaten something like that before
obviously vegan chicken but
uh yeah anything with garlic is great
i put a sheet of garlic in my in in my
food whenever i cook
is it just well is it just a chicken
dish with
it is grating yeah that's popular in
korea huh
[Music]
garlic ice cream no thank you that's
that's that's where i
uh tab out
i guess i have never really eaten the
real deal
the real garlic chicken i gotta try it
sometime
easy to go overboard there is no going
overboard with garlic
yummy yum yum yum i hope i can try it
sometime felix
maybe since you since you recommend it
to me i guess you haven't eaten it
before
but i want to eat eat it too the real
deal
not just some garlic on the chicken i
guess they do it differently
thank you for the red super chat
slow poke thank you okay this time this
time this time you're not getting me
i'm i'm focused right now i understand
what this is going to be
everyone else oh my god but you oh
you read my mind everyone else is doing
it so i want an order to please i'll
have two number nines number nine large
is number six with extra dip
and number seven two number 45s one of
cheese and a large soda thanks colonel
kiara
you know what just like two days ago ago
or so
i was thinking to myself that no one has
ordered a big smoke
in a long long long long time in my
super chats
even though back in the day
everyone did it every [\h__\h] second
super chat was a big smoke order
and i was like oh they kind of ended
that meme where did that one go they
they don't do that anymore
it used to be everyone i was so mad at
some point
because there were really long messages
[Music]
i felt like they like you were you guys
were trolling me because they were so
long i had to read them when they were
red ones and pink ones
it was painful
[Laughter]
did you guys stop because it was so
painful for me
yeah i got like 100 of them before
oh i made the mistake of saying i would
read them
i guess i did once yeah
ah the mean cuddle
yeah it got old after being used 100
times
but thank you slowpoke for bringing that
up again
this time this time i am i am prepared i
was prepared for you
and i'm i am actually i was thinking
about
that meme just recently so i like it
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinkie kiana can you
explain
melvin casey to me is that just a german
thing or is it eaten in australia also i
have
never heard of it but it sounds
disgusting
ew eh
let me go go
[Music]
ew that's so disgusting
that looks that looks really bad
yeah is there isn't that big
then
ew that is so disgusting
wait is there an english word it's just
building cases
[Music]
in the local dialect and often known as
spinning cases spider cheese is a german
specialty
cheese it is made by flavoring balls of
cork
with a caraway insult allowing them to
dry and then leaving them in a wooden
box containing rye flour and cheese
cheese mites cheese mites for about
three months
an nc enzyme inseam and seam
in the digestive juices excreted by the
mites
causes the cheese to ripen
yeah that sounds disgusting
and it also doesn't look very good evil
cheese mites mites
i did not know that such a thing exists
and uh it doesn't really seem to be a
thing
in my country either you guys are just
as shy as me
nope nope nope nope nope nope nope nope
nope
[Music]
indeed indeed
i mean i'm guessing that it probably
actually tastes like good if you like
you know that kind of um like
really ripe cheese i guess if you like
that stuff then you probably
like the cheese but just thinking
just thinking about it i don't know it
probably tastes good i
i believe you that probably just tastes
like no more cheese probably
but yeah shall we shall we get hatsuma
to try it
she seems to eat anything so we have to
get someone to test it
let's ask hatsuma
you eat it with the life minds no
[\h__\h] way i mean that must be a line
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] it seems that the mites
are still
on the like in the cheese
[Music]
i can't
i can i can
[Music]
i thought
you know it's it's the country next door
so i thought that they don't do any
weird stuff
i i have been wronged
i don't trust the germans anymore
[Music]
i want to delete this knowledge out of
my brain
i want to get rid of it please
oh my god can we continue thank you for
that pinkie
thank you so much tai chi thank you also
for pinky this is garlic speaking what
can i do for you
tai chi your name is garlic now
thank you for answering the phone no one
was answering the phone
i was waiting and waiting and waiting
and waiting and no one picked up thank
you tai chi finally someone picked up
thank you for the pinkie
i'll see laven thank you and crispy
uh this is a japanese super chat but
this person only has a
emoji has his name and i don't know how
to describe the smoke this emoji we had
that before
i know i know
not today
[Music]
fight
i was nervous and i used my phone and
pro i promised i could have done better
i promise i am an artist
it's okay shaolin maybe you can join
again next time no problem
you guys all did great i'm so glad you
all joined and i'm so glad it went well
today
no troubles no no problems
thank you for behaving everyone i'm very
relieved i was very nervous
about this but everyone did well i mean
next time we play it who knows what
happens but i think we're gonna
have some more fun next time
challenge and challenges
you drew you drew garlic
ginger in the danger s17 b-42 dungeon
showing dungeon
[Music]
i was having a pretty bad day until i
saw you were live i love you so so much
and i love the fact that our birthdays
are pretty close
whoa thank you for making all our days
better you're welcome
thank you soon
don't worry about it elsie love and
duncan
oh that's funny while previously kiana
searched for zelda today members were
searching for a link
[Music]
our boy thank you for the red silver
chad said that i can't normally make
your streams because time zones but i'm
glad i could make tonight
i'm glad you made it hope you enjoyed it
thank you for trying to come to my
streams even though it's kind of tough
with time zones thank you i appreciate
it
[\h__\h] it's taiki
hi you're trying to tell me it's taking
no time tight
thank you okay i'll i'll try to
pronounce it correctly now
[Music]
our boy match kisses for you
hope to see you again soon in the stream
furlough duncan a clay dungeon
[Music]
for the pinky
i'm dying the 4th of august is my
birthday
tomorrow so i guess in your time zone
it's already your birthday you are my
best idol in my whole life when i'm
depressed
deep your energy energetic stream kind
of kfp bring me up
i really appreciate this not much huge
this is my return i hope everybody being
[Music]
happy
oh my god i just opened up twitter for
one second and i see a yuna fan art
[Music]
um
my pro korean let's go
happy birthday to you
wait there's another korean super chat
that i cannot read
[Music]
what is this crusader chicken
why does it say immortal skin in english
it sounds like you have some kind of
chicken word in your name it says
immortal skin though wait immortal
immortal
what does this mean
phoenix chicken ah why does it translate
to immortal skin
interesting what's your
they're making fun of me
it's hick danke mr casper's dancing
thank you for the pinkie so it turns out
drawing on the phone is hard
ah you are using the phone well at least
you can use your finger with that i feel
like that makes it easier than using a
mouse
at least even then my hand drawing was
recognizable
smug no it was not seriously that was
fun
glad i was able to play my with my
aussie after i got bunked from a mogus
ah and i was able to start an m frog
drawing friend and the world could
always use more for a chia
raquiara is pretty pretty damn cute
anyway you're the best and never allow
anyone else to say otherwise high five
yeah thank you thank you for taking part
don't apologize thank you guys thank you
guys for drawing everyone's apologizing
in the
in the super chats don't do that you did
great
valkyries that was it i mean it was
mostly stick figures but
we still connected with one another and
got
almost all of the topics pretty decently
synced up
uh i kept grossing the drawing skills
yeah they were bad but
but but that's that's the fun part too
seeing everyone's bad dresses and
someone sometimes seeing a few good ones
in there
but still like we were in sync we
weren't seeing
yeah that's the ksp
fb connection can't be uh
telepathy
my pancreas wrangles this was honestly
something drying paco now is not that
difficult i think because she has these
really
standing out features like uh bunny ears
and the the braids
and blue light blue as long as you add a
light blue color it's probably pretty
pretty simple
so yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
he wanted a compliment you did great
cat that is an albedo dancing
lucky all jmp employees were fired from
chef attire
because we care for our employees
whatever whatever
your story's burnt down what are you
going to do now huh
soldado 94 danger thunderslav 21
[Music]
and patrick you know what mama looney
actually seemed like kind of open to
participating it was just that she was
in the bathtub so
next time i'll get her in oh it's gonna
be good
it's gonna be good but it's gonna be a
bit a problem to communicate it's gotta
it has to be like
simple english words in the prompts
because if we're also getting akira
and um maybe
another person who i was inviting was um
who is often drawing like gifs
of me and other her life girls and it's
also
often in the chat as well japanese
member
and so
yeah if we get those in some japanese
artists
and some more english japanese artists
wrong oh
i don't know if i can get that many
japanese artists together but but we can
still mix it we just gotta have some
simple topics i think
gif i don't know man i don't i don't
mind saying it both ways i'm just not
sure which one you guys are gonna
like me you like hearing me say
yeah i got she draws some really cute
ones and i think his drawing style would
be great
to quickly whip up something in in
garlic phone
[Music]
people would be mad either way yeah
fireballs 1765 dungeon
lizard wizard duncan alexander mentions
fireball 1765 you know what
we could actually also play garlic phone
in a members only stream as well
that would be another fun game where uh
we could hang out and have some fun
together for members only because i
wanted to play more games with the
members
oh yeah let's do that
[Music]
yeah you could post the link in youtube
chat yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah cause dennis members
owe me anyway
[Music]
nice thank you for the pinky thank you
for the stream
and your cheer i woke up this morning to
the news of my oh
grandfather's death and i'm expecting an
email today
with will determine the next two years
which will
depend to determine the next two years
of my life so thanks for your cheer
it was just to pick me up i needed
you're welcome
that sounds rough my condolences but
you'll get through
it you'll get through it and i'm sure
that
happy times await you
thank you so so much for your support
and i'm glad i could cheer you up a
little bit
if my streams help you with that then
please watch
as much as you can thank you soon for
the support
please take care of yourself and take
some time
if you need it
[Music]
morgan porter thank you
ah sorry that you couldn't join yeah
the links didn't show up um
that fast but next time next time
there's always a next time
this is just the first time we played
this one i want to play it again
thank you for trying though if we do it
in a members only stream i think the
chances will be higher that everyone can
take part
uh tear sheet thank you christina
manzanita
sad that i was able to get in this
i mean was not wasn't able to get in
this but this avengers
avengers style artists get together was
amazing
maybe i'll join the next time please do
please do and yeah i think i think um
it was a great spontaneous idea i'm
sorry that i took away the chance from
more viewers to participate but i think
that was worth it so
thank you moon dog for being
cooperative and supportive but you'll
get in there next time you remember
anyway so
we'll make it happen yeah what worth it
thank you i'm glad we all agree on it
[Music]
not that i didn't want to play with you
guys i want to play with you guys too
some of them were viewers anyway that's
true that's true a lot of them were
watching the stream at the very moment
um
my throat is uh hurting i was screaming
so much today i feel like
[Music]
you can dance
that was good i was really excited so
good thing tiana is mostly quiet
[Music]
i want to try super jet in german
someday oh sure
no problem got any cough drops i know i
know but we're almost done we're fine
if i have the one hour where i'll be
quiet
oh then i'll be fine rachel thank you
for the pinky
before i suffer in an intensive week of
assignment
submissions oh [\h__\h] i just want to take
this chance to thank you for how
talented kind and caring you are
you're such an amazing addition to
hololive and i love you and your content
you're doing great
thank you that is so sweet
that sounds very stressful but i wish
you the best of luck
and i'm sure you'll be fine
take a little bit of my phoenix luck
[Music]
take it with you thank you for your
support
and your kind-hearted words thank you
and i appreciate it very much
good luck
yeah thanks for the pinky what a great
stream last round was so good
yeah it was i'm glad you enjoyed it f oh
thank you i had a blast
black armor dankeshen gidi dankeshen
treverjeet angelson artist collab was an
amazing idea thank you
today's stream was fun i wanted to join
this game too but my youtube seems slow
since i'm using a mouse i must be more
bad at drawing than i usually no
no problem maybe try again next time
people were having some issues uh
getting the link
so i'm sorry sorry
and midnight every now and then can you
tweet out the twitter handles of all the
all-star artists
and yes i can i will have to
do another tweet where i'm i'm just
gonna post another
gif gif after this stream and i'll do
that
coirs dancing
how could you say jeff i used to look up
to you but now i don't
know what to do with my life i'm so
sorry
bruno silver thank you lord is the
evil lord is lord sith evil lord
self-evil
you have organized such a wonderful
impromptu collab among your artists this
is for this you deserve oh clap [\h__\h]
club this stream is so much fun to watch
glad to see you have fun
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
spontaneous but good stuff
yes yes glad it went well we're almost
done with super chats
[Music]
cabbage thank you for the red silver
chad
what collab outside of her life would
you like to see from your gen mates or
have for yourself
only theoretically without considering
if they know each other
hope it's okay to question something
like this
um
[Music]
i want to collab with nabi sensei
and eventually someday
maybe promo um
[Music]
i kinda wanna maybe collab with
uh fruit at some point maybe
[Music]
this is just good way too good music
i'm sure there's a lot of uh people who
i
would like to mention but can't think of
right now because brain empty
but those are the ones that i can think
of from the top of my head
[Music]
outside whole live collab mama my mama
we're doing it soon though i think we're
gonna do it soon
yeah mama
yeah baby too but you know we we tried
doesn't change my my my desire for it
but
yeah anyway continuing thank you for the
rental chat
i hope you get some of those collabs
that you are uh asking for
and i'm almost 247 and thank you and s
dev senpai duncan
your favorite german savory dish
gonna be visiting my family in germany
this weekend and i can't wait to eat my
film of liberty
specifically german like i love labor
case to put like
savory dish she's like
no well i
well uh that's actually that's really
difficult to answer because like
most of german food we have in australia
and um i'm not sure if i should count
those in
uh uh
i don't know how to answer this
[Music]
um but i do love liberty labor cancer
summer with cocaine
[Music]
i don't really like baklava it's not
sweet enough
i don't like curry breast i like it
it's pretty good hmm
awesome no [\h__\h] way what
last what look at me like
yeah that's a sm
[Music]
i just spoke a tiny bit of australian
accent
german shush
every other cult thank you for the pinky
look up kazumatsu it's a type of cheese
don't be eating anything while looking
no i don't wanna not another disgusting
cheese
i don't wanna but it's a pinky
kinda have to okay let's take a quick
look
why does it come up with like illegal
dangerous
[Music]
this rare cheese is infested with lime
nuggets
okay i'm done i'm i'm so [\h__\h] done
huh
thank you thank you sorry i you said
your name wrong
it's my birthday on august 7th oh that's
which day is that saturday
i'm glad to i got that before i turned
18.
oh a baby
you were baby sorry but you're a baby
i found you kiara thank you so much you
made me happy
i love you boss i love you too
[Music]
i'm sorry i won't be able to watch your
future streams if
i'll be attending class and i need to
study for my future
and you won't you won't come to my
streams at all
at all one of your female supporters
tanki
tell me you'll be coming sometimes
[Music]
that's so supportive does that mean yes
is that a yes
and baby is that yeah yes you'll come
sometimes i think it's a yes i'll take
it as a yes
yes okay why would you write that
like that in the first place it's
[\h__\h] scary don't tell me goodbye like
that
i don't like it i don't like it when you
guys
say goodbye to me
but good luck with your studies very
important of course that comes first of
course that's a priority
just just don't don't don't leave me
just think of me sometimes and happy
early birthday
do your best you can do it
it's good that you continue working on
your education
i respect that and i look up to that
[Music]
foreign
m
i sang this yesterday fully during the
super jet reading
so that was fun if you missed it watch
it because i
i have to stop myself from singing the
full song again
i love this version so much
[Music]
myself
thank you thank you
bell star now this is rowan hood doctors
and thanks to the pinky sticker
thank you that's cute is that a little
oh wait it's super small it looks like a
tiny chicken
but now that i look at it in big it's
not
thank you dog i appreciate it blackwind
thank you
for pinky hey boss this stream was great
and you never fail to make my day
brighter quick question when everyone
gets 3d models would you rather be
in the cat's whole live edition or lord
of the rings hello live editions
i would have to say uh lord of the rings
because i am a huge fan of one of the
rings and it's
def as much as i enjoyed cats a lot of
the rings are still a million times
better uh
so yeah who would be frodo who would be
sam
who would be pippin who would be m m
mare
what what was it mary mary mary mary
mary mary right mary
[Music]
good eyes frodo yeah i can see that i
can see that
[Music]
although i think i think our
personalities don't really fit
them at all anyway oh
[Music]
honestly uh i see why you gave good
alfredo
but personality-wise it doesn't fit at
all
[Music]
amis golem shut up hey
that's mean no callie would be kind of
oh
[Music]
okay if we're branching out out of the
hobbit then yes yes
i would give her gandalf or inna ina
could be kind of too yeah
yeah that's right
[Music]
kiana is kelly's legolas kiana is
strider
ina would be sour
yo shall not pass
well i [\h__\h] love kimberly i'm okay
with that but why would i be gimli i
don't understand
kiana is aragorn is the dark lord
i love these ideas okay we have to read
the super jets
thank you i'm kind of sad because i
can't send a super chat on my actual
birthday yeah cause i
i won't really be streaming hot but i
was thinking of having like a
like a chat room open yeah see you on
twitch don't get me live don't worry i
would continue supporting you attention
you're my one and only aussie
again taiki thank you i love you
skye dancing hope you can enjoy the
ttrpg
if not then uh archive is totally fine
by the way i have received notice that
we will start today's
uh ttrpg i think 30 minutes later
[Music]
i really enjoyed today's stream it got
me through the end of
moth paperweight with a smile on my face
keep smiling ah
you're welcome thank you
stream reservation i'm gonna uh open it
once i'm done here i'm done in two
minutes i promise thank you thank you
james mcphee
i hope we can do it again and i hope
you'll tune in again next time and good
luck with your paperwork i
i know end of the month is always
[\h__\h] tough for certain places certain
jobs
yeah annoying stuff
i know that stuff i wasn't really much
involved in it until now but it still is
annoying
um
thank you thank you oh looking forward
to seeing your panel of megacon orlando
you're coming yay thank you amazon
and kaku that's it guys i'm done
thank you everyone for the support i'll
do garlic phone again soon
uh afterwards we have today ttrpg and
tomorrow is zelda
let's go although i do have to do some
things tomorrow
um like important things to prepare for
uh germany travel so
there is a tiny i will try to have it on
time but there's a tiny possibility that
i will have to start maybe half an hour
later
or even one hour later but i'll try to
get everything done beforehand
for tomorrow but anyway i'll see you on
ttrpg next and enjoy when we say awful
ttrpg
[Music]
and
you