[Music]
ah
i have problems
[Music]
huh
my phone won't turn on
[Music]
hmm
do
[Music]
hello
sorry i'm a bit um late
i just
woke up
uh because
because of the main review i was awake
so long like until 7 00 am or so and
now i didn't sleep so much
and i couldn't prepare much i'm sorry
i'm like
tonight
[Music]
seven a.m yep yep yep um
i i don't know what my my thingy is not
charging properly um
it's kind of weird
um so maybe maybe if we wait a little
bit it will charge itself up
uh and then later on i can move
but
i don't know why
it's like normally
normally i charge it through not through
like us usb i charge it for the wall
if you know what i mean
uh
and uh that's not working somehow
but but that doesn't that that
in the usb it doesn't charge it fast
enough
so
i usually don't do that because it it
doesn't
it doesn't catch up with uh yeah the
usage
and
[Music]
uh
so wait i think starting uh from half
half past something
is when
something starts right uh
sorry i i have been busy i don't know
what's going on that well
um
yeah i have a charging problem
oh wait what once one second
yeah i don't know why it's not charging
anymore with the with the wall adapter
um
i think i'll
ah damn it
i'll have to
buy one
yuppie
because i have the tournament today
ah
all right all right um wait one second
uh loop
tony is high to call
let's see uh
holy
i just did the update so oh my god
oh my god it's so lag i don't
i
oh i was worried about that
is that gonna fix itself
oh
okay
you see this
are you seeing this
it's kind of laggy or are they really
moving like that
press f for the what f
oh you
everybody wanted me to show the thing
what
ah
oh this is awkward they're having fun
and stuff and
i am not moving and my game is uh
my game is really really laggy one
second let me oh my god
let me turn on here the audio
it's laggy takes people a lot of time to
eat food oh really is it everyone is
like don't worry
you're telling me that everyone
as everyone's stream is looking like
this
everyone
uh maybe maybe people should join the
server and girls
in groups like
10 people
maximum
oh
did we not think this through
i was worried because of my internet
connection that i was gonna have issues
uh one second let me put on some pcm
i thought this was gonna happen um
ah join voice chat yeah i guess so but
uh but i feel like i would be uh
gordon is not lagging
um
i i feel a bit awkward to join them now
uh
do you hear the bgm
that that's awkward
[Laughter]
well
say hello to my chickens are they still
here
i have a bed at least yeah they are why
does that chicken look so
dirty
that was just the light
ah
how is the how the fireworks gonna look
like with this leg
[Music]
are you gonna be lagging
i'm yes because i couldn't see i
couldn't see uh everyone in the chat i
wasn't sure if it was you or amazing
well of course it's me
you know
who wants to try out her kikiri key okay
did really well with my gut the other
day i'm going to put this back because i
want to back it up
oh wait now they can hear you oops sorry
guys i didn't see this
i'll go to the neighborhood
oh
gang's all here
oh wait can you hear them now
oh
hello
yeah it's laggy for me too it's cause
there's so many of you yeah okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah definitely
fireworks
[Music]
this place is amazing god i can't eat
food
so
much there's so much did you get one
flag
yeah i think so but i think i shot it
off immediately i thought it was a
firework i shot off the firework they
did
oh i still have it
what's everyone up to it's just fun to
watch everyone have fun
i hope you need it
i don't know i have to but it just takes
a million years oh thank you
oh yeah yeah yeah everyone's got these
like uh green and brown and yellow
spirals coming off of them and it makes
me feel like they smell
oh
makes you feel like what like everyone
smells really bad
oh
yeah i feel like everyone's real stinky
right now stinky
everybody's stinky
[Music]
oh can we have like a i want
actually no i don't want to touch
anything here
[Music]
then you get it through here especially
i only want to take things people give
to me
yeah i was gonna say everyone has a
yukata and i'm like what i wish i got
one but it's fine it's fine no time no
time to make one nice
i had someone
make
one i think even for each of us
but
it's kind of like a bed
it got like um
it
happy
minecraft music this is a happy occasion
we need to have fun i don't want this uh
happy holidays
what are you trying to sleep on
who is who's on me
what is that on me
what is this fire sound
face they want my bed
this is my bed
[Music]
oh the the ice race will be um
interesting
yeah i'm wondering how that's gonna go
i think i got kicked out of my bed
by
someone is this a sign
wait what do we do
ollie's on top of you oh wait i don't
have to sleep
oh are they playing with my
chickens
hey if you shoot the chest oh my gosh
but this will be really easy because
they're moving so slowly
yeah where are you yeah
i'm part of that
construction
i see
i thought i thought there was no way you
could have made this because you would
never possibly do this to your employees
but what what what do you mean this is
all like it doesn't hurt them
it does this right it doesn't they don't
die from it or like they don't take
damage it's all good it's all good and
they say they like it they they like it
they like it i know that they like it
that's for sure
i know that first person did you try
shooting them i don't i don't i see
people standing around but maybe it's
because
uh did is anything left in the box
huh
oh yeah like four snowballs
and other people
uh i guess have uh carry the rest
one
try your best
all right i'm gonna try my hand
i'm gonna hit the camera again please
here we go i guess the reaction of them
being hit will be like super delayed
oh this is wait this is way way way
yeah i threw the snowball and it took
like a half like a second and a half
gosh
oh very cool
this is awesome oh thank you i had a lot
of fun building that
yeah
nice job
i also
i partially was one of the people who
built this huge green thing in the back
how does this work it's supposed to be a
noodle slide but we built it under
extreme time pressure you're supposed to
go up first
in the water
and then at the top you're supposed to
be the noodle uh who
slides down
wow
thank you you can beat the noodle
yourself or you can take one of the
boats that is on top of the noodles line
i think it just looks good at
no
am i sparkly i'm bubbly
yeah you don't like that
noodles
oh you're stinky too now
you think it's a good scene
yeah please don't hit me
[Laughter]
i'm going in the back
i'm
going
i'm waiting for you down there
here i i'm trying there's just there's a
corner that's really hard to get i am
you might want to start a bit more in
the front
yeah there's a boat it's a boat
yeah on the noodle slide you can either
be the noodle yourself or you can go
down with a boat
on the noodle slide that's so cute
thank you thank you uh i i tried my best
building it in in five minutes oh no
oh no
i tried to get the boat i tried to get
the boat off and now there's a hole hang
on i'll put it back
yeah
okay
fine crisis averted you know what
something i'm just gonna
there's a boat up there anyone who wants
to take it
no i need to put it back every time i
try to hit the boat
um
it like makes me get inside of it
you have
your new outfit on that's cute oh yeah i
found it on twitter thank you
person's name that i didn't take note of
but i appreciate it
thank you artiste
yeah i got it i just need to change it
wait i'll come up to you i'll come
ah ah i got it oh thanks kiara kirsten
if we put it like
here
on it yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah right
there would be good oh did i get in
ladies
we're not destroying the slide
yeah
if i built that one that's
that's gonna hurt ouch
it's a bit easier to be than noodle
yourself
wait whoa
hello everybody whoa that's so fun but
how do i get out of the boat again
ladies oh this makes me nervous
does anybody have a helmet
you don't need a helmet believe in
yourself bring my own looks like you're
wearing one
ah
oh yeah my hat my hood no one yet
oh hello
and bye
all right and
hello everyone
what what toy senpai is swimming in the
air
we get a nice view of everything from up
here at the top of the noodle are you
are you coming down now
from the noodle yeah
oh noodles
on the slide
it's scared the good is scared no i'm
not
no i'm not kelly are you so slow
i'll go too
what
you want to tandem
yeah are you okay
is this the way we go
down down just down oh we still can't
see them but we can't draw okay
what is happening oh
oh she's flying
yeah
um especially
i'm just going to blame it on the lag
that that didn't work so well don't
don't blame it on my side my god
[Laughter]
by now
stand by no
thank you for using the bamboo
waterslide thank you very much
it was super fun
thank you i appreciate that
both work but i enjoyed it yeah
his boat is cursed it's moving on its
own
he'll help me eat it
i don't know
does she see herself like that as well
or is it only everyone else and one day
she's stuck
that was not helping no
that was not helping where is everyone
i didn't do it i didn't do it i didn't i
didn't do it
not me this time stuff
no no no not free stuff not free stuff
okay so there's some wings there that we
don't even have yet on on the answer
about girls when are we slaying the end
dragon huh
i think botan wants us to follow her oh
yeah there's something right
okay
i'm gonna end the dragon whenever i'm
ready
i'm ready yeah i'm down too
me too
soon tm
the tunnel of love
tunnel of love oh my gosh
oh
this one
oh wow it's pretty neat
[Applause]
ladies this is beautiful that's so cute
oh wow
oh is that wait is that the race because
it's already half uh
half past i'm cute but look at me too
who wants to get on the boat with me and
oh you can go together i want to get in
with you that sounds fun cause i don't
know how to ride the boat okay no
problem coming here let's let's do it
together yes that makes you and me
okay
all right you're the pilot
you're
here we go
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
that was fun
that was really cute pretty yeah
whoa whoa this is nice thank you this is
really nice this must have taken a while
yeah
very pretty
there's so many of us
oh you can go up with oh cause it floats
cool yeah that was cool
how do you get out of the boat
[Music]
oh
it should be okay
um
i might die
oh
yeah you've got those like smelly
spirals around you what's the i'm just
thinking how do you smell me oh yeah
because you didn't wash your hoodie
you need to wash your hoodie girl you
need to remember to do that spoopy
mm-hmm medical tent whoa
[Music]
there's no darkness
careful it might be zombies
come
okay both on senpai
where are we going
i don't know botox and fighters said
come on
maze oh then there's a dead beat here oh
she's a senpai look at the little
skeleton can i go free i'm
okay
[Music]
do i really want to go inside
okay
are they gonna are they gonna kill us
it might
okay okay we're gonna get out spooky
wait a minute oh wait this is one of the
horror houses
oh it's a horror house i'll go in i go
in
yeah open the box what's in the box
[Music]
oh
wait
okay okay
there's some spicy things written on
here
girl are you okay what happened girl
it's fine uh low health is full
yeah how you like that
oh scary oh
oh
[Music]
oh there's music playing
yeah i'm eating the berries you tried to
trick me with
everyone looks so funny
everyone's moving so funny
[Music]
what
what the hell did you feel here what do
i do here
eat more bread
wait is that chicken
doesn't look like a chicken what does
this mean i'm eating but my uh wait the
color is changing
yeah mine doesn't either
[Music]
everyone's trying so hard to eat but we
can't we can't fill our stomachs this
is hardcore
it's hardcore mode
[Music]
oh my god
is it because we killed them where's
chiara i'm i'm in the horror house uh
with mikko senpai and she built it
very very spoopy there's like even super
spooky music in here like with the
music blocks
eyes
nice
where's the ice race gonna be at once
okay i'm coming i'm coming
cd
i'm cute bunny ears
hop you
whoa i put on knives what
i didn't have oh
[Music]
rocket fire
it's not ice cream it's graves of their
elytras
[Music]
oh
wait how many one two three
four electro grapes no wait there's more
but they didn't write anything
it's gonna follow everyone
another survive oh my god identical to
the picture i have meat skin my map has
led me to you
[Music]
she was just waiting for me here
should i sleep here too
[Music]
oh
wait what hat what's happening
how do we race on the ice race i need a
bunny with a boat yeah i have a bullet
nice
oh i get in your boat get up how do i
leave yeah i don't want to tandem
okay it's so dark so when that race
should we sweet
[Music]
i'm just going to hop in the back of
someone's boat
what is she doing all right we got three
at a time
psychopath
huh oh this is madness
it is
where are you
hello everybody
whoa hey ollie can i get your boat
oh i'm probably fine susie senpai is i
don't know if she's trying to guide me
to death or if she's trying to help me
but um
she looks very scary
get in the boat get up getting in the
boat watson
you cannot hide it says oh yeah oh yeah
let's go death team let's go
ye
[Music]
oh gosh oh ollie what have we done how
do we
how are we going to time this for the
two to one girl oh no
oh no oh no where are you guys going oh
okay oh we were still
no i want to get out of the boat
there are a lot of people here let me
out
i want to be free there we go
wait are we missing the actions
i think they're trying to get in the
boat or deciding who's going in the boat
oh okay what the hell is that
i should probably set my spawn point
because i'm gonna always be swatching
first i'm gonna die
i don't think we can die here yeah
there's people doing them
oh cool
i'm so cursed i guess but that's okay
okay i can hit somebody in the
spectator's
i'm still going to want to watch i'm
going to watch
but it's so dark i can't tell good luck
ollie huh
they have up there left oh
okay i think i made it outside oh yes
that was that was how to get outside
thank god
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh my
gosh backwards go forward
let me write oh whoa whoa
huh
oh my god
wait they're doing the boat race already
[Music]
that's fine
all the way okay
fall down eof efficiency and watermelon
i was just okay we're good we're going
to one of the don't bring me there
[Music]
though
i fall down
[Music]
that's also spooky
ladies and gentlemen joining us today
for the ice race we have deadbeats kfp
employees
[Applause]
like the race is already over
in the blink of an eye
i see some names let's go there
luna's house okay
stop eating just oh there we go oh
is this the starting line this way this
way
that's so fun what am i missing is the
ice race still
ah yeah finished i don't know
i wanna go too
i bet i bet you guys could do a round
two
yeah i think coco and ollie won
i got sabotaged by lag
i mean let's be real it's uh it's pretty
intense but still very fun can i just go
on my own
the
the leader
i've already steered the boat so if you
want to do it you can do it
okay okay okay
second ollie is
we gotta be careful
i don't know about you watson but i
think that uh the chances of them
falling down are pretty high
[Music]
in the boat oh
well thank you for i'm sorry please rate
my uber uh on the app with five stars
and give me a little tip thank you
yes
they're actually doing it
this place is amazing it's like
a theme park
yeah yeah endless stuff to do and so
many people to interact with hey it's so
cool
and i work really hard here
oh
inaudible
oh yeah she's on the call with uh lamy i
guess
i think so she has a date with her tell
me something wow
what a chat
oh yeah
oh never mind send it to my angel
hello my beautiful angel
[Laughter]
oh
i wonder if you can order starbucks at
10 p.m
[Music]
yeah everything's fine guys sorry i was
just looking for my
phone so i could order some starbucks at
10 p.m oh it's a coffee or like a cake
pop oh coffee it has to be i have i have
a tournament i have to get up to
practice for it 2 a.m and then it starts
at 4am
oh my goodness good luck with the
tournament
good luck to good luck to you as well
kusatori
i know you've been practicing
of course of course
let's see what happens
what whoa
what what i do
why'd you growl at me what happened
can you cook the wings like you knocked
me off i thought you knocked me out
thanks guys no i didn't i'll get four
hours of sleep
that's just enough
oh and did that go well
you know
per day instead of sleeping for eight
hours at one time if you just sleep four
hours twice a day it's almost just as
effective
what
yeah it's a true fact if we put them
together as a human species
put them together
for four hours i see
you can sleep
you sleep in between every stream
yeah that's what i do i've been taking
more naps as well
yeah that's nice
thank you
just gotta give him your brains
oh oh it's supposed to be a car
like
[Music]
yeah
i want to push somebody off but i feel
like that's um
that's so cool
that's so smart
you
all right
what do you mean it's for my own good
yeah what do you call it in english
amaze it's gold
last month
here it must be here here and then it
must be here
and then oh
and then it must be here and then right
here
[Music]
i'm in the glass maze if you can help me
get out i'll give you one cookie
oh i see you anywhere
i go right
all right
like um
whoa whoa
[Music]
having social difficulties
making friends and
acquaintances or prefers to stay uh by
themselves
oh stay in their own lane yeah oh
and the other way around would be yokya
yeah like if you're really good with
making friends and conversations with
people then you're yolkya so which one
are you in
india oh i tried me
both
yeah both at different times
yeah exactly nancy was stuck
yeah because she's an egg
yeah
yeah we needed you to do that because
amelia not amelia ian isn't here
this way
can't believe eating nothing doesn't
eating things doesn't do anything in
this world oh there's a bank
a bank whoa poke a bank they take out
some money yeah take out the line
i don't the reaper doesn't have to stay
in line let me take this money out yeah
okay girl
that's your first dude all right finally
how do you get in here do you
sorry that it was not here afterwards
i think we're wrong
this is the stand up i guess this is
what we get for trying to rob the bank
i think i just went wrong in the very
beginning
this is happening
oh sorry easy
[Music]
gather everyone
maybe is it that sounds like it
lunch time oh no
this is difficult hey what if we're
stuck in the maze
yeah you'll be stuck forever i've been
stuck here for a while
no
if you die in the game you die for real
you can't
he's a big brain
let's go horror house yay
hey get to the back forever you want to
be late to the event
hey guys
oh yeah in 10 minutes
the fight we can see the fireworks from
the cheating wait is that the fireworks
yeah
what am i doing
[Music]
wait what kind of contest i want to join
that one
oh
they would like us to join with voice
chat if we want to participate
so i guess on a big server
they're stuck again okay
i'm stuck in the i need assistance
yeah oh wait
[Music]
we made it
oh
[Music]
seven minutes easy
hey
that was really spooky
oh my gosh ah
how do i get out of here
richard senpai do you know the way
very
[Music]
oh maybe this is the way out i want to
join the team
the horror house is really busy right
now miko senpai says don't join anymore
oh
subaru senpai are you okay
huh where did my foot go
did i not pick it up properly even
though i thought i did
oh it's something
is that food
i'm stuck in the maze i need help can
somebody guide me out of this i don't
want to be late
wait wait wait wait wait maybe
[Music]
uh
senpai
oh wait we're on to something now now
we're cooking here we go
crunch time the hell is jeff doing here
[Music]
where
did you make it out so happy for you go
gamers
still
i'm still here
someone let them out
they're rngb
here we freaking go all gamers we're
getting out of this one oh
oh
oh yeah
oh oh whoa whoa i'm sorry
totally crazy
she's following your steps i think so
hey guys whoa it's real crowded
nice
did watermelon rescue him
nicely wow there's a lot going on right
now
i want to leave oh no
oh
jeb oh when you
when you give a sheep to the name it
turns into rgb that's cool
all right yes
yes
where is everyone going now
you guys have a lot of i'm gonna follow
ali
yeah
leave the face
oh you say something everybody's here
nice
nice oh asked me to
oh are we gonna enjoy it uh
yeah i wanna join the sniping
room to join
[Music]
um
hello
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
okay
so
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
is oh
oh
[Music]
like a google translate
just walk back down
but it doesn't really matter you know
why
come on
no
[Music]
i heard that
oh my goodness
[Music]
of
oh
today
[Music]
is
panties
[Music]
there's no way that this is the right
path right
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
i love to embrace death
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
purple
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
did kelly not set any
safe spots with her bed
cali doco
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
okay i'm back
oh
foreign
[Music]
okay
yeah let's go
no no no it's cute
is
[Music]
everyone is supposed to take one bow and
one uh five arrows out of the chest
only five though oh i took two
okay
so
um
okay so as a team together we should try
to win because it says teams versus
teams okay okay let's go
today
[Music]
hmm
so apparently there's some kind of uh
function with like when you hit a
certain spot then there's some iron
falling down and then that will count
like whether or not you hit it like
sounds very complicated but it's working
somehow
okay okay
[Music]
oh
foreign
you're supposed to like when it's our
turn we get to shoot uh at the red uh
glass place two times and then three
times at the
white glass area ah
yeah okay
right
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um
minecraft master yeah
is
um
shooting
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
marble cake
no no no no no
um
okay
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
fireworks
seems like they got some kind of update
or so in the server because the lag is
kind of gone
yeah
[Music]
oh it's so smooth
no no no no
no no no no no no no no um
is
foreign
danger zone
oh
[Music]
nice job
nice is she in here
in the other group
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice
nice nice nice
[Music]
foreign
oh
okay
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
she's still dizzy from dying
um
[Music]
okay
don't kill us some fun
please
[Music]
do it again
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
sorry i was trying to listen but my
brain was zooming out i cannot really
translate right now
oh
i need to adjust the volume of blue
shield and buy i think
um
[Music]
like the headphones and
me too
but
i'll unmute i want to listen
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
oh
you can do it
don't let your dreams be dreams
thank you
my
english
[Music]
and kanata ninety was asking for
having a fight so
it's all good they all like each other
they're they they're friends
[Music]
oh
thank you
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
you know
um
[Music]
videos
okay
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
so basically
you take four arrows one bow and then
you start off by uh shooting two in the
red area and then three in the white
area behind it and uh there will be like
well points pounded by some
super special
thing going on in the back with iron yep
that's it
okay
five yeah
don't try to shoot the same thing twice
try to get each one once
okay okay
i got confused
two in the front three in the back
okay
[Music]
all right okay
yes
kelly first
okay
[Music]
kelly tip you apparently you should
probably try to um aim a little bit
higher than the
thingy yes ma'am okay
no problem here we go
thank you thank you
[Music]
number two
yes
okay
[Music]
here we go
okay
[Music]
did you know you were so good did you
know you had this talent
no no i'm surprised there you go
wow thank you so much okay
okay last one
[Music]
next yeah
go go go we know you're good
all right
[Music]
winning team winning team
oh
she goes in for the third one she's
aiming concentrating and she goes
[Music]
oh
do you have an advice
uh
it's a little bit higher than you do oh
i'm not really too high but oh
do i do i aim outside of the box or
inside of the box yeah outside of the
phone okay thinking outside the box okay
um i don't i don't remember how to shoot
ah there we go
[Music]
go
oh
[Music]
ah
okay
uh
a bit higher
because i'm further away i guess should
be higher
just slightly slightly slightly higher
okay
imagine that you're a cupid and you're
shooting at kelly's house
hey kelly this is just helping me to win
don't you want that too
i mean yeah
hey it's all for the team kelly it's all
for yours
okay and the middle one
go
ahead oh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
last one
it's the ping it's the
[Music]
until now
foreign
is
[Music]
oh
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
she's like sorry be risque
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
oh
nice
oh my god
[Music]
it
oh
[Music]
um
oh
who's calling me
um
oh
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
is
cute
[Laughter]
myself
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oh
wow
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
let's go the pressure of being the last
oh
okay
the pressure was too big
[Applause]
let
oh my god who would have thought
oh
foreign
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
all right
don't worry you're in the team as well
in our heights
[Music]
is
i
[Music]
let's watch it together
yeah
[Music]
hi
hello
en team peaceful
shooting you though
nice i didn't know
was gonna up real bad but i got one
bullseye
you got a bullseye yeah one one one only
one
still though that's really good i was
very surprised
yeah good job good job
it was fun
i was surprised it was super fun it was
pretty chaotic too but in a good way
everyone was having such a good time
very chaotic my ears are very like wow
which team were you again
i was with
what was with oh team elite oh
yeah
well how many
uh points did they have together
yeah 146 i think oh
okay the the fireworks go up here in the
middle right
maybe
i think so probably yeah
probably
so 136 oh i see i see oh 136 oh my god
i guess we'll watch it from here
okay
oh ladies
ladies
i guess tina is still on a date so
nice that's okay
that's called that's called
in english and japanese
yeah someone who
who has a real life with like dates and
stuff
um
oh my god she's in a date
[Laughter]
enough
yeah i picked it up from the chat this
wasn't me don't blame me
it's a
did you do the haunted house oh yes i
did oh we're fine
fun but horrifying
yes
mikko senpai and sushi senpai very
horrifying indeed very very
i saw subaru senpai like on the ground
like laying down and i was very confused
ah did not move i thought she was dead
well
there's a special seat that google
senpai made where's that special thing
we have to pay for it
oh is it a thought
above the noodle slime the bamboo nose
sign hello hi amanda
i think it was like you guys probably
okay
no but we we were really good i think
yeah oh up here is really nice
yeah we've got some nice seats here i
don't know if that's the premium area
but it's pretty
i have to play like a super chat or like
can i just throw a rose here
you want me to super chat you said pie
i'll pay with potatoes i'll take potato
i got hormones
melons i want to be next to all you
ladies yeah
beautiful summer festival
yeah
oh it's time
so colorful they put so much work into
all these stalls and and and games and
stuff it's so cool they really did i
wasn't
i wasn't expecting so many oh then you
underestimate uh
uh
it's crazy but actually it was not only
usada constructions who participated
like we built a lot of things but
um for example vata senpai who is not
part of usada construction she builds
yeah i think like at least at least two
things maybe three things
oh wow yeah so much so anyone was
allowed to build things but it was just
mostly uh our project
oh
what if we could do something like this
in the end server yeah future future
generations and stuff like that to like
welcome themselves you definitely i
would be so much why don't we throw like
a carnival to like welcome
the future people yes yes a fair ground
like yeah carnal yeah we should do
something like that oh yeah we couldn't
we can do overseas version like not not
necessarily a japanese festival but like
our kind of version
yeah
yeah let's do it kelly
yeah the the moon is really pretty isn't
it
yes all right okay
cool
yeah i'm sorry
i picked up that line from the chat they
told me to ask you i don't know what
that would do
i don't even see a moon right now where
is the moon yeah i actually i i actually
don't see it
oh by the way we could do oktoberfest
oh yeah that's a fun idea
can we all get leader hoes and
the traditional german slash australian
wink uh
dress yes yes yes like milkmaids can we
all be milkmaids i guess it looks like
that yeah
yeah we can all carry a bunch and have a
bunch of cows but we milk you know the
thing with dandruff dresses is that
um they really
accentuate the
chest part
oh
what are we going to do about that
i'm growing watermelons all right
stuff some stuff in there
yeah melons
it'll be perfect
oh more people coming up here
hello
like new years
yeah
make a wish ladies or maybe we started
she's just waiting for a suicide but
okay
sweet
yeah we gotta make a wish though for for
what we want for the year oh
yeah it's i don't know any kind of dope
wish just like what we want to do
i don't know i feel like if there's
fireworks maybe that's a shooting star i
don't know i just want to make a wish
but we can't say
can we
no we can't or else it won't come true
okay
think of a wish everybody okay i got i
got one
i got one too
i got one
yeah
it's gotta be a secret you gotta keep it
a secret
totally because if we if we say it then
it won't come true right so yeah exactly
uh
so i guess in that case if there was
something we didn't want to happen we
couldn't think of it as a wish and then
say it out loud so it would never happen
how did you know that that was what i
was thinking about
so my so my wish is to never have fun
with you guys ever again oh come on
yeah oh no i said it oh no oh no
no it will never now it'll never come
true my wishes
i
i never
want to be married with kelly
oh come on you can't play that way
i just did i just didn't
you told us to make wishes and now if we
say it out loud it will never come true
so this was your word yeah you inspired
me i mean i mean yeah
a girl fireworks sure are romantic
aren't they good
how how how are you feeling uh good and
um
are you feeling some romantic tension oh
wait wait is that anything oh
oh that's sweet
oh here we go where is it
i can't see it potatoes yeah where are
they maybe it's like where is it
[Music]
oh my god
wow
happy summer everyone that's amazing
yeah
it's so great
wow
oh wow
[Music]
why did elena die now
does she want to go down yeah i want to
go down too
yeah
don't don't dump
okay
oh wow
so colorful
happy summer everyone
[Music]
so glad i'm here
wow wow there's a lot of violence
we're getting a super fun summer you
guys
yeah
[Music]
i'm watermelon
yeah maybe in some other way i don't
break my neck that would be nice
[Music]
it's so noisy
i can barely hear you guys
[Music]
don't be scared oh my god they look
really scared
aren't you getting so scared
it's okay babies
don't worry
mama's here
[Music]
don't worry don't worry don't worry
you're safe in here
what's your safe place
okay i calmed them down
oh michelle
they have a really good spot here to
look at the fireworks front pro
how long did this take to make all these
fireworks holy cow lots of tnt right
yeah
all right
[Music]
yes
ah
[Music]
that probably gives miko sent by some
flashbacks
hi
howdy
[Music]
do whatever you want with those eggs
thanks i appreciate it
i think people are
people are looking at us kelly this is
uh should we get somewhere private um
because why not no i'm cool right hey oh
you wanna dive in okay
huh wait no i just wanted to throw
something at you
thank you
happy
what the hell is that
nothing hurts
we have me for everyone
i love you guys
[Music]
wait this is going on so long holy
yeah they have a lot of fireworks huh
oh my gosh yes i want that too
yeah
oh but it's ending now the timing
oh no
ah
more more fireworks please should have
done it earlier
oh i still hear some boom booms
oops
how do you change camera view again is
it f5 uh it's f four and four four five
i think it's your back and then
one of them is back in one of them's run
i forget which one that one might be
back
cute
gathering somewhere on one side
okay
torches well they're they're building
fast
oh they're making like stairs so each
and everyone can stand on one like
oh cool
that's a good idea
good
idea how are we gonna
oh nevermind i'll just
watch
okay
how many people are on the server right
now
uh
it is uh
oh when you press tab you can see
everyone that's online
ah i don't see a numbered oh wow you see
it like wait when you try to sleep it
says uh yeah then there's uh 29 people
on the server right now oh wow wow
what did i just hear an enderman
oh okay she said stand wherever you want
to stand so maybe ian can try to stand
together yeah
okay okay i'm still standing with you
guys okay we're on the lower part maybe
ina can
figure it out what we're trying to do
yes i think she figured it out
oh cute together
i want to scroll out more to get a
better picture you're right
[Music]
do our best oh my god um i guess we need
maybe
maybe a cameraman but then there's one
person missing so to shop them in
wow
[Music]
peace
wow
i don't really have a good angle because
i'm at the very corner i hope you guys
uh maybe gouda or amir are getting a
good picture because they're in the
middle
good one nice
yay i get one too by the way do we have
the update on our server already
probably not right
it might work on like new chunks but
we've generated a lot of chunks
[Music]
oh my god
m
yeah
i think we got it i think we got it yeah
i got a pretty good one
from
that was amazing
oh
[Music]
now we fight to the death rate
now we all have to slay each other oh no
no
whoever's left
is the winner
well
you and me are uh having a fight anyway
tonight is that not enough for you
oh yeah actually speaking of which i
gotta go because i have to sleep for two
hours
i think i gotta go
um i'm gonna talk to my people for a
moment though thanks girls
and thank you see you
next time we do a collab which my guess
might be my birthday if there's nothing
before that it seems so
yes you looking forward to it i'll i'll
tell you guys what we well what we will
be doing sometime soon
okay
[Music]
okay guys
okay uh see once again uh
i was not really able to talk to you
guys but i'm gonna make up for that on
monday i want to do like i am back for
my vacation stream on monday tomorrow um
but next up is the tournament just let
letting you guys know in case it were
not updated tonight in a few hours on
the shadowverse
uh
official youtube channel
um i will be participating with kelly
and some other people in a shadowverse
tournament i've been practicing even on
my vacation with my coach several times
and before that of course as well uh
it's gonna be interesting
and i practiced a lot as much as i could
in in the time that i had so i would
appreciate it if you guys would come to
support because we're not streaming it
on our channels it will only be on the
shadowverse channel
um
and um
i don't know i will try my best to fix
the the camera thing um
something's wrong i guess with the
charging
and
maybe and it's
sunday and that is a problem
because on sunday in australia wink i
can't wink right now wait for me guys
wait for me
and why are they fighting
they're doing a yeah death match
and what was i saying
uh oh yeah sunday uh shops not really
open um i don't know what's wrong
because it charges when i have it
connected to the
pc
through my belkin adapter
um
but it doesn't charge much it doesn't
charge enough it doesn't keep up i i
told you that um
but
it doesn't charge anymore when i put it
on for the plug in the wall
so
i guess i need to get a new
evil
i don't actually i'm connecting it with
a with a european plug adapter thingy so
i don't know it's evil the the charger
the the
the one i got in japan
because it's a japanese charger it's
either that or it's the
the adapter
maybe i can buy uh for the iphone i can
buy a
a whole new charging thingy together oh
do you know what i'm trying to say i
can't speak anymore
uh
english not very good though
yeah adapter may be broken
um
yeah no i'm not gonna get a wireless
charger because
it has to be on wire
to improve the
functionality and the
power of it
also because with the belkin adapter i
also have it attached to effort to an
ethernet cable which is necessary to uh
make it work somehow with this shitty
european internet thank you europe for
the shitty internet
um yeah it sounds like the adapter is a
problem
oh gosh um really hot also yeah so
tomorrow when i'm doing the the
stream uh the welcome back stream we can
talk about my vacation we can talk about
my neck
because we didn't get to really talk
much about that yet
yeah uh for now i'm like
loki fine i i have
been
prescribed
seven uh pain medications per day
seven
[Laughter]
and i got myself some
uh
warming thingies
that warm my neck
um
yeah i'm okay right now i just also need
to
eat something proper and practice a
little bit more before the tournament
but i feel like i'm ready as as ready as
i can be
actually my first match is against
giggle
and
uh
the deck that giglock plays
i've been practicing against it many
times with my coach and
it seems like
it's really just luck like even with my
coach who knows what she's doing
uh
i've been having a hard time
winning it really is just look the deck
is really really
um
yeah my deck is not very good against
his deck
and then against kelly's deck i
practiced uh
a lot of times and one each time
so
i'm
i'm i'm confident against her deck
but who knows what will happen and
there's also this take two match as well
that i'm playing against faye and in the
take two
you have to quickly make what kiara
what
huh
hi
should i do you want me to leave
[Music]
who's that guy wants to take a photo oh
oh oh oh oh
where are they
i see some people here but
what
down the slim street ah
let me try to find them
ah i see them
okay okay good that i didn't log out yet
i wasn't in the last osakan photo either
because that was an holiday
i'm here
we wanted to take a picture
is this really what's happening
there's only osto
there's some people missing
oh yeah
apparently they're going to take it in a
little bit so gotta wait here
we're gonna do it here
with this background all right
so yeah uh
uh oh she's playing stream there
uh yeah where what was i talking about
oh yeah the decks and the take two
thingy like you make a deck at the spot
with random cards that's being offered
to you
and
and it usually ends up being a mess
and you can't really
tell
yeah who's gonna win because
it's it's very unpredicted
very unpredictable to take two thingy
so i'm playing that one against faye
uh
and uh
yeah i i i don't have any hopes for that
one
the
a draft i guess that's what you call it
maybe ah and
i think that one our coaches will be
helping us as well but not every turn
they're not allowed to
um talk to us every turn
um
it depends uh
on on the match like for the take too
much there's a bit different roles
yeah yeah i we will do our best
no no no the coaches are allowed in the
middle of the game but only during
certain turns
um like for for the normal matches i
think it's uh every second turn like
from the start the first turn and from
then on every second every other turn
and then in the take two
it was a bit different but similar
that's gonna be a mess potato is gonna
be a big mess
should i go
up to piccolo
there's still some people here
who are not part of us
oh come on
a cat
hi cat i can't let me get out of here
can i
i don't want to break anything
[Music]
how do i
i'm not dead
maybe maybe like that
wait for me please
i'm coming
m
i want to go up oh i can i go up here no
[Music]
wait let me go up here hi enderman
poor in the man got stuck there
hello
cute you for example i bought them is
empire
i can eat food normally no
no it's still kind of laggy wait i'm
coming up my bed
i'm just trying to go faster
nice i got up
[Music]
is this are we complete
it's really difficult to position
yourself when it's mirrored
oh
my sister is next to me
cute
cute cute we look so much like one
another
okay orange one orange at each side
i like the balance of that
[Music]
on a date
don't fall down now oh we're all looking
so cute why is he in the back come up
the simple come to the side
okay she told her to come to the front
okay
all right
cute
[Music]
ah
it's taking the photos
foreign
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
okay i told them that ian wants to
do some kind of festival as well at some
point
so that that time we will invite them
over to our place
yeah but it will be
um some kind of different festival i
thought the oktoberfest idea was really
nice uh but to be honest even though i
i am of the german speaking countries i
actually uh
never have been to oktoberfest it it was
always happening around me but i never
felt interested in going because i don't
drink alcohol you know me
and
but
isn't there this thing about oktoberfest
that it actually doesn't happen in
october
when was it again november or wait was
it actually in october but i thought
there was some kind of
weird thing about it that it's called
oktoberfest but it doesn't happen in
october wasn't it like august october
august maybe i feel like it it's
definitely summertime
but that i think that sounds great we
can do a lot of the things and later oh
yeah okay that makes sense then what
actually it does make sense why is it
cold not
september fest i guess that sounds a bit
weird but maybe only because we're used
to saying oktoberfest
oh
well that sounds great
yeah i think we can do a lot of things
with uh oktoberfest
yes yes yes yes yes
and and as the only german speaking
person i will do my best to
even though i have never been to an
october fest before i will do my best to
make it as real as possible
i will go you know what i will go to do
some researching i will go to
oktoberfest tacoma kiana will
participate in oktoberfest
to do some researching
[Music]
i should i should probably leave now
i'm going to try to organize a new
charger maybe
hopefully i'll find something
oh
uh well thank you guys for watching i'll
see you guys later in the tournament and
then on monday for the
it will be a chit chat stream and also
yeah i gotta put out a schedule
and i will do my best to put that out um
probably
tomorrow
to be honest today too busy can't think
about it yeah
oh wait yeah maybe there will be no
oktoberfest no but honestly it might
happen there might be oktoberfest
because there's also like other events
already happening
it's going pretty well in australia wink
wink wink link
in germany as well i think i don't i
don't know much about how well it's
going in germany but i listen and
no actually no i do know
yeah because there's also like
conventions happening again
i think there's a good chance especially
especially because oktoberfest is
generally like outside
um
well we will see
what do you mean they already canceled
isn't it
it's not like there's only one
oktoberfest
yes
okay well then again that's even more
reason to make it happen in minecraft
and that's actually
enough time right now september is like
perfect to do it because that will also
be um
anniversary month
one year anniversary month
the official ones castle well then there
you go maybe there's some small
ones canceled in germany ah
i see well it's not cancelled in
minecraft
i have made it my personal goal to make
it come true
i'll make it happen trust me
september looking packed yeah that is
that's true kind of um
i guess um
oh yeah we could connect the two servers
into they can all come with their
japanese accounts they don't have to
make a new account
i think by then we'll definitely be
connected because we first uh want to
slay the dragon and then we'll connect
the service
okay guys
as much as i would love to talk more to
you guys
i gotta do some things so i'll see you
all
uh
later and tomorrow
okay
[Music]
that's
ah i hope you guys enjoyed the reddit
meme review as well by the way i i uh
it started for me at 3am and it ended
for me at like half past
five
and uh
obviously i can't i was so excited i
couldn't sleep right away
so
oh i was up way too long
but we'll talk more about it tomorrow
okay
then
i see you and in german we say auf
wiedersehen
sorry for not being able to move i'll
try my best to fix it i have to fix it
until the tournament
bye bye
[Music]
do
you