[Music]
e e
yay
wow be
hello
hello we
here so
here I'm I'm so sure like every time I
like Swit like switch around my camera
around this creeper head I get like a
small
heart hello do we want to do a little uh
sound check by introducing I just want
to check the volume from
everybody okay uh let's start with
Callie
hello hi check1 two my game isn't
showing up hi it's your boy what's going
on everybody whole English Cy myy Reaper
D singer I do a bunch of things hey
everyone how are you it's 7 a.m. here hi
I yeah she's the only one with 2.0 here
moris in
2.0 wow you're right actually hold on a
sec I am she's too advanced for us oh no
oh man the tech the tech is
unprecedented except when I'm in OBS all
right here we go I got it I fixed it we
good what what you fixed oh the the
screen yeah it's just obsp and silly
what's this iron did you do the iron
farm did you make it wait yeah wait wait
wait I want to to explore don't explore
too
much say something uh hello this is
small piloting Amilia Watson hello oh no
it's small
a what's wrong with I'm here to Ender
Dragon these
that's
that's yeah nice and the dragging on
those the fight better not drag
on
yeah say
something today we're spanking the End
Dragon spank spank spank with Lun L Chun
yeah the shoe of Doom
what's L
cha I don't know what the it's a it's a
chew it's it's a sandal it means sandal
oh okay yeah let's go sandal Spanish
right yeah yeah it's like a Spanish meme
kind of but also reality oh it's is it
like the Australian
thongs yeah yeah is
it oh it's like it's like a thread it's
like oh I'm going to get the Chan like
I'm going to beat you with it no not the
CH the
CH o
sounds
I okay Anda say something hello this
is
English okay beautiful I think it's all
relatively balanced I think so as all
thing should be if it's not the case
chat please complain feel free to
complain
me now before y'all I mean y'all are
already running around I got to give you
a tour of some new things for the ones
who haven't been playing that much
recently I mean I also stopped playing
for a while but
um uh mmm has been working just saying
M she works so hard on fixing it after
Rage Quit
okay yeah which is understandable
considering
everything consider o
it has it's cuz I I followed like a
video tutorial but in the video tutorial
they did it like a one block lower I
think so I had to raise the platform so
when you stood here you were too tall
but now I kind of fixed
it
way it's okay I won't blow it up if I
scoot all the way wait I'm coming I want
to see wow you can actually really get
attested it you can get all the way in
it doesn't exp
lood don't jinx
it don't jinx it you know what you guys
know what happens when all five myth
member GA something goes we don't have
to we don't we don't have to put it to
test you know it's working if you just
stand back a little bit it's good oh but
I think we might actually have to use
this for enchanting purposes enchanting
um feel free to get your levels up
afterwards wait sure sounds good you're
wearing your outfit in
Minecraft oh
aerobics yeah I like the shiny details
erotic aerobics thank
you I'm wearing the same outfit too I
did I just realized I didn't realize I
was using this K you're matching
[Music]
yeah okay follow follow follow
follow instructor what do we what do you
see this you're slapping their cheeks
right now he got to come see the he's
practicing for the the the real deal the
energy this pink house uh it used to be
prettier and it used to stand next to
the pandas but I had to move it in order
to also try to get the iron farm to work
so I moved it all over here and I had a
lot of villagers with a lot of jobs in
here but walk in walk in the children
are going to leave probably that's okay
e children like that let him run there
used to be more jobs and more people but
when I lost in today everything every
single villager despawned for no reason
and I had to start from
scratch back to another
villager wait how' you wait you had to
start from scratch well the way I did it
well I had some problems with the with
the iron farm too I fixed it like a
million times in the past few days there
was always something wrong with it and
um sometimes the villagers escaped or
died the zombie escaped or died or gol
killed the zombie or so so one of the
escaped villagers I was able to bring
them over here and then I had one spawn
out of the one block and then I make
have them make babies again so thank God
that was good
happyer yeah
you but they're not I mean I I had a one
time I had a one villager with a mending
book unfortunately he's gone no
I I did out of that I made one mending
uh pickaxe and one mending sword so
those can be used for XP farming if need
be the sword nice especially but yeah
we're in the last day so all of this is
not so
important um but one could still get
armor from one of the guys one has a
full diamond armor set oh
ni um and then there's fish in the water
now in the palm
oh fishing big Improvement and no
dolphin I'm joking dolphins are dead I
never kill them secret we
massage fair and square I don't know if
did everybody already see the
Improvement on the one block spawning
thingy the chocolate bars flower on top
of it oh yeah child H yeah what are the
improvements the water fault from
running away from home teach him a
lesson there's here s disobey your
parents okay well we can walk up here
and I'll show you cie and me started
building this iron farm it was a lot of
stupid work because we had to find a
really old version iron farm and we
built the wrong
one and really good you had to do um it
didn't work for the longest time can see
inside I
ah she my hand take
me it worked before because okay I put
rails down because only with the zombie
sitting in the boat it just didn't work
um it needed a certain amount of
millisecs of ticking the
villagers uh to spawn a Golem and so
with the mine cart going back and forth
back and forth chiny block it makes so
that they don't see it too often and not
too little but it's despawned even
though I gave him a name tag so [\h__\h] him
wow that's God what a shame yeah I also
the zombie several times ah I got like b
a bunch of iron out of it but you're
already out of
again why are they despawning why are
things despawning thank you is it the
server old version it's very funny the
server is very buggy it's a lot of
things happening well I will say Kiara
thank you for trying trying your best
and it was fun working on this with you
it has been EAS but Kelly it worked for
quite a while after I added some more to
it and I got a lot of iron out of it so
useful that's good hopefully the iron is
put to good
use oh please come back
up okay hold
on I'm a stu on Trails I just wonder all
right I've got happen that's pretty fun
where the
exit let me put the block
[Music]
back can you put the anyone wants to
drown you just hop in here and end it
all thank you try
me can't drown me I have
gills hey you can't drown there it's
safe safe for even sharks safe for
drowning yeah I don't think is safe safe
for not drowning it oh
okay uh oh yeah and I don't know uh I am
behind so basically check it out at the
nether portal first
chest I think we got like two more
totems or so oh we have like 14 more
golden carrots in the other chest
andest right next to it we have
five everything except for the helmet I
I didn't have enough diamonds and
emeralds anymore for another helmet the
best player should keep the iron
one everybody please take something uh
of one of each you can take something
unenchanted and with the unenchanted one
you could go to the enchanting table
first you might need to get some
levels wait do we take now I take now
yeah take now take now just don't lose
it don't L don't
die and the only other problem is
there's not enough diamonds there
weren't enough diamonds for diamond
swords I only have one diamond sword
that has mending which you could use for
XP farming for
now and uh the infinity bows were lost
in the past streams too due to
unfortunate things happening like circum
glitching we we all give five golden
apples and that was your boy did
that yeah you're welcome I'm the Apple
man I think we'll be fine even with no
diamond swords we'll have to make iron
swords perhaps and there is there's one
bow that is fancy some bows bow oh yeah
but we can the other bows yeah let's the
other I want a
bow uh take one there's one no non-
enchanted bow uh actually two I think
they're not Wow Bow
W yeah take it take it and see what you
can get out of it uh if you want the the
ex
uh the The Mending sword for exp farming
uh I'll put it into the middle shulka
chest that's how about feather falling
can I enchant my boots with feather
falling I think the boots most of them
already had it but if you don't have it
on then yeah if you have a feather
falling book please take it take there
is a feather falling book by the way
someone want nice one it wo the
wo just show that it rhymes
I'm going take this and enchant it
unfortunately if you want to use one of
the books we currently don't have an
anvil and I don't know if I have enough
iron for an anvil don't we need that oh
does it work in the in the enchanting
table too I never did it like that
before only Enchanted without a
book you put the book in there
book can we make iron sword we need the
I thought we had
one the an is broken they break
eventually so yeah we need we need one
to
combine let me
see we start
digging are we going to
dig one block uh block I know this is
painful you just got to sit through it
uh I'll try them now we won't be able we
need more iron if we want to make I
didn't get cob I think we need
it pickax we need 30 iron right 30 wait
wait I have two blocks of iron now we
need one more block and I have another
seven of
iron one
more right now
too I'm going to make
us bars so basically my diamond and
finish our
equipment hey kind of egg that's cool
they like eggs that would have been nice
earlier yeah I know that villagers are
reptiles yeah they're not humans or I
have an important question I thought of
earlier does anybody have experience
with
reptiles I had a few lizards before do
they smell like do snakes yeah they do
they they have a very specific like like
lizard pea smell kind of O lizard musky
so do ferrets actually like different
animals kind of have like I don't know
if you smell horses before stuff like
they all have different smells M stinky
yeah smell no I want no it's okay you
don't have
to thank you sharks are not reptiles
right that means that I don't have
okay do sharks have a smell other
thanish probably just
fishy musky oh
that's IR pickax or
Pi okay I I I mind it with okay diamond
pickaxe oh I'm picking up the blocks
organiz what are we quit
organizing yeah I'm just putting stuff
into random chest
now no don't destroy the
organization organ it's over isn't Smite
the silver man uh
sword yeah I think it's pretty decent
I'll put
don't we need a bunch of blocks like to
make a bridge across the end okay so we
have nine
iron would
be I mean yeah we we we'll definitely
need some blocks are we going to do the
bed Tech
tactic did we try that the first time we
killed him we does anybody when you jump
on it work happens what is it I don't
know if you if you use a bed in the in
the end it explodes right so you kind of
NE but you can jump on it it's also in
the yeah it knocked out a large amount
of Heth I remember it did that too oh it
actually made a decent difference so we
have one person who's like the sacrifice
and then they no if you block like like
hide behind some of the Rocks you don't
take that much
down okay the
Expos somebody has to be the tank I
changed the difficulty for today's uh
caruse from easy to normal cuz we were
on easy the whole time we've been on
baby moon yeah but it wasn't so baby we
died quite often and you know had our
own issues a we're never going to hear
the end of it now does not make me feel
better love some
music yeah oh beautiful what are we
listening to everybody
what's it called I didn't see it I just
put it in it's nice I think it's said
blocks or
something oh no all right Party
Time get my
oh go get it go oh nice need sword
[Music]
it's a good working
song yeah Mining and working song maybe
because of difficulty change no they
despawned before I changed the
difficulty I checked they were just
gone Riptide Bane of Arthropods wow how
helpful the Bane of
Arthropods kill the
spiders
yeah of iron ore we can make three
potions of slow
falling cuz we have a a single Phantom
membrane maybe I I'll work on that I'll
cook this iron cook up some potions
again wait do you know where the where
the thing is I put it some I saw it on
the on the in the Box okay okay okay let
her cook let her cook
we I'm cooking
need
coal this was actually the first time
that uh I ever was at least involved in
building like a functional Farm like the
iron farm in my whole Minecraft history
in these past four years I've always
avoided making Farms is that kind of fun
how do you feel oh no sorry Fun's the
right word but pretty
fun accomplished like you feel
accomplishment right when you finish it
you're just like yeah yeah and a lot of
frustration when it just doesn't work
and when things glitch around in this
old version of
Minecraft we got three more
emeralds Diamond a block of diamond oh
let's
go block of diamond mhm a block that's
good yeah that's really good that's a
lot of diamond
the last diamond helmet that we were
missing if someone
want
[Music]
diamond sugarcan farm my
mom that was my
M oh it's
slime that's a Mee D he's spicy yeah oh
kill yeah beat him
up beat him up beat him up beat him up
[Music]
did you have a nice nice birthday I
did I slept so much after my birthday
stream a good I Ked yeah a big stream
yeah feels good mhm yeah it does MH love
having a big
Eep oh that sounds so nice right now h
no it's. I'm fine I'm fine I'm
caffeinated right now I need somebody to
put me on a leash and run me like a like
a dog on a treadmill or something did
you guys see uh the myth uh Ramen
collaboration was announced a few hour
saw Dy let go get some Ramen in LA and
in New Jersey this summer you can geted
Ramen
Jersy Jersey I'm so sorry there's a
Ramen there in
there sorry my chat I have not retweeted
it yet I just woke up sorry they
got and everybody's got like one
item GA has like
a I think oh I'm slurping here
in here Callie has a chocolate cake
dessert it looks yummy what's mine
what's
mine is a a mushroom Ramen I think yummy
with lots of mushrooms on it it looks
really good I have an orange
soda orang
sod which is I mean you know there need
to be some nice uh basic Refreshments uh
what's mine what's mine what what do I
get something
you I already said you have the Boba
team oh okay iy
pearls the
pearls pears Watson's egg
what I like the idea of it being her
pearls feather yeah like she's the
detective that found not's eggs just
like villagers oh no oh no the Lord
eggs that's why there's so many of them
so if you don't fairly chew them you
have the risk of a small Aly hatching in
your stomach is that what the alien
movie upcoming is about it's about the
oh no going a direction I think is uh I
support that
idea that's exactly what I want to
happen oh my goodness my inventory just
exploded with
things uh-oh
where
go you too can have a small a inside of
you no thanks drink the BBA I'm
fine oh I think it disappeared probably
on the ground life's all about new
experiences
right
exactly and if you say
so come back oh he came back oh oh
creature oh my God he's oh creature
careful now
hey hey why are you going me in
particular funny
Target he's dead definitely did not help
in that battle it was killed by a sword
that I named the after myth instead of
the aftermath the
after what happens after myth oh what
does happen after my
yeah does the world just
explode gobbled into a black
hole Goble
gobble I just the name after myth on the
sword looks really aesthetic I have to
after dinner myth can you imagine debut
not saying Kitt but saying gobble gobble
instead can you imagine I think that
would
be isn't that a turkey thing I feel like
she would have been called
okay what wait what oh I thought she was
as animal what what is she uh turkey
yeah exactly
no and they
go a pea foul a pea foul know why I
thought she was Turkey foul
tarnish sorry she's a turkey as much as
I am chicken really aren't they making a
new Phoenix Emoji it's already there if
only that existed for you in the chat
taking it just claim it what are they
going to do know I'm too attached to my
chicken emote at this point add it oh
that one's cool though it looks really
nice looks so
it use it born a little too little too
early yeah a bird ah oh so how how we
doing on the iron front we have 13
singular irons and two blocks ooh okay
about to be five more iron added onto
that o with with the 1 I can make
another block and then we
need a few more
singular uh we
need
wait wait that no we can make it we can
make Anvil let's go let's go Anvil time
now please choose your books and
enchantments wisely and keep in mind
that you don't have to use the books you
can also just throw the piece of
Enchantment into the enchantment H the
piece of armor into the enchantment
table wait if we by chance put looting
on The Mending sword will we get perhaps
more items from the
mmm perhaps m some iron from the zombies
what my sword already has uh some uh
other enchantments it's already full
oh I'm going to go farm some exp now is
piercing good for arrows or is that just
sword piercing piercing I wouldn't put
that on anything tph oh is it not that
good Smite what about Smite Smite is the
for sword I think
you could put someone could put
protection on their chest or
something oh it's for Undead I see
piercing three piercing three
respiration I'm trying to figure out
what would be good for a bow and arrow
cuz I feel like I'm going to end up
using a bow and arrow oh wa aim
correction do they have that aim
correction oh if only they win
a power wow too bad we don't have power
yeah power but the bow if you if you
don't have the right book just put the
bow um well you need some levels but I
can also maybe do it for you cuz I'm
it's okay I can get levels you can put
it on the enchanting table that's behind
the Diaries mhm the diar can I please
check can I put flame on the bow yeah
fire flame should only burn like enemy
mobs and like TNT and stuff oh okay TNT
I want you
too oh boy try it
out oh maybe not oh maybe I shouldn't be
here we might actually uh I might hurt
you because I have sweeping Edge when
we're next to each other might be a
little bit dangerous maybe that's why I
put thorns on
my on my
armor smart wait did we confirm we're
just using iron swords my
bad we too we only have one diamond
sword the one that I made I thought we
were using Stone swords anyone going to
take the W
bow you can you can use it the power of
you can use it I trust you I take the
strong sword you take the strong bow
okay wait what should I put on this
regular
bow wondering but power is
good you can get inity good but um
only we still have uh diamond blocks we
have two diamond blocks we have two then
you can make some more swords out of
that swords or
axe it's a cheaper to make
just make it's your
preference
preference you can only enchant it once
let me see sword is enchant another one
yeah sword is cheaper to
enchanting they're
enchanting I'm an
enchantress
wow good stuff in here good isn't
uh good level 30
wait why is there so many bookshelves
how do we make more books because I made
it so that they chat told me that if you
make more shelves then it will be
stronger free more books the
better a oh by the way if you're looking
for lapis L it's in the chest next to
the lais next to the enchanting table I
took all of it there was so much in
there you can't take all of it I take a
stag okay
I think this is kind of
Overkill yeah I wouldn't mind you know I
think I we
can I
want we we asked for an enchanting table
K built the
library the enchanted Library I couldn't
stop I couldn't stop anymore oh my God I
started and then I couldn't stop it was
funct I really got addicted man
wait so you wasted how many materials
building an extra and I was wondering
how much trouble you had building like
like a you know the usual enchanting
table we see like in a in our Minecraft
server was just like one layer of books
I just walk
over see three I thought I thought if I
make an enchanting table and it's not
like the full power then it would be an
embarrassment to myself so I should go
full or go nothing I thought you were
little books you have oh somebody in
chat says we can break the bookshelves
for more books if we're low on books no
no no you can just make more books we
have enough and there's cows for Lea
where's the leather I don't see it the
cows the cows and I think there's some
more books in one of the CH one of the
chests uh a few more books are there's
like a couple more in the enchanting
box yeah yeah oh wait both back here
wait take some enchant them go enchant
them have fun with my enting
table wait a minute their last leg so
it's like this one looks nice I'm going
to steal that one mom give me some hey
wait who's got mending anybody did I
miss that conversation just the sword
there's mending on my pickaxe and on my
uh sword oh I can give you the sword if
you want to farm some exp last
no no I don't want I want uh no I want
bending on this bow
well okay mending yeah I used to have a
villager with mending but he died he he
despawned I guess we can just get her
enchant books and then enchant yeah this
is trash never mind don't think about it
putting mending on there does it even
make sense when today is the last day
and this is like the last hour pretty
much
no we want power we want to get big and
strong we don't need mending we have a
collection of uh puppy
[Music]
somewhere I know that word in Spanish
papel oh there's a lot of paper
here
[Music]
yeah is that
French I don't
remember I making up
things chess says yes CH says
we we
we well guys I want to warn you we now
have a new member who speaks
French
not too much she will sense it and she
will come over and then um correct
us how
to I only care about people correcting
me if it's a language that I I kind of
know a little bit is it is it BL or
R
we
Mame you guys where's all the monsters
yeah I want to find someone's sucking
them all up wait I'm almost done I need
two more levels then I'm gone that's one
and half line of the DMV man it's like
we're lining off for like
something yeah L to sit on Santa's lap
something like that Santa M Santa
Santa hello dried it up you guys like
the M Santa or the mall Easter Bunny
more I'm partial to the m Easter Bunny
he looks more miserable actually maybe
it's cuz I can't tell cuz he wears a he
wears like a like a a a fursuit so you
actually can't make direct eye contact
unlike the mall Santa you can make
direct eye contact and I don't like that
yeah it makes me feel uncomfortable I
prefer the big fake Bunny man right yeah
go down one level one yeah go go down go
go down the mry go socially acceptable
they in the back no go over here the one
the one socially
acceptable Kelly can you move one to the
left me yeah oh that's too far that's
too
far yeah yeah yeah okay okay nice I took
a picture peeking peeking
for okay okay um what happen it's not
spawning
anymore spider there spawns a little bit
but oh yeah maybe there's a spider I
hear a spider up there somewhere should
I go up there I'll go up there is that
maintenance time the declogger oh no I
don't want to tou
yeah she's the if if we go to sleep if
we go to sleep everything will despawn
and
then yeah I don't want to touch it
CU you know what happened last time no
one could blame you amen no one could
blame you
yeah R sleep I have witnessed an I'm a
rage quit live when she fixed it for the
10th time that wasck I did that for your
content you ra the beds good switch the
beds because of experiments you are now
in the experiment you're part of it I
knew it cool I'm someone get hat I am
I'm observing your sleeping patterns
depending on who are you're sleeping
next to in myth who are you sleeping
more soundly oh sleep study yeah sleep
study currently I didn't consent to that
okay though you in the small
print of GA I didn't watch it but I it
says I keep on getting it recomend and
that's something about GAA being a test
subject what yeah why are you a test
subject I don't remember I'm going to
have to watch the
clip she was she was the one we're all
being tested constantly wait you have a
tin foil hat emote that's yes yes
because I always make conspiracy
theories and stuff hold on guys let's
put on our tin foil heads for a
second that's great
ITA drew that you think that's
encouraging cult-like Behavior yes time
may maybe should stop that I just need
one more enemy then I'm what do you mean
we're not a
cult not a okay does somebody want to
use the sword because okay um here don't
don't lose it I won't I mean unless it
blows up
again because it's me for some reason I
get the feeling that it might happen no
no no no don't say too close all right
no it's really safe you can like get
really CL I'm going to take that advice
and I hear a spider
again you know maybe while you guys are
doing that I'll just fish maybe we'll
get a nice bow out of it oh yeah can you
get bows from fishing yeah we have look
of the sea or something um yeah look of
the sea one kiss of the sea hey better
than nothing one of the uh things should
be enchanted one of the yeah it has look
of the fish or not lock of the fish lck
of the SE the fish the of the
fish I Enchanted to eat do you guys ever
think about if you threw a rock deep
into the ocean you would probably be the
the the last person to touch that rock
for a very very very long time a
interesting isn't that crazy never
thought about it that way that's crazy
shall we go rock uh throwing then Yeahs
like
let's do it ly aw well I can give you
like an equivalent take a block a one
block whatever it is go to the edge of
this of one of our platforms and just
throw it off okay yeah I have a stick if
you want to borrow that give me there
you go thank
you fine
Ste just thring the stick off you're
going to miss it Kiara you're missing
this content okay okay okay okay I'm
coming are you at the at the
mmm got name right I'm going to do it
she got to it she's going to the last
one to touch it I'm the last the last
person to touch this
stick
goodbye there it goes wow how do you
feel after thisal moment wait I don't
think I was the last one I threw it I
think it touched the bee the be's down
there oh wow you threw it right on the
bee I think so right there maybe it
caught it in its mouth or something like
a rose be on a stick maybe you helped
the Bee by throwing it a stick maybe
that's exactly what it needed I couldn't
throw my bone so I threw him my stick
sorry
be yeah the be that's all the way down
there yeah you
st yeah it's all the bees that Spawn
from the one block but didn't know where
to go so sad oh no so they just went to
hell instead okay to hell wow they went
to bee hell what a shame we should build
down there be for it like a be
life okay I'm going to enchant something
now wait Ena did you see my reply to
what you sent me
earlier I think so sent me a big fish
building and I
see oh I saw that oh infrastructure
[Music]
and there's literally like a big big
building that looked like you know a
shark and I was like a big fish need to
send that to K it's a building I think
like in India or something big fish it's
pretty cute building it
is hey man where's the paper do we have
any paper yes there should be paper
still
some PU
[Music]
where wait where's the paper which box
um found it okay I don't
eat if you need more there's also a
sugar canane
farm a lot of sugar
cane going to buy this what is this what
did I just
build maybe I don't need it I don't need
it I guess this is fine he hurt me but I
want to enchant one more
bow mean SP one
more I just bu what level are you going
for 30 I'm only
26 oh you can get there
yeah
Contin I got to Google what this thing
is in Minecraft oh I should also
[Music]
yeah slay children is that not how
I in in video
games I you get pumpkin
seeds we have a few in the seed box I
think you can uh Harvest pumpkin and
then put it like in the crafting area
and then I can get seeds
too I have okay that's good I thought
I'd make more pumpkins uh pie
do I
got I that while a little
more you know what we want have to
prepare golden
apples there yeah there's plenty and we
have some cool potions too and we have
we have we have freaking totem of
undying I think I think we'll win four
of them yeah he somebody didn't take
their diamond armor is it on purpose cuz
I don't want to lose it or did I make
too
many maybe you made an extra set no 's
wearing itell are you wearing it too I'm
wearing mine damn where where did that
come from I got a pee before we fight in
Minecraft ah though can I have this
Banner ominous
Banner do it do it I want
it I don't think it does anything in
this mode
Tech don't think so arrows
[Music]
arrows I'm
crafting pumpkin need an EMP space
yes one next to it one immediately next
to it is what I've
[Music]
learned that's right what do you mean
doesn't I don't
get need help no
G oh you can't use this one okay a
little more
guys where's all the paper did you take
it in my mouth she
ateer she ate her homework I'm going to
force her mouth open paper in the
shulker Box 61 in the shulker did you
read all our Diaries Kiara I have been
reading them at least from the ones who
wrote something oh I forgot about it oh
no
yeah I get a star you definitely get a
star you and Callie get a
[Music]
star you always start riding the moment
we talk
about like doing your homework last
minute before class starts yeah
literally while the teacher is
collecting the
homework
incredible who wants the tried it now
the day didn't even end yet oh do
anybody have any wool there should be
should be by the the sheep sheep
yeah huh 29 wool is in there yeah it's
near the farm here in the back on the
way to the iron farm on the way to the
iron farm like the first floor on the
diamond
sword I see it's in it's in the box
right here give it to me
okay okay I'll cut some more so thank
you try not to uh I'm so sorry Mr sheep
oh I'm so sorry that's right I got a
gold star the honest way why is there a
polar bear in here that seems counter
sheep oh I'm so sorry oh I see name
pumpkin can't grow like this
kind of I
[Music]
see Unbreaking three get back up to 30
kind of wanted the sword to have oo
sharpness I'm going to make a new iron
sword we have enough iron for an iron
sword
right yeah maybe oh actually we could
should we make some more am I just at is
that what it is oh there's four iron
here left over but probably try and find
more so everyone can get iron sword I
don't need one I have my diamond
sword uh oh this is like a TIN Tiny HP
box for this it's only two iron I was
surprised maybe if we get lucky we get
another diamond block from mining the
one block a little while ooh true we do
get lucky so often we do get lucky every
once in a
while see we actually maybe we still
have some more diamonds do we
we might have enough for a diamond sword
I think we have two diamond blocks and
three diamonds are you okay then if you
don't need it we can make swords some
more swords for everybody who needs one
yeah I could use a sword enchant
it I don't
so one right what do I need do we need a
diamond sword oh I would love one if you
would trust me with oh so probably make
make four iron swords Whoever has
diamonds they're in the
chest now we
wait I saw diamonds in what maybe you
noticed I don't know if you noticed but
I think I did this off stream when you
weren't around do you see and you're
Atlantis gate did you see the Bell that
we previously talked about it has now
been
added it cost me 32
emeralds you got to remove the red block
though wait you have a bell yeah the
bean Bing dog oh we have we have shiny
Melones hey what's the sword for uh XP
stuff I have it right now can I borrow
yeah I need
five okaying just tell me and you're
dead
Okay like off the Bell sharpness three
ping bong ping bong ooh and Unbreaking
three sharpness three knockback through
looting three good good good
good I made a a pill
it's the banner it looks like the can I
change
that you can change stuff on the
medication banner I don't like it h hpe
h what banner I made a b there's like
guides so you can spell stuff and make
like a certain shape like a cookie oh
are you are you trying to make your
shield look nice no you can put that on
the shield that's cute what are you
making it for if it's not for the
shield for me for fun for fun yeah you
ever heard of fun before funy what is
fun F is for f
St
together that's SpongeBob right this
this another SpongeBob reference in the
myth MC stream a maybe of
course fun is not
allow I got an
idea no
fun what's your idea
girl uh
secret I think I I know what your idea
is impossible you cannot guess are you
making I have an idea too five different
shield banners all our
colors
no that's not wait is that actually what
you're making no no you genuine no
okay that would be cool
though
no oh hello fishy time to die
okay I'm almost
done what dang
it what oh
[Music]
there's you can't mine gold ore with a
stone pickaxe it just disappears I know
that I just wanted to get rid of the
block at that
point yes four more iron that's we going
to show that Ender Dragon his boss oh
I'm so excited should I change the
difficulty to hard no
I
could us having more diamonds than iron
is hilarious to me yeah we're so rich
the iron draw that's why we made the
iron farm and I'm telling you it worked
for a while and it helped me with uh
raising my villagers who then despawn so
I CED glad it had a purpose yeah it had
purpose oh okay I'm level
30 spawn a with they said it'll be fun
don't worry
it will be fun yeah I'm done I'm done wa
who's done I'm done she needs my sword
yeah I just need some XP to finish
something enjoy thank
you wait are you sure I'm not going to
blow up not going to blow up I'm trust
your old work trust it you made it so
perfectly hey you be
good it couldn't be any better than
that by the way for food I have a a lot
of fried chicken and and uh grilled
grilled whatever a 43 cooked chicken
that's kind of excessive don't you think
oh there's I think there's more in the
chest at the nether I made another chest
there so there should be plenty yummy
and of course golden apples as you know
what
punch make sure you grab your golden
apples golden apples
wait what is
[Music]
again I don't
know oh what extra Hearts big farts oh
hey who
there it also it just also has punch oh
oh yeah
arrows okay stick Flint okay free why
that much
Flint yeah Flint is really little but we
have I have a lot of bows uh they should
all be in the in the weapon chest oh
wait where did they go we have I have
like 31 arrows I I think 31 would be oh
wait I have them I have a lot of arrows
if I'm going to put the arrows
into the is
everything chest around the
portal uh the ne
Port
NE is it nether or never you say never
NE never or never I say never because I
cannot pronounce th oh that's she has a
list yeah is a speech imped
[Music]
no not true
no that's just how austrians and Germans
pronounce
it okay I'm actually actually actually
often they would just actually no the
really strong German accents they would
just replace the T with an
S
yeaha
is danger danger no wait that's
partially Japanese accents I think but
yeaha sounds cooler okay
okay uh yeah okay okay at least I don't
talk like that
so is uh quiet so uh what's and what's
another word with th to describe the
never
[Music]
Thursday on on Thursday we go
day I want uh no threatening doesn't
work because threatening they no they
wouldn't say threatening they would say
threatening with f yeah I want heavy
German ACC and K to beat me up I don't
know
[Laughter]
why uh what does this flag mean
gaur
uh po you haunting me yeah I was
thinking so because the day I watched
the Poland Austria match but I won so I
don't know this cannot bait me or or
taunt
me it's a reminder a reminder of my win
Poland's coming back for
you I think they're out it's not the
last okay next year coming back for you
I say about that eventually Poland will
have their
renge wait that's not Poland what do you
mean
what a of be wider
or is it Chad says it's an Indonesian
flag yeah it's the other way around this
way is
Indonesia oh ID let's go ID let's
go hey show some support for ID yes we
love ID let's go hello hey I got a quick
question what's the difference between
enchanted golden apple and regular
Golden Apple oh One Enchanted no I does
nobody know you got to test it out can
[Music]
Google the chat encyclopedia come on
guys and golden apple I'm going to be is
Enchanted Enchanted is far better okay
can I enchant all the golden apples with
lepus lazuli oh have so many sorry I'm
you doing over here
huh no you giv you extra a power one bow
power one Unbreaking bow
ooh you can probably combine some of
these bows to like get like a fully you
can't make anym uh what call B and then
make I could use Unbreaking one that
would be
good yeah you'll have to uh repair it
though but you can just combine the
normal bows to make like a yeah I have
an enchanted B already so I can combine
it what's the max enchant enchantments
like five or uh three I think I think
free for for a bow it's fre yeah I'm
breaking power
five we got a lot of gunpowder would you
use I I already used a lot of it iron
are you making TNT I'm the demo
man we could bring
it that's my plan it was going to I'm
going to surprise you
guys okay I will be surprised stay the
very end
I did not hear what you just said I am
here for the
bows okay so personally I feel like I'm
fully prepared I have fully uh Enchanted
armor part at no not fully said demo man
I thought she said devil man devil
C singing The Devil Man theme I borrow
the sword oh yeah you go at the end when
you're done with it it goes back to the
wow one
okay I'm the W
my you don't sound like waha
guaa
guaa Das is that's is not good that's is
good that's is [\h__\h] that's is good close
enough I'm surprised you came out with
that
much thank you how are these chickens
laying eggs out side of their little
zone They are going too
far they need to be told where their
places M yes oh I put four enchantments
on my bow I guess you can do
that four I got to go smack does that
work does that even
work you know what actually hold on I
almost have I have enough experience
hold on I can get I can make another I
can enchant my other bow and maybe get a
better enchantment doesn't
work how did you get four I don't know I
just I have you enchant flame power
punch and breaking nice flame Power
Punch I think like once you enchant
something once like you have a chance to
get other enchantments on the same thing
what I remember
stretch oh I could anv
it it's okay I think we it's it's
already Overkill everything is already
overkilled so oh Chad wait Chad says
combine it on the books but I didn't do
that I just went one by one with like
four books at the Anvil Oh I thought you
did enchantment yeah I thought you did
the
enchantment
yeah o ah ooh ah o ah ooh ah
I'm ready me too 20 gifts thank you so
much yeah g is really committed to the
999 blocks wait where are the golden
apples yes extraordinary around the
although Call's working on them I
think fixing them self-restraint that's
the word I was looking for yes you don't
feel the urge to mine you don't yearn
for the mines at all girl no
number you can't even see it yourself
number when I hit tab I see the okay
[Music]
oh I suppose how is
everybody G's got like 6K oh my Lord put
that was ping that's not the Ping that's
not the Ping
I I I played a lot off screen a little
bit too much I thought it was the Ping
too in the beginning especially
guys we're big and ours are all super
small 6K
ping oh thank God that's like an entire
6 seconds behind is it
she she's living in the past oh
no yeah no thankfully it's not
that you're sure who's uh still
preparing and what are you preparing ing
person who's still preparing I'm kind of
prep my but I'm just getting levels to
enchant some stuff I guess okay we can
prepare the the portal cuz we need to
like if someone dies like to get back
easily so we can kind of make it like
look nicer like put a stairs down into
the port want the the the yeah okay okay
you want to go in already no I'm just
saying like prepare it so that uh you
mean on so it's prepared in case someone
dies yeah on this side on this side on
our side okay yeah you do like a chest
I'm still preparing
something yeah but it's directly under
the one block so I kind of have to
destroy this construction I suppose no I
think it's bigger
than so you can make it like off to the
side a little bit cuz it's like right
here probably maybe From
Below let me
check like right here would this is fine
like we would be able to get oh
H yeah I'll make that a little bit
bigger down
there scary scary scary scary
scary should probably get the blocks out
of
here wait do I leave blocks
underneath I guess it doesn't
matter
um good what are you doing waiting for
my turn at the PPP can you get me some
stair
blocks thank
you wait I got to go threaten the guy
that was in front of me what I'm coming
back I'm stuck behind me I'm coming back
from my spot I'm coming back from my
spot M don't what did I do
hey W I would have given it to you but
now it's going to be a blood bath I
can't get back up I was going to put
stairs here to make it easier a what do
you need I'm here now um slab or stair I
got slab for you
okay slab of meat CH some slab of meat
right
here uh I'm
waiting how do you make a slab wait how
many do you need you're going to get
this
many yeah six is fine that's like the
default
number oh my God wait what wait what
okay where are you
all hello you dried it out in a green
light wait
light did you get them oh my God now I
only got one I think there's too many
spiders up there it's cled over here got
stuck in the water then darn
it wait look how behind you toilet is
clogged again toilet clogged I got it
you know you clogged it no it wasn't me
okay there we go now we can get up and
down easily I think we should I guess I
have to get rid of one of these blocks
one oh yeah now we can jump in it's not
night time we can't
sleep well of the shound that's fine
we'll
wait surely Sun's going down looks like
it's kind of about to go down yeah Sun
is setting we can maybe sleep and then
get rid of the spiders
spoter guess this works
M I'm making the area a little bit
safer keep Rey at least I'm not falling
asleep I'm
here so hopefully maybe um I'm going to
give you girls a a time limit in 30
minutes y'all y'all by the latest yall
be ready yeah I'm ready
what ready would be nice hly I can go
now I don't really
need me I just want to make more arrows
here you get out the way I mean hi I
need some I I gave you the sword please
respond I gave you the after my oh oh
wait I thought okay I don't get to keep
it it was not a gift
a thank you maybe we should set up an
emergency chest sorry I didn't know what
you're doing I was just putting stairs
there yeah yeah
do put them
there
okay my
pumpkins
pumin that's all I got okay perfect
nice
nice want to make it a bit more
visible yeah
damn
okay 40 arrows probably going to be
[Music]
sufficient um there's more arrows in in
the chests where the armor was if you
guys need more okay I was just making
more uh gravel whatever
flint rocks to eat yeah snacks to have
on the trip yum yum have you enchanting
the
apples have I been what have you been
enchanting the apples you can't they're
not craftable no you can only have
regular gold but we have two Enchanted
that we just found luckily so two people
can grab
those nice I don't mean to alarm anybody
but I think something just pushed me is
a server
hun what something pushed you maybe it
was maybe maybe it was one of us fear I
don't think anyone there where are
mm I mean
M yeah let me
see I will I will observe you think
something pushed you something pushed me
are you
sure yeah I was standing here and then
all of a sudden I was over here I saw I
move I
did don't look at me like that that's
probably just like an an enemy in front
of you yeah yeah yeah probably just like
him kind of pushing you to the side but
there's a block in between them this is
how all ghost stories
start us not believe in G you have to
believe
me show me okay I believe you again I
can't just make it happen I don't know
oh they're behind you nice I don't I
don't know cie I'll tell you if it
happen again she's crazy right she's
crazy I think I mean I don't know like I
said this is how all ghost stories
start okay so what do you it just
happened again were you looking I wasn't
looking I was hold on I'm sure we got
the footage somebody throw back the tape
I'm sure it's just like just a mob kind
of pushing you easily a little bit you
lightweight so you know it
happens
okay what
happens sh collect
oh you got that at least the the EXP
Farm's working now yeah I just need
three more levels and then it'll be 30
and I'm like might as well enchant this
bow has a Backup backup
bow bow yeah we'll put it in the backup
chest oh maybe somebody doesn't have a
proper bow yet then true we can give it
to them who needs a proper bow I just
have a power three bow I think that's
fine call you passed your yarn to me I'm
going to punch you for that s about that
can't
be goba you need a prop a bow I'm
working on on it oh okay so that's what
you're currently on okay okay okay
yeah
I'm nothing spawning again huh should we
sleep through
[Music]
it okay sleep is always nice
let me quickly for my study rearrange
the bed St okay fine
no my bed I didn't get all of the beds o
give me the beds I need to do my science
stud so close oh oh who who took the
bed not me wasn't me it's the ghost
no all right all right
um today's
Arrangement will
[Music]
bech the iron sword is backup sword
hello chicken can you get off the
enchanting
table that H
there yes okay ready hey where'd you
go I'm coming I was making a backup
you're taking too long yeah I was Mak
potion it's
science wait wait a second kind of
science okay she's sleeping in the
sounds like sounds like a notal science
to
me in their natural habitat the myth
members seem to be attracted to their
own image
colored I'm trying to sleep
here shut up
[Laughter]
well we can't sleep as long as the other
members are not coming to bed go I'm
writing my journal give me a sec my
diary you're writing already oh she's so
excited to ride in their
D my god
oh all right come on come on I'm coming
I'm sorry rush perfection K oh
W oh can we just make her say anything
or right in the
chat Point set I like this
TTS I am your
TTS next to speech go go to shating
that was good damn you nailed it first
try wow
W impressive now om is the TTS a
level I don't think so that was good
that made me
happy wait what's it mean uh uh
um
uh greetings ladies and gentlemen but in
a very I would say Austrian
way
ah
gratifications
greetings wait I'm going back to the
Bavarian BL Scot is quite the Bavarian
and Austrian way to greet uh grot yeah
you don't hear that in North Germany
M I say that when I want to greet
someone politely I
say hell you lose you snooze you lose
gar
Gar on my side W yeah I mean while we're
still waiting go for yeah I just need
two more levels and then we'll be good
to go but how about we make that that uh
extra ration chest or that for example
if somebody dies past have a chest by
the portal okay I'll move it over
because there is already some extra
rations rations and then I have like a
couple weapons like I'm enchanting that
can be backup
weapons backup I don't know about if
we'll even die we have the totems we
have we have so much stuff I'll move
everything over Kelly can you move the
the pearls yeah okay now I have a very
sturdy sword well relatively sturdy
sword that's all I needan
teleport oh yeah that that's that's what
I meant the eyeso vender what do they do
and we need to put them into the uh the
empty Slots of the portal there's one I
open it up no we already have everything
oh it's already in there oh is that what
the sound was no no it's not in there
but uh it was already prepped and we're
moving it over here don't don't put it
in yet though okay I'm getting free XP
let's put it stop sucking about all my
XP vacuum is that the
Strat like where's where is it parasitic
Tendencies that's the
Strat that's the Str can we yeah I'm
down here I made chest for Stuff damn it
okay I'm
underground
oh I don't know how to get back up there
stairs on the side
oh I promise guys I promise I'm not
stupid you
I'm not getting any XP I thought it was
in my
mind I got to charge my
bow jump up here and then you can get up
here but yeah it's it's kind of
weird parkour no you're okay is this the
chest we can put all related end the
dragon typ things can go in here got a
free level guys I got free two
levels2 I would have been 30 by now
what I want free levels what
deal no free
levels okay I Free level extra food
no yes so if you die you can just take
some stuff out of
here I think that's enough why is is so
slow okay looking fancy what a deal
indeed okay
all I need is my sword and then I'm
ready to
go I'm just waiting for good to finish
leveling slow yeah I well I would have
had four extra levels of two people no
that's not how it
works oh no they
didn't which kfp someone just called me
a hag in your
chat what the
I'm going to freak out in a sec oh I'm
going to freak out how what level are
you not good that's offensive it could
be a compliment though depending on you
think about it how you think about it it
could be I feel like that's only
supposed to be used for like really old
ladies my
day
9,000 over 9,000 will I reach the big
10K you did no
but will I why am I
dying better not blow anything up now
would I do
that
yeah where is my
donkey okay I'm almost done I
promise I just moved again oh did you
see that you were watching you must have
seen that Sor I was reading the chat the
Clippers will get it to ban no wait it
is it is I it's oh my
God what was
it it's the
ghost the
ghost I just realized this won't really
work cuz I think it's
herobrine oh it's cuz Kiara's she used
oh I saw her footsteps
okay wait what it must all along goba
wait
what invisible
what I thought it was losing my
mind I'm going to
cry where are you I will I will give you
the I will why am I flying why am I
flying why am I why am I flying what the
[\h__\h] I feel like I'm flying wait I'm not
flying I'm just where are you get down
here uh uh she's over here look at the
spiral she's right here I'm blocking her
oh I see was it you from the beginning
even from the start of the ghost store
no I was standing next to you when she
said she was moving C are you guys done
I'm done it was
was oh wait you need this wait you
stinker I have a sword you lose Watson
car sword yeah give me I need my my waa
sword
back more
level I'm hungry for levels I can't I
can't help but how much you need it for
anything I'm 28 I was going to make an
extra weap if I had the invisible potion
I could have sit by her and got some
I want to hear there spiders in
there
you you're making me feel like I'm
crazy exterminate the spider I saw
Bubbles and I thought I actually had
ghost or some kind of I don't know curse
curse on
[Music]
me
spooky being chased by ghost
let me give one more level and then I'll
leave forever such a chicken are you no
slurp up my let's finish
out work oh oh slurper exp slurper I'm
almost there I'm not the same person I
used to be okay I got some crumbs not as
Brave anymore huh I'm more Brave oh
really prove it keep the Ender Dragon
alone don't take the Ender Dragon alone
you can take you can take prove your
bravery still a few potions there's a
luck potion a strength potion and an
instant health potion I think luck is
maybe unnecessary go you can have a
Watson thank you yeah you're
welcome here
too and yeah so we're looking
beautiful beautifully
prepared shall we go soon yes I'm just
making a cool bow to put in the chest
okay o
enchant Shante a
Shante
flame
Shante remember you were saying some
name and then people thought that was
name of new member and you like leaked
something but you didn't what was it was
it like Mary or so in the last uh
Minecraft
stream uh maybe I don't remember what I
said what oh god what did I say Mary mhm
our new member Mary okay yeah when they
when they knew that we had new members
coming but I think the names weren't
known yet they were like oh gooa gooa
surely that was the names
right are you kidding me I
got she wouldn't slip up like that I'm
I'm I'm rock hard when it comes to that
we're locked down it happen it could
happen
nah I would cry if I accidentally leaked
a name or so of them makes me so nervous
I made of iron iron nothing comes in and
nothing comes out wait no everything it
can come in but it won't come
out are you
constipated no I meant with
words my Lord you all
you know what I mean Sil I
mean we all have problems that we
struggle
with
sometimes sometimes it's something like
that it's okay it's okay we we share and
we
care we share
care all
right distant Kelly hell
yeah more you going to make me wait the
more cursed things I'll say I'm ready to
go I'm sitting the Creeper face I'm
waiting okay am I ready to no no okay
I'm just enchanting something okay
enant oh wait are we going to do the
thing we doing it like now now what yeah
oh the murder of the Dragon yeah yeah
okay I'm going to take a PE break I'll
be right back okay byebye baby
[Music]
okay hey what's she looking at
guys what she looking
at beautiful
flag I Sor don't mind
me get down here
spider all right I guess I'm ready now
why you looking there girl
I believe she never stopped after
999 this
[Music]
girl I mean I believe it we can have oh
we have a we have a high score right now
so the lowest now is GAA she wasn't
always the lowest though and uh the
second lowest is CI but hey we worked
hard on a lot of stuff in terms of
blocks the
lowest and then there's Ena and then I'm
a really close what is it the block the
amount of
blocks has like 1,000 well
999 Calli has
1,600 then uh second is no third is Ena
with
2,600 and then am is second with 2,700
and I am first with a wapping
6,800 hi
Callie hi of the path just the way
like oops middle of the path soup my
soup oh
yeah
[Music]
uh
um Nan what is wrong you need
something um we can help you can we
no everything's oh no I'm innocent no I
said cany not can oh c
yeah yeah cool I was making sure to
establish her innocence in any case true
f are there any extra
totems uh there's only those four I
think okay feel free to take one I don't
know I think I think everybody already
got one I don't have one me oh oh let me
check but there were n there's no more
yeah wait what you to took all the
totems n I just got
here check your inventory empty your
pockets no you can't make
me this is a search do not resist I'm
resisting you I'll be able to see your
inventory if you
die drop everything you're wooden you're
wooded I don't I don't have any fighting
use your against Dragon I don't want
that you your pocket junk it's not junk
it's my in
it's my
inventory okay so who want who want to
them wait maybe not me me take it take
it take those totems one per person one
person will not have it I'll be the one
who doesn't have one oh yeah K die wait
should I have it P kind of poooo I think
you you can car K I don't think I would
need no it's okay I have some apples so
wait so do the regular golden apples do
anything yeah they give extra
okay yeah they're good for you okay yeah
the chest is down below just why there's
a lot of items floating
no what chest um just at a at a
MM oh oh oh yeah I think we don't need
it anymore wait somebody said that poves
streamers only should have the uh totems
what do we think about
that that is part of my plan
oh well you can have mine then you can
have wait car you can take mine then no
streamer isn't you right now you think I
would die take this Enchanted Apple cuz
Okay we take this pretty good apparently
well cuz if I die nobody's like missing
out on anything but if Kar dies then
what but make sure to take a shield and
have full armor maybe you can also take
a k you can take an instant health can
you hold a shield if you can I'll hold a
shield potion of instant Health healing
I got spash too so you be okay take what
you need look iron bar oh I'll take
meat y Yum Yum Yum you got everything
too ready to wait going to empty my
pockets oh my open up wait wait I'm not
there yet I was already
I'm not ready I'm scared it's kind of
hard to see it uh oh well maybe we need
to get rid of those blocks there wait do
we have 15 arrows is that bad there
should be more arrows I think like this
should work Arrow uh oh wait uh I put
away my tools can someone get rid of the
these blocks on I got it
just the wait cuz those be careful with
the slabs at the bottom cuz those going
to open a don't don't don't open where
I'm standing okay I got the pink one
what else the the wooden one I got 15
shots I'll just make sure they're good
water bucket what why water bucket the
stone uh get that red you get blasted
off into the air and don't fall in stone
Kiara oh yeah does anyone want slow
falling potion I have two extra I it's
so yeah that's good Cy thank you can I
get one no wait streamers should get one
I have water bucket I'm
fine yeah I'll have one so thank
you okay we're so overprepared probably
no this is excellent need water bucket
thank you H it's just when like you need
to you know save your
fall or no for the Ender D end the men
if you look at the end they'll call you
but if you have water around you then
they can't touch you I'm scared of water
just don't look at don't look in don't
look in their eyes don't do it look at
them
easy easy easy I made M oh W somebody
scared of water o so shall I put the
Eyes in
[Music]
Splash it's okay we're fine we're fine
we'll be fine oh we should bring some
blocks building blocks I have a bunch I
have 64 52 stacks and somebody I say
either Ena or am once we're in should
build a safe platform
please okay please please maybe cuz
she's
streaming okay can I have a donation a
generous donation of
cobblestone you might have to go with
other stones have stone here I have very
pretty uh terracotta Give It To You O
I'm
nervous no need for nervous we find do
this
okay I'm going to I'm going to put the
Eyes in I'm going to put them in we've
done this before haven't we guys we died
a lot didn't we a couple times I think
we died it'll be fine it's going to be
okay I feel like we're even more
prepared than back then possibly put in
the
eyes Okay finding it was harder last
time she doing it when do you eat the
apple Apple I'm I didn't grab the
apples oh yeah take take your apples
take your fans grab your apples I have
one apples they're in here har wait
where is it by the portal are you
supposed to say
one take
five five person
okay wait Callie made many many golden
apples yeah the ench ones are special
that's special loot that we found oh
wait I took one of those is that okay
uh it's probably fine or should I take
I'll take the I'll take five for the
regular do you want to see the one using
the flame ballb wait wait wait wait wait
I'm not ready hold on there's a
flamethrower you can give me like two
minutes or something just stall a moment
hold
okay where's the
Anvil H at the other boxes section
ah yeah kfp says get out of the ring
before you put in the last one okay I'm
already out I'm already out can you
imagine if she wasn't though that would
be
pretty it would be silly
no I'm
scared will be mythical true what's the
button again to quickly put something in
your right hand do you guys know or does
chat know
Buton F yeah I thought oh yeah it is oh
it is actually F girl wow you did not
lie to
meh she wasn't paying respects to
you all sorry I'm almost ready I'm
almost done what are you doing nothing
what are you doing a surprise a surprise
I have a Sur surprise too what's your
surprise uh don't worry about it oh
okay I'll tell you mine if you tell me
yours wait does it involve me
dying wait I can't die at the end that
my surprise what is your
surprise nothing okay we will all stay
alive yeah no deaths right no death run
my question was for you right no no
death runs
man okay I'm ready you say you shouldn't
enter
then no death
allowed my
feelings no walk off into the sun only
one death is allowed that's you me
okay I'm hyped I'm I'm ready to put the
iron I'm ready do it I'm for the mag
[Music]
ready second try at the end of dragon
Spar I'm scared somebody else go first
yeah please and make stream
first I
slipped kidding
Apple okay can someone bring some uh
Whatchamacallit
uh not blocks it's
uh
torches torch I have
okay didn't know we need torches eat
apple if low
Health okay is it safe to go in N hold
on give me a second I'm just making sure
it's we
water go go my go go Au AUA do we have I
want water the bucket with water you got
a bucket got my bucket okay
is it ready you you can come in I'm
building I have a bucket no glitch
please no glitch okay oh
nice wait why did I lose my water the
dragon scary already there's yeah W
should oh God oh God oh
God okay put torches down wait good are
you still over there I'm sorry I lagged
up for a second I'm wait don't come in
yet wait okay can you bring ladders can
you make ladders really quick for me I
have 20 how many do you need 40 oh okay
no actually 20 should be okay that
should be good if
we attack already wait wait wait wait
let me just I I can I can make more
don't die don't die stop stop stop stop
here 32 no no
no wait who got rid of the blocks up top
what happened Go Girls Girls Girls come
come let's fight I feel like it's
starting because they already I lost all
my
items my
TNT wait Who removed the ceiling oh no
oh no oh no no I died
again I'm not wait to go in there then
we all wait wait what do we need to
do away wait for it to go away but my
stuff we're snowballing what's happening
going to lie there for while don't worry
it's going away it's going away wait now
you can come okay and it's all like all
your loot all your stuff is in one place
so you'll have to like split mine's in
the back corner the dragon is spawn
camping turn it back to
easy yeah yeah get your things again and
then yeah I'm dropping stuff that's not
mine what belong to am I lost all my
stuff with all my
potions easy I have all the potions here
you lose it here I died it's still there
right my TNT my TNT it's all there I
think that's mine here's a bed this is
also yours and then this is yours and
then a bucket of water for you is still
there wait what happened to the
ceiling oh boy uh is not mine it's not
yours I don't know whose that is then
got potion of slow falling do that
belong to wait I I did seal off the
falling or the ceiling right it was not
enough I guess or I don't know
we that's fine I got it should I come
in yeah you can come you can come okay
ceiling is too
low it's okay we're going to go oh it
wiped them teleport okay time to go time
to go time to go guys get out of that
spicy stuff
no that's bad that's bad well h no
golden apples though all the golden
apples are I'm
lagging just just everybody keep on
running and uh I'm pressing w i moves
and people spot in that's I'll tell you
Ena when it's safe to come back in I'll
tell you I have it in my eye okay it's
disappearing you can come in now okay
why are there so many Ender what you've
seen this before GA I don't remember
is all my stuff F I have I have your
potions I think I have no weapons and
nothing I got 15 here I have everything
hey good thing I made some extra weapons
oh thank you
naked oh here and does anyone have my
armor and
stuff uh all I had was that ah he's
coming
y y well I guess I'm playing
oh I could use a
bow oh thank you oh there he is I see
him should we kill him
let's I guess I'm to support this
run oh boy what what are you missing
know uh all the arms armor
sets where' they go does anybody have it
in their
inventory mm I have Bo this and then
what I'm wearing wait I have armor for
some reason you have extra armor yeah I
also have give it to oh my God I have uh
12 golden apples I must have taken your
stuff I think you took my golden apples
oh wait I have it come take I'm so
scared right now okay no need to be
afraid I'm going
to Dr there's a lot of TNT everywhere
what the what did the end them man doing
all they I'm putting TNT so that when
the dragon fly is close you guys can't
shoot it oh
smart um sorry I'm yelling hi I don't
know if it's high enough though that's
why I wanted ladders so I could get
higher he hates does good have the
equipment to Ena no I don't know where
Ena is right now oh I'm in the middle of
the stage kind of okay he doesn't care
he still hates me can we I don't want to
start this too much without Ena being
equipped wait wait wait can you I have
pants I have your pants she has my pants
water should i him yeah kill him kill
him here here here here you away
okay we
G oh boy all right now they're all they
all hate me a lot okay die let's go guys
let's
go
okay let me make
him D that too
early hey you guys didn't see what I did
to your buddy right okay we're good
there's more with that came from buddy
boy oh you want your apples yeah that's
shot
ah oh God thank your time how do I split
a stack uh it's a left click right
click NOK
you all right let's go kill him get
him this was a bit
anticlimactic you mean we're fighting
him
now here we
go get him we need all of them right do
we need to climb up to some of them cuz
there's
cages I don't have enough blocks to
climb up on anything me neither wait Ina
here take I have your
pants ow come on
than can you not shoot does anyone have
my
water my yeah I'm going to die
no it's all right you're good which ones
it's only the cage ones oh
one something attacking um Can can we
shoot the dragon instead and like him
Sho at
him I'm shooting at
him my aim is not
great shoot Adam yeah I'm shooting
trying okay do heal if we don't get rid
of the thing my aim is
bad we so far have done no damage on him
hey really but I hit him several
times use pickaxes and stuff oh I man
dragon's getting healed eyes yeah oh we
got to yeah we Havey those got to go can
we go back someone needs to die yeah we
need blocks I have blocks I have a
pickaxe I can mine just mine mine some
blocks if you can and then go around to
the cages I think the others are C be D
do I just use a pickaxe on
him yeah he's Landing get him I don't
think it matters cuz we have to get the
cages first before he damage
heal I missed there is one that's like
slow falling
Hallelujah nice are they going for
me why are they
screaming oh dying oh wait they're angry
they're destroying their lord under pear
all right I can go to up to one
cage I can go up to one too go go go and
when you go down you can mine the blocks
back and then you can go to wa I think I
can also go up go go go go go those
cages I'll go up I'm taking my
potion yeah try to try to Le the dragon
away from the whoever's climbing I guess
I'm climbing now I'm also climbing
should I not be climb yeah you should
you should go yeah okay
wait what do I do with this thing do I
like destroy it or
something I love courage help me I got I
got one I got
one I got one oh this is not one oh was
that not was that already
empty uh it was just it was a Bedrock
okay came back explode it'll be
fine hey there's one of stck
I a lot of Ender Ang I could fly up to
one of
these there's a really tall one that's
still I saw it while I was flying
there's one he's te to right now that
that's it's so high oh that one up there
yeah can we climb there or no we have a
really high shoot but it's so high if
somebody gives me their blocks their
stack if they have them I can do it I
have 45 right now I have 26 and 56 59
here you go Watson
oh there you
go please don't sh me please don't shot
me I got an Ender
pear where're my
friends you're having a party there they
love you a they really like me oh what
are we going to do about these they're
so tall I'm distracting them okay come
to me hello so sparkly all right I got
it are they you you are they I think
they're all gone
okay when you walk away are they going
to kill you yep okay I'll stay Point
don't
worry how do you unro them a murder
kill them allur I'm
okay look very purply over here yeah
shark
bait he's taking the TNT I don't oh
end
end no no why do the hate us so much we
St we should have pumpkin heads hello
boys yeah we have plenty of pumpkins for
pumpkin can I survive a
fall guess there's no more buckets huh
he's pering is he no no come down he's
coming down he's coming down he's going
to land get him I cannot see much
there's just how does he manage to
always there's arrows are not hitting I
this is this is not as easy as I thought
please help standing over I think we're
over prepared I was like are you sure
he's I'll go in with a sword when he
lands
again it's worth dying once I can pick
up your items no you're having your own
little battle
here you're his own internal battles
wait I I could use some of these
pearls they slip through okay wait I
don't think we need blocks anymore cuz
we don't have we got all the stars
a is it
inevitable is this working we don't have
that many building blocks anymore if you
guys build up I'm by the pillars and uh
Enderman can't see me
here come here end and Enderman more
like I don't have iron for iron bucket
unfortunately I think we should have an
iron bucket somewhere in the base uh in
one of the chests like where the
diamonds are prank don't look at wait
pause guys I got to take a snack
yum no no no the end sorry I'm talking
to the end boys I know it's a joke
anyway but oh okay you can't just pause
this all right I'm
ready oh I wish oh that's 12 golden cars
that's probably that I used to my sword
on the
Ender oh no is is your sword dead um
time to hit it with your
fists or make some make the TNT explode
why am why am I being the
Archer CU I believe in you clappy more I
got a couple hits on him a couple only a
couple though Cal Dragon there's
water T down I'm brave I'm brave I'm
brave I'm brave I'm brave I'm brave I'm
brave oh you're the bravest oh [\h__\h] oh
no [\h__\h] I'm alive I'm alive I'm
alive don't is there water do you guys
have water no I don't have
water
I
a yeah aim not very good for me either
where okay I see him I feel like they're
not
connecting oh he's coming
down
nice get him got beat him up
sorry get him get him in the
dead my hole
seear work what do the pearls do I
thought you can teleport when you're
flying and and bring yourself back to
the ground oh you can if you like hit
the ender pearl if the H ender pearl
hits the ground before you do then yeah
oh okay nice shot come
on how many shots do I have
left it didn't hit in time I I I threw
it right away okay he's there
there is no iron for the buckets for
water buckets CH kill I can't
reach more arrows pretty soon here oh no
we're good am I actually not reaching
him am I too
small I built some stairs next time he
someone might have thank you thank you
[Music]
pleas oh boy
get down here young man get down this
instant nice shot somebody just got him
thank
you good job dead
ey dead ey this Ender wants to beat me
up you still being you're still there I
see you from afar I'm
helping in my own way you're going to be
the reason that Endermen are going to go
extinct that's that's a good thing
yeah oh no he's he's ping me get him
guys get
him I'll be with you in a moment getting
closer okay he's kind of low he's less
than 50 yeah a he
freaking leave me
alone yeah why haven't I used dead eyee
yet yeah we should have given gooda a
pumpkin helmet we had some in our day
missing all my
shots I mean every time the dragon is
going up I have different entertainment
he's low he's low oh he's going down for
the
head
yeah oh my God all my hits are going
through these guys this is okay uhoh
well oh I lived
I Ste
me night Comet night Comet coming right
up I pass night com
it I don't have ar oh wait I have four
where' they come from I have arrows if
you're sh if your pain is better
well nice P upile come on oh is he
coming there I think he's coming
yeah I'm going to help
now hit him now yes come on I
[Music]
yeah we did it oh now he's the disco
ball now we can watch the
credits
again oh the Y look at the egg wait
let's take a picture first yes yes yes
yeah take a pick together where uh can
we make stairs so like a platform there
she goes there she
goes I didn't use the totem but IED used
all the
apples y oh my I was here too this was
such a weird fight I died five times or
so I had a good time is free oh there
she is hello how how have you ended the
cycle of what that was Kill Them
All cuz it it seemed like the more you
kill the more you
aggro they just wouldn't leave you I see
America
um I'm sure Kiara feels real included I
feel let's
go I mean if if I just that Dragon at
one snippet of it then it is the
Austrian flag yeah you're red and white
in there yeah red white red yeah some
part of that is
me let's go nice okay let's all gather
and uh take un un photo oh we don't need
the I mean okay the feel like funny I'm
going to hold a golden apple cuz that
was my
job you are barely
visible okay wait what's a fireworks
star I I made one but I didn't know you
had to combine it with fireworks do you
want it no I like I'll make it when we
get back you have to combine it with
like a firework girl pick up your armor
oh true guess we don't need it anymore
cute wait what if this is how we die yay
I'll take that death all
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait why are you throwing away uh stuff
okay look cute like you always
do oh
girl come
back I'm okay the flag is there in my
Steed it's okay I already took pictures
okay it it was a good one are you dead
no no I'm back in my
hole ah such a beautiful night got to go
some credits together girl okay give me
a sec let me
uh let me boys
please go fight them go fight them my
sword going to die wait why are they not
attacking you because I didn't attack
them I listen I I
shoot I want to help you but um it's
nice to see you fulfilling the side
quest alone I okay all I got is a wooden
hoe now staring up at the sky are we now
take my
swords the Ping the
Ping this Shader thanks Bir Go hi
call oh you know of The Voice
look up into the sky with
me doesn't this remind you of elen
ring R I'm thinking about elen R to come
out just like Minecraft I was watching
you fight aelle for a while it's almost
sa I think
it's okay I'm not even looking at him
anymore it's safe all right it's not
safe it's not safe it's not safe it's
not safe okay it's
safe let's
go let's watch crit okay are we going
yeah I guess took good picture together
[Music]
together is trying to kill us all is
trying to blow us
[Laughter]
[Music]
up okay guys I'm watching the credits
right now oh my
God wait spoilers tell us what do you
see
wait what's going with your special
credit what's it
say it says Long Live
Minecraft dude no live M too shall we
jump in together what about the eggs um
we can that eventually but we don't need
it
oh do two one
jump
jumping I thought you already watched
the SM one block it won't let me in what
have I done please help what hey at
least you guys went to a different
screen just jump off wait I'm floating
on top of it what have I done nobody
else is here it doesn't work for me
there's like glass underneath it's like
a fake floor maybe doesn't work one guys
there's no
credit but at least you got through I'm
not getting through I didn't get through
no I'm still in the end guys me please
help please help I don't see you guys
either we all got split into different
realities yeah oh I don't like this end
I don't like this we just crashed the
server we're all in the end but we don't
see each other that's so lonely yeah if
we die we turn back to our world though
it's like a metaphor for life it's like
a long long dream we had I'm not going
to die here I'm going to stay here I'm
putting my flag back down I have all my
cool things so oh I can't access my
inventory anymore I can't access my
inventory
what beating the game broken did you
beat the game is that it is this how
it's supposed to be I guess
so well I wish I could be standing by
your side let's try re oh I can't I
can't I can't open the E Escape screen
to disconnect neither can I it breaks
your computer when you beat the game we
stuck in the game this is my bad end no
hey I'm I'm making fireworks I thought
you guys were going to come back we're
going to celebrate but I guess not I
want to be with am we die oh wait oh if
you tap out of your game you can get
into the Escape screen screen the um
disconnect screen and then you can log
back in and you end up in ah I ended up
back in the house of our
beds safety nice that's pretty cool hey
and we still got inventory yay we got it
I'm alive oh she
lives after being by Ender
endlessly
beautiful we found each other again
knows the power of alt tab I can't it
doesn't work when I alt
tab oh say can you see computer
good where she go I'm stuck in the
void very very nice are you putting it
up there I did full screen but it still
doesn't
work on top of Atlantis control all
delete is Atlantis one of those States
now it is didn't you know
that so how many states is it now in
total 52
55 oh I hope that's correct I hope it
ISP I'm never going to use wait there's
even a liberty B
it is we should shoot fireworks off of
the Atlantis gate when it turns night
time oh do you want this I have a
fireworks star I I oh yeah yeah yeah
here thank you my menu didn't work I'm
just restarting the game okay
okay where should we watch him should we
watch him from the top of the pp or
maybe from the top of here top of PPP
would be cute because of that fine art
yeah dude yeah that is where we
yeah is it safe up there we need to
build like a I don't know boss ladder
that if anybody has ladder oh yeah I
have
ladder the Red Blocks and then cross the
bridge and make
more Okie doie yeah make big ladder I I
will R man oh that's surely going to end
well nobody ever well the cameraman
doesn't die but uh I'll watch from down
here for when they fall
you getting the good car angles
mhm oo just like jackass so can we open
that up is that going to be okay to open
up isn't there going to be a lot of
enemies up there no we're not going to
open it up we just go on top of
it a do not open it do not open it how
do you go around it though it's shap
like a giant mushroom you can get up
just build blocks or something yeah no
problem yeah maybe done this before
maybe not from Dara maybe from where the
other stairs were and then straight up
so we end up at the edge of it I guess
oh okay but be good you do not want to
crack that
open it sounds a little
spicy wait wait so wait wait wait wait
wait it's like opening box watch where
you're walking oh my goodness yes you
you're going to push me off the edge
behind you what do you the Ping the Ping
[Laughter]
don't worry goba wait no this is how we
have to do this this is how we have to
do this okay
yeah go wait thr me the
ladders just going to throw it off the
ledge okay oh catch
good shut up give me say nothing
shut caught in
4k
stop throw it
bro how many myths does it take to make
a staircase shut
up okay Co is clear oh if you guys heard
we catch the sunset Oh yay okay girls
you can come up I don't think we're
going to catch it though this is like
holy Holy
Ground
CAU way oh the sunset's dying uh that's
okay catch the maybe we'll catch the Sun
right oh yeah that
works get your lawn chairs out get the
barbecues popping off I was thinking I
was like this should AB really
put and now we get to hear the beautiful
sound of monsters as well all right I'm
making piles everybody takes on
fireworks this is one pile this is the
next pile this
cute right the next pile
star sepal firework stars in in my
inventory from you me too okay I think
we have enough though who didn't get
fireworks there's another pile over
here thank
[Music]
you all right where should we go like
here looking over the thing oh yeah go
third pict yeah
yay wait we just shoot them what about
the firewor stars do they work too yeah
they're in the fireworks I'm not sure
how I think you have to look down and
then wait I'm
bald
cute
cool I'll shoot
some you look down blue
yeah
fireworks oh
wow yay happy New
[Music]
Year Ju
it's so pretty some of them are not
exploding properly oh yeah I
accidentally made like regular ones oh I
got
[Music]
those
beautiful okay that's all of them I
think yeah there's like the regular one
wow
pretty okay that's it okay did it
wo oh that's finale oh it's raining cool
it's snowing wait can we take a picture
where we we have like a good shot of
like the the little things we built over
there oh here we face this way and then
yeah let's take one together let's take
off the
armor yeah a wait what's wrong with my
head I'm bald same what it looks fine to
me I look like yeah it's a bug i' I'd
rather wear my helmet than that I look
like you have to confess your sins to me
wait I don't have a helmet I am a
nun you canot wear helmets I bet I look
bald oh I kind of yeah I do look bald
whoa uh right I want to have empty
hands where it was was it this
okay um Golden Apple wait I want a
better view got have the golden apple
okay okay ah I'm don't go wait hold on
I'm in the wrong View
because for the screenshot being on the
edge is kind of
bad oh should I should we
[Music]
expose Callie let's expose the the
stupid foreheads let's do it okay
ladies okay
cheese
chees
wow cute this is what we built in about
a week or so what F3
F6 f for screenshot F no f f F2 F2 and
if you want to get rid of the UI it's F1
yeah f f f f f F1 but I mean how do I
change perspective F5 I can't believe I
still have forgot F5 there's three
different perspectives so you have to
switch around I think we should all Run
and Jump Off The Other Side together
guys wouldn't that be so fun
yeah
okay well C you got screenshot I think I
think it took well if it didn't it's
cool okay I guess we're going to leave
all this behind time to leave this
planet behind wait can I have a little
speech Yes we going get before we speech
speech speech speech spe speech speech I
am happy that we were able to give
everybody some nice nostalgic feelings
not just chat but ourselves perhaps too
with these loud zombies that I'm hearing
in in the background uh I want to say
thank you to the girls for participating
in this project and and myth is number
one myth is best myth is
cute my is
forever let's
go let's jum guys let's go let's go with
all my homies
homies but we
about okay this I I'm going to log out
because I don't want to I want this to
be the
end all
right
everyone we did it roll the credits
y again
[Music]
thank you the diaries
oh the Diaries it's somebody wrote some
stuff right I did I forgot
it I forgot too to write the final entry
I want to read what what GAA wrote Oh
I'll I'll give you my last diary entry
are you going to write it no I'll just
say it out loud okay say oh oh yeah I'll
just see man hard we were not
overprepared it seems like it that's
about the extent of my my time today it
was fun the dragon bit back yes it
wasn't the dragon it was the Enderman
the end glad was a challenge yeah
chaotic it's like we did it for the
first time because it seemed like we had
no idea what we were doing H I
forgot okay let me let me then check
gasa do you want to give a vocal diary
entry for us uh I would like to say this
e wasn't that bad had a lot of fun thank
you k for putting a lot of work behind
the scenes put together so unnecessary
to make so many things I know but it was
fun it worked out yeah indeed indeed fun
thank thank you thank you everyone for
you know the fun times got to
love thanks for the reliability you know
for building the
base I kind of
broke no no no no no somebody needs to
be brave enough to do it and it was you
exactly okay all right uh should I read
it out loud what G wrote what yeah yeah
okay uh she wrote she wrote wait she
wrote two entries for day it seems wait
we going back in oh you want to read no
it just
mean out loud yeah your face okay I'll
read it then cuz I've been reading your
other entries
too okay H uh day five tonight we fight
tonight the Ender Dragon Falls tonight
the new Champions will rain tonight the
spoils will be ours tonight we will rise
T night well is this a song is a chant
you didn't say it right you didn't say
it right okay say it right say it right
no I was trying to voice but I can't do
good voice Middle School it's like
tonight we fight tonight the Ender
Dragon Falls tonight the
new in caps walk you didn't say white
yeah forgive me goo forgive me it's okay
the next one I'll read better okay day
six no Elden ring Dragon thing yet but
the server is oh this is not as dramatic
as I thought it would
be wow critiquing is not the message is
not dramatic no Elden ring Dragon thing
yet what does that
mean we didn't fight the elen
dragon
Dron but the server is haunted it passed
a message to me
message I could
spooky well now I need a a a a vocal
ending uh ENT tree please
Google the
end beautiful true
beautiful thank you okay then I have one
more from
am y I shall see I prematured my the end
then I saw a riding a few times
today oh oh a I cannot even read this
sorry I was pouring my teeth for this
great moment I thought left like aise in
I did guys that's that stain I have a
hunch I might be wrong but I think I'm
right I think I'm a love Smith y
[Music]
cute she wrote a million hearts into the
diary and wrote Love myth my love love
iped those manually too wow a lot
work okay this one gets an a amen an a
for amen an a I
passed she's passing with flying
grades yeah thank you for writing the
Diaries and that's it that was myth one
block Minecraft the series the season
and the season finale we all had a blast
and the Ender Dragon has been also
blasted I also got
blasted hole Yeah we all got blasted W
status wait what
blast we were
blasted right oh nice
yeah y thank you for watching thank you
everyone that's it thanks everybody
ulate ulate ultimate ultimate
byebye leing bye everyone