[Music]
do
so
[Music]
my
so
[Music]
foreign
you
[Music]
do
bye
so
[Music]
i'll do
i'll do one more oh [\h__\h] we're in the
wrong corner
uh do one more pull why does it sound so
weird what uh uh why don't ah
do i sound weird i feel like i hear
myself double
uh
i think
we're gonna do
one more poll
um
this looks like so a lot of people can't
i sound normal to you guys
a lot of people still can't watch this
room i'll do one more poll um
can you see the stream
yes
no
because in theory i could isn't tomorrow
my day off i could just say i'll stream
tomorrow
and then youtube should be fixed until
tomorrow i do sound weird in my head
this is weird
oh well um
uh
yeah cause there was one sixth of people
saying no
uh
what what am i saying
no
what did i just say
60 percent of people said no
whatever i just said before that made
absolutely no sense
160 what no
[Laughter]
i think i was thinking about two things
at the same time
uh
i feel like
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] i feel like uh
i have a curse on me right now
because
see when i try to open
my stream before uh it didn't
start and then i refreshed and it didn't
start it did start then and now i open
it again it doesn't start
but
where's my pole where's my pole right
here uh
oh now it's still fifty percent holy
[\h__\h]
still fifty percent like yesterday my
equipment my my galaxy live basically
broke
uh
and now
how do you get out of a [\h__\h] game in
the ps5
and now and now and then and then uh my
cats were manipulating me because the uh
smoothie turned off my pc while i was
putting up a stream slot
hmm maybe i should stream tomorrow don't
joke on us tony i'll just watch the vod
um
and now youtube is stopping me from
streaming
and it's not only me it's been others as
well
how do you how do you [\h__\h] close the
game
are you close the game
ah okay i found it
okay
[Music]
i mean
ah
i mean you guys can watch the vault but
i know you guys prefer a live stream
um tomorrow for me it's fine i can
because like otherwise tomorrow there's
nothing that i needed to do tomorrow
that i can't do today or the other way
around
and tomorrow it will definitely be fixed
and then
you guys won't have to suffer
like this
what do you think
what do you think guys
for the best i think i think i'm think
maybe as well because otherwise so many
people come into the stream it doesn't
start and a lot of people also i think
won't even bother to refresh
um
they'll just be like yeah it's not
working okay bye
and then even the people who do refresh
as we see 55
are not getting in
yeah
[Music]
um
yeah
that's that's fine for me
youtube's so weird at the top of my chat
i see four members
messages
from the same member you know those
green messages shouldn't it be only be
able to send one are you guys seeing
that too
i see four from the same person
sending two months uh
messages two months anniversary messages
or so
it worked briefly and cut out ah i don't
i don't want it to be
so scuffed
um
no you don't say it
you don't say it
i see it too oh
let me look at my calendar we'll just
delete this stream then but um let me
look at my calendar
uh schedule meal
so nope there should be absolutely no
difference whether i do it today or
tomorrow um
okay
oh yeah youtube is so weird i think it's
been like this for a couple hours now
yeah i saw reina and eofy had problems
probably some other members as well
uh
you're finally in
i'll i'll do one more poll
ah
but it's looking bad
it's looking bad i'll do one more poll
voice
are you
seeing the stream
i'm in i'm in
yes no
um
okay
and it says again that it cuts out for
some other people who got in
i can see now i'm in i'm in i'm in i'm
in i got kicked
[Music]
okay now it's gone it kicks people
yeah it looks like that even if you're
in now
[Music]
and now it's back i'm in i can see now
oh
yep kicked
[Music]
oh oh oh yeah i think i see something
happening too on my screen like it's
tries to load and then it stops loading
like my own stream
okay
um as much as people could just watch
the vault i feel like you know
it's better to
stream tomorrow maybe
um
[Music]
oh i see
an error has occurred
dollar sign begin link
dollar sign end link did you guys see
that too
um
okay
a lot of you guys say you're in but then
a lot of people say i'm getting kicked
out again
maybe there's a maximum of people who
can be in the stream right now and the
more people join the others are getting
kicked out or something
please stream
[Music]
working now
finally in
our mobile seems fine
[Music]
it works now really
for a second maybe
twitch
all devices work really
is there anyone who's i mean they
wouldn't hear me i guess they wouldn't
hear me if i asked
maybe i'm still getting kicked out
uh
it works then it kicks me out and it
works when it kicks me out got kicked
out but now it's back
[Music]
oh god the chat is so fast it's still a
bit screwed up
um
so i'm getting kicked out
[Music]
i think uh
is your
in this youtube kicking
you
in and
out no
stable
yes
[Music]
m
okay
staple oh here's another here's another
poll
here's one more poll also if this is
actually happening on hello vaudeviewers
um
skip skip
skip to like later
oh
oh yeah yeah yeah oh the viewer account
went up by a lot maybe that really means
that it's fixed
[Music]
[Laughter]
i just see your thumbnail oh [\h__\h]
isn't yeah there's an actual view
account now
hmm
[Music]
for 13
still say that i have an issue
thirteen percent
um
fixed
okay
shall we give it a chance
not working okay
okay okay
youtube faces fabulous oh
well
okay
okay i was thinking we're really not
doing this
all right
shut the weight
uh let's just wait
i don't wonder why i hear myself double
though
do um have
oh
well i think today
i'm gonna get
uh uh uh
uh used to this
now i'm not disappointed i just shop
no it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
either way hello finally here oh
yeah to you i apparently sound fine so
that's good
is it because
yes ps5 of course i have a ps5
had it for a while now okay i'm ending
the anketo
uh i'm gonna tweet one more time in case
people were watching and then gave up on
it because it was
blocking around
and youtube seems to be stable now come
back
too much
[Music]
please come back
if you gave up already
so we're going to play allen ring
elden ring
out of the ring
ring rolling ring yellow ring
[Music]
welcome hello i'll get a key i'll say it
again because
some of you may have not heard it
cakey get the maidens get those maids
maidens yes yes yes
i will do my best although today i'm i
gotta be honest i'm
[Music]
i wasn't looking forward to this ellen
ring episode that much because
logically
today
we're
we would be going through
or i suppose we are going through
that stormville
castle
and
i have a bad feeling about it
um
yeah because it looks so dark and
difficult and there
is probably going to be a pain in the
butt a pain in the ass probably
if if stormville castle is what i saw uh
in the
a little bit in the in the stream of
uh india and calling then then i'm
scared and i don't want to do it
where do i put this again
[Music]
we will help you thank you
i'll be fine i don't know
i don't know
rachel what's your elden ring album ring
alden ring did you see the awesome
thumbnail maybe that's why youtube was
bugging around because it wanted you to
look at the thumbnail
i still checking network connection yeah
i don't have a subscription
[\h__\h]
stop exposing me like that
um
[Music]
wait why are we here did i go here after
killing
market
where did we end that last time is this
why we ended it
did i kill margaret and then explore
this area
my turtle shield got nerfed
a song
i killed the sentence
oh yeah yeah right oh yeah right
um
okay so i gotta go
i guess
the fel omen
is it because he has fallen did it
always say the foul omen
oh [\h__\h] but i also heard that margaret
got nerfed
and that people now have less struggles
killing him than before is that true
cause i'm kind of salty that that
happened after i killed him
no
yeah i wandered around and killed a lot
of things i did i did that oh a bad
woman oh
fat like fouled out okay
i forgot how [\h__\h]
give me that back i forgot how to play
the game let's go
it took crony free tries what the [\h__\h]
no that actually makes me mad
i heard it also took um someone else
uh who wasn't
uh someone else really didn't struggle
with it either was it iris i don't know
uh audio is fine
she's magic oh
i heard oh yeah i heard magic makes it
much easier
also because you can keep a distance
and so
i have to go through this
do i have to
is all of this the castle
for example
ah maybe it was elena i don't know
ah
magic 20
all that
i can skip the castle but that sounds
like i'll be skipping a lot of levels
and stuff as well like
um
like i'll miss out on a lot of
exp
but but at least that means that i don't
really have to do it super clearly right
i can try to rush through it
i just want to go straight through here
well i guess i can't
okay i'm scared
you got the skill but i don't know
if i really got this skill it's been a
while
which way do we go we go that that way
or through the store
this is gonna be like a horror game
i know
[Music]
you scary
why are you standing in the corner like
that and whisper it man [\h__\h] freaky
he looks so scary
i would advise against taking the main
gate into the castle okay
it's tightly guarded by hardened old
hands
oh
try the opening right here
that one the guards don't know about it
you breached it pretty big how do they
not know about
oh i have a choice
[Music]
which one should i go with guys
take the main gate yeah
ina killed him
hina
don't trust him
main game
i think it is harder
ringgit he wants his manga okay but it's
harder
don't take
okay yes that's the spirit
long neck of tarnish that i like
but the way he talks makes me think that
he's trolling me and leading me into the
more difficult path
is he trolling me
but you guys say main gate is harder
okay i
i believe that now
signing pool
what was it
what
summoning pools what was that again
summoning pools
what can i summon here oh
ew
he steals from your
what
that dude steals my runes if i die what
that dude
is
what
it does
that was a spoiler
but i'm gonna die
probably
uh oh well maybe
maybe i won't die i'll probably will die
oh [\h__\h]
he's a faithful that was obvious he was
sex from the beginning
i don't know how to fight anymore do i
have to fight
upward down
i want some time oh those holes look
cool
i guess they're from like being bombed
uh by
some monster
up okay
i want some time today to talk to chit
chat with you guys as well so we're
gonna do some uh talking by a fireplace
if we find one
is that even real burp
israel is moving it's
uh
thingy but
it looks huge
i'm scared
[Music]
is that a hawk
what did i go up for if i have to go
down here
don't i have to go down now
i don't see any other way
unless
big birb berber friend nah
can i soft lock myself here
no no no no how do i fight
[\h__\h] uh
[Music]
what click right stick oh okay
no
[Music]
uh
wait so did he steal my runes but my
body is like far away how would he steal
my runes did he go there before i went
there did youtube lag when i was dying
i forgot everything
i got him
yeah
[Music]
see
it didn't have to be like that if i if i
just
had a chance to warm up properly
what is it
no no is there another one
yeah there's another one
if i go even further down
i hear some
[Music]
sound
it came right back
that's grace
that's i see someone up there
um
exam
summoning pool is now functional
i touch the grace
can't go up there
should i go up or should i examine the
bottom
[Music]
fireside chat yeah i think it's a bit
too early a bit bit
bit swirly
[Music]
it's cute it's kind of cute though
insane
i'm just trying to free them from those
chains man
insane
i forgot how to play as we can see so
it's gonna be
problematic today
[Laughter]
is the bird
what the [\h__\h] is
killer bibs
come up here
okay okay
learning by dying
uh is the mother of eleanor not learning
by doing it's learning by dying
oh
okay do we go this way
the flag scared me
you have something cool bolts oh okay
i'll take some bolts
that's the spirit
yeah but i
really really really don't have the
the
what's it called
the routine
anymore in my hands
no the button smashing it doesn't happen
automatically anymore
previously it was like
intuitive almost but oh
i was about to drink
no i love bibs i love burps i love
burpees hold on tony
forever follow tony
forever
oh my god
um
[Music]
how do you run again
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
control
now i lost 2 800 or 3 000 or something
so [\h__\h] mad see i don't even i don't
need to worry about that dude stealing
my runes
because i'm doing a great job losing
them by myself
wait where's my weapon
why why why why why why why why
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
not
why
i want to shoot that verb
oh [\h__\h] now i have no bone darts oh come
on
can i like sneak up to you i feel like i
can't
i can't try
ah it didn't work uh-oh
wait
ah
i don't already want
i know i knew it today is gonna be a
pain in the ass why am i even bothering
to go to these purposes is there an item
there someone said there's like an item
here
oh you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
it's the wrong way anyways this is not
where if it's going there
smithing stone
that's not really worth it
okay
stupid [\h__\h] boobs
using my shield i don't know how the
[\h__\h] you use a shield
do you really expect me
to use my shield right now
i don't even know how to roll anymore
like i i am so lost right now i need to
get used to the controls again
how smart are you
[Applause]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] how do i run uh
uh
can i run
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
but this is what kills me
unbelievable
no no i can do it i can do it i can do
it as we all can see
you think fire can hurt me i set a whole
[\h__\h] stage on fire
the other day
oh
there's another one there's another one
oh he's a platforming hello
okay chill chill chill i i'm i'm
actually amazed i survived that
[Laughter]
young
wait i should go oh a nice looking
shield i should go back to
ah but then he will refresh
okay let's not go back
i hope there's a lot of graces
look there's a lot of graces uh
scattered everywhere
um
[Music]
oh hello
no
does he have a horn too they probably
all have a horn the ones with the fire
and this is
safe to enter
someone are you alive
shh
he's gonna see me
the next grace is so far oh [\h__\h]
hello oh
oh okay
i guess we're fighting you look like the
guy who gave me the quest
hmm
uh
there's someone there
why are we in the castle now i don't
want to go for the castle it's so big
and i don't like i i saw how it looks
like when you play online there's all
these people these ghosts running around
i don't i don't like it the messages are
stupid anyway
it's partially trying to troll you oh
are you coming this way
no okay okay good good good good
well he's huge
he's so strong oh no we're fine we're
fine
we're fine
the first attack did barely any damage
but
we good
okay
who hook claws yeah
interesting
some are helpful yeah yeah yeah but in
order to play online i need to um do my
membership thingy but
i don't wanna
i don't feel like it
oh
are you insane
oh are you
coming here or did you just want to
clear oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
hey
yeah
okay
easy easy easy easy no problem [\h__\h] out
oh you're so live okay
no file damage for me no fall damage for
you i suppose
i'm like
constantly uh anxious right now because
i don't like this
it's freaking me out
why magic there
oh
uh where to go
it's too big what's in here
open do i really want to open this
i don't i don't see anyone oh but there
are there's a ladder that goes up i
think
should i go
up
here
oh
yeah no not yet
all right first you
oh daggers nice i hope i won't lose them
it's locked oh is it locked anyway
okay
well then
[Music]
oh hello
standing there menacingly
don't just stand there
[Laughter]
the smoldering butterfly seems to be
somewhat of a hint
okay okay okay we're doing fine
these enemies are nothing
i'm just gonna clean the path a little
bit
hello
[Music]
okay
can i go down here and then go back up
what what what what what what what what
what was that noise
nothing
i heard someone attacking me i swear
oh no it was just a
it was just nothing
it was nothing okay
right now i gotta go all the way down
again
do i
oh okay
okay i'll go again
is youtube being okay for everybody now
by the way is this is it kicking out
anyone at
all must have been the wind
wait i heard that somewhere
it must have been the wind
i heard that
i remember that um
hey i hear footsteps too it's okay it's
doing okay youtube
what's up in the wind
no i'm actually not referring to skyrim
oh wait that wasn't must have been the
window
what was that what was that i'm thinking
of
something
uh where you had to hide
under a
box and then move move move move and
then stop okay there's probably a lot of
games where you have to do that yeah
metal gear metal mgs
i think
where are we going
i had just a bucks not not wind it was
just a box oh where are we going
is this is this uh a sac
a dead end
what
ah because i was crouching
i'm scared i'm scared
is there gonna be a jump scare oh it's
way too dark um
i show
i have a lantern
you may recall i have a land
i know it i know it that's why you guys
told me to click to heal
what what is that this the guy oh hello
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
die that's okay that's okay we can come
back we can come back
okay okay
okay okay okay uh second time second
time we're gonna
do it no problem but why the [\h__\h] are we
out here now
oh
you're gonna call your friends
do it now do it now then
oh wait
you can't see me here
when you turn around
i forgot how to run i forgot how to run
i forgot how to run again
can you see me
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
no
or did you still get esp even when they
fall down like that
okay
you still get it ah okay okay okay
as i remember some people partying here
yeah yeah
yeah
one dude
[Music]
beautiful
this guy i can skip oh yeah yeah but i
mean
why not
why not oh
hello shoot me
shook me
nice
impressive
okay
how do you run guys
how do you run
how do you run guys how to pull
[\h__\h]
oh hold ah
thank you
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
wednesday
something else now okay
now this dude again
i wish they had a grace
uh
hello
i wish that they had the grace close to
the
so that enemy that we just encountered
man
bro
circles to roll i know i know
i know that
okay we're back we're back go back
just fall down
there you go common shoes shoes
[Music]
shoes don't we don't do we even have
shoes
shoes oh yes we do
wario graves okay i'm gonna guess these
are not better
yeah unless you want to do magic i guess
okay
uh
this way
what
back and clip get the item and then run
what you mean i don't even have to fight
him
and you mean i don't even have to kill
him is that what she's saying
where would i run to
because like there's nowhere else to go
here
[Music]
ah to the other door that was closed
i wanna kill no
no no no no no no
no no no
no
i don't want to waste my
um
my flask
for that little hp i hope i won't regret
it you know it's just just our second
try
so
[Applause]
there's no huge use encroaching
gekko
hello hello hello sir
uh
oh god oh god
i'm not used to it okay
ah
[Music]
why don't we start from here again
hello just call your friends already do
it do it do it do it
that doesn't count as no no no no no
that's not fair that's not fair you
didn't toot you didn't do the toot
shut up
tell her she's doing great why would
they do that when i'm doing horribly
badly what would be terrible
[Music]
hello
holy [\h__\h] that's hot
[Music]
i went in there with six flasks before
oh that's a bad start three flasks
three flats how can i do a free flask
that's impossible
oh
well at least you don't lose the item
um
that you gain
isn't that nice
okay
do you open the door for me is he coming
out
no
i do hear footsteps though
it's freaking me out
he opened the door for me
[Music]
grab and run you mean from that from the
dead body
i want to give it one more try but we're
free free flasks were kind of
uh
we don't have much
chance dooley
snake snake you think you won't notice
me you'll notice me
there's a chest on the left
no i don't i don't want to just run
now
see the chest
it's that over there
but i have a light on
shhh
are you whispering why are you not
whispering
you don't have to lie no i don't want to
but i could shoot him
he doesn't seem to notice the light
why i can't even uh focus on him right
now
he's like
not active yet yeah i can't
interesting
how does he not notice me
how does he not notice me this is so
scary
oh okay
my hands are sweaty
i'm breathing into his
knees right now
um
oh [\h__\h]
i'm winning
oh i was holding my breath oh my god
thank you frowing daggers they kind of
helped me there and that sneak attack
wow
[Music]
curved sword talisman
is that a good item wait what ah that's
the key
yeah my hands hurt and my my heart hurts
[Music]
i couldn't breathe man
oh man my hands are spaghetti now
[Laughter]
uh where was that door
where was that door
ah that door
oh he's still here oh god i forgot i
forgot about you that's what i was
hearing
okay
oh my god
[Applause]
don't kill me
huh
what
i added
[Music]
what if i die until
the next um
grace do i have to kill that dude again
not too far from my last grace okay okay
okay how do i climb up again
i forgot how to climb uh from the
underside no
can i climb
ah there no okay
didn't show it at first
a door stays on long ah okay okay i'll
go again and i keep the talisman so i
guess that's okay
okay
i see nothing
ah
left over right
there's someone there
i can sneak up on them
maybe i know we would have to jump
they would probably hear
that shield oh where did my shield go
ah which way oh
[\h__\h] hate this game
[Music]
why you guys not warn me huh
what is that looks weird
uh-oh
is this the right one
you didn't know
don't lie to me
wow this looks really cool
is should i go the other way first
new menu item
[Laughter]
uh
keep going
okay
increase this dropping rate oh
look at that view
what is that over there
let me look at the map
is it this part yeah
so good
so gooey
what a view
is there something
around the corner
oh here
snake snake snake snake stick
snake snake's next thing
about him okay
ah
oh good really high up now
is there gonna be a boss up there
it would be lame if there was no boss in
this castle right
oh god oh god
oh okay i think he turned around um
um
is there any
like a secret side path no really you're
not gonna reward me for going there
i can sneak past him
run upstairs okay okay because i don't
want him to kill me now if he's like the
other guy
oh yeah he is like the other guy
oh sheesh
so when he walks back there i could
sneak past him right
is there nothing here that's worth it
worth getting okay
just run run upstairs
run or sneak
quick
okay
well if he notices me i'll uh run
he didn't notice me
okay
he won't suddenly come up here if i make
noise will he
i want a lost grace please
please give me a loss grace
you're so scared
i'm so scared
oh there's an elevator here there's an
elevator over there ah
i found it
isn't that kind of sauce
is that so sauce
okay touch
okay we're we're safe for now like in
some way holy [\h__\h]
oh
hi hawk
i just want to look at this view damn
we're in
the castle
very much
what do i do now
should i go back and try to kill that
dude
level up i don't have enough to level up
i need like way more than that
but
i could use my
my few
uh stones thingies how much do i need
again 4899
[Music]
i don't think i have enough
i didn't what no no other crafting here
i have
gold and just the small ones
how much does that do again 400 uh
not too far from a level up yeah
i was trying to kill him
i will try
i think
should i
it might drop either armor or or exp i
could jump on him on him from here no
how do you do that kind of jump attack
here
dude
if i die here
few
i too for the drop attack oh
i never did that before
never did that but hey hey hey hey we
have a chance i just have to get my body
back
[Music]
almost i didn't really look at his hp
but i had a good feeling about that one
okay okay
once he's here i'll drop on him and
hopefully not die too fast
i'll get my body
holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
very close
i always hold my breath man when i
fight against dudes like him
okay first first uh try
fourth time is the charm right
now
i i failed again though did i push r2
too early i guess
or do i need to hold it longer because i
only like
pushed it once so then i'll have to like
hold it longer
wow
[Music]
well now we have nothing to lose
oh man
i looked so cool
of course i had to stumble over my own
feet
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] am i doing though that the
falling attack never works for me
oh man
i hate that whole
[\h__\h]
repeating history
i'm doing pretty bad right now
okay
i'm gonna get you
[Applause]
that's [\h__\h] whole i mean i would have
died anyway but let's let's say it's the
whole whole's fault
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
looking gravity man
oh i watched this super interesting
video yesterday speaking of gravity
uh um i've been watching a lot of videos
from this channel
um it was a video about
what would happen
if the moon would fall
on us
who's
it was funny because
um of course will this will never happen
in real life but
um
there were some references to
zelda
searching down the game that we all know
and love
oh
idiot
me too
both idiots
both idiotical
i'm so stubborn i'm so stubborn
and uh uh
yeah majora's mask and the channel is
called christmas and i thought it was
funny because spoiler alert
spoiler alert
after
about one year of the moon coming closer
and closer and closer to the earth and a
whole apocalypse
happening um because the earth was
falling apart due to the moon coming
closer really interesting what would
happen even if it will never happen
um but then
after a certain point the moon gets so
close to the earth that the earth
gravity is strong enough
and the moon close enough
to
to basically make the moon crumble like
a little apple pie
so he was stuck
[Music]
well that works
well that works i didn't realize you
could make him do that oh that's so
stupid
oh my god
[Music]
i want to jump over there
oh what is that drawstring fire grace is
that uh the thing that you can throw and
that they were throwing at me
okay
who can't play this gravity game hell
yeah i missed his arm that's okay
um
okay well so now we go
uh should we try going up there what's
up there
[Music]
is there something here or should i go
outside
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
he saw me i think he saw me
are you strong all week i think you're
just a weakling
fight me fight me
okay okay just a weakling just a
wiggling yeah anyway so the moon would
finally uh like basically explode and oh
[\h__\h]
crumble into many many tiny little
pieces and would actually look pretty
beautiful
but uh until then
basically the whole earth would be
flooded uh with the ocean
[Music]
um thought i could run there
so
for you to survive during that you would
have had to
made it by a
kind of probably
uh
uh hiding in a in a underground
boat uh what do you call them ubot
hugh underground boat submarine
submarine
the german word for it is underground
boat uh ubud
uh
yeah and honestly not many people would
survive from that but but but but then
everything after that whole
apocalypse does he ever run out of
errors
after a whole apocalypse
you're like if you if you make it until
the very end then
then you can try um
re-populating the earth
repopulating
the earth will be your job
he's like [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] come over here
already
interesting yeah feel free to watch that
video
he's really pissed off this dude must be
really pissed off
okay
oh dagger is nice i like i like some
throwing items
oh god if i
jump wrong here we're gonna have a big
problem
i'm scared wait how about we just jump
here
that's that's simpler
and do not fall yes
so wait i don't know if i'm even going
the right way is this is just the way
they want me to go or the other way
what is this path
oh there's nothing here
ah except
this
this is the way
i hope he doesn't have a win
yeah multiple ways
be careful
this one is parkour and takes longer oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] wasted my daggers
okay
i'm eggs are careful because i'm really
scared and suddenly they come with these
jump scares and [\h__\h] i don't like it
i don't like jump scares
oh all these people are like pretty
wounded and dead
that's so hot ass
i'll help you be really dead oh
where did you come from
give me your give me your weapon the
shootie shoot one please it's cool i
want it
you should get yourself a bow uh i have
one um what was the problem
i don't know there was some problem
okay now we're here
where do we continue
that way
where does the
parkour continue
um
okay this reminds me of a different game
jumping up on oh oh god houses like that
we go this way left or right
[Music]
assassin's creed
on the right
oh
so dangerous that's where i'm gonna fall
[Music]
i don't
why are we doing this path man it's like
there's nothing here
like the most
difficult one
right
should i jump over there oh god i can't
even
oh
okay all right you can do it
okay
there's no item here
ah
no no that wasn't it i thought i found
the reason why i heard myself double
wait
is the item down here
keep going inside
[Music]
then i can't go up again
is that okay
i guess it is
stone sword key
a key
[Music]
now the only option i see is jumping on
this roof
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it was a phoenix apparently
i want my exp bag
you stupid ass boobs
mom to that
oh
oh yeah which way did we go
and we went up
no
not again
understand
[\h__\h]
stop i'm not gonna bother with the other
ones i'm just gonna um
i'm gonna go up
again
you're the camouflaging into the wall
wonderful
[Music]
what is that place
here i go losing my exp again
is there an easier way
is are the other perhaps that i'm seeing
easier like this one
secret area
[Music]
wow
it looks very scary
[Music]
is this way better
oh you didn't know that place what was
that oh
if
that's the easiest path this one
okay
hello bob
talk to me
i don't trust you boobs
i don't trust a single one of you
what
oh that's what that fire was
oh [\h__\h] you
i hate them i hate you
oh [\h__\h] i hate you
oh i see you too
oh god
[Music]
man
you're taking all my flasks
so these barrels are
dangerous
is what i'm taking from this better not
hit them
because there they might explode
with some fire explosion
yeah
i believe that
okay so oh so there's still more
parkouring but what is this looks like a
church
oh thank you go i really need some
golden runes because i died so much man
losing my runes so often
oh we can do a thing though
why would i want to do that alarm
everyone that i'm here
what do i hear boob trying to attack me
i'm over here
wait
what is that
programming why would the burp not fly
straight over here why is it going that
path
that is weird
that is not
what you should be moving around like
warhawks talon
he could have just yelled
come over here
okay i need a little bit of guidance am
i supposed to jump down that where that
hole is
here
i think so
yeah okay
is there something here
the floor it looks like if i jump on it
it's going to crack
i'm gonna jump to the side
yeah
oh it's really a church
there's some dude there
is it unholy to kill someone in the
church
i would suppose yes
it's an npc he's friendly
he does look friendly yeah
oh wait
is that our friend who helped us with
margaret
nice to meet you
the pleasure's mine yeah roger is the
name
a sorcerer as uh you might have guessed
roger
a little something
here in the castle
hot footing it from the troops that is
but enough about me
what are you doing here in storm what am
i doing here this place is bristling
with tarnish hunters you know
i know i know our kind
for grafting grafton
a place i'd stroll into without a
purpose in mine
what a hot sexy accent you have man
am i here to defeat god drink i didn't
know
that's the boss of this castle
i guess that's what i'm here to do i see
here to challenge godric i guess so upon
a great rune are you
maybe see it then i take it
the guidance of grace
well
enjoy it while you can
i'm tarnished like you
but unlike you i've seen neither hide
nor hair of this guidance for the
longest time oh that's lonely
i won't forget how it felt when i first
came here to the lands between
i'm privy to a few magical battle arts
would you care to learn one
it's a fellow just once guided by grace
i'd love to help you out oh please do
please he doesn't seem to remember our
memories together
i can't buy anything even though it's so
cheap
yes
[Music]
wait maybe um if i at least
i could try
should i buy one
i can't use it oh
he'll move later will he go somewhere
else
will i use it i don't know maybe if i
like something for
um
like a distant
uh battle uh uh
like you know like my firing daggers
something like that would be helpful i
can buy it at the roundtable okay okay
well now i have a thousand though why
would i not buy it now
because otherwise i'm just gonna lose it
again
i'm just gonna lose it again let me buy
something what is this i could still get
a little bit more though usable on small
and medium swords axes hammers
as well as pole arms and stay staves
spinning weapon
no that's not really what i want though
what are these those are not even
magical skills aren't they what are
these
i can slap it on my weapon
a spinning weapon so it will be spinning
like
like a beyblade
that's funny
now i don't know what to buy
the l2 button hmm
okay well we're there it was nice seeing
you
i'm glad i didn't have to kill anyone in
the church
where do i go now
why do i go now
this way
hold that way
flintstone
range attack yeah i want a ranged attack
let me just get some exp
even the tiniest amount is necessary now
oh
wait it's never one of those big boys oh
[\h__\h]
but the grace is so far away again
and there's two
where do they go
ah
ah those just should i run after them
yeah
well i have a bad feeling
a bad feeling
we're gonna turn around now
it's so fast it's so [\h__\h] fast
what if i go into the church
you can't find me in the church no
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
oh
he has to stop following me at some
point
i think he stopped
no i still hear him
no no no no
i'm back here
no he'll stop following me now
oh stop there why are you still here
i'm not here
why is he still there
no
what about now
is he done
following me
what
i was supposed to run past it's not too
late for that isn't it don't you think
it's too late for that
not here
are you just gonna wait there until
she's going ah okay okay
i think he forgot about me now i could
hit him from behind
he's still very uh hesitant to go back i
think
eh
can i
but this place is really dangerous to
fight
what what
is he just patrolling here now
no
[Music]
why is he attempting to jump onto
he's just patrolling here now
run past him
is there like a shortcut
can i jump down here that's just that's
kind of mother i would probably die
is that too much damage
although
i can first jump on that roof
isn't that a shortcut
it looks like i could make that jump
no maybe not
[Laughter]
can i no you can
[Music]
some people say yes some people say no
be careful he's still over there
[Music]
yeah no that's no it looks fairly close
but if you look at the gap then
no
ain't gonna happen
now
[\h__\h] i'm kind of stuck
i'm [\h__\h] up so bad
don't look back look at that
is he slow i think he's too slow to
really figure out this path so quickly
like me
oh
okay
yeah no way no way he can't do that so
fast
okay
what's awaiting me here now though
safe
wonder if he's still following me at me
now though
why am i just dead
i need i need a grace please
what
grace ahead
okay
where is the head
here
i don't see it where is it
look down there
i hate you
wait
wait where can i can we like
oh i'm scared
where's the greens
this is the way the spider ends
i only have one flask left
there's another one
stealth
we're in a spider
oh
there's a shortcut in the room of the
spider
oh hallelujah
yeah
oh man
why didn't you have to tell me to look
at this finder
you thought there was gonna be a golden
grace
i'm so scared
if there was a grace close by i wouldn't
mind fighting these but
now it's dangerous
what if i go up here
something's gonna kill
me something's gonna kill me is there
like a verb
where am i going
is it safe
why is that thing again you
you that reminds me of that a little
nightmares game that we played
[Music]
sorry guys i'm such a chicken
chicken they're going outside
climb
[Music]
down
down here
wait what do you mean word down down
there
no
no that's where we passed
uh the other side this side down here
it
i would fall pretty low
really
and then we have
not there
by the body body body body body body
body
here
i mean that looks like i could land
there but i don't think that's the other
side
you mean here no
that was that the same thing just in
wait maybe we
haven't been here because there's a mob
here
that we didn't kill
okay
why
why are we going there
i'm scared
i'm so scared
someone's coming
no
maybe
oh wait was there's a dude right there i
could open the door
i only have one flask man
one
open
open the door they say
open the door i'm going to die when i do
that
yeah i'm going to die if i open the door
[Music]
i just unlock it for a shortcut
and then go where
a permanent shortcut
is that a strong guy
hello
okay
okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
but now
this is the room with the spider again
there's a chest
i don't trust it no
no no no i don't
ah
is that where godric is what is that
gate
[Music]
[\h__\h]
would i wouldn't wouldn't there be a
grace
you're still alive huh
okay
go for the fog is the fog safe zone
but what about the chest
oh [\h__\h]
i need to go to the other room
i'm gonna open but uh
use the stone start key for this one
loot room not the fog not the fog
two dudes behind fog okay that doesn't
sound safe to me where is the other room
where is this bike
speeda
is it looking at me
it doesn't fit for the door does it
oh god
um
need to go back up right way right hand
side like right across
i'm gonna be panicking once i walk back
in there i need to know where to go
on your right go to the right there's a
lift
straight ahead and then doorway to the
right
um that where that there where it's a
bit brighter
hello
hello spider hello
my character's right yeah yeah okay eh
my cat yes yes
i have a bad feeling i'm gonna die here
and we're all gonna cry about it
cry about it
[Music]
can you go away
or or is it to the very right like right
here
no it's it's not evening time it's still
daytime
linda did you do this part
oh fortnight wait were you joking about
fortnight was a fort at night no it's
the fourth and day fourth day not
fortnight
crotch
no
[Music]
he's so scared
it's like right there
run
right here
here
this one there's an elevator do i take
it
this elevator
yes okay
and then
do i see the grace when i go up there
is there a grace there's no grace i'm
safe
[Music]
there's a grace
this is not where i came from
this is where i came from
so it would have been fine to just die
there because i already opened the
shortcut
oh what
what
ah
now i have my flasks back we can try to
kill those
the spider i desperately need some exp
man
i'm safe now
somewhat yeah but i feel like it
ah so i have to go through the for the
gray fog in order to um proceed
is that where we have to go through
yeah in the chest so let's kill that
bastard
is that thing easy to kill i hope so
now the elevator is unlocked
no
it's not the fog oh
optional loot
huh
okay well i do want to
shhh
[Applause]
ah
there's your face there's a girl's face
on it
trying to charm me
don't scream at me i'll scream back
is that a maiden oh man yeah going
going okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh it's like come at me girl
okay
good
were you angry
it's not amused i think
oh
attack when it screams
[Music]
i never
i never perry
you might i might just uh
do this
good for the first attempt
i definitely feel like i have a chance
go go go go
go go kill spider
that gave me a heart attack before we
need to pay back pay it back for what it
did to me
um
wait where's my body where's my body
it's my body
oh okay
okay let's do this
let's do this
come on
out
doing really bad
ugh
second try this was just a second
try we'll get there average day out in
australia
oh yeah i'm good that i live in austria
not australia
it's time like these where i feel really
thankful for that
this is like
a trial
for
the people who think they want to live
in australia you can give it a try here
and then change your mind
oh yeah mummy was drawing hajima and it
kind of looked similar to that you're
right
okay
it doesn't notice
when i run around like
oh this
the way it's really seems to like limbs
i think i understand why it likes to
attach it to its own body
i don't know
let's see if we can get the stealth hit
no we can't
apparently not
ah
hey
i need to cook my foolish ambitions to
rest again i think
it's like he's he's dancing
my first try was the best one
why
why was my first try the best one
because i was just trying just chilling
i didn't feel so pressured yet
i think
oh i got some oh
good hits in but
i was on the ground i should have stayed
on the ground
icon
it's okay
it's okay we're gonna get him
i hope it will be worth it though
beyblade deal
no blocking is
no
chihuahua playing elder ring
it just it's just not
something i do
i tried to get used to it
but it's not my thing oh bye bye
elevator
see you soon
yeah
let's just look at it as um i'm trying
to put myself
uh to give myself a challenge it's like
i'm giving myself a limiter you know
just see it that way
i'm trying to
make the game uh more challenging more
difficult
because i'm badass like that
where's my body oh okay
the challenge run yeah yeah self-imposed
rules
oh god you saw me
okay
okay first we need to clean the stage
out
oh oh wait except i mean i was at a
really good point there but
play with me play with me speed up
ah
about to die
does it do that when i get too close to
it
is that one that happened
okay okay good stuff
was the wall the wall was in the way
the wall was in delay
i think we got closer though i got i
wish i was stuck i think i felt like i
was stuck i don't know if it's just an
excuse but it felt like i was stuck i
got closer though yeah yeah
yeah
oh hello look at that
i brought the elevator back last time
because i knew i would die it was all
according to keikaku the plan was to die
where's my body this time
where's my body all over
ah over there okay
you're having some trouble there
you're too fat
you're too big
you need to stop
okay okay chill chill chill chill chill
chill chill chill
i know you're really excited about
having a friend for once
oh it screams when i hit its face baby
because it was holding its eye
as if i heard it
oh [\h__\h] yeah
can you stop
stop
maybe not necessarily because now it's
screamed again and i didn't do anything
out
[\h__\h]
he really is ours
[Music]
oh what did you eat today some funny
beans or something
he is
armed in many ways yes maybe
he maybe you can lend me a hand
too
yeah
deal with him
just kidding
um but are you playing on pc or ps5 i
feel like i would have known already if
you play on ps5
try disarming him thank you
thank you for that pun i wish i could
have come up with that by myself
wait is she even playing it
maybe playing it is not playing it
run run
ow
yeah she is okay okay that's what i
found
okay time to fight [\h__\h]
i'm sorry
[Music]
i became turtle
reject humanity
return to turtle he has some nice
looking swords though is that what i get
if i kill him
one of those swords
one of those toothpicks
yeah scream and sound and let it all out
oh it was black at peace oh yeah yeah i
i i like black at peace
but only really the old one the old
blackout piece
reyna is really strong in this game her
build can legit pvp
what
are you telling me dana is a gamer girl
i i i
i want to say my gameplay today is
really bad but that's because like
honestly
because it's been a while and every time
i don't play a game especially this one
for a week i really really really
need to
get back
get used to the controls again
it almost worked i feel like i almost
had it
but yeah i can do better elena i know i
i swear i swear
ow i can do better
i can do better
i'll just keep on telling myself that
maybe i will get better
yeah i am
i cannot can i really not backstab this
one yeah
that's not fair
[Music]
i tried i'm trying
stop telling me what to do
when it comes to fighting i'm trying my
best already okay
i'm trying to find the right moments to
do certain attacks okay so just
stop
please
hello
i got the first hit though
i got the first hit this time
would you mind cleaning up the hall
get it ready for our dance session
spider uh
today on the news local spider wants to
join kfb dance school
to get closer to hollow myth idols oh
[\h__\h]
turns out the spider was just a [\h__\h]
creep
ah
i'm too scared
i hate to stay so much in the way
i hate it
[Music]
but this is a good warm-up
if if there is a
the god rake battle if it happens soon
and this is a good warm up okay
ow
don't scare me like that
oh
it's like it's constantly using caps
lock oh god
i almost
i'm almost there
yeah i know i know i know stop using
caps lock
wait only one flask oh [\h__\h]
i'm already dead i'm already dead
speeder
huh it's not a spider that looks more
like a human if you look at it closer
[Music]
oh man
i don't i don't want to give up at this
point
i wanna do this now
um
you can do it
yes
yes i can do it
let me drink some water
oh so heavy
oh
my junk
oh yeah
okay
um i wanna go in when he turns the other
way but he already saw me
okay
[\h__\h] that table
yes okay
good stuff good stuff
[Music]
wait how am i at 98 did i at some point
not pick up my body
how am i at 98 xp i didn't notice and
which one did i forget to pick up my
body
or was it always just 98
ow
oh maybe it was always nine yards hmm
but yeah that was a wrong
place to ah
i
what was that
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] don't go there
oh
[Music]
he's stealing my room
that is that why inna killed him should
i have killed him
is that where my rooms are going
every time when i die is that what's
happening
what
every time
oh come on
don't kill me is needed for a request
later
he better give me something good after
the
what was even his request to me to go
for the castle
and then what
he keeps them from from you
for you until you kill him
i get them back if i kill him but you
know what then at this point it's not
worth picking up the 98
exp come here
[\h__\h]
huh
yeah
okay i really want to kill you
i really just want to kill you if i had
a
raged weapon would be really nice
i mean i probably have something
probably
i'll [\h__\h] i'm just running away and
doing no damage
i don't wanna
i don't wanna anymore
i suck
i just suck
i sunk
i suck
oh
oh my song
i sunk
if i can't kill this spider then i can't
kill godric either let's be honest
although with a helper
of my summon and my helper perhaps
ah
godric is easier
what if i just kill godwin first and we
kill the spider another time another day
we can come back here because the
the grace is so close
[Music]
and maybe we should do that
now which way is god rake because i
somehow ran in a circle apparently and
came all the way back here which really
pisses me off
where where is godric where do i need to
go i lost my patience i just want to get
out of this stupid castle
[\h__\h] through what
what
run past it straight ahead
ah there was something on the right side
like looking like a room
but i didn't see a door yet
um
passed by the left
oh left i thought the no there's
something on the right side need to go
left i don't see a door left maybe
there's a door
okay
past the spider though right not right
away left because that's where we came
from
oh i see it
bye bye
okay
nothing scares me
nothing scares me why is the music so
scary
[Music]
is it
is it here
up there
ah straight ahead outside what is here
though can i just get up to the second
floor
[Music]
i'll do that
there's an item over there
go outside and summon
what is it immediately there
oh
there's a lot of
peeps here
they're all looking at me too
they're all waiting for someone to come
ah [\h__\h] this is where it would be ah
good to have like a
arranged weapon can i make something
no what's that
i can make some of these
do i have
run past
is that really gonna work
i have two of those
um
maybe that's the lace what did dana say
squash is called squirrel squirrel
i rolled through them all
well if they can't do it then i can do
it too right
and just wait is that big thing sitting
in the back
godric nah god i don't even know what
god rick looks like i have not been
spoilered i mean i've seen some boss
enemies but i don't know which one
godric is
you did the same okay
which side is easy to run through
[Music]
i don't really see anything as easy but
okay um
stop being such a chicken kiwa
[Music]
oh
okay easy
why are you telling me this now
use furl calling thing a remedy to
reveal some signs of players from other
worlds but i don't
i don't have an online subscription
up up left left left left okay
very left or first up and then left
whatever
okay thank you
here
here here
yo
touch
wait i'm busy dog
now we can talk
okay this is okay
oops why am i turning off the light
if it just kills me then
yeah then it's outside again
go away go away
go away big ugly thing
touch grace
beautiful this is all according to
kekaku
okay uh so i can already smell god rake
i think
i suppose it's up the elevator or is it
here
that's not open from this side okay
maybe it's a shortcut as well
[Music]
my damage is low
i've been leveling but not in this
episode i haven't gotten a single level
up in this episode
i'll get some exp from godric
what do you mean use elevator to get a
shortcut is it just another shortcut
i want to go to godric
what is this sound i hear
something shiny
what are those
why are we still not with godring where
is he
oh
well there's why are they so
helpful with this now
one before
before i look for so many
braces and i couldn't find a single one
my empress outfit looks like something
out of this game you think so what do
you think guys
is it i think it's a bit too colorful
oh there it is
why were there three graces in a row now
they could have placed them way better
but okay
um
what are you
can you give me some exp
hey you're not godrake right you're just
one of those
dudes
[Music]
yeah i
i always uh
killed them eh
before
uh on foot so wow nice damage on the
enemy
and on on a horse until now
wait isn't he weak anyway yeah he's just
that's not bothering that can't be
godrake
come on wolfies
i'll be right with you customer
just
those are probably xp that i will lose
again though
unless i rest at the
at the grace and then do it over and
over and over again
yeah i'll probably lose those exp
hitto
ushi
um i mean that one over there
they forgot what they looked like
why is it so empty here is
just
such as hell
what is this golden tree doing there
okay
[Music]
npc in room
which room
that one
what do you mean in the room where i
where uh
maybe see on the left huh
what
oh wait
that's a dead dead npc
but smapping stone
there's a room here
it's closed
maybe you do mean that one
this one
be proud
a lady fine warrior me your only mistake
was your choice of muscle are you
talking to him that the winds left you
i'm talking to him huh
that's one of the dudes that
tried to kill me
why are you being so nice to them lady
well who do we have here tarnished are
you
very tarnished one of godric's lot i'm a
tannish turtle
nephili
like you oh by decree of my father
how utterly repellent this is
this grafting of godric's ill befits a
lord
he's tainted the very winds
i don't know what you're talking about
but i guess i should talk to you one
more time challenge godric i ask you
call upon me
the winds run foul with his deeds i am
gonna be my helper father would permit
me ate the fight oh sure
please
but i've idled long enough yes npc time
is over fished we must each follow our
own guidance
down whatever road takes us to the
throne of eldon lord
eldon lord
elden lord
apologies
eldon ring elven lord lord of the rings
fellow tarnished we must each follow our
own guidance okay you just say the same
thing now right so is she basically
saying that she's gonna be my summon
sniping stone four smithing stones she
is really strong
ooh so
you're welcome to help me and assist me
in my fight
is that a bird it looks so weird
let's go
what if i wouldn't have talked to her
would i not be able to uh to
call her
but i'm not i don't say anything to
somebody here
[Music]
does she just does it already is she's
supposed to be summoned already
pop some golden runes
uh
yeah i'm just ah here it is i'm just
scared that
i don't have enough to get to
what was it um
uh
what 4
800 or something
yeah
and then i'll lose my exp again let me
see how many i have
uh
golden rune
i feel like this is not enough
and it's not enough i'll just you lose
it
uh
[Music]
ah golden seeds too
[\h__\h]
there's knowing if i'm gonna lose it all
again
upgrade
upgrade weapon
and flasks
ah
[\h__\h]
increase amount replenished
yes
wait wait i don't have enough seats i
only have one scene
[\h__\h]
visit the blacksmith okay
okay
you mean i gotta go
uh
wrong button
here
to the round table
and my weapon is what plus
two my shield i upgraded a little bit
too but you guys told me that's useless
unfortunately
hey buddy
long time no see yeah i'm still playing
elden ring i have not given up yet
i took you for dead yeah yeah yeah
same to be honest um you know that dust
is life over phoenix
that's just how it'd be sometimes
plus three can i do another one plus
four oh
oh at least i made use of my runes with
that so now it's plus plus five
let's go
wonderful
hmm
where was it secluded cell
kokoda
plus plus no way this plus four but
is it plus four plus five
no no no no no i guess plus four
yeah plus four okay the next step would
have been plus five but that's still
pretty good we got two upgrades now
obviously
i won't be able to kill him first try
but let's just get to know him
i will i summon you
warrior and
i suppose the jelly would probably be
helpful again
i'm
gonna go with the jelly where is he oh
she cuts in
is the statue gonna come to life no sure
oh you are him
okay one two three four five six does he
have six fingers
yes six fingers what the [\h__\h]
can you lend me one
you have more than enough to let me cut
off one
he seems actually pretty nice man
oh oh you have more than six fingers
what is it with the people here who just
want a [\h__\h] ton of
limbs
i
am the lord of all that is golden and i
am the empress of all that is red and
orange and fire
and i shall kill you
perhaps
uh
[Music]
ow
is that your famous phrase
i don't even know what that means can
you speak english with me
the
unfit to be graft
what does that mean in proper english
i'm gonna go uh
oh sick burn
i don't feel that burnt
[Music]
oh wait
don't be so close to me
[Music]
wow
dance
okay he seems fairly easier than
margaret yeah
[Music]
what is he doing what is he doing
did he just rip out his arm
you're gonna become a dragon now
what
you're going to use his head oh oh it's
going to come alive
[Music]
zombie dragon head
am i gonna watch this phase two scene
only once
[Music]
what
you insane
but he's like
he is
poisoned
okay nephili is dead
pretty much
where am i where
ah okay you're killing my jelly now
[Music]
hi
i'm stalling a little bit
i hope
i hope that the poison does some good
stuff
don't get stuck
oh
ah no more flags
there's the boy somewhere else no it's
still there still there
okay thank god that is dodgeable
[Music]
i'm gonna stall as long as i can i don't
care
i know i should attack now i should
attack
um
[Music]
i'm running out of space
okay but for the second try come on
come on
follow my second that was my second try
right
yeah
turtle turtle strats yes i'm a turtle
i'm supposed to be slow
that's what i do
yeah once everybody's gone i'm once
again a chicken but he seems very
manageable
[Music]
i do wonder though if jelly was the
right choice
but for now
seems okay
okay let's try
to do some more damage before everyone
else dies
um
[Music]
oh
jelly is already so low low health
yes
[Applause]
yes let's go
i watched it again
i know i need to heal i know i know i
know i know
i tried but then the sequence came
ah there you go
i tried to
roll through it
oh
[Music]
this is
[Applause]
yeah
i went in really aggressively um in some
moments because i was like i gotta do
damage i gotta do damage i gotta do
damage
what great runes
the great ones you receive by defeating
shard bearers
have lost their beneficial power with
however their power can be restored at
divine towers wait am i not getting
runes from you but just something i have
to bring somewhere to get runes
is this one of those circles
is it one of the circles and i need to
recreate that elven ring logo
is is that is like like a puzzle
i can puff okay so wait is it one two
three
four no three three circles i don't know
maybe not many wrenches yes yes
so that was one of the big ones
the big big ones that was bigger than
margaret apparently but weaker though
however the power can be written see the
description of each great room to
discover which divine tower you should
visit oh
is it is that also like a dungeon
remembrance of fifteen thousand
remembrance of the grafted oh i didn't
even pick up my body
remembrance of the grafted what is that
what was that pretty flowers
margaret was strong at least before him
before he got um
nerfed
because apparently he got nerfed
rest rest
oh thank god this place looks really
similar to the market fighting space
just a bit bigger what is that dude
doing over there
is that the dude who gave me the side
quest that [\h__\h]
uh let's level up
he did get him before he got nerfed yeah
yeah so
i
i will say i am
i'm um i had a had a more tough time
because she was tougher too
bigger
and
strength
you can do one more
maybe one more bigger
what did i do last time
i figured it would be a 21
[Music]
more maybe more
now my stamina is fine i didn't really
feel like i was lacking too much stamina
let's do more bigger yeah
okay two bigger one strength sounds good
to me
yeah
endurance and abdom
okay noise
no
so who the hell are you
what are you doing
what are you stepping on what a pathetic
excuse for a lord you were
craving to the bone
is that god
like that it's so tiny after all that
grafting where did that get you
know
vicky you
[Laughter]
yeah step on him step on him do it
that's gonna he
minimize himself
oh
he deflated hello there are you the guy
this weasel was
goddrick was always looking down on me i
can see that boy bloody deserve thanks
to you ah yeah thank me i'll tell you
though what goes around comes around
what are you trying to say i had an ugly
heart
an uglier countenance and met the
ugliest events
thanks to me
now
i suppose i'm free
i can do one so i gave you your freedom
what is that worth to you huh
what is your freedom worth to you
sure you can but thank me
with money i suppose it is all you gonna
say
i can do whatever takes my fact what if
i kill this dude
can i
is is he the guy
who stole my runes
yeah bunny he looks like the other npcs
so i wasn't sure
he not missed out on this ah because she
killed him too early
now what if i kill him does he give me
back my runes
don't kill him now
he's a merchant
he's a questline okay let's not kill him
let me let's take a let me take a look
around
unbelievable i can't kill that [\h__\h]
spider nor can i kill those stupid
long-haired knights that have been
following me around however i can manage
to kill godric and market margit
and the lion lion dude whatever he his
name was lions something
why
why go back to the spider
you think
that i
am able to kill the spider now
i think it's because
for the bosses
i have more
time
[Music]
more
um
[Music]
maybe i should teleport
i should teleport
and some helpers who let me
take control of the situation
where was it
here
yeah the spider doesn't have summons
ah
[Music]
the tower
um
huh yeah here
no i want revenge
i want revenge
and now i have three extra levels
so who knows maybe maybe maybe we're
suddenly much stronger
tells tomato
i did level up yeah
yes i did
what was my level before i'm level 30
now
[\h__\h] speeder
no time to waste
i will kill you
so
hmm
oh
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
oh fancy a tactile is that maybe maybe
an attack i can learn from you
after that attack ends would be a good
attack a good timing to hit him
[Music]
i can do it i can do it i can do it
[\h__\h]
i thought like two more hits
and then
crumbling
[Music]
okay second try but but i feel i feel
better now i feel like probably the
reason why we couldn't get the spider
last time was because i just tried too
many times
yeah at some point
you don't get better you just get worse
that was a fine combo though
from the spiders
oh yeah by the way did you guys see
obviously you guys saw it the new emotes
you know asked a while ago
for a stream
if we wanted
any emotes
and i was like
actually
yes
i'm i am what
what
please opie
i was saying actually
for a while now i was hoping for tin
foil and the yawning mode i still need a
thinking emote though but maybe i'll
make one myself
yeah okay i was just like [\h__\h] no
dodging aloud anymore yeah yeah i killed
you and you dropped
nothing
and an axe okay
finally
the bleed came out of nowhere man
uh it's because i didn't waste so much
time
[Music]
in between oh wait you were alive
[\h__\h] where did you come from what the
actual [\h__\h]
i didn't see my hp
no
wait does the spider come back
i want to pick up my hp
oh
this spider comes back doesn't it
is one of or or does it does it
yeah it probably does
he doesn't come back
ahead of myself i was like oh we're fine
we're fun spiders gone we're safe
we're safe
it's okay though
it's really not a big deal
all right
clearing up this
hall
beautiful is there something secret up
here oh wait do you guys remember that
chest
is it up there oh hello
isn't it where is that chest that i
missed
i wonder
exile hood
there was some
chest that i uh almost got but then i
fell down
it was somewhere close by i think
no this seems so familiar
uh to the right it was in there
i fell down because of you not again not
again not again
pickle turtleneck
that's what was in there
i found something more cool
so oh another key
oh we can try going for that um gray
door
the the grain fog door is that cloth
brick by the way
should i
fall down where was that again
it must have been a must have been
somewhere
here close by
oh i'm scared ah
isn't that somewhere here
what oh dog
um
sorry to disturb
sorry to deserve sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
i'm i'm just looking for some directions
you
all of that flesh is probably rotten
chrysalis chrysalis memento
uh is is this dude
is that cr cry chris elite chrysler that
dude that's hanging up there
i got his memento
beautiful
i will take good care of it
quest adam
for the jellyfish girl
is that someone i met
i don't recall
a jellyfish girl
wait where the hell is that gray fog
look
rodericka jellyfish lady
here
so i know there's two people behind
there
i'm scared
but i just killed
i just killed godric so
i
i can do this
ah
yeah
oh [\h__\h] what what why can't i what the
[\h__\h] why didn't that go away
you look uh kind of big sheesh
oh my god
[Applause]
okay no they don't have much hp
okay okay okay sheesh
okay
okay all is good all is good all is good
another cool looking shield oh
iron wet blade that sounds new
cool
oh hello
oh it's really dangerous here i could
totally fall down
yeah
oh but there it's there is something
down there is that again like the secret
the secret are you alive
i think i'm done here
did you just say she oh yeah i picked it
up somewhere
i'm like a baby i hear some words
somewhere
in english and i'm like
even if i'm if i don't want to remember
it
i just remember it i remember
give it to the
you mean to the lady who gave me the
jellyfish um
what in one of the first
graces that we found
is that the way you mean
ah
[Music]
okay a dancer
i completely forgot what she wanted from
me um she must have been
uh
somewhere
was it here
no that's a church it was past the
church was it
do you guys know what it was called
you want me to go to the round table
she's at the round table now
what
why
yeah that's probably where she
originally was but apparently she's not
there anymore
i don't even know what she looks like
[Music]
oh my god
talk
that's an option
purchase
cool stuff
offer a belt ring
no no no no no no
ah she's still in the shack oh okay and
then i'm getting mixed uh
mixed signals from you guys okay i'll go
there but maybe i can again
uh do some weapon upgrades with that
weird
thing that i just got is that something
i can use
now those are of a challenger find them
well
oh did he say that because i just killed
godric
i know okay
i still need smithing stones what are
what are the
ones for that i picked up though and
what is that
oh golden
bird plus
one
on there plus one
change ashes of war
uh we have wild strikes what do we want
storm crawler
i don't know which one is the best to
choose ashes avoid changing your team
you can get a new weapon with this with
his remembrance i don't know what that
means
stormcaller
okay
uh standard
maybe
okay
just use whatever oh okay
um
what was it again
storm blue
[\h__\h] i forgot it again you guys told me
and i already forgot it again oh wait
was it here
no yeah here
oh
the shack the shack
new room
oh
oh well
lady
i know your father had never come back
and i honestly thought so too because i
didn't realize that i had something to
do with you it was a pleasure to see you
hmm
can you pass on a message for me
if you see the little chrysolids in
stormgale castle
tell them i love them
did i not accept her quest
i'm sure i'll be joining their club soon
what club
oh it wasn't the memento from the one
that was hanging but from the bodies on
the ground
ah
stop crying they will
believed in me
they all thought i'd make something of
myself me
who can't do anything
i think i'll head to the round table
hole ah perhaps i'll find my purpose
there
i think i'll head to the roundhouse why
do i never get rewards and
[Music]
she teleporting
oh no it's just uh her shield okay so if
i go to the round table hold now will
will she be there
and what
what will be
her job there
what will be your job ah there you are
warming up at the fire isn't that nice
that looks cozy
greetings
nice to see you again mm-hmm indeed
it's always nice to see me
i should have told you yeah you should
have told me because i had no idea what
the people in the chat were talking
about the round table hold
cover quarters of the two fingers and
gathering place of champions who vie to
become elder lord i never knew the
guidance bestowed upon us tarnished had
such fantastic roots
although
it's all a bit much for me in truth just
talking i'm still looking for money so
much purpose
what's your babies
please allow me to express my i will
allow that for giving me that keepsake
from my men
it was as if i was frozen with self-pity
you really got to like
force it out of them you have my
gratitude
golden fed golden seed golden seed
that's what i need right for my flasks
now i can get one more flash
talk to the blacks
didn't i just literally just talk to him
welcome member welcome egg inking oh
your divinity have mercy brought me
forgiveness
the road is yet long you good god is not
easily failed
but one day without fail i failed god
victory
so please grab your forgiveness queen
america
who is it not happy about it didn't
notice you there um i'll be doing my job
same as ever
do you have a side quest
what i talked to you about the prayer
those words were not meant for you huh i
may be prisoner to you tarnished love
but my prayers no to me you're not my
prisoner you're my uh uh
well the guy who does my upgrades
i'll be more careful too
are those two connected somehow the
question
can scarcely swing a blade
but she has a gift
for spirituality spiritual another one
like how long ago
their eyes share the same hue
okay
apparently that's all he wants to say
now
for
now they are connected
what have i talked to you again it's a
little bit much for me i'm still looking
for no that's the same oh tell me what
the blacksmith said yeah
i possess some kind of gift
i don't believe you you don't know it
how does he know it if i do have this
talent
and goodness knows it would be my first
i suppose i should try to hone it
shouldn't i
i'll ask master hugh to teach me
certainly he does appear intimidating
who is master no love for us tarnished
i know he's trapped here at the round
table hold
so
i can tell
the guy the gentle soul
him that she wants to talk to him or
something like that
yeah
about rodrika the cow
just you're like five meters apart can
you just get in one room and talk to
each other why am i the message bearer
are you out of your mind
you'd stay with an ugly brute who only
knows how to smith ruder sir
she's a nice girl besides she'd never
agree to it
she just talks a lot
what is that
when you assign an ash of war to a
weapon you can use it to change which
stats the weapon scales with
since your strength and dexterity are
almost the same you should set your
weapon to quality uh-huh
okay
wait i'll try to remember that i refuse
to believe it
i don't doubt you but i know when
something's too good to be true
ah triangle and square not a hold off
okay so now
go back to the girl
no i think we're done for now that's
weird
oh he can't move yeah but she can't move
she can go over
uh ashes over
quality
i i i i'm having a hard time like
judging these kind of
things i know when it's blue it's better
and all that but
besides that the scaling
[Music]
i don't really know but
i guess yeah it goes from d to c while
everything else
is not as good it goes from d to c and d
to c i guess that is better
re-enter
uh you have to go somewhere else first
not a big difference no no
still though
table of last grace i thought it was
called round table okay
and back is she still standing there
no she's not standing there anymore
did she walk over to him finally
are we done with the
no she's still like where did she go ah
here
oh
having a little picnic close to him now
you can finally talk without me
good to see you again doing it for you
thank you very much you are welcome i
have you to thank don't i
i don't know that's why you did master
hughes i guess so i can happily announce
that he has taught me the noble toil of
spirit tuning spiritually i was yet
unsure of what i might be able to
accomplish
but
if i might be able to help you all
i'd certainly like to try and if there's
any chance to ease the suffering of my
dear men who were grafted
well i certainly must try
rodrika the spirit tune apprentice
pleased to make your acquaintance okay
but what does that do
ah i had a
a feeling it would be for these babies
with the spiritually many you could
spend runes and grave glove warts to
strengthen the spirits you summon from
ashes
runes and grave gloves would you have
any
oh i do to strengthen named spirits
you'll need ghost glove word words yes
okay what a terrible word
it makes them stronger
i'll make the jellyfish stronger first
but wait how how much can i
see that
how much it was before
huh
yes i upgraded the jelly
but
i would need grave glove ward 2 which is
i guess a strong aberration but i can
also do the wolves then
i cannot see how much stronger they get
oh
i can't see the stats okay but i suppose
it's worth it because otherwise it
wouldn't exist i would suppose
how are you
feeling now that you have a roommate
here a pretty cute
roommate
i was gone for one second
no matter it's all the same
lay out your arms then
no comment really oh
i spoke with the girl
she has a gift for spirituality i've
noticed yes so i told her everything i
know good i'm indebted to a spirit tuner
i met long ago
it was all i could do to honor her oh
i'm sorry i doubted you
yeah i hope you become good friends stop
being so shy
and invite me to your wedding once it
happens okay
okay
okay i just gotta check
double check if they're really done
talking to me because
they just keep on talking talking
talking talking
talking talking talk to roger he gives
you ah
rosia
uh did he want me to kill godrick was
that what he wanted from me
uh where was he
in like a church church church church
oh wait i have to walk over there
there's no uh where's the closest
he's here
oh did he say that he was coming here
too uh
god god break tonight uh razia where are
you oh i found you
you stinky stinky
stinky little potato
ah
we meet again after all you need a
shower eyes for any offense given my
bearing but i'm quite unable to move you
see
so
what do you need what happened and i
want your hands to be on top of the
blanket not underneath please
ah you defeated godric and claimed
yourself a great rune
yeah
looks like we both got what we wanted
out of stormville i guess don't worry
well done friend
something to mark the occasion
ah go on
take it
looks cool
plus eight
yo
as you might have guessed seal i still
can't move
my fighting days are behind me yeah i
would have thought so uh that nothing
changed from five seconds ago
wait what happened
you can't stand anymore
what happened in the time that i was
gone
jump down
why would i jump down
his legs got cursed oh that's why you're
stinky
oh no oh there like some kind of curse
that makes it like a rotten
mpc boss oh okay
glint blade phalanx with frosting sword
cool
[Music]
oh cool
what's your
moss is there something to fight here
like a testing subject
invaded
oh but that's an npc right it's a wizard
oh you taught me about wow
all right a stabby stab weapon
magic is cool i kind of want to try a
magic character too
they do seem to be a pizza is there ever
like they seem to be really good with
bosses but is there other times when the
magic
characters are struggling too
like maybe with smaller mobs and like
neverow alleys or something they can't
be that lp right
i could respond later um oh i got
something from that
not in this game
yes yes yes yes yes yes
you not struggled
with what
you know isn't magic is she
basically as fitness ah so in exchange
for
um being able to use magic
like in other games they're a kind of
weak butts are they
he's not hard what the [\h__\h]
she's trying to live with uh this one i
saw but wasn't her in her case wasn't it
no npc but like an actual
player
because i think i saw her fighting that
but huh
there's an item what did i miss an item
why would i struggle with that
what why would i struggle with that
did they use the same weapon
i was why was that can he come
back wait come back find me again
it's always an npc
but i just poked him a little bit
i just poked him a little bit
i like this weapon though i like my
morning star too but i want to try this
weapon a little bit is it stronger it's
not strong is it
and my morning star
i mean look at my morning star
it's a
physical
109 plus 23
and what i'm carrying now is
oh it is stronger currently
the item you mean the shield
that i just did he dropped was that a
shield
oh
wait what did he drug
wrong weapon
what
you mean wrong weapon
ah this one okay but still uh 122 plus
yeah this one is still stronger because
i guess it's close plus eight but if my
morning star was plus eight then it will
probably be stronger
just because it's a [\h__\h] morning star
um
okay oh
i don't know what to do now
we
finished the
castle
what happens after that
i guess there's probably still some
things i could explore in it but i don't
want to be in there anymore i want to
explore outside
so
which way is it
huh no the other way
damn he really just
pulled out the head
damn
yeah
oh and you're still here i'm gonna keep
you alive um
you should consider yourself lucky
and be thankful
bye-bye item what item
there was no item there
few people at the wrong
do i still have to be careful
because i have 2800 runes i don't want
to waste it but that's a nice throne
although kind of a tiniest throne room
man
it's tiny
but the front looks nice and i can stand
on it
hmm
i've seen better frown rooms before
nothing was down from the blacksmith has
a free item
oh
item is worthless to my build naruto
why are we still in here let me leave
why did the light change
why is it turning so red
why is it so scary why is there no one
why is it so empty
[Music]
i'm so scared
am i almost outside
safe really
maiden dear maiden where are you
oh he had no maiden
oh big suffering
please take my griefs
ew
well you should have subscribed to a v
tubeler
they could have been your maiden
watch v2ba every day
grasp happiness outside
it's outside
read the grapes description
where is that grape
ah
yellowing oozing eyeball of the infirm
is his eye
that's not a great man
the music is so holy right now
we're on the other side
we're there
oh i think i heard that there's like uh
three different continents and this is
one of them
so
this is the whole map we almost saw all
of it good is this is this part not
filling up anymore because the table is
there
so i wonder if we're gonna be in the
next continent soon
i guess it's ah wait it's free
continents and there's three
elven rings
maybe
oh there's six oh
oh okay
leonia of the lakes
i was just trying to figure out
the logic i guess i was wrong
what is that girl over there
let me sneeze in your face
wait
i think it disappeared because i talked
hello
is someone there yes my name is
and i'm journeying in search of the
distant light distance
not so distant would you donate any ship
really great in your possession to me
eyes eyeballs
i can't tell which one oh will it help
you to see for a while when i eat one of
those grapes it's not like rape i can
feel a distant light in the back of my
eyes ew that's so disgusting
to my true duty
is a finger maiden
well i'll give it to you
but it sounds disgusting thanks to you
now i can feel it
i was kind indeed
the fingers be upon you thank you i hope
oh
i hope fingers will bless you too
soon enough
um
i
i will look around a little bit but i
don't think i'll be playing too long
after this
because i'm kind of satisfied with
killing godric
um
i just want to look around a little bit
i think and then we're going to read uh
super chats from a previous stream
no super chats uh
for this one
no no no no no i just need to
read once from before and i still didn't
tell you all about my
adventure in germany so i will tell you
about that
yeah fireside story where am i going
where am i going where am i going where
am i going
is that a friendly village or
not
ah
oh
i guess it's not
it doesn't seem to be friendly
okay that was easy
bye-bye see you later suckers
what is that
a grace
and
nothing's ever ever friendly yeah i
don't know like little villagers or
something
that would be nice
is everyone against me is everyone
like my enemy everyone these people are
not my enemies you're new around here
surprised you found me in my little nook
is that your bag scratcher
and he's as good as anyone else's
why don't you take a look at my that's
literally like an item that exists for
back scratching in real life now i've
got my hands on them
there's a happy village
i guess i mean there's the round table
but i want to see like a village like
outside that would be nice oh so holy
[\h__\h]
why did i never
see
this before why is the [\h__\h] moon so
close
and the sky is beautiful
he sells smithing stones
and some cool clothes oh astrology
[Music]
nothing for me a cookbook though do i
need that
24 hours left yeah it looks a little bit
yummy
[Music]
the moon looks beautiful tonight
you would not believe your eyes if 10
million fireflies lit up the sky as i
fell asleep
because they do something blah blah
i knew this is too beautiful to be true
i knew i knew i knew i knew it couldn't
just be that peaceful
they fill up the open air and fill
teardrops everywhere maybe also some
blood
as they try to kill me
it's pretty i like this
this
crystal bud
fireflies
very sus open area there
it's our dinner
oh
what do you call it again uh ling lingu
i don't know
oh
i'm gonna make some
dinner damn he can stab pretty strongly
too
lobster
strong lobster he doesn't want to become
dinner it seems i'm sorry cause we were
looking forward to some lobster right
i've never had lobster before oh it's
daytime now
it still looks so pretty holy [\h__\h]
looks even prettier almost i think
i'm not sure what looks better that
looks really good
it i checking it
ah
the light holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
it looks so nice where is my body
oh there
oh i don't know what day
uh
what time of the day it is right now
what is that that you pokemon
i will kill you
[Music]
unlimited great gravy supply
oh
yeah yeah
yes
i take it back we're having lobster for
dinner after all oh it's just a strip
really from that huge body we get one
strip of flesh
that's not very much that's not very
helpful
how am i supposed to feed one million
chickens
with that
huh
purified ruins
wait we're getting so close to the tree
what the [\h__\h]
why can i
[Music]
why can i summon my
my things my my friends again
why
are we talk
can we just talk
quick talk faster
oh [\h__\h]
come out one and all from the darkness
on the ground
and let us offer onto the maiden our
eyes oh another eye
what you don't want to give me your eye
think about where we're going
before we grow old
papa
what is that
interesting area it looks really nice
really pretty
what are those swords
oh that's the map that's the mouth
that's the mom
no
this marks millennia's southward march
the blade of michela and her clean
knights grant her wings never to be
clipped
i thought i thought this was one of
those map thingies
what it
is not damn
oh but there's a grace
i'm coming for you
so far there's barely any
enemies around
zinzentiki
look on the map
what am i supposed to see here
ah this is where the map thingy is right
let me get rid of the
other ones
okay
over there
i can see the map on the map yeah i kind
of knew that
i thought i found it by accident though
[Music]
is this really the right way yes
flask upgrade near the finger maiden oh
you're right i i i i have two
uh golden seeds
let me get off of my horse and then the
olivia
appropriately
oh [\h__\h]
disgusting
okay
oh it's because i killed a grip okay
okay great for violet uh-huh
and now we get the map
map leonia east
nice
new map has been found leonard east
oh
it gets bigger like that i thought it
was cut off there that was the end of
the map
that's a weird piece of map though
hmm
oh it's just because uh
like this will uncover anyway when i hit
but no
i'm confused
but we got the map that we were looking
for
and i think i will
go here
much much bigger oh really i thought
that was it
and i thought that you just um changed
the
continent or something
i thought that was
just like they see a different map then
but okay okay
this is better
and flasks shouldn't i be able to add a
charge
yes
we got seven flasks now
wonderful
i'm gonna do this too sake or two do i
have one no okay
okay cool
yeah i think i'll end it here yeah i
don't feel like playing more today
but i will read super chats and i will
uh from a previous stream to make it
clear
and i will uh
talk about the rest of my location we'll
talk we'll talk about that first um
that is the skill apparently
to the l2
l2 but isn't that the the skill on my
shield
i have to do this
ah
oh wait how do i
how do i use that what is that
how do i make it
wait that actually looks familiar didn't
one enemy that i was fighting use this
ah that will attack an enemy
automatically once i walk into it
how about this one then
go
oh
[Music]
oh it doesn't even take up that much
mana
it was stinky stinky stinky stinky
stinky
[Music]
yeah that looks cool
good stagger for finisher well at least
now i can
it's somewhat of a ranged attack
although i had to get pretty close
for it to work
i don't know i can't stop running around
oh but
almost poisoned
let's go here again
um
yes i wanted the ranged attack
okay
we will rest here with the donkey and
the weird
santa claus in yellow with the back
scratcher and the butterflies beautiful
my new friends
everyone's here
you and batman are the only holy members
of stream right now oh bottom is
streaming and yeah she always streams at
weird times but yeah usually
sorry my european gang around this time
it's usually not many people streaming
although
maybe normally even
maybe normally it would be a bit more i
think a lot of people said okay youtube
is being a piece of [\h__\h] today so let's
not stream
of course it's vata who else would be
streaming
[Laughter]
oh my two favorites ah
that's lovely
but while we're here at the fireplace
ah
what where did i leave off last time
when i was talking about
um
the food that i ate in germany and
dusseldorf what was the last piece of
food i showed you
i showed you
[Music]
the tonkatsu right i showed you the
tonkatsu and the meron soda and the
taiyaki i think i showed you the taiyaki
too
so that was in the evening we brought
that home and then we watched tv i told
you uh everything up until that point i
think
i think yeah
and then and then it was the last day we
woke up and we got breakfast and
then we uh packed our stuff together
chilled a little bit more in the hotel
room i think and then we
then we checked out
and
that's when
oh yeah i i brought
me and rmt
to
a bakery
there is
there are two japanese bakeries
in germany dusseldorf
um
[Music]
and you might wonder wow what's so
different between a japanese bakery and
a normal one well i mean
yeah it's
it's not that like insanely different
but they have a few original
things that they sell there
uh we went to both of them but
interestingly the one that's on the
big famous street
was way less crowded
probably because they also didn't have
much more in stock at least at the time
when we went there
but the other one which was on a side
street from that big famous street
uh
that one has had a line of people
waiting
and it was like after
after lunch time
um
were they pretty close to an actual
japanese bakery i would say yes
yeah actually from what they were
selling yes and also the the the
um
the staff were speaking japanese as well
and there were actually also a lot of
japanese people standing in line it was
either it was 50 japanese people and 50
weeps just trying to get some
japanese bread
i i wanted to get some bread um
just because not because i think it's
like so much better than our bread here
um i think i generally prefer
our bread from bakeries but but i wanted
r t to see like what japanese
bakery what a japanese bakery is like
and um
and also because it was a good
yeah
thing to pass some time
and
my plan was that we buy that bread first
then go have lunch and then the bread
uh because we had a
flight some
time in the afternoon the bread we could
eat like
um
at the airport or in the plane or
afterwards for dinner or whatever that
was my plan
yeah is the merchant listening
you're listening
[Music]
listen
so this
is all the breads that we
bought although there were some
duplicates that are not in the picture
uh
so
from
courtney i don't know
so on the very rack you probably can
recognize it's a meron pan with
chocolate chip
uh
chocolate chips yeah
uh in the very middle is a curry bread
i bought that one because i know that
that's the good stuff there's like a
curry
mass of curry inside and the outside is
a little bit crunchy but i had to warm
it up you have to heat it up
you can even get it freshly heated then
it's a little bit crunchy but i had to
reheat it at home it was still delicious
but it lost a little bit of its
crunchiness but i really love uh karepan
khariban naga
the one below that i think was the
shukurimu
uh that i got in the not so popular
bakery uh the meron pan as well
i think you can see the difference uh
depending on the packaging
the meron pan and the top right one
i don't know anymore what that was
because
uh that was something that rmt bought
so i'm not sure
uh
and then the the middle
top one
i think
i think is a really really cute shape i
mean it's basically just the bread with
some chocolate inside but it's such a
cute shape
so that's that's what makes it special
then on the top left i think that was
also a metal pun but a different one not
with the chocolate chips
yeah it's the coronet colony
chocolate corona
[Music]
yeah i think i first got to know that
when i watched lucky star that was my
first time getting to know a coronet
and then below that was like a twisted
sugar donut
uh like kind of fluffy
uh
it's yummy but it's not like it's like
super super
like
specifically something japanese but i i
bought that quite often when i lived in
japan as well yeah yeah
go in
and then the bottom left
is a teddy yucky burger the moment i
stepped into that bakery and i saw that
there's there was one teddy yucky burger
left and i was like rmt i'm sorry but
that one's mine that one's mine that
one's mine and i woke up with it quickly
and grabbed the dead yucky burger and
i'm like yes
i got the rare
yucky burger
[Laughter]
yeah teddy yucky burger
i ate it after
coming home
what is that it's just a burger with
teriyaki sauce
in in japan um
in the japanese mcdonald's they have it
on their main menu on their default menu
which we unfortunately don't have
overseas
yeah
yeah you gotta be quick to get the the
best stuff there
we stood in line by the way for
30 to 40 minutes it felt longer it might
have been longer i feel like we might
have been standing there for an hour to
be honest i'm not sure
yeah the line was especially
slow because um
they were only letting in eight people i
think
uh at the most into the store
due to the sea thing um
so i think under normal conditions it
wouldn't be that bad and also
something i figured out later on
uh this was a saturday so maybe during
the weekday it's not that bad
but the reason why it might have been
even worse on saturday uh not just
because it's a weekend but
apparently
every weekend
uh
there is a gathering if i understand
correctly
uh of like
you know
people
japan fans and cosplayers and weeps in
the the big park where that big
convention happens which is somewhat
close to this uh japanese
city street
in the city center um
yeah apparently it's every week
so
i think probably what they do is that
before they go to the gathering or
afterwards as well they probably go to
the street get some bread or get some
other dinner lunch whatever and then go
to the
go to the
meeting probably
um
that's probably why the line was longer
than usual
yeah i heard it was every week
well we went to the park on the day
before uh
on a friday
and it was pretty empty i mean we saw a
small group of people there
uh that looked really edgy and they were
doing some
weird thing with fire they were like
they had some fire on i was like what
the [\h__\h] are they doing what the [\h__\h] in
the in the japanese garden
yeah
what
what what what
what did you say that was so funny
i rang out what what is what does that
even mean i'm not gonna say that out
loud anyway i'm glad i bought the bread
because even though i didn't originally
intend it to be my dinner uh i got home
pretty late so it did end up being my
dinner
and the curry bread was so good it was a
little bit spicy but it was so good
it could stop
very good so we did that first and then
oh
uh rmt
picked up this
at the bakery as well wait one second
red beans uncle
um i was like i'm not sure you're gonna
like it arm tea but i think it's worth
trying because it's something very
popular and common in japan
it's basically japanese sweets
so
you should give it a try
[Music]
yeah it's red beans azuki beans
that are just not really
common in austria to be used for
anything and also i mean mochi itself
sticky rice
yeah so it's really new
for someone who has not
um eaten much japanese food before
she
gave it a try
i think she actually
uh
may have finished eating it i'm not sure
[Laughter]
um
i prefer
[Applause]
mochi with different fillings um
[Music]
oh you know what i like ichigo daisuku
that's that's something i can enjoy
i die for mochi now
but i thought it was better for her to
try this mochi
than
which was like handmade by japanese
people
with the proper ingredients and all that
then trying the frozen ones that
recently they do sell in our
supermarkets yeah
um i thought it would be better to try
the original even if maybe the
supermarket ones are more adjusted to
our taste buds
um
but but but you should try the original
yeah giving her a little taste
of japan
and we talked me and rnt talked about
this on our trip and i completely forgot
about this because it never actually
happened
but um when i was in japan
right right before i left rmt and i were
talking about her uh joining me in japan
for a little trip like when i went there
to be there for one year
um
that was before the sea thing was
breaking out and she was planning on
visiting me while i was there just for a
little trip
and we were planning for that and she
was like
uh
looking up hotels and all that and i
recommended her a hotel to stay at and
all that and it never happened
because then
soon after i or immediately after i went
to japan
uh this evening broke out and she had to
cancel her trip and therefore she never
came to japan
so this was
a little opportunity for me to give her
a little bit of a taste of japan
to
in exchange for not being able to go
there
[Music]
and then we went to an izakaya
after buying the bread we went to an
izakaya it's like a
a mix between a japanese restaurant and
a drinking bar thingy
where you drink alcohol and then order
lots of yummy food and then share it
with people
um
and it's one where i've been to
before and i wanted to go there again
because it was so good last time
problem is
we got we got our seats pretty quickly
but they were really stressed out and
they didn't let us order much
um
before uh the their lunch break the
restaurant's lunch break
um
and i underestimated
how hungry we were
so uh
and how much it would fill us up but i
ordered
some yummy gyoza and uh
i wanted tamagoyaki but they didn't have
it on the lunch menu so i had to order
this uh
tamago nigiri or something like that
uh from the sushi menu
and
but that was really good anyway because
i got my tamagoyaki just with some rice
extra that's okay
and everyone was all the staff were
japanese in here too
um
and they were wearing typical izakaya
uniforms as well this was something that
rmt ordered
it was it looks really good but i don't
like sushi so that's that
then and then and then i ordered as
some
uh
some of these
yeah
yakitori
i think the restaurant was called
kushite
uh and cushy is these um
what do you call this in english again
restaurant
is like a place that mostly focuses on
skewers and yes they had a lot of
skewers on their menu the sauce was so
good oh i love i love the sauce on these
skewers because it's like so thick and
so strong mmm really really good sauce
[Music]
but then
they kept on stressing us out even
though like when we entered they said uh
the the last order is that time but
then they kept on asking us earlier to
the order because they're gonna
uh
not let us order anymore even though
there was still some time left until the
original time that they told us so i was
really stressed out and i didn't know i
didn't know because the food didn't even
arrive yet how would i know if this
would fill me up
if the food didn't even arrive man they
didn't give us any time to think about
it like basically we sat down
and the first thing they say is
this is your first order and your last
order
yes it might be a bit early but no more
orders afterwards we're really stressed
out today and i'm like okay [\h__\h] but i
don't even know how big the portions are
because the skewers were actually kind
of smaller than i thought they would be
would you go back yeah of course um but
i would go a little bit earlier
so that they give me more time to order
and think
and eat
now but they were nice they were so nice
the
the staff was really impressed about my
japanese
i wanted to enjoy the japanese
atmosphere so i
i i ordered in japanese and they were
like oh
wow
nihongo joseph but like for real ojozu
it's like i have this dialogue like down
that i can
basically
say it while i'm sleeping
so
after that we still had a lot of time
until
our train and our flight um
and
we were still a little bit hungry and
they closed they kicked us out earlier
than i thought they would so
um
i looked oopsie and i wanted a dessert
so
there was something that really stood
out to me on that street but it was not
japanese so this was basically the the
only or the first
non-japanese food that i ate on this
trip
um
and it wasn't even food
[Laughter]
let me show you
on that same japanese street there are
some restaurants that are not japanese
restaurants this was just like an
american
burger restaurant and all that with some
insane milkshakes
ah
it looked it had so many it looks just
crazy they were huge they have these
huge
things on top that you can't even reach
the milkshake first
okay
yeah and i saw it and i was like rmt
i know
i know that i will get sick from eating
this but i need to eat it anyway
and i asked rmt to share it with me so
we shared we did share
um we tried our best but to be honest
this was a cookie dough milkshake but um
to be honest
um
the cookie dough thingy on top
tasted kind of weird so i tried to
combine it with everything else like
they'll
eat the cookie dough at the same time as
drink slurping the milkshake and getting
one of those chocolate chips as well
and then it was somewhat edible but it
wasn't even that good but i wanted to
eat it for the experience okay
dough can be weird yeah uh
it tastes kind of weird yeah
so i i drank all of the milkshake but i
left a lot of the cookie dough
uh on the side yeah the milkshake was
fine in itself
but
yeah that's okay they had some amazing
looking burgers there as well but
yeah i didn't think i could handle a
whole burger at that point
and then we still had so much time
uh and rmt was saying she
really craved some coffee
and i looked up where there is good
coffee close by and there was one
literally on the other side of the
street
where the reviews were saying that this
was where you get the best coffee here
like absolutely amazing coffee
um
[Music]
and it looked pretty nice like interior
wise it looked pretty good too
well i didn't get coffee
i got tea
but the tea
was amazing too
that was amazing incredible and they i
was looking at them making the tea
and
they weren't just like
you know putting a [\h__\h] tea bag in
there and waiting a little bit no
yeah in the hotel
in the hotel called number four fear
in germany
i did a cycle that
was really really good this was uh a
fruit tea
with
i think hibiscus
and something else
it was so good i actually got two cups
because it was so good and because
we were sitting there for like one and a
half hours wasting our time until the
train leaves um
then i was like i've i felt like it was
rude if i was staying for so long to
only drink one cup of tea because it
only took me like 20 minutes to drink it
um yeah so i got another one because it
was also really really yummy
it's so good it was so good and they
made it so well and the coffee rmt said
that the coffee was amazing as well
so big success i would say
yeah
would you say it was divine it was
exquisite and divine
yeah we were chilling in a really comfy
lever sofa
and oh did i tell you i might have
mentioned this because you already know
about the hotel so i guess i already
mentioned something like this
but then yeah i mentioned the toilet
right they had a japanese toilet there
when i say japanese toilet i mean one of
those um
automatic ones
that can like purify your butt
[Music]
yes
butt shower
a true throne yes i mean
i've seen even more advanced ones in
japan but this was definitely uh one of
those japan toilets so
that was surprising to see and they had
they also had like hairdresser hair
salon seats there for some reason um in
the
in the lobby and they were selling cup
noodles at the reception
it was an interesting hotel um
interesting hotel
and that that hotel is right on that
street
uh
on that
japanese street
which is by the way
right at the main train station
of
uh
of of dusseldorf yeah
i think that was it because after that
we
after that we went to the train station
but turns out our train was like
one hour late
so after already trying our best to make
the time pass
german trains are not as
exactly on time as they claim to be
because we were sitting there for
another one hour
trying to pass time
but it just passed by so slowly
deutsche bahn
but
big brain moment
um in the morning time
when we were thinking about which train
to take rmt gave me two options either
we take the train
where
um we would be perfectly on time for the
for the flight and wouldn't have to
waste much time in the airport either
or we would take the train where we
would be
one hour
uh too early
and would have to waste one hour at the
airport um this is not considering the
check-in time
so that that would be extra as well
um and i was like ah
you know what
it would be so comfy to just arrive
there and then walk into the airport and
go
but i have a bad feeling because the
trains could be late so let's go
with the first one and the second one
the one that arrives too early
and makes us wait one hour in the
airport so now we see that was a really
smart decision because our train
had one hour delay
[Laughter]
yes
so then we arrived at the airport at a
pretty good time
it was really smart a good call from me
yeah
um
it was a good call
i had a feeling
i had a feeling people
have this image of german people being
punctual and i think they're trained
being punctual too but they're not
they're not none is uh wrong information
out there
it's macho yeah
so that was my food trip the second part
of my food trip um or the last
last little bit of my food trip to
uh germany and i would do it again
anytime because the food is so good
yeah
hopefully next time i'll combine it with
some i don't know going to dokomi uh
privately
perhaps
oh my god
there's so much cat hair in my in my
glass now
no where'd you come from
[Music]
was it on the outside or on the inside
it's on the outside
okay
pouring pouring
all this talk about food makes me hungry
again
[Music]
and
now we finally have that
uh
taken care of i will
go to an idol meeting and then i'll see
you in my office for uh the continuation
of the super chat reading from my
um
from
basically from the live concert yeah
okay
okay i will not open up super chats
again no no of course not
i just finished reading the ones let me
make it very clear i'm just finishing
reading the ones from before
can i read them by the fire
and you gotta go to my office
yeah yeah i don't want to have this on
screen forever
need some bgm
because there's a lot to go through
i need some bgm
sonata
yes yes okay see you
in a little bit intermission time
[Applause]
feel free to stay if you need someone
to cure your loneliness i am here for
you
[Music]
um i'm gonna make some tea so it's gonna
take a little bit longer
[Music]
i'm back
are you still here mother
are you still here
oh
seeing you here
i got my team a big jug of tea
how to close game
i never close the game properly
let me tell you i really like the the
new layout of my office now it was it
was so um
it was not really
fought through originally
when i first
put furniture into this room i i wasn't
sure how i wanted it to look like
but now
now there's much more space
yeah friday kiana still here let's let's
keep her here because
it is just a beautiful thing to look at
yeah you guys don't see it um
that's because i i i didn't change this
side of my office i changed the other
side of my office
you know i'm in my real office yeah yeah
oh did did that not come across properly
yeah no a patsy i remember that
uh
no
and yeah
oh i also bought a new plant yesterday
welcome new plan say hello everybody to
the new plant
and i had to give one to my mommy
because it was dying
uh
so i i wanted to make up for the lack of
that one plant
and i got a new one
yeah yesterday
yesterday i got a new plant there's no
name there's no name for the plant no no
no i don't name my plans i'm not
uh at that
point yet
where i know there is people that love
their plans so much and have so many
that they give them names but that
that's quite qu quite the planned otaku
like not even not even my mom gives her
her plans names i think because she just
has too many
is there anyone here who gives their
plants uh a name
it's a pretty big one though the new one
that i got it looks really pretty i hope
i don't [\h__\h] it up again
you know what kind it is ah
you know what i looked it up yesterday
and i think i can tell you it's uh
ah
ella
i looked it up if it's um
poisonous for cats and no it's not
i named my cactus kiata
oh really yeah
and that plants those would die here
relatable my name mine tim
just kidding ah
everything has a name everybody needs a
name no no
yeah plants are cute of course you have
to name them are you serious
wow you're one of those huh
a banzai bonsai tree
but you mean bonsai tree
bonsai is the word tudo you probably
just typoed bonsai is like when you
raise your arms and you go like
i think you meant something else
let me um put up some music
[Music]
and eat a fruit can because i am in pain
it kind of hurts right now
it's probably the screams again man the
alden ring screams
elden scream
i can't drink my tea it's too hot still
i have one soccer touching what really
yeah are you kidding me you have a
sakura tree
do you have like a big garden
you know recently it's been getting so
hot like not hot but so warm and the sun
has been coming out where it really
feels like
spring is here
it's beginning to look a lot like spring
time
feeling really warm
time to take out those skirts
out of my closet
and look really
cute
outside
luckily i changed the background it's
fitting now
[Music]
i don't know what music to play
um
[Music]
what is this again
oh
and i don't like this one
this feels like something that would
play in yakuza 0 now in the disco
[Music]
oh
yeah i mean i've seen i've seen
some
plum trees so far but no sakura
[Music]
it's spring music it's not really spring
but it doesn't really sound like spring
music but yeah
um i probably won't be playing alvin
ring for the next two weeks or so
i don't even know if i'll really
continue anymore after this well but for
now i think i'll take a break from it
[Music]
just so you know
um
i'm hoping to be able to play tune tunic
tunic
sometime soon
um and
uh i might even want to give kirby a try
for one episode because kirby is coming
out this week are you guys planning on
playing it it looked really cute in like
the
the demo looks really cute i saw someone
play the demo
[Music]
i don't know if if kirby is kind of
difficult for someone who doesn't play
those kind of games what do you think
[Music]
not planning on playing it
maybe games are
one episode yeah it could be a one time
thing although
maybe a one or two episode kind of thing
ruby is really easy really
is it forgiving oh yeah i think i saw
there was like an easy mode
it is an easy mode right i saw it
and kirby's just so cute man
mary go forward hit button win oh maybe
even i can play it
um for tunic i know it's really
difficult i know that it's kind of like
similar it has a similar style to uh
like like for example
the old zelda games
like dungeon wise and all that and
riddle-wise and and perspective-wise but
but it's much more difficult so i might
be having a lot of problems with it if i
play it
which is okay which is okay because need
some challenges sometimes it could be
like my
my new um
i forgot what was it called the austrian
game that i played uh having a little
brain
empty moment
um ori ori
could be my new ori where it's really
difficult
but i'll actually get good at it and
feel so proud at the end of it for
finishing it
i can see that happening
yeah orient the blind forest
so that and then there is some other
things i've been trying to
make happen
um
[Music]
i invited some girls from monopoly
around soon
because
um
recently very recently
i
i feel like i've kind of
awakened
towards
all these cuteness
i i see some cuteness in ollie now that
i really haven't seen before
but i feel like she's so so so so sweet
with how supportive she is
so i wanted to invite her to collab i
was like olly we should collab yeah
and she was like yeah let's do it
quinana senpai and i said how do you
feel about playing monopoly with me and
some other girls and she said yes let's
do it
so then i also invited elena
and ame because ama didn't play monopoly
with me last time
so that's the new
group of people it's a weird mix i know
but
it's gonna be enid monopoly
[Music]
i i said to ame even though she wasn't
in the last collab but i was just
saying it
in case she saw the last monopoly collab
i said to her
i promise i won't be as salty as i was
last time
yeah i just wanted to do some kind of
collab with ollie so i figured i also i
was like i want to collab with ollie but
i also want to collab with reyna so
let's just do a big collab
a fairly big collab
oh and uh
should finally happen soon i got an
answer from subaru
but and this reminds me
i didn't get an answer from the other
ones so
let me
remind them
um
is dead
[Music]
hello
oh
huh
welcome back
you were just giving me some space right
so i could message
the birds
you were just giving me some space right
you live on your onion
okay okay
oh by the way
uh
to all my sea viewers
on sunday
um austria is
going to be having
daylight savings time so i will be one
hour closer to you guys
so
my streams might be a little bit easier
for you guys to catch
a little bit
summertime makes me
able to get a little bit closer to you
guys but i think that also means that uh
streams for america
are going to be a bit earlier
right
or not
i'll be one hour close
[Music]
if i start my streams at the time i
usually started wouldn't it be uh
earlier for america
no earlier for
sca
later for america
so it's good for everyone
wait i'm confused but
i'm confused
uh
one hour earlier for everyone
yeah
yeah so you guys do have to
come to my streams one hour earlier
maybe
i don't know but on on my schedule i
already um
thought about the fact that daylight
savings time is happening
so the time on sunday is correct
at the moment
i know me too
um
summertime summertime
i missed the eldering part oh
you have to watch it afterwards i guess
yeah uh i need to read super chats to
finish them
uh
yeah
let me pour some tea i think it's okay
now to pour it and then wait a bit
longer
now it's really hot
it'd be really hot
i'm drinking out of one of um
those cups that ina talked about
yesterday i was watching her stream and
she talked about iris's cup that has
those like
spikes
i have one of those but in the shape of
like
it's it has a cat face and the other one
has um
this one is actually it looks like a an
alpaca or sheep
face and has those ears at the top of
the the mug
but it doesn't poke my eyes out i don't
have any problem with it
i don't have any problem drinking that
out of that cup
alpaca cute yes it's a really cute cup
hmm
no i'm drinking a different tea for um
fruit and pork
how are you not blind yeah
it's really not that difficult to not
get your eyes poked
you gotta act really stupid in order to
make it poke your eyes i think
and especially with um monks like that
you usually drink something hot right
so you kind of drink carefully and you
don't just like chug chug chug chug and
when you drink it carefully i think it's
really hard to make those ears poke your
eyes
just sipping yeah
sorry i'm trying to
give some time to my throat but
[Music]
it's still not feeling
that great
let me put up the thumbnail though
of the super chats that we're reading oh
yesterday until like all the time until
the stream
i was uh the whole time i was feeling
like i'm doing a yakuza stream
so yesterday i even already made the
yakuza thumbnail and then i put up a
yakuza reservation privately
and then i realized wait a second wait a
second wait a second i'm not doing
because i'm doing elderly but then still
today in the morning i also felt like
i'm going to play yakuza i feel like i'm
really motivated to play yakuza but i
made a really great pumpkin for yakuza
do you want to see it
so great it's a good one it's one of
those legendary thumbnails
three two one
i already know what i'm going to title
it it's going to be
kikkity kiki or butts
[Laughter]
you know what the way that the
the characters fight in that game it's
pretty fitting because we fight with uh
our bodies rather than with weapons
mostly so
um it's a very fitting pose for a
fighting game
no we're reading super jets from this
one
okay
[Music]
um
okay okay
oh [\h__\h]
bumble design is my passion
yes
may i paint my car by kfc of course i
saw i saw your tweet
yes yes yes of course i was like
gotcha gotchy
of course but i'm surprised they don't
have like that many choices like they
only have like a few
colors that you can pick from
that's kind of weird like why can't you
choose whatever color you want then
um
it's like a
otaku car
and when you when you put like some kind
of anime
characters or whatever on your car
then you call it itasha also for example
do you know
have you ever seen like when
the otakus have like these bags with
millions of pins and badges of their
favorite character on it that you call
an ita baku
basically everything like that where you
decorate something
in like with your oshi or with like an
anime character or whatever you call it
ita something something
paint car
yeah
yeah eat the kimono from la podasso as
well
i think a lot of people have that that's
easy to make
people like to use like a bag that has
like a see-through plastic um front
so then behind the plastic front you can
put the badges and stickers or whatever
and then you can
yeah
see-through
and but the badges are protected because
they're behind the layer of the seafarer
plastic
i never had one of those i like to put
like a few small things here and there
but not like a i i don't
completely cover
the whole surface of something in
anime badges or whatever
[Music]
are becoming really popular
in the u.s
okay now let me open my super chats
before i fall asleep
oh i think it was in reachable distance
patch
scene
um which one there's four
[\h__\h]
[Music]
there's four
ah
ah wasn't it was it ah
before i hung bao
yeah i said something like that
ah
i found it okay okay
perfect that helped me
okay
reading time
wow thank you for the rest of the chat
amazing performance tension you rock the
stage with your fury
i still don't know how to read that is
it theory or fiery
fury fiery fiery
fiery fiery
fiery
fiery fiery fire fiery
okay
fiery
fire passion and dance i'm so happy and
proud to see the culmination of your
hard work and dreams viva la quianga
thank you
yeah
thank you thank you thank you
i'm really happy that the performance
um like really it came together so
nicely with how they put up all that
fire in the background and all that
and the song and the band and everything
it was just perfect
perfect everything was perfect
i was really happy that
it just all came together really nicely
and
like everything was on fire it left a
fiery impression i think and it made it
clear to people again that i am a
phoenix
not a chicken
hmm
it looked like a deep fryer
what
there were some moments when the
background really looked like the shape
of a phoenix
but like those
things that
um
when you go to a
mental
therapist person and they show you a
book and and they're like what does it
look like to you like some kind of ink
blob
inkblob
that's what it looked like to me like a
phoenix but so uh
what's the word
what's the word for it again
abstract yes so abstract that
it doesn't look 100 like a famous but if
you you can see it you can see it
an abstract phoenix
it's so perfect standing in the middle
of that
singing the song that's literally titled
phoenix
yeah hong bao thank you
julissan
foreign
the stage i can't put it into words how
amazing it was to see you singing and
fully dancing up on stage your
choreography was amazing i'm just so
happy to finally see the stream of yours
come true and then i could see it live
cover you piano oh thank you
i cough you too that's a really old
old insider that we have
thank you so much for supporting me
and cheering for me thank you there's a
vault
[Music]
i cover you
ah
so much cub in the air
kiwa club
oh my god cub forever
thank you for the pinky congratulations
stencil and your performance was amazing
pure fire hell yeah
you look so confident had such
incredible strength can't wait to see
you soar again soon no words to express
how i truly feel oh
but i think you expressed it nicely i
just clucking love you my talented ocean
ah
i clucking love youtube thank you
thank you so much to vitori
glad you enjoyed it it was very much
fire
very much pure fire on stage thank you
did i look confident
i was nervous though but i guess you
can't really read it from that face
need that um 3.0
facial upgrades
to really show how nervous that was
but to be honest
as i thought
it's like so short
and um
let's just say that
and this is somewhat true anyway
when all the lights the spotlights are
on you on the stage
it's to be honest really hard to see the
audience
it's really hard to see them like you
get really blinded by the spotlight
and that kind of helps a little bit i
guess
you can't really see much of them
you just try to look into the distance
at least in places like these
now even in smaller venues as well it
really depends on how the spotlight is
um
uh
uh shining at you
um you gotta tell the
uh light people whenever there's like an
mc portion or something
to put the spotlight on the audience so
that i can see them properly
yeah
but that's one thing that
i like about uh outside venues
and i thought about this when i saw some
fan art the other day um
[Music]
from
whenever korean uh viewers
it was me outside
performing on an outside stage did you
guys see that
i went to some concerts where
um they were performing outside too and
those are kind of rare but
um
those are really fun because it's so
refreshing i mean if it rains you're
kind of [\h__\h]
oh i'll show you
i found it
this one
this one is
[Music]
when there's good weather then it's
really nice if the weather is [\h__\h] then
you're kind of [\h__\h]
yeah
would be nice i don't know if that's
like possible for us ever to perform
outside on a stage like that but it
would be really cool
because it gives you completely
different
um like more open vibes to it like in a
in a big venue like this
sure it looks cool when everything's
dark and the light sticks light up but i
think outside venues
are really nice too it's really
refreshing
[Music]
instead of the light sticks
you can see people
throwing around their
merchandise towels
and also you can see the the colors of
their oshi t-shirts
much better if it's like an idol group
then every idol has their own color so
everyone wears a different color t-shirt
sorry i have something in my eye manny
nanka haiti
you can see people actually jump more
easily
for example yeah
one thing i want to implement in the
choreo one day if it fits the song
is like um
because i really enjoyed doing this at
concerts where i went to
is like a part where everybody takes
their towels that they bought from the
concert merchandise
and
um like
how how do i say rotate it in the air
rotate rotate rotate through the chorus
or whatever and then there's this part
where everybody goes like
and you throw it up really high up in
the air and you see air all the towels
in the air and then you go you try you
got to try uh catch it
but yeah
those moments are always so much fun
in concerts
yes spinning the towel above your head
like a helicopter and then
throw it in the air and try to catch it
those are some really fun moments in
concerts yeah
um
i was also worried that i would miss but
it always worked pretty well
no no no you don't really
it doesn't really happen
that often that you like lose your towel
and that
unless you just
even i and i'm really bad at throwing
things
even i was able to throw my
uh towel
not too high but still up in the air
straight up there so i could catch it
even i was able to do it so it's not
that difficult
apart from games yeah you have to
clarify that didn't you
sure sure
sure
i just chunk it forward that's not how
you do it no
you're disqualified
papa
i bought a link your wish towel yeah
they had towels like that the the long
ones
uh the the
narrow long ones but they didn't really
use it at the concert they should use it
they should make use of it would be so
much fun
rotate rotate rotate and then peel
catch
it avocado
logical paradox thank you for the pinky
actually two pinkies you were
interrupted it seems
10 to your performance was just
absolutely delightful seeing you up on
stage was wonderful divine exquisite i
was awestruck by the dancing and singing
and the kickity kicks man you got me so
hyped thank you
oh and and my only regret is not
recording my reaction actually i went
full chimken roaster mode
so it's probably for the best i didn't
record myself your performance was the
absolute highlight of day two for me
thank you so much for everything thank
you i'm really really really really so
happy that i could make such a positive
impression
i i didn't expect that
you know so many people also non-kfp
people were saying that my performance
was one of the best on that day
and i i really feel so flattered and
honored by that yeah
everyone did great so out of those
people to leave such a great impression
i'm really happy because i'm usually not
the one that stands out that much um
so yeah
i'm so glad i was
i was being acknowledged like that
it's a great feeling
that
[Music]
thank you guys
thank you
i'm so happy i really wanted to leave an
impression man
oh boy
already looking forward to the next
chance
when i get to perform
i actually
because i was so motivated um i
commissioned
or started commissioning
um
two new choreos because sparks didn't
have a new core
sparks didn't have a choreo yet and the
song that i'm working on right now i'm
already planning one for that as well
just so that i'm ready when i need it
more more dances more dances i need a
dance for all of my car for all of my
songs
i can't just go on stage and just do
step step step step
no
no no
it's gotta be something special
[Music]
so thank you logical paradox for the two
pinkies i'll give you a kiss for that
judy thank you for the pinky mate thank
you congrats kiana your dream came true
be on stage
with your senpais and gemmates
amazing performance i'm so proud of you
i cried after your dance coming from
that high cheering
you on screen
sorry to my housemate oh
again i'm very happy and proud of you
thank you
really glad to hear that and yeah sorry
to your housemate um
maybe maybe maybe uh you already told
them about
your big love kiwawa
and i i think they were
they would be understanding if they knew
that
it was because of such a huge concert
going on
there was a good reason for being loud
and cheerful
a good reason for that
yeah yeah
thank you so much i'm so happy to hear
that even from home you guys were really
really excited to watch and
and for cheering for me
um
on the other side of the world on the
other side of the screen
looking for the top thank you for
two red ones
does this add up to a special number
uh
250. i guess it doesn't really mean
anything doesn't
long ago i promised i would give you my
500 virginity for 3d but i didn't expect
you to have a 3d concert before debut
ah
so i'm splitting it in half
here take one half of my 500 virginity
what does that mean
oh because it would be your first 500
super chat
interesting i did not know that that had
a specific term
i guess we can have a virginity for
everything
jokes decide you've done so well all
this time every sacrifice that led you
to the stage today you sounded like a
blazing star but i want to see more of
you me too
the goals list is gone reduced to at
homes but the support you deserve is
just beginning viva
here until the end the concert fired me
up
pun not intended or pun attendant
thank you thank you thank you
okay you promised me something i didn't
even remember that so it's not like you
had to follow up on that promise i don't
think anyone remembered it but i guess
the promises are promising you you stay
true to your promises wait it was a pun
yeah i don't know cause fire
the concert fired you up because there
was so much fire on stage now
i guess the pun was not intended
it was not intended but you still made
it happen
uh oh your employee number
ra uh uh i wanted invisible ink and i
can't remember it anymore
that is
i i however of course know your uh
employee number
it is
zero
two
four
zero two four
small number
because
you're here since a long long long long
long time
[Music]
do you like shrek
um
i prefer donkey
but yes wreck is okay shrek is cool
[Music]
what do you call this genre
disco
70s 80s disco
is it 70s or 80s
[Music]
oh by the way if there's anyone here who
wants to make me um a new weapon for the
pr snow because um
i
i uh
i've used every other weapon and the
ones the old ones most of them are with
my casual outfit arms
um so i can't use them with anything
besides my casual outfit
what do you want um how about um
some uh
like a
[Music]
uh some some some tools to put together
together furniture like a screwdriver
and and and what do you call it so
the
it's not a screwdriver
another hammer a wrench yeah i think i
mean a wrench
and
but what else what else could be nice
i'm running out of ideas that's my
problem
it could be something that's not even a
weapon but we make it into a weapon
a banana
how about a banana
a banana is a weapon in mario kart so
can i can you
put a banana in my hand
[Laughter]
banana banana please
it will be my weapon catchy banana it
will be perfect because uh because yeah
we have touchy banana
[Music]
banana
yeah banana
oh one more idea how about a cactus
that's a weapon
a cactus in my hand
but the bottom part should be you know
um one of those pots
okay so wait forget the first ones
banana and cactus is better
for for that i would be covered for the
next two episodes
i feel like since we've had so many
weapons now i need a new weapon for
every episode
because i've been doing that for the
past yakuza streams
now i feel obligated to use a new weapon
every time also for the thumbnails
just just this once
i i will have the thumbnail be the kiki
kick but then i will also go back to the
usual pattern
and i need more weapons for that
[Music]
for which arm uh uh from from my side
the right arm
would be good but i can just flip it
anyway if there's no writing on it then
it doesn't matter
[Music]
hmm you didn't use the flamethrower
it was probably either because it took
up too much space
at least at the time
and now it's probably because uh i
didn't i either didn't find it or it's
because it was a casual outfit and on
the on the thumbnail i have this outfit
so it's the wrong cufflinks
a spatula i'll take anything i'll take
anything
the sliver i used the shoe before
if that's what you mean i used that one
before
yeah screwdriver ranch banana cactus but
maybe start with the banana and the
cactus
[Music]
oh a crowbar have we have we ever had a
crowbar i feel like we might have not
have a crowbar before
oh one more thing we could do is like a
seal like one of the i don't mean an
energy seal but i mean like one of those
seals that he used to seal a demon
[Music]
there are no demons in yakuza so far but
who knows i mean with yakuza i expect
anything to happen
[Music]
oh and another cute one would be maybe
just me holding up one of my cats with
two hands
and then i'm going like shark
[Music]
my cats will fight for me
okay i have many ideas
[Music]
oh now the ultimate weapon
because it looks it looks um
i i want it to look dangerous but
actually it's just so cute so every
enemy will be just like oh
and then walk away
they will die from cuteness
okay right super chats
looking for the top i didn't give you a
kiss i think
it's been a while since you got a kissy
i think
did you miss it
thank you for your support
thank you very much
thank you for the red super chat
was at the venue you see him you see him
i see him i see him i know exactly which
one he is
[Music]
now
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinkies uh
actually that it adds up to a red one
did i give it a kiss
[Music]
so casper is right
i'm so proud to call myself your fan
[Music]
thank you
um
oh you you're you're the fan in my
kimono outfit
sorry i wanted to make a joke
[Music]
oh oh oh stop throwing tomatoes at me
no
i know it wasn't funny okay i'm gonna
leave the stage
oh
stop throwing tomatoes at me no
boom she's back hey
hey
i'm gonna pour some more tea while i
have the time
i'm like tea tea oh
titty
[Music]
baby
yesterday i watched some
twice fan cams for some reason they were
suggested to me and i couldn't stop
watching because they were just so
beautiful the girls are so beautiful
not really the type to watch fan cams
but
i was intrigued
and couldn't help it
[Music]
do you have a favorite
not really not really i like um a couple
of them
i don't really have an oshie
sorry to say i know it's boring i know
you guys always want to hear who is who
i
i don't really have someone who i stand
in the group i think they're all great
kiwamo fan cams yeah that is something
interesting that's something i can get
into
my bias
[Music]
now from twice i don't know it's
probably because i didn't get too much
into anything besides besides their
music i don't know their personality
that well
um
[Music]
let's change the music
i want to change the music any other
kpop groups we got into only girl groups
and the wonder girls
sing
what was that group called
they don't they don't do stuff anymore
[\h__\h] i forgot the name
uh
mamamoo yes i didn't mean them though
oh is that a group called again
i zone yes but i didn't mean them either
exit yes but i didn't mean them either
ah
[Music]
dammit what were they called again of
course my brain
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no the one where they had some drama
that there was apparently some bullying
it came out that day and there were some
bullying problems uh aoa yes
that's the grave that i really liked
them
they were [\h__\h] hot
really sexy
great super chat i'm trying to one
second
yeah okay i'm not a machine
[Music]
oh
that's nice
yeah i like a lot of uh
the female
k-pop groups um but i'm really just like
on the surface level surface surface
level just listening to the music i
don't really know much about like how
what the people behind it are like
because i i don't understand korean so i
don't really i mean there's some
subtitle content sure but there wasn't
that much back in the day i would say
there's more now definitely
[Music]
where was i what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah just write the first sentence to
make a joke
whether it's some silly little joke or a
creative stream idea of yours or one of
your amazing super collabs or you
rocking the house down an amazing 3d
glory you are always treating your
chickens to something special the fact
that you're such a genuinely good and
caring person makes you makes being your
fan all the better we're only about 1.5
years into this journey and i can't wait
to see what the future holds and please
remember whenever you're going through a
hard time no we're supporting you
however we can if you ever start
doubting your talents remember us she
can support you for a reason the praise
is more than well earned
hey i am takanashi
and i'm awesome there now you praise
yourself too
you think i think you're smarter or
something like that huh
[Music]
yes
oh and when the well-deserved kiwawa
solo concert eventually happens might i
request you seeing girls girls girls no
hey that was a joke
that was a drug song but maybe i make a
song until then in my album
that has the same title but it's a
different song maybe it will be like a
party song like girls girls girl let's
get down on the floor let's dance girls
girls girls give me some more yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
and it will be a reference
to that old girl's girl's girl's
[Music]
joke like a summer
type of song
[Music]
what
crew what
[Music]
but mostly crew who the [\h__\h] is that
don't know who that is thank you for the
membership welcome
egg
mayhem some wait i forgot to kiss again
i think mr caspix thank you
thank you for the kindness and the sweet
words and for following me
on my journey for such a long time
thank you for the red super chat
congratulations i hope you enjoyed
yourself your performance was brilliant
thank you for everything since your
debut it's been a blast despite being
largely vaught gang oh
but you're donating in pounds you're in
basically in my time zone aren't you
i'm excited for what having 3d unlocks
for you in the future
um
oh i'm excited about that too
maybe
no i'll shut up now
don't tease too much
tencho
um but yeah i hope you can catch more in
the future um catching them live is more
fun i think but still thank you for
watching the voice that's important too
you're making an effort to make time in
your busy day
to watch me
anyway and i appreciate that thank you
so much hope to see more of you though
thank you very much
[Music]
four two eight nine donkey sharing petsy
duncan
[Music]
wait
that's it
isn't that where you started where i
opened the superchats again
[Music]
because that's where pet scenes again
and i see some super chats that say
super chat to time i add more super chat
now
wait where is the date
[Music]
there's
did i do it
[Music]
so it's unbelievable
i thought there was way more
doesn't seem right
is there anyone who says that the super
chat hasn't been read out loud
from before i turned them back on again
[Music]
because i said when i turned them on
that i will only read them in my private
time
which i read some of them not all of
them
up until now
[Music]
cassette is near the end yeah and patsy
i remember that the last one before i
turned them on again was the patsy super
chat
[Music]
e-i-e-i-e is a 3-million noise
wow
wow out of
nowhere last time you said you were
almost finished i was kind of
but i ended it at a weird spot huh
[Music]
i think
there was a bunch of greens and yellows
near the end when you turned to free
chat before you disabled them
[Music]
what no but the last one was patsy
i'm i'm not sure
my yellow super chat was last
[Music]
there's another petsy one from that day
i mean yeah i saw more but
[Music]
wait
ah i see one where his pet whether his
patsy and crayons are tasty
[Music]
i don't know this is this is this might
be it yeah
[Music]
this is possibly it um
really but what are those like the ones
that say
[Music]
huh okay
what happened
ah wait i think i understand it now okay
i think there's a couple more
[Music]
i love your confused noises
i have this thing that
i really hate um
being quiet on stream for more than uh
like two seconds if there's nothing else
like like a game going on like then i
can maybe be quiet for a little bit
longer
um
but in a situation like this i like to
fill
silences with some noises
to keep your attention span of to to not
give you any time
to like go somewhere else
um
you don't say
you know i know you know
i don't want dead air even if it kills
my throat man
[Music]
never
never will i rest or be quiet
[Music]
jangling those keys in front of you
no no don't worry i usually always
recover after a few uh one one hour
honestly after one hour after the stream
my throat is always
back to normal
[Music]
i just need like a moment
where i stop talking
like an hour and then everything's cool
[Music]
i worry current generation's attention
span is not being challenged by
providing consistent stimuli okay it
might that might be true but i'm i i'm
trying to do my part i might not be able
to suddenly flash my boobies to keep
your attention
but who knows what what we will get with
live2d 3.0
who knows
what possibilities might open up to us
oh just the word of me just me saying
flashing boobies got everyone's
attention
words are powerful
very powerful see see look at the chat
girl
look at them go
[Music]
baited
ah
okay so let me continue we should still
be close i think to the end can you
thank you for the pinky words are hard
but like you
but like you ah oh where's your heart
but like you were incredible you killed
it you were beautiful and i'm dead no
kyo's dead [\h__\h] absolutely perfect the
stage was bloody made for you oh oh
those those british words
i can't wait to see more of you and 3d
together with the others much love yeah
i'm proud of you thank you
thank you thank you thank you very much
i hope you come back to life do i really
have to give you one of my precious
feathers huh they weren't supposed to
die so soon
it's too early come back come back also
here you gotta
be um in
my other yakuza playthroughs in the
future as well
so need you this is just my second one
stay alive stay alive
having a cardboard cut out of you with
already
[Music]
if if that's what you want to do
do it
[Music]
but
no pressure man
i mean i feel like it would be fine if
it was one of those like otaku weddings
you know like uh there was one
that was like final fantasy themed and
they had like the sword or something
from
some final fantasy character i think
stuff like that like it would fit in
there
but in a really really normal
normal wedding
if there's suddenly a cardboard cutout
that would stand out weirdly
[Music]
you might as well add some more
cardboard cutouts in that case
give me a plus one give me a plus one
don't let me go alone i don't want to be
alone i want a plus one and my plus one
will be
[Music]
jamma too yeah but um it's hard to get
like a full body picture to
um print out in the cardboard form
why not both okay give me a plus two
yes please
[Music]
uh
moose fabulous red super chat moose
thank you i love you that kicker cake
and dance you are the dancing queen so
proud of you tanjo thank you
yeah it seems like i have gotten a
reputation now
of being a dancer
which i don't mind um generally dancing
is fun and
all but
i do i do dance much much much much much
much much less than i used to
years ago
so
i'm feeling a little bit pressured now
a little bit pressured but at least i
mean
i think i think everyone in the whole
life is mostly busy with streaming
so
it's not like i
have to be a 24 7 dancer
i think there's like
a bar that's reachable for me
[Music]
thank you
now during the vr thing i didn't really
like tone it down like i tried to be
slow for them
because i know how tough it is to to
learn a choreo uh
for the first time um
but also i was just like really debuffed
with the vr headset it's
it's painful
i really
um
i'm in pain during that for many reasons
it's really stressful but
trying to make the best out of it during
those vr collabs
like i mean just just the normal vr chat
collabs were already exhausting and then
at dancing and all that to it
and talking constantly
giving commands trying to
you know
motivate my girls
it's quite a challenge
[Music]
i think this is when i came into the
chat
and everyone was like
chidi duncan jim chase duncan red
dankest from smiling bread dankesh and
black friction buddy
june 9th thank you for the red super
chat
wait a second
you you often forget your super chats i
feel like
i like to order a kick and a kick please
and thank you
joe knight coming right up
it's like my special move now it's so
perfect we coined that word a little
while before
that concert and i was like why did i
not come up with this earlier because
it's like it's right there it always was
right there
kitty kick
such a great word and now it's just it's
like my special move
[Music]
it's like my ultimate yeah my signature
move
[Music]
everyone knew what to say i didn't even
need to tell them to call it a kicker
cake suddenly everyone was saying
yo
it was so obvious
[Music]
gotta push for that whole fighting game
yeah like a tekken tekken style whole
life fighting game
[Music]
um
now originally we came up with it before
the concert but like during the concert
everybody suddenly started using it
[Music]
it was like intuitive for everybody
yeah
[Music]
thank you tonight
fantastic cute cool
can't wait for more live 3d performance
yay thank you
thank you i hope i can do more soon i'm
working on it i'm working on it and
there's
there's still some things that are
unclear and that i don't know how to go
about
um but yeah i'll try my best
please wait a bit more
thank you thank you thank you ah a
thanks for supporting and watching the
concert
[Music]
bob dylan
spicy chicken taco thank you
soon
boohoo seven two three done
now i've reached the end yes yes yes
now we're there
[Music]
oh
yes you did you need to chat were you
drunk too
why you guys not remember your super
chats
why are you guys so surprised
thank you thank you
thank you guys for the insane support
for the concert it was only one song and
you guys go crazy but i guess it was
somewhat of a debut so
it was a really exciting moment
thank you brilliant
way too much
oh just tired ah that's understandable
well i really really
am happy to hear that i made you guys
proud
and that you really enjoyed it really
makes my heart feel so warm
it was the song yeah
yeah i'm really glad i chose hinotoni
um
i think it was the right choice
i mean it's kind of like my theme song
afterwards it's it's a song about the
phoenix about a chuni bjorn phoenix
the title is phoenix i feel like that is
just the best way to introduce myself
like that on stage
[Music]
feel like my dream my own dream coming
true when you performed
very strong impression
it was the first original song yeah a
very very special song to me
[Music]
we'll continue to make your heart run
with our love and our pride thank you i
said it before i think last stream but
i'm also really proud of you guys
yeah
i'm really really glad to have you guys
such a sweet and loving and caring fan
community that i have
everybody is so loving
[Music]
sounded even better than live
performance
thank you
i'm glad you think so
a great source of nutri
hey
no no no no that's not what i'm saying
[Music]
i'm made to be on stage
i'm definitely very happy and blessed
to get the opportunity to be on stage
yeah
anyway
so i think tomorrow is another day off
for me
i'll chill
i'll chill and record something
um and then and then and then we have
yakuza
on the day after
yeah
finally
enjoy your day thank you guys did i tell
you i think i said it maybe in the
beginning of the stream but i made
french toast this morning last night i
was like i want pancakes i want pancakes
or something like that with berries and
all that [\h__\h]
ah
and then i woke up and i was like okay
i'm not gonna make pancakes i'm gonna
make french toast because then i gotta
use up my my toast bread
i haven't made i haven't cooked anything
in a while especially breakfast because
i was i'm always so lazy in the morning
i just wanna eat something quickly
but
i did it i made really yummy french
toast yeah
my french toast is really good
i like my french toast more than the
ones that i have eaten in like for
example in that really
[\h__\h] fancy hotel in paris
yeah which i think is crazy and it
reminded me again
so shocking the moment when i found out
that french toast is not something that
came from france man shocking
i was so shocked
i'm sure some of you guys didn't know it
either
[Music]
homemade is best
yeah
i mean i don't think that's the reason i
think they just didn't know how to
properly make french toast i guess
because it's not something from france
had the same misconception
yeah that was last year and my trip to
paris is when i asked my my french
friend
oh french toast no
what's franchise and i'm like you don't
no
but you're from france you don't know
what french toast is
she was like no
then i'm like wait
what the [\h__\h] i showed her and she still
didn't know
i feel like even if you if it's not from
france
french toast is quite a well-known
breakfast so
shouldn't it be shouldn't it be pretty
well known i guess not i guess maybe
everywhere but in france
they know what it is
oh yeah right because it wasn't called
french toast
it's called something else yeah
something like bread something lost
bread oh yeah right
lost bread i'm gonna go to
france
again
i don't want to go again but i want to
travel everywhere i want to go to so
many places
eggy bread that was the problem when i
ate it um
at that hotel
it was so soggy and soft and eggy
but it shouldn't taste like
pure eggs
it's not supposed to it was that's not
what it's supposed to taste like
[Music]
the egg shouldn't overpower
the
whole
toast
toast before salt exactly if your french
toast ends up too soggy then the problem
is that the bread wasn't hard enough
before you put it into the mixture or
you pour the mixture over it so if
you're working with fresh bread then you
need to toast it before you pour the
mixture on top of it
i sound like such a smart chef
the chef with s i am lucifer
[Music]
yeah i mean yeah if you're making eggs
on toast or something like that then
yeah
make it taste eggy
but
french toast no no
[Music]
chef with s please guys
there's a important distinction
chef with s
[Music]
you poured water directly on the bread
no not water what the [\h__\h]
five-star breakfast from
first myth of kalam
ah me cooking on an enough collab like
that no probably we would be really
silly speaking it would probably be
hotel breakfast or something like that
or we would just go to a cafe i don't
know
who knows who knows if there's a kitchen
available
maybe we can all cook together
although
if it was in japan it's probably a small
kitchen
and it probably won't even fit all of us
in the kitchen
hmm
if it's like a kitchen in the hotel or
so
apartment like some hotel rooms
have a kitchen
with it yeah
[Music]
you should cook for ami when she visits
i will but i will give her the choice to
either sleep at my place or sleep in a
hotel if she wants to if she wants some
privacy i totally get it like yeah
she can sleep in a hotel if she wants to
or she can sleep with me if she sleeps
in my place then i will make her
breakfast
and then for dinner
i'll bring her to a fancy restaurant
do we have a guest room yeah my my
office is my guest room i have a bed
uh a bed that you can
even make into a double bed
in my office perfect i have a guest room
yeah
and your best host
i mean i'm all a talk host for a reason
yeah
[Music]
he had an airbnb
hotels don't have cute cats easy choice
yeah i agree now that definitely gives
me extra points
yeah
and we can watch a movie before going to
sleep or so
yeah i need to talk to
ame about when exactly she's planning to
come
because i don't know
[Music]
it's been six hours only
only
i didn't play for so long today that i'm
sorry about that but i don't know i felt
like you know it was a good point yeah
we did stormville we did god drink so
huh
yeah
we killed a [\h__\h] spider
stupid spider
i'm getting really hungry now though
actually i have a snack here i prepared
a snack i have uh like salami sticks
yeah but do i want to eat it now or am i
gonna i don't wanna cook immediately i'm
gonna cook later
[Music]
i'm gonna eat one of those
but i'm also gonna probably leave you in
a moment
oh
by the way guys my
my old
old
chihuahua
is coming along nicely or it's basically
actually already finished
i can't wait to show you
maybe i should ah nah nah let's keep it
let's keep it as a surprise
and i'm even gonna get it animated
a little bit like not like live 2d but
like moving and
blinking and smiling a little bit
um
is that from the collab
[Music]
no
actually no but i will be able to reuse
it for that
actually
um
i'm getting it for something else
but i will also be able to use it for
marines and by collab if we're doing it
yeah
oh talk lookie mama
no no
no no no let me try to eat this i want
to eat this i'm sorry
let's get rid of this
[Music]
back in my day
oh back in my day i remember that day
when i first appeared on stage and
freebie
oh yeah that was wonderful actually let
me tell you a story about that
yeah behind the scenes me and callie
we're standing behind the stairs
shivering and shivering and talking
about how gerious we are
yeah
but then i saw kelly
walking up the stage behind you know i
was standing on the side backstage and
she walked up there and i saw her
leaving
and i saw her i was looking at her from
the side
[Music]
and she suddenly suddenly the moment she
stepped on there i could not notice
the nervosity and yes that is a word
younglings you guys are just not
educated enough
your nervosity suddenly disappeared
immediately she had that
uh performer energy and an aura around
her yeah yeah
so ah did i tell you yes yes did i tell
you uh
that day when i first had my three new
appearance yeah actually
actually me and kelly were really
nervous behind the stage we were
standing there shivering and and uh
really really nervous about going up on
stage
but then
then kelly went up on stage and they
were standing on the side
what do you mean i already said that
what do you mean no way
no no no
but anyway
well now you remember that day the first
first time i appeared on stage in 3d
great story oh thank you sit down my
child and listen
listen for stay for a while and listen
you will learn many things
if you just stay for a while and listen
just listen i haven't had anyone listen
to me for a while huh
what do you mean you were here yesterday
no you were not i was waiting for you
when you are not never coming to visit
me i'm such a lonely lonely lonely
grandma
i've been waiting and waiting
you were not here yesterday no no stop
lying to me no no no
i'm having a deja vu right now
really while i was talking i was having
a really weird dish of i mean i mean
not because i kept on repeating myself
but because of a different reason
[Music]
did you guys feel like it was a deja vu
as well
[Music]
oh man
i hope vod watchers won't be um
too confused in the beginning of the
stream
because like we waited for a while and
did uh
polls and all that
[Music]
i don't want to cut it out because then
chat is gone so stupid you cut one thing
out and then chat is gone why is it
lying down why are you gonna be like
that
um
[Music]
pin a message
i wonder if they look at the comments
before watching the vlog
[Music]
yeah i can go through the vlog and
and look where where i actually start
playing the game is when when this when
the game comes on to the stream so yeah
it's gonna be all right my vod watches
have i mean
everybody who watches my vlogs must
already be a really patient person
because my vlogs are so long
so they'll be patient with me surely
i'll be that job
okay i guess i'll go now um
[Music]
what's
able to stream normally today
and i caught up on my super chats
yeah
yeah yeah yeah have um a nice evening
everyone don't miss me too much tomorrow
okay i'll be um recording something
on the side
and looking forward to seeing you again
when i play yakuza you have some time
tomorrow to catch up
if you missed the previous episode it's
really really getting fun and
interesting so if you're not watching
this serious i think you should
know
that
night
[Music]
not miss you too much ask for the
impossible i'll come here and give you a
hug
[Music]
yeah
look at that you get some rest on your
everyday thank you
um
i got some rest yesterday i also cleaned
my apartment again guess so it gets
dirty so fast and i ate some good food i
told you on twitter that i i got some
pretty good
um
the empanadas were with carne meat
not cheese a lot of you guys said uh
wait
empanadas
i think yeah and you guys were like oh
cheese empanadas are so good but
actually i got uh meat empanadas
oh i didn't take pictures but uh the
food looked really good
and uh
i
most of the choices they had were with
avocados in it so
uh i chose one of the few options
without avocados because i don't like
avocados which is probably
a problem with that kind of food because
there's avocados everywhere for some
reason
um
so this this kind of aleppo i was
thinking is probably not that
maybe not one of the most popular and
common choices but i got um
[Music]
wait am i mixing them up
empanada is the one that's closed right
and areppa is the one that's open
with the cheese all over it mixed with
some other things
yes okay
okay so i got a tuna ave
which was so good though tuna salad
with that cheese that they use
[Music]
but i don't i was thinking tuna is maybe
not the most common one but it was so
good tonight rippers are amazing oh
maybe this is not that uncommon
i haven't tried that it was really good
it was amazing
[Music]
hmm
you can put anything in another people
yeah i saw they had so many different
ones it was fascinating if only they
wouldn't put apple candles into
everything
cairo
where are they originally from because i
don't want to claim anything wrong the
store claimed the restaurant claimed
they were from one specific pla uh
country
but i'm i'm guessing that it's more like
a latam
um food like from
like a couple of countries
see the chat is also saying different
things
[Music]
they come from different areas
but a lot of people say colombia oh
colombia and venezuela aha okay
venezuela is what i thought yeah
well i thought
[Music]
but you guys seem to eat it in a lot of
latin
countries
if i
am not getting the wrong impression
[Music]
okay i understand everything now
what what sauce do you eat uh
arepas with
no empanadas what sauce do you eat
empanadas with because uh they were out
of sauces
so
i ate it with
i only i only had sweet and sour and
ketchup sauce at home so i ate it with
ketchup but it was really good though
it did fit good with it normally no
sauce you eat it without a sauce
[Music]
tomato sauce yeah so ketchup did fit
well
it worked it worked we eat it with no
sauce
really
vinegar
lemon juice lemon juice
[Music]
no sauce maybe that depends on the
country maybe this is something like you
know
depending on where you're from
you grow up eating
them differently
no sauce or red sauce yeah i can't
really eat spicy things so eating a
spicy sauce with it is not really an
option and it was already a little bit
spicy
on its own that made my my nose
uh
run
lemon
you squeeze it on top of it
that's interesting
[Music]
regular tomato sauce well not so i get
it but i just didn't really have any
other options at home
[Music]
i want to try more new foods like that
so
i was looking for a food that i haven't
eaten before
and that was a a good one yeah usually
usually i'm kind of scared of eating
things from different countries that are
so different but but this kind of food
arepas and empanadas they were not that
that like
far off from what i would like
and uh
and
actually the
ah repa
remind uh reminds me or like it it gives
me um
it gives me kebab vibes
[Music]
tamales oh i think they had that too
probably
like basically because it's just like a
sandwich with lots of things stuffed in
there
[Music]
yeah
and when you bite into it it all falls
apart i was trying to eat it carefully
though so mostly it stayed together
mexican curry oh that's probably really
[\h__\h] spicy
[Music]
they have corn flavor yeah you guys know
i love corn
[Music]
probably because i'm not used to it but
if i had to choose normal bread and
cornbread i would go for normal bread
if i had to choose
the the cornbread was interesting never
happened before i think
and probably good for people who can't
eat normal bread right
um
[Music]
is a
i i assume that uh arepas are always
with cornbread
i assume
[Music]
no thank you to snails no thank you
thai italian food is really common here
so yeah i've had it before
frog oh [\h__\h] off
[\h__\h] off no thank you
good
be reasonable with me
why are you coming up with those crazy
ideas now you know i wouldn't like it
crazy crazy do you really expect me to
go eat snails and frogs tomorrow
no i want to become a frog i don't want
to eat a frog
[Music]
oh i watched this really really cute
video uh i think it was from a korean
channel
yeah i'm pretty sure it was just a
really cute video where
um a guy went to
um the mountains or something forest in
the mountains or so and he picked up
like tat not not even tattles but frog
eggs
um and then he raised them
into frogs
and the whole thing was filmed and it
was really cute
yeah
he raised you know the channel you know
it
can't pull so cute and the frog was so
cute it was really interesting how the
tadpoles turned into frogs i never uh
saw that so
closely before
and like the whole process
uh
leave them in their environment he did
bring them back he did bring all of them
back
um but the thing was and he told this in
the video that that area
uh like how many percent it was the
majority like what 70 80 90
of the frog eggs there
that the frogs lay end up dying
because they don't make it or they end
up as food for others or the water um
like kind of disappears and then
they just die because of lack of water
and all that
so
just for a project for himself and also
in ca uh
in in order to raise more and let less
of them die he brought a lot of them
home and then raised them properly but
he did a really really really like a pro
like everything was perfectly handled
do my korean bros which
know which channel i'm talking about
[Music]
they do a lot of those like nature
videos
and then and then they were oh it was so
sad um
he there was a part in the video where
he went back to the spot where he got
the eggs and he saw that a lot of the
water disappeared and and um and he saw
that there were some like tadpoles in a
tiny tiny tiny tiny puddle
um
and and yeah then he brought water for
some from somewhere else and then poured
it over that tiny tiny tiny puddle to
save them
it was so nice
i i was really moved man
[Music]
oh video
really moved me man
the whole video
moved me
i think it made me cry a little bit
yeah
that's so nice
my hero we need yeah
man most people are just saying ignore
those dying tadpoles you wouldn't even
see it because it was so [\h__\h] tiny
you wouldn't even see it
new
what a chat
it had a lot of views so it's a really
popular
channel and all that maybe you can find
it
a korean korean channel
giga chad
we're just crying about frogs okay
yeah
all right i think i'll go now i feel
like i said this five times now
see you soon chadpole oh that's funny he
should name his channel chadpole
[Music]
what's going on
but anyway i should stop yeah
thank you guys for watching
i will do my best to become a frog
someday
um i think i learned some things from
that video how to become a frog
okay okay
and in german we said
bye bye have a nice day
tonight
[Music]
she's tough man
stuff i'll become a mix of all the
animals and look like a [\h__\h] monster
terrifying monster
yeah bye bye
[Music]
new ending soon tm
do
[Music]