[Music]
do
hello
and then i'm fixing them
oh hi everybody hello
so today we're doing it with really bad
walkie-talkie equality to get more you
know immersion kikitiki everyone
[Music]
oh god yes that's terrible
it sounds even better in walkie-talkie
quality
uh
so uh uh yeah we're playing this game
again this is part two uh you guys
better watch both point of views uh
because otherwise you'll get confused uh
probably more confused than we even are
but
both me and ame are ready to
embarrass ourselves today once again
[Music]
uh
and uh
last time i think at chapter six
uh i don't think we can finish it today
we're not even gonna uh hope
hope to finish it um we're probably
gonna do three hours maximum
because uh i have the convention that
ame was on yesterday i have that today
at the same convention so i gotta be
there in time yeah
yeah
kfb represent
uh teammates represent
i saw some really cute ahmed cosplays
there yesterday
but was one of them actually you
um
i don't think so uh since i was playing
um a different great streamer yeah
ah okay
okay
and a cutscene i can't tell her
is that her in a cutscene finally
another soul here to save me
i've been capturing hellish castle for
for i skip one now listen there is a way
for us to escape but i need your help
you see that apparatus over there
get it to work i feel like we skipped
one i think we're on chapter five once
you're done meet me upstairs in the
greenhouse good luck friend
hello super creepy are you still alive
oh uh i just was in a cut scene and i
think we're on the wrong chapter
you mean we're too late to to to
too advanced
yeah because the last time we were
playing we're doing the alchemy one oh
we switched places oh
i think we did yeah because i think i
see the thing now that you saw before
okay
time traveling
copy what copy what
i don't know
um well i think yeah i think we we had
to
what did you do what did you do oh is
this the thing you did last time
no we're not gonna do that [\h__\h] again
are we nope nope nope nope okay okay
we'll exit to the lobby okay exit by
all right oh that's the wrong thing
give us one moment
[Music]
oh yeah
okay so wait
chapter
hey
um access i can only go up to chapter
six
but i think the one we just tried was
chapter six now
[Music]
yeah i thought i did too i think it
maybe just didn't uh
i didn't save it properly
[Music]
see your room
is that really your room
uh as i invite
okay
i guess i have to do it again
no
not now we'll remember how to do it i
don't remember anything i remember
i remember
oh yeah yeah we'll speed run it we'll
get it on the first try
okay
wait um
you can hear me twice in him now okay i
switched places so i
i don't know
we'll see
oh okay
then i pressed ready let's go let's go
[Music]
[\h__\h] again
was she laughing does she hear me
i can hear you
okay yep uh i'm in a different place now
that's for sure
oh you're in what i'm in there
are you guys is she in the right area
no
was
no what have you done
hey can you guys can you guys give us a
guy to walk through okay cut cutscene
over
okay
is this your time loop emma did you
create this time loop
maybe
oh god okay um
i remember it goes from
red green to blue to
orange green to red
blue blue
a blue blue blue to orange screen
so uh chad said we could open the vod
and we can like just uh go off of your
perspective from last time
or or someone from the viewers can open
it and tell me what is to the right side
of that into the left side can can the
chat help me please um i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna rely on chat okay i'm in
all right kfp get to work
well i guess my job here is easy i'll
just sit back and relax
i just have to watch
oh
i'm pretty sure i remember so it's like
i went from
green
this red green to blue
to
yellow green
to yellow to
[Music]
red blue to something like that i went
like
because i think it skipped this one
do you do you remember the order
i think so sort of
okay um
but do you remember the order as it was
like
on my screen like
uh do you do you know what's next to the
one that's orange and green
red
red red red or red only
just red
okay so that i'm gonna put that to the
one on like there's two two thingies
where i can put it the one on the right
side and the one on the left side
connecting but i guess it no it only
maybe i could get an image on my side
guys somebody make the image and put it
in hashtag
uh so red only either connects to blue
blue
or blue green
it's on the outer ring so it goes like
this
it went it went
red green blue
blue green red
okay i think everything that worked um
continuing please
that did not work
okay
that did not work it looks
into me well it started differently from
last time so it started at blue blue and
it went to red and then it went to
orange green and it stopped
yeah yeah cause i don't have all of them
in there yet
oh what comes out the orange green
do you know
uh if we're going opposite
then no i don't know
what colors could be connected with
orange green on your thingy
yes there's a blue green there's blue
and then there's just orange
i think chat was saying that it should
be blue green
i i don't have blue green
uh
okay so it's either only orange or only
blue
okay testing
[Music]
blue green
oh
it works it worked until there so i need
i need to know what's
red and blue uh there's only the only
option is blue orange
we're doing it we're doing it we got it
i think we got it in the first try
hopefully
that is weird because i don't have a
blue orange i only have orange orange
and blues blue blue red
orange green
orange
ah okay
um just a single blue
okay i will try it
[Music]
blue blue
red orange green
orange
yeah okay that was not it
that's okay because uh we could just try
again and it'll be the same i guess when
you like start a new chapter when you
start again from the beginning that it
randomizes so it's not the same as last
time obviously
oh no
okay but but now what
um i don't think it's right in my head
now it's still the same as the previous
try
[Music]
hopefully
yeah yeah it'll be the same as the one
we just tried so it doesn't work on the
end where like
um
it goes
uh red blue doesn't work after orange so
maybe it has to be a different one
because uh there's nowhere else to go
after that
it wouldn't go back to the point okay so
uh
what was connected with uh
with uh orange green again sorry
either orange blue or blue green
[Music]
did i die last time oh gosh because it's
standing in the water and what was
connected to blue only
uh
just orange oh sorry just red green
technically i guess because it could be
if it goes from red to orange green and
then blue it can't go back up there
but uh
i guess it could also go to single
orange
okay uh i'm testing
oh it looks like up until there it's
working
so what's next one more time uh with uh
orange and green
uh either single red
blue green
or a single orange
hello chant
so much
it starts at
red green it goes to blue this is how we
were doing it before
it goes to orange green it goes to
yellow okay
okay i think until that point it worked
again
but the last time i put in
uh
the remaining
which one did i put in what connects to
red and blue red blue
uh blue blue or blue orange
okay and i used blue blue and i died so
but i don't have
the other one that you said
so what the hell
i think that i died i think i was the
one who died because i was standing in
the water over here when it uh went
wrong
oh
oh oh ah okay you mean that was a
timeout
okay
sure that works time now
okay testing testing
testing yeah you kind of have to watch
the livestreams i want to see like this
i don't know what's happening on her
side
we're going to be using orange
red blue
blue blue
okay
yeah
nice
yay
that was fairly fast thankful
it's because of our two big brains put
together
which will now disappear and become a
no-brainer
oh yeah it's mixing the concoction we
gotta make a concoction here i think
what's in concoction
oh god this looks complicated
and we we stopped here last time
ah you know what i think it is is
because this technically isn't part of a
new chapter it's like part of the same
chapter
yeah probably
at least we're not in a time limit now
i'm gonna describe what i see in front
of me um i see
uh
what is this a
hexagon with a n at the top and then
with little gears that can be moved
around
uh like a maze and i also see
uh something to mix potions
and a lever
what if this thing is vibrating
oh
it's a sword
it's like yara's sword
[Music]
oh sleepy
hey that sword is like your sword well i
have a sword but it kind of looks like
your sword
pick it up pick it up
i have it but it's broken
um okay well i i'm in a room that has a
free big barrels tunnel and
um
a lot of tubes
tubes maybe many tubes
tubes
okay
uh where shall we start
good question
uh
um
what is that
i mean pipes i see a lot of pipes
that are
they have like buttons underneath
oh they're like kegs numbers as well
[Music]
and uh oh
they i have two leathers
two levers that are next to the
pipes one is orange one is blue
uh
okay
i found some uh pieces of pipes
me too me too
this needs to be connected uh i have i
have
three uh
free
three pieces of pipes i has
oh wait four
um
yeah okay
and
i have a bunch of different ones
um it looks like you can you can collect
all the pipes
pokemon
yeah yeah i got the i got the pipes i
pushed the um i pulled the
yellow leather and now
i have some yellow fire running through
the
pipes
but
it's stopped
uh so i found a book here to make like
different uh potions or something and it
looks like uh
it's got some instructions here that
each bag turns into
uh oh there's like a powder that you can
mix with the liquid that makes like a
different fruit it looks like so we're
trying to make a fruit that's uh kind of
looks like a mushroom and a pineapple
put together
and the way we make it is by mixing
green bucket liquid with yellow cup
liquid to make green big bucket cup
liquid
actually don't know what i'm talking
about
i think i confused her
hey i see like yellow smoke coming from
the pipe i don't know if that's you
yeah yeah yeah that's my my smoke i
think my fire my guess i guess it gets
connected i turned it on i can also turn
on the blue one and
there's
the barrels
i guess the yellow one
kind of is connected to the barrels i
guess they all are connected to the
barrels
and the barrels have some colors on them
though
one is a
purple
one is orange and one is green
does that say anything to you
no
okay
good um
that necessary
don't think so
so what is the point of this okay
like this then no
okay so this one
do you
did you just change something over there
uh copy that i
did i wanna
i think i need the triple connector here
but the triple connector
uh so it's coming
where is this coming from anyways
oh it's coming from the bottom
okay
i guess
because what exactly did you change over
there
uh i'm messing with the pipes the pipe
connectors and i i think this is uh i
don't know it's like some sort of gas
that i'm trying to ignite within all
these pipes and have different
connectors so i'm just trying to make
sure that it's working
and so each of these is lit except for
this middle one and this middle one is
the top one which means i need a three
piece connector so maybe or maybe i'll
just put maybe just put this one
okay well all of these are lit
and now
i don't have any input from this so i
don't know
oh
here it goes
uh so two oh did i have the triple
connector i only have two
ah because it's coming up from this one
by itself
i guess it's fine
do it oh red lover this one
ah
okay
[Music]
did you did you activate some red fire
uh yes i did
okay well that's useful i can swap
between red or yellow i don't know what
this is for but i'm assuming it's the
liquid
turn on the the red one again
okay copy that
i wish i could put this pipe away
look down the pipe
oh
this one
did you turn ah there it is okay i see
the the gas
the red gas now
okay
i think we need cups do you have any
cups
i i have no cups no
i only have uh uh tubes
oh
where the cups chat
so slow okay what is this
is anything happening on your screen i'm
messing with like these little gears not
real like i see like the general color
of the gas is now
orange
not red
and i try i'm trying to connect it
that's that uh it goes to the the
barrels because like the tubes the pipes
they are kind of connected to the
barrels
and
but
yeah i think i have to try around a
little bit to make it
connect properly i guess
okay
[Music]
these are ladders
okay maybe we have to fix the pipes
gotta fix the five
uh i want to reach out but also i kind
of want to solve it myself so
do you have any other colored and red
don't activate it but do you have
anything besides red
sorry i messed it up uh no i only have a
red and yellow but i'm gonna try to fix
my pipes on this side
okay
i mean i don't really know what i'm
supposed to be doing to be honest
but okay we have uh two pipes here so
let's connect that
i made orange
what what excuse me one
yeah i made orange too
[Music]
i think
did i mix them
maybe something will happen when i put a
little correct clip
there not be a blockage here
seems good right there's no um
oh what the comment doesn't connect oh
there goes
this name is good
we're orange now
my orange chat
thank you
i am now activating blue i'm just gonna
try the blue first
i'm gonna turn yellow off
can you uh keep red activated
is red on right now or is it orange for
you it's
on right now
is it red or orange
it's on right now
oh it's purple oh it turned oh i was oh
okay so uh
i see i'm getting it if i do this
okay we can't talk at the same time on
the mic like on the walkie-talkie
oh yeah sorry um
it's all purple
but something i am not doing correctly
what
all right so maybe if i describe
what the area i'm in looks like it might
help you so
i have a red lever in the wall uh
connected to some pipes and there's one
two three four five
six seven pipes which are each named
respectively by their numbers
i have i have those numbers as well
okay and then um i also can see a flame
so there's like a flame
and that represents the color i think
you probably have something similar too
yeah yeah yeah right now it's purple
yeah mine too i think um
this represents like a liquid because
there should there should be like a
container that you can pick up
is this the way we came from
it's probably the exit
maybe i get the barrels with the
connection uh uh one moment please and
uh update i found some juice
are they all the same color
i guess they're all the same color okay
maybe we can uh change the color of
these with uh
the pipes
these aren't connected to the pipes
right okay
i guess i guess it isn't it shouldn't be
looking but i can't put anything in
there
i found cups and i filled them with
juice
oh okay
okay you do you
and put it under there and get the juice
i drank the juice and i can't move
don't drink it on me that's that's
probably really bad
all my directions are my i okay i'm
going backwards
i can only move backwards
okay i'm better now
i'm just gonna leave the pipes alone
okay let's go try and put the juice in
the thingy
maybe
maybe it's
um
maybe this one
oh no that just goes upwards
like that that goes nowhere
no it has to be the straight one
i conclude it has to be a straight one
um
but this one is maybe now but there's
frame coming out and here
there is one coming out this is two
coming up
what if
put this
like this
so
blue goes that way
[Music]
no no
and trying to
recombine it so it's purple again but in
a different way because i think the
first way was not correct
that's just like a mixer
so we have the recipe
we have this canister we have some pipes
now i suspect this uh thingy up here
i suspect this thing appears um
to kind of control the pipes maybe
these ladder symbols confuse me
but when i was messing around with this
stuff i don't think
anything was changing for kiara so i
have no idea what this is
all right besides the pipes uh what else
what else do you have
nothing only pipes
wait um
and free barrels yes barrels and pipes
barrels and pipes
three
that have three colors
one of them is purple one of those
orange and one of them is green and i'm
currently creating a purple flame
uh that should
oh wait
yeah that it should go it should connect
to the barrel and then fill it up i
suppose but
uh i have i have a leak somewhere i
think
okay do you think the leak could be on
my end since i also can see the pipe so
maybe like it's supposed to
yeah maybe i have a leak at number one
i
guess copy that i'm on my way
malika number one
hmm that changed everything to blue and
i still have the link
okay i made it
i mean i turned it in
ah
i turned i turned green uh a yellow one
now it created something green but now
it was now it's gone again what did you
press
now it's green again
okay
but so now i don't really have any leaks
anymore
uh
um
okay never mind let me let me test out a
little bit
because i don't need two blues
that is
wait a second what do we have here too
i'm drunk yara
what did you drink again
juice
[Music]
what did you just do
um i connected my flames
okay keep them that way maybe
can you describe
can you describe again what uh
what what you have in front of you
um i have all those numbers that you
said i have them as well they're on
on below and on top of um big big big
pipes
and then i have single pieces of pipes
which with which i can connect the pipes
and there's like gas coming out of the
pipes
um and i can turn the pipes
so that
pipes get connected in in the right way
i guess
and uh
then
in some way at some point they should
lead up to the barrels and fill the
barrels up
and also i have the two levers with
yellow and blue
okay so can we confirm like if we fill
it with a certain color like if we
um contain all the leeks if it uh fills
the barrel with like a certain color
liquid so that we can test because i
have juice on my side
uh yeah for example when it was all
purple um i was hoping for it to fill up
the purple barrel but
it um
didn't fill up because i guess something
is leaking
okay uh what is
what is your way to identify leaks and
maybe we could try again and then uh
press the lever and maybe that'll do
something
um
my way to identify them is
well i just see it leaking
okay
you turned on red i think
um
okay i will
i will try again to make purple
by by turning off yellow
which gives me a leak though but
otherwise how am i supposed to make
purple if if yellow is on i need for
purple i need red and blue
and you activated red so i activated
blue
and now yeah now it's purple
okay do you have any leaks
i'm gonna try it all over i'm gonna
remove all the pieces
okay copy that
i'm gonna drink more juice i am a little
bit sleepy yeah
all right so we can mix the
eggplant powder
with the juice
which makes an eggplant or we can mix
the blue egg powder with yellow and it
makes a blue egg
oh we can mix the pokemon with the
purple
and we can mix the papaya with the green
[Applause]
now it looks like what we need is this
um pineapple mushroom
we mix it with the yellow to make the
red and then we need a green bucket to
mix it with the yellow to make the green
juice
press the spray pump the canisters and
i'll fill it up
maybe i'm missing something here
this lever but i don't know what it does
what is this even for is it to like to
cook it and nothing happens
i can't even put anything in this one
there's no one supposed to put in there
maybe we don't have it yet
we got the juice purple juice
little yellow
we got this thingy
all right kiara anywhere in your
vicinity do you have uh something that
has gears
and ladders
maybe she has a book or like a
instructions i i see one gear but i
can't pick it up or do anything with it
does it look important
no not really seems like
decoration all right there's a door
that's locked so
yeah i'm i really only have this room
with the barrels and the
uh the pipes
okay so i'll just describe
has been saying you're doing the wrong
puzzle but i
i mean i can't really tell
i'm doing the wrong puzzle
well okay for me i only i have a lot of
stuff here to be honest i have barrels
which i can get juice from i have this
uh contraption which looks like it might
affect affect the pipes but uh
it just has a bunch of um cog wheels on
it that are movable and then one two
three four five ladder uh icons on it i
don't know what they represent i don't
know what it's supposed to mean but
there's two red
um
gears like cogs on it and then i also
have
one contraption which looks like it's to
mix um
which uh i can close and it mixes
something and then i have another
contraption which kind of looks like a
fryer where i can put the cups of juice
in but nothing happens when i do that
and then i have two books which
describes some recipes and then i have
those seven pipes with a ton of uh
pieces
um do you have
at the pipes do you have anything that's
connected with number one
oh then i gotta get there one second
it takes a minute following this game is
slow as heck
and
if we have to figure out a way to unlock
her door first but i don't know what to
do with the gears
all right i'm at number one and i have a
four piece connector pipe uh which is
connecting in all four directions
okay
did you like insert that somewhere or is
that like already in place
i inserted it
you inserted that
ah
can you get rid of that
okay got it
okay
uh what do you have
so
ah is that
like put that four piece connector put
it at number five maybe
uh so at number five um it just shows
like where the flame would be if it were
connecting earlier on but at the moment
there's no uh flames coming through to
number five and there's no place to
connect it the only places that can
connect pipes is between six and seven
at pipe three which connects to two and
then at pipe one
um
[Music]
ah but okay over copy
uh actually another question did you
turn off red or was that connection
connected with the four piece thingy so
if you take that off i have no more red
i just turned it off the red is
controllable via liver
please turn red on
[Music]
365 damn you're
i'm still not getting red um
oh it's because i don't have a pipe in
number one
oh okay
um put it put it there again i guess
yeah thank you
all of the flames are lit
okay keep it keep it like that yeah it's
all right and not a lit
and i feel like i don't have all the
pieces to try to solve it myself you
know
like i have all the stuff i feel like i
have all the stuff for like a later half
of the puzzle but
there's like
something that we have to unlock or i
don't know
like what is this
this needs to be unlocked
and i suspect that
it probably has something to do with
this but i it she doesn't have anything
to help me with this so i guess it's
something i have to solve myself but i
have no idea
like
what this could be
maybe i'll look around for some uh clues
um i see one change and that is oh wait
ah you said you have six to seven and
number three as well right oh can you
put something at number three one of you
cube's fees
uh on my way
uh yeah
ah let's change the color back to blue
so i just removed the pipe um so there's
like a
all right so the way it works it looks
like is that the number two pipe is
coming from you whereas for me
the number one pipe is now connected to
red which means it's feeding into three
and two which mixes it
can you the the the piece that you put
into six and seven can you put that into
three
copy that
wait that was a four piece connector
right yes
why are you guys saying anyway i didn't
do anything
i have
no more leaks which is i think a
progress
but
please hold on
is there a lever something that you can
turn the barrel juice into a different
color
yeah but um i need i need it to be
purple right now
ah do you have any other piece that you
can put into the the last six seven
connection
yes i got a uh
i got an l shape two connector or i
guess the one connector but it's like
you know two ways
uh and then uh one piece
uh yeah put that one one uh way
connector in there
well there's nothing there's nothing
coming out of uh
of this one
of the there's not there's no flame at
four five six to seven
oh okay then i think
you will need to put
any piece
and four
i can only put
the pieces between six and seven at
three and at one
i don't know why it's like that is it
because there's no flame here do you do
you have leaks anywhere
like nickly no
but i am missing a flame at number one
because i put the third piece connector
instead of the four piece connector oh i
do have a leak actually hold on i'm
gonna just i'll fix it on mine
okay i think i already had it like uh
i don't know because uh
this one that uh okay all right so my
red is coming in through one side let's
put a
you think this one needs a four piece
connector
there now we have red going through
every single one
and then blue comes in from two there's
a three piece so we'll put it in here
now it's purple how come there's no
coming in from here
where's this coming from anyways
uh so i no longer have any leaks from
one to three and i now have flames
coming in from four to seven they just
disappeared probably based off something
you did
yeah yeah probably
um
so now i have the same leak as i have
before but i
i'm not sure if that is actually a
problem
yeah uh
let's let's let's see what else you have
like uh everywhere maybe there's
something else you're missing
yeah now now it's back to only blue
color i think you removed the red one
yes
um
do you have like any sort of map or like
uh some sort of symbol somewhere because
i have this piece that i think is
important with the gears and stuff and
i'm
not sure what to do with it
is it what does it look like only gear
is on it or
uh so it's kind of like a it's a it's a
hexagon and it has
um
different
uh circles connected with dots where
within the circles and dots oh sorry uh
different dots connected between each
other and in those connections i can
move gears
uh
throughout like the puzzle
does that make sense that i explain it
okay chad is saying it's just the pipes
we just focus on the pipes
okay um
um
little shits
maybe i'm right
huh
you guys have the guide open so you know
right
cheers
can you
um
stop the gas
that
comes from number one
this blue flame comes from chiara
which comes from number two
okay so
the pipes coming out of the floor are
coming from her
okay i will remove all my pipes again
okay
uh
okay so right now i have only
blue uh that goes
from like into
it's trying to go to pipe two anyways uh
can you turn red on again
after that red is go
you guys see that
uh
can you send
your red flame
to
six and seven is that a thing you can do
[Music]
okay i see fire
um
so
the thing is i'm the flame that i get
from you
um
i get the number two from you the uh
pipe number two feeds in from you
and then so does four
five six and seven
uh
yeah
um
i i i
all right if i have a flame that comes
in through one uh can you
get the
sound can you get some red
fire going through number three
that fixes that
then
and i have a leak i don't know if that's
important
oh okay uh oh wait i just had purple
there for a moment that looked good yeah
i don't know if it's important if i have
a leak
now it's blue
now it's purple um
keep it like that
okay so we just have to figure out like
on her end whatever is making this
to that
but the thing is
it's coming up through here
okay i think we got it
nope never mind
oh wait whatever you had before
okay i turned it back to before
or one more before
yeah leave it like there
okay
uh okay i see you hold on one second
this is this might remove your flames
let me check something
yeah i have some
other leeks now
oh i don't want to drink
all right hold on one second
i'm drunk i drink too much juice
all right can you mess with the
connection the connector that comes from
two or three or one one of those just
mess with them
yes
wait
all right wait whatever you're doing
just leave it there
can you put the four piece connector
into
the last one yes
no now
but the four piece connecting the last
one oh no never mind that ignore me
but i think i need gas from one
i currently do not have any leaks
looks good on my end
[Music]
everything on my end looks good the
colors are mixed and also there's no
leaks
yeah the colors are definitely good but
now i have a
a connection that
is not working i will i will i will
test around something
we just have to make it so that neither
of the sides have a leak i guess
that's that changed
all
right
the leaves
this is coming in from there
oh
i guess technically speaking i don't
need the four piece here like if i had
the three piece
i can't even scroll through my pipes
this is
um
maybe we should start from the beginning
oh hold on i'm messing around with it
i think what it is like obviously
whatever you're changing also changes
the direction of my pipe so we just have
to figure out the way
um where neither of us have any leaks
all right um
can we start from the beginning
all right
um let's just go to the first pipe
copy that
let's do one pipe at a time so i think
the first one i'm putting
actually has to be correct
so i just sent blue over to the next
pipe
um
[Music]
i guess
what are your options here
and the
thing
right so i have red coming in from the
left connector which can be connected to
the three other connectors and uh at the
bottom connector it would ignite one
flame at the top connector it ignites
two flames but it still comes out on the
right connector
uh in the first pipe
all right at the moment and pipe number
three i can connect um
there's a red coming red gas coming out
of the left connector and blue gas
coming out of the top connector
uh
can you um make it so that it doesn't go
through number one
please i'm so lost but i think
yeah okay
yes
um
but i still need bread i just don't want
it to go for number one
okay but uh this creates a leak on my
side
uh i think i think that's okay um
but please
uh
can you somewhere
except for number one somewhere else mix
blue and red
okay nice now i have purple
pretty color
okay
uh good
okay let's keep it there
okay
next
i'm getting it okay i'm gonna send yeah
i'm gonna send the purple one
uh to
number five if i guess no i don't
understand this where is it
[Music]
what is this this
connected to four or four tubes
um
well it looks like for me if you send it
through
i don't know actually
okay
[Music]
looks like it has to come in from both
four and five
[Music]
i think once we move past the pipes
we'll um do better
um
i don't i i don't i understand
okay i'll describe uh so four and five
both come out uh individually from the
floor for me and they both need their
each flame ignited and then there's one
in the middle so i don't know if one
comes out of four it might ignite five
and then go to six and seven
was that helpful
is it because like the setup that we
have over here isn't
ah
um what happened
okay now it's blue
sorry i have to take knight three on my
side but um
i don't know how to do that without uh i
have a leak i don't know if it matters
maybe it's supposed to maybe it's
supposed to come out here
all right
i just feel like i don't have enough
pieces to make it so it doesn't leak
there
mommy you are fine i mean it's fine i
have the kind open i'm gonna trust me
and
[Music]
but um
because there's a flame here
like doesn't it have to be connected to
three
even though chad is telling me no that
whatever i had is fine
i know maybe i should just ignore chat
i should just ignore you guys
i guess that's fine because one isn't
ignited
maybe it's okay
it's okay maybe not all the numbers have
to be lit
how's it going kiara
oh
uh
i think like on my side
um there's no leaks
and everything's purple
i hear noises
was that
i thought i heard it bubble
do you do you have any leaks now
i do not but uh number one flame and
number three flame are not ignited
but chad says that i they said that i
had the right pipe connector so i don't
know
i'm sorry i do have a leak between six
and seven at the bottom
okay
[Music]
maybe i'll just swap do you have more
leaks now
uh hold on
so just swap one second
okay
i don't know
it should be a three piece connector
here too but um
i need six and seven to power through to
four and
five
but if i have two going through
it doesn't convert flame
maybe it's okay if two isn't going
through
can you take out the the four-way pipe
from six and seven
already did
thank you
one moment please
well it's all ignited i'm lying
it's good right
uh
ah
did you just turn on the number one
yes
please
no no feeding from number one please
thank you
um
i'm the problem
can you send
a
red from
four
three four
one of those right you have okay okay
one of them
and two
i mean like this into three
like that
uh
yeah probably i think
one moment
i think
just to ignite all the flames or is it
to ignite it without any leaks like i
don't i don't know what the goal is want
no leaks and we want my i have this
pressure
thingy
meter on my side
and i have it i need it to be on the
very
um
right side
uh and right now it's a little bit of uh
in the middle
sorry okay i start again
i have a pressure meter
and
um
now it's in the middle now it's going
below the middle now it's changed to
below the middle i need it to be higher
i need it to be at the maximum okay how
is it now
uh now it's at the middle
so
i need it to be at maximum pressure
okay well i don't have any leaks right
now on my side with how it is
i understand correctly i think i do so
uh
um
uh there is a leak at one again
and the the
the red one that you sent through
three
um i think
can you send the red one only for one
and three right
only for one and three
do you have any other way to send the i
sent it through one but i can't i can't
get it to three because if i send it
only to well yes i'll definitely
it must be the four-way connector
right
does it well i guess it doesn't matter
it does the leaks only
i don't know if the leaks only affect
the pressure on her side or if my leaks
also affect her pressure
i don't know maybe it doesn't matter
she said red to three
all right i have red going to one and
three
uh the three is fine but the one i don't
want the number one i don't need that
okay
okay okay okay
uh keep it like that for a moment
okay
how's the pressure
yeah the pressure is higher now
so that's good but it's not at maximum
yet
okay
okay i sent i sent the purple flame up
to number three can you send that
to
the next plate
uh nope there's no way for me to connect
three and four four just comes out from
the ground
is there any way for you to fix
any leaks you have except like uh don't
don't make it come out of number one
now it's number one
now it's stopped
yeah now now it's now is uh
not coming for number one so that's okay
but can you connect number three to
number four
i don't think so
i don't know what connects i don't think
i mean like
okay
okay do we do you have the purple coming
through
ah wait keep it that way
mine is number one not have to be lit uh
okay
um four in the three in a minute one
second one second please please hold the
line
okay
do you have a leak
yes i have one
ew i have two weeks one
ah if you turn off number two is it
possible for you to turn off number two
then it won't have a leak
um
[Music]
no
uh
i can't turn it off
it just
comes
through the ground
i don't have anything any way to turn it
off
or
um
i can i can try to not send it to number
three
or an inside how do i turn this off to
not send it
to
number
six
or number five
one moment please
so
i don't think you guys know what you're
talking about in chat either
all right well number three is off now
for a moment for a little moment when i
put something in i think at the same
time you put something in there to
change something but for a moment it
went almost to maximum pressure it was
like all the way to maximum pressure i
think
i mean i wasn't changing anything really
i had it set on like one thing for
like a 30 seconds
okay um
maximum pressure
[Music]
it's like with a kettle thank you
i don't remember how i had it before
i think this is how i had it
[Music]
can you
um
do
you
have
at this very moment
a leak
yes i have a leak uh where it says
number three there's a flame coming out
of three
and there's also a flame coming out of
two and two is leaking but three is
connected to the uh pipe that leads to
one
um
i feel bad like making a kiara take the
lead on the puzzle but i don't have like
a pressure meter so
i can't tell like
if what i'm doing is correct or not you
know what i mean
i'd be trying to help more but what else
am i supposed to do
besides besides describe
what i got
[Music]
uh so i think
um like when you said the pressure
changed to maximum there was a flame
coming through
one from your end
that's the only change i saw
um
[Music]
i don't know how to help but
i have leaks
coming from number three can you stop
that
okay
now
i have a
i have purple so that's good
it's working whatever you did now was
correct
yay
we got the first colors
oh
okay let's take out all the pipes what
do you mean
and make uh
orange
okay
blue and i will turn i'm turning on
yellow uh you can keep on red um
but i guess it will have to come for a
different place we'll figure that out
let's start from the beginning
um the wayne yes
i think that is already
something good whatever you did
because we already have orange flowing
for a second one and that one goes for
me
to
wait what did you just do
uh i just mixed it but um i made it so
it's also coming through on my end
but wait wait wait wait
this is wrong
all right i'll wait i'll take everything
out
i currently
um
have
uh
i have it going through i have orange
going through
five now but now it's yellow again
can you
uh
while you place the pipes
can you tell me exactly
what where are you placing them okay um
i just connected red to yellow which was
a red exit flame 192 number one which uh
seemed to turn your flame orange
at the moment there's nothing else
coming out of anywhere else
okay
where where does it
um
where does it stop for you now
um all i have from you is um yellow
coming from number one
uh i also have some coming out of six
and seven
okay can you connect that somehow
now
um i have flames that are going to four
and five and i have one coming out of
three that i can connect to two if you'd
like
um
[Music]
i'll test it out
how's the pressure
uh
it's like a tiny bit above middle
oh and i think
uh the two
doesn't really lead anywhere for me so
the two is unnecessary
yeah yeah
um i put i put the
connector
that sends it to five
and six
and
uh
now i have almost almost maximum
pressure
okay i do have a leak um
that doesn't help if i set it through
two because then it uh makes it leak on
your side
yes and it's less pressure
now it's even less now it's more
now it's less pressure
[Music]
i think this would have gone a lot
faster i guess
[Music]
the pressure meter
and organized by doing that by looking
at that okay
uh
green is made by
yellow and blue
and blue
so i'm setting blue
um but i don't i don't have yellow
you're the only one who has yellow red
now
can she send blues for the other ones
you can send uh
yellow as well
um i guess if i send it through two
are you are you able to send yellow too
or do you only have red
one second
okay
it's green on my end
oh okay whatever you did now
well
i think it's it needs to stay like that
wait does that mean
okay we're sending we're sending green
uh to i will send green to number three
um
okay i see
wait now it's not green anymore yeah one
second
okay
now it's green again
and uh
even if i send it with a straight pipe
uh it'll still come back right oh
matter but um
the blue is coming out of two
and i just need to send it into three
but i need to connect it through here
maybe
um
[Music]
do you have do you have
leaks right now
if yes yes
oh where
uh on number one because my my uh pipe
when i send it to where it connects to
number two it uh loops back around and
leaks into
my one area here
outfit
um
okay something you did changed it back
to
yellow now so something that you
disconnected now i think
some at least somewhere yeah now now
it's green again somewhere it has to be
connected so that my blue and my yellow
mixes to
um green because like both colors come
from my side yeah yeah i don't know
i just uh well i still have a leak so
well then i'm gonna mess around with the
pipes a little bit
okay went down on pressure
[Music]
pressure is higher now and in the screen
again
no
ah
um
like you have to send it through three
oh i can try to not set it for free one
second
it might help but then i just connect
the one and two
i don't want to disconnect this i mean
it should be fine if i just connect it
it's just the pressure i see
ah
one second is it still going for free oh
wait maybe
ah there okay there hold on one second
i don't know if the pressure will be
good on this because uh
it should swap
i think it'll still come out either way
one second i'm gonna change it really
quick
no either way i'm i'm also changing
something to test it out
uh i still have a leak
where is it uh it's coming from one
one second
[Music]
uh when you send yellow through three um
can you
like if you send it through three maybe
and and not send it through one is that
possible
oh we'll we'll check we'll check
sending it for free now um we'll
try to
um
there's no way to send uh yellows for
three
ah
yellow two three uh i thought before
yellow was coming out of wait maybe one
second
uh well it only comes from one
uh-huh
okay is it coming for free now the
yellow yeah yeah is there a way to stop
it coming through
one somehow
really
i could connect it going to the left um
does it be less leaks
i guess it's probably impossible
stop it i'm going oh oh oh sorry
actually i need to change something
because it's definitely not going to
connect to the barrels okay
i guess it has too
yeah yeah we'll keep it keep it uh like
this
okay
it's okay if there's a leak
one leak
can you stop it coming from freeze
uh
[Music]
yeah nice work
oh well that took us
way too long oh my god yeah definitely
would have been faster like if we'd
known about the pressure thingy
my door has opened
oh
i'm in a new room
i see a big big big plant that looks
like the piranha plant from super mario
sunshine
oh
it's moving and i see papers that show
me like plants and potions
i have some juice bars with orange green
and purple
okay
i have plants
um
[Music]
seed
packets i guess
and i have on the other side of the room
i have
a
big
container
with some signs
okay that could be useful so um i'm
gonna describe again the thing that i
have it's a hexagon
with uh gears inside of it that can be
moved uh which are connected in some
places and it has five ladder icons
okay uh
i am on the ladder right now
uh
what signs do you see
okay so there's a
like a north and it's kind of like a
compass on top of the hexagon like
there's an arrow pointing up with an n
inside of it and then uh
i have a compass too i have a compass
too
okay uh and then i have some gears which
are movable inside of the hexagon and
it looks like
so it's a hexagon right so it's got one
two three four it's got six sides this
might be um parallel to like uh the
shape of your room maybe because there's
ladders in
uh two of the north corners
in um one of the
uh west corners uh down by the south and
then one by the east and the bottom
uh
um well i have also six signs
like astronomical signs
uh around the compass and also around
the whole room i'm in i'm in like a big
hole in the ground with a ladder and
the signs are are around the ladder as
well like for example they're on the
fourth piece of the lava i have like a
planet on the sixth piece of the ladder
i have stars on the seventh piece of the
ladder i have sun
the eighth one is a sparkle and the
ninth the last one is uh the tenth one
is a moon
okay
i'm gonna move around with some stuff
see if anything changes for you
nothing's changing currently
i imagine the red ones would change
something
so
i opened something
oh the signs are all moving now
uh it's turning
a lot of stuff is turning
i think i just turned on water
yeah i think we're on a timer now so
okay ah
not again
okay so something in the middle of mine
is is now moving whatever you just like
something oh okay okay hold on
oh oh oh my ladder pieces are
like not aligned anymore
i see
it
i can't i can't climb up right now
because the ladder piece is yeah gone
and uh water is like halfway
um like under my elbows
so the the the latter piece with the
plastic i can reset it because i feel
like
i guess it's fine
one second i'm messing around with it i
might be able to
i just need to get it to work smoothly i
think
yeah i can die a few times i'm a phoenix
doesn't matter
all right
okay
that's good so i'm assuming the red ones
have to be turning um water is around
my breasts
okay i'm trying my best right now
yeah i'm gonna die in a few seconds it's
okay don't chill try to figure out
whatever is going on at work
it doesn't connect is it because the red
one like it just doesn't work out
okay maybe i have to connect it to all
the ladders
the
the the the first symbol the planet
symbol is by the way at me
oh
and now i'm drowning
okay
this is fine
i like i like water i guess the red ones
don't move i thought okay i'm bye bye
[Music]
i guess i'll die
okay we'll figure out on the next one
yeah we will we will
okay i'll go into the
i'm going to the container
all right
i get it now it's good that it resets
they all have to be turning which means
this one's next this one which turns
this one which turns these those work
this one is in the way so it's connected
to the ladders and
going down
right now and uh should i immediately
turn on the water or
one moment
okay
now that i know that's how that works
and these are broken they're out of the
way here but
if everything needs to connect i don't i
don't know if all the ladders need to
connect or just like certain ones need
to connect to her
maybe in a succession like in an order
okay so before when uh the room was
filling up is it like you could climb to
one ladder and then the next ladder and
then the next ladder or
um
like was what it was what i was doing
like what was it moving three pieces of
ladder and the fourth one was gone the
fourth one was the planet that is uh
also aligned to northwest in the compass
oh okay the northwest one
okay uh if you turn it on i think it
should move
yes i'm turning it on and the ladder
piece moved
uh yes the ladder piece
they are gone and water is filling up
okay
my thing isn't turning yet so i think it
has
two steps away from being back in place
the first one
i think i think two two steps uh one
second
these weren't connected shoot
oh
need one in between
[\h__\h] how did i do that
um
here we go
okay
and then we had one
oh okay
um move move keep on moving yes yes yes
yes yes stop it there
okay okay going up going up next piece
is sparkles
uh
what is the compass direction of it
and it's like one step away from being
in front of me a lot of people
i see that disrupts it uh oh okay from
down here maybe
if it moves here this one remove this
one but then
oh are you turning the one below me but
i guess that doesn't matter anymore
because i'm already under one above
okay i got it i can't wait
are you okay
yeah
i got it
[Laughter]
um
yeah stop now
okay okay next one is the sun and that
is aligned to
the direction
north east
one second
i wonder if i could get this i have a
lot of time oh we have a lot of time
just need to get these out of the way
i hope they don't make me move the south
one so it's gonna be pain in the ass
all right
stop stop stop stop yes ah oh please oh
yeah we gotta go one one more round
about because i'm i'm one way one one
piece away from the last thing let's
move this one
oh wait
and stop please
perfect perfect next one is uh the star
shaped one
um and that one is at no north new york
uh south west
southwest
okay this one again
southwest southeast
oh i forgot how i did this one
is it too close
uh so i have one okay here we go
close
oh [\h__\h] this is hard
i think i have a lot of time
maybe move it from the uh no that won't
work
okay hello is it working
uh
something else is moving but i don't see
which one that's why nothing wait where
am i
oh you might have something below me i
think oh okay i see
i see because i assume that it would be
like directly south
should i waste a lot of time
uh is there any way i can help you
uh no
i'm on my way
okay
oh
yes the thing above me is moving uh yes
yes yes and stop stop stop this yes yes
yes yes okay last one
moon shaped one is
an east east
please save me i am going to drown like
a fish i'm trying okay i guess fish
don't drown
like
without floaties
shoot how do i get it over there
i feel like i don't have enough
what's the shortest path
uh if this is turning that one then we
can use this one here
okay
oh okay um i was it was like really
close to the ladder to go up but you
have to turn it around one more time
okay got it peace but yeah
okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
the water it goes for like uh
i guess we needed that water to go up to
the
ah it goes all the way up to my planting
area
oh
now there's like water coming through
the
for some um shower
thingies
and they
put water on the
on the
url uh
soil soil
sprinklers making water go pew pew pew
on the soil okay
uh okay
pop that
i am i can take
seed packets
oh
what do you have over there
uh so nothing new has opened up to me i
still have um i have like a little mixer
or it's like a fryer or something
and then i also have a mixer and i also
have
two books with two different a few
different recipes which i can read out
to you if you'd like
oh
yes i also have some recipes uh but yes
please do
all right so i got one recipe book that
uh has the
triple eggplant packet and it says plus
the red juice equals a red eggplant
plant and then it's the blue
uh egg plus the yellow juice makes the
blue egg plant and the
uh tentacle of the taco plant uh plus
the purple juice makes the sorry taco
seeds plus purple juice mixed taco plant
and a
weird shaped banana plus a green mixed
banana plant
oh okay
um
some of the things you mentioned
i think
are on my recipes as well but i have
different recipes i have recipes that
make for example
uh two fruits combined turned into one
um red juice then i have underneath i
have
one combination that makes the the white
juice the white portion
and one that makes a light blue potion
one makes a light green potion
and one that makes that combines the
red the blue and the green one to turn
it into a black one
with a
uh deadbeat
on top of it
copy that
um
okay and the the the fruits that are
uh
necessary to make the potions i have
like
seed packets of them
i guess i can plant them let me plant
some of them
i've already done this stuff but i'm
gonna get this pipe out of here i don't
like seeing it
it's giving me bad vibes
okay i already have some plants growing
oh
some funny looking ones
i'm gonna send some juice over
what you're sending juice to me i don't
know
oh i just found mine cards
i got mine cards my cards
yeah and i got a lover i guess i can
send something to you as well
oh
but i don't know what uh okay uh
send me some seeds um
let's see i'll just try to start by
making
the red
potion
first so i'm gonna make oh wait two
fruits
and one that is like a
alien
i hear anything
uh so i have a book here that uh has
like a pineapple mushroom
and it has like a weird face on it sort
of and it says
uh
yeah it's just in the book and it says
if you mix it with yellow it makes a red
potion
what are we even trying to do
uh
red potion
mixes for you with a juice and a fruit
yes but wait is there something like is
there a goal like maybe we can figure
out the goal because we can mix all this
stuff but we don't know what we're
supposed to be making
uh the black deadly potion i think they
want us to kill the
the big plants in my room
okay
plan okay
so i need the
red the blue and the green portion so i
want to start with the red one
and
the red one
needs
yeah two plants wait wait plants but do
i have them let me see
this room is real really really big what
did i plant here
so wait uh like the juice that you made
earlier with the pipes that doesn't
affect anything
uh
i i didn't make any juice yet
i mean no juice
the pipes
that's just
uh which pipe do you mean
don't worry about it then
okay okay
um okay so i'm gonna make the the plants
that i need for the first potion okay i
have a recipes for plants here if you
need it
uh yeah can you tell me do you know how
to
make
the
one that looks like um
uh it's like a greenish one
oh and it has um
some
[Music]
uh the only plants i see here are a
triple eggplant blue egg with the wings
uh takodachi with green tentacles and a
moldy banana
the triple eggplant yes yes i i i have a
package for that and i need that one for
the red potion but the other one i need
for the red potion is
uh
this is expensive plus red equals yellow
green
plant that i cannot find a seed packet
for
uh so you have
a recipe to make
that plant
or
uh sort of it says uh yellow the moldy
banana one plus green juice equals the
plant so i think you need to have the
packet already and i don't have anything
to make the packet
ah okay
what's this little mushroom thingy
what one one one moment please
oh so uh on my other book there's a like
a mushroom pineapple looking face fruit
and it says if you
mix that with the
yellow it makes the red potion and also
there's a green juice in a bucket and if
i mix that with my yellow because i have
access to yellow drinks so if you need
yellow drink maybe i could somehow get
it to you
yellow juice yeah i only have orange
green and purple
okay
i like this game i like solving puzzles
it's fun
do you have minecarts i'm sending some
over there right now
uh i do not have any minecarts no
not that i know but maybe i'll come okay
i should have arrived in a moment
they're coming
you guys it'll come from here
like a little hall
yara
you're ready to hear your voice please
home i love you too ah man
i'm here i'm here no worry don't worry i
just collected some juices the ones that
i have the
orange green and the purple one i just
put them in some buckets
okay
don't be scared am i don't be scared
where's the minecarts
what did that not arrive
not that i know of oh i see it i found
them there's nothing inside of them
though okay i'm gonna send you back some
juice
yes please do please please let's send
three juices
huh
okay
uh i was trying to add some of my colors
to
how can i get here
i lost connection on the last half of
that
ah i added some
purple juice to one of my plants to make
it grow but it didn't grow so that was
not the right thing
okay
i sent back some juice
sorry sorry i have the first plant that
i needed it just looked different when
it was growing but now that i take it i
already that's the one i was looking for
okay i have the
the weird
i think you call it pineapple mushroom
mushroom pineapple
yes
now let me plant the free eggplant one
but how about
get rid of these ones
i don't want to grow those
i want to grow
these ones
pour the juice on them
sorry what i sent you some juice
juice juice juice
just uh
currently the one that i'm making right
now needs no juicing
okay
drink i'm thirsty oh let's talk about
juice
make me thirsty uh and you can you just
send me whatever juice you have there
right over
uh copy that already on the way already
around
oh
nice
super speed delivery yes indeed it has a
raft i can't confirm
i have this big bottle and the only way
to get water from it is if i stab the
cap so there's a hole in the cap but i'm
drinking it like a big baby bottle
and wait do we have only any other
juices besides the yellow one
do you have any clue over there on
why the eggplant is not growing
um it looks like here the eggplant needs
red juice
uh do you have red juice ah no i only
have yellow juice
red juice
oh can you send me back any fruits
i'll send you a couple right i'll send
you the ones that i have that are on the
recipe
okay
oh can you send me back actually uh one
second
do you have that pineapple mushroom
yes one second
i know which one is supposed to do which
it looks like this one's like a infuser
or something like
maybe don't know
do you want to do this one first or this
one first
sanding mix it or infuse it probably
infuse
this is to get the juice out
look at him
um i guess i'll put it in here first
let me get a cup of juice
you send me more of those
okay
i can't eat it
it looks squeaky
i have made orange juice
it's red it's red i have red
red oh please send back to me
or no keep
uh keep keep the keep the red juice for
now
that's that
i'm i'm making wait do you still need
more of that one fruit uh yeah if i use
that fruit i can make the red juice
but you already have red juice so you
don't need any more right
yeah but what if you need it to grow
your fruit
ah
no it doesn't look like it i need orange
later
orange no you need orange my orange um
you know what
send it over can't uh can't be all
harmful but i'll send you one more fruit
fir
okay copy that
i can't i'm not gonna drink it maybe
i'll drink the next one
let's send it first
i'm scared i don't want to mess it up if
i drink it what if it's gone forever
sending you the fruit right now
uh please send me my order as well thank
you
okay it's on the way
noise ah that's so fast that
if this is
so fast that means that we're really
close to another as as if i could not
just walk for that tunnel and see you
oh uh definitely do that
okay so i'm making the next fruit for
the next
potion i'm gonna try to make the white
one
bye
and for the white one i need a long
[Music]
banana
let's call it banana banana with orange
juice
banana with oranges okay um
well
i you have the orange juice um but if
you want to make the banana we need the
green juice and the green juice is made
i think you have to send me green juice
in a bucket and i mix it with yellow
juice and then it makes green juice in a
mug
oh okay okay
maybe i should send back some uh orange
juice no i said no it's not yellow juice
i already sent back yellow juice i guess
thank you some things
[Music]
thank you uh i don't think i need the
orange bucket but um
okay thank you
oh wait wait
if i do this what is this for
like i can't place anything in here
i don't know what it's for oh well i
guess we'll figure it out later
all right so let's put the green juice
with the yellow juice
get some yellow juice
[Music]
yellow juice with the green juice
both of the red and the yellow potion
i'm sorry
uh that's okay i have a green juice
don't waste it i'm setting it
okay i wanted to use use it to grow my
plants but it didn't work okay i'm going
to send you another red juice
okay
oh so now i have a limited green juice
i like the sound of the juice
now we make some red juice
in that bag
uh i guess i'll send the yellow just
back
all right your deliveries on the way man
okay thank you that doesn't let me drink
it it only lets me drink the yellow
juice
so
you said green juice goes on banana
uh one second let me confirm uh yes that
is correct green juice on the moldy
banana over
it has worked
i have the banana
what are you gonna do with it
banana and orange thingy okay i'll send
you the banana and orange juice do we
already have the orange juice
i got it you can send me the other
colors because once you send me a bucket
i have it for like forever
ah okay
i think anyways
oh wait what am i supposed to be doing
with the banana what a way what am i
supposed to be doing with that stuff
you're sending me the banana i think you
have to mix it with the orange juice
uh okay
the orange bucket the orange bucket
copy that
and i'll send you purple and the other
color as well
just for late
okay uh scratch that i do not have the
buckets forever
oh okay okay should i send you one more
orange as well cause i just for the
other stuff uh no that's all right i i
have i have it
okay
wait why am i mixing the banana with the
orange
uh because that makes a white portion
stop that eat the white potion later to
mix it with uh
tentacle plants
to make green potions oh
okay
all right your delivery's on the way man
girl
oh
later after the stream
okay i got the white juice um
so next up
next i will make the i will make the
plants that are necessary for the blue
potion which is two blue plants one
it's like a ball of tentacles and the
other one is a holy egg
that's blue with some
shapes around the egg
i see it um yeah
it says on my recipe to grow that one
you just need the yellow juice which i
sent you a bunch of
oh for the for the holy blue holy egg i
need yellow juice yeah it says yellow
juice mixed with the seed packet for the
egg
grows the plant
okay nice because the other plant i
already have anyway okay i'll make that
plant brb
viv
they should uh put some more parkour
stuff around this map so
i got something to do
like a stack of boxes
oh
oh my god it worked
yeah you holy egg and
other things okay
we're gamers please mix for next blue
juice
oh sorry what am i mixing
blue juice you should get blue a blue
potion out of that yeah but uh what what
what two things about mixing
uh the things that i just sent you those
two only no juice extra
i wanted pure i want the pure flesh from
those fruits
your extract
extract
you need anything else
ah oh yeah i guess for the next potion
um did the did this one work the blue
one yeah it's in the cart ready to go
but i'm just trying to see if you need
anything else
oh oh i
need
white white juice i have but i need one
more plant that i'm gonna make next i
don't know if it needs juice it looks
like the
the taco dachi
ah taco dashi yeah i have that in my
book um it says purple juice for that
one so you should be covered
okay wait hold on let me double check
that it's a one second is it bucket okay
yeah purple juice straight from the
bucket works
okay
all right your delivery has landed
oh thank you i made the plant successful
this is easy it looks beautiful
yay
okay we're back tonight let me check my
recipes so we have we have the
we have the white potion we have the
blue potion we also have the
red potion right
uh i think you have to send it all back
to me because i have a thing to mix it
all together like a it's like a little
mixer that i can put three potions into
yeah
i'll send you the white juice and the
the takodachi plants to make green juice
okay got it
wait
okay the things that are arriving now
you have to mix that together
oh to make a green potion
yeah that is necessary for the green one
how do i mix it can i put the potion in
here
not the green juice but the potion
i only got that i only got that last
part
am i making juice or potion
ah now you're making potion uh green
potion by combining the taco dancing
with the white potion
okay
whatever
and then we have to make the red one
again because that one was having juice
but i needed a potion
i guess okay
wrong thing in the beginning
uh
you have enough yellow juice
yeah i have i have the the one in the
mug can we turn that into potion into
your place
uh
well if you need red juice i just need
the pineapple mushroom
okay i don't know if i should be sending
her the green juice back but oh well i
sent the green juice
okay
i think you can probably keep that one
the oldest juices but okay i'll take it
for now send it back i'll send you back
uh
uh i'm like the the the plant first and
then i'll send you the the the other
potions that i have because i think you
have to mix them into the uh black one
okay
you guys see my sweet parkour skills
i think the other machine just like
mixes do you need to you need the triple
eggplant too though right the mushroom
and the eggplant
uh
unless you have a recipe that says i
need that uh to make the red juice i
just need the pineapple mushroom
and my recipe says for the red one
you need a triple eggplant and the
mushroom pineapple
uh to make the red potion
oh yes yes he has the red potion
copy
okay one second
i see it's confusing because there's a
potion and then there's just the juice
we just need the potion
i think you can go around this corner
like strafe
for the triple eggplant which juice was
necessary again to grow in
red juice
so i need
i need a that's what i needed that for
okay
okay i'll send you those two fruits
are they fruits
maybe they're vegetables
yeah probably
it looks tasty okay what i'm sending you
now combined will make a red potion
and with that
uh when you send me back the minecarts
i will send you the
the blue and the green potion
and then you can mix the red blue and
green into a black one i think that's
choppy that parts are on the way
hearts are on the move oh i got it
all right so put the red potion in here
now we wait
okay sanding blue and green
we're almost there
all right oh i see i can turn it
alright here we go
rip what do you mean it's fine
all right here we go
all right and i'm assuming i put this on
this
all right i'm sending you the death uh
ray
okay thank you
it's on the way
oh my god uh
oh dear okay i'll kill the plant i guess
good luck
that's good
it does it doesn't look very dangerous
but it did the trick
yeah
[Music]
door open
oh my door opened again okay i'm going
to the door we can't do one more riddle
i think
okay
wait how much of how much what's the
percentage of the game we have left guys
okay
oh
this reminds me of uh
okay
[Music]
it's all right
temporary
[Music]
amen
hello
hello did you also see a weird cutscene
uh it wasn't that weird i just have a
sword that's like rebuilding itself it
kind of looks like a diamond sword from
minecraft
cool stuff i'm in a really messy room
right now
uh me too there's a ton of like uh
different things i'm gonna go ahead and
describe my room first and then you go
um so there's a bunch of paintings
around the room and that are mixes of
different animals there's also let me
see what else i can interact with
there's a paintings with patterns
something else up here
i have the things good
i also have uh this jewel that i can
try to turn on but it does not turn on
and also i can remove the paintings on
the wall so maybe
i don't know where you're supposed to
match it
oh
okay
um oh look i
do
i cannot remove them
but i was able to move something on the
flower
like a puzzle
oh okay you can move the flower
paintings
yeah i'm going upstairs and upstairs i
have
i have a desk and i have a
world so
uh
thing
and i have more paintings i have more of
that uh
flower pattern thingy that i can operate
i have a little box little chest
treasure chest i can't interact with
most of these things though i have a
shelf
i have
and not so much up here except for that
those paintings until
oh
i found the book
and
uh the book
i can't i can't inspect the book and it
shows me
uh
the
oh god okay sorry i'm i'm gonna try to
describe this it looks like
um
it looks like a clock
but with no clock inside but on top of
it is a
ball
okay i have something like that and i
have a book that like shows directions
for it but i don't really understand it
at the moment um
maybe
we should uh try with the paintings like
uh try something with those
okay
i can't
do anything with them though
uh
okay uh describe like the general shape
of your room like on my room i have a
fireplace on the bottom floor do you
have that
yes i do
oh do you have a painting above the
fireplace
[Music]
no i don't
oh okay
uh okay
do you have any paintings along those
stairs
pick it up from i picked it up from the
chair next to the fireplace it's
the sand clock thingy that you can turn
around
an hourglass
yes yes
uh okay
i can barely pick up any things but yeah
ah
actually after i picked that thing up oh
i
[Music]
started getting like
uh
sparkly things
in some
places
like
um
i can place the items that i picked up
only in those sparkly places
like it's telling me to place it there
but i have a bunch of one two three
my brain hurts
guys this is the last level the second
to last 11. i have 11 places where i can
place those tiny items
[Music]
okay
um but anyway let's uh you wanted to do
the oh
you were able to pick them up
so i also have a
can candle thingy that has one two three
four it has uh seven candles on it
and i can turn off the candles on and on
i have them too
but i can not
turn up
okay so starting from
there on for you
i can turn them on and off so maybe i
should match them with yours so starting
from left to right tell me if it's on a
run or one through seven
yeah
left to right okay my left to right is
are we looking at it from the same angle
uh
i'm looking at it towards the fireplace
like i can see the fireplace behind it
okay then from left to right from that
angle is the first one is on the second
one is off
the third one is on
the fourth one is off
the fifth one is off the sixth one sixth
one is
on
and the last one is on
uh something happened i heard something
now you heard that too i've been hearing
some noises for a while now
is it up here
[Music]
are you doing something with the with
the camels
uh yeah i i got it and i when i uh
reached what uh
when i reached
like all the correct thingies some
something i heard a sound or something
like opening
yeah yeah my draw opened oh mine too i
have a book
i took the book
yeah i got a book mine has the letter i
on it yeah i have the same one
okay so i guess that one is uh
that candle thing is done
okay um how about let's try the
paintings you said you could do stuff
with the paintings
no i can't but you you're able to move
them around right
yeah
oh uh do you have any paintings like on
your staircase
yeah i got the okay staircase is
well
one of them is the the one of the
movable flowers
okay you know those those flowers
above it is uh
an animal that is free animals one of
the animals is a
a lion
one of them is a
camel looking thingy one of them is a
bird that's eating its own tail and it's
got bird feet as well
okay uh can we start from the paintings
on the bottom of the staircase like what
is your first painting
on the bottom of the staircase i have no
painting
uh your second painting you said was the
flowers
yeah the middle one is the flower thing
that you can move the third one is uh
the one that i just described with the
lion's name like it has a snake tongue
and the bird that eats its own tail and
the llama it's like one animal that's
free animals
chemera
okay also for the flower paintings i
can't move those
[Music]
um i can i can
okay so maybe
maybe we have to uh do something with
those two if you can move them but i
can't
yeah okay
what does it look like on your side
[Music]
one second
uh okay you already described the flower
painting um on my staircase
yeah if you want to do that one first
yeah um
i can turn four pieces
it's like
divided by four oh okay so on the bottom
there's like a rose bush it connects
like a rose bush uh on the very bottom
[Music]
it looks like a rose bush right guys
on on the bottom row you see a rose bush
yeah so on the very bottom like touching
the
frame of the painting is a rose bush and
then on either corner as the sunflower
sorry sorry on the left side right the
left piece or the right one as well
uh both the bottom pieces on the inside
corners
on the bottom it's a rose bush on the
outside corners on the bottom it's um
sunflower
was that noise oh okay yes okay i have
that aligned and about the top one
at the top the top um okay for the top
row the bottom corners of the top row
are both sunflowers
they like sunflowers bottom middle or
bottom right or bottom edges
a bottom bottom middle
uh okay then
in theory that should be correct
i think
but there's
more of those paintings i have one
that's upstairs um if you go upstairs
and then go right
[Music]
here as well
yeah um i have one above the chest and
the candles
yeah yeah yeah have that one too it has
a little bit of a different flower
pattern
okay i'm gonna go ahead and describe it
on the bottom two
in the outside corners
is a flower with three petals only
ah
i i didn't get the first part of the
sandals because i was also talking can
you repeat please
on the bottom row on the outside corners
on each of the outside corners for the
bottom row is a flower with three red
petals
[Music]
i think i think i got it can you do the
top row
all right the top row is the same thing
but flipped so for the top row the top
outside corners are both um
the three red petal flower
we got it
it's in the bag right
oh well so doesn't mean it just becomes
one perfectly aligned picture
for this one yes not for the other one
though okay
yeah for this one true yeah the other
one didn't okay let's go downstairs
okay the one next to the clock
okay for the
bottom bro the inside bottom corners for
the bottom row is like one big petal
without uh hold on this is confusing
because there's another one that's kind
of a one big pedal hold on one second
yeah
what's the best way to describe this
okay um
on the bottom row the top inside corners
which connect to the middle
are the ones which look like a bird's
feet
[Music]
ah
you mean several bird feeds
yeah
okay so the big one they'll be
yeah okay yeah i think i got that one so
that means that on
the
middle bottom
is a somewhat big petal with two green
leaves sticking out
yes okay okay then we got that one uh
top rope
on the top row the bird feet flower
is both of the bird feet flowers are on
the outside top corners
[Music]
oh but the other ones didn't open up
doesn't mean we have them incorrectly
but i got a book out of that
and maybe if we get all of them right
that's the one that's supposed to open
ah okay okay
then uh yes okay
next thing
we can do the the one with the clock
that has a book inside too the one it
has a book that says p
yeah i see that but i don't know where
it's supposed to do the clock
circle tank and the and the
um
on top of it that's like purple blue
color
what
oh oh or behind the
behind the um candles
yeah i see the orb
yeah yeah the orb one so for that i have
a book that uh says
it shows me some some crystals
and it says no touchy touchy
but then on the next page it says if you
do touch itachi
then the orb uh
lights up
and then the crystal also lights up and
that will make something out of the
uh
circle orb thingy pop out
sorry for that amazingly easy
explanation
i have the same book and um i think it
has the same diagram
but i don't really understand it
um
did we see those crystal fingers around
in the room
yeah there's about four or five of them
there's one on the top floor there's one
on the bottom towards the door
there's one by the
[Music]
paintings
we should do my paintings i don't think
i have them
okay uh how about we do the how about we
do the paintings um the animal paintings
like around the room i think they're
supposed to magic
um
should we start at the
staircase
yeah i got the uh i got the
i think i have the okay yeah just yeah
let's start at the staircase
okay um next to the flower painting that
we aligned
um
diagonally or
above it
right above it
like
right
sides
on that above
but not directly above it diagonally
above it there's only one place for the
painting to be yep
uh it's the one that i described before
it's a chimera that it has a bird eating
its tail and the camel thingy and a lion
with a snake
uh tongue and bird's feet they're
standing on it's one animal standing on
bird feet
uh
with a bird
with a beak eating its own neck which is
the tail of the animal
okay got it now the one next to it to
the right
okay next to it that's where the
staircase is already ending and you're
on the second floor though the first
footsteps
uh so that is an animal that's a bunny
with
angel wings white wings bunny feet and a
bird that eats its own tail again with
the tail being the neck as well at the
same time
a bunny or
angel wings bird feet a bird eating neck
does it have a snail shell on its head
[Music]
no snail shell only bunny ears pickle
only bunny ears
we're gonna take all the paintings
[Music]
only bunny ears
don't have that one
[Music]
all right uh let's go to the flower um
that's that's above the chest on the top
floor is there a painting to the left of
it
yes it is the same thing but with a
snail shell
okay
i must be missing the bunny one
somewhere
uh
then check over here
maybe i don't have it yet am i missing
it am i blind
i don't have anything with bunny ears
because this is a horn i think she would
describe it as hard okay uh
where else do you have paintings
sitting on that floor
sorry i have one more painting on that
floor
okay
uh it's next to the
bookshelf
on on and next to the i do have another
one
other bunny that was without a snail
shell
i saw the position you got it
uh yes
okay
there we have
um
it has a snail shell it has long bird
feet and it is just a bird in general
okay next painting is
next painting
oh you got this one
yeah we'll go uh there's like a painting
to the left of the stairs when you're on
the first floor
uh
left of the stairs
do you mean like in front of the windows
yeah
okay it's the same thing but with two
beaks
all right any other paintings about like
above the fireplace or
i have one painting that's really weird
it's above it's next to the door the
entrance door it's just a dude and it
says
nepias
uh where
next to the entrance door uh to the left
side of it or like looking
from yeah well got it all right i have
one more piece next to the entrance door
i got it i got one more painting left i
guess above the fireplace
well now above the fireplace i have no
painting
okay wherever your next painting is then
um
[Music]
ah sorry uh there's one more um on the
floor next uh in front of the window
[Music]
it's a snail shell and i can barely see
it it's really dark but it's like uh
[Music]
do you know where it opened
no i don't know
[Music]
at top of the staircase where somewhere
on top of the staircase on top of the
staircase
ah okay i found it
all right um
yeah then shall we now do the the last
thing the i think it's the last thing
i don't see any other way
go to the clock
oh there's another book here yeah yeah
okay
to the right side of the clock um do you
see like something that you can move or
something like that
ah
yes i see some button
buttons
when i move the buttons the
um
the
thingy though the the thing comes out of
the clock
okay so on my clock i have uh three big
circles with a different amount of like
uh strikes on it so i can tell you the
numbers so like for the first one it's
four
uh as if it were
uh nine ten eleven twelve one
that makes sense nine ten eleven twelve
one okay that's too much
uh so i have four strikes where it would
be like 10
11 and one on the clock
guys that on the
is that on wait you said you had three
three
knobs uh yeah there are three knobs on
the clock and then on the very top one
there's four strikes which are in the 10
11 12 and one spot as if the circle of
the top knob was eight o'clock
how many do you have on the other two
uh six on the bottom which are in from
places uh eight to two if therefore
o'clock
i know that's important
and on the third one
uh three as if it were eleven twelve one
okay okay okay
oh when i move them
uh the time actually
oh
the one on in the middle makes the time
uh the seconds go faster
yeah the time goes faster
is there anything on the bottom one
sorry sorry can you say that again
is there anything on the very bottom
uh it's like a reset button
i think let me test it out
oh
who's that
i press it once and oh oh you press it
too
no i can't press it i can only look at
it
uh one after i press it once
something slightly moves and then i
can't
and i can't immediately press it again
i think it's like opening a lock i think
it's supposed to like at the end um
uh open up the
the the door for the book
yeah so i guess we just have to get it
correctly
[Music]
oh okay okay
uh sorry i kinda
[Music]
i really
uh don't wanna interrupt right now but i
really need to go to an aisle meeting
oh okay
take it down oh i mean yeah i'll be fast
i promise sorry
[Music]
i'm describing it right right guys right
at the top one there's four marks which
are in the 10 11 12 and one place
and then in the second one there are six
marks which are in the
eight nine no this is nine ten eleven
twelve two okay nine to two i think i
gave her the wrong i said eight two
i just guessed i didn't count it
[Music]
i'm a little bit sleepy i'm probably
gonna sleep
yeah i'm gonna take a nap after this
but uh kiara has to go to and i don't
know if we'll be able to beat this level
in time is this like the second to last
level or something
cause like we already knew that we
wouldn't have enough time to be able to
finish it because she's at the
convention like um
a little less than an hour and like 40
minutes she's gotta be on for like
a little over 45 minutes
final set of puzzles oh so wait
like um
because this is like a different chapter
area once we come back and start again
will it just start in this area instead
of like well i guess if we open this up
and maybe it'll go to another area
you know what i mean like for the
electric thingy
uh yeah
the paint out yesterday was pretty cool
they were like uh
people
that were cosplaying
us and myth that's cool
and then um
yeah they were like people
i remember some people's names
[Music]
and yeah it was fun especially with you
know there's it's fun to do it with like
another person too
because we both got the answer
nina was really sweet
yeah there are like two or three people
cosplaying me
it's pretty cool
and then um
yeah the room was smaller i guess
because it's like raining a lot so they
had to move the room
um but the room was smaller than like
the one that we had in the other panel
but it was still filled up all the way
i wonder if anybody like couldn't get in
this head
nobody was cosplaying bubba but somebody
did have a mask that had the small
rocket on me
i think she's back
sorry i'm back
no problem
okay okay okay where were we uh clock
yeah so i figured out i figured out
where i went wrong so on the second knob
it's actually
uh six marks from nine to two
okay uh when can you can't move them can
you
nah they just have the marks that i just
read off to you
when i move mine
does anything change that you play
no probably not until you press the
button at the end and we got it right
ah
okay okay
uh
wait
[Music]
i wonder if like uh for this thingy like
if she touches the orb
i'm trying to figure out what each knob
does my middle one changes the the speed
of the
the clock i guess
the lower the lowest one makes the
um
birds at the top come out
i'm not sure what the top one does
though
i don't think it matters what they do as
long as we have the like the marks i
have as long as i give them to you
correctly
okay okay
uh okay so i'll read them off again from
the top on the very top
there's um four marks in the 10 11 12
and one spot
yes
okay and then in the second one there's
six marks in the 9 10 11 12 1 2 spot
okay
and then in the last one there's three
marks in the 11 12 and one spots
okay
press the button
okay i guess that's not what we're
supposed to do
okay maybe we're supposed to do
something else
ah
ah wait i'm not sure if i did something
wrong one second uh
[Music]
ah
i have
four dials
at the top
one two three four five
one two three four five six at the
middle one
and three dials
in the uh below in the lowest one
uh
it changes
the sound of the
clock
okay maybe maybe we're just supposed to
get it to the right time
[Music]
what is the right time
time doesn't change at the uh top it
always says the same
it only changes the
um
[Music]
the big circle thing in the middle that
goes from left to right
does that one move for you
uh it looks like it's just moving
normally on my side
what's normally
see i can make that go faster but when i
do that on my side does it make it
faster on your side as well
no
okay can you exactly this is a rhythm
game maybe
can you exactly tell me at what rhythm
like just
uh imitated
[Music]
one two
one
i got that one i got that one i think
uh
maybe we just have ways behind that
like behind that clock that's moving
[Music]
what
um behind the clock that we just like um
adjusted the ribbon
what is that called pendulum chimes yeah
oh yeah charms okay
um in what position are those is that
the left one higher than the middle one
or something like that
[Music]
okay uh hold on let me find it let me
think of a good way to describe it one
second
because i can change the position of
those
all right the
middle okay this so the
far right one is higher than the middle
and the left one but the left one is
higher than the middle
okay then i think i got that one too um
ah i know what the last one does the
lowest uh knob um makes the bird come
out right but
i have three different sounds so when
your bird comes out what sound does it
make
okay
did we get it you guys wait i have the
three different sounds they're different
but they're very similar so you could
cook
um
sounds like all of them
uh yeah just look different too what
does it look like you
uh it's a jester
what's i think all of my free are
jesters but they have different poses
one has the arms like a certain
dominance one has um
on the bench it's sitting on
uh the one end mine is sitting
[Music]
nice work
oh my god
i like that one that one's nice
is that how you're supposed to do it
you're sh
you're sorry i am motivated
i'm
and did you get the book
yeah i got it
okay then i think now it's really only
the
the orb thingy left
ah
thinking that uh
the orb is is your
round orb glowing
no
is anything glowing for you
yeah oh now the orb is glowing
that's it
now it's not glowing anymore
oh actually no mine that's probably not
the last one i still have items that i
have to place everywhere but we can do
the orb thingy now it's glowing glowing
glowing
it's also glowing now now it's not
one second
okay
okay so when it's glowing then i'll
touch
i'll attach one
okay okay
tell me when it glows i'll see i keep
telling you it's not glowing
still not glowing
[Music]
something just moved
i think
ah it's going it's going it's going fast
fast blow okay is it still going
something came out of it
something came out of the some um
knob came out of the thing
okay is it still like it ah
it it's not glowing but i think the
first thing you did was correct
now it's glowing
uh but only now now the first thing is
uh went back in
the bolt the i have like i have uh i
think five bolts
that can came out of can can't come out
of it
the first one went back inside though
yeah i have the same orb and i see it
pop out i just need to know when it's
like actually going because then i press
the thingy
okay
so i guess we'll try a different one
after this one
it's it was glowing very softly now it's
glowing very fast and very brightly
but the knob is not coming out i just
hear a lot of noises i think that you're
activating them now it's going fast fast
going
slow glowing
ah so it's like a
fast glowing very fast slow glowing
[Music]
as fast not glowing was just growing
fast growing fast glowing
knob came out so i think fast glowing is
better than slow glowing
yeah so when i get closer to like the
different crystals around the
area for me it's either fast or slow and
i guess the fastest one is the one i
should touch so tell me whenever it's
going fast
okay
okay it's not going now
as little glowing slow
slow
fast fast faster
fast fast yes knob came out yes yes
we got it uh slow growing slow fast fast
fast yeah fast fast fast yes knob came
out number three
fast glowing fast glowing fast clothing
fast going yes number four
put in your book spell
oh they spelled something
but i still have something i mean i
still have a lot of objects and i think
i have to place them around the room
because i have the glowing spots
all over the room
okay what are the objects
sorry sorry can you say that again
what are the objects
i have um
i'm not sure if i have all of them but i
have
okay the cube place it next to the uh
orb machine
right or left
uh right
[Music]
okay one sec
hourglass
ah
okay i have a
uh
i also have the the
globe
okay let's do the uh hourglass i want
you to place it on the desk uh on the
bottom floor across from the fireplace
with the scale on it and place it on the
right corner
okay
done uh now i have i have the cube and i
have a box that's open with a key okay
the
box place it on the fireplace mantle on
the right side
[Music]
okay okay
wait that box you place you said it's
open it has like a turning knob thingy
it has a
key inside and yeah on this on the right
side
it's a turning thingy in
it's not a record player
oh wait maybe it is
ah wait is that a key i guess yeah
that's probably a record players it's a
music box yeah
okay so what is it that you have left
uh a globe a standing globe not the one
that's next to the desk um
in the ground floor that's a different
globe
but does it look like it
it looks very similar but it has like a
longer like a single singular foot to
stand on
a singular foot lobe
oh okay uh in on the top floor
uh
legs to stand on it's like a mini globe
on the top floor on the second floor um
on the bookshelf put it on the second
bookshelf on the left side on the inside
corner
[Music]
oh
i think they'd open up something
there's a chest behind you
what is this spell
[Music]
what's this
wait sorry where did you find that one
uh
on the staircase
um
on the second floor there's a chest
underneath the flower painting
ah ah here okay okay got it
so
is there another rainbow is down in it i
think that's it
what do we do with these books
i don't know
place them in the bookshelf
i don't think so i can't i don't have
like an option to place them anywhere
like put them down
um
let's try to find
some spot where it i found it dirted or
so i mean it must be somewhere nevermind
wait no i thought that i thought i could
do it here
i'm glad you didn't hear that didn't you
get really excited
uh yeah
oh there's some
one more chest that looks like it can be
opened i don't know if you see it it's
next to a broken door to the left of it
by the clock
[Music]
if you mean the same chest i cannot open
that one can you
uh no but okay i found the place to put
the books uh next to the fireplace
there's a little bookshelf underneath a
small painting
ah
okay
what can we spell with this
i'm sure we're supposed to spell out
something and that's probably somewhere
in the room hidden is it nepeas
what
yeah
okay you know that that weird painting
we put next to the door that's some
graffiti on it it says n-e-p-i-a-s
and that's exactly the letters that we
have ah good point but my painting on
the top row it says esp so maybe we
connect it like your top row goes in
front of my top row or something
oh okay never mind i'll just i'll just
place it what my painting says
okay okay
oh i got mine
[Music]
uh maybe we should swap our words
okay okay
uh like can i spell the thing out that
you have over there or
uh yeah i'll read it out to you um on my
painting it says esp
you have a t
i i don't
yeah you have the same books now but
okay so e-s-p-i-a
yes e-s-p-i-a-n
okay i i didn't sell
uh okay for you it's n-e-p
[Music]
okay we did it but we should probably
end it here because the next one
probably gonna take too long
yeah but uh i don't know if it'll save
here like uh can we at least go okay
just go into the door
yes yes i am inside um if it closes
behind us it's good well even if it
doesn't save i think
if we if we don't play it like five
months later we can kind of remember
what we did
oh yeah yeah it'll be we'll speed run it
the next time
uh okay
[Music]
okay well then
uh
i guess that's it for today
yeah
that was uh i think in the beginning we
had to warm up our brains that was why
that was so frustrating
yeah i think so too
and let's turn on discord and sell this
crappy wonky talking
watch that over
vilest of deeds had tricks to fool
hello
hi
thank you you did a really good job too
i think we our communication skills are
pretty
uh on point
i was amazed by you doing the the ladder
thingy because i i was basically doing
nothing while i was on the ladder it was
all you oh yeah i just needed the
directions yeah i could like visualize
it in my head based off of what you told
me though
yeah that was that was fun my my least
favorite one was a freaking tubes pipes
fiend
yeah
yeah i hate that one i think it's like a
probably if we were swapped i probably
would have missed the um pressure meter
too
so
yeah
uh as a game changer once we found out
the pressure thing
i also think it was confusing because
you were already able to go to the like
other riddles that came after that even
though i was stuck in that room and i
only had the the gas but you were able
to see other things like that is so
confusing you won't know like what to
start with what what matters and what
doesn't matter yeah
this chat they kept uh yelling at me
they're like no i mean do that later
yeah but can't blame you if i were in
that position i would probably try to
figure out maybe the other things matter
as well i don't know
yeah so
we we both had our uh ponkotsu moments i
think but
all in all we've both tried our best so
yeah what the heck i think we did a good
job you know once we got the ball
rolling our brains were like firing away
yeah yeah the last room with all the
small riddles was good i think because
they were not too too complicated
yeah yeah
um yeah i mean do you have any advice
for the convention you were there
yesterday i'm going to be there in like
half an hour yes um
you don't want to do a wave so you know
just make it happen
got it wait did you do one no no
no no
well then i'll do it again i did it last
time i'll do it again i'm excited
okay uh i wish there was so much
yeah i just i i feel like it's it's kind
of difficult for me to ask the audience
like all right guys everybody we're
gonna stand up now even though you were
waiting outside for three hours you know
wha what wait that's fun they love the
kind of stuff
it's hard for me to hype them up i think
you definitely do it better
okay i'll do my best
and what what kind of what kind of
questions did you get this time oh it's
kind of cool because like uh they asked
me and enough both questions at the same
time so we could like answer questions
about each other and stuff like that so
i think it'll be cool yeah
oh
ah but
questions about each other you don't
mean like couple questions like what
what kind of uh uh juice does the other
person like to drink the most no no not
like that just like uh oh like uh how
did your initial impression of them
change you know from now until then that
sort of thing
oh that's cool because last in the last
convention where both both of us were we
were separately
alone on one day and then at this
convention yesterday was you and enan
today is me and you know so it's it's
cool that they ask like questions for
both of us that's nice so yeah
yeah oh so maybe i get some
takutori questions
yeah you will you know hopefully this
game is the employee like last time
huh
what the same person was there no i'm
just saying i hope there's a kfb
employee oh
they're they're they might be there on
the cover they might try to hide their
chicken feathers because it's a bit a
bit like you know you stand out in the
public yeah
but i saw yesterday oh that was so sweet
i mean i saw what you did with photoshop
on twitter and put you put like yourself
in cosplay there so cute
uh yeah there was like a and there's
like an empty space there you know it
felt it felt like unbalanced without you
so
ah man you look so good with orange hair
and and uh
you also put in some highlights in your
hair and all that it looks so good oh
thank you well i mean well that's your
hair made me
oh well i hope i hope uh
i can
um make a good impression on everyone
today
it's gonna be fun yo i think you're
really good at hyping up a crowd so yeah
this is gonna do it's gonna go great
um you're very good at that too though
you know that
yeah you are yes you are
yeah i'm very much so i'll take it oh
thank you
also you are at all like we have this
tour of five conventions right and
you're at all of them yeah yeah i wanted
to do all of them because uh i don't
know it's fun
now i kind of look i lowkey regret not
selecting all of them like you but at
the same time i felt like it's going to
be too stressful and honestly it already
is so
yeah especially because like uh well we
had a break between this one and the
first one but like the already the next
convention is like this coming weekend
but then after that there's like a month
break i think because the next one is oh
yeah that's right
yeah but the next one is next weekend on
our anniversary yeah
wait am i on that one i don't even i'm
not even sure
i don't think so i think i think it's
cali yeah and
maybe i don't know oh okay yeah that's
probably why i don't have it in my
calendar
okay that's good then because i'm busy
with other stuff like tesla varies
release things oh
yeah i've been waiting for that for ages
is there any game that you were waiting
for at the moment to release
this month i think it's this month it's
a dlc for uh outer wilds which is a
space game
i think i saw anya playing that today
yeah
yeah she she's i think she's on like
party eight or nine she's been playing
it for a while now it's really fun well
did you play it already on your channel
yeah i beat it
whoa you're gonna play the dlc too yeah
i'm gonna play like uh like one week
after it comes out because then the chat
would be like
i don't know
and i can't watch i'm gonna get spoiled
yeah but you know what if you you you
should you don't like backseaters do you
if you play one week later then they'll
tell you how to play it
on the first day so they don't know how
to play that's true that's true i guess
i could always watch it later after they
play
yeah yeah yeah
i'm always like if there's a game coming
out that i was waiting for i i would not
be able to wait a whole week to play it
never
oh
yeah somebody will spoil it that's a
good point
yeah
yeah but anyway however you want to do
it you do you um i'm going to check it
out too because it sounds interesting
very interesting
so nothing i will play it though okay
because it's like a puzzle exploration
game and you have to like put all the
pieces together and you also get the fly
spaceship and yeah
i like the spaceship idea but i don't
like the puzzles about that
yeah it's pretty is it's a pretty big
brain game
is it as big brain as this game
um
i wouldn't say the puzzles are his big
brain but just like the whole mystery
and stuff like just solving it because
you kind of like have to solve a mystery
so yeah
i would say it is
oh oh okay it it's a lot of reading
ah i like reading
wait my chat's gonna say
okay you can read what
they did before and i sent them to the
user room so they better oh
they're axing they're axing gotta punish
them
i will you guys i'm writing down all of
your names all of you every single one
of you
rude oh my god is your chat ever like
doubting what you say as well oh all the
time yeah they're always like i mean
you're wrong i mean you're wrong and
sometimes i'm wrong but most of the time
i'm right and then i get to rub it in
their faces
but dude that's nice but do they doubt
like your skills like when you say i can
do this and that like i can go i can
jump from a 20 meter
uh you know those those jumping things
in swimming pools oh yeah yeah probably
yeah oh would they doubt you if you say
that
yeah they'd be like
but you you would be the best in that
ground pounding the water
oh yeah i've seen like a video like that
where it's like super high up and it's
like a challenge like to jump i wouldn't
i would
i would do it but i definitely hesitate
because i kind of like that feeling of
like oh god am i gonna do this i don't
know
really does your butt ever hurt from
ground pounding
um yeah yeah sometimes my tailbone
because like you know how when you sit
on it weird
yeah that happens
yeah when i when i sit in front of the
pc for hours and hours my butt will
start hurting just from sitting so i
can't imagine how much it must hurt from
ground pounding so much oh it reminds me
that reminds me i have to say it was not
on purpose to have my mom come to the
minecraft server when you were on
vacation i was not on purpose yeah i
thought somebody was like uh maybe she's
trying to avoid ahmed she doesn't get
ground pounding i love that logic that's
theory but no actually she's coming back
to the minecraft server next week and
that will probably be the last time but
we'll be like building for probably like
five to six hours or so so
you could you could come by if you're
awake you can't say hello to my mom
she's a business hi
i'll stop by no i'm not farmer you know
you definitely are but she thought that
maybe your ground pounding uh thing is
serious and should be taken seriously
and i thought no no no no it's just
jokes
don't worry about it i wouldn't do that
i'm very respectful
yes i believe that
i believe in you amen thank you yeah
chad that's one of those things chat is
like
again again here they go again
i think my mom wants to
meet you she just doesn't she's a little
bit of a sunday maybe she doesn't admit
it but she i'm sure she will be happy to
meet you she was very shy when gouda and
ina suddenly showed up yeah um but then
afterwards she said she was really happy
and the girls were really sweet so i
think she would be happy to meet you
did she met cali already
no no callie was not around either so i
think yeah it was a shitty time for her
i think
yeah so maybe next time
oh you don't force yourself i think it's
going to be a shitty time for you too
i'ma wake up weird times
okay
that is true all right um i'll get ready
for the convention and
i'll talk to you soon and we'll plan out
the next session of this stupid puzzle
game okay well yeah we're gonna beat it
for sure
yes next time we'll beat it um maybe
schedule some more time today we didn't
have so much time excuse me
we probably have like two hours left i
bet
hope hopefully yes hopefully not so much
yes
um
yeah so what do you always say at the
end of your stream
no no no no i mean
um
bye-bye
wow
i don't have a catchphrase
you gotta come up you know now you have
a good opportunity to come up with one
because you know it's gonna be uh one
year anniversary now is the time to make
up new things i was trying to say i was
trying to get aya like saying aya to
catch on so i was like saying ayasami
um
okay
i think i think yeah has has potential
oh thank you thank you yeah
all right uh then you say i asked me and
i say
i'll be the same guys
tomorrow in a mongoose and unarchived
karaoke stream
i'm nodding but i won't be there but
have fun i'll show up together in this
room because he said you're doing like a
german anime or did you jordan yeah i'm
singing a lot of german karaoke songs
like there's there's some um animes that
were on german tv with german openings
so i'm singing a bunch of those like
digimon and
pokemon and sailor moon and dora me and
all that kind of stuff but i'm also
going to be singing anime songs who
didn't get an official uh adaption of
german opening which is the fan made one
so i'll mix it up ah that sounds really
fun
yeah so maybe you can
check it out if you have them i really
like your yours your rendition of sparks
oh
[Music]
uh disclaimer please do not start a fire
today uh at least not without me being
there
okay
yeah any parental supervision
yes yes i will be the supervisor so i
assume
i asked me goodbye everybody thank you
for watching
we'll see you next time
[Music]
hello
hey guys uh teammates investigators
thank you guys for watching
uh i like puzzle games thank you guys
for all support thanks for the super
chats
i really appreciate it uh probably on
sunday we'll read them
i think
wait is that tomorrow on tomorrow
tomorrow we can catch up on super chats
and uh hang out for a little bit okay
usual time probably
i'll see you guys then
yes tomorrow
still i'm feeling a little bit better um
so we'll see how the next week goes
okay i see you guys
bye thank you for watching thank you
support
[Applause]
credits
[Music]
thank you