[Music]
he
Mina s yo de beats what's going on it's
me your certified boy and me Mor cop k k
c just Mor Mor's also fine too those are
all fine things to call your certified
boy welcome everybody uh to my kingdom
of cringe yeah I hope you guys are ready
for a good time together um and today I
will be interviewing a very interesting
person somebody that I think is actually
um extremely interesting why well
because it's me sadly never mind maybe
less interesting than I thought that's
what I thought today I'll be
interviewing myself about my brand new
album release Phantom which is releasing
today in all places at 100 p.m.
depending on where you live I think they
a 16 where wherever it is that you live
basically maybe I don't know I don't
know do you know how to read a clock I
don't I I don't know I don't know how to
do anything except ask questions that's
why interview Moria is here today hi I'm
interview Mory a very special version of
my that only conducts interviews when my
real is also present dot do dot question
mark I don't really know what I'm doing
or where I was supposed to go with this
doesn't matter though because now it's
time for
questions uh today are you ready to
answer some questions for us today miss
gu what should I call you cuz you're
basically me but I don't know myy cie
either anything
dumbass that's cool I guess yeah I'll be
asking you questions then also sorry
sorry if I interrupt you I've been known
to interrupt a little bit it's very
silly you're a silly one anyway let's go
ahead and get started with the album
with the album first question oh man I
didn't think about what to ask are you
kidding me this is your job I came in
here with a whole with a whole plan and
now I have no plan all right shut up
silence be quiet shut your mouth I'm the
one asking the questions here okay
dmy all right first question is what is
the theme of your brand new album
Phantom okay well basically it's a
combination of the word Phantom and
pantomime Phantom being well I'm a
phantom pantomime being a type of play
okay very cool question how many songs
are on the album um well 10 10 but also
we have bonus tracks depending upon
which album you grabbed so it could be
up to 11 but uh 10 officially for the r
what was your favorite song to make out
of all of them son my with junen Johnny
is probably my favorite I'm probably the
most satisfied with it and and you know
we got to speak English with each other
working on the song so that was pretty
cool um I didn't really have that kind
of experience with another artist
getting to like kind of jam on a song's
lyrics before getting into the studio
and recording it what what was the genre
that you were going for here were you
aiming for a certain genre or like were
you just doing the thing that you always
do that's super inconsistent you just
make whatever you want all right it's
kind of rude don't really appreciate
that but um I mean yeah it's not an
insult but it's not an insult I'm just
saying I don't want to make that a lot I
know I know I don't want to make the
same songs all the time basically is is
what it is you know so I I try to kind
of mix it up and just make what I feel
like making yeah that's what I do that's
what the dead beat's known me for I
guess okay yeah that's all well and good
also I have another question though yeah
what what's the
question ah gee I forgot what it was are
you kidding me this is your job no I'm a
great interviewer
silence silence I beg to differ don't
talk [\h__\h] about someone who's right next
to you but then also at the same time
don't talk [\h__\h] about people that aren't
right in front of you either that's kind
of rude also word gets around too when
you talk [\h__\h] about people people find
out okay well but if you're me though
sorry this is supposed to be about the
new album isn't it okay uh what kind of
hold on a second I got a question it's
about the music videos do you have any
more music video plans yeah yeah we have
a couple that are supposed to come out
you know go-getters and one other song
actually that I don't think you guys
what of the music videos that have come
out so far is your favorite um well you
really interrupt people aot you really
interrupt people a lot um well I did
that time sorry yeah can you please
silence for a second sakiyama Overkill
right now I'm more of a fan of 2D
animated music videos I would say just
because like I want to wait for my 3D to
get updated then maybe I'll want some
more 3DS but you know it's kind of rough
right you know dead beats know that you
know it is what it is I like the 2DS a
lot check it out PR good choices I would
say right there not bad not bad at all
my favorite has not yet come out so I
hope that you guys will look forward to
it I just answer the question that wait
it was sakiyama wait but aren't we the
same person so shouldn't I am I lying to
all these people and saying that my
favorite hasn't come out yet do we have
different taste I don't know maybe on
different days possibly but I don't know
who could say I don't she's so silly she
she's a funny one can you please stop
aren't you you're silly stop it stop oh
come on don't be bashful or anything
like that we I mean I'm you I know how
you feel all the time really that's kind
of embarrassing to think of people
always say that that we should be kinder
to each other right MH well no all the
time the dead beats are like yo Mory be
kinder to yourself well this is me
trying to do that okay hey you're doing
okay am I really I mean it I may yell at
you a lot and say like oh yeah those old
lyrics were cringe Etc and this was bad
and this sounded like [\h__\h] but you know
that's fine cuz we're supposed to do
that right literally every artist does
that to themsel yeah I think that's
normal that's not bullying I'm No Bully
you kind of are though Mor stop being
mean to cie yeah I'm No Bully well they
say I think you're doing great kid what
okay that was a little that was a little
patronizing patronizing patronizing
which one is it is it patronizing or
patronizing patronizing it's one of them
it's one of them yeah I would say so
maybe yeah I don't know well don't don't
worry too much because you know listen
the album release is going to go just
fine all right you know I'm sure that
I'm sure that you probably want to
you probably want to just I don't know
kind of talk more about this yourself
you don't really need me sitting here
asking you questions correct the dead
beats are here for that right true
enough yeah you don't really need me
here right just talk at them you know
yeah I think that'll go fine like I
usually do are you scared that I'm are
you scared I'm leaving I mean kind of oh
don't leave me interviewer myy don't
leave me I'm just nervous that's all
stop being nervous you got to stop being
shy at a certain point okay to do this
kind of business you have to have a
little bit of an ego and you got to have
a little more confidence okay so buck up
okay chin up I don't want to chin up
Bozo today's the release of your second
major album and you're very proud of it
I mean I I'm proud of it and I'm you so
yeah I'm just going to put that out
there okay well you know you're the more
prouder side of me more confidence let's
become one you want does that sound okay
well if it'll get you to shut you want
to become one yeah
okay let's become one let's become
one yeah that's fine with me that's fine
with
[Music]
me mea song that was strange anyway I'm
here I'm back we've become one what is
this don't worry about it that was just
a strange thing I thought that maybe if
I separated like a piece of myself and
like put it in another corporeal being
maybe I could like have that piece of
myself interview me but I'm terrible at
interviewing myself so I think maybe
it's it's best that we don't we don't
follow that
path I'll just I'll just talk to you
guys myself and she was
absorbed a Shiki gumy shinig gami you
got to you got to get creative sometimes
when you realize that you're doing a Hol
Melo radio episode that's just yourself
just yourself right here to to perfor
perform Tois no I didn't mean to read
that that just came up randomly on the
stream chat hi everybody it's me Mory
CLI welcome to H melow radio episode
episode 4 a special episode that is just
for me to celebrate the release of
phantom M yay welcome everybody I've
heard the word on the street is that
some folks are already able to access
the album I think it's on
Spotify question mark well did you guys
know that if you grab if you grab the
iTunes version if you grab that buy it
download it I believe there's like a
special deal I'm not sure if it's on
sale or whatnot but if you download it
you also get to hear a super
embarrassing rough demo of Tide with
ugly singing and and incorrect
Japanese but I mean it's part of the
process so I thought that I would I
would share with share it with you guys
you know the iTunes version did not give
you the track oh boy time to go tell
universal time to go tell
Universal it might not give it to you
until it's 1:00 p.m. your
time we're
saying come on iTunes you got to you got
to give them their super
embarrassing rough
track s super embarrassing ugly singing
is the rough track in iTunes only thing
it is it is but there's supposed to be
some kind of like sale or something
going on anyway let me go ahead and open
up that link this is always kind of what
happens you guys this always tends to
happen for whatever
reason I can listen I don't know
purchasing on iTunes seems impossible
for
me anyway Universal
Gat oh no they didn't put the rough
track in there oh boy the streaming's
live though H I'll listen to the whole
thing while I work out whoa cool
skeleton can you do that even all that
muscles
really curse you time
zones Amazon let you download the zip
folder but it's empty with no music
files I bet you just got to wait until
1:00 p.m. your time that was what they
told me they said that it was supposed
to be 1: p.m. the time of wherever you
are in the world Etc that was what it's
supposed to be but I don't know I don't
know start the ri no riots no riots
we're here to celebrate everybody we're
celebrating oh my gosh I forgot to play
the first song the first song was
supposed to be the intro to all of this
dang it well I think that as soon as you
see what song we're going to start off
with today on hello radio you'll
immediately know
what the theme for today's radio song
Choices is going to be are you ready
check this
[Music]
out [\h__\h] it kills must people takes guns
re kind of was in the ruins of Hell us
to Ling the audience cuz to my surprise
natur Li she nice stoping the
[\h__\h] de she human sure can't
stop the Pacer make sure standing off SL
out high five I see you buy [\h__\h] I
believe you C Hell in a Lal sense a
bit
super at the kill dream my the scene
it's like that if you take my advice
you'll be you don't know but the other
say that I like so much more along the
lines that you read you [\h__\h] see so I
don't know a so could you let go slow
from me so I'm not asking for do me a
favor bch is so
[\h__\h] with the till we get him say
all up it's what you want me coming in
the night for
ex
[Music]
any no I wasn't dancing I wasn't dancing
to that old Dumb
Song are you kidding me anyway that song
is kind of where a lot of things started
so I thought that I would play that
right the theme is is probably not
really completely apparent just yet but
I'm sure that you'll figure it out yes
you were caught in 4k I don't know what
you're talking about are you kidding me
no no no kidding me humble beginnings
humble beginnings I don't know maybe I
certainly feel like I got humbled the
more that I started doing things if that
makes any
sense but I wouldn't say in the
beginning I really thought I was the
[\h__\h] or anything like that it was
definitely a different frame of mind
though I was a a lot more confident in
that like I'm just going to go out and
do what I want
right but then the harsh realities of
the entertainment industry begin to
creep in and you know things change
right over time can't be helped but let
me think how many things have I released
in the past well dead beats was the
beginning of all of it right to
reminisce a little bit dead beats was
really kind of crazy because I don't
think anybody really expected something
like that to like get as big as as it
did you're having fun doing something
unserious oh yeah I was not serious
about anything it was just funny and
cool but once it started doing well I
thought to myself maybe I can make
something for real out of this you know
something that isn't just a hobby Etc I
think over time it definitely changed
quite a bit dead beat Jerk it now says
that dead beat interesting that you say
that because actually when I when I
think about it when I think about it
um a lot of a lot of times when I get
asked to do radio shows Etc especially
in Japan Mo mostly actually only in
Japan they're always like dead beats
dead beats dead beats play dead beats
I'm going to
sneeze I say dead beats play dead beats
we want to play dead beats why do they
want to play it so bad I don't know they
like it I don't know if it's something
about the the way that the the rap
sounds to them or something like that
the more like high-pitched and like
cocky sounding obnoxious sort of
sort of rap they like that they like
that yeah again it was It was kind of
doing unserious things very
playfully so play Dead
bears Dead
bears why are we talking about bears I'm
pretty sure that was a typo right thank
you for the
blessings We Are The Lovable
sort 90% of gold skulls are here because
of the Dead Beast EP it did bring a lot
of people in here and a lot of folks
stayed interestingly enough they stuck
around why I wonder but it makes me
happy I'm
glad that song was actually supposed to
be the very first song that that played
in this radio program but it wasn't so
because we're a bit behind schedule in
that regard we'll go ahead and play the
next one and you guys are definitely
going to be able to sniff out a theme
after this one I think check it out
[Music]
tonight the Moon is r a crimson R but
Ros got a Wier so I'll live forever
instead and now I can't get rid of all
of these thorns in my head bring on the
hammer I guess I'll live inside your
memory another story that IGN the
deceased I live inside of a castle pray
I'm never released I rather kick it in
the dungeon cuz I'm back in a beast I'll
bet my heart on the cars because I trust
me the least
do it precious moment it of emerald
scream sh it the best all about it keep
Shadows this creeping feeling of idty
losing in on every side of
me red tomorrow red
today
dread turn back time I'll always be a
priser to my ambition last pedal
I'll dance your tun but hold your breath
just who's running to show when this WEA
runs black I'll ask you I everything you
imagine when my finally up the sun is
falling down I'll turn Stone
again ah yes red one of my old faves
it's a lot a lot of times I wish I could
go back in time not go back in time
can't do that I wish I could be recorded
or something like that but at the same
time I think it's also good to not
re-record songs especially ones that are
so beloved by the community because
they're a window back into a different
time let them be make new
songs hey can't turn back time am I
right yeah also did you check that out
the year Mori cover right the year Mori
cover actually you may notice a bit of a
similarity with this one and also un
alive and also
Cinderella that's right I like
consistency you guys know that I'm a big
fan of consistency
ex it's a little sarcastic though
because songs do be a little
inconsistent but the one consistent
thing throughout my songs is that you
know it's me that's for sure that was
another thing that I thought about a lot
lately I was thinking to myself what is
the what really is why did I get here
and then I know that a lot of it was
being very lucky right and being in a
great situation and Circumstance but if
that was the case why are still a lot of
people listening is what I think to
myself and then I had to let myself go
and realize that For Better or For Worse
there's something very
different about what I make there's
something very diff in a way that yeah
you do know that it's me when I'm
singing it it couldn't be anyone else
you never scratch your head and think is
this so and so
it's always
muy and I think that that's a really key
component to sticking out in a very
saturated Market I say that a lot um
that like skill is One Piece One
Piece of the puzzle but you got to be
different you know that's that's just
how it is for Better or For Worse and
when you're different sometimes it gets
difficult being different also brings a
lot of difficulties you know that beats
oh but that's fine
I'm having a good time that's what
matters right something I wanted to do
really quick is I wanted to talk a
little bit a little bit about the track
list and if I had to come up with what
would be like the theme for each song I
want you guys to know this so that when
you go like to your listen through of
the album you kind of have like a little
something to like guide you along the
way of figuring out what the lyrics are
about right so for tide
I'd kind of say that the theme for this
one is
Resurrection resur come on man it says
alignment center it lied to me
Resurrection oh coming up from from the
bottom you know and and hope maybe hope
would be another one that I'd put in
there hope for sure but you know we we
have a hope
already everyone's going to think iris
song iris song iris
song next up let's see after
tide oh boy this is one that a lot of
folks have been very eager to hear how
did this turn
out how did this turn
out what's the theme of sneaking do you
guys think if you had to come up with a
theme I think it might be
sneaking it goes hard hard myy thank you
I like to imagine Ryden fighting a boss
to sneaking Revenge I'd say that the
theme of sneaking is probably sneaking
but when it's sneaking with lotus
juice it's
revengeance it's got to be
revengeance but yeah no Lotus juice
killed it as I've mentioned before ever
since the beginning when I first heard
sneaking I always thought to myself I
want to sing this with a
dude I want like a I want a male
vocalist to to kind of carry the more
like harder Parts cuz I just think that
the
Cadence the Cadence is
more
fitting right I think the Cadence is
definitely more fitting for for a male
vocal but I mean there's an e in there
okay sorry I I apologize I can't spell
I'm sorry but I think that Lotus juice
was the perfect choice for the song
Because actually to be honest with you
guys Lotus juice was my first choice to
ask when we made the original version as
well but um for whatever reason
production issues and stuff like that we
couldn't ask someone else to be on it
and I was like a dang sadness but it is
what it is next up we've got go-getters
oh this one's super easy the theme of
this one I've actually stated in quite a
few interviews and such was freedom
sorry I'm just better sorry we're
go-getters being unapologetically
yourself even if the world sees you as a
villain it's a theme of Freedom it had
to be a bit more of a a general theme
just because I was writing to try and um
and kind of make up a theme that fits
several different quadrants right so
something that myy could relate to
something the audience could relate to
something The Suicide Squad could relate
to and something that would be good in
an
anime so there were a lot of different a
lot of different quadrants I was trying
to fit into let's go
[Music]
forom absolute
Banger
forom there's some Eagles in the chat
now let's go do the
wer yeah creating a theme for an entire
group of vastly different personalities
could not have been easy it it
definitely the the difficult part was
choosing a theme that was General you
know coming up with like more complex
themes is something that that I feel
like it takes time but it's actually the
the actual process of doing it isn't
isn't too hard it's forcing yourself to
be more General and come up with
something that you don't find to be
generic enough to roll your eyes if that
makes any sense generics fine for this
kind of thing when you're trying to to
make a song that a ton of different
folks relate to right um I think that's
okay but just not in a way that makes
you roll your eyes you feel me next up
we've got Overkill this is a really
tough one because I feel like the theme
can't just be explained in a couple
words um
maybe maybe
expectations you know what's expected of
you especially you know people people
like me and my friends and stuff like
that um kind of trying to live up to
expectations
um
forced
competition between friends never feels
good when we're all when we're all cheer
cheering hard for each other and trying
to support each other that sort of sense
of forced competition doesn't make any
of us feel very good and it's it's been
on my it's been on my mind for a long
time cuz you hate the idea that you
might start resenting your friends
because of outside forces making things
you know a competition where it doesn't
need to be if that makes any sense so
it's kind of a a scream about how I feel
in regards to
that you sure it's not tomato circus
I've thought long and
hard I've thought long and hard about it
and I don't think it's tomato
circus and then we've got cult following
oh boy this is this is an interesting
one so the this one
cold
following is
about um Cult of
Personality I'm pretty sure this is the
orgasm one um I'm going to be honest
with you guys I wrote this song because
I wanted uh a hard an a hard rock/metal
Anthem um to imagine me leading an army
of skeletons that that's about it
really I know that's the dorky answer I
know that that's very silly um but
that's what I wanted to imagine um right
it's a bit of like it's an it's an
exaggerated take on um I guess what it's
like to be a person that has a large
following um it's a bit of a a cynical
look um at all of that I would say it's
not necessarily how I truly feel myself
um or anything like that but it's kind
of an outside looking in
perspective um yeah
H sounds awesome very you very me but
yeah that's that's cult following I
would say um and then my favorite on the
album do my this one's very very much
just a song
about this very big thing that a lot of
people can maybe relate to impostor
syndrome oo do we know what impostor
syndrome is dead beats and any of you
guys heard of impostor
syndromes uh there's just one there's no
syndromes it's just one um so like there
are a lot of lyrics that I'm sure we'll
dive into tomorrow uh after the show
because I'll do a stream after
tomorrow's show to kind of like wind
down do a listening party and stuff like
that um but yeah imposter syndrome
something that a lot of folks like me go
through um feeling like you're out of
place like you don't belong there
however there is more of a positive spin
on it because John son said let's like
put a positive spin at the end um it
doesn't need to be too positive but like
some kind of level of like hopefulness
of kind of rising up from that and
destroying that that impostor syndrome
if that makes any sense um Rising above
it in some kind of
way now it's about time that we do some
call-ins you guys then we'll continue
going down the list of
songs if you don't mind yes yes it's
time time for some Callins I'm very
excited oh oh hang on a sec whoa I
didn't prepare hold on hang on I I
didn't prepare the
thing hold on a
sec we maybe have unexpected guest here
so I'm going to really
quickly go make a thing really fast I'm
going to make a thing really
quickly hey I'm always down for
unexpected guests you guys know me
I love when people when people drop in
and they just like hey and I'm like oh I
didn't know that you'd be there I didn't
know you'd be here makes me happy okay
uh let's see I can export a quick PNG
hold on a
sec here we
go and then we can get this tots umachi
started you guys that's right because
guess what I went ahead and sent my
album to a bunch actually everybody I
sent it to everybody in
Holo um yay every everybody in Holo got
to have a listen if they wanted to right
and I said um if you would like to drop
by the stream and tell me what your fave
song
was then let's go you know um please do
so come say
hello yes so let's go ahead and welcome
a caller really quick you guys don't
mind if you guys don't mind
all right here we go you're on the horn
hello
hello oh you're on the
[Music]
[Laughter]
horn that was pretty good you that was
pretty
good nice
job why' you understand what I just said
Pickle Senai you speak
English speak Armando
Armando sorry excuse me arm
armo no
p no
no that's a pretty pretty good
impression I will
say I
needing P Armando Armando yeah I haven't
been able to do anything of the Bingo
but at least I can maybe take off the
prank oh yeah that was a good prank go
for whatever you got to do to get that
hard B shees has she not said to you cra
oh maybe once I feel like I heard it
like that that
crackly kind of okay that kind of
sounded like a demon but you know what
I'm saying she rolls to R sorry for
being empty on expected caller cuz I
wasn't sure yet like if I could come but
I ended the other stream and now I'm
here and then I go dance dance dance
yeah go dance dance dance welcome K
thank you for coming to the radio show
calling in first time accepting callers
appreciate you dropping by I'm on the
radio you're on the radio hey anything
you want to say to the the folks at home
um hello I don't know if my if my mommy
is listening oh maybe my cats are my
cats listening to this I want to say
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow hi K cats hello yeah meow meow meow
meow they remember you they know really
they know my voice or they probably
don't know my voice but they'll know me
if they see me I'm a presence yeah all
cats thank you for calling in today gu
making time to come say hi are you okay
you sound kind of tired oh yeah it's
been it's just been a lot preparing for
the release of this album now it's out
and I'm
like you know there's still much left to
do I'm exhausted we we were very busy
yesterday it was busy can I make people
jealous yeah uh Cali gave me the
beautiful album it it's like big and
square and like really big and it got
like cool stuff inside and she signed it
for me I did I did sign it for you cuz
you're my friend friends get special
privileges and I got like a like a
postcard a special one and it's like the
girly cute one yeah yeah yeah it's the
it's the m fashionable howu trip fashion
it's not I guess it's not is it G I
think it is GK but like you can't tell
cuz I'm kind of crouched a little bit
but it definitely is yeah so the post
gotard and then I got the the the
trading card right which is like the 3D
one you said it's rare oh wait did you
get oh yeah um so basically it is it is
to me because the other trading cards
are like me and my my new Underworld
order outfit um for like three of them
then there's a weird cat and then
there's me in my default which is the
one that you got
yeah so it's the only one out of all of
the trading cards that has me in my
default outfit but it is really it looks
really cool you say default like it's
not cool but no no it's pretty neat
there's like a moon in the background I
think it's cool yeah yeah everybody
wants a weird cat though yeah yeah I
want the weird cat too see if I can find
one and send it to you weird cat yeah
just for you though any cat any cat is
welcome yeah of course so Gua out of the
songs that you have gotten a chance to
hear on my album which one did you like
like the most I I feel like I have to
say mayoi midnight oh oh yeah with the
with goo yeah I mean you know family you
know we got to like you know familes got
to stick together yeah there's like
three different languages in there it's
crazy but it's not only honestly I I
also like I listen to the others two and
they're all like really special and cool
and like they sound really well produced
so
they were all great um obviously bangers
everywhere uh cult following was really
sick oh yeah did you like that one Kiara
it's crazy I okay can I say something
don't be mad at me there's like a part
before it hits like becomes I don't know
how to describe before it becomes like
really strong yeah the part right before
that it gives me tail of
Swift wa a good way it's like kind of
channeling tail swi yeah yeah if the
whole song was like that you know you
could say this is a Taylor Swift T
Swifty song no I'm so sorry it's a good
thing it's cool because I didn't expect
it I was like oh is this a Taylor Swift
Swifty Style song and then you hit
really hard got to hit him with the Gap
Mo and this year 2024 right yeah true
why not why not you got to Aspire to be
like you know Taylor and oh Tay Tay I
mean yeah cool I mean it is a very it's
like a pop rock song I feel like in some
parts you know so I get it yeah
appreciate that well thank you for for
listening to it Kara I appreciate it so
much you're welcome I'm sure you worked
hard on it I did I tried my best I tried
but I hope that everybody really enjoys
it and thank you for making time to say
hello today Kar I appreciate it sorry
for squeezing myself in I I I hly I was
confused uh because I saw you were alone
and I thought oh oh should I maybe I'm
going to call in that because you were
alone but then I realized oh you don't
start until like 30 okay yeah I was
having a little chat with some with some
dead beats and stuff like that but yeah
no it's okay I was just happy that you
said hi Thank you thank you for letting
me know your favorite song
[Music]
too wow P pakora
pakora P PCO oh thank you P PCO thank
you PCO I don't know how you do that cuz
I can not do that impression it's too
good it's like you got to try to sound
tired and
Gremlin I don't know yeah like I guess
it's kind of similar to when I try to
make a grandma voice oh yeah yeah yeah I
feel like that's easier for me to do in
Japanese but recently I don't know it's
not it's not popping off as well these
days like do do your do your grandma
voice oh oh hello there sunny boy p p
yeah make it a bit cuter
it's hard you can do it though but I
mean I feel like I feel like you are
better at Impressions than I am I am P
so obviously true you are the same
person after
all okay well thanks a lot Kiara I
appreciate it enjoy the rest of the
album and enjoy your dance
lesson bye picot
bye p p goodbye what's
PCO there goes totally
peora Big Ups p
p farewell to Kiara until next time that
was that was a nice tot match nice tot
match with
Gua looking forward to possibly yeah
more guest oh oh we have a call hello we
have a caller hello hello
hello
oh oh they ran
away I'm sure she'll come
back I'm sure she'll be back
soon we'll just wait maybe she had to
run to the restroom or something like
that she just had to run to the she had
to to go to her Idol meeting really
quick she she'll come back I'm sure it
was weird cat guys it was weird cat oh
CH them about that oh okay okay okay
it's okay it's okay it's okay Ah that's
okay just some technical difficulties
don't worry too much about it though Our
Guest caller will be back any moment for
now let's chill heating emergency the
weird effing cat is cutting the phone
lines you
see I love weird
cat really don't say that oh hello hello
hello hello haachama
congratulations thank you so much ha
Senai I appreciate it new album new
album yes release thank you so much wow
it's already it's already release yes
already Yes nice yeah 43 minutes
ago yeah 43 minutes okay
today okay okay yes today yeah
thank you so much I appreciate
it
hear you listened a little bit thank you
so much
wow thank you so much oh your favorite's
go-getters yeah it's like goget pop song
make it sexy
sexy
sexy yeah really voice was sexy doy
doy oh yeah yeah yeah tension the
tension is rising the whole time Rising
tension Yeah dance oh please Dance
someday yeah I want to see haim's dance
yay yeah because you're number one
strongest it
thank you yeah of course I'm so happy
thank yeah no I'm happy too thank you
and yes thank you for delicious sweets
nice like wagi I love wagashi I like me
too oh you too yeah I like
I I
like
[Applause]
really really
soft
wow wow I'm gonna try thank
you ah I forgot uh where is it
uh you know you know
47 to oh 47 to to 31 ice cream all of it
I I
surise
yeah oh my God I forgot all of it it's
okay don't worry oh yeah for yeah 47 n
so a prefecture
prefecture preure
47 I did it I did
it
maybe yes
yeah oh Japanese I
yeah me Japanese I can't I can't speak
it but you are you are my English
teacher yes I'm your English teacher so
I'll teach you say so English I promise
yay yeah no more boy
okay what no more boy no no I need F boy
you don't need you don't I don't need it
okay oh what what do I what do I need
now uh now you need uh nice boys only
yeah clear clear boy yeah yeah clean boy
ah nice boy yeah I need nice boy too
husband yeah husband oh yeah you can do
it yay I support you
last last days
oh yeah last days too you like it thank
you oh my gosh I did my best
yes oh like a soft G gentle song kind of
yeah yeah it's like a yeah more chill
song
I I could I couldn't hear all of it so I
I want to listen yeah please do I hope
you enjoy all of last days I want to
listen later yeah I will listen it later
and H your English is very very good
it's very good so I think you can
understand the lyrics if you listen and
read the lyric I can I can I can study
English yeah yeah yeah study with that
song
Because deep meaning
oh nice nice yeah so check it out I was
study English yeah do your best I
believe in you thank you thank you so
much today for calling thank thank you
have a great
day great day
too
byebye thank you thank you
bye-bye wow Haim so nice I love talking
to haima she is she's so sweet and
always comes to say hello to me and like
toachi with me and play games with me
she's just so
nice good luck to hat with your English
studies love chamers she ate bugs too
that's a charm Point lady who's tough
enough to eat bugs let's
go I mean yeah
that's how that's how I
feel I wanted to join in the bug eating
but sadly my recording finished and I
literally I jumped out to go do it um
and then it was
over I was like running over to where ba
was and it was over did B kiss the
spider
what what I know that Fu Moko ate bugs
and they had no issues they came in and
were like oh yeah bugs whatever yeah
they're kind of they're kind of hairy
and I was like how can you do that you
two they're strong those two are strong
stronger than I that's for
sure mostly
fuaa MCO at a bunch of bugs hey good for
them they get one box crossed off on the
Bingo that's pretty cool seriously
congrats to
them fua and hatam must split a
tarantula the whole thing oh was crazy
did you eat an off stream bug no I
didn't and I'm not going to lie to you
guys and tell you that I did I'll find a
way if we can do the hardcore Bingo but
I need to finish regular Bingo first to
be
honest maybe we'll have a little more
time for that after after the album has
been released right right now it's
pretty hardcore into the promotion
time yeah so I'm doing a lot of music
related streams and stuff like that
which I don't know I feel like I feel
like a lot of times aside from holel
Radio I don't really feel so much like I
need to do streams related to music when
I stream I want to play games and stuff
like that or do collabs and like maybe
try some more creative stuff later maybe
karaoke but when it comes to this kind
of stuff you know like talking about
lyrics and stuff like that lyric Dives
and whatnot don't really do them so much
I should try a little harder though
because music is what I do after
all moo would rather eat bugs over not
though that's crazy to me I don't
understand and yeah also the fact that
they did it once for Bingo and then the
second time just for
fun wow I really admire those two
they're
crazy just have fun with it well we're
going to dive into the lyrics tomorrow
for some songs so don't you guys worry
not all of them mostly the new ones I
think is what we're going to do do a
little listening party as well cuz I
know that have we ever done a real true
listening party before I
wonder I don't think that we've done one
in the same way that like for example B
did one right actually listening to each
and every track and talking about it oh
I'm excited to listen
though just have fun have fun viu is
hysterical as in when bibu was eating
bugs was she hysterical as in she was
funny or as in she was crying and
screaming and losing her mind eating the
bugs maybe both both both is good anyway
time for small ad ladies and gentlemen
did you know right now that if you get
iTunes if you download the iTunes
version of phantom it counts towards the
Big Goal that we're trying to
reach oh
boy oh no no all right that's fine
that's fine so let's see one
second all right so in terms of spotify
and iTunes you guys um it will I think
it does really exactly from now just
because there was some kind of issue
with the release settings and such so it
looks like um it looks like it's 1: p.m.
jst everywhere so the album is available
everywhere you guys now if you refresh
this this stream there should be a new
Link in the description um so basically
it says you need to take a screenshot of
the iTunes download purchase screen and
submit it through the application form
to access the demo track here's the
campaign page and then monichan linked
the page so you'll be able to see it in
the description if you click there and
don't worry if you've already bought it
and like oh no I lost my receipt or
whatever just go to the store Page where
you've already bought the album on
iTunes take a screenshot of that if you
bought it you should be able to access
it anytime receipt doesn't matter you
don't need to send a receipt just send
the page that shows that you purchased
the
album I don't need written instructions
did they not put the the written instru
instructions in there all right I'll do
it myself
I'll do I'll do it myself that's kind of
an important
thing that's a bit of an important thing
all right I'm going to now put it in
there for iTunes
promotion all right
and save there you go
H step one buy iPhone
Buy iPhone no no no you don't need an
iPhone just purchase on on iTunes I
think it's a little different than Apple
music I was under the impression that
iTunes was defunct but I guess not if
it's not oh well but making a purchase
there of the album digitally will also
count towards the grand goal that we're
trying to reach so and I think it really
is possible but again just got to push
it further still just a little a little
H
hey hey
I just got some I just got an image sent
to me that's very
exciting I just received a very exciting
image would you guys like to see the
exciting
image I'll show you the exciting
image here we
go it looks like on the charts in
Japan alternative album
number one so far that's probably I
think that's the quickest that this has
ever happened for any any
charting dang a lot of you guys want
that iTunes track huh that uh that rough
demo
huh we're there yeah usually usually
when this happens when I release a new
album it at least takes a couple hours
to get to number one on the
charts but Get Wrecked Green Day no no
[Music]
no
no no no
no number one
yay uhoh YouTube what's going on
YouTube no no no no no no no no no no no
no lag lag lag lag YouTube please
YouTube not like this
H I swear the hype is too much it can't
be handled that's okay we'll wait we'll
wait refresh it's good now just give it
a
refresh yeah YouTube has not been on my
side
lately after speaking with after after
speaking with um staff and whatnot I
have confirmed my worst
fears that there are various things that
are happening that
are how how do I say
basically I'm fighting an uphill battle
with
[Music]
you but hey we got to celebrate the the
wins right like Phantom number one
alternative thank you so
much what is number
one
Phantom is this a Jeopardy
question anyway um we're going to open
up the totachi again uh at about
2:05 right so in about 7 minutes from
now or
so she was number one you kind of did a
listening on your remaster cover stream
back in the day bins a day Green Day on
the phone with YouTube right now no no
no it couldn't be no no no it's they'd
also be gunning for yushka as
well anyway this is a big this is this
is worth celebrating
everyone yay you got the big box and
it's already shipped that speed that's
the really good thing about the Mor
Store right thank you very much
Universal for the my store prayer hands
prayer hands Emoji in front of
me number one let's keep it going yeah
I'd love to to keep it to keep it doing
well this is the best birthday gift ever
oh happy birthday to you
deadbeat oh all glory to the Mory store
let's keep it rolling let's let's keep
it moving you
know if we keep it if we keep it shoving
together how about it h
she was number one congrats keep the
fire going
um fire fire light the fire and I also
wanted to play the next song right and
now you guys are definitely going to
figure out what the pattern is um but
you may wonder why I chose the next song
out of all the songs that I could have
chosen right um I feel like it's one
that doesn't get talked about much slash
I don't talk about it a lot slash I
don't really sing it too often but a lot
of dead beats really like so I thought
that I would share a fan favorite with
you guys I'm going to keep this on the
screen cuz it makes me really happy so
let me just pull it down here
though all right um so with that being
said please listen to the next song on
today's holel
[Music]
radio started like a whisper but CL as I
FLW at times I almost miss her just do
as I do we lose is confusing but I need
to trust me she's plugging up her ears
in pure Rebellion must be fear of
contradicting a life in the uning a
voice of V all pissed y yet forgiven
even so I am failing to walk to her
nails on a chard BR the sight but she
talks back with a bright out from time
to time shouts loud and speaks to my CL
chasing we like racing the clock mind
leaving us behind just step back I'm
sure you'll find the Two of Us in tand I
will not let us die so let's try to
stand against the odds they can call us
anything like [\h__\h] cowards and frauds
but we are the ones who get heard then
we reap the Applause it's deeper than
identity crisis like this because it's a
lifestyle it want to sketch it out first
the crowd Sayed but always ex shells
walking over any VI I'm sending ain't
you ever sick of pretending so we'll
take a solid look in the mirror should I
give her all of it should I fear her
here and now you're part of me rest in
power heart of free Soul stand against
time put your hand in mine here and now
you're part of me every hour feels like
the B Shield she's with the real that
was resting Power by me myy c yes the
power that rests inside of me the true
me deep inside of
me yeah really cool collab song that I
did anyway um I'm really quite happy
with the lyrics of that one um that was
another one where I feel like sometimes
some lyrics pop out and I'm like oh yeah
that was pretty good actually like that
was a decent lyric right um I want to
sketch it out first the crowd says paint
it which is the idea that you kind of
want to start off going at your own pace
kind of from nothing start off slow and
steady but you know outside forces would
be like be perfect immediately you
know start start off in all colors just
100% work towards a finished product
right now is something that I struggled
a lot with
[Music]
right yeah I'm really quite proud of
some of the lyrics in that song one of
your fave Mory tracks thank you see
that's why I chose it now maybe folks
can kind of see that the theme for
today's Hol mow radio tracks being
chosen is one song off of each of Mor's
big releases M oh hey guess what we have
we have uh not a call but a
comment thank you for comment
happy wow okay so we have one member who
wanted to call in but is unable to call
at the moment and so she wanted me to go
ahead and read out to you all what she
said and she in English too that's very
kind
wow thank you so
much okay so this is from toas Sama to
Sama who says and I quote Overkill is a
very hot song Oh I thought that that
tosama would really like Overkill
actually thank you so much tosama
favorite song
Overkill hard sounding a song that makes
you want to shake your head and last
days is a stylish song I Like it wow
that's twoo for last days huh a song I
would rather listen to than sing it is a
very high
song Oh but I did it I did it I'm glad
that I did
congratulations on the album release I
haven't been able to listen to the whole
thing yet because of my schedule thanks
for letting me listen to it
first wow I love Callie's music I listen
to it a lot I'm so
happy thank you so much to
Senai I'm so glad thank
you thank you I'm
so happy chesi
wow thank you
to
love that was so kind so kind of to Su
to leave such a sweet message about the
album very happy to hear that that she
enjoyed it and that she's still going to
listen to more of it yay
cuz I did I did share it ahead of time
right with everyone thank you to and in
English yeah in English too I could I
could have used deep L but but that's
okay
because Senpai Senpai is so considerate
putting that into English for me yeah
Overkill does seem like a song that that
uh toos Sama would like I kind of want
to hear toos Sama sing Overkill cuz
she's got the vocals for it for sure
right yeah I think out of all the
members in Holo to kind of air more on
the side of like rock and metal oh to
Sama voice it really fits perfectly yeah
I love hanging out with to Sama we've
gotten a chance to hang out quite a bit
too I do hang out with a lot of members
just don't really get a chance to talk
about it a lot mostly because you know
we just got to be safe we are Idols
after all you know we got a lot of
people watching us so sometimes it's
good that we just enjoy things on our
own and tell you guys many weeks
later yeah I know that to also hangs out
with ba a lot you guys know Bae is my b
after all that's why I call her ba did
you know the ba can also be a Japanese
name I didn't know that maybe that
sounded kind of weeb for me to say that
out of nowhere all of a sudden but
anyway be
be yeah it seems that she's practicing
her passion English very very proud of
toas for her passion
English very cool very few JP members
call her ba though true I've noticed
that but sometimes a bam but it's mostly
hak
hak hakos is another name that's kind of
like very similar to kapi pronounced
different completely different in
Japanese compared to the English right
cuz we call her heos
Bales BS but JP
sayak
right they're completely
different hang on I'm going to I'm going
to put this back up on the
screen um since we're still waiting for
since we'll be sitting here waiting for
more callers to drop in we're going to
go ahead and move along with the program
and accept calls throughout the show so
look forward to
that I have a little announcement to
make it's not a little announcement it's
actually kind of a big it's kind of big
but I'm sure that you guys already kind
of guessed about it I think a lot of
people have already guessed that this is
a situation but I've been told the
go-getters mvy will be done soon that's
what I've been
told well today I'm here to announce to
you I'm going to announce to you guys um
who is making who is making the music
video The Studio in charge of my
go-getters music video
is WT
Studio yeah yeah PCH PCH PCH p p p p wit
studio is making the whole
thing the whole thing uh so naturally
they um they've been they've been busy
we kind of knew that didn't we I never
said it was wit wouldn't it be crazy if
it wasn't wit studio and it was a
completely different studio and people
were like huh I thought it would be
wit I thought it would be
W yeah but I figured that you guys kind
of like assumed after all
right because it is go-getters right oh
yeah they are they are also making a lot
of anime as well but you know Suicide
Squad Isa I believe it finished I
believe the anime is over and so and so
now
now now they can they can work on Mor's
music
video yeah I didn't assume we guess that
see there are some dead beats who had no
clue no clue that it was going to be wit
Studio but yes um it is completely and
totally 100% in-house wit studio um for
this for this particular project I've
already seen the storyboards I wanted to
ask if we could get like some kind of
screenshot or something to share on on
stream but it appears that we cannot for
now for now um even though I've already
seen the I've already seen the uh
storyboards and like rough animations
and stuff like that right uh but yeah
that's probably that's the biggest
reason I that uh it's it's been delayed
is that of course Studio wit has a
million different projects that they are
working on but I never thought it would
be the same Studio as Suicide Squad a
well I kind of I thought about that too
I thought maybe we should you know ask
someone else or gather like a small
group of animators or something but um
you know the company kind of uh
persuaded me and I also kind of thought
well I guess it makes sense right
they're connected this song and Suicide
Squad isekai um and so yeah we decided
let's ask Whit we asked about I think it
was maybe about 10 months
ago
February February maybe it was around
February it was definitely it was before
that it was before it was announced that
I had any involvement with Suicide Squad
isekai
yes well only for eight
months eight months H
yeah it's a while but I
mean yeah they are definitely working on
a lot of stuff that's like years down
the line but you know they they accepted
it and so I'm looking forward to seeing
the the job that they do on the music
video I'm sure it's going to be great I
mean from what I've seen right like I
said um there has been a delay with it
right but based on what I saw the
quality is so high already like they
didn't
it seems that they aren't rushing it
which I do appreciate I'd hate to get a
rushed product more than
anything so
mhmi go get her dance maybe we'll
finally get to see that go-getters dance
being animated in some way when can we
watch it we shall see um I was told
either end of this month or beginning of
next end of this month's coming up
pretty soon though though it'll be here
and gone before we know
it here and gone before we know it
especially with breaking dimensions on
the horizon right true enough well while
we're waiting for more folks to call in
how about we go ahead and listen to
another song shall we what's uh that's
when the exclusive merch is coming out
too right the exclusive the exclusive
thing is dropping at the same time as
the next music video that's coming out
and I was told
I was told that's going to be
[Music]
it dang
it um I was asked a question it's it's
so I hate I hate not having a concrete
schedule but sometimes that's that's how
the industry goes for whatever reason
how the business works I wish it wasn't
um where they're like well my we don't
have all the answers for you and you
can't tell the dead beats yet because
because we don't have the answers for
you right well what I will say is that I
have a brand new outfit coming out and I
will be using that brand new outfit uh
to lead into a new music video and also
advertise the special edition limited
like merchandise that's coming out um
for the thing the big collaboration that
I'm excited about um but I've heard I've
heard 22nd I heard up to the 25th it's
going to be around that time possibly
while I am in New York for breaking
Dimensions um it's going to be around
that time so I likely will be doing that
reveal from New York is what I heard but
again I can't promise you guys any
timeline things because I'm always being
told just wait a
minute yeah I'm sorry about that guys
but I'll do my best to keep pushing them
you know I'll do my best I think that
it'll be around that time hope the
internet holds out well they'd have to
choose from to be at a place where
internet's okay right we be able to use
it more than the one piece outfit well
the one piece outfit was a collab outfit
so I don't get to use that often this
one will be a normal outfit so
yes yeah hope all goes well we are
patient live from New York it's Mor
let's take a listen to another song
shall we this time I went ahead and
instead of choosing a fan favorite I
chose my favorite from this particular
release here's the next song check it
out what I want my
fing now stop running you know me as
that chck won back down I'm coming the
gun who threatens your Empire a fire and
Earth should be bur you can expect to
meet the angel that you had
now the tables have turned the bridges
have burn with Des human Applause we
want to live and re sh that I wanted to
say I be you all to be part of the
making
the
got the voice to take them high I got
Notions own reolution
make I'm afraid of you
hey make afid
of
AF
afraid to prove make afraid
that's make him Afraid from Shinigami
note my debut release from
Universal yes thank you so much for the
gift memberships by the way I really
appreciate that BBA um that song in
particular I um I it's an interesting
situation because I saw a dead beat
saying didn't you lose the rights to
that song I did not lose uh the rights
we definitely had the rights there was
some kind of I'm not sure if
if it was a whoopsy or something like
that but somehow the rights to sing it
during
karaoke disappeared um but I can sing it
at like big live shows and stuff like
that that I want to do it's just I can't
sing it in like an archived one for
whatever reason I need to go ahead and
ask more details Etc it's just a bit of
a weird
situation but yeah big shows I can sing
it it's just karaoke that I can't which
is very strange at the same time if I
was able to sing that song during Reg
archived karaoke I would be singing it
every single
time I would be singing it every single
karaoke
100% well thank you very much for more
gift memberships yat thank you thank
you glad it's not banned from live shows
though yeah thankfully thankfully that's
the good
newsg Daddy
please please understand I well I well
that's fine it's fine
oh hopefully will be solved fingers
crossed am I
right then VR chat 3D Live Well this
time guys guess
what guess
what I'm getting a legitimate mini 3D
live tomorrow I'm actually going to head
to rehearsal after this so hope that you
guys will anticipate and look forward
forward to that yay 3D mini live um I
got a little preview of what the the
graphics are going to look like and it's
uh it's
artistic the uh the stages that I'm
performing on are
beautiful
beautiful but you know
Mor's there's a reason that I I'm
spending a wish right to update myself
um and I think that the the shading mode
that we're going for for the show is
definitely
eclectic it will truly show how badly I
need that
update I was kind of spinning around a
little bit um during the the tech check
and I was like
oh oh
wow You'll see I want you guys to not
stare too hard in my face and just just
enjoy my live performances and my
dancing and all that if you
could if you could it just needs an
update you know as a lot of us do and me
and kiar were talking a little bit about
it the other day like
dang I wish we could all get a bit of an
update it's part of you that we love
what the little scoffy Mori that you'll
see tomorrow at the 3D live I still want
you to look forward to it will it be as
long as the Cinderella live or a bit
more um let's see what was my set list I
will be singing five songs H five songs
which amounts to maybe like well also I
plan to do a couple MC segments as well
so I think it'll probably be something
like
20 minutes 25 minutes depending upon how
long wait maybe not 25 well it is a mini
live after all it's not a full-on live
30 maybe 30 you know Universal said to
me oh we plan to make it 30 or so but I
don't know
I I'll only know probably after
rehearsing a little bit so we'll see no
commercial
breaks it's quite many but I got to
choose of course all the songs I wanted
to do Universal asked me they said what
are the songs you want to perform what
do you want to sing I was like oh me I
get to choose made me happy so I think
that's how things will be from now on
Mini live means I'm going to be shrunk
yeah you won't be able to tell from the
scenery just imagine that like I'm a I'm
a tiny doll and like the settings I'm in
are little doll houses yeah it's that
kind of many live I
guess I'm glad they that they asked me
though what do you want to sing Mory and
then um a couple songs that I that I
really love from the album that you guys
also haven't heard I decided not to sing
because I just want you guys to listen
to them on your own right yeah chibi
Mory live no
downtime there'll be a couple m sees
though so we'll have a little bit of
downtime we'll see I wonder what I
should talk about maybe I'll talk a
little bit about the songs uh I don't
know during during this time I'm always
kind of like very ducky duck you know
like part of me wants to um how do I say
like run away and like not think too and
not think too much um about how the
album is doing and stuff like that um
and just like let it cook you know but I
don't know can I do that
anyway while we're still waiting for uh
anyone to drop by and say hello let's go
ahead and talk about some other songs
the theming for some other songs shall
we so midnight
mayoi what's the theme of this
song lost with
friend in
city is that a theme or just like a very
very literal explanation of what the
song is about
I imagine I want to imagine like you
guys in a in a car with your best friend
or something like that and like you're
exploring a city you've never been to or
something like that any of you guys
going to New
York any of you folks going to New York
I want you to to run around with your
friend uh in New York City thinking
o
Paradise yeah it's maybe a little less
romantic than Tokyo because you know New
York is is fine I don't know how it
compares to La maybe a little stinky
but just run around it's a little you're
hearing o Urban paradise and then you
see some guy like lean out the window
and like throw a bucket of water on you
or something like that quiet out
there and then you see somebody like pee
on the street and run away
yeah I mean I'm just you see some rats
like run around through the trash
o
Paradise how romantic I'm walk in
here there's rats everywhere bada bing
bada
boom walking over oh my God
what are all these little puddles on the
ground there's a couple stains here
forget about it shoe box size Street
rats that's a big
rat that's a big rat that that rat's
bigger than ba it's a big old
rat anyway why is this P it wouldn't be
yellow it would be like a dark color on
the on the cement on the street side
You' be like eh what is
that what could that
be you know what it
is anyway lost in city with friend play
it when when you go to New York anybody
who's going to New York if you can't be
in New York play it to pretend like
you're in New York next up
skeletons um this is this is definitely
like a very dreamy song that's kind of
like more like laidback and like um
self-reflecting right
um a lot of my own Journey
is in the lyrics of this song I would
say so it's a song about
reflection um and a song
about um wanting your life to be as good
as a fairy tale but it can't be that way
if that makes any sense kind of like
more more
dreamy
um life isn't a fairy tit fairy fairy
tail skeletons it's you guys
yeah yeah
skeletons why skeletons you may Wonder
it's it's mostly from the lyrics like
wasand skeletons you can't you can't fix
all the all the cracks it's like we're
Dead
skeletons can't fix
them sometimes you're just
dead sometimes a dream dies sometimes
things don't turn out the way that you
wanted them to because life isn't a
fairy
tale you
know sometimes all that's left
are the Crusty bone remains of what you
thought you could be what you thought
life would be but you got to make the
most out of
[Music]
them life isn't a
f i mean it can
be but yeah it's a it's kind of like um
a song that's full of um catharsis
yeah it's the catharsis song oh oh otama
wait a minute hold on a
second do we have a possible hang on I
also didn't make a uh hold on a sec wait
where's where's the song title song
title go away well we have so many
surprise uh surprise guests today which
I'm always excited about you guys know
that I have no complaints I'm just
extremely excited extremely did I say
that correct I'm sure I did
hang on a
sec you guys know I'm no I'm no
complainer when it comes to friends
dropping by but was like oh
surprise
surprise okay hold on a sec hang on I'm
working on it I'm working on
it yeah that's okay no no complains just
just Mory working on it oh wait hold on
a
sec hang on oh okay I can't hear
okay next caller will be back
shortly next caller will be back uh once
they figure out the Discord
situation
okay hold on a sec I'm moving things
around I'm so happy yay friends friends
friends friends friends
rasterize this is why I kept Photoshop
up I'm so glad I did that oh my gosh
what a genius brilliant genius idea my
Mor's brilliant genius
idea
okay whoa whoa whoa
typing I'm so glad to much to much to
much yeah I said that I would keep the
call open um until the hour ends just
about
so yeah
so we will definitely we will be
accepting Callins to the radio until
then I've always wanted to have somebody
jump into the radio and be like you're
on the
horn maybe I should say that you're on
the
horn this is
silly oh no
PRS there you go speaker you're on the
air you're on the air air is fine but I
like you're on the horn more because it
sounds kind of Western ooh speaking of
Western oh my God my text and accent
comes out so hardcore in do my I
realized
that who's all on me I sound like a
cowboy the cowboy voice really comes out
you can really hear my text and accent
he's kind of awesome though I didn't
even realize
[Music]
it you're on the horn oh it sounds
medieval to you what like a like a horn
that you call from like to rally the
troops or
something theme for doai
Texas
classic it's
Charming standing on chicken got to hear
it now I hope you enjoy it doai is my
favorite one I'm very very proud of how
it sounds the bluesy guitars in the
beginning are my
favorite oh my God I'm obsessed with
them I said they're like do you have any
mix requests I was like turn up the
bluesy
guitars turn them
up
yeah University of Texas should have
sang in The Cowboy karaoke I feel like
I'd probably ham it up a little bit more
in that case well while we're waiting
for the next caller to um
to get stuff figured out on the Discord
hopefully hopefully they'll be able to
get it figured out if not though it's
okay no worries at all oh oh
hello wait can you say that one more
time yay they're
here congratulations
congratulations b b thank you so much
for coming I'm so glad you guys can say
hi yeah we're so glad we a to make it
yay thank goodness oh my gosh yeah cuz I
I was going to do this for quite a while
I'm so glad that you could jump in and
say Hello thank you both of you you're
both so B
I was just saying I was saying to I was
like Callie somebody just released her
album not too long ago right another
album oh my God
another she releas know how you do
it I mean work is I feel like work is my
hobby but only if it's music work music
work is my
hobby all that
creativity it's amazing we really really
respect you
call
congratulations it's amazing thank you
so much my face hurts from
smiling it's a common effect when these
two jump into the call as my face hurts
from Smiles dang it smile protected
thank you yeah that's my job their job
smile oh my God I'm so happy you guys
are so sweet thank you so much did you
guys have a favorite song by chance yes
it was difficult it was difficult
because go G is like listen to it a lot
it's it's all over the place and we were
even shopping and we heard it really I
was like the S go get oh my God it's
Kell that's what F yeah they played in
the store that's crazy I didn't think
they do that what the heck
cool but so it's really hard to
choose I think we both last days really
stands out the skeletons was really good
I need see the lycs why can see the
lyrics
oh yeah well I mean when I when I send
you a copy you'll be able to see the
lyrics in the
book thank you you guys will get copies
for sure I I always like like a a call
some by before for your music and stuff
you do like a lyrics breakdown like
dissection stream I always really like
listening to that and like like hearing
how like all the feelings and the
decisions and stuff that you put into
that so it would be nice if we did
something like that too oh yeah I'm
doing that tomorrow actually now that
you say
that like a listening party mhm because
lycs are really really important to us
so yeah last days it was between
skeletons and last days but I think
because of the way like it really heats
up last days really stood out to us
thank you sneaking also together with
the Revenge with lotus
ju it really it's really H the guitar
it's hype isn't it yeah
thank you so much I was really excited
to do like a more rock version of that
song just to fit the album more and fit
my taste more it's so fun mhm I'm glad
that you liked it so much you guys wow
last last days as well is very like I
feel like I put a lot of like my own
personal emotions and like you know kind
of like my more like sad sadnesses into
into it and stuff like that so I'm
really glad it starts off kind of soft
but yeah like you guys said you guys
said it perfectly heats up you
know like both of those track skeletons
and last days kind of for us felt a
little bit reminiscent of end of a life
yeah end of life is one of your songs
that we really really enjoy too one of
the many one of the many oh man thank
you so was saying like it's really
amazing this whole album you can really
feel all your growth and everything oh
thank you so and just all the love and
the hard work and just this is the
current the current Cali s right here
yeah you're
right this album very much yeah kind of
encapsulates like me as I am right now
for sure I'm glad that you guys felt
that while listening to it thank you I'm
so glad thank you so much wa you guys
you guys played played Metal Gear right
yeah we haven't played the third one yet
though yet though okay yet you're
definitely going to though right yes we
we have it we have we have our we have
our copy it's
oh my God everyone's going to love that
so much when you guys play that game cuz
it's such a classic I'm looking forward
to it we've had so much
fun I'm so glad yeah well sneaking is
full of tons of those kinds of
references it's very much a silly a
silly MGS themed song so I'm glad you
guys like
it thank
you I'm midnight my too really like that
one yeah coobo it's very very different
from I feel like the other songs that
you've done so it kind of stands out in
that way as well and then it's just
really relaxing relaxing I feel like I'm
floating a
bit that's a sweet way to think about it
wow floating man I want to listen to it
while chilling out the album has more
chill songs on it this time but also
some like really hard rock songs too so
it's kind of crazy it's like chill near
the end and then really like hype and
intense the beginning it has s of like
that that story that progression there
yeah know was so cool too like I felt
like both K by your voice and I's Voice
works so well together like you get such
an interesting flavor going on thank so
it was really exciting listening to that
track too I'm so glad yeah is son is
like also kind of like lower voice
register like me in fact I felt like I
was the one that was the higher voice on
that track which is crazy it's never
that
way it's usually not like that so yeah
wow well thank you guys so much for
for listening to the album and like
having so many thoughts about it just
means a lot to me no we're looking
forward to listen to it more intens yeah
I wanted to listen to it a lot more deep
I want to be able to just sit and listen
and think I feel like I haven't been
able to do that yet so I'm frustrated
yeah usually like we want we listen to
call but we listen to music a lot when
we're going on walk so we be the kind of
obnoxious people like uh with the music
blasting from oh really I was going to
ask if you guys share headphones or
something like
but when you're walking and stuff it's
kind of tricky you know so but luckily
there's not really anybody around so
definitely that is true kind of turn it
down you know yeah the ma there's not
that many people around so it's okay
it's chill that's cool sounds like a
pleasant walk honestly yeah man that's
so cool thank you guys so much though I
appreciate you making time as well to
come tell me what you thought
about we're happy that we're able to
I'll send you guys your versions I
promise thank you just for you guys
special for my my cute K high of
course thank you the least I could do
honestly and again
congratulations thank you so
much yeah oh my gosh true yeah the 3D
tomorrow yes that's right tomorrow oh my
gosh I'll do my best I'll do my best
aren't you guys doing something soon
today have we having a 3D collab on
Saturday oh that's right yeah that's
right the 3D collab with Advent are you
guys streaming today by chance I yes yes
oh today D yes we we'll have to check
that out then I'll have to go take a
look very
curious G you guys let's both keep doing
our all three of us keep doing our best
yeah and then we'll break the dimension
break the dimension together
I'm so excited to to do that with you
guys it's going to be so fun let's have
fun
okay I'll see you guys
later thanks for calling in thanks again
you guys byebye
baa there they
go bow
bow Bor bork the dimensions Bor Bor bow
the dimensions bow B the dimensions
together oh I'm so excited I'm so
excited to be able to to go on an
adventure with those two again as well
as everybody else thank you so much for
calling in foko I couldn't say it I
couldn't say you're on the horn I
couldn't I don't think that they'd know
what it means but but then again I feel
like not a lot of people would know what
that means not not just Iris for example
but
like fullon like English first language
like uh like Amelia wouldn't even know
what that means or gura they'd be like
huh H you're on the horn maybe am would
know maybe I could I could see Iris
being like horn what horn but I feel
like ba Bae is so much just like my
soulle sister that I could say it I
could say it to
her maybe maybe
Bae if Bae came in and be like you're on
the horn she'd be like
what and then I explain it to
her yeah
narissa to be honest maybe I should just
try that in the
future I need to ask people if they have
any last words though from here on
out unless they're they're JP I feel
like what would I
say it just doesn't sound as threatening
as in English any last words you feel
me it's just not as threatening right
anyway you think riss is American enough
maybe she'll get it
well while we're sitting here waiting
for more friends to drop by how about we
go ahead and listen to another song
together you guys oo I wonder what Mory
chose for this next one shall we find
out let's find out together here's the
next song check
[Music]
it let's
go so Bo of easy I need a bigger Target
to satisfy what I
crave I heard you want to play my heels
on your neck come try and
Escape I got you in my sight right now
still alive seeing how I excite you
death so de I'm still the best at making
y cry but I'll get good my
mind watching you from the Shadows where
wonder the fear me stronger sh up
that very last breath get tast to one by
one falling into my trash the touch of
manc this is how it feels on the edge
can the end take very last breath for
face to
death okay okay okay
okay yeah yeah all right I know a lot of
people expected one and wasted right if
you're going by favorite songs on the
album I might choose one and wasted but
I wanted to choose um taste to death
just because well we got jok 6 coming up
next right since jok 6 is coming up next
I decided maybe not a rock song for this
one but I'm pretty happy with uh with
Taste of death I like how it came out
the music video is fun um it's a good
song I like it it's Poppy you know
sometimes you'll get these pop songs
from Mory out of nowhere it's like who
but I really had to embody a different
Mory for that I'm too embarrassed to to
to get into it but when I recorded that
song song cuz it's the song about it's
the it's the lust song right I had to
kind of let a different Mory take over
my body you know like not interviewer
Mory she's a little different
but you
know a different
Mor is what I will say I had to let a
different Mory come in
basically yeah that's fine that's fine
rare a rare Mory
SSR wouldn't it be kind of funny if like
as a YouTuber you decided to just make
self a quint tolet would that be crazy
you'd have to really do a lot of backend
work
though naum more I do love nezami scheme
though as well from
Cinderella there was a a song that I
made that won't come out for I think at
least half a year so I don't know I'm
not I'm not sure on the timeline but
it's for a really really big thing it
might even be like on a on a on a scale
of how many people will end up hearing
the song bigger than go-getters probably
um but the director of that project
actually showed me nezami scheme and
said this is what made me decide that I
wanted to ask you to do this I was like
really really you like that I mean I
mean it made sense cuz it's a great song
but I was like yo I'm so glad I I made
this song so he went for something kind
of swingy I can't wait for you guys to
hear the news about that I don't know
how if it'll really be up y'all's alley
we'll just have to wait and see cuz it's
a very specific type of project but it's
an extremely mainstream project if that
makes any sense I don't know I'm being
cryptic I'm being cryptic because I
can't give up too many details but this
is the same director that I I told a
little story about before that was like
really cool and
like and like I guess how do I say I
really appreciated that director's
comment I think about it a lot of times
when I'm kind of down on myself about
the work that I'm doing and stuff like
that I remember that director said
you're like kind of edgy right you're
like rough around the edges and like
dark and whatnot but there's this
there's like a warmth inside what you
do I remember that the director said
that to me and I remember that that
stuck with me and I thought to
myself even on days where I feel like
what I'm doing like isn't really the
quality isn't high enough for the
success that I've attained I think about
what that director said head and I think
maybe it's okay to just keep going and
doing the best that I can with what I
have with what I can do right I
appreciated that maybe there is
something about me that people like you
know that people keep coming back to
enjoy yeah so I think about that a lot
these days and when you can't trust
yourself trust others
right I think that yeah like you said
debb being self-critical is important
and you can't improve unless you see the
flaws but you shouldn't let it stop you
or get you down a lot of times I've been
thinking recently since I've been it
been in it for like what almost 4 years
now I think to myself a lot of these
days about purpose like why am I
actually here doing any of this right
like what's the point of it what is my
reason of being here
Etc
um I think about that a lot you know and
for a while I've kind of thought to
myself well you know my time to shine is
kind of finished um and so it's time to
help others kind of thing right just be
as good of a senpai as you can be and
help everybody out that's where I find
that I have meaning if that makes any
sense right so I think in the past like
year before a year or so maybe it was a
little before when Advent debuted I
thought to myself there's really kind of
no real reason for me to continue being
here besides help other people right
um and I'm a person that like if if I
don't have worth
somewhere I don't really feel like like
there's a point for me to exist anymore
if that makes any sense I feel like I
need to have something that I'm doing
some reason for being not just lying
around and doing nothing watching
watching TV you know on the sofa with a
40 or something like that and so I
decided that um even if doing something
like making making really good music
that everybody can enjoy is something
that I can't do um then maybe what I do
instead is help other people who can do
that right and so I decided I'm just
going to be a really good Senpai and
help other people and welcome the new
people and and make sure that they excel
in what they do but there's a happy
there's a happy ending here there's a
happy ending here this isn't How It Ends
this isn't how the story ends um I think
because of a lot of those like kohai and
stuff like that helping me out they
helped
me in the
end
they they they helped me by helping me
realize that what I've done is we you
know myth worked really hard
um you know those were really weird
times
honestly and it's not just the end of
the
story it's not the end of the story just
because four years have passed
right it's not the end of the story I
can keep going I should keep going cuz
there's still more that I have left to
tell the world you know if I could
be I guess if I could be some kind of
symbol or something like that I wouldn't
want it to be a symbol of someone
who who is like the most skilled at what
they do and always creates bangers and
whatever I'd want to
be I'd want to be a symbol
of Never Letting anything ever ever ever
ever stop you from doing what you want
to do and making what you want to
make that's what I want to do and if I
throw in the towel and
just resolve myself to being on the
sidelines or in the background or
something like that um and I lose that
opportunity to continue being
that bees can stop you true bees can
stop me too from doing a lot of things
they're nasty
guys they are nasty dudes when they want
to
be bees can stop a lot of people believe
it or not getting locked out of your own
house o
true P cult's Tendencies can stop me can
stop me
true a lot of things can stop
you but at the end of the day when I
when I really think about
a lot of the more harrowing parts of my
life and my career and stuff that's
gotten in my way none of it really
actually made a
difference you know only how hard I
tried my
best and you guys being here helped
too you
know nothing that got in my way ever
actually
really really stopped me from doing what
I wanted to do I can't think of a single
thing that I wanted to do that I didn't
do
yeah
so
cool I just realized
it so I'll just keep it
up I'll just keep it
up I'm having fun I mean look at
this thank you
guys let's keep it going shall
we so
emo yeah I'm emo it can't be
helped it can't be helped that I'm
emo the queen of
Darkness like Queen of
Darkness shall we go ahead and listen to
another song
Everybody shall we
you guys want to hear another
song next
up I'll explain why I chose this song in
a moment but for now no words just enjoy
[Music]
uhh are you listening I'm one by one to
play The Toy Soldiers of
[Music]
corporations in theed di that is and in
the street
[Music]
Mir Mir tell me again if it was that I
made it over
strong Lou clear up just say that I'm
enough you lie so
well that's Kono Carousel Carousel of
imaginary images people may say where's
Left 4 Dead lullabi Mor know hold on a
second any other day I might choose left
for dead leabi but hear me out um Left 4
Dead leabi to me um you need to listen
to the whole thing and we only play
about one chorus on this radio program
but I want people to listen to it need
it's a song that needs to be listened to
in full in my opinion you can't really
stop listening to it Midway through
second of all second of all um de song
is performing at the bokan tomorrow yay
congrats to deodo song so I wanted to
kind of bring that up and say congrats
to deodo for performing at bokong cuz
that's a crazy crazy amazing
opportunity I'm so lucky that I got to
collab with a de do I'm so happy about
that collab too I'm glad that we became
friends I'm glad that that we can both
admire each other and cheer for each
other jok 6 love jok 6 jok 6 is very
important to me because it marked a
turning point in my making music where I
realized that I kind of I wanted to kind
of change my Approach with making music
I don't anymore just want to write
whatever comes to my mind I wanted to
pay more attention to the process and
the the quality Etc in my own way it's a
little too complex for me to really
explain in words I feel properly but uh
anyway it's a it's an important album to
me I'm really not album EP it's very
important to me when all is said and
done
uh let's see now we were talking about
songs actually and I have a couple I
have a couple special videos to show you
guys that I haven't seen yet I haven't
seen yet but we'll finish talking about
these first these songs okay last
days the theme of this one is super easy
actually compared to some of the other
songs
um this song is about
endings which is scary I know everybody
kind of gets scared like endings my are
you going away no no as a matter of fact
this um this song is not about my own
end um interestingly enough though I'm
sure one day it could be but no day soon
right um endings it's more about being a
person witnessing endings being a person
that's sitting there the the line is it
going to be just me left behind right um
are you ending someone else ending
someone being the person who ends
someone um no it's it's more about yeah
being witness to endings and being the
last person left because at the end of
the day right all you guys going to be
dead right but I'll still continue
persisting because I am death that is
what death do right so the feeling of um
you know you live forever you're
Immortal um but all these people around
you will die right and it's just you
left
behind you know survivors guilt
almost kind of but seeing all of your
friends go
away yeah there are a bunch of different
ways that you can interpret it but
that's the most simple way I suppose
that's what last days is
about so take it how you
will um and then we've got through the
blue oh this is oh my God this one's so
complicated this is a really complicated
one actually now that I'm really
thinking about it
um cuz this one also has this one has
some of my own personal story in there
that I can't dive too deep into but you
know I lost
somebody um and I don't talk about it
for various reasons but I did lose
someone in my life and it very severely
affected
me
um throughout my
existence uh yeah so I finally decided
to write a little bit about it um in
this song and it's about it's about
finding happiness in the midst of The
Blues from losing somebody cuz ever
since I lost that person in my
life um I always kind of felt
like how do I
say like I didn't really have a lot of
um I feel like I didn't really things
were just they became so different I
think about that person a lot I think
about what we would be doing together
now if they were still here um you know
maybe running around Japan together
maybe they would be making music doing
something creative Etc I think a lot
about that and I think about me just
being here as myself without
them and kind of what it's like trying
to find happiness despite those thoughts
um being there and thinking to yourself
well someday someday I'll I'll be happy
um
but in the back of your mind you know
that because they're not there
anymore it can never fully be the way
that you want it to be it can never be
the full complete happiness that that
you wanted and you just kind of have to
live with that you know you are changed
I'm going be honest yeah losing somebody
changes you
you're not the same person that you were
when that person was still in the
world you know and finding happiness uh
again can be very difficult I'm still
not totally there there are still days
where I feel like I'm still chasing
happiness amidst all of it
um
but I like to believe I was a good
influence I hope that I made that
person's time on Earth happy even if it
was extremely
short
yeah um I like to I like to believe
that not 100% way to be able no 100% way
to be able to tell uh but that's just
what I hope right I hope that people who
have also lost someone can listen to
this
song and uh and relate to it in some way
and Chase your own happiness
so that's what I have to say about that
song and I hope that you guys enjoy it
one comment that I got about that song
from an interviewer was that it's
strange because it sounds kind of like
there's like a happy tone to it even
though it's a sad song I think of it
more as like a very wistful feeling kind
of like laying on some grass in a hill
looking at the sky thinking about the
person that you lost and there is a more
of a yeah happy tone to it because well
we're chasing happiness right trying to
find a way to be happy just playing my
guitar out on the grass alone in the
middle of nothing thinking about
somebody that I lost reminiscing about
the days we had
together kind of didn't really want it
to be a sad tune it's like a Bittersweet
feeling you know yeah wistful is a good
way to describe it at least that's what
I think
so it feels like a P3 song Now That
connection's almost unsettling oh true
enough actually if you really think
about the themes right
I think it's a it's a very chill
relaxing song um but at the same time
when you listen to the lyrics you're
like oh wow this is deep I told Mama
Mory I'm like you're going to cry when
you hear
it cuz she'll get it
right even though it's supposed to be it
sounds like in in tone it's a happy song
lyrics not so happy but I think complex
songs like that are so
interesting you know
and that's how I feel about it memories
of you is like that really sad song but
the vibe doesn't reflect it yeah but
that's what makes it so amazing I love I
love songs that have like a more upbe
it's it's upbeat but it's not like happy
enough to be like a very Ganky Happy
song it's like upbeat in like um in a
way that for example memories of you
it's very upbeat in that like you get
the feeling of the singer reminiscing
about all these happy moments that they
had with the person that they lost right
and then the lyrics reflect that and are
are sad about someone that that left
them right but like the the song is so
upbeat that you can't help but like just
think about like looking up at the sky
and like smiling you know thinking about
that person that left you H it it's the
kind of feeling that hurts your heart
when you're when you listen to it that's
so amazing that's one of the one of the
reasons why I want to keep making music
to someday make stuff like that you know
yeah it's like a ju to position it's a
complex feeling those are the best kinds
of songs that you can't quite describe
perfectly yeah so that's how I feel
about that that's what you feel when you
listen to end of a life I'm glad oh oo
voice crack that was an intense voice
crack I'm glad that you feel that way
listening to end of a
life hoping it doesn't make you and Mama
Mory too sad no it's okay it's a part of
moving moving on you know never
forgetting but still being able to move
on and
life well thank you for for listening to
me talk about that I'm sure that we'll
speak a little bit more about it during
the uh the lyric dive tomorrow right
there will be plenty of time for that
I'm
supposing yeah oh yeah did you guys know
about the show for anybody new that
dropped
by
oh check it out show is happening
tomorrow make sure that you're there
it's in 3D and I'm performing some songs
new songs off the album make sure that
you're there uh for PST it's uh the 16th
at 9900 p.m.
PDT
yes so be excited for that you must be
or if you don't want to be that cool
too if you don't want to be that coool
too now would you guys like to see some
videos I received some
videos I received videos from some of my
collaborators
I haven't seen them
yet I dropped them in here they played a
little bit and I was like oh no the um
I'll I'll talk about it in a sec there
there's one in there where like I'm
alone in my studio and I just go cool
and I close it and I like look around
I'm like there's nobody in here it's
just me I'm such a dork the way that I
said
cool out loud I felt so embarrassed of
myself nobody in
here that's how happy I was was anyway
the first one that we've got is from the
producers of last days and recently we
did a song together that's right you may
know them uh as the
incredible t uh
tyo L here they are so hi guys this is L
and congratulations Callie on your full
album Phantom M it's to your heart
finally paay off we're so proud of you
chance to produce one of song in Kell's
album called last AG it's really
challenging and it's kind of like a
thing that we never done before but Kell
was super nice we actually went back and
forth into studio trying to like get it
right you know cuz we wanted this to
sound right so thank you so much for
letting us work on this song it's been a
fun fun collab all of you out there you
better check out this album till we meet
again until we meet again bye you guys
they're so cool you know those guys are
awesome actually they gave me some
really great Notes too because you know
i' I think I've said this before maybe
in some interviews you guys haven't read
yet possibly um but they're awesome
seriously they care so much about the
process and like making the song sound
as good as it can possibly sound right
so I did my first recording and then I
went back into the studio for a second
day to do some other songs and they gave
me some notes um and we're like yeah why
don't you try doing this like maybe if
you sang this certain way on this part
it would sound better and they were
totally right um cuz like you know in
the song Last Days a lot of the a lot of
the notes I like kind of dropped at the
end a little bit instead of like
sustaining them or like holding them
straight I talked a little bit about
dropped notes before but um I'll go more
into it tomorrow when we go over the
song but they gave me so many wonderful
notes to like help the song reach its
maximum potential which I really
appreciate about those guys so they're
so cool really awesome folks um I've
Loved collaborating with them I'd love
to make um an original song together
someday uh we've done some remixes of
each other's stuff but that's about it
for now hopefully we can make another
song the habits I have yeah exactly
sometimes I need uh collaborators to
point out habits that I have to make the
maximum best possible song you
know thank you so much lemonator 50
gifties that's a lot of gifts what the
heck thank you oh my gosh thank you so
much lemonator memberships are really
really quite important to me actually um
for for various reasons um if there are
a lot of members basically good things
happen I can't I can't explain more than
that but it just means a lot to me and
I've had so many members thanks to you
guys so truly thank you so much for all
the amazing gifts um supas are still off
though still off um I'll I'll turn them
on again at some point you know now the
album is out but I want you guys to buy
the album more than anything so if you
want to send a Super Chat
maybe instead of doing that what would
really make me happy is if you went and
you purchased uh Phantom physically and
digitally if you could digitally also
cuz I mean a lot of people don't have cd
drives on their PCS these days so why
not grab a physical memorabilia as a
piece of merch and then go get the
streamed version bye bye bye it would
make me very very happy now we have an
we have one more guest or rather
collaborator video to share with you
guys are you guys
ready we guys ready are you ready for
this one I'm not ready I'm not ready to
watch it but I'm going to play it
anyway thank you so much by the way
everybody giving gifts thank you so much
thank you thank you you guys are awesome
thank
you here we go what is going on this is
lotus juice cop congratulations on your
new album hey I listened to the whole
album and it's amazing it's amazing how
you have no garbage tracks I
mean listen to to the whole album
they're all dope beats and what I admire
about you is that not only you got the
dope flow you can sing too um I love
that track number 10 through the blue
acoustic guitar and and the finger snap
with a lot of rever and your smooth
sweet vocal kicks in I loved it he's
so and such an honor to be featured on
your album thank you you looking forward
to um to your future and then um mad
respect man so congratulations once
again keep it up peace
con I'm such I'm so embarrassing I'm
such a
fan how did we make a song together
ah
respect juice is the
coolest man I'm so
happy I love that I like how you have no
garbage tracks in there my
man I'm like knocking [\h__\h] over in my
room he's so cool I've literally been a
fan since childhood oh my face hurts oh
my God honestly Lotus juice Su was my
first real exposure to J rap like even
before even before I got all into like
net rap and stuff like that and uh
joined the the net r/j RP community on
Twitter even before all of that Lotus ju
son was the first my first
exposure to any of that and like that
was the first time that I thought oh my
God like JF can sound like this like it
was just man he's so
awesome anyway way H dang it YouTube has
sensed my my fangirling
moment you indirectly called him old no
I didn't what the I'm old like forget it
what are you talking about no just is
well it doesn't look like it that's for
sure my dude looks so cool with the
glasses
and
for I'm so glad I really didn't think
that he would listen to the whole album
but he did no no garbage
tracks that's so funny cuz it reminds me
of something that an old comic
instructor said to me um about like oh
yeah you know when drawing Comics is
kind of like you know when you releasee
when you release an album and there's
some filler tracks and there whatever on
there but you don't really care it's
like the main meat that's what drawing
Comics is like some panels are just like
garbage whatever panels who cares but
it's not like the main money shot I'm
saying that reminded me of that but I I
don't want any of that I don't want the
filler I don't want the the garbage
tracks I don't want the the garbage
panels in my Comics you know no trash
here let's go no trash unless it's got
gaka gaka is the only good
trash do you know what a money shot is
there all okay hold on there are all
kinds of definitions for the word money
shot okay it's not only the way that
you're thinking about it there that's
the money shot right
listen no that's what my teacher said
hey take that up with my teacher not me
okay you call it a money well yeah
the garbage panels are the best because
they're the best meme
material okay that's also
true true do you guys want to hear a
little bit more
maybe possibly like a little bit
more potentially possibly
[Music]
potentially what are we
thinking maybe another song
might be
[Music]
nice shall we have another
listen all right let's do it whatever
makes the money yum at it so this song
now that we've gotten to this point
right is from Phantom I'm I'm going to
play my favorite here we go
[Music]
hello again my H is far the tide is high
but I'm still low you raise that gun
like you're ring for me babe Cut and Run
we can never free yeah there is never
any
go hide and seek take a peek at the
scale no one can teach I dance with the
that you know you m reach picking around
to somebody tellep fact and boys Wells
ready not boys and girls high up on your
phone R steady through the perfect
siners made of
gold people come and go only way that
you can go not to give a damn it oh oh
feel the drive
breaking loose come and dance with
me I am
what can't catch your still in may take
a Le but I tell myself don't mind cuz
I'm
all
yeah that's don't mind do you guys hear
I'm so excited about this one I'm so
happy with how it turned out it's like
Arby's it's got the
meats
y um keep playing it you're GNA have to
go listen to it
yourself but I'm so I'm so proud of that
one I'm really happy with how it turned
out did you guys hear um at the part
where it's like uh what is it high up on
your throne riding steady through the
glow perfect siners made of gold from
there on until the hook Jun Ken Johnny
joins me on the
track he's in the
background he does the vacuum vocals
it's really cool your dad would like
that song A Lot the music yeah see
that's what I I always thought I was
like I'm going to show this to my family
cuz like this is the kind of music that
they listen to just on the regular right
so I can't wait to people to this song
I'm very happy with how it came out um
because there are like rap Parts but it
starts off with a lot of singing and I
worked really hard on um improvement
with my own vocals and stuff like that I
think it's a really catchy song um I
love the ly guitars in there there's a
tide reference right The Tide is High
and that was on purpose of course um
Mama Mor's going to be proud I showed it
to her when we were driving down the the
highway and it felt like we were just
listening to the radio is what she said
she's like it felt like we were just
listening to the radio
together which was kind of cool I don't
really I think it's it's kind of rare
for me to make that kind of song so I'm
very happy with
it so I hope that you guys will listen
to it a lot um I'm really super
excited um about the release of that one
don't mind don't mind don't mind tell
myself don't mind I'm betting all on me
here we go um but yeah uh I had a lot of
fun in the booth recording that one too
with Jun kenong because we talked a lot
about how the song was sounding together
a lot of times it depends on who's in
the booth with me but sometimes I'll get
producers that are like oh COI no
problems and stuff like that but junin
song was someone that was kind of like
that was really good do you think it
would sound better if we did this or
like junan son would be like can I get
like two more takes to see if you maybe
have a different approach that sounds
better that was that's kind of rare
honestly with some producers and I
really appreciated that because I'm not
precious about those things I'm not a
person whose feelings are going to get
hurt if the producer says you know it
would sound better if you did this right
I'm not a person that really cares about
that I want to make the best possible
thing sometimes I I worry that there are
producers that are scared of hurting my
feelings and stuff like that it's just
in the way that you phrase things Jun
kinan knew perfectly how to do it you
know he'd be like that was good but we
can make it better you know Giga is
actually very
similar but you know G Giga of course is
very much about the quality like 100%
right you know junan son being very
involved with the production of the
track same with Giga gives me the vibe
that if it's not like we're just making
a track that's for me and they're just
going to get a paycheck and go home to
to them and to me I feel like it's hard
to explain but I really felt like they
cared about making my my
music sound as good as possible if that
makes any sense you smell unique today
producer who doesn't care about hurting
Mor's feelings hey I smell good I always
put on perfume cuz I want everyone to
think that I smell
good it wouldn't feel very good if they
said that sucked do better well yeah no
one wants to hear that but here's the
thing though I'm going to be I'm going
to be honest with you if you think that
the person in the booth sucks you making
them upset and feeling like they're not
doing good is not going to improve the
music that's that's just business that's
simply how it goes right so what you
need to do even if you don't want to lie
to them well I don't want to lie to them
and tell them it was good okay don't
what you say what you do is you say all
right how about we try doing this and
you just don't say anything because you
actively going out of your way to like
kind of insult them because you're
frustrated with how the music is turning
out is not going to make the music sound
any better it's not going to improve the
piece in any way by scaring them that's
not how it works you know music is a
very emotional art um and people's
emotions in the booth will be reflected
into the track
so okay fine you don't want to lie to
them okay but don't be mean you know
don't be mean not quite my Tempo hey
have you guys seen
Whiplash in before whiplash
y whip Whiplash is coming on its 10th
anniversary and I saw a what is it a Tao
Tao
notat edit it was really funny it was
really really
funny wh Flash oh man what a great great
movie I love that movie you guys see the
Tao
meme it was really
funny it was really really funny so yeah
10th iversary coming up soon I might go
see it in theaters again just if I'm
around in the states I'll go see it
again Watch along oo that would be
good that would be good so Whiplash I
love that movie so much that movie is a
great example of what I I consider to be
unironic cringe does that make any sense
not cringe in the way that it's lame or
like the way that it's become to mean
like oh that's stupid that's cringe or
whatever cringe in the way that it's
hard to watch it you know like I cringe
at every single thing that that they
that the characters go through that they
do to get it's
uncomfortable it's the base actual
definition of the word it is so
uncomfortable to watch the way that
flasher treats the MC yes it is
horrific but you relate so much well the
way that I relate and the way that I
take the message of Whiplash and that
whole movie is I actually I mean it is
it is in and of itself maybe like
literally a very good story about a very
extremely abusive Ive uh musician that
completely and
totally abuses his student in a way that
affects that student's mental health but
what quote unquote in the pursuit of
greatness right the way that I take it
though is I actually also view it in a
sense of the way that
we as artists view ourselves and the way
that we critique ourselves and Bash
ourselves for our own work and the way
that we hurt ourselves in the pursuit of
making something
great that's the way that's the way that
I also take it I think it would make a
great watch along though it's its own
horror
exactly I feel really bad for the main
character yeah but you know if you quote
unquote want to be great right but at
that point it's like is greatness is it
is it is that level of greatness like if
you want to achieve it you need to go
through some [\h__\h] right is that worth it
I think it's really
interesting yeah I think it's a
wonderful movie
got to cross that off the Bingo don't we
true enough true
enough yeah it's like will that will
that make you
happy it's your fave movie yeah I think
it's I think it's really good it's very
well done and it's uncomfortable I hate
watching it but like it's good does that
make any sense I love movies like that
anyway we went a little off topic from
the mo music
but but I wanted to mention that just
because we were we were talking we got
on this t tent somehow hey Mory can Yap
too not not as much as the others but I
can I can it's because I've become more
comfortable over time but back in the
day I had a bit of a hard time yapping
yappa
yepa
yeah it was a little difficult for me in
the beginning but
anyway oh I have time we might have
another
caller cuz I'm just here yapping away
I'm just
yapping I'm just a yapping no need to
close up shop early I like talking to
you
[Music]
guys Yap Li up Yori Yori Edge Lord
moment oh yeah I took a freaking I took
a quiz I'm not going to post it anywhere
because there's some stuff in there that
I don't want to post that might get me
in trouble but I took a quiz quote
unquote a quiz on the internet about my
anime taste and the the choices that
they had were few and far between but I
got categorized as a tasteful Edge Lord
you probably think the world is out to
get you you've probably spent several
hours explaining to your date why quote
unquote Griffith did nothing wrong
you're scaring the hose dude okay I'd
like to go ahead and defend myself
really quick I think griffth Griff sucks
just so we're all on the same page I
hate that guy I think he's super
interesting though like I'm super
interested in the character absolutely
hate him though and I think he did
everything wrong so quiz was incorrect
about
that
g I'm disappointed in you what are you a
Griffith fan disgusting sips
wine hey you can like him if you want
that's fine that's fine I disagree
though who is
Griffith okay dead beat I'm going
through um I'm going through a berserk
Arc right
now I'm really loving it I'm on I think
I hit volume 21 last night because I
haven't had a lot of time to read but
I'm planning on gobbling down three more
volumes
tonight I ship Griffith with a sword in
his skull there we go dead beat after my
own heart feel that what Arc is that I'm
still in the conviction Arc
I'm still on the conviction Arc uh
spoilers spoilers for berserk if you
want to read
berserk shut your ear holes for the next
10 seconds please spoilers spoilers for
berserk but they just put Casa on the
steak and I can't wait to see what
happens next
not yo I
had my jaw was on the floor I was like
there's no freaking way this is real oh
oh I hope it gets
worse oh I hope it gets
worse man I love it it's it's it's crazy
I can't believe I'm saying I hope it
gets
worse it can always get worse hello
father
hello it was so funny because I had seen
that horse face
[Laughter]
before i' had seen it before
and I scrolled down to that panel I was
like
oh this is what that's
from I was like
okay I know I get it now that it's the
meme I Now
understand this is pretty
funny I'm only for a skeleton on the
skull Knight is so cool Skull Knight
right that's what he's called I don't
think he's actually said his name he's
never said I'm skull Knight or anything
like that it's just do we just call him
that oh yeah it's basically lwig the
holy
blade
true
what oh my
gosh no worries take your
time I'm chilling
just hanging out I got no plans his name
is Skull Knight he is a knight with a
skull his name is John berserk the
name's a spoiler okay never mind all
right fake spoilers in chat thank you
for telling me that because I totally
would have tried to find out
okay I totally would have tried to find
out also Persona 3 Rose I'm about to
make you really
sad I mean I'm going to I'm going to
finish Persona 3 don't worry I'll finish
it this month um but I really want to
play Dark Souls 3 I really want to play
Dark Souls 3 please understand please
forgive me please forgive me sorry
Persona 3 Bros just a little just a
little taste a little taste of Dark
Souls
3 I can't blame you I'm P3 Rose we will
finish it we will finish it this month I
promise well it's a Mor promise so can
you really how much stock can you put
into it we're very close to the end of
P3 I kind of have to for various reasons
that will become apparent soon
so what's a
Persona um those my promises I'm just
really oh oh oh we have guys we have a
caller that is here today are you guys
ready for another call all right welcome
you're on the horn hey who's
there
oh oh I'm sorry hold on a second I have
you at 1% I think we were playing a game
together okay hold and then I put you at
one there you go hi
hello it is I your
fan can I have your autographs yes of
course for you anytime anytime
ol congratulations on your album oh
Ollie thank you yay oh I love you're
using the soundboard thank you so much
olly it's so hype right now thank you
you're welcome I'm sorry I'm late I
overslept oh no worries I mean I'm just
chilling out all good I figure people
are over sleeping so I'm just hanging
but thank you for making time to call me
my pleasure oh Ollie gives you big hug I
miss you so much motorboats you oh my go
hey hey hey hey whoa whoa whoaa whoa
hold on hold on hang on let me move
myself downward so you can't do that
anymore I'm shy I'm shy you can't you
can't sorry
Chad oh no no no guys it's just RP it's
just it's just RP don't worry don't say
it should have been me it's just
RP for now for
now ol thank you so much for calling how
are you I want to know how you're doing
I'm I'm I'm great it's just uh you know
um hollow life stuffs busy you're busy
you're super busy I hardly ever see you
stream nowadays true well I mean you
must be drowning and work yeah it's more
like I'm on vacation and stuff like that
I want to go see some family but I'm
ready to get back on the grindstone you
got you know me I love to stream I love
streaming these days yeah you workaholic
you s by you it's fun it's fun it can't
be help it is Ollie Ollie what is your
favorite song off the album have you
gotten a chance to check it out I have
and I I have two favorites actually two
oh my God you liked that many so much to
make them your faves yeah I I listened
to all of them but I was I was still
kind of deciding which one I like but I
didn't I decided oh I like these two the
best okay which ones did you
like you have a guess okay uh let me
think um this is this is a tough one uh
let let me think okay can I have a hint
are they are they in the beginning or
end of the album oh uh they're they're
in the middle in the middle okay I think
that you liked um I think you liked
don't
mind and uh cold following what did you
like holy [\h__\h] how did you get don't
mind did I get it yeah don't okay I got
Don't Mind Correct y ding ding ding ding
ding I'm glad you like it that's my
favorite song too off the album yeah
it's how do I say it it's a it's a swing
but it's not like too hard on the swing
I love it it's kind of
rock yeah yeah little bluesy guitar in
there yeah I'm glad you like it I tried
to I tried to sing with my whole heart
it's like a little so put a little soul
in there you know yeah I love that so
much it's how do I say it it's classic
yeah I don't have like any other word to
Classic I like that to describe it
honestly Classic's a good word I'd put
in there yeah Tex and
soul other one is actually skeletons you
like skeleton oh I mean I guess it makes
you're a you're a zombie after all so of
course did like a song named skeletons
you zombie
you it's it's like a 2020 Mory core you
know yeah yeah yeah oh okay so you kind
of got like a you got a feeling for like
some of my older stuff like maybe end of
a life or something like that maybe yeah
yeah that's why I love it so much I'm
like this is the old Mory she's not dead
yet let's go she's not dead yet not dead
yet well I mean I can't die I'm death
after all it's
impossible true that makes to both of us
oh true we both can't die that's why
we're besties oh my gosh you're just a
good point hly I'm glad that you like
that one so much yeah you know now that
you say it I feel like my vocals are
yeah pretty reminiscent of like a an
older version of me but maybe like a
little more singing possibly yeah that's
what I thought too and I don't know I I
just love your soft waps a lot a thank
you so much olly I try to like pull it
back a little bit for those you know not
go too intense cuz it's supposed to be
more laid-back and soft so I try not to
go like full intensity on those yeah
more like relaxing feeling I hope that
you can enjoy it while you're just
chilling out you know yeah I
love well I mean I love all of the songs
but like those two chef's kiss French
kiss um lots of kisses as herb would say
as herb would say lots of
kisses a that's so nice thank you so
much olly I'm so glad that you enjoy him
that much yeah I I I I hope that here on
out you uh well I mean honestly you're
already at the top right now but uh just
so you know that I'm always supporting
you at the back oh no you're at the
front of my mind all
the you're always at the front of my
mind olly I love you very much you're so
sweet you're also very like gumbad all
the time and I really respect that about
you so keep doing your best cute zombie
Kai Chad she says she loves me she says
she loves me okay well love can take
many forms o love can take many forms
right friendship love romantic love but
mostly friendship love I don't
know there's also a thing called friends
with benefits o I don't know if I'm
ready for that olly that's that's just a
lot I'm shy I'm you got to hold my hand
first
you got to hold my hand she wants me to
hold her hand Dad no I mean I'd be okay
with I mean if you no it's just that if
you want to get close to me you got to
very gently hold my hand for I'm very
I'm sensitive I'm a sensitive
girl well well well well let's not say
that in public it's getting very very
out of hand right now oh no no no okay
doie do later hand holding I'm not the
hand hey I don't think hand holding is
that loot it's just a meme my goodness
y'all calm down calm down you can't win
just give in okay fine I give up thanks
olly for supporting me yeah you're
welcome I hope you have a great rest of
your day thank you so much Ollie for
making time to come let me know what
your favorite songs were and and I hope
that you enjoy the album in your
day-to-day life it make me really happy
of course I'm I'm I'm uh looping it
right now
y see thank you so much I'll see you
around Ollie go have a great rest of
your day okay you too I love you love
you too oh my God what is ah no don't do
that I was I was going to go hide under
the desk again like Ollie
don't don't do
that oh
man oh man Ali's great I feel like
because she's cohi it's a little easier
for me to to play along but M and Cal I
get scared she's just so sexy you know
and I'm I'm here like standing bowlegged
with like a bottle of Gatorade in my
hand like hey kids skateboard over my
back what's going on I'm your dad like
the least sexy being on the
planet I
can't I can't and then she's
like and I'm like oh I mean yeah my
butt's pretty big but she's like I can't
I can't lose to you with your huge butt
I'm going to be honest with you my butts
may be only 1 cimeter bigger than SOS we
both have pretty big butts we cannot
lie hey how do you do fellow
kids o
o now I get
nervous I've said before I feel kind of
like nervous about hugs right for
example hugs hugs are one thing I
nervous about but if it's Hol M I like I
like bear through it if that makes any
sense and I love f m hugs their hugs are
just so warm and friendly if that makes
any sense you know like if I can feel
the friendliness in a hug and it's just
friendliness then I'm fine with it right
what if it's suic no no no no no suic I
respect too much don't want to touch I
will I will stand a firm two feet away
and and do it like a little bow okay
maybe not two feet that's a little close
four feet do a little bow
yeah yeah F Moko give great hugs though
I love their hugs yeah and so say is
great too it's just I'd be too scared to
hug so say again I I just I have too
much respect for her if that makes any
sense professional side hug but say say
mind though I don't know again you know
one big thing is that I feel like JP is
just very different
[Music]
when it comes to like things like um
hugs and stuff like that may maybe it's
okay because I'm got C
if it's a girl yes ladies oh ladies no
problem I
can't Lads I can't no no no I don't even
want to think about it
hugging the lads I can't I can't no no
no no no no no
[Music]
no Maes I'll just start squirming no no
no no no no I
can't no no no no
[Music]
no so you want hug yo no yo is like my
grandpa D no maybe not Grandpa Uncle
older Uncle not Grandpa older Uncle I
don't want to hug my older Uncle that's
weird that's a strange
thing how about a respectful fist bump
for the lads
anytime I'm fine with that Grandpa pain
yeah go crying in the club no no no it's
not like that it's not like that
ch
[Music]
ch hey
a wow hold on a second wait a
[Music]
minute oh man with the mission tweeted
about our song in my
album I can't believe I got to collab
with man with a mission hold on can we
segue into that really quick can you
guys believe I got to collab with man
with a
mission J junen Johnny specifically well
someday we're going to get that man with
a mission collab as in all members
someday but for now junen Johnny song
can you believe can you believe that
junen song said yeah I mean to be honest
though junin son's always been my
favorite junin son is my favorite member
of man with a mission
so I was very like whoa
[Music]
cool you know and that picture we took
together oh my God cool wolf
man he's the goat and like honestly
honestly English so fluent I was like oh
my gosh that was I think it's one of the
first times that I got a chance to make
a song with somebody in the studio where
like they spoke fluent English to the
point where I didn't have to hold myself
back if that makes any
sense I could completely and totally
like speak 100% fluent
English
um and not worry about whether they
whether he could understand me or not so
it was really cool you went to their
tour they're awesome aren't they
cool and I love their whole backstory
too love love their music so much you
John Kens song gave me so many good
pieces of advice for doai as well for
the lyrics which is another reason why I
feel like it's it's a song that I could
hear on the radio
um you know I know there's Japanese in
it and maybe America's not quite ready
for Japanese on the the radio unless
it's like uh Megan Megan theast stall
and thank you
Megan thank you Megan let's keep pushing
for Japanese music on the radio in
America little by
little I'm going to sing that at the
next the next unarchived
karaoke um we're get we're getting there
little by little thank you Megan little
by little see all we need is like main
mainstream stars to kind of like push a
little bit more with the Japanese and
and then we can get there
right yeah I I can't though
obviously obviously I can't slowly but
surely it's going to happen eventually
but no I like that song I like it it's
fun it's fine I'm just head
bobbing okay you gotta understand where
I come from right you got to understand
my my roots and like even like hearing
about how the song was produced and like
how she made it with a an actual
Japanese rapper like of course my mind
goes places because I've been in that
same situation and I can totally
Envision how it came together and I
think it's really cute just tell them in
Spanish oh no no Spanish Bros is like
huh Spanish speaking Bros are like what
are you talking
about oh
man
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay that would work though I yeah for
people that don't speak Spanish don't
worry we're used to
it LO
mucho CIO
[Music]
that would actually work you really
think so h i
wonder I think they'd be down
anyway was that
Spanish I mean there are some
similarities but very light similarities
I would say in the in the
phonetics possibly
potentially any weird language which is
either Spanish or
Chinese
yo o that's how you know someone only
speaks one language that's okay to only
speak one language it's okay it's okay
you share the pronunciations a lot of
like the RS and stuff like that for
example a lot of times in like uh
Japanese songs there's a lot of R
rolling as
well especially ad songs
not in the states Spanish is too
widespread for that to work you think
people would know immediately
probably be seething hey she can roll
her RS she just has to try really really
hard is the
thing yeah true
enough yeah oh she dropped some awesome
R rolles when you saw her live nice
she's a great live performer love the
Ado box that's pretty
cool I'm proud of biu with her art
oh you know what will be really fun
actually I was just thinking about this
when I'm in New York I want to do I want
to do some streams from my hotel room I
purposely okay hear me out I
purposefully asked for a bigger room so
that I could bring friends in
there and I want to I want to stream
with a bunch of
friends we'll see what I'm planning on
doing is I'm planning on setting up a
stream and then I'm just going to go hey
I know we're here right if you want to
come
over just get in here wouldn't that be
so exciting right before breaking
Dimensions going to jump on the beds for
shame why not pillow party not pillow
party pillow fight pillow party sounds a
little that sounds a little salacious
somehow if you want to no force them I
can't I can't I can't yo some members
are really good at like at being more
forceful like you will get over here you
will do this collab right I can't do
that I can't I get too scared I get too
scared it's not a yo but
y fly and sleepover only with people
that want to come though if some folks
want to get their beauty rest
understandable got to get the beauty
rest right so that we can look really
good on stage for you guys of course
[Music]
but tell the forceful members to get the
others to come by I'll just be like hey
Kiara go grab everybody Kiara will be
like got it and I mean that in the best
way in the most complimentary way
possible whereas I'm too scared to be
like I can't force anyone to come over
here Kiara can you Kiara will be like I
got this Kiara's like I'll go get
him she she'll drag him she'll drag him
in kiar can you round up the best the
guest yep
Kara like leave it to me she's a
go-getter she is the extrovert she says
she's introverted but I feel like in a
group of introverts she's probably the
most
extroverted yeah I'll just beg her Kiara
help Kiara get
him could be fun could be
[Music]
fun I mean there there are there are
some people that be like come on over
and they be like yeah like I wouldn't
worry so much but I don't know I just I
just I get shy you guys know
me Kara knows how to do it right that's
a go-getter speaking of
go-getter she's an outgoing introvert
that doesn't like awkward silences true
true I also don't like awkward silences
but instead of actively doing something
to quell them I just live with
them at least these days I don't
know need to improve Mor's
confidence I'm
fine don't worry so much about me I'm
okay oh well I mean
yeah yeah I know that that there may be
are some members Su I want to hang out
with Su in New
York I just I need to be more
confident you know I need to be like
let's hang out cuz otherwise I'm like I
don't want to bother you I should stop
this release should improve your
confidence maybe if it does well I don't
know I feel like it's been doing really
good though they they told me about the
sales and that they're way better than
anything in the past so that's really
good but I don't know I there's a lot of
pressure I
guess stop being afraid I don't know she
has a very commanding presence
maybe I'll just I'll just do it I'll be
like
hey do you want to hang out in New
York okay hold on wait hold on hold on
I'm realizing something we're in a
country where everything is English
she's going to need help walking
around who could help besides well
actually there are
15 other
members that's why I got to send her a
message now and be like
hey I'm happy to be your guide now's my
chance
true
yeah I'll just be like oh yes I will I
will show you my Planet my
world now is the time better than any
other
time let's go it's the perfect
plan and any anyway we'll see how it
goes I love when a plan comes together
don't you dead beats don't you love when
a plan comes
together RIS her up with your American
hey guess what Senpai I speak
English but then there are a lot of
other members who also speak English and
also speak fluent Japanese that's fine I
speak enough I speak endearing
[Music]
Japanese no no no don't say
Empire State Building
[Music]
[Laughter]
Freedom
[Music]
lady don't miss your
chance I'll make your
work you sound like a voice action no no
no I'm just being silly I'm being hammy
right now
kizzy
stop stop stop stop
[Laughter]
[Music]
fore skib
don't forget Goa
sori tell her about the GES Gizzy
this no no no
[Music]
no prank
okay leave it to
me no
[Music]
problem sity how do you say I'm walking
here walk
[Music]
is but I don't really know how to say it
is like a Yankee sound maybe you add Z
at the end who could
say is like the very literal way
like literal way to say it I'm
walking that's not
right you k
y
y I'm walking here
[Music]
I don't
know I don't know show where the ninja
turtles live cool
[Music]
let's fight iut
the well I'll keep every everybody
[Music]
safe leave it to
me
anyway this has been really fun I had a
fun time I hope that you guys had a good
time too thank you so much everybody for
taking some time to come see me to come
hang out it was good it was a good fun
time I had a good fun time I hope you
guys are excited for the show tomorrow I
hope that you'll go watch it I'm going
to do my best to give my best
performance but I got to run off to
rehearsal pretty soon here
so I got to head out but it's been
really fun you guys I hope that you had
a good time and please listen to the
album Lots please buy it on iTunes hey
if you buy it and you send the screen
shot uh instructions in the description
you can get a very rough demo of Tide
it's very ugly singing singing it's a
full of bad Japanese
rap but it is a part of the production
process so I hope you guys will enjoy
listening to it nonetheless please go
ahead and purchase it on iTunes if you
do if you do listen to it uh via digital
as well if you make a digital purpose it
counts towards the goal that I'm trying
to reach uh with billboard so um I
really think if we push a little further
we might be able to get it I'm really
nervous cuz there's a lot of
expectations on me right now um but at
the same time I want to just believe in
the dead beats I believe in you guys I
believe that we can make this happen um
and I'm going to do my best as well to
give my best performance tomorrow
possible um and with that being said
let's keep pushing dead beats I'm your
Mori I hope they'll remember me and I
have one more song to play for you I
think this is another big fan favorite
and that's why I chose it so please
enjoy everybody this final song from me
and I'll see you all tomorrow for the
many fun things that are to
come well take care everybody okay I'll
catch you guys on the flips
side and please enjoy this last song bye
everyone please enjoy
Phantom peace
we'd
run right
through those nights I'll never find my
way back to you inside this Labyrinth of
Life there was Madness in the meaning
never laugh we were screaming at the top
of our lungs to the Nom this said he
never
died I'll
fly no
through those Heights on never find
another chance to say thanks for saving
my life I was hopess it was stinging
running roadless we were singing at the
top what was the root of it all I
couldn't say used to jumping the
fich which rug it off without complaint
not a sound or used to trying to find
friends cuz in the end nobody sticks
around it's when you shoved yourself
into a crowded place that you turned
around and found yourself in love and
outer space to SS no strings laughing at
our own dream just what the hell was so
funny up the wrong tree stemble used to
fall in Great Heights the concrete
jungle singing cuz it's all right we mix
the EnV in troubles rhyming our
discontent and though it's history I
can't forget the time that we spent
convinced to this could mean another end
exist between Twisted Al fic where I
miss my CH not Ascend disappearing into
the never happen is me that I can never
befriend Let It Go fade in Fade Out this
Gracey dream without without direction
flly there's nothing left but there for
me reason that it won't stop the rain
from pouring
on right
through those nights find a way back to
you inside this laby of light there was
madness in me
never we were screaming at the top of
our
[Music]
nevered sh the world without when the
and
does it matter
the Fant
[Music]