[Music]
so
weiner schnitzel wiener schnitzel ich
bin
ich bin air shrekt
heimlich maneuver oh yeah i didn't even
it didn't even teach you that one yeah
i'm heimlich okay
we're here on takanashikiya's channel
welcome kelly for uh thank you for
coming to my channel because it was my
loading screen and this is my background
so i think it's my channel yeah
happiness
happy to be here thank you
thank you hold on uh thank you
oh donkey and and um and she uh
[Music]
uh oh sorry everyone's a little shrekt
right now
you guys know they're sure
ass like air shreds those air shreks
those air mauries
those those are those air shreks they
look like jordans right but they're
green
my voice is dying guys but guess what um
guess what
i'm okay
i took i took a special check to make
sure i'm i'm okay and i'm okay
apparently but my throat is fun which is
bad because guess what feed carnivals in
a couple days so
yeah oh that's fine i'm not sure if
she's really okay but the document says
she's okay okay so i'm okay that's what
we wanted right that's all we wanted
[\h__\h] everything else that's all we
wanted that's right i made some tea for
us we have honey
and also you didn't drink it yet so i
want your reaction um of my mom's
elderflower
water it's not so strong i put it too
much tastes like elderflower yes
yeah my mom made a [\h__\h] of elbow
syrup and i poured uh it's for kelly i
think she has found the liking and
elderflower stuff right yeah i love we i
recently drank some elderflower prosecco
yes yeah and it was it was delicious it
was a it was a little too delicious i
think you know i kind of looked a little
crazy there
yeah but but it's fine it's fine
i've developed a newfound
appreciation for elder flowers yeah i'm
glad because it's a really really really
yummy flower
but today we had a really long day
of sightseeing yeah i had a lot of
schnitzel yes finally i'm i i'm glad i
was able to
make you eat all the most important
austrian dishes now today was
wienerschnitzel and she oh my god she
like inhaled it it was gone in like five
seconds she loved it so much butter
potatoes yeah yeah and lingenberries
yeah lingam merry jam yeah she ate it
properly with the lingam merchant which
because normally when i tell people that
schnitzel is being ate with um sweet
relatively sweet jam in austria they say
that doesn't seem like it would fit
what did you think
it was perfect because it wasn't overly
sweet
but
if you guys didn't know the wiener
schnitzel
is it's fried in butter yeah which
tastes really good it's always not
always yeah but the good place is they
fry it in like butter butters mites
that makes it taste even more better yes
yes yeah it was a very really really
good place yeah perfect it fit perfectly
way better than i ever could have
imagined
it was i want more yeah
but i want more of it so i gotta gotta
get some more to eat i'm gonna do it
it's easy to make it's actually fun to
make it yourself because like you you
you first you you bunk the schnitzel
with the hammer really loudly
and then you put it in some flour flour
flour flour
and then you put it into the egg and
then you put it into the the breading
and then you put it into either a [\h__\h]
ton of oil or an airfryer or butter or
whatever fryer yeah
yeah yeah
yeah if we ate the one with the cup no
the true finish this is made with cow's
meat yeah yeah but there's pork too pork
is fine too and chicken is hot i like
the calf meat one that one was very good
no actually i said cup but i mean veal
meal is the right
word oh
i see wait so i had veal
oh i didn't even know was that okay
that's i just didn't think that i was i
was eating rudolph clearly you don't i
own an air fryer do you own an air fryer
no i don't know what the [\h__\h] that is
are you kidding me what is that wait for
once i know a meme thing and you don't
know it what is that it's a like a an
airfry is like i have it in my kitchen
it's like a big box and then inside you
put something in that you want to fry
like fries or schnitzel whatever chicken
nuggets whatever um and you don't need
uh any oil except like one spritzer one
swoosh
or like one
one drop that sounds extremely dangerous
no no no no no not at all and you then
close it and it heats up really fast
it's like an oven but you need um way
less oil to
fry things than with um
with like if you fried normally in a
frying pan
so you save so much oil yeah clearly you
don't own an air fryer wow okay i don't
know how to talk to you anymore
now uncultured i can make fries on the
go yeah
with like one drop of oil oh look at
this i'm excited now yeah yeah
i do want to point out real quick though
yeah kiara if somebody knows less memes
than you it's me all right no there's a
reason they call me papa around here
okay i don't know what's going on ever
who knows last memes
chat me it's me
i guarantee you yeah
[Music]
yup people always say i don't i don't
even know what the fringe meant until i
joined whole life dude but like when i
uh collab with whole of english whole
myth members they always say that i am
like i never understand the memes from
you girls yeah but you you pick them up
really quickly i just forget something
really yeah see and see papa knows that
i mean yeah papa knows best yeah i
forget it anyway
old memes
memes her chat tells me
that's that is correct i do know the old
ones i tried to be hip by picking up the
things that my kids tell me i i am yeah
you'd be surprised how many like new
memes fly over your head when you just
like immerse yourself in like like
japanese culture on twitter and like
never look at english speaking twitter
ever again for three years and then
suddenly you come back and you're like
what is happening yes
well kelly before your voice dies you do
you wanna start with one song we see and
then we can sing and then talk and sing
and talk we prepared a lot of songs a
lot of songs yeah we'll just start with
this one okay okay
oh this is a fun one oh i didn't write
the new wrap for it though you rap
yeah i was gonna do it's fine i'll just
oh freestyling we'll have to test out
the audio though
guys you're welcome to tell us
uh
if you like the volume balance or not
because we'll sing it again and i'll
come up with a new rap there it is
hey
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
we're back again
[Music]
let's go
um
okay
[Music]
left side
oh
[Music]
yeah dude that is very nice
sir good kelly if you're gonna continue
at this rate
you'll have no voice left after three
songs sir good
food
that's what's so good
oh you remember owski
yes they're good and she's been like
like picking up so many words like what
that she sees on the street side
house gang is exited and and uh air
shrekt is i was surprised right
i told her something funny if you want
to say that shrek surprised you you say
shrek
had me a shrek
shrek surprised me hey you guys want to
know another funny thing yeah
so when the car stops it's it's wagon
hulk yeah but what if we what if we're
going somewhere chiara then the wagon
sound like what you wanted to stop but
what if we were going she was laughing
like a stupid stupid small chat when we
were buying tickets for the public
transport and i said okay just one
ticket and she says what is this one ein
fought and
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
and we were running after and i was
screaming we want to fart too we want to
fart too
you want it
i think i think yeah
some gas
that you really need to let out okay
it's okay i mean
that's just a human no i'm sorry that
you have to collab with adam sandler
today but this is how it has to be okay
okay and you said to me you said when
the car starts going it's ver fartin
that's what she said to me they're part
of the
[Laughter]
yeah
german is funny i always say thank you
continue studying german in your
language you need to continue
learning
okay i'll do my best
take some more elder flower because my
throat has got to pull through the rest
of then i'll be fine oh damn okay then
let's let's continue a little the next
thing you guys can sing for my diaphragm
yes fighter fight or fight or fight on
this song yeah
[Music]
um
hey
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
is
foreign
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
me
canada
[Music]
it doesn't have to go through my throat
oh my god you just push it through the
old windpipe
fake fake vibrato is when you when you
push on your stomach like
[Music]
kelly's suffering but that's okay
because i'm suffering with my friends i
really am madoka
would you like to make a contract and
join whole river as a vichy would you
you know you wanna
you know
yeah that's what cube qb cubey nice
what's his name cubing cube cube cube
cube a cube
cube
nine maybe
it was yanku all along i said this
before a long time ago
who's behind cubie
yeah he brought us down this intriguing
path
suffering still suffering don't know
what's happening i mean my throat's
suffering
well you know it was not suffering or
maybe it was a little bit of suffering
but today
i brought
i i brought kelly to a museum like
normally
i'm not really the time to go to museums
but i thought today
how about we bring cali to museum to
teach you some some austrian history and
culture because i noticed
besides mozart you didn't seem to know a
lot which is totally fine like you know
austria is a small country yeah yeah but
the names didn't really tell you much so
i thought maybe it's better to hear it
from a museum audience so we spent like
how long nine ninety minutes long time
felt like i think two hours it's belly
two hours that maybe we may have been
slower but yeah that's cool [\h__\h] it was
cool right yeah i'm glad we went it was
beautiful all kinds all kinds of
austrian stuff yes yes very beautiful
like a lot of like um old stuff
yeah and i got lots of souvenirs yeah
yeah you did buy a lot of souvenirs you
had so many bags to carry
yeah for friends and jp like jp
nice managers i'm excited to give them
you even bought like one of those
it's tacky but i think you're gonna make
it look cool one of those tacky t-shirts
i did but it was a cool tourism it says
it says austrian t-shirt oh my god hey
but it's so cool it had a little design
okay yeah i wouldn't wear it but yeah i
can see it on oh yeah i made it
nobody i'm not saying nobody in japan
can read romaji they they can i'm just
saying that
it's easier to wear it in glorious in a
pond okay it should be fine i want you
to
coordinate that into an outfit and show
me okay
i'm gonna make it look super good rock
that austrian shirt and i'm gonna wear
my new shoes that i made a stop to get
yes
i found the coolest shoes on the planet
and i said stop
we have to get these shoes
and kiara was like well we have there's
like a thing the very important
appointment that we've got lunch
and they're the coolest shoes in the
world and i
i am thinking about outfits with them
already so you know whatever i challenge
you no i can totally like when i saw
those shoes i also thought
i can see you wearing those like i can
see you coordinating those of some
outfits yeah they were super classy so
let me describe them to you guys okay
i'm gonna describe this air strength
strikes
yeah like they have like these hover
sides yeah cover shoes yeah so like they
were a perfect mix of like
very like high-top almost boot-ish
converse except classy and black and
white
and like
it's like like cool yeah like they start
off a classy shoe at the bottom but then
they turn into like a boot like high top
boot that goes up really high and like
you look like
like a
a gentle being
wearing they would uh work also with
your currys
they would they would but like i'd kind
of want to wear like some cool slacks or
something like that or like or like
maybe some like summer shorts with a
belt oh maybe not i don't know i'll find
the perfect outfit yes
yeah maybe half pants all right then i
hope those shoes will take you on a
journey
yeah a journey
how long is the journey that we should
go on i'm sure the shoes can make about
a thousand years until they fall apart
why why
why they take me to meet my friends
across the world
i mean
you met them while being with a friend
so
[Music]
that was a good transition right that
was that was pretty good you were
thinking about that
i respect it so
i'll reply the longer we wait oh that's
you yeah
the longer we wait the stronger it makes
us as we fight everything
[Music]
[Applause]
ages
[Music]
i bet this
a wave we can write
connecting songs across the sky
take off inside the longer we wait the
song that it makes success
[Music]
we'll make it ourselves and make
memories
there ain't a mystery our brains cannot
solve
we just shine brighter evolve
connecting songs across
the stronger it makes success
[Music]
the longer we wait the stronger it makes
success we fight every day
strength and finally the feeds this
journey
[Music]
a is years
[Applause]
[Music]
i mean when i belt the note and it's
like not it's like coming from my
diaphragm and not my throat it's fine
but
i still haven't worried about you yo i
have more training to do
you know this is just the friendship
kind okay you don't have to like
like take it like a live concert fine
good chill i just feel i don't know like
chill girl that i always do i'm like oh
it's a serious show i got it
i gotta try but it's not serious we're
just getting that's so serious because
we're on your big stage
on my stage
i need your chicken in the back he's
chicken have a name besides is he just
dj chicken
you know what nobody ever asked me that
before his name is now the chicken the
chicken
i like that
yo what's up the chicken circle there's
no one
[Music]
wake up
wake up wake me up inside can't wake up
say save me
[Music]
call my name and save me from the dark
oh
my tear is already in lukewarm i hope
you guys are still warm because i gave
you the firmness cup this is so good
she's drinking out of the negative
firmness club that nancy gifted to me
before
oh my god
yeah there's just a little you know it's
it's just a bit of um do i it's a soul
residue uh in the back of my throat that
i just need to kind of if you want i
have this but it's maybe a little bit
hard to sing with it in the fruit oh a
lousy like gummy though
good luck singing with that don't spit
it out no i won't
this will help me
okay ready for some
i don't know sparkling your writing
stuff oh yeah oh wait a minute
okay make it right here oh wait ride yes
ride in german is fart
yes but you can also say raiten
like um right he would ride a horse is
a a horse title
but ride a bike is a bicycle
farm
i like carame fart
no no no no no no sparkling farts
no
okay i don't come back to me i don't
remind her
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
can you believe it together
[Applause]
[Music]
economy
is
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Applause]
and i'm just gonna say
you are the one who wanted to
today sing a screamo version of fona's
original song but then i decided then
you i
said no no
you're gonna kill your voice do that at
a time when your voice feels better okay
you talked me down all right whatever
mm-hmm i was smart to do that
i'm frozen
yes
you knew how angry it
crashed
i mean look that was that was my that
was my body not not me necessarily all
right
i appreciate you looking out for me meng
thank you back soon i'll be back i'm i
just don't want you to ruin your voice
for you know the end of the week oh yeah
because it's happening right
it is a big it's fine yeah
i'll be a-okay this stream is brought to
you and sponsored by kfp as you can see
in the background the stage is sponsored
by kfp this is kfp so wienerschnitzel
oh we sell a wienerschnitzel burger oh
burger can you imagine we actually have
that in austria the schnitzel in a
burger pat burger buns i believe it we
do have that it's really good welcome
back
i'm moving and grooving small
moving and grooving small now i'm big
yeah yeah do you see only big
should i be bigger no you're just tall
it's not really did you know cali
dad
takana
our our sizes our official sizes
are
with our shoes
and and you always think you're taller
but are you aware that you're wearing
heels and i'm wearing flat seats no no
one can see behind your shoes
[Music]
and my phone's dead um
maybe there's another way around this
it's not charging it is it is but the
app is just too powerful
let's take a tiny break
no it's charging maybe but the app is
too strong
what if it's um
3.01 at 2.0
um i don't know what this cable is but
i'm going to disconnect it and then um
connect this one if you need to change
it into not your computer but
legitimately yeah let's zoom in the
charger
um
oh you know what mine is fully charged
use my cable that is oh but wait i need
the internet oh [\h__\h] it's also because
that is also connected to the internet
uh but
you could take this one right yeah
try this one thank you i'm donkey i need
to charge i'm fine
hopefully that charges faster
donkey
that's my new favorite insult that i
heard while i was um in europe um was
you're a donkey
people call each other donkeys here
sometimes i get to know english in
britain
yeah maybe they said you're a donkey
[\h__\h] donkey
you're a donkey donkey i love it
hey hey british beets
hey british caffeine
are you okay i'm fine do you need like
more honey yes please it's more honey in
the kitchen
honey honey
we're live for the reason
that kelly is gonna lose her boy girl
something something loving you maybe i
should make you a voice
what's up that beast
my voice is [\h__\h] fun i've always been
fun
my phone is my phone is coming back oh
finally you have to kill yourself
kiara this is an angel speaking
kiara this is your guardian angel
speaking i'm a guardian angel are you
listening to me where the [\h__\h] were you
until now i'm i've been behind your
shoulder this whole time no i'm your
guardian angel now listen to me you are
i have something important to say that's
just my manager no it's yes this is this
is this is janma
i have something to
say you're a donkey no she would never
say that dude you're right
you're all right donkey kiara you little
[\h__\h]
you're little [\h__\h] you're a little [\h__\h]
you better come back here now so that i
can say thank
or sing the next song alone okay no i
want to sing the song i'm just waiting
for it to power up a little bit for now
at least put you up as a
thingy sure we can do a cardboard song a
cardboard tune i shall become cardboard
to them
yeah where are the cardboards
uh assistant somebody bring out the
cardboards png folder okay so we have we
have uh this beautiful face oh that's
you and then i shouldn't oh i do that
too i replace pictures too
where are you i'm here i have one here
oh it's me as as my yeah oh yay
cardboard singing yeah one song with
cardboard i'm here though
behind the scenes in your puppet
you know because right now we're
cardboard maybe this is fitting the oh
yeah this is a good one okay let me
scroll down
oh yeah this will make my throat feel
much better yes all right i take the low
key you take the high key
okay okay good but when we sing
separately we just do our own thing okay
oh man
wow
my
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
foreign
my
[Music]
close enough
okay
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you sir shrek
here
[Music]
nice
but i wanted to make this longer than i
have
i think we definitely should sing this
one because i feel like we parted it
nicely
we already have 49 minutes so it's good
you gotta sing that one yes i think my
phone's ready let's let's uh see if the
camera is gonna make a revival of the
century a little piece
on the battery we can keep these up here
anyway hold on big big nasty cough
that's okay
oh that's a dry boy
oh that's a wrap oh my goodness
oh my god i see i'll be back a rooney
shortly
now one more thing we did
[Music]
i usually wouldn't do this uh if if i'm
not with a tourist so i'm glad i was
with a tourist but
we we rode a horse carriage yeah i was
sick yeah
you dorsey's
so cute and we didn't see much of the
horses because we were behind them and
then there was like a the rider in
between welcome back oh my god i'm back
in that guess who's back back again
she's back go again kelly's back oh yeah
well yeah i'm so happy we got to do that
even though it was pretty expensive
um
but they were nice and they uh i saw
when when i entered the the carriage i
saw there was some milk tender chocolate
in the carrots and i'm like oh i love
that chocolate so the writer was like oh
you want it and i'm like is it yours he
was like yeah it's mine and i'm like
oh yeah i don't know but then he left it
for us and i'm like girl you need to try
this because this is one of my favorite
uh austrian chocolates like german
austrian chocolate did you like it it
was amazing it reminded me of it made me
think of austrian twinkies ah yeah
similar problems yeah and then and then
the dudes started having a conversation
with you saying that afterward he was
going to go twirl something
yeah and he invited you to twirl it yeah
i said obviously no but i didn't even
understand what he was saying i think it
was like a slang term for i think so
yeah for making a dish with cabbage a
special kind of cabbage only found in
the underworld yeah um you said he was
speaking in riddles yeah
the chocolate so
that's nice yeah we saved this because
we're really really hungry
um
this one is
the hunger
ah i got you to eat everything i wanted
except one thing
with glucose
sandwich thingy yeah let me see um i
think
you can
um
get it at the airport too i will give
you instructions okay well i don't go
there for a little bit so just let me
know yes
okay you'll show everybody one more song
and then depending on how you feel maybe
i don't know how i feel yeah okay let's
do okay
uh also scuffed greek incoming
i don't use greek
lagoon
shrek
yes
shrink
we love this island
shrek means shock in german
wagon hulk
beer farting
okay okay
[Music]
cowboy
um
[Music]
hey look at this so-called gem of the
pastures on scrawny now i'm your master
return to what you know it ain't much
it shows
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
reasons
no matter where
you are
[Music]
[Applause]
so you think that's all huh
just gonna leave me like it's nothing
going without
me
return to the
season your feet
[Music]
montana
watch
[Music]
oh
it's okay i can sing one more really
yeah i think
we might really only have had one more
left anyway oh right did we sing
everything else i think we mostly went
by the order
well that was beautiful thanks that
works so well it's a as a collab song
because there's like two types of gouda
yeah
you got you got red sharky yeah yeah
blue shark and the mix of the nihongo
and the eggo
super good very good i love it so so
much so good
yeah i like it oh sure okay i don't
think it's really only that one left i
got one song left in me one song
i think it should be a fun one yeah and
then we're perfectly at one hour oh my
god we timed it perfectly once again
wow okay this one you can sing calmly
okay yes i know shh
i'm gonna sing it in a whispery moe
voice and then suddenly she starts
screaming all i can say it
might just [\h__\h] around and find out
all right let's go last song everybody
just see you guys before we get started
just you guys know i'm not in pain it's
just that i can't sing so my throat
doesn't hurt to drink yeah i know right
my throat doesn't hurt
but anyway
[Music]
i will not be speaking
for a long time after this because i do
have to part ways with kiara even though
i have some of my own plans for this
place before i return um
for v carnival i will not be speaking at
all yes um
better not be speaking no because i need
my singing voice to be perfect so yes
all right whispers hard on your voice
okay then i'll just i'll just australia
yeah then i'll just be myself i'll just
speak but just calmly yeah
i mean sweetly gently gently yep all
right then demo so none
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me go
[Music]
quack
okay wow
holy [\h__\h] how do you come up with that
it's everybody's circulation i didn't
come up with it it's already made up
that was amazing oh dude i love these
kind of mashups yeah well you made it
very special genius i tried to help a
little bit at the end yeah i know you
did great yeah sang pay phone and work
work work work like that and some weird
uh children tv songs
that works too that's incredible nice
you were survived kelly i lived you know
what i feel kind of okay i'm going to
take a nice long hot bath
i need to give you i'll give you a bath
bath bomb yeah give me your bath bombs
like bath bombs yeah i love them what
would you like what kind of scent
do you have elder elven flowers ah no
you have
i like i like to call it elden flowers
and ring flowers
i might have like something flowery
definitely yeah 100 yeah i'll give you
something nice wow
yeah
that was fun
it has been a long time yeah and yeah
also meeting in real life has been a
long time over a year
[Music]
you didn't change at all
no really no you're still saying i'm the
same yeah
i like to think i'm better
yeah i mean definitely uh not worse
that's good i guess
yeah it's good if you don't change
really i think so
oh yeah i guess so hmm now that it's
over i can say it oh
es
valesti
i think i think eventually i really need
to teach you like a do a german teaching
story i want to learn teach me teachers
especially
[Music]
ballustic time with your cat's day why
are you saying stick just loose together
i want to have a loose to get side with
your cat say yes yes yeah just to get
excited i think they will be here for
you as long as you want please have to
stay with my kitty cat okay yeah i know
they're hard to leave
chunkers and small chunky wonky and
smoothies
[Music]
which one do you think
you like more or do you like both
jonkers yeah
jonkers are so shitty
yeah even though she's just she's very
popular with uh
visitors really yeah
she's just so i mean
her fur isn't as fluffy as
it has more layers though yeah
and and she's so fun to hug for all the
deadpies who don't know what the hell
she's talking about she's talking about
my cats
hippers all the time a motorboat yeah
have you showed uh have you showed me
bonkers yeah well bonkers is my
raccoon
a bunker yeah i have a
third pet that's a raccoon that shows up
during uh hand cam streams yeah um
a gray colored something
which is totally not joker's or smoothie
i see it this is funky bonkers oh
bonkers you gotta get that taken care of
you know
[Music]
yeah all the time this is what you know
what oh sorry for the chat if that
happens you in the chat you know what
you need to use something called an
extension called hyper chat i put yeah
it works i didn't use it now but it
works hyper chat yeah yeah you're just a
little bit about that
well yeah really hyped chats yeah so
thanks for coming you guys
we really love and appreciate you i'm
sorry that my voice is painful to your
ears but i don't hurt my voice doesn't
hurt it's just it's hard to get words
out that's all but um it was worth it we
should have done the karaoke yesterday
yeah yeah but it's fine because i
wouldn't change the thing i i wouldn't i
learned something valuable today
sometimes you can just be goofy with
friends during karaoke and you don't yes
yes
it's fun
i had a lot of funny moments yeah i need
to go re-watch them again because there
are moments that i liked a lot
you can hear yourself in a version of
what if you were born with a really
husky voice yeah i love it i'll probably
cringe super hard not in like the cringy
embarrassing way but like in the cringe
like ow that really must hurt ouch
listening to your voice makes me feel
pain kind of thing um
can i say something what is it okay just
like um say about my new outfit yeah
yeah
on saturday
saturday um c-e-s-t 8 p.m
or
what is it est
let me quickly look i have a new outfit
reveal this time is uh although not all
of myth because it's my 1 million um
subscribers anniversary outfit and i
would be nice if you guys could come go
look i'll be there wait what was it i'm
scrolling i mean i would be
it's uh 11 o'clock pt 11 like the
morning time 20 uh 8 pm cst and a sunday
3 am jst if you like in the asian cea
time zone yeah yeah go check it out guys
i didn't show kelly yet you were no it's
gonna be a i want to be surprised
because i have my own guesses yeah from
your silhouettes i listen to your
guesses and one of them could be right
really
i'm excited i mean it's not that hard
the silhouette is pretty simple so yeah
i can't wait to see him thank you yoda's
cool everybody yeah cool
well and cali has your re-cannibal
i do
it's a live actual like live with people
their shell
i'm really nervous about it but i'm
excited and i have many wonderful senpai
that are also performing there
um and who knows what kind of magic
might happen right i think you guys can
get tickets to stream it actually um i'm
not sure about the details but i'll
tweet them as soon as i get them and put
them on my youtube channel because uh
j-chad should be sending them to me so
that i can make sure you guys can see it
um and i'll do my best at the concert is
asmr i know right it does sound like it
well this feels more comfortable also um
this month expect something big for me
as well
something wonderful um that you guys may
be able to kind of guess um what could
it possibly be i do promise a certain
something every month right once a month
uh and that will happen this month too
with something really great i got it
today and it was really really cool so i
hope you guys will be excited for it wow
um so that's all i have to say guys and
uh we love you guys so much yes
you guys are great do you want to say
something in german alvida peace
did you say that meant something weird
no no not like that not like that no no
auf wieder peace is okay okay
aviator peace
sir good and cheese juice
juice juice
juice cheers and juice cheers and cheers
cheerios bye everyone cheerios
by
[Music]
do
you