[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
Faire
thank you
[Music]
ah muted
uh
Michael okay hello okay
[Music]
Mama muted hello
how are you guys doing can you hear me
okay okay
um
so I I you guys are making me kind of
nervous because there's uh too many
people
I was just um you know I made sock
poppers recently
as you may know made sock puppets
recently because I made them I didn't
make them because I'm crazy I made them
because I wanted something nice for the
Advent calendar finale
and
um
I don't know how I got the idea I forgot
that already but I wanted something
where everyone can participate in so
that I have all all members of Ian uh
there
sure attention sure shut up
yeah and then when I was making them
um I showed a little bit of the process
and a member stream and then when I was
done I was like playing around with them
and
my members enjoyed it so much
and not gonna lie I really enjoyed it
too
playing around with those
uh but you know the setup was you know
kind of scuffed the point of view of the
camera was from above
uh so the hair was always falling back
from the sock puppets
um but I don't know it kind of worked
but still for today I I bought some I
bought some nice sparkly paper and now
we're doing a a frontal view camera look
and and I'll just be I'll be down here
and I'll be raising my arms like this
um I hope it will work out well
I made a nice frame the sparkly frame I
bought like a sparkly paper
and made a frame I wanted to do more but
I've lacked the time I honestly didn't I
wasn't planning on going so serious into
this but uh yeah ideally I wanted to be
behind the frame but I'll be in front of
the frame because now I I glued the
frame onto this is a curtain I glued it
onto the curtain
yeah
yes it will be archived because
um I won't be doing anything new
I'll be
reenacting
existing covers and songs
um ideally no it's not permanently
glutes on my way I mean I think so it's
like um double-sided tape
don't worry
um but yeah
um
no I will be sitting on my knees I'll be
kneeling uh what was I gonna say
um
oh God I forgot what was I gonna say
forgot
don't show your head Kiara well I'm
wearing an omu cat merch I already
tested out like how high I can go but
even on the chance of chance that you
are that I accidentally show up up there
then possibly you might only see the omo
cat hat and that's like Canon I would
say it's kind of Canon
so I think it would be fine in theory
What's it gonna say Aya ideally
um you know I only have two hands
surprise so I can't do songs that have
more than two people
um but also two is generally ideal
um just songs with one is not so
exciting so I'm trying to do mostly
double like uh collaborations so you
know people like Bales for example and
me we have the most collaborations
uh out there so we might be making a lot
of appearances
yeah
all right but we start with um a solo
how about that my playlist is like one
two three four five six
no wait one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve
maybe 13 songs
oh
and then we'll read super jets so it
won't be too long I'll just mess around
a little bit have some fun and then I'll
read super chats
oh yeah
okay guess guess who's the first the
first
um performer
yeah
foreign
[Music]
I kind of also noticed that it's a bit
more difficult this setup than compared
to the last setup so I don't know how
funny it will really be I'll try my best
this will be this will be warm up the
first one will be warm up no it's not
kiwala first one is not kiwawa
first one no no no
no no no
well let me try to
uh
oh God I'm this makes me nervous
oh I'm I'm going I'm passing by did you
see anything
I don't think you did oh sure I [\h__\h] I
should have moved the OBS window over
here now I'm already like
[\h__\h] wait I'm going back
I'm going back
okay
it's like a maze
myself is like a maze you saw my credit
card ideas I don't even have a credit
card
I don't have a credit card so that's not
possible I shall
Rachel
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay this this could this could possibly
work thank God that my one of like my
third monitor is
uh thank God like for monitors welcome
cintiq so I can like move it around and
I don't have to use the mouse because
the mouse is far away but I have my my
pen okay
all right in the off chance that you see
my head
it will be an almost cat head
okay I'll kill cookie oh nervous okay
first before
yeah one of my best puppets I think
one of my business all right please
enjoy Ina's performance I feel like a
child
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
everybody
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
wow
holy [\h__\h]
I'm not really kneeling I'm like kind of
like standing up partially but
oh my neck hurts I'm trying so hard to
look up and raise my arms it's kind of
exhausting the original point of view
was better it helped me more it was
easier but that was the first
of none other than
that
in your knees
wow
amazing for The Voice what a beautiful
performance that she delivered for us
oh my hands inside the sock puppet are
sweating
yeah thank you so much for taking your
time
you're welcome
to be here today but in yeah this is not
the last that we're seeing of you today
is it
I know maybe not
oh oh wait she's not going backstage yet
she's she's staying here whoa what for
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
my headphones are stuck
underwater Voice without filter
on my microphone
and yeah take the microphone cable
thank you
sorry did you see something
five golden rings
foreign
so in character it's not really enough
it must be the real you know
a sewing character is perfect
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
at all
the way
[Music]
today
foreign
[Music]
that's so [\h__\h] exhausting
damn
yay
nice
[\h__\h] nice let's go all right all
right all right all right Inna can take
a break
if you didn't know the song before that
says song cover that I released with um
Inya like a year ago how long ago I
wonder
I should say here where's my pen here
oh
yeah one year ago
oh wait it's like almost exactly a year
ago
a year ago minus five days
whoa
yeah you guys really liked that one I I
understand why
it's a fun song
yeah
the drama over icons icons
I'm preparing or the the idols
the members are preparing for the next
song how you guys doing today
how's whatever country you're in how's
your city
how you doing guys
the next
performer
and the next performance some of you
with special members only tickets may
have
uh seen this one before but this is a a
new version
[Music]
where could it be
kiwawa Channel
oh oh what does that mean
is it oh God this this puppet is falling
apart
I don't know if she will survive it but
she will do it her best
let's go
[Music]
foreign
there is
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
sometimes
ah my neck
I need a new neck after this
now kiss
[Music]
okay
um
today
whole live English
does not consist
of 10.
members no
today whole life English
consists of 11.
what does that mean
I'm sorry it's not what you think it is
but maybe another time however
I have invited a special guest
who was first not really in the mood
but I was able to convince the special
guest
oh
um yes okay
she shall moved it a little bit
okay no problem
[Music]
what does it mean what does it mean it
won't oh I might have to I may have to
move
uh because it's not in my tabs
it's not in my tabs right now
if it if it shows up in my recommended
that would help me but
no it ain't there
it ain't there okay I have to move from
my from my little corner before okay a
little break everybody
ugh
let me get out of here
oh
froggy Walla oh that would be a good
idea too
okay just use a frog puppet
just like that
okay where's my mouse here
oh sure
you know what that should be
what's the the little shortcut for
moving windows windows and out and left
but no
shift is it shift yes shift shift and
windows okay if I move that over there
then I should be good for a while
oh
okay I'm coming back oh wait I'm gonna
bring up
let me bring the rest of the salt
puppets
everything's okay
I'm okay we're okay
what's up
just throwing the girls
closer to me
okay
this is not helping
the condition of gargura
her insides are like
falling apart she needs to go to the
doctor I tried to fix her but I couldn't
fix her
okay okay what
where's my pen
or more Pango
you guys see my pen I'll find it I'll
find it when I'm back in my seat what's
up okay
okay the concert concert is
continuing
in a second no I lost my pen
ah there it is hmm now that I reach
without you guys seeing who the secret
guest is here
okay I got it
I got it
oh yeah right see
[Music]
let's go
I
already hear it
[Music]
I lost it
hey oh
I Now understand that was totally not
what I was going to play that was an
accident
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
so cool
tonight
[Music]
foreign
mama baby
[Music]
oh nothing better
there you go
[Music]
ah
[\h__\h] it's falling apart at least it's
not yet still noticeable
from your point of view
I need to give garguta a little break
man she's worked so hard
so hard but hey I made this new one
I made evil
okay look she even has blood on her TVs
yeah yeah she's had a good dinner
already what about you guys I guess
thought
most of you guys probably not dinner
time yet
um
our new edition
to the team
[Music]
it's tomato Gouda
ah tomato when I was making her she
first looked a little bit like Bales
because of the red hair but then I added
the white hair I think she looks like
not good now well you know spiky teeth
my butt you can definitely know it's not
it's not uh Bales because there's only
one set one row of teeth
right
all right
ah actually
[Music]
um
all right let's do this
let's do this
next song
next song You Know
um
we'll be with Iris the thing is for Iris
I had a problem
she has I think yet to do a duet song
cover with someone like a properly
released one
properly
released one so I had to do something
oops choose something from a karaoke
session oh not that one either
I love this one which one was it that's
not it either
why about this one
where is it
ah
about time someone releases a duet song
called a virus huh
what was that what was that oh yeah
hi Reese it's saw Chris
okay are you ready
are you ready also my voice kinda
this horse today
merry horsey today sorry but this is
good I don't have to talk much during
the concert because it's it's a
collaboration with
10 other whole life members
so I don't have to do that much
in theory
putting on a sec a sock a suck it suck a
puppet a sock with um
only I never suck hand is really
difficult have you guys ever tried
but with your hands
probably not oh sure okay
[Music]
my live CD is so useless today why
didn't why did I even put it up
okay
Ahoy hi
[Music]
I got a hi
hi guys
[Music]
my house
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
Ichiban
[Music]
what's the kind of uh
-huh yeah
[Music]
thank you
anymore
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
a conversation
oh yeah I have to revive
um someone
just for
one more song come on you can do it
okay I don't believe in you
I believe in you your head is departing
from your mouth but
come on
oh yeah it's looking really bad
I'm trying to not move her too much
good night
the more I'm doing this the the more I
feel like maybe I am crazy
maybe I am
sure
where is it
which one of my tabs could it be
sure
oh that sounded
that's not it
what am I doing
oh
I forgot to lower the volume a little
bit again
calliopeia Maury
[Music]
good day
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
oh they're good as dead
[\h__\h] dead new music video yeah yeah
you're welcome I think um
they should probably pay me about 500
000 dollars for this production value
but
yeah
I might just this once give it for free
you know I have to get some like
business contacts and so on
[Music]
in the beginning you still have to do
[\h__\h] for exposure
and then later on you can you can uh ask
for
the big books
hair is so messy maybe I should just
just stop using gouda and just use gar
instead because she's still intact
mostly because she's fresh out of the
oven
okay
oh
uh what oh that was that was so [\h__\h]
fun
reflect two like oh my God anyway
who's in nostalgic one an oldie but
Goldie
you are that's Cassie
[Music]
noise
Make some noise
[Music]
I wanna change
not anymore
[Music]
get your eyes
darling
[Music]
it is
foreign
[Music]
all right
hello hello everybody well that was an
oldie maybe some of you don't even know
it anymore
ah
where's the Applause
clap clap clap clap
okay I still have q in my head
whoa world that was my first song cover
with a gen mate
was it also my first song cover in
general maybe maybe but that's where I
started my my journey of
collabing with all my gem mates
started with care we and I recorded that
song in her place because I was still
living in Japan at that time well that
long ago huh
for sure
Cali's taking a little break
good for her
it's important to take breaks
Cali doesn't really know how to do that
so I had to force her
okay
how are you guys enjoying the photo of
English concert so far
the first ever whole life English
concert
produced by yours truly
what's that
oh
ah there it is
go next go next
[Music]
foreign
believe me
[Music]
foreign
booty
[Music]
thank you
you like this move
[Laughter]
it's kind of difficult being this way
last time I did it was kind of easier
um but I wanted I wanted it to be like
this this time
thank you
[Music]
you know who we haven't seen much of or
anything of yet
Council
Council council.com
[Music]
um
I'm thinking of which one to start with
um so I think I decided I think I've
made up my mind
[Music]
I'll use them
support supporting
reporting oh did you see something just
now
did I spoil or something did you see it
made up my mind don't need to think it
over if I'm wrong I am right I can't get
into my glove
[\h__\h]
okay I have to take up the other sock
first to put up put get into my glove
it's complicated
[Music]
I [\h__\h] love and starch
no no not anus tights
sorry it's just too funny for me
inside
[Music]
when the other great dreams
it's the Stars
[Music]
just my dreams
foreign
[Music]
and wait for a prince to kiss her
that was kind of what was happening I
think I think judging by the lyrics that
I have uh listened to probably properly
now for the first time
I think it was something about her
waiting to be kissed right she's gonna
close her eyes and please son
something like that I'm pretty sure okay
okay
um okay thank you Father for that sweet
sweet sweet
Charming Lovely song I do want to kind
of do anal starts now I really want to
do Anna's toy
oh yeah yeah there's like there's like
three different there's all the summer
there's ojisan and there's ojisan
there's so many types man even I don't
know anymore which one is which
it's tough
so tough man
I don't have the URL for
ain't no start but let me try to get
there
[Music]
she's going downstairs
do do
[Music]
I can't I can't take it anymore
hello
[Music]
foreign
there's nothing in my hands
[Music]
let me write days
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
gone again
for me
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
it
incredible performance
[Music]
my God I can't believe
I can't believe I got to hear ayna start
live
in 3D
4K 3D
performed by
none other than that
yeah
myself
okay
um
I hope you guys
didn't
plan on sleeping tonight
because this will give you a nightmares
this might
give your nightmares
where is it
look [\h__\h] hellmate
I know no no no no
maybe later
[Music]
oh
my goodness
[Music]
together
wonderful wonderful wonderful
that was The Nightmare inducing
[Music]
okay okay okay she seems to have a lot
of energy she wants to sing more
will we allow her to see more guys do we
want to hear more from The Nightmare
inducing Bells tacos um
I think we do
wait I'm putting on my
my support glove but it's actually the
wrong hand
foreign
she just needs coffee yeah this is her
look this is how she looks in the
morning when she hasn't had a coffee yet
um
I would say it's pretty cute
looks better than what I look like in
the morning
oh does it hmm that's concerned that's a
concerning statement
I'm not sure about that let's go okay
okay okay
uh
baby how's your life
baby how's your life let's forget
everything and have some fun
[Music]
making your Spotlight yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
this way
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
it's about tomorrow
[Music]
baby baby
mm-hmm
oh I'm shaking
I'm shaking
Bales absolutely smashed dads didn't she
amazing
bloody hell mate I was incredible I
figured maybe it
um being behind the camera is actually
kind of easier to do than being in front
of it hmm
hmm at least at least for the next song
let me try to do that
I need to learn more awesome accent I
have no idea how to for me it's all the
same when I listen to it it's not the
same but when I try to copy it it's all
the same
but maybe if I like bring it back into
my memory then by listening to a video
if it's more fresh in my memory and I
think I think
it wouldn't be so bad
the air is terrible here today I I'm
like
dying it's like there's a hedgehog in my
throat what the [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
um
next door
it's not too late for this
I think
[Music]
Christmas
oh secrets
[Music]
now you're dead
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
only
now
please
[Music]
who died
holy
Glory now
[Music]
she got hands
oh God let me take a throat caddy this
is terrible I'm dying hi Santa
[Music]
like the second half of the concert you
missed a lot but hope you're enjoying it
how do I
come on
bills and bills and crony trying to open
a fruit candy
okay that side that side looks good
other side
[Music]
I got it I got it I got it I got it okay
spicy okay maybe we'll maybe with their
their hands not my hands it's their
hands
this is the most clumsy way I've ever
opened the fruit candy before
okay there we go this I really recommend
this one by the way it's the uh
well you can't read it it says
Honey Honey Lemon
spicy no no not spicy spicy not good for
my throat but I know what you mean oh
good Chef that will help me
okay okay
oh
um
there it is there it is I think I'll go
back down again
this makes some things easier but also
makes some things more difficult so let
me go back down
you didn't see anything did you you
didn't see anything okay okay okay
what
[Music]
it's time
every day every heart
la la la la
[Music]
is
a good time
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yesterday
I can't eat it
[Music]
stay back
Humanity clings to the passing Nostalgia
will they ever escape from the change of
time only the clock will tell me
[Music]
meaning
everyday
[Music]
oh my God she's gonna have a new outfit
did you hear that you're here what
oh
this was a little sneak peek to her new
outfit
you're welcome
you're freaking welcome oh I don't know
how many songs I have left let me check
I did this one I did this one
I did the uh this one I did this one I
wrote this one
I'll get this one
oh
I'm kind of
hmm I'm done no way this one I didn't do
this one
oh
[Music]
what was that
I have to change socks
some fresh socks
are in order
um
you already know
you guys
subscribe it's more fun with two socks
you know solo songs are they only have
so many Stone songs like Iris for
example but
it's more fun with two songs man
also like by doing crony song I feel
like I got a big cramp in my neck
because I kept on lifting up one end
only
yeah
I need to make more this this should be
enough motivation
for some members to do more Duets please
so I can do this kind of stuff
okay
I don't even know this song so well
but let's go
[Music]
Bye Bye Baby
I'm ready
[Music]
foreign
thank you
no
wow
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
ah I don't want to stop yet
what else could I do I could do so many
solo songs
[Music]
more and more I'm thirsty for more
how about this one
mother's solo
[Music]
maybe you guys had
an idea what else could I do ah Kelly
gooda King
on which channel was That Cali or good
up
first before blood of course I am but
that's only solo
[Music]
will you find it
hello
which is fun I want to do it again
no no
uh you're working
cheers King they are King
okay
a funny idea for later we can try it out
uh
uh okay get these socks off of me
stinky stinky socks would sound very
different stinky stinky sock no they're
not stinky they're not really stinky
I'll go for um gar if that's okay
I'm I'm scared I will break every last
remaining bone
of gura if I
use her anymore
what's up
okay did you notice queen and king they
both have the same song
just notice now unless I saw it wrong
but it looks like it
three two one
[Music]
on my place
foreign
[Music]
website
yeah dude that was sick
okay that was lucky
[Music]
I took up the wrong sock
my dad
I have one more idea
I don't know how this will go
I have there's really no idea but
let's try I'll try
oh my I'm yeah yeah my king cover yeah
yeah AKA
um
heart challenge no wait what was that
no right I never did I never did the
king cook it was just
it's just a link to
well
a king cover of course what what else
what else would it be
okay okay how could this
way
okay
now then one day per year so you better
get your fix before we close it's rare
to see us like this you know
if you'll just follow us this way we'll
show you to your seat
is this your first time at a meat Cafe
today is your lucky day then we're not
just any old maid Cafe
um
that's right
I guess you read the sign outside
we pride ourselves on running a meat
Cafe work all your words can wash away
with the help of our healing ear
cleaning treatments
so please go ahead and relax
uh here's your seat
please get comfortable with these
pillows
I suppose we should introduce ourselves
since we'll be taking care of you today
it's so small Cafe so we're the only
ones working here
please be patient with us if the service
is slow
I'm Vanna and I'm good
and you
what's your name
a lovely name
well that Master
what would you like to order
we have a special today too
maybe you saw it on the sign outside
since it's Valentine's Day this feels
like a horrible selling a limited time
only drink set
it comes with an iced lychee lemonade
with I'm gonna be killed strawberry
jelly
Topps with whipped cream and sprinkles
and the selection of hard candies
so
how about it
say no she's gonna kill you because yes
she's gonna kill you because that's the
only thing on the menu
what did you expect from a cafe open for
only one day hmm
excellent choice oh girls talking yeah
I'll go prepare your drink
good I will keep you company in the
meantime
you must be pretty brave to try out a
maid Cafe with a new reviews
weren't you worried
I guess you saw the cute Maids on the
sun and figured it would be okay
I'm surprised you still wanted to come
in when you saw that we don't have any
license to sell food
that's also very horror movie like
maybe I should never said anything
wrong you'll be fine on you
we're just making lemonade right even
kids can do that
I like your spirits
see
you're not afraid of the onion
you're not afraid to try something new
I'm like that too
you know I've never worked in a place
like this before
you has but this is all new for me
too
do you want to start
don't worry it'll be fine
I'm sure you've cleaned your own ears
before
and you don't have a license either come
here
how far should I go I don't want to bust
your eardrum
[Music]
um
how's that
really
thanks
maybe I could get used to this after all
[Music]
you couldn't tell right
it's hard not to be nervous when you're
trying something for the first time
it's not just me everyone feels that way
you were nervous too
I'm right aren't I
cause I'm not the only one who's new to
this
[Music]
don't accuse me of being nervous if
you're not ready for the accusation to
come right back at you
now
sit down and relax
yeah
you're cleaning
getting to the fun stuff without me
um
here is your drink master
I forgot the candies
um one moment please let me just don't
worry
I'll get them you stay here
oh if you insist
thank you good
so master
have you been enjoying your time here so
far
that makes me happy
I wasn't sure we would get any customers
today
I couldn't have asked for a better one
stop it thank you for stopping by today
you have my gratitude yeah
uh good I told you that she's new to all
this
um
it's chill
I suppose I have some experience with
the relaxation techniques like ear
cleaning but
I have never upgraded a made coffee
before
that was her idea
so
it really means a lot to us that you are
willing to take a chance here
I hope we won't let you down
I didn't even write my will
should I clean your ears as well yes
there'll be a clean let's clean your
body here this time
clean cadaver
okay please clean my ears
what
ah
I really am relieved to have a customer
today
I was worried
worried that no one would show up
here you are like a gift
[Music]
foreign
if only we were open for more than one
day
and you could you could come back here
uh but
you won't go to other counties after
this all right
it won't be like ours
nothing will be
so don't bother with them
you can trust me
I just don't want to waste your time you
know
really
would be a shame
to never see you again
she's hinting that she's gonna take your
eye if you leave a delivery
welcome back
so then we get started then
well officially
hmm
let's clean your ears pop
when was the last time you cleaned them
don't tell me you've been walking around
with 30 years all this time hmm
just kidding
I think they're pretty much clean
already but only because we did such a
good job earlier but Mortuary assistance
lean back and relax and let us take care
of everything
you've already did once I can't do
anything but nothing leaning back
we already know that you wouldn't be
nervous because of this kind of thing
right
but
just in case you are nervous
it's okay
it's only natural to be nervous with two
cute cat girls are cleaning your ears
right
[Music]
no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no human flesh
[Music]
yeah
indeed no no no
no no
[Music]
um
no bears you're taking everything no it
fails she's so right she looks like
bells to me no no no
I'm hungry too
when I'm a shark I need to eat
you're a freaking tree
like veggies small human
ah no you're right actually
um
[Music]
this is a long commitment
bones oh it's only bones left bones are
my favorites there they're healthy
[Music]
how long is this
yeah
oh God it's eight more minutes no
how many more minutes from here
I've done this any longer okay okay
point of view you are their meal you are
the meal you're not the customer you're
in the meal
okay
oh God oh God
Michelle
I'll do
one last one
[Music]
we got back into my spot
foreign
[Music]
I think this is like this could be very
inspiring for everyone who's doing ASMR
the girls maybe can take inspiration
from what I did
and they can um
oh
yeah I fixed it but you didn't see
anything right
and in the future they can make their
ASMR videos like this like I think I
think it it gives it an extra Charming
touch
nope okay good okay
my normal cat
hat shall not be seen
okay I'll give the last one to someone
who didn't have much screen time
okay but I kind of want to don't do it
okay I'll find one more
I'll I'll find one more
for sure
okay
oh
[Music]
all right this will take
my my knees are so weak
okay
when these are jelly
what you thought that was Anna that
sounds like I'm Into You
arms heavy huh are my arms head is that
a meme when I say my knees are rigged do
you guys ask if my arms are heavy
because it's a meme
I'm not up to date with the memes
and
moms
I'm Savvy mom's spaghetti
makes a lot of sense now where's mom
where did my pen go up here
Michelle all right all right I I haven't
listened to this one before but at least
I know the song
so surely it'll be fun
last time
we're gonna teach you guys
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
together
[Music]
[Applause]
please
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
you ready
me too tonight
[Music]
the world
oh I feel emotions
oh man Iris smiling through the pain yes
the pain the pain in my heart you know
it was really funny and interesting
about that song is that you have such
like good high range that when you hit
those high notes you are like using your
head voice and not going into falsetto
oh no no no I'm totally using my faucet
are you sure because to me it sounds
like your head voice it's like a mixed
voice I think
ah
I need a [\h__\h] massage
yeah yeah
that's it that's it that's it
I would clap but I took off um I took
off the socks uh imagine clap well I
mean I would show you but I guess you
can just hear it
[Applause]
oh that was the first ever
revolutionary amazing legendary going
into history historical
oh incredible flawless
amazing Halloween first concert
the emotions are overflowing everybody's
crying everybody's just asking each
other for tissues because they can't
hold back their tears it was just a
dream come true yeah whole life English
is real
we're real
the emotions are real
uh thank you guys thank you thank you
thank you thank you
we can do it again sometime maybe I can
make some sock puppets for some other
covers that uh have a whole lot of
English members with like all of Japan
or ID members or so for more variety
have I changed your life or your socks
you should change your socks your socks
are stinky I can smell them till here
Lord when's the last time you changed
yourself also they have holes buy some
fresh stocks there of holes
stinky stinky so holy like it's more
it's more whole than sock at this point
oh my God my neck
I was constantly like
like kind of how does how to describe it
like perching up
with my neck extended like a giraffe and
my arms
reaching for the Stars
clicking exhausting okay uh camera is
off so I can move this now
let me sit down properly
um
oh
I feel like an old grandma right now
drink water
oh that was so exhausted next time I
left a little different setup
oh
you're wearing your finest fine eyes
[Music]
hadow let me move back my welcome tablet
oh and I sound not so distant anymore
tablet there we go double arm gun Bonnet
Alicia
okay
please sell the puppets no I still have
some use for them I'm also a little more
Masala
I still have some plans or do I I mean
not really but I'm thinking I I'm gonna
continue using them
and fixing them
um because it's like really broken
it's
unsavable
puppet merch
you guys want puppet Birds what like
like the socks themselves and do I have
to mass produce my socks
I wonder if if there's a way to like
um not like have to do it by hand but
like in if it was really merged if you
could kind of like
um yeah Mass produce it in a in a
factory hmm
hmm
are you guys no [\h__\h] away you guys
say yes to everything you're gonna say
yeah what sock merch yeah yeah sure
I don't believe it
I don't buy it
and then the sales numbers are [\h__\h]
finger size Pockets puppets oh yeah yeah
that would be so cute too like even just
like to make it you know that when I
would make it finger puppets then I can
do more than two people at once with
finger puppets foreign
okay it's um
one and a half hours to go until
midnight so I will read some super chats
thank you guys for
um Coming hope you guys enjoyed the
little fake concert
um I uh
uh
I'm hungry
um
by the way yesterday my brother you guys
were like uh poor brother poor brother
freezing outside but turns out he didn't
even like come back on time on to like
for midnight
he came like 40 minutes after midnight
yeah I was like where the hell were you
so it seems like it wasn't that cold
that it would be urgent or so it wasn't
suffering if it was suffering he would
have been like waiting in front of the
door
so
yeah you guys you guys don't have to
worry so much for my brother
he'll survive it let's move to my other
office
oh
[Music]
it's a group picture
so sweet okay let me put the chat to
where it belongs and then let me turn on
some bgm
[Music]
um
I need more than two hands man to make
my dreams come true
bro tell yourself what I was thinking
just jokingly thinking that I could ask
my brother for help but he doesn't have
the same artistic and yeah artistic in a
creative sense that I do in terms of
like movement and how I want the puppets
to move you know
okay
he wouldn't get it he would not get it
I said a date with Canada Senpai for uh
going karaoke together and she just
wrote to me I'm so excited
too so excited oh my God
oh my God so excited
he didn't want to stick his hands
through his stinky socks his hands into
my stinky socks but if they're fresh
socks I bought them just for his purpose
I didn't even use old socks they're all
fresh have you noticed how they are all
the same color and length yeah
yo guys why are you still here
why are you guys still here
I'm gonna read some potatoes and kfp I
love you by the way did you know that I
need to tell you I love you
Holo laser help me out here where are we
continuing to read
[Music]
I don't think I ever had them in my chat
before what happened
why did they come here
I mean they're always welcome
but
That's So Random that's so Random
let's just stayed for a while
foreign
like once in a lifetime really like
legendary and something for the history
books kind of concert so of course of
course you wouldn't want to miss it
makes sense yeah
don't worry about these puppets has
traveled
everyone knows about them
yeah it was the first time you guys got
to see uh Council race in 3D so
maybe maybe
some people missed it then they have to
watch it because it's important it's the
most important day in a YouTuber life is
a free debut free debut yeah yeah
you couldn't miss it I spoiled her debut
yeah good question good question oh
hmm
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] help me I don't hear it
holy oh my cute
um earworm was replaced with Holy Holy
Night
Holy Holy
night
shy Christmas
oh there it is oh but you guys don't do
it
oh there it is what the [\h__\h] it wasn't
that already just had to reset it
I think this speed gem is fitting
or what we just did loud okay
[Music]
it captures the spirit
my throat hurts man also by the way I
said my advice yesterday I said my flag
on this um uh colorless but I think it's
important to say that it's not colorless
after all I missed it I mistook it it's
still like yellow green
am I still sick does that mean I'm still
sick
I still have yellow green uh flag them
and like
yesterday during the stream I had so
much of it coming out right and then
today today no when I was sleeping I was
trying to sleep so much man it's so
disgusting and annoying
it means I'm almost to you
RGB flag them
means your groceries I [\h__\h] up no
thank you
[Music]
might take a while final cleanup did you
finish the full set yeah I did I mean
the the antibiotics I did finish all of
it I did I did but it does the colored
flag gum I say that light is on Purpose
By the way does it come from the sinus
infection or does it come from the
bronchitis or from the laryngitis or can
you not know
I wonder from which one it comes from
it's probably just clearing out yeah I
mean I definitely have like times where
it's worse when times where it's better
right now it's better because it's just
overall like really dry right now
sinus at first
from the sinus infection
so maybe I still have a little bit of a
sinus infection or it's just the remain
reminders why does it not just go down
my stomach
why does it stay in my throat it's so
annoying it's been like two weeks man
okay maybe more like one and a half ever
since that part started
good morning from Japan Ohio
[Music]
you can swallow it well I sometimes I
try to like when I feel some things
there in my throat I try to swallow it
down but at the same time I'm I don't
know I know this it just doesn't really
go down on it and and it just makes me
cough so yeah
foreign
[Music]
it just floats in your throat yeah it's
so weird like why does it not go down
like with all the liquid I drink or all
the food I
tell me that the food goes down but the
flag of Bones why it's not sticky it's
not like glue
so weird
this new fruit not in your esophagus
what is that
wait that's different wait
then why am I drinking water
[Music]
the stuff for my my flag of my mucus and
all that is
is it different pipe
it's all connected
[Music]
oh yeah I mean I know there's one for
breathing and one for eating
I think I knew that but
[Music]
like a cough syrup makes no sense though
because obviously the cough syrup goes
down your eating pipe
but if the flag gum and all that is in
the other pipe and that's what makes me
cough and all that
that makes no sense
[Laughter]
you guys feel you guys are feeling hella
smart again aren't y'all
[Music]
uh I actually many years ago not not
that many though that's the concerning
thing maybe like
maybe tend to
15 years ago
I had a really late realization about
some other different
pipes and holes
but I'm not gonna get into them
[Music]
can't talk about those
you won't get it you wouldn't get it
oh
what's that word
[Music]
oh yeah
[Laughter]
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no stop stop oh no we can't go there
we can't go there
number
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah okay yeah I'll say I'll say yes to
uh
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
I learned that two years ago and I'm
nearly 40. let's go
thank you thank you
I learned it before I was 40.
I've played with socks
oh
oh there's so many things you can do
with sock puppet theater well I could do
like um the birds and the bees or
flowers on the bees
explanation with sock okay maybe not
um
I wanna look into sock puppets with
hands though
foreign
I wonder how you do that I was trying a
little bit today to use uh my phone my
phone to give it a little bit more
emotion but I don't know you probably
know this but I I sometimes I have a
hard time to
um
like
uh go with the ribbon like
um
but then move the mouth in a different
Rhythm AKA like the body should move by
the rhythm of the song and the mouth
should move by the rhythm of what
they're singing you know what I mean
that's so difficult especially even more
difficult with two so that's
two hands trying to do the ribbon with
the
for the song and then especially if they
sing Different lyrics and two that's
three different rhythms and I have to
uh mimic
um
you need like a Drama brain yeah I'm
sure drummers can do that right yeah
yeah I could say with the with their
feet they do like a beat right and then
with their hands they do something else
up there and then there's even drummers
who sing while they drum right holy [\h__\h]
they're multitasking I can't do that
it's so difficult oh my God
it's crazy
foreign
[Music]
okay okay
um
May could you please tell me could you
please help me out guys also does anyone
else's Discord like have um when you
open it
on the on the top left
you know where the DMS are
and one thingy a red circle with a one
in it as if you have a DM but I have no
DMS light Aspire okay thank you
because I have no dances I checked like
what the [\h__\h] what what is it it's
coming it's killing me it's [\h__\h] for
me too oh is it a bug
there's a friend no no I have no friend
requests I don't see anything like once
I click it
no it leads me to my DMs but I don't see
anything there
foreign
no DM that I missed
this is annoying me wait maybe I can do
right click and then no that doesn't
work
message request
[Music]
why would you see message requests
Nitro oh
maybe
maybe that's it
oh
um I need something here
I don't know I'll check later thanks
though
yeah my Nitro my nature ran out
Discord where are you when I need you
this chord used to come to my chat I
haven't seen them in a while neat
Discord Discord
this card I'll call this corn
there's a new message request feature
they're working on it may be a bug
related to that oh
thank you
I have freebie doko
this chord changed oh [\h__\h] has anyone
seen this chord in other chats reported
to me
frantically switching accounts
they were in the clubhouse
you saw it
in my recent Clubhouse stream
s
you sure
Dragon Days
yeah they wear oh well that's so recent
I didn't know this
hey thank you Discord son
that was around the same time
thank you
as now I could be they could be a
mongoose
[Music]
they really like YouTubers home
funny
okay uh slightest fire did you guys say
slightest fire
yeah yeah okay
oh my neck
[Music]
foreign
but I couldn't I think that will be one
of the streams I can do in Japan
with my gaming laptops slaying Aspire
should be no problem
so we'll attempt that again in Japan
[Music]
hopefully next time
trim trim my deck
you heard right I said deck
[Laughter]
I said back
[Music]
I said that
back
okay
[Music]
oh for the pinky okay little girls
episode two thoughts Roy has at the
rapid Shields and Paris is Minto
that time
back then you know it really made me sad
I was such a mean [\h__\h] back then
Tristan teases Roar with Mary yeah yeah
that that's one of those cases where I
feel like it just proves that I think I
mentioned this in my stream before and
you guys were like no that's natural but
this is so true
um when when boys like a girl they often
just he's the girl and Bully the girl
so they don't know how else to um
tell their feelings you know it's
[\h__\h] lame
yeah it is true it is true I don't do
that well thank God because it's not I
don't like it
[Music]
girls wanna chill yeah
no don't think that much
[Music]
when girls like someone then they talk
to the other girls and they're like hey
oh my God you know what foods responded
the other day he looked at me in the
middle of biology class and I I look
back at him and then he just looked away
with five minutes later he looked at me
again can you believe it he's going on
oh my God it's so cute you two are
totally made for each other you know you
were born
and then and then and then she'll be
like oh can you can you maybe your good
terms with Tristan right can you make me
like ask him if there's any girl he
likes but don't don't tell him that I
wanted to know and of course yeah okay
no problem
yeah
oh I didn't see that in the movie
oh this is reality
I wish Tristan would look at me too
get you someone who looks at you like
Tristan does
and then the other girl goes
[Music]
any girls here in class more and then
he's like no
or more like oh no because he's still
young
and then she's like oh [\h__\h] what do I
say to my friend oh
well he's naive he just doesn't know it
goes back to friend
uh Tristan totally likes you oh my God
I'm so happy okay okay all right so
there's a lot of us love with her oh wow
oh I think I did that in elementary
school I think that's real
so girl writes Anonymous love letter
[Music]
I think you're really really awesome
you're really cool I like I like the the
hats that you wear sometimes and like I
like how you always have chewing gum
with you and one time I
um I when I saw you spit the chewing gum
into the trash can I reached into the
trash can to
get it back I hope you don't think I'm
weird it's just you know I wish I wish
you would notice me but for now I'll be
a secret admirer I love you
yeah written with a sparkly pen a
sparkly pink pen
[Music]
and then she would put it into the
locker
on the launcher stands Locker
and then on another day
yeah yeah another day another day she
would after Tristan left the class
she would
write something with a permanent marker
on his school table
Yeah Yeah
you're right I
traced them plus and she would write her
name and then she would
uh like Scribble over her name
[Music]
so that you can't read it anymore on
purpose though
yeah and another day and another day she
would
um before she would come early to school
to class and she would write on the
chalkboard
um you know that umbrella thing with the
name initials or so
and she would write T and her own name
underneath right and then everybody
would come into class and they're like
funny
funny well who did it hey
sitting on a tree
or whatever
and then and then Tristan would be like
who the [\h__\h] did that and the girl would
be one yeah I wonder who her man Tristan
that's only sucks right yeah but you
know
now I get to talk to you
[Laughter]
swings maybe I I might have written a
Anonymous Love Letter before maybe but
I'm just making up a scenario in my head
I really am a bullet no it's not
bullying
that's love
[Music]
I'm just telling you what girls do in
like Elementary School
or yeah Junior High I don't think they
do that much anymore but maybe in the
first year of junior high or so
when they like someone well we're all
way past that age anyway let me go back
to my super chance
[Music]
sometimes the girl just punches you on
your shoulder no it's the other way
around
you're in an all-boy School in Middle
School dear
[Music]
please take your pills I already took
all my antibiotics
I already did
you want me to overdose
[Music]
a girl likes to punch my shoulder
I'll punch her
I should be the only one punching your
shoulder I'll punch her tell me her name
and her address
foreign
[Music]
coffee without her asking sweet no need
to comment just and join us yours oh but
I didn't I did do a big comment on it
but yeah it looks the best look I think
because everyone's favorite character
person he's so cool but he will
eventually really test your patience I
think as a fan as a viewer because like
he's he's like the the dump protagonist
kind of well he's a side character but
he still look kind of a dumb protagonist
because he just doesn't get it
but Lorelei also doesn't get it they
both don't get it anyway
thank you for two pinkies it's been over
two years damn we're getting old chat
and yet here we are listening to Tanger
talk and scream on a daily basis
I don't scream on a daily basis
don't yeah
it gets hard to remember everything but
I still don't want to miss what happens
next so true also like they'll remember
[\h__\h] I totally feel that it's tough It's
sad
you're quite the Entertainer boss the
other day you asked me where is the love
Sanji but I think it's their question
mark my definition of love is too
complex yeah
anyways I wish you all the best kfp and
safe travels bus
let's do that I don't remember that
[Music]
is the love there
it just ain't the same
[Music]
anyway uh thank you
a kiss for you
thank you for being part of it okay for
two years are my throat has been feeling
itchy
thank you
for your support for such a long time I
don't doubt you love you know what
you've been here for two years I
shouldn't be doubting Your Love ever
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you as always
Optimus Prime dinosaurs
minor 49 or 220 201 thank you
I'm glad I am your favorite
thank you for all the right Super Chat
you both die
oh why man
why was my birthday
I might have wished you happy birthday
on Twitter did I it's the first video I
celebrate with you on kfp I'm so happy I
found you on kfp the first birthday holy
[\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] I've been so stressed with
school so you're at least three right so
stressful schools your stream's always
streaming up I don't know I would be
doing as much art as I do without your
support beloved Wawa
[Music]
I'm really happy to have you Dr mom
you're like you know so OG and
you're the creator of the timkins
of so many champions
I really appreciate you helping me out
with a lot of things thank you for being
such a great person I hope you stay that
way as you should because you're lovely
the Way You Are
um I don't deserve you
happy happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday in
your show happy birth for all your
timkins that you've created too happy
birth to you
[Music]
oh sorry it hurts and her pants too
thank you Mom
wish you all the best
um sorry I'm so late
[Music]
yeah the tractors this latest buyers you
gotta learn to play with what game gives
you oh
um if you just hope for things you
already know how to win with you're
going to lose also focus on
filling out your deck
good gamble detention
out my deck while I keeping it small
I know how to do that I think
[Music]
I think
sip
oh yeah last time that wasn't the issue
I think
what the [\h__\h] what why is it what
what's going on
I shouldn't have given my cough syrup to
my mom just yet
lastly was mostly bad but last time was
mostly bad RNG
it was bad RNG I was just that was
payback for me being too lucky so many
times
laughs
[Music]
it's like when I try to breathe I I
um my my breath gets cut off
so where's the
flag in the breathing tube right okay
then that makes sense that
um
wait but if the flag isn't you guys what
do you guys trying to teach me makes no
sense you guys were saying that it it
doesn't go down with the food and all
that because it's not in the eating tube
but if it's
if it's in my um breathing tube then how
come I can cough it out
[Music]
from my from my from my eating tube
but
whatever whatever
you guys this is the this is a
conspiracy theory anyway there's only
one tube
[Music]
you guys can't manipulate me you can't
Gaslight me into thinking there's two
tubes there there's one tube okay
there's one tube
oh God
a candy in my mouth it doesn't save me
why
come on we have to do this
also thank you taraka again for the nice
pinky uh all slightly Inspire again
please help me then DJ DG DG Nick thank
you
[Music]
foreign
um
I'm worried too you're not the only one
yell mate
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
it's not always like this
I'm having a a moment
[Music]
I can't swallow it just swallow it you
said it's in a breathing tube how could
they swallow it made no sense
which one is it
oh
[Music]
I don't have a spitting Cup right now
I'm spitting it onto tissues
[\h__\h]
yeah I can read super jazz in Japan oh
I can I was gonna do that anyway because
I know I'm not finishing today I was
gonna do it in Japan later on
toddy it's a mixture of lamb sip Honey
whiskey and hot water called a book
that's it
it comes up to the point of connection
between the tubes essentially would go
down the other side into the eating tube
oh
blowing into a straw into a cup of water
creating bubbles can help what
[Music]
what
why would that help
[Music]
yeah bro Tony watched Avatar and really
liked it
I think he said he liked it more than
ever well maybe maybe it was the other
way around
[Music]
but he really liked it
I need to watch it too
[Music]
a-l-l thank you for two pinkies thank
you hey boss I have one games you might
uh find interesting the name is Paul
shonomics oh the game of that game and
the gameplay of the game is very similar
to what you're playing right now I
recommend this game you can go check out
whenever you feel like no pressure I
think I've seen someone else play it
probably there's a bunch of potion games
out there right now
[Music]
what what
ah that one was a cute girl
oh no no one streamed that one actually
I feel like I read the super chat before
that sounds familiar I looked this game
up before
this is not the first time I'm getting
this one recommended I'm having a deja
vu
[Music]
did I read the super chat or did I read
a different one with the same
recommendation
uh potionomics potion nomics yeah
it doesn't quite narrow it though
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] potion
um
[Music]
actually I was really happy about it
seems that I don't know maybe they
changed it back again but it seems that
all the myths found discords
change their like
server icon to the sock puppets
maybe they already changed the bug
I heard they did
you know that
that touched me that made me so happy
[Music]
Kanto showed me
chronium what no way oh wait that makes
me so happy
that's so sweet
that is so sweet
thank you guys
[Music]
now the red one
yeah I know good as dead it has to be
car now
gouda is in an emergency uh in the
emergency room being operated on right
now and they're trying to fix her her
spine
and I am Sauron
don't forget to take your gift to Japan
Kiana oh my God
you're so sweet for trying to remind me
you mean the the iron beat
I also bought a lot of um
souvenir snacks uh to give out because
I'm gonna meet so many members for the
first time so many people for the first
time so yeah I I this time I was like
I'm not gonna buy it at the airport it's
gonna be so expensive
mm-hmm
not Mozart because I thought you know I
I brought some people Mozart's balls
before and some people liked them but I
think in general it's not that not the
tastiest thing
so I'm going with manner Wafers Manor
waffles this time
because they're they're not like
like worlds changing but
I don't think you would like anyone
would dislike them
they were like basic and yeah
they're not crazy sweet so
um
[Music]
I don't think anyone can have a problem
with those
um
[Music]
I know people who don't like them when I
when I was younger I didn't like them
much either just because they were not
sweet enough for me I wanted sweeter
things with more chocolate but nowadays
I appreciate them
and there's Simplicity I Like It Anyway
where was I
oh sorry boss ignore the last Super
Channel I fell asleep so I didn't see it
I was dumb chicken it's awkward I need
to change the question do you know uh do
you know what I got nothing I'm ready
put me on the menu
[Music]
is that why
hmm
so confused it's okay a-l-l
a
it's okay
maybe that's why I feel like I heard it
twice
missing a little bit of context but I
think I understand thank you thank you
for the two pinkies though which makes
the red one
[Music]
thank you thank you you sent it twice
oopsie oops oops
um I I don't know if I will play
potionomics
um what let's
I thought it looks cute
maybe privately
[Music]
and like I see some screenshots from
like
um not the dialogue screenshots but like
when she's in some kind of room
that graphic is so cute
the style the Arts Direction
noise good stuff
I'm gonna skip those sneeze chats thank
you though
for the pinky Google refunded my stadia
Founders
I read this before
not tell me about I read this one live
oh okay okay I'm not going crazy then
thank God I thought I was going crazy
[Music]
time Loop okay I'll skip that one then
thanks for the pinky
deja vu
what's onions
L again or a-l-l that question again for
the pinky you know what I changed my
mind don't put me on the menu I'm just a
fat chicken I'm not ready for this oh
God I can already Imagine The Taste it's
delicious and juicy sounds good put me
back on the menu
[Music]
you can't decide huh is this your is
this your final answer
hey it's my final answer the other day I
I watched um
the first time someone got the million
and who wants to be the millionaire uh I
watched that for the first time
I was actually like really surprised how
a lot of the questions even the ones
that were worth more money
um
we're actually pretty easy I mean of
course in between there were questions
again where I didn't know the answer but
then there were questions again where I
didn't know the answer
and I think it's just because
I I I'm assuming that nowadays questions
are more difficult
because nowadays there's so much more so
many more opportunities or like ways of
getting smart and getting your
information
hmm
and like back then when he won the first
million
it was like well maybe there was already
internet but
um apparently Google back then wasn't
the way it was now you like nowadays if
you type a question into Google
you can't actually a straight answer
right you get those little questions and
then the answers to it and so on
it's really easy to find an answer to
your question
but back then it wasn't that easy and
people got their knowledge mostly just
from having good general knowledge
by going to school and traveling or
whatever I don't know
[Music]
so I would say that maybe that's the
reason why back then the questions were
a bit easier
[Music]
there's way more like materials
now
oh yeah library library is back then you
had to go to libraries read books
so those few questions that are meant to
destroy your run while easier ones
attract the competition oh
oh and I still so many easy questions in
between nowadays
I haven't watched a recent one
so Kiwa are you ready to be a
millionaire when I was younger
um I used to watch that show a lot we
have it in in Germany and Austria too
two different ones actually I think
and I used to watch that myself a lot
when I was younger
and I was thinking when I get older I
want to be on this show
and I want to become a millionaire
when I have to I have to I have to learn
many things
before that because now I don't know a
single answer to any of these questions
I'm so stupid I was like so fascinated
how
could they know so many things
oh
[Music]
but for me back then
as a child of course I I was I would
have been fine with not winning the
million I would have been fine with just
winning the 5 000 or so yeah
[Music]
I was like
when I go there and make the big money
AKA 5 000 bucks
I mean even as an adult 5 000 bucks
pocket money can help you out in a lot
of situations right
um even a thousand
no
[Music]
of course
yeah but as a child the dimensions were
so different
[Music]
you know a lot of people don't have even
only before whole life I didn't have
um
even close to a thousand in my savings
maybe maybe not even 500 euro in savings
constantly
constantly on the grind
um
constantly struggling constantly around
zero
[Music]
let's say things what's that
yeah
thank God I joined whole life a man
hey what was that
BT tour Duncan well I don't know how I'm
supposed to read that but happy belated
birthday thank you soon for being
lovely lovely chicken
next one is Google
[Music]
sorry
I was out with my brother a little bit
today and
uh
I tried to hold back but there was a
moment where I had to spit something out
and
I tried to hold her back but then I I am
I did I did it somewhere where it would
be acceptable and then
[Music]
I said I'm sorry to my brother and he
said you're disgusting that's what I
know
[Music]
I know
I know I don't want to do it either
[Music]
thank you thank you soon
for the red super chat with no text why
what are you thinking what does this
mean what does this Super Chat mean
thank you thank you thank you for the
support it's really late that I reply to
it I don't know if you're gonna see it
well thank you thank you I appreciate it
I hope you don't get sick from my kiss
open to interpretation
okay I interpret it as kiwawa I love you
so much
you are the light in my life every day I
wake up I look forward to your streams
please be healthy and happy and I will
take you as an inspiration uh to become
just like you
wow I wish you all the best wow that's
that's so sweet to hear that thank you
for your sweet and kind words
well said well said
[Music]
not your mind reader
I know thanks for the pinky
thank you for showing me this game Boss
I've been extremely addicted to it oh
really
by the way have you ever heard of enter
the gungeon is that a typo
or dead cells those are my two favorite
roguelikes I would die of Happiness if
you ever decide to try them on the
stream I've never heard of them no
it is gunjan
why what is that supposed to mean
that looks cute
[Music]
oh it's with guns oh
it looks cute and the other one the
other one was dead cells
oh that one is um like a side scroller
what do you call them what do you call
these no no not side scroll uh oh this
is a roguelike combined with
like the metroidvania yeah it's it's a
roguelike metroidvania oh [\h__\h] that's
sick
that's crazy
that's crazy that's a crazy combination
[Music]
you know what my brother's favorite
roguelike we talked about it today
uh is what's it called again
Isaac Newton just kidding I said
something Binding of Isaac
[Music]
never played that one either
yeah but he was talking about how much
he loves it
yeah yeah I know I know I've heard of
that one I know that one
is
only Oishi did you know how much we
appreciate you how we always get hype
when it's wild time how amazing you are
for just being you what I want to say
once again is we love you thank you for
making our days always so special what
happened bro Pro
what made you say these things I'm so
sweet
Mamma Mia
[Music]
thank you for the sweet words
am I really a one and only ocean was
this before you met Ophelia
because
[Music]
before
thank you
you're not the only one though I've been
seeing
I don't know why it's on my timeline but
sometimes I see some kfp posting
screenshots and and and like
pawning over Ophelia in their tweets
mm-hmm
no and I'm like hmm
sad they don't fall over me like this
anymore
I guess the honeymoon face is over
um
[Music]
fine whatever not that I care
I don't I don't I don't care
I don't care I don't feel replaced
whatsoever
and so following you all the time
[Music]
yeah yeah make excuses sure sure I'll
follow you forever
[Music]
froggy lava is the only Aussie
I will accept that one
[Music]
um
thank you soon
until you're at least
I am let's see
thank you there we go
thank you yo I finished these Super Chat
it wasn't that much why did it take me
so long
I had a coughing fit in between
that might be a reason
okay okay oh
I can finish quickly
this one
if some of you gotten Chihuahua
encounter side
have you guys been trying to get me
still doing my missions oh yeah I
already takes a long time sorry to
everyone who hasn't gotten me
I'm sorry
[Music]
I bought it thank you wow I got you
yesterday oh
my God I'm a free skin yo I would be
happy about that I would be delighted
thank God it was one of you two oh you
also got a man
but your skin just gotta get yelled yeah
for that you have time though right so
no stress at least you have the skin now
and with Yuna she will come to you
eventually
I got you as a Christmas gift to myself
you know it's been like I've been
looking at like how people have been
arranging their uh
like main screens
with all kinds of small Chihuahuas and
other members small versions there's so
many different ones it's so cute
it's so cute the small ones are so cute
they have so many funny emotions
[Music]
one
where the the chickens go down uh like
some kind of portal
that one's so cute vacuum sucking in the
chickens consuming them
there that's the rarest one oh
I didn't know that
[Music]
Chihuahua small Jazz Jack's art never
misses yeah right chest X art style is
so Charming so cute it's adorable
ah there's a QR one at first I don't
remember that one anymore
the motion of it just
nothing special it's just a just like
whatever
[Music]
an email and birthday merch got
delivered let's go
ah it's a cat here's one
it's a motion oh no
[Music]
creative birthday
um
I hope you're feeling better by now
Andres
and clothes donkey shouldn't be factions
[Music]
done Danny with the funny
oh that's right before I got sick
oh hey
Mario Kart guys
[Music]
uh where's that thumbnail
can I save it somewhere else
I will put
I will put this one up
and and it's it's a placeholder at least
it's Mario Kart related
I don't want to go looking for it now
[Music]
turned out good didn't they
all thumbnails relate to the party you
gotta watch The Vine
tickets
wait I didn't read these right I didn't
read these yet did I I feel like in some
stream I I read something but maybe I
didn't maybe I'm imagining I didn't okay
[Music]
twins varying twins oh yeah that's funny
that's so cool I'm kind of cringy at the
same time it was funny though it was
nice seeing Rory get her Grandpa to open
up over golf that was cute Emily points
out that Lorelei is controlling like her
oh do we share any personality traits
with Mama Dori
um yes
I probably do stubbornness would be the
most apparent one I think
my mom is incredibly stubborn
um and I might be so too but I want to
say that my mom is way more stubborn
than I am though
I think I have to say she's more
stubborn than I am
[Music]
herself
um
my mom has been like freezing her butt
off
in her house in the middle of nowhere
because it has no like proper heating
she has one oven and you know
there's no central heating or whatever
she's been freezing her butt off
it's been really really bad
and I offered like
you know she was like fantasized
fantasizing we were thinking about going
to a Sicily over the winter
[Music]
um just wanting to be somewhere else so
I offered that she could just stay in my
place while I was gone I have enough
rooms my mom's my brother's gonna be
here but she can be there too
sit down
stubborn
[Music]
I said though if she changes her mind
she's always welcome she can always be
here
I'm not here anyway so
no my place is not in Sicily but it's
warm it's warm and I have Central
Heating
and you don't have to worry about how
much you eat because I'm I'm paying it
and it's a nice apartment close the
apartment
well
for that I said just do it do it do it
you should do it maybe she'll change her
mind eventually
[Music]
but I think um we might have gotten a
little bit better recently in terms of
coldness just a little bit a tiny bit is
still cold as [\h__\h] my brother stayed
with her a couple days before he came
over for Christmas
[Music]
um and he told me he's been like wearing
his
like like several layers of clothes and
like a military jacket or whatever you
know like the really warm ones that you
get for going to the military or
whatever I don't know
um yeah [\h__\h] ton of layers of clothes
and still freezing
[Music]
and every time you want to go to the
bathroom
that room is not heated at all it
doesn't reach that room so it's like you
in the freaking Antarctica when you go
over to the bathroom
and sit on the toilet seat
[Music]
But Mommy if you're listening to this
you're welcome to stay at my place while
I'm gone
yeah get cozy cuddle with my ketokatos
that is the only condition you have to
cuddle with my ketokatos
oh was I ah looking for the top
functions
thank you pbnk thank you for the rest of
the chat thank you soon
in exchange for a little Health a lot of
time and mental damage and giving up
watching Canada's stream
I'm finally able to graduate graduate
from University yeah I didn't see you
for a while is that what you were doing
I'm free and going to take back some of
what I've lost first of all I collect
some Kiara neum as possible
are you back
congratulations on graduating from
University that was surely important so
I am not blaming you or whatsoever but
I'm happy you're back hopefully I'll see
a lot of you
you better be around
thank you so much and so much
congratulations welcome back
[Music]
foreign
which one which part is congratulations
[Music]
thanks for the pinky yeah today is my
birthday oh very happy to spend it with
y'all love kfp so much and everything is
always so much fun and coffee hope you
can guess first place today
I didn't but I think did I get second
Maybe
I wasn't so bad on that day I think
surprisingly I think that's second yo
that's basically first in my books
that's first in my books if I'm up
against you guys
yo that's first that's a win that's a
huge win for me
yeah yeah yeah second against nosaki
basically first exactly
I got first impact for the
impersonations uh
foreign
[Music]
you enjoyed seeing that didn't you
happy belated birthday anyway I'm on
number congratulations
it's been a while but I hope you had a
lovely birthday hope you're not feeling
too old
no matter how old you are you gotta
embrace the youth in your heart yeah
enjoy life every day
thanks for your support game 8 9 10
Danke Schoen Ricky Tunes Danke Schoen
MDB thank you for the rest of the chat
hi thank you I've been watching you for
two years now a year ago I joined the
membership when you debited your ball
gown ah here's looking forward to
another year of seeing the Phoenix sword
hi oh the the fancy dress you mean the
party dress
thank you very much for joining
membership and supporting me for such a
long time I'm glad to still have you
around
I'm glad you didn't get sick of me yet
ironically I'm sick
I didn't mean it like that though hey
thank you thank you thank you I hope you
will continue supporting me I'll be
doing my best I'm trying I'm always
trying my best
yeah
thank you so much MDB
[Music]
um
MK thank you for the pinky based
smoothie oh wonder what's movie dude
hmm something something bad I'm sure
evil smoothie
thank you for supporting smoothie though
she's a sweetie I love her so much
Joker oh one nine five thank you for the
pinky I think yesterday has been two
years since I've joined membership oh
and tomorrow is my birthday oh that's
what I got sick
bad timing I love being here and I'm not
listening to you talk about everything
keeping you and don't stop going Your
Own Way joke are you here probably not
huh
thank you for two years of membership
for supporting me for so long I
like
thank you I'm so sorry it took me so
long I got sick on your birthday I hope
you're healthy though
hope you had a lovely birthday I'm sorry
I couldn't stream during it
but I hope you used that time that you
had wisely to spend with friends or
family
um
and get lots of well wishes for your
birthday and presents
in any case
you know sickness sucks it really
[\h__\h] does please stay healthy yo we
get older and with that we just get
sicker ever [\h__\h] die
another bone breaks well you guys saying
that's not normal
ah happy villain a birthday
congratulations
[Music]
if you don't mind
please
stay the way you are and stay here with
kfb
Mrs donkey show in the game recruiting
and see our Trooper Scout Danke Schoen
Islamic fellow then the shinstevic
fellow again thank you what you watch
the l-o-tr watch along now so late but
thank you
glad you liked it
is
[Music]
oh that's a weird amount one for free
143 dollars why High attention it was my
birthday yesterday so I just wanted to
say thanks for another great year of
caffeine your 3D performance this year
were absolutely incredible here's to
many more yes I hope so I hope so
I was finally able to do a 3D birthday
and stuff like that so it was a lot of
work
a lot of work too
learned so many choreos and record it
all in a scuffed situation about I hope
next year I can do more 3D but without
all that stuff
let's hope for the best and
um maybe you will be there
during all of it Chief masamune I'm
counting on you
you'll be there right
location for your support and happy
belated birthday to you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for supporting me
I hope on your birthday
[Music]
you were treated really well because you
deserve it you do yes you do
Kevin C thank you for the pinky hey girl
when I was younger I went on a skiing
holiday to Austria it was amazing we
arrived at night and in the morning when
we woke up there was snow everywhere it
was beautiful oh
that I indeed can't imagine it would be
nice Austria was amazing really enjoyed
skiing oh is that like did you learn
skiing there or where are you already
able to ski before I wonder because
I'm surprised if you were if you learned
it just then and I'm surprised you had
this really good memory and experience
of it because
I don't know I don't know I don't have
good memories of relearning skiing
but skiing itself once you have it down
is so much fun it's so incredible such a
great feeling I hope you come back
castria to go skiing again sometime in
our beautiful mountains you're always
welcome
um
thanks for sharing that with me
I know
I don't know
[Music]
be cool
cotton essential
money
um
[Music]
Europe
foreign
[Music]
exactly for a Japanese fella and telling
him that
I was just happy to know what I had from
the doctor because you know like for all
the other issues that I have where I
don't know what it is
just [\h__\h] sucks
not not having like an answer and
therefore also not knowing how to treat
it it's demoralizing maybe that's
feel
like
I don't know
I feel like
it's like gaslighting yourself
if you go to the [\h__\h] ton of doctors and
they all can't fix you they all can't
tell you what the [\h__\h] problem is
then
start questioning yourself
[Music]
maybe this is normal
maybe this state of my body is normal
[Music]
two years before they even believed she
felt the pain she said she did
you should at least believe it you need
to chat thank you soon
thank you my thank you secret Scorpio
donation okay
and foreign
[Music]
okay okay
that stream with a different thumbnail
is finished
[Music]
hey I I read like super chats from like
three or four streams
wait a Super Chat is here it's been so
long you guys don't remember your super
chats
right down
write it down where's your receipts
stop there yeah I guess it's almost
midnight so I will do that
[Music]
um
hey I'm so busy I'm so nervous I'm so
busy I'm so nervous
I've read more
soup I got some more time
um
yeah
I'll try to stream again soon
soon
[Music]
we've been this week of course this
weekend is
oh the end of 2022.
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I hate that
[Music]
I'm gonna be honest guys things that I
was trying to work on
around the end of 2022
a lot of it got like delayed and like
I wasn't able to do as much as I wanted
in
like the very end of 2022 so
I gotta work hard in 2023 that's for
sure
but
um
I don't know
there's so much I want to do and oh
I feel like it's so difficult
to push for it over and over and over
again
when I I am I can't do so many things at
once alone
oh man oh well let's try our best in
[Music]
you guys are sweet I love you guys thank
you thank you thank you
[Music]
you sending a Happy New Year's super
chat now
I'm probably not gonna read that until
2023 maybe possibly
so good call on that one
Paul
[Music]
if there's anything we can help please
tell us you guys are helping just by
being here in my streams really
just by
being here
not leaving me
okay guys and in German we say avidazine
[Music]
wish me luck
yeah hope you like the song public
stream it wasn't as good as I wanted to
be but I hope it was fun nonetheless for
you guys
somebody
[Music]
yeah tomorrow
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]