e
[Music]
[Applause]
n
pap
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
PA
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
K
KY
key yeah
yeah you get it you know
it they get
it welcome to wa play rage game
for first time nah I mean the egg game
for
example definitely that was a rage game
I've played rage games before I haven't
played uh this one and I haven't played
um the the
prequel so to
say uh-huh I am not as experienced in
this category as others
perhaps is there a bgm they they make
like comments right or or is that only
in the in the other
one I should I bring some bgm with
[Music]
me no commentary oh oh that's so sad I
want to
be roasted or
told things about daily life that
inspire
me it's made by a different guy what
they're not from the same
people it literally looks like a
successor we can help with that I am the
commentary okay um I brought some
tangents with me so that works
okay okay do we need bgm then maybe like
a
light not very intrusive
[Music]
bgm I'll I'll find
something anti-rage
bgm let's
see
ah what do we got
what can I offer what can I
sacrifice
my my audio wants to be mean to
me
see I knew it oh this is so
cute ah wait I just realized oh wow
that's loud the water
the water is really
loud everything's
loud a little
bit still kind of loud but okay that's
fine what's up with the a audio I don't
freaking
know oh yeah
oh wait that might be
good for
[Music]
now you can work out not to this right
to a different one
H you're kind of low volume me all this
is the most I can go also it's just cuz
I was looking away from the microphone
definely definitely loud audio wait you
were going into a really emotional
Direction and this this is why you are
end up at why okay I like this piano for
now it's it's sophisticated so how does
this work I can dance no no no no this
way what if the where the game drops you
off in the beginning is not really where
you want to start off at what if it's
like somewhere else what if there's like
a secret best starting
point oh I oh I get it this is how you
swim oh right there seems to be
nothing oh
or oh there is something can I can I
clamp here how does clamping even work I
grab right okay no we
cannot I it seems like I cannot hold on
to awkward
swimming it was a nice spot but I uh
seem to not be able to hold on to
it no I have I have
absolutely perfected my swimming skills
over the last
summer let me check this side just in
case no okay
well I thought that might be a thing
that there's more points to stop uh
start
yeah okay fine I will not break the meta
or be the meta I will do this okay how
does this work how do
you
what tell me how does this
[Music]
work left-handed Mouse oh I I I do I am
left-handed but use the Mouse as a
right-handed wait so what you just click
but how do I get the second hand wait
what oh wait a ah pull up with W or
space q and e or Mouse ah ah is it like
aha
oh oh God I need to get used to
this so left
hand right hand let go of left hand yeah
I need to I need to embody this I need
to lock
in and then hold on and then pull up and
then let go of the other hand and then
hold on and then pull up and then left
hand and then pull up and then right
hand and then pull up and then left hand
yeah okay now we got it oh why is he so
[\h__\h] wobbly
actually impressive how he has so much
body strength and then we got to go to
the right side maybe I should
have wait we shall proceed from from
here yeah pull up oh no wait oh God his
fingers must be so [\h__\h] from climbing
like
this I'm falling down
already yeah I got it okay sometimes you
got to use the momentum
right unlimited grip strength holy [\h__\h]
yo his nails are probably it's
glitchy glitchy in German we say
glitchy what was I going to say yeah
probably has like no
Nails oh but okay this can't be so
difficult
like you can already tell like
oh oh no hold that's where you got to
hold on to can can you perhaps stand on
this instead of grabbing onto it because
that would do us all a favor how are you
supposed to get up there that's
impossible
no I'm already at the top of this
mountain so he can't feel his ah did he
like did he get like par paralyzed or
something this is really just a matter
of uh accidentally letting go I
think
yeah I don't know how that works but
sure okay may just permanently pressing
space is fine that's what I'm doing now
okay it seems like you kind of have to
go over there that's why they prepared
the Rocks over
there where where did all these come
from I want to see a screenshot of the
whole Mountain zoomed out this is
glitchy I don't I cannot hold on to
this I want to see how this mountain is
structured oh look at
that that's okay that's exactly what I
wanted I kind of wanted to slide down
but that happened way faster than I
thought it
would
yeah oh [\h__\h] I don't think you want to
see that why not is it going to break my
spirit
no no not that
one no no no no no no
no yeah that looks good do we want to go
to the
[Music]
stone no not
mukashi I want to prove the game game
wrong
no it's difficult to go like in between
like when I want to only go to like his
elbow
[Music]
height cuz I want to go to the corner
but also I want to hold on to it with my
left
hand yeah okay he eventually slides down
to hold on to that that's that's fine
that's
[Music]
nice easy
grasp but okay
[Music]
uh I don't like this
sound
[Music]
yeah can't make it guys I cannot make it
and then I keep on slipping down maybe
you got to be fast here maybe you got to
believe in the slippery one for a moment
and then just to quickly grab with the
other
arm oh
oh never
mind didn't work I'm not sure what I was
doing what the heck my
reaction
same no no no but okay like even when
it's slippery it seems like
seems like he can get a grip uh when he
has both hands on
it but then you want to let go to grab
onto the next thing
so you saying ah [\h__\h] right them up
there we got to go to the right side but
why did this I'm obviously that is like
the only
choice that was given to me
see how fast I
am all right this is
glitchy just going to keep on saying
that cuz today my German brain seems to
be very
strong German
brain on the
uprise where else can I
go this
feels I have like a lot of grip in my in
my in my ah
in my fingers this this normal when
playing this game that you get so that
was on purpose guys caught up in in the
grip in your fingers okay what do I do
we're just going
to repeat everything
ah ha
Swing Swing little man yeah oh God I'm
going to get muscle pain in my fingers
let's go
swing to
win swing to
win yeah that's why I wanted to go thank
you wait wasn't I here before already
okay how do we how do
[Music]
I
no how do I get up there or is left is
there something left
[Music]
oh I don't know what the [\h__\h] I'm
doing come
on I'm so he's but thinking of his
fingernails kills me
[Music]
there must be something on the left
side oh no there isn't there is nothing
there but you cannot climb on the
slippery slope can
you he has no F in that's what so
[\h__\h] disturbing to me
[Music]
why why do people make these kind of
things
why what kind of fulfillment does this
give to
you go make a proper game go make a game
about
frogs I don't know what I'm
doing some people just like to watch the
world bird
I suppose so you know my
mom my mom she was like when are you
going to play Yakuza again my dear and I
was like wow the day has
come you have I almost had it the day
has come where my mom is
asking for me to play
Yakuza my mom the one who was so so
disturbed by it previously
[Music]
she wants me to stop playing all the
KES and yet I defy her like this why why
why I had it I had
[Music]
it this is so
stupid wait I'm losing grip in my
fingers
no maybe actually using the keyboard
buttons for uh the grab might be
H better okay come on this is the best
position I could possibly be
in yeah no it's like 1 mm
oh let's go rocker s again
with the the
typical questionable Super
Chat what what am I going to do from
this position
huh no no dude you had
[Music]
it [\h__\h]
no she gave up with that Mass Effect she
gave up she mentioned it again but she
joked about it rather than meaning it
seriously she was like ha ha ha Mass
Effect
no but I think she um might like the
idea of me playing The Witcher
um and you may have just watched
Callie's Birthday Countdown stream where
I called in and
[Music]
I bought
cie the complete set of Witcher free
with like DLCs and all that and I bought
it for me too why did I do that cuz I
started uh watching The Witcher cuz I
ran out of things to watch and I was I
was craving something that's like Game
of Thrones you know in terms of like
fantasy oh
no yeah and yeah so toss a coin to you
Witcher a valley was it a valley of
Plenty a valley of Plenty a valley of
plenty
toss a CO to your V whole valley of
plenty of Plenty
yeah too bad the BART is just um a moral
and does cannot support
him for his whole life as we might want
dead I swear to God is this can is this
even
[Music]
[Applause]
possible maybe I need to
believe almost [\h__\h] add it you little
[\h__\h] I swear to God
[Music]
got to take that leap how
what wait how does how does the leap
work are we playing Leap Frog
now how does a leap work
[Music]
no don't I cannot leave no I I ah see
there's a moment there I just he ah he
just needs to be in the right position
there's a moment where his hand does go
there that that was not it
[Music]
can we just buy this guy a cat tree and
call it a
day sorry I have nuts in my Fro I'm
eating cashew nuts I have enlightened I
have found
Enlightenment [\h__\h] hell um so yeah
The
Witcher the tweet that I sent out where
I was extremely frustrated that was in
the middle of episode 7 and I was like I
stopped exactly in the moment [\h__\h] this
man where uh Silla like her
mother like The Witcher is there right
to pick up Silla and her mother shows
him someone who's not
Silla and I thought in this moment they
replaced the actress that's what why I
tweeted that but not only that like even
even though they didn't replace the
actress and it was just like a fake
Cilla on purpose um even even then I
must
[Music]
say oh I got
it never again oh oh you can hold on at
the top yeah
okay and it's just it was just so
confusing and yeah in the end it all
made sense but was that really worth it
to make it so overly confusing did you
really have have to do
that oh
[Music]
no oh is my argument
no
h yeah yeah it it makes sense when you
guys told me that the book that the
first season is based on is uh a
collection of short
stories wait I want to do it with the
other
hand let's go a collection of short
stories that are also kind of like in
the in the book I guess kind of
aligned not randomly but like it's just
a a collection of short stories so yeah
okay but they could have aligned the
timelines at least in the first season
like for the for the live action but
okay then that means I guess why they
maybe didn't do that is
because maybe maybe the reason
is um I'm thinking that it might be
because then we wouldn't have seen Silla
for a long time and I guess they just
really wanted us to see her
uh
beautiful cuteness what do you mean down
what does that mean you little
[\h__\h] I got to go down I guess so cuz
there's nothing else is this a trustfall
situation or
what NY I see
something they think they're so funny
[Music]
yeah
wow [\h__\h] you and right now more
down I thought we were going up I
thought we were trying to get
higher now we're going down that is not
what I
Aspire um I just I just want to
rhyme I just want to rhyme a little bit
and now I find myself in big big
[\h__\h] why am I back here [\h__\h] sucks I
was deceived
Bamboozled so much for going down too
far down yeah you think you're so funny
game cuz that's what you're going to oh
it's not how far you were supposed to go
down no no
no I know should have gone to the right
back what what what what you gone to
down what what too far down what do you
mean shut
up okay so now I'm also already in
season 2 of The Witcher and I know
people say like although did you guys
mean like season 1 big criticism that
it's
too too all over the
place and you get confused they fixed
that in season 2 but people were still
telling me season to still sucks they
may have fixed that but it still sucks
so far I don't think it sucks
I'm I'm at the point
where uh y
Yar she
realizes
she I probably they'll find some
solution for it but she has no magic I
guess Now
spoiler season 2 is okay but season 3 is
bad and I know why you guys told me that
Henry Caville
didn't want to play The Witcher
anymore and they had to switch actors
which is so
sad and also like I've watched like
three episodes of the first season or so
to it took me that long or so to
realize but Henry cavil the actor the
name must sound familiar to to me and
his face should very much look familiar
to me because he played uh Henry in the
tutors which is a show I loved and
watched ages ago and I'm
like wa free free episodes and I'm like
wait the profile or something like a
very specific angle of his face looks
like him let me check if that actually
is him Superman I didn't watch
Superman I don't know him from there I
don't care
yeah Henry played
Henry I don't know him from [\h__\h]
Superman who the [\h__\h] is
Superman sorry to break your little
[Music]
hearts I love
Superman um yeah and I looked it up and
I'm like oh my God how did I I watch so
much of his face in the tutos how did I
not realize this before
oopsie I can get back pretty fast now
look at
me yeah um it's the absolute shitty
lenses I don't that maybe it's because
of the
original eye color but for yenfa
they from what I have
observed for yenfa they colored her ice
in post
production okay for Henry who is so much
on the screen they gave him those shitty
shitty color
contacts these kind of shows maybe it's
from because I'm I'm a lot more critical
about these looks with color color
context there's a lot better color
context that you could have
used um but ah I really don't like the
look you
know that you get with these shitty
lenses they should have done it the way
they did it for yenfa
yenar but I guess they just
couldn't um maybe maybe yennefer's
original eye color was just brighter so
it's easier to edit it in post
production and for
him I think he might have dark brown
eyes by default so coloring those in
post production is difficult do a flip I
don't know about a flip but I don't know
where's the best position to jump off of
lower or higher or middle maybe the
middle first big jump come about it oh
my
God ah what what it might end before
[Music]
that what stupid [\h__\h]
game not worth it not worth losing all
my fingernails over
this good that takiar has some leftover
fingernails that she could share with me
AKA I'm speaking from his point of view
right now
you really can't play this game for so
long because the the the the
grip in your fingers just disappears
after a
while anyway
so that the eyes kind of bothered
me and I I guess people love his grumpy
voice but I kind of
don't it's it's nice in the beginning
but when other people around him all
talk
normally it just starts to get kind of
[\h__\h] weird thank you for the UDA
thank you for the
memberships
UDA that's geralt's voice again sorry
LOL why oh it's accurate to
geralt I
mean what did the book speak to you was
it an audio book
certainly not Henry's voice how the [\h__\h]
did he do that my God he's like that in
the game well in the game it might be
fine but I don't know in the show it's
like it it felt uncomfortable after the
well like why are you talking like this
like even when you're angry and you're
angry angry and trying to scream he's
like get out I mean I said get
out get out that's how you bring emotion
and passion for your voice
voice nah I think um surely it comes
across better in the game and maybe it's
just me but like after so many episodes
of listening to that voice I'm like G
please stop being so [\h__\h]
Cho don't try to make your voice like
this for me it doesn't do anything for
me nobody has a voice like that IRL he
faked it
too I don't believe it I don't buy it
oh you you mean that his his voice was
also Changed by mutating into a
[Music]
Witcher I thought I had
a kind of like Batman does Batman also
have a voice like that I I guess so I
guess so yeah he's a heavy
smoker poor
guy we all make bad life decisions
you know watching the show now made me
come to this
realization that all these cosplays The
Witcher cosplays that I've been seeing
so far at conventions and so on I always
thought Siri the Siri cosplays I was
seeing I always thought that was like a
genderbent version that ladies are doing
because they want to cosplay Gerald but
want to make a gender bend version out
of it a lot of people think that I I
really just thought so because they look
so I don't know similar I guess at that
point when she's an adult I guess so she
was like oh another gender band uh main
character of The Witcher whatever his
name
is yeah let's go I know you can do it
just need the right
momentum you f that for a while too I
think the clo thing is also like I mean
not really like but like if you don't
know the show then seems to be not so
uncommon to think that way H so
boy why am I doing all this for when I'm
just going to fail at the jump again
[Music]
huh D also they position things like you
need to grip with this hand but they
know that you have to reposition because
you're not going to land there with that
hand you know what I
mean they do that on
purpose so very
much like here we arrived with the right
hand but we got to switch because we got
to grab with the right hand and then
again we need to switch hands
here he do it on purpose there is a
shortcut
n like I wonder if you can jump over
there probably not
all
right scary scary
scary I think
also to give you guys more of my opinion
if you may want it I like
the the way uh the monsters look but I
don't like a lot of the magic like
sometimes it's really just sound effect
effects I've noticed there's no actual
visual effects maybe they were just lazy
as
[\h__\h] just where where is the
magic and some of the magic is just
cringe but okay
like budget maybe I hate the burning
Arrow strope what what's what's the
Trope about it what what is the
trope special effect Sabrina the
Witch a light magic setting heral can't
do much I don't mean him I mean like
yenfa and and her
Mages you should have learned from CH
but season one of chant was very cringe
but that was many many years ago so
they're allowed to do cringey
[Music]
sfx no I do like it I'm so far I'm
enjoying season 2 too um and it's really
motivating me to play The Witcher free
cuz I realized we have perms I looked it
up and I was like oh yeah we have terms
oh I haven't played it before let's go I
want to play it but
um I would have to play it while playing
Yakuza but at the same time I uh I I got
uh Dragon's Dogma and if I'm going to
play that then I should play it probably
sooner rather than later cuz Witcher
free has been out for a long time dragon
Dragon Dogma hasn't and I should
probably play the one that's been
released
recently rather the one that has been
released ages ago and I can just play
whenever the [\h__\h] I want even though I'm
more motivated to play Witcher right now
you know cuz I'm watching the show on
Netflix yeah but it would be wicher free
and I just want to know just want to
confirm I feel like you guys already
told me so in the pre-
chat
um is it okay to play which free what
about one and two where did the rest of
them go can I just uh jump into number
three okay but where where what part of
the story does that pick up where would
I be in the Netflix
show or is it completely
separate there janky most people skip
M oh boy way in the future oh 10 years
after oh oh
okay F to the Future Okay H okay then I
guess that's
fine then I'll try to watch the Netflix
show as far as far as I can but then I
wish I could like immediately connect to
playing the witch on stream but like now
you know this feeling that I have to
play Dragon's Dogma
first how the [\h__\h] do you do this jump
guys I'm scared is there a certain
height where I should start can you tell
me at least that guys from seeing other
members
[Music]
play do I need to do it from higher up
you got same jump Nissa got stuck
at middle rock usually that's what I was
thinking that's why I in the started
last time I was up
here
remember
[Music]
okay should
I pull myself up while
swinging I'm not
sure yeah yeah I don't mind thinking of
those things as separate stories that's
why I also I don't know I I just you
know I I
I mean I didn't read the books of both
The Witcher
and these all these other shows where
people complain about the books being
different but I just see it as its own
thing you need a lot of momentum you can
jump by rotating your arm in a clockwise
rotation and then let go at 2 a.m.
is
huh yeah what what what what
what what
[Music]
e sensor I don't know I wonder how Amed
did it if there's really that many naked
bodies I've had naked bodies show up
before in my streams I
think Little Rock called pointing
hand um two wait one two like here
here I'm I'm really bad with
clocks like up here
yeah
right yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay yeah I know I know didn't Rissa
talk about this
[Laughter]
recently no but like for real I I I
don't even want to make it into a joke
for my stream but like I didn't learn
how to read uh an an non-digital clock
properly
until maybe 2 years
ago maybe one year ago I was
like up until you guys have no idea how
much I was sweating
internally my whole life when somebody
asked me like uh no when I asked someone
when I'm like in a room and I want to
know the time and I see a clock in the
room but I I I can't [\h__\h] read it so
I purposefully I ask the person around
me what time it is to hopefully have
them say it out loud to me by looking at
their own arm clock or them reading it
out loud for me and then they just point
at the clock and they're like there just
read it um there there's a clock like
something like that I'm like yeah and I
look at it pretending that I'm reading
it but I'm like not sure how long how
long does it take to read a clock some
people surely I've seen people read it
in like 1 second I've seen people like
stutter a little bit and read it in 5
seconds so I was like M nodding and I'm
like okay and then and then I I just
accept the fact that I don't know what
time it
is no we have we just have digital
clocks everywhere anyway and nobody
[\h__\h] taught me and in school I guess
I just like in when do you learn it in
elementary I guess I just somehow
swooped through the system without
learning
it and then they never taught you again
and whenever it came up like in a
different way for example like in math
sometimes you know they use clocks or in
language
classes like uh Italian somehow I just
always kind of made it through without
really knowing just guessing wrong or or
not guessing at all
uh going to the toilet whenever the
clock is on the
menu yeah you know how [\h__\h]
embarrassing this this for me to share
right now and your absolute shook head
fness
guys you know that's that really hurts
me right now I want to cry I want to
[Music]
cry but then there was um a moment
I feel like I'm kind of I kind of even
told this to kfp before cuz it feels
familiar to me you know in my first
year uh of H
life uh I collabed a game one of those
we were here together or so games with
am
right
and in the middle of the
game that's like a riddle solving game
you know you too thank you I love you
there's this one moment where you
there's a riddle but it's not about
reading the clock in the end but you may
think you have to because there is a
clock involved and you're like okay how
does this what kind of riddle are we
talking and so on and we're like trying
to compare what she sees on her screen
what I see on my screen so you kind of
want to ask each other what time do you
see on the clock and I freaked out and I
I'm like oh I I I got to go to the
toilet I'll be back and then I went to
the fake toilet and I was looking up on
my phone like I was trying to find this
moment of the game in like Solutions and
all
that I was sweating and sweating and I
was like really [\h__\h]
nervous um this was actually kind of
[\h__\h] traumatic to me and then I come
back and I I in that short amount of
time cuz I didn't want to stay away for
too long it's been like 5 minutes or so
and of me leaving Amma Alone um in in
the in that time I didn't manage to find
the actual solution I think but um
thankfully
eventually I uh I found the solution and
it was not uh based on the time but
yeah this is funny to you I don't know
it's just really it makes me want to cry
the amount of
stress this not knowing has put me
through um but then there's like most of
the time I go for life not needing to
know it so you know cuz I have my phone
or on the PC it's digitally and like
everywhere it's like pretty
digitally and yeah now um I a while ago
I don't know how long ago maybe yeah
just while I'm in Holo I was like I
can't have these kind of moments happen
to me again on
stream and yeah that's pretty much the
motivation I had I was like I'm going to
sit down now also because h of learning
Korean as well cuz I saw I looked for
the material she gave me beforehand my
teacher and I was like are there any
clocks coming up and I think there were
indeed clocks coming up so I was like I
I I I cannot be asked what time it is in
Korean of these clocks when I don't
[\h__\h] know what time it is I was like
I got a I got I got teach myself now
yeah so I I I went on YouTube I watched
a video that was made for 5 year olds
perhaps I pre-planned for the clocks I
watched a video that's made for
5-year-olds and I learned how to read
the clock and I think I'm I can read it
now I I still the the look at clocks is
kind of traumatizing to me so I still
try to not look at them I I want to
avoid looking at clocks I I haven't had
I've been living alone for a long time
and I haven't had a uh a non-digital
clock anywhere for many many years which
it's traumatizing to me okay prove it
but I can't right now my hands are bound
my fingers are bound to the
stone but there you go here is one of my
top three top two most embarrassing
tangents that I could ever give to
you and ridicule myself
you're
[Music]
welcome 2:00
2:00
to I don't know I'm going to
fail I hate clocks I hate
clocks oh
man I don't I [\h__\h] hate
this can't I I can't get the
[Music]
ah thank you for the
meal there's no way there's no [\h__\h]
way Pro you
[Music]
I want
to I
just yeah I'm really embarrassed by
telling the story why did I tell you
guys the story I'm so embarrassed I
don't want to talk with you guys anymore
I can't look into your eyes
anymore thank God you don't have eyes
chat I don't want to look at them
[Music]
well at the moment you don't have eyes
okay you may have eyes behind the screen
[Music]
but I hate this there's no way I'm going
to do this did narissa ever get past
this point cuz you would say she was
stuck here I I would feel very connected
to her if she never got past
it she
didn't that's funny this is not very far
into the
game this is really not that far for how
long did she
try up until this point is pretty
easy just got to figure out how the [\h__\h]
you
jump and I keep you keep on like falling
down when you swing so it's like maybe I
should stop from
higher to free
hour thank you for being proud of mean
there it's not really something to be
proud of to learn cuz it's also pretty
simple and it was necessary somehow I
mean you know I've really been through
life for a long time without knowing how
to read it I've somehow come uh a life
out of it
[Music]
but I felt it I felt the stone on my
fingertips [\h__\h] this I'm never going to
get past this point
I wish I could read the super chats but
they go way so fast we'll we'll do our
Super Chat reading after this whenever I
feel like ending this which is now but
we're going to try a little bit
longer I always be proud of learning
something no not this one not this one
that's no you don't have to congratulate
me for that or anything just um don't
laugh at me okay
it's actually traumatizing for
me why did I tell you guys this I'm so
embarrassed I want to die I'm like a Sim
right now I could die from
embarrassment at this very
moment I would feel
actually so connected if anybody would
tell me that they had the same
thing problem so to
say but you're probably too embarrassed
to say
it you was just you was you was the same
way when I was 10 shut
up that's still
early I think plenty of people do really
I think at least it seems to be kind of
a thing with the newer Generations like
anybody who's like I don't know 15 16
now they grew up in a in a some of them
may have grown up in
environment where you really didn't you
weren't taught and you didn't need to
know it cuz everything is
digital yeah but I'm not that much of a
tumor so I don't really have that
excuse I could read them before but I
lost it is that something you really
forget I guess
[Music]
so same with cursive writing oh cursive
writing yeah do they not teach cursive
writing in school anymore I think in I
think in Austria they do but in some
countries they don't
maybe cursive is some people really
can't read cursive I realized I'm
like what I mean maybe like I understand
like um for example Japanese people cuz
first of all they that's not their
writing system they learn romanized
letters but I guess that's the extent of
where it ends they probably don't learn
cursive or they just touch upon it
simply I don't ever see people write
cursive in
Japan sometimes I just forget that they
might not be able to read it if I write
something in cursive down um so for that
I would understand it in like countries
where the writing system is not our
Latin romanized
letters by
default
um
yeah that I understand you haven't
considered that it's it's a thing it's a
thing cive is kind of dead here what for
real I like cursive I I always enjoyed
writing cursive more than writing block
letters cuz I feel like you were able to
write faster and cursive cuz it's
scribble scribble
scribble no cuz it's connected too you
don't have to let go of your pen and
attack the paper again it has a flow so
that's you can write papers faster and
all that yeah yeah
yeah that's the point yeah I guess
so but then there's so many people's
handwriting who you just can't [\h__\h]
read They're cursive as
[\h__\h] woo
nice okay I'm back I'm back guys I'm
back and I'm ready to
attack okay whatever I didn't even think
much about that I F I should just go for
[Music]
it yeah okay well guys I told you a
really embarrassing thing about me you
have to tell me one embarrassing thing
about you that's just how it goes was a
tradeoff tell
me like your most one of your most uh
embarrassing memories things what do you
want to know everything can't ride a
bike n that's not
embarrassing there's a barrel skip here
a okay I can attempt ow I'm I'm just
guessing you just got to try your best
to get the right moment to hold on to
that up
[Music]
there one time I reped my pants in the
kindergarten I don't think that's
embarrassing that's what kindergarten
kids
do and can't swim that's um I wouldn't
say that's like a lot of people can't
swim as adults too that's fine I can't
swim well either I'm just
like forcing it that's really the most
embarrassing thing you got for me
guys
wow I once walked into a brle by
accident that is a bit embarrassing in
the moment but um not really no no I
can't tell my not being able to tie
shoelaces I think that was also a thing
for me for relatively long I can totally
tie them I I didn't take so much time to
learn how to tie my shoelaces okay not
as long as ah woo with other
things but I think I I used to have that
issue too as a child okay that wasn't
too long until I learned
it shoelaces velcro kids yeah I would
always go for like velcro
shoes wait you too oh my God someone
told my CR I liked her and I ran away
from her yeah that's that's um you know
I'm not trying to like like
um diminish or so your embarrassment but
you can at least find maybe um relief in
the fact that a lot of people have a
story like that so it's like a common
thing that you know crash stories are
just
embarrassing diminish okay didn't learn
to ride a bike until I was was in Middle
School yeah I think that's fine I also
haven't learned how to ride a bike until
I was
[Music]
like I don't know pretty late into my
teenage years and I'm still not good at
it so I wouldn't ride it in busy traffic
cuz it scares the [\h__\h] out of me that I
don't have confidence in riding a
bike until yesterday
no I still don't know how to ride that's
fine honestly like um I think it would
be very help ful knowing how to ride a
bike is really helpful I
think in
life wherever it is on on the
countryside or on the on a busy in a
busy
City if you can't afford a uh
uh not a horse um a
car for example oh I want to read that
I'm probably gonna end up reading that
anyway if you can't yeah afford a car or
gas or so
or you moved from the countryside to a
city and you realize that you don't
really need your car in the city but a
bike would be nice you know that's
that's that would be really
convenient how the what is this like how
can you actually apparently you can do
this is this what you guys mean with
Barrel
[Music]
Skip it's hard
oh move
right right side of the barrel not from
the barrel itself ah uh so you skip
touching the
Barrel bar skip isn't real from The Rock
on the right so okay here oh well yeah I
mean it could be possible yeah yeah yeah
got really close even just
now yeah that's that should be
possible all
[Music]
right I wonder there's a a good hand the
green tip yeah I get
it
[Music]
mhm right hand seems to reach better for
this you think so but I'm my Lefty
I'm a
lefty speaking of
crushes I want to let you guys know I
don't have a crush on the store
lady um but the like at least one other
person in the store may be thinking I do
and I feel a little bit ridiculed by
this person no I just appreciate a nice
lady who has a nice smile on welcoming
smile not a judgmental one a genuine
genuine nice smile who who likes to talk
to me you
know I just really like this
lady
and no I don't have a crush oh my
God so so okay I go I told you guys
right that I was concerned that she
maybe quit in the 3 weeks where I was
gone because I didn't see her anymore at
the store for and and then I asked them
and they told me she didn't quit she
just broke her toe ironically the same
day I was told that she broke her toe I
almost broke my toe as
well seems
like somewhere in my brain I was wishing
to suffer the same fate as her out of
Love or Whatever soulmates Destiny it's
Destiny so we have something in common
yes yeah we could talk about something G
like oh my God you're back from breaking
your toe you know I actually also break
broke my toe I totally did it for you I
love you no I don't have a crush okay
soulmates soul
soul soulmates no way oh my God broken
toe me too let's
go no so um but yeah so then um I
noticed this one employee who's was
there often I I asked once about her and
he has this dump smile on his face this
whole
time even before I asked her like he's
just rather than replying with words he
just has this dumb smile that seems very
judgmental and like he's ridiculing me
but then like he would ask stupid
questions like um oh he even pranked me
so the day after they told me about the
toe I go back and he's like oh she
actually did quit I'm like what what do
you mean what do you mean she quit did
she quit from the day yesterday until
today and that's why yesterday you told
me she didn't quit but today you say she
did like what no no no way no but he's
like smiling like a [\h__\h] idiot
pissing me
off like why you why are you doing this
and I'm like I don't believe it and he's
like no yeah she did she did I'm like no
like when would this happen when would
this have happened yesterday you told me
know he's just trolling me it pisses me
off eventually he said ah just kidding
why do you why do you like her so much
and I'm like it's not like I just she's
just nice okay
like do you want her number I'm like no
stop whatever I don't need her
number so
stupid I
just just like just just like Chad
sometimes don't always assume that I'm
like in love with someone or so just
because I'm I talk fondly of them
doesn't automatically mean I I'm in love
with them I want to make babies with
them
[Music]
please no I didn't want her number not
from someone else especially and if I
wanted someone's number if I wanted her
number then only because I want to be
friends be F because she's nice
okay sometimes sometimes you just want
to hang out and be friends I don't
really want to hang out with her because
I have enough friends already like I
can't
really handle any more friends you know
the friend ccle I have currently is
really fed with me not being available
much and just being mostly non-existent
in our friend Circle just existing by
yeah
existing and that's what I
need
[Music]
okay if she if she was like hi you know
and I'm like
okay anyway so they they tried to prank
me okay I'm like [\h__\h] just stop stop
being so stupid the other the other
employees are nice but this one guy but
I think the rud guy I told you about is
gone the root guy remember the rud guy
who always talks [\h__\h] about his
co-workers even while they're in the
same room and who just always overshares
his anger with me while I just smile and
Nod I haven't seen him in so long so I
think he's gone thank God and I I I bet
the other employees are so happy because
he was like the most toxic person in the
store I'm so involved with the people in
this store I'm getting so involved in
all the
personalities but yeah they all
recognize me and they're all nice to me
and they're always like oh hi every time
they see me that's the thing cuz I'm
like a regular every time they see me
like hi like how you
doing yeah other day I walked in in a
pajama at like 1:00 p.m. but it it's not
that I was
awake that that I wasn't awake for that
long I was awake actually since like 700
or 8: a.m. on that day I just like to
not wear anything but my pajamas these
days and they made fun of me like you
just woke up hard I'm like no was my
wake is 8:00 a.m.
[Music]
okay yeah they know me too well it's a
bit uncomfortable at this
point those lazy days for real what kind
of pajam just any
pajamas go there a lot
yeah sitcom Behavior huh who me or
them okay come
on oh close close close close close
close close close close close close
close
seems very manageable but maybe me
skipping this one jump will just result
in another jump waiting for me a
different
one wait I need
[Music]
to no get to the very
tip oh you idiot [\h__\h]
Moren yeah here
[Music]
no skip the jump go straight for the
fall what it's not sking the jump but
it's just a shortcut to a what no I
don't need that in my what that's still
not worth
it I thought that was skipping the jump
we wasting my time here cuz I can get
there really fast
anyway no need for that
no no no thank
you no thank
you it brings you to the jum well then
[\h__\h]
no can I do like a e
yeah my hands are so sweaty my right
hand is so sweaty sweaty
spaghetti sweaty spaghetti
how you guys liking my tangents today
huh you like me embarrassing myself this
should show you how much trust I put
into you guys and how much I love you
what kind of relationship we have yeah
and I just I just you know this is who I
am I just tell you all about my life and
my every day and my problems and my non
problems my my good whatever situations
whatever just just let just talk n k for
you that's how we
do this is how we
do the good
blems I'm not drunk don't drink
alcohol I
reject the existence of
alcohol don't need
that okay here we go we do a little
swing
drunk on
chat this is how we do
[Music]
it that was a lot of
momentum elud elud I feel like I haven't
seen you in a while and suddenly you're
here with all these memberships thank
you and red Super Chat thank
you how you doing Mr GAA
less for you more for me no please don't
don't see this as a more for you kind of
situation I'm I'm going to try one up
here this game is so [\h__\h]
dumb I just we we should practice
jumps okay
no
[Music]
momentum I don't know what you mean I
can't really do a 2 a.m.
jump a 2:00 jump
it doesn't matter right it's same it's
the same on the
clock just got to look if the if the sun
is down or if the Sun is up
try tracing the bottom of a circle when
you swing what do you mean the bottom of
the CLE yeah I mean yeah just swing in
like a yeah bow shape yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
obvious going to
work now he just let go on his
own Wing a
girl no never never going to work never
going to work no I'm I'm not the jump
I'm just practicing the jump down here
welcome to the
stream controller really do you think
it's easier with a
[Music]
controller
ooh no I cannot go
higher try both hands oh
interesting you mean
ah H cuz then M
no F to beat it with a controller
wow maybe controller is the way to
[Music]
go whatever we're just going
to just going to go we're just going to
go let me try a shortcut
again
wait no the tip
yeah the tip of the
[Music]
grassbur why why does sometimes he have
momentum sometimes not it's weird
come on no you're like on the I need to
go on the back layer of the mountain
don't you get it don't you get
it yeah
there rasper tip with the right hand
better he's a little bit below the
[Music]
tip yeah no no not perfect but
okay ah
slipped a God damn
it this okay that pretty that could be
good see you later suckers bye-bye you
guys stay down there and watch my ass
jiggle
goodbye watch that cat from Below
[Music]
there's no way that is so big of a
distance I'm not capable of
[Music]
this you want to swing at the left uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah I get that I get
that obviously obviously duh
[Music]
like he he falls down so much got to
start
higher but like but then I'm too much on
the left side oh my
hands I'm losing my grip
[Applause]
okay this is such a dumb
[Music]
game who wants to play a game like
this oh oh my God I was like the moment
I woke up today I was excited to tell
you guys about my dream cuz it's whole
life related and it was so real like
realistic kind of you
know okay I wrote it down it it was so
vivid too
but wait oh my
God too I'm too
focused too in
it need to
sneeze ah it was a nightmare though kind
of lowkey not too bad of a nightmare
though it was
a sunset Mare
[Music]
okay [\h__\h]
dip dip
[Music]
yeah almost had
it don't keep us in
suspense I'm just never going to tell
you now
never never
if only this game didn't have any jumps
but more stuff like this I would be
[Music]
okay oh thank you for sharing another
embarrassing story let's
go looking forward to reading that later
[Music]
who
[\h__\h]
[Music]
sa no I don't know
o
[Music]
o if I fail this jump I'm going to teach
tell you my nightmare I'm starting to
get really confused with my fingers now
[Music]
so I mean
okay let me bring out my notes I feel
like I still remember it pretty vividly
because I wrote it down just in case
okay so this was Fest related
okay so um if I think it was like Monday
before the actual
Fest and for some reason we had
rehearsal on Monday instead of like
Friday or so and
um we were there um in like a big Hall
like more like it was more like the
stage was in the middle of the expo hall
and we were actually there there was not
like you know vtuber screens you know we
were
actually like flesh in the flesh there
and we were just like you know
performing doing our rehearsal and we
were performing like a new song that is
not to be revealed yet that that doesn't
exist but um you were doing that and
then we we rehearsed another song that
was already known like I don't know what
song it was could be like something like
bright our bright
parade yeah and then the song ends we're
kind of done with the rehears I look I
look behind the stage cuz it's like in
the middle of a big expo hall just like
a random stage you know besides Expo
boops and all that and I look behind and
there's I see like you know in a stadium
those kind of seats like a lot
of a lot of seats are that elevate
really quickly like on every there's
like stairs and on every stair there's a
there's a chairs I guess kind of like in
the stadium that's how it was like built
in my dream and I I look behind the
stage and I see a [\h__\h] ton of fans
sitting there and like half of them were
dressed in Orange and like cheering and
looking at me and waving at me and I'm
like oh what the there's people in here
while we're doing our rehearsal I wonder
if they heard the sign that they weren't
supposed to hear why are these people
here but I was like happy to see so many
kfp there so it's like okay cool
whatever yeah but then we stop and we
were done with the rehearsal and they
were like I guess I don't know why they
were letting people in but they were
letting some people in to check out the
Expo early I don't know why and we were
also getting the chance to check out the
Expo early so so yeah everybody all the
members scatter and look around and
check out the the Expo
stuff and I do that too a little bit but
then I get a little bit overwhelmed so
I'm like okay I don't know I want to go
backstage like this is too much too many
people that are uh around here so I find
the staff and I ask if there's like a
backstage place where I can just chill
and and
rest it's a Dream It's a
dream and so they take me they take me
backstage it takes like quite a while
until they can bring me there like 20
minutes
apparently and yeah I'm being um
carefully transported to the backstage
area and I chill a little bit there and
after a while I realized like it's been
like an hour of me chilling in the
backstage room and nobody else has
joined me and I'm like I guess they're
still all out there or so so I go back
out oh on my own and I I'm in the expo
hall again and I see
nobody absolutely nobody no fans no
visitors no members no managers no staff
nothing like what's happening why is
nobody here what what happened then I
find jenma like roaming around like like
she's kind of stressed and on the phone
and you know she got somewhere to go
that kind of look and I'm I sto her and
I'm like JMA where is everyone and she's
like what are you doing here I'm like
what do you mean what am I doing
here what she's like oh
like yeah actually everybody flew out in
a plane to a different city because the
hotels cuz this rehearsal was Monday but
it's was the the event was going to be
on the weekend right so there's still a
couple of days and they didn't want the
members to stay in a hotel closed by to
The Venue so they actually took a
[\h__\h] airplane to fly out to a
different city uh but like a really
close
one um to uh just like yeah be in a
hotel that's like further away and
apparently I missed it they just like
forgot about me or just thought I I'm
just gone and they just accepted it they
didn't try to look for me or anything
and Jenna kind of like blames me that I
I I should have known because uh
everybody got the notice in the WhatsApp
group and I'm like what WhatsApp group
I'm not nobody added me to any kind of
WhatsApp group
whatsoever I had no notification I was
just chilling backstage where a staff
actually brought me there why did no no
staff let me know that we were leaving
and I'm missing out on an airplane and
so on and she was like oh yeah oopsie I
guess the memo for the WhatsApp group
didn't go out to you
either yeah and then I'm like okay well
can I still go there like how do do I
get there and gemma's like well sorry
you there's no more no more other
flights for you to get there you're not
going to get there there there was no
way yeah but apparently at some point at
some point they found uh a different
like a plane for me to go on to a
different place a different Hotel
different from everybody
else and I was just going to stay there
alone and like but I'm just like why did
this happen why was I so like forgotten
about and why did nobody think of me why
did nobody think to look for me
huh so I was kind of pissed you know and
then um I don't know if this was implied
in my dream or if it was really so but
somehow we we jump over to
the to the assumption that this must
have been on purpose it wasn't an
accident that they missed out missed me
or that I missed the plane was an
accident because I
realized uh before the rehearsal there
was like a food
buffet yeah I think I was sabotaged I
was set up or
so uh there was like a food buffet okay
in the middle of the expo hall and this
is so specific but there was um a fruit
platter a cut fruit like m mostly melons
I think it was like those not the
Watermelons the other melons they were
cut in this like moon shape and I was
apparently taking
some but I T I touched one with my hand
instead of using the
the tonsils or whatever tonsils
what you know what I mean
tonsils s
yeah yeah honey de lemon melon lemon
melon and so on was there and yeah so I
I apparently touched something but then
yeah I just I just took my fruit and all
that and then in hindsight I realized
somebody has sent out a member who saw
this who witnessed this has sent out a
letter a formal letter a complaint to
all members to
see where anonymously this member was
saying I am absolutely like disgusted
and appalled by this one member Among Us
who has touched the food with her own
fingers because that is like my biggest
my biggest no no my biggest what do you
what do you say uh what's it called
again not
catnip the the one thing that pisses her
off the most is when people pet peeve
yeah when people touch food with their
own hands and that pissed her off so
much so she made a complaint she made
this big public uh not public but like
open letter of complaint
and while realizing that she was writing
that about me most likely and was really
pissed at me I realized maybe she must
have like done something talked to the
staff so that I wouldn't be notified
about the plane Le
and me being left
behind yeah again this is a dream
okay so uh I knew who wrote
that somehow even though it was
Anonymous my brain just kind of knew and
I eventually was able to confront her
directly about it I found her again at
the
Expo and I was like what what's your
damn issue like because of you I kind of
like missed everything these past few
days of me being all alone was because
you had such a huge issue with me
touching with the tip of my finger like
just rearranging something apparently
yeah okay that's not hygienic but like
why are you so [\h__\h] pissed off
man why do you do this why do you have
to like create this this chaos man and
she was
like and then I'm like what do you want
what do you want and then we start like
a little bit of a fight H like cuz I'm
like kind
of making her like I'm like come at me
come at
me and she like kind of comes at me and
I just like slightly push her and she
falls down by me just slightly pushing
her and then I just I don't know why I
felt the need to do this but I gave her
like the softest punch ever on her
shoulder but people saw how I punched
her and they were like oh my God no
[\h__\h] way takanasi kiar other members
saw it no [\h__\h] way takasi kiar
punched one of our co-workers who's also
her coworker what a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] she
hurt that girl for now with and she's so
aggressive she's so [\h__\h] aggressive
what's wrong with her and I'm like oh
man okay I shouldn't have punched her
just now but really it was like there
was no power in my punch anyway like um
I just like I don't know was like Bonk a
small
Bonk but yeah we just really pissed off
because like she messed up
everything and um yeah she acted like
she was so hurt and so injured and oh my
God but so I thought okay this is a
problem we uh they saw the other
coworkers saw it so they're going to
tell management that I punched a
coworker and it's just going to escalate
and I'm going to get fired but then
while they were still watching the
situation unfold I like helped her back
up and I'm like sorry let's just let's
just talk it out and we talked it out
and we ended up like making up and it
became a like te happy
situation and yeah uh she forgave me I
guess and yeah that was that was kind of
it
yeah that's kind of it just like my
anime
and then the other co-workers saw that
we were like making up and like
everything was fine so they didn't they
didn't tell on me anymore either you
know but like what the
[\h__\h] what kind of dream is this it was
so vivid and so detailed and so long and
so well connected my other dreams
usually are like really like random and
mixed and like all over the place this
was so like real when I woke up I was I
I felt like I just watched a [\h__\h]
movie
[Music]
I didn't know who it was though my my
dream never revealed to me who that girl
was who has a huge pet peeve taboo on
people touching food that she might eat
you
know it's not a completely unreasonable
pet peeve you know but I just like
touched it like a little bit it wasn't
like I was all over it but yeah and it
wasn't like she had to eat that one
piece that I touched but
okay go find out if any Holo member has
a pet peep like that then must have been
her but my dream never really showed me
any faces or anything or any sign that
one this member might be that member you
know was very unclear everything else
was so clear but this wasn't clear at
all God damn
it I like a bad Chinese light now
my
dreams they are here to entertain
me I don't know it was um there was
quite a big a part of it where I was
like alone at that other hotel and some
stuff happened there too but I I don't
remember that part so
[Music]
well was like that with food too if
anyone made food we made sure he got
some first before other people had a
chance to touch it oh very sensitive
doesn't
it a [\h__\h] so
[Music]
close [\h__\h] this
game how were there I don't know why
there were people it was just you know
random things that happened in dreams
there were just a lot of a lot of fans
there early access to the rehearsal or
something like that I
guess
yeah another try at the jump just to
fail once again aren't we
[Music]
excited feel like I had a good swing
there for a moment but
I'm at the edge of my
seat yeah but I was happy to see so many
kfp there was so much orange there
guys so much orange made me really happy
thank you guys for being in my dream I
appreciate your your support going that
far you go overseas for me you even go
into my dreams for
me you're like everywhere I can always
count on
you I'm I'll give you credit for that
for being in my dream thank you for
being there I really appreciate
[Music]
it the melons being touched that's a
line that was drawn not by you guys but
by by some coworker
[Music]
being alone after uh yeah I don't know I
don't really think I think this dream
was really random but I do have to say
that like now there's two occasions
where there were a lot of Ian members
mingling um in Japan having fun together
while I was sick this time and also
during my frd debut stay in Japan and I
got to say yeah that was kind of like I
was feeling really lonely like man I'm
missing out on all the and they're all
like bonding while I'm all alone
and
yeah but hey I got to say narissa is so
sweet cuz narissa I'm surprised she
didn't get sick she spent time with me
while I was sick just to eat some bread
for breakfast cuz I really wanted her to
eat this like particular bread that I
kept on eating um during my stay in
Japan this time cuz I found a nice
Bakery and I was so proud of my find I
kept on telling her about this bread
like oh we got to eat it and then I saw
she had a she had already made like a
promise to go for breakfast perhaps or
late breakfast or more like lunch
probably but they talked about breakfast
uh with other members and I saw that
conversation cuz it was in an open chat
that we have and I'm like oh okay like I
that that sounds like more fun than
eating some stupid bread with me in my
hotel room together so I I wrote there
I'm like don't worry you no pressure to
eat bread with me if you want to go you
know with them like I
understand sorry I Let Go On by
accident from sadness and she was like
no no I can eat like all of that like
I'll do it don't worry don't worry it's
okay I can have two breakfasts or so
also they seem to and in the end it was
more like a lunch anyway from from their
perspective cuz it was
later yeah and then we just ate some
bread on top of my
bed bread spread bread spread bread
[Music]
spread just enjoying the bread
appreciating the
bread and then she then she left but I
was I was already like sick at that
point and she still risked it for the
biscuit there was no biscuit there was
no biscuit
indeed there was melon pun and shield
pun so sh pun sh pum translates to Salt
bread yeah and we have salt bread like
bread with salt chunks on top of it in
Austra too
salang but I like how
salang and shield pun is very very
different so so
different I um I think generally Austria
makes better bread than Japan but when
it comes to shopan oh my God I love how
Japanese people make their shopan their
salt
bread come
here it's usually very
buttery and it just has generally a very
different texture and all that it's it's
just very
buttery wait was I supposed to do this
with the right hand like grab of the
right hand I
forgot too many
tangents I mean grab the top with the
right hand or no left hand right I did
it before with the left hand I
think you eat it by itself yeah like
normally I would put something on bread
you know I don't eat the bread itself
but this Japanese Shian and I've had it
in several bakeries and it's just
amazing
everywhere it's just so good like they
they absolutely nail it wherever I go
it's so good on its own because it's so
buttery and like crunchy and soft and
everything and the the sh is not like um
it doesn't burn your [\h__\h] tongue and
throat the the salt I
mean dress up an orange and just talk
about K like she's in the third
person
[Music]
a it's like a type of qu no no no it's
not a quas but it do be kind of hollow
inside sometimes
yeah the feeling I get every time I do
this I'm amazing I'm
amazing here we are again
[Music]
guys there's absolutely no point for me
to continue playing this
I'm obviously not going to make this
jump
ever jump from lower okay I'm going to
give it another
try this so stupid I'm not raging though
I'm just like laughing isn't that
nice yeah W tangents this this is you're
you're that's what you're getting from
that aren't we all delighted by
that my fingers hurt though why do we
have to do this why do I have to suffer
while you enjoy huh my
tangents you better be giving me good
tangents of embarrassing stories in
those super chats as a good
exchange thank you for dropping one
thank you and the hashtag I guess okay
okay okay looking forward to that I do
read my hashtag most of the time I just
for the Easter stream I didn't read it
cuz I was like so
like but the clips that I saw from it
they didn't seem so bad the audio didn't
seem so bad at all I'm sure that there
were many times where you just couldn't
hear the others but I told them
beforehand that if they weren't around
me they wouldn't be audible in the
Stream and and sometimes like for
example the egg hunt I think it was
better because they were messing around
so much over there talking so much that
you wouldn't really have heard what's
going on in the in the battle they were
having like a completely different
scenario on the side a second POV would
have been good for that perhaps but no
one would have paid attention to the
actual egg hunt then in that
situation
um they were building a [\h__\h] uh
statue over there and like turning
themselves into big giants and all that
um but the reason why I did uh
uh like
proximity uh voice this time uh as
opposed to Discord last time I was
thinking of doing Discord this time too
but there was an original plan to
implement like code the bgm into each
stage like into the
game now we ran out of time so that
didn't happen but that was still the
plan until the like 30 minutes before
the stream so what we did manage to
achieve was cing sound effects into the
very last game that was made on time so
if I were to use
Discord uh
audio I I don't know I could have mixed
it probably like Discord audio with game
audio but somehow you know I was still
like the plan was still to use proximity
and use the bgm from ingame and use the
sfx from ingame and so on so I was like
cuz things were like getting dropped and
cancelled at the last minute like oh we
don't have time for this one anymore we
don't have we don't have time for this
one and so on and I was like really
stressed to get the stream started cuz I
delayed it so many times so I just like
I wasn't in the right mindset to change
my plan completely you know cuz like
some things were already uh abandoned
and I just I was already so [\h__\h]
stressed out that I couldn't like last
minute change everything cuz I I would
have had like to do L audio tests and
everything while we were all like having
a lot of other issues you know it was
just too much for me
[Music]
yeah yeah this time I took way more time
than before cuz I wanted to avoid the
scuff that we had last time in Easter VR
collab and then still we still had scuff
so next time we're going to plan ahead
even earlier and start working on it
hopefully even
earlier
yeah if there is a next
time how much did I'm going help out she
didn't help out at all this time cuz she
was busy and that's fine you know I
should be able to do this kind of stuff
on my
own yeah no Amit this time I I invited
her but she's busy at the
moment that's okay and I feel like I I
want to take um responsibility for these
kind of things on my own and I want to
be able to do these things on my own um
cuz I enjoy organizing big collapse and
VR the VR stuff that Amma does always
seemed like a little bit um ambitious to
me that I thought like oh I can't do
this but um I kind of can it's just a
yeah a big project
always and the question is is the payoff
worth it I'm not sure about
that I'm not sure if it is
um both mentally and
financially
yeah that's okay though that's okay cuz
I just want to I just want to organize
every once in a while I want to organize
something fun andig
that viewers can enjoy and members can
hopefully also enjoy so just so that we
have a good time if I end up um paying
for it financially and
mentally then that was worth it that's
worth it cuz then in exchange we get a
fun event that everybody enjoys yeah we
need these kind of fun events in the
middle of doing endless pointless
streams like
this
now just something more meaningful you
know yeah come together everybody join
forces and have some fun in a in you
know I mean obviously the all these
games of the eggs those are in veryy
pointless too but it's the community and
the the fun we have as a group yeah
that's how was this pointless we got
plenty of embarrassing I could have told
you embarrassing stories any other time
I kept these
tangents for whenever I need them when I
when I'm playing a game that gives me
absolutely nothing to go
Offa yeah that's it that's it that's the
point the point is of these streams like
the VR
streams is to to come together have
fun uh spread a feeling of community to
the viewers who love that [\h__\h] they eat
that [\h__\h]
up and for us also to just like get
together and have fun like we're in
school and we're going on a field
trip we will have no no I still have
some more
tangents also turns out I said something
wrong yesterday I don't have meat and
greets in the Bangkok event there is no
meat and greets I'm surprised I assumed
there were meat and
greets there is no meat and greets
unlimited tangent
[Music]
works yeah maybe I confused some people
who are planning to go and they're like
what what does she mean meet and greets
I'm missing out of meet and greet where
where where where where could I buy meet
and greet tickets what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] wa you don't tell us about this
before no there is no meet and greets
I'm sorry for uh confusing
you doing the zoom meet and greet like
back in Co I am not allowed to do that
anymore I did that once that was the
first and only one to ever do this as
like a toen as a um extra for buying a
full set right or something like that no
I did it as a extra for you guys doing
something and then I asked if I could do
it again and they were like
nope
um upper managing management or so I
don't know behind the scenes they just
like didn't like that we did
that I mean I got permission and all
that to do that but I think it was just
logistically uh you know not something
they want to
handle and you know if more people if
people see that and want to do it cuz
I'm a
transcender then it's just going to be
more work for them to organize
this you know you know I'm a transitor
that's always the danger with me doing
stuff people wanting to do the
too so
true why why can I not reach it now
what's the problem what's the
[Music]
problem I think it's the left hand you
got to go with the left
hand so stupid inspirational I have to
believe
[Music]
I am biased
why what what what you mean I'm what do
you mean I'm biased you mean I'm based
right dope blit super
[Music]
based ah [\h__\h]
hell
ah biased for my left hand but it worked
before and I see I'm like literally
there
I I can do it I know I
[Music]
can I'm getting so sick of this game
what a stupid ass
[Music]
game but I'm taking it well don't I am I
not taking it well I'm taking it well
but my fingers really hurt from this
it's not good it's not not
good always trying to get the right
position cuz there's one spot that's a
little bit higher
oh [\h__\h] this I don't want to play what a
stupid
face I last 1 hour more than you thought
I would well it's the power of tangents
let me eat a cash you nut
[Music]
woohoo I'm taking it better than other
people
you know I have
matured in my time in whole
life I don't want to rage in these kind
of
games I
mean even when I raged in the past it
was all about entertainment yeah you
know like the egg cracking
game
ah there's certain times where I rage
it's
genuine but that those are often not
even rage
games but I wouldn't rage in a game that
is made for Raging
because it's so simple why do you rage
you know I don't know it's it's just
there's no point in Raging in this game
you know I mean yeah if I get much much
much much much much much higher and then
I fall that's something to rage about
yeah but I feel like it's it's it
there's no point in Raging in a game
like this
right cuz it's hard to explain what I'm
trying to
say cracked the
system cuz this is literally all the
game is
about yeah see
yeah it's just a pointless stupid little
game there's no point in thinking too
much about it just a brain empty kind of
game
yeah the moments where I usually rage in
a game is when things just don't really
work and and are just confusing and
stupid this game works let's just use
both
hands oh wait not a
hold a hold
[Music]
I see who I do get more
momentum but how do I reach
out how do I reach out though I I don't
think I reached out at all did my hand
reach out I can register it reaching out
to
[Music]
anything fire now people say the middle
is the way to
[Music]
go can we get much higher start higher
you'll catch it while upside down auh
you mean my whole body up should be
upside down and then I can catch it
we'll see we'll see I'll give it another
try I'll give it another try shut
[Music]
my fingers though my
fingers I can't do this much
longer he in that other
game what's the other game called again
I keep on
forgetting the game that I F is like the
prequel of this uh do you also have to
constantly grab with your fingers IRL
like can you also never let go getting
over it
yeah no okay that sounds way less
exhausting time to play
[Music]
that so close you little [\h__\h]
no
[Music]
no getting over whenn that's also one of
those games that I've just been
keeping for whenever I have nothing to
play or maybe like a marathon in the
future where I feel like I need some
filler game
[Music]
I'm literally right
here not having a backlock I do have a
big backlog right now yeah that's why
I'm
it's n this game oh I'm just playing it
right now cuz for
once I am here when there's a fotm game
going on that I don't mind
playing I've been missing out on so many
fotms just look at pal world I was still
kind of hopeful when I joined in late
looking at everybody's big ass bases no
one ever played it again no one
[\h__\h]
sad I didn't even let go he just let go
little
[Music]
[\h__\h] people it died off so fast I think
may maybe because the server until the
server was up it already took a while so
people were maybe already losing
interest like the the girls themselves
not the
viewers I I don't know it's so sad maybe
maybe if a big update comes people will
join back in we could motivate them I
don't
know it's so sad cuz I also missed on
like hanging out with gur and B world I
can't [\h__\h] believe
it [\h__\h] believe it the alliance that
we could have had would have been
marvelous but it was just like the hype
was so short people play for a [\h__\h]
week and that's the one week where I
couldn't play
[Music]
it dude just grab ever thought about
that just hold
on stupid
sussy dud
[Music]
do you like cards no I don't know how to
play
cards but that's not not something I'm
embarrassed about see like I wouldn't
know how to play poker or anything like
[Music]
that I mean I would like to learn it
because so often people want to play
card
games B Co H nah not interested I have
so many games I need to play guys I need
to play Yakuza I need to play Dragon's
Dogma I need to play The Witcher free I
need to play the um DLC of tales of
rise and then there's probably even
other games that I'm still like hoping
to play a Twi is like a whenever kind of
game Whenever Wherever I have Red Dead
Redemption but that's also something
where I feel like just like whenever I
have time it doesn't feel like I need to
play it now but those games I just
mentioned those are games I feel like I
need to play them
now now or never no no although with
Witcher yeah with Witcher it's just like
because I'm watching the show right now
I wish I could stop that's not an
[Music]
option fotm ah you think that's fotm
right now I don't know how many people
played it in whole life
I think FAA played it
right I have other stuff to do I need to
do H talk and I need to do girls talk or
do I might want to say girls talk huh
yeah yeah yeah hold on get that grip
[Music]
wait never skip finger
day got to work out those fingers
wait if I the thing is if I start on the
edge it will make me fall off when I
[Music]
swing I don't know that doesn't feel
right at all
[Music]
what [\h__\h]
what what was I supposed to do in that
moment was I supposed to let
go
whoa very confusing moment to
me that was too much I should have let
go before he turned over so that he
could turn over while he was flying
I
[Music]
guess that was
close I was
close I don't want to play this anymore
this
[\h__\h] what's the
point not going to I'm not going to
subject myself to this any longer
[Music]
where's close game on here I can't see
it cuz I have something there Rage Quit
excuse me I'm not
enraged I'll close it
differently there you go you're not
going to get that Rage Quit from
[Music]
me so everybody Welcome to the
office good decision yeah this game is
not worth my
[Music]
time
yeah yes I am Michael Scott I
am mightly
inconvenienced that's what I just did
yeah tactical retreat
it's really shitty compared to getting
over it okay okay I I I I like the
aspect of not having to constantly have
a grip in my middle finger and my index
finger I like Thea of that so I I will
get uh go and play that game one time
one time one
day yeah it's just Mouse Moving it looks
like
fun looks like so much
[Music]
fun quing seems like the point of the
game so you won no the my problem now is
that this is a game on the games list of
Wawa that I didn't
finish I should have just never played
it
this just unbalances throws up the
balance of my amazing
ratio going to burn the
loose yeah do
it it's not worth to ruin my ratio for
[Music]
this how long is that L I think it's
pretty pretty long by
now I I should get myself a copy of the
[Music]
list there might be some things that I
don't agree
[Music]
with what do you mean I finished GTA San
Andreas wait did I play GTA San Andreas
or was it a different
[Music]
one San Andreas no I didn't play San
Andreas
[Music]
TR bone
champ nah that's not a game you need to
[Music]
win I guess I didn't play San Andreas on
stream you're just saying I should
[Music]
yeah I gave up because it's pointless
welcome to the
stream you missed so many
tangents and I still got more but I'm
not going to tell them now or do I have
more actually I don't have more that was
pretty much
it I was going to talk a little bit
about I don't know I could I could have
talked a little bit more about EAS of VR
but it's fine I do think that the ideas
behind the games were nice that we
fought
up they they turned out pretty good too
they were functioning there was no scuff
in the the functionality of the games
that's pretty
[Music]
dope yeah the biggest problem was just
um the score for
me yeah and the other things were just
small
things like the picture not showing up
uh next to the Statue we fought we
thought we fixed
that and explo that Mo ah explo exploit
that Mo I found yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
the position she was in was apparently
really good I I didn't think there was
like a position that was better than the
others in the egg hunt
game but I guess there was she just had
to go left and right and left and right
and I I I was playing
um in VR mode I didn't have full body
tracking on but I was playing with the
goggles on and with the hand
trackers and I I didn't know I forgot
somehow I forgot how to jump and so I
couldn't get up on that one platform I
tried several times and I just wasted
time trying to get up there just
couldn't get up
[Music]
there oh yeah yeah the questions I
didn't realize until everything was over
that you guys weren't able to see the
questions cuz we saw them all
um yeah that's in h said that was really
embarrassing that you guys couldn't see
the questions there's like certain
things
that like for example the egg on the
spoon as well we realized that when I
picked up the spoon when we were testing
it that the egg was visible to me but it
wasn't visible to any other
player and then
supposedly that was
fixed we f
so but then there was no time to uh test
the fixed version and I just had to
trust it and turns out they could not
see my egg and you guys couldn't see it
either I guess the egg on the spoon but
there was an egg and it was really
really wobbling I was like I was
thinking maybe my idea is too ambitious
to implement to make a game in VR chat
from scratch where you pick up a spoon
and it works no matter if you're in
desktop mode or in VR but ideally I said
let's just let the VR players play this
game cuz then you wobble you you move
your body IRL so the egg will definitely
wobble but even for desktop it was
working you pick up the spoon the egg
wobbles and there's obstacles coming at
you originally the idea was that you
walk a
path and you work towards the obstacles
and all that but uh the way it turned
out to be in the end made way more sense
because you can't walk really far IRL in
v are depending on how big your room is
and how long the cable is and all that
so this way it's better um but yeah that
was great because my exg I was actually
I was so surprised everybody else was
doing so well in the in the the spoon
thingy game because I was first up and I
was really struggling I was getting down
IRL on the ground and all that to dodge
but apparently I was still too big maybe
it was the model side
maybe my frogy waa model was like bigger
than the others or so I don't know what
was going on but I dropped my eggs so
many times and they just like
immediately got it on first
try free non broken eggs in a row for
everybody else yeah I saw the clip of
Ollie of course I thought I saw I was
thinking she was generally like pretty
quiet during the whole stream and I was
a bit worried but uh seems like that's
what she was up to just staring into
everybody's
Soul yeah maybe I can't really tell cuz
I was in VR couldn't really judge if
everybody was much bigger than me I
don't think so we were like relatively
balanced but I may have had bigger hit
boxes but I think the yeah yeah the
teabag I saw I saw I also tea backed she
uh who did I tea backed FAA or sh I tea
backed FAA maybe yeah
but I was going to say um in in general
I'm really proud of how the games turned
out there's so much potential there and
it's kind of crazy that we can create
something like this from scratch in
freaking VR chat it could be its own
game released on
Steam
if uh worked out a little bit more but
yeah the tournament was
amazing right I am I I think it was good
that that was at the end because
everything was supposed to lead up to
that and I wanted it to be extra
unnecessarily dramatic I based that game
um on two
things the you know the egg cracking
game at the very end I based it on two
things number one the tradition that we
have here in Austria maybe also in
Germany and other countries at Easter
you take a a cooked egg paint it ideally
yeah it's called a
beckon you bump your egg against the
other person's egg either like usually
you don't just bump directly straight
into each other you you bump your top to
their bottom or the other way
around usually from what I've seen and
then you see which one breaks
first or more breakage
[Music]
it's a whole thing in Austria yeah have
this tradition in Russia as well oh same
in Poland
OH you guys not do that in America is it
just like this side of the
globe I haven't I don't really remember
playing this as a child but I remember
even um when I worked in the hotel as an
adult I saw my colleagues play it I'm
like oh you guys seem to be having a lot
of fun there never heard of it we might
in some places yeah maybe maybe don't
think I've heard of it in the US just
paint eggs and then hunt yeah we do that
too this is just another fun game I'm
surprised you guys don't pick up on that
game it's
fun it's called something else in in
Austrian we say
a so that's what it was based on and
also the whole like drama of it was
based on the rock paper scissors from
like
akb48 uh like those big events I told
you about where they do rock paper
scissors to to to decide which member
which members get to be in the next
songs music video it's like so [\h__\h]
dramatic they act like it's the end of
their life or the beginning of their
life lifechanging
moments yeah because you get a chance
even if you're an unpopular member in a
group of several hundred of members
finally you get a chance to shine if you
do well at rock paper scissors so it's
was like it's got to be like that it's
got to be like this lifechanging event
in a big arena in a dramatic buildup
with dramatic music and everybody's got
to be like really serious about it even
though we're just cracking some eggs
it's got to be super dramatic that's
what I told the members and that's what
I uh said to my team who worked on it I
was like this has got to be super super
dramatic it has to be about life and
[Music]
I would have made it even more dramatic
like commentating it but I was already
so exhausted and stressed out at that
point I wanted to cry and
die yeah the explosions were great at
the end the explo explosions bugging out
was kind of a great
[Music]
feature so I think that came across
really well and turned out really great
you guys seemed to enjoy that one the
most I do realize
after uh like going through it all that
the egg hunt it dragged out a little bit
and it was generally just chaotic
because the the score wasn't working um
but yeah I had to commit to it at that
point and I was so glad when the other
games were shorter and easier to get
through cuz I was like I got to say I'm
I was like really like why are things
not working I'm sure everybody's like
really pissed off and disappointed like
both the viewers and the members must be
so like what the [\h__\h] is this
[\h__\h] I got to get through this though I
started it now I need to commit to
it did you guys
hear my stomach
growl really loudly at some point cuz
HMA
said it was
audible no I did there was one point
where it it was so loud I was like Oh
that's oh my God that's really
embarrassing well some of you guys maybe
heard it okay I don't know when it
happened anymore but it was so
[Music]
loud not sure
when between some of the early games
yeah it might
[Music]
be got to give a shout out to HMA for
getting up so early to help me with the
cameras again I was a bit confused in
the beginning because like we didn't
really have much time to go through the
cameras the camera settings this time
and then I I kept on like peeking under
my VR goggles to see cuz there's a
button in our um camera system in VR
that I have to press so that it sends
the camera switches and everything to
OBS directly
instead of just like my POV so I pressed
that and it sends it but I kept on
peeking while during the stream in the
beginning under my goggles to see what
is being shown on OBS because it's
different from my POV and I noticed it
was it just wasn't
showing
uh like it was like on weird angles it
wasn't showing the eggs for example or
close-ups of the members and so on so I
was like is it broken is it working
what's happening and that stressed me
out too but I think it's like a we just
didn't have
uh the right angles prepared for that
area maybe again so that would have been
a good thing that we we should have uh
adjusted and attach uh uh and tested out
properly but yeah some of the angles are
just like kind of set in
stone
and can't really be
changed it's not as flexible so it is
what it is
yeah it's hard to predict what angles
there would be what what angles would be
necessary where the members would
be yeah so maybe if we showed off the
eggs like took the egg and then go to
the couch area maybe that would have
been better so sorry for the confusion
like I was genuinely confused as
well but yeah it was fine I think uh I
didn't rewatch The Stream or anything
but the angles seemed to be better later
on
right they were pretty um static I think
for the egg
hunt Ollie kept staring at
us Ollie was so helpful to me because
she uh during the the last game um
because her turn was so late she kind of
had nothing to do I guess so she kept on
like uh moving the the little coins of
the member
in the in the
scoreboard that was big TASC I didn't
even ask her to do that and then the
other thing she's the one who kept on
adding these like sound effects cuz she
was on desktop mode so she could
activate her sound effects I guess like
the yay Applause and ding ding ding ding
ding and that was really great cuz it
added a nice
touch in this case I think it was really
really um helpful to have have some
sfx from her side cuz it was supposed to
be like you know like a game show kind
of I didn't ask her to do that either
she just did exactly the thing that I
needed and I I also have to say like
before the stream when members were
gathering I had them on standby for a
while um and I was like please wait the
world is not ready yet like they were
still fixing things please wait and I
was getting really stressed out because
I already had to delay things and
everybody was being really sweet but out
of all
people shot was like the most like sweet
about it and calming like it's okay it's
okay don't worry about it sh was giving
me the most calming
words trying to calm me down yeah I was
like oh my God
shy thank
you it really felt like it had an effect
on
me it was really supportive really nice
of
her yeah I felt bad cuz I wanted to be
the cool Senpai who is really composed
and has everything under control but I
wasn't that and she still was really
really nice and she also like thanked me
she was the the first to thank me for
urbanizing all of that and and yeah
preparing everything I'm like
thank
you thank you too
[Music]
much you already are a super cool Z but
I don't know I don't know about
[Music]
that I got to do something with she wo
we want to collab something with shoi
shoi I like saying do does anybody I'll
say shii I like to say shii and
Ka
Moi
[Music]
NOA shei I think might be unique to me
she not sh Shi No
[Music]
shoi yapping collab oh yeah yeah yeah I
heard she's uh really good at yapping
just like me me she she we and fauna
might be the best yapper of Ian I have
so heard actually nista is also really
good at
yapping yeah the best yappers of all
time even more of anything I heard I
heard I heard she has crazy tangents and
they all like uh interject each
other and I think she she interjects
herself a lot
right I would not survive
the day when you guys
combine tat sh is wild nice it's good to
know that I have a great successor one
day in terms of yapping if I ever leave
then I I know I can put the crown on
sh's head and be not worried about my
legacy of yippity
Yap don't cry
cuz Big Girls Don't Cry and you're a big
girl aren't
you I know you
are carry on the
Yap okay we shall Read Super chats
because I'm excited that um this is a
short
stream we shall take advantage of that
cuz there's going to be long streams on
the way
[Music]
again oh also I kind of I kind of have
to record something I just
realized I'm probably going to record
that after the
[Music]
stream I have recording
deadline which I think was either today
or
yesterday it's it's
okay did you make that no I didn't make
it
yet I can make it
quickly
[Music]
um I can make it
now at this very
moment so I said
Friday it's Friday
Friday here's another appointment made
by
me Friday is oh yeah the the 5th
right uh yeah should be
[Music]
good I'm surprised I'm not blocked from
the system
yet okay and he done appointment has
been
made can't wait to hear it got cancel no
no
tomorrow
tomorrow I
shall write the thing and then before my
appointment I'll go out and print it at
some print
shop yeah
okay what is this cute just saw
something on Twitter I'm a ghost did you
see the ghost the froggy waa not froggy
waa but like I wish I could save gifts
directly easier
on uh
Twitter yeah the hoodie ghost is so cute
I I'll retweet
it you can see it on my Twitter
Cape
ghost that's so
cute okay uh super so I finished the
blah blah
[Music]
blah
S stand back she's frogging reveals
okay thank you I uh I'm going to pull it
up stand back she's
frogging
okay let me change bgm although this was
this was a pretty good one
for this situation wasn't
it [\h__\h]
loud I really like this
one this one is so
Zelda love it
[Music]
wait to go back
no it helped it did didn't it no FS
bgm sounds more like Pokemon to me
[Music]
whatever
h i I lost my WB GM I don't know where
it
is it's somewhere but I don't
know where
[Music]
exactly we're going to read these Super
Chat wait let me get rid of
[Music]
this
okay what find it yeah okay don't worry
I'll find it it is somewhere on my
PC oh yeah and it's also on
[Music]
YouTube and oh Al probably somewhere on
a
Drive
py
PA for the pinky this is kfp ct7567
calling all remaining K
loyalists the frog has breached
containment I repeat the frog has
breached containment this is not a drill
do not engage the frog on your own for
without tension we cannot be reviewed
you mean revived
right thank you I saw couple of kada
loyalists so to say that kept on
believing in
me and wanting me to come back I I've
noticed I have registered that uh in my
brain don't worry I was quite delighted
but uh it really sweet you probably
learned from the happenings of last
year always believe in the Wawa we had
to act like we like the Frog yeah yeah
sure sure sure it was just an act of
course I never gave up hope no matter
what the frog says what does the frog
[Music]
say explosion last year was so
funny I could have done that again but I
was lazy
mhm I was uh gone that week sure sure
uhhuh uhhuh Christina snitched last year
yeah she did some snitching
I was in Japan so I missed all the Frog
streams oh my god oh
okay welcome back you're welcome to
watch the V
still it's okay because the you know all
the views you know it's my channel again
so it will go to me all the proceeds
will go to
[Music]
me one mom sentence for absolutely
nothing I don't know if it was really
nothing you must have supported froggy
waa
when you shouldn't
[Music]
have I'm going to GA earnings
yeah and I'm going to write down every
name who sent a Super Chat supportive of
froga huh every name and I'll write it
in my death note just
kidding oh you know you know I got my I
got the the merch where uh it's like you
know that little notebook that I made
with the pen the Wawa notebook the small
one it was like what do I use it for
what if I just menacingly
write you guys' names in
there and just with no
[Music]
comment I'm just to fill it with your
name we'll see what
happens how
terrifying I need my ears to listen to
you o you know what I mean it's worse
than
that the fry
note who's up next but there's so many
of you guys who are already
[Music]
fried no did not listen no no
no I'm sure it's fire
my notebook is a cookbook
wow so
versatile space waterful thank you for
the red super chat K it might be froggy
waa week but this Super Chat is all for
my osih waa cuz I'm now a 2-year member
and I've been reborn as a Fenix chicken
to celebrate may I get an employee
number please six and 12 are open still
oh you want one of the smaller numbers
huh could you give me one of those
please H number 12 it is congratulations
I'm surprised you keep track I guess you
looked at the list there's many lists at
kfp it
seems you guys are so
[Music]
organized I did nice yeah the 12 shall
be yours congratulations thank you for
two years of support and thank you for
obviously staying loyal in that Super
Chat to me but at this point froggy waa
didn't really make an interest yet so
this is still all forgivable I can
[Music]
forgive you're not the only one with
have folder we have a list
too yeah but do you have a
folder a list is nice but do you have a
folder I'm sure some of you guys have
folders for like my members wallpapers
and all
that well in in fact I do well actually
in fact yes I
do yes I do
yeah I guess you do I guess you
[Music]
do what do you mean you have a homework
folder with homework under exclamation
not the quotation
marks what are you hiding in that
homework
[Music]
folder I know what's up
horny bnk thanks
SP much much love to you for your
loyalty it has been
acknowledged until a couple more years
shall we go take a 47 R and Hood D for
the pinky I'm night chicken now it's
crazy to think it's been 3 years since I
joined kfp shees it's such a big part of
my life now
[Music]
it makes me happier than I've ever been
here's some more time spent with my
favorite I mean Phoenix
Wario oh man yeah it's it's a huge part
of my life obviously but if you say it's
a big part of your life I'm very
flattered I'm happy but don't just
saying don't let it like overtake your
whole life like um I think that can be
harmful to yourself but as long as it's
like in a
healthy um
boundary and it makes you feel good not
like yeah depressed or whatever negative
in any
way then it's good you know
yeah look at me I'm the sanest
kfp as long as like you know I don't
make you feel bad then that's good and
yeah as long as you feel happy you
know need to have a good balance too
don't uh like how to say what's the
word
neglect other parts of your life like I
do I neglect other things way too much
I'm happy when I'm not Reliant that's
good that's really good but even I can't
[\h__\h] help but neglect so much
that that is not related to whole life
like that's so
sad it's really
difficult
yeah always be responsible with the w
consumption but uh on the other hand
watch everything and watch only
me watch watch
only watch watch only
[Music]
I responsible chicken I enjoy watching
you when I work yeah so many of you guys
watch me when I work I'm so lucky to
have you guys who are able to watch
while you're working that's like my
biggest fan base like of live viewers
like I would say like 80% watch me while
they're working let's see let's see
besides on the weekend let's make a poll
a poll a Paul poll let's make a poll
[Music]
um I guess this would probably only be
mostly na
viewers apply to na viewers mostly
European viewers and and and yeah
anything but and day probably this
doesn't apply to but that's okay um do
you do you do you do you say watch me
while you
[Music]
work except for days
off and yes
no
or I don't have a
job
slash I um a student
[Music]
start it's called freelance that's a
job that's a job like if you're
freelance you work from home and do like
whatever coding or drawing or whatever
and watch me I think that's yeah that's
work even though it's a lot easier I
would say to watch from home while
you're working than watch from like an
office or whatever while you're
working wow there's so much yes holy
[\h__\h] 60%
guys yeah that's I feel like with other
Ian members who stream during prime time
this would not be the case cuz obviously
like during Prime Time most people don't
work they're at home chilling just cuz I
always stream at this
[Music]
time it's a big shame as a fellow EU oh
it's not a
shame I usually stream when you probably
aren't working
anyway unless you're like a evening
night shift kind of
person it's late at night yeah this is
mostly like talking about
na I guess this is also what you got to
consider a lot of the 177% and 25% of no
and I don't have a job SL I'm a student
a lot of them are possibly not
na so damn
if if this poll was only for na people
I'm sure the 60% would be even higher
[Music]
I'm EU and I watch you on the job oh
thank you I'm in Asia but work for na
time oh maybe from
home you're NE in community for Vault
gang my beloved W gang W gang I guess
there's some people who might be
watching a VOD also while they're
working just because they're they are
bored at work and they need to catch up
with my vods
but I still don't stream while they're
working it's just Vault
time not
hold I sometimes watch BS at work there
you
[Music]
go oh the big hurdle is staying
awake skill issue my talent I can see if
possible during
breaks what do you work in the evening
or what
you're sounding like narissa more and
more what what what
part W on demand I like that I like
that I like that I need to use that for
[Music]
something wait we can actually call our
vods from now on instead
WS vs are just W on the end because
that's what it is
W
gang that's so
cute okay continuing super
[Music]
chats thank you Rowan
Hood W
[Music]
gang than
you you really like froggy waa I know
you always talk about froggy Wawa in the
preet froan Frog thank you soon ulti
frog thank you soon Elsie hoopen thank
you soon eating Mike Tyson's ass than
Michael H D Astro KF gate agent D for
the res chat oh my God your purp so cute
W I want to say thanks for being such a
bright flame that helped me get through
some rough spots in the past few years
it's been near three years now since my
no you cocka burp passed away and you
read my akas Ula song maker oh man
that's a long time ago I hope to show
new Birds soon I hope so too show me new
Birds
did you know I was like on a bird
watching uh uh
binge like a little while ago where I
was watching parrots and
[\h__\h] I was watching so many I can only
imagine this must have been part of your
life you got to get back to
that get yourself a nice
bird a bird for a bird AKA you're the
bird that the bird is for
cuz you're a chicken yeah go get
yourself a bird do you want to get a
cocka teal again or do you want to get a
different kind of bird what's the
plan I'm watching her I'm your bird you
are the nice thank
you when I watch more bird throw glasses
off the shelves that's like the best
content ever teal I think so again same
type of bird not a not I guess you
really found a liking in them they
they're really silly
they do be really
silly and I guess like maybe easier to
take care of than the parrot for example
parrot seem kind of like you need to
train their brains keep them busy and
they're big so
big king of the pr what the [\h__\h] you're
welcome I'm I'm glad if I can maybe like
distract you or change your um like
where your mind is
uh get it off of something that's nice I
hope she's okay hope your mommy is okay
watching you while my parrot sleeping on
my leg what right now you have a parrot
sleeping on your
leg are you sure it's alive poke it poke
it poke
[Music]
it
cute I wish my cat slept on my leg
thank you w you're welcome show me
pictures what you waiting for go get
that
BB don't poke it let it sleep no don't
poke the par no poke it poke it poke
it I'd sleep on your leg I'm sure you
would get out of
here per use his pick it's super
effective not poke yes yes poke the
parrot
[Music]
only one has the build for it ah is the
other one way too
[Music]
big d
d hey yo
[Music]
D
snitch you say you're so loyal and yet
you haven't redrawn all of the
membership badges into frogs for frog
week let's do that next
year all the membership Badges and all
chicken related emotes must be changed
into frogs too yeah I will I was
thinking about it like in the middle of
frog week and I thought like ah now it's
too late late I should have done that
from the
beginning but at least one frog froggy
waa emote would be nice although like
really I don't think she comes up that
much during normal days so it should
just be like froggy waa as an emote
that's usable in any situation like with
an emotion that comes up
anyway it could be something with the
tongue p p I don't know how to use but
could be like a te
P do I have a te P kind of face
emote let me
check no I don't think I I don't think I
do I have like a wink that could be like
that
yeah with the
gun but for that we have the threatening
CI with the knife I guess
yeah Wing's the
[Music]
closest we could replace the nine and
make something new out of it like
there's still some emotes where I feel
like we don't necessarily need
them could be a pedal pedal yeah
maybe no
no
m m
need to find some inspiration what it
could be but
[Music]
uh oh like
that you you want one like that
oh I guess that would be something we
don't really have but what does that
even convey that
[Music]
face no I'm not looking for things I can
replace now I'm looking for an
idea while with gun would be funny I
guess so but
um the hello is all yeah yeah yeah yeah
I don't I'm not looking for things I can
replace okay I already have something
m a smug
[Music]
face I guess
yeah what does a smug face look
like like this kind
[Music]
of I'll make all the German chickens
badges for the totally not real real
German
channel oh that will never happen we
don't need that I don't need
[Music]
that I mean if you want to do
it anyway back to Super
chats I could be done by
now thank you Astro Mah Jackson FB than
you soon Avenged me thank you soon Cruz
than you soon spank it spank what the
[\h__\h] spank kfp beheim why you make your
name more complicated is is it because
cie complained that you put kfp in your
name but not beat or so did Callie
complain your name is just getting
really [\h__\h] busy and
cluttered spanking
time has she got to you to your
brain as she influenced you are you here
spankenheimer
[Music]
are you here I don't see
you all right what is this imag dream
you were going to meet bman Jaan but you
haven't talked about it yet I was just
wondering if you were planning to at
some point or keep it private either way
it's fine um I did I say this before I
feel like it's um like weird uh I needed
to find a point where I could how to say
face it out to talk about
pomu I discussed this with her too
because pomu seized to exist kind of
right and I need to phas that out you
know to possibly talk about someone else
you know
but um but yeah uh I don't think there's
much to talk about I met her we had
fun m
uh she was cute
uh we had fun we ate
food we did some unusual
stuff I brought
her to
a
event pleas BL
BL
yeah I'm met her like four days in a row
or
[Music]
so kind of
crazy did she bring you to a m Cafe no
no no no no no no no no no no I was
joking about that to her too but uh she
was like M cafes aren't even so much my
thing it's it's more like a different
kind of
Cafe so anyway ski scoop that
um
yeah it's it's difficult to talk about
anything we did or her now okay so let's
just like you
know
yeah uh wait so spankenheimer
[Music]
spank I don't see him around in the chat
oh wait oh no
[Music]
yeah we met and we had a great time oh
it was really
um full circle moment in many
ways yeah where the [\h__\h] where the [\h__\h]
are you you're always
here maybe he can't Tye because cat is
laying on his hands that might be that's
really realistic with spank and H
you might not be able to type
[Music]
anything or stuck in the meeting I guess
so okay that's okay you'll explain
yourself to me eventually I'm sure
promise you won't tell Kiwa but frog is
my Oshi if only frog had cat
ears wow but the thing is you're saying
that in the Stream where I was still
mostly
K you little [\h__\h]
spanking you deserve some
spanking ideally with the froggy waa bug
um
the
The Eliminator Contraption which is uh
swatter fly water thank
you thank you I'm
Tracy oh what happened to your profile
picture h H
forg indeed
forg or or or shall I say
gor
gorf
Thea
AG Mike the master sword master link cat
ah it's the dude right you didn't just
use the profile picture if you're not
the dude the dude is in my chat
link cat wait link cat is a member for a
long
time wait the the TOA TOA Senpai fan
that uh became a little bit of a meme
um I didn't no I had the honor of having
a
celebrity as one of my own as well wow
thank you I'm I'm
flattered seems to not be here right now
but
uh greetings to
you you were one one person that really
stood out to me besides kfp in the
audience you were behind him at the
fence what the [\h__\h] there's like so many
seats how does this happen he just oh
wait what the [\h__\h] I haven't really seen
this guy around he must be new or
something yeah like what the [\h__\h] 42
mths what the
[\h__\h] I didn't know you're that person
[Music]
now you have a great picture to use as
your profile picture isn't that
amazing you don't have to pay a
professional photographer to get to go
get your portraits taken no you got one
for free from the
Fest damn thank you I hope you will one
day scream like this about me as well I
mean you may maybe already
did maybe already you probably already
did do you have the same passion for me
hm I
[Music]
wonder where is where is the passion
where's the
passion he paid for Fest yeah but it
wasn't for the purpose of getting a
picture so what a deal he got the free
picture VI let's
go oh damn let's go let's go passion
passion fruit let's go the quos artist
than for the pinky [\h__\h] you wa I promise
to remind you about the bug candy store
when you returned with Grasshopper
lollipops and chocolate covered
scorpions what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about and finally the plushy what what
what I promis to remind you about the
bug candy store like an IRL one what
when you returned with Grasshopper
lollipops and chocolate
color are you talking about like I
wanted to do a stream like this for next
frog week and I asked you guys to remind
me of that where would
eat grasshopper lollipops I I mean I
could have possibly said that yeah yeah
did I want to do that [\h__\h] I damn it I
I'm reading these super chats after frog
week it's too late
now froggy said that who knows how
serious frogy waa was about that I'm not
sure about
that thank God thank God I didn't get
reminded about this before I made the
schedule and all that thank God I did
not want to be on the the pressure of
having to live up to those
[Music]
promises thank God I'm out of
this frog week is over I'm
safe J SW D maybe next time bug snackbox
reveiew he said that actually is a great
idea holy [\h__\h] like several not just
those two Treats but several bug
treats I call it the bug snack box
reveal we already have so many great
ideas don't we oh way waiting
me oh my God oh my God
what what this is the first time I get
raided by AI Sanji
member I feel like it is thank you oh my
God I appreciate it the waiters for from
whu
[Music]
welcome whu was so
nice whu was so nice all the girls were
so nice to me and I was nice to
them
wayu
wayu we have like
similar like M food
[Music]
taboos at least when it comes to like
Yakiniku yeah so I think she took me as
a as a reference if I say I I don't
really like that because this is this
and that she trusted me about that okay
okay M I see I was like I think you
would like this instead yeah no tongue
no inner test tongue test intestines and
stuff like
Dad yeah and raw meat they gave us like
this raw meat and I ate it and it was
like it was it's like um what do you
call the raw beef uh beef Tatar we have
that here in Europe
too and I ate it before but I just don't
I I can eat it but I don't really see
the point because it's like there was
really no flavor to
[Music]
it I can understand it
yeah but I I knew I knew we were going
to get in trouble maybe you guys heard
the story already but we kind of got
like the staff was a bit angry at
us and I knew that would happen I knew
it would happen I I told the girls like
oh no oh
no if the if the the waiter comes in and
sees
this we will be met with disgust in
their face
cuz yeah you we shouldn't do this I
understand you want to do it and I also
want to do it like Grill the raw meat
that they intended for us to eat raw
Grill it on the
grill oh this was like in in other yako
places you have more freedom and you
know but this was like a
[Music]
more how to say like a more fancy place
so they come in and explain everything
really Det detailed and tell you what to
do with it and so on yeah
but you
know I I I I I knew like they intend you
to eat it that way so you shouldn't eat
it
differently um but yeah we just did some
gajen
thing and the thing is like it was
really hard to grill it because it was
cut up into little little tiny tiny tiny
pieces like it was um like made for a
hamburger like you're going to grill a
hamburger you form it into a hamburger
and Grill it like that but no you eat it
raw but when you place it on the grill
it like stops sticking together
and like the grill had these little
[Music]
um holes so to
say where the heat was going through and
you can grill meat on there that is in
one piece but these tiny tiny tiny baby
pieces you could you can't grill it on
there so we like grilled it kind of on
the very very side on the edge of the
grill and I was like okay okay guys
Grill it but like get rid of it really
fast so that the waiter ideally doesn't
see what we have on the grill here okay
just get it over with us and they still
saw it though and the waiter was
appalled like what the [\h__\h] are you guys
doing please don't do that and I'm like
yes so so so so
so no no comment I knew it was going to
happen I also I I tried eating a raw and
it's like
yeah but it's way better when it's
grilled so I also was guilty of doing it
but I got rid of it really fast from the
grill I was like really stressed
out I remember I'm I doing that
too um long long time ago remember that
team
yellow uh after Sports Fest that
Yakiniku where I uh was there with Amit
and love Japan's members and so on and
uh yeah we got some stuff that you were
supposed to eat raw uh cuz the Japanese
members ordered it and I I told am you
should eat a raw but like she grilled it
and I'm like okay like like you know
it's not so common to eat raw beef or
whatever in other places it's not as
popular you know and Amma didn't get in
trouble because the waiters weren't all
the time watching us spying on
us am said [\h__\h] that yeah do this the am
way I'm like nah and honestly I feel it
I feel
it TR me all you want I ain't eating raw
meat I even had
um basashi raw horse meat before
and I mean the flavor and everything is
fine but I just had really trouble
eating it because the piece maybe it was
the one piece I had the one piece is
real but it was really chewy and that
was difficult for me just couldn't chew
it down and I really don't like it when
when food is like
[Music]
that and the thought of eating raw meat
is just not H raw no raw meat yes and
also uh horse meat isn't so common in
Austria there's some horse lebaka
semma but I avoid that because I don't I
don't know how I feel about eating
horses but in the end it's just a
cultural thing like if if eating horse
is normal in the country where you grow
up in then it's normal and then it's
nothing weird to you but then in other
countries it's less common so it's weird
to you and you want to avoid it you know
in some places it's way more normal and
and for you it's
like how how could you eat this
animal well it is what it
is horse girl M have you tried alligator
me yeah yeah I think one time I ate um
in like a big
Buffet kind of style restaurant
[Music]
oh I think in Japan I wouldn't be
worried about getting food poisoning for
raw meat it can always happen but in
Japan I think they're uh really proper
and take care and everything so I
wouldn't be so wear it there same with
their eggs I hear you know the reason
why they can make so much stuff with raw
eggs is they're their eggs are just
superia I don't
know for raw food yeah they're strict
with the
quality SOA
now I recently ate Koba beef in Japan
and I think I've been spoiled for
life well the thing is like I also
before I ate kobba beef before I thought
uh also it was like extremely luxurious
and oh so rare and all that but then I
realized after eating it a few times
that there's
um like different ranks within the Koba
beef as well they're all great but you
don't have to go for the most expensive
one even the the lower rank ones are
really yummy too and not as expensive
and you can find it all
over but I'm I I I would say it's worth
like experiencing the highest rank Kua
beef like once in your life at least and
like a I I recommend to do it in a t bu
[\h__\h] restaurant where you sit on the
grill not on the grill ideally in front
of the
grill and uh a chef prepares it for you
and then just eat it with
[Music]
salt yum
yummy yeah Ro you
beef it's
O if you're on the grill you might be a
cow yeah be careful if you find yourself
on the grill something's wrong with this
situation be careful to
observe
[Music]
calmly I'm getting hungry
too what do you do on this channel I
just
joined
what what your name's familiar to me are
you sure you you're new here what do you
mean what do you do on this channel I
play game and I sing song and I
[Music]
talk I Yap okay moving on oh my God
please J D he sat 99 D Bruce J Lee D Ry
Moonlight D for the pinky we should add
the frog eating art for our battles in
kfp which one let's start getting some
gloves for our wings I don't want more
accidents in the training grounds what
are you talking
[Music]
about gloves for you I mean yeah if you
want to do that I'm not going to pay for
it good
luck good luck funding that boohoo 723
Danish delar danan Studio raping for the
pink Ry Moonlight than for the pinky as
well again
what the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
[Laughter]
this what what no what did they make me
read what
do they make me
R Oh you talked about that Lake and I
remember the child it's a childhood song
what is a tongue dresser what why are
you guys so no no
PO I agree but I also don't understand
yeah I don't I only remember the tit
Kaka
frog pretty nasty song I see
nothing bad don't worry
okay deep L
[Music]
okay transplate
ESP
[Music]
ESP I should
uh at Lake tiaka there was an old woman
pooping and
oh yeah okay what the [\h__\h] this a song
why why why
why okay never mind moving on tasty boy
thank you for the red chat tasty
boy what happened to you Flappy
boy oh cuz you're tasty to froggy
waa you're not just a flappy boy to are
you you're tasty
boy I see what you did there that's cute
thank you for the RP
Chad that's cute we got to support vas
in all manifestations no matter how tiny
slimy bratty Rascal trigger happy Looney
butterfly consuming or stinky they might
be as long as they are cute so let's go
tadpole gang we're the meanest and
greenest our trip is the
realest oh you're so cute I love you man
that's so cute thank you Flappy boy
thank you for the red super chat thank
you for supporting me in all forms but
um froggy Wawa cannot be
supported how dare you back to your
usual ways okay take off that frog cap
take it off immediately return to Orange
reject Green Return to Orange reject
green yeah she killed
wow why would you support someone like
that H what does that say about
you Al so you were in
danger your life was in
danger well I'm green now
yeah don't put me into difficult
situations where I can't give you a good
[Music]
answer thank you tasty boy Dan Al Dan
yeah finally I'm done really
unnecessarily long what the [\h__\h] going
to read the the kfp
101 Super Chat
P um really quickly it's just a few
Jacob 47 NE he starts a 99 Dan Sabin de
Dan M Dan and maxel the first Dan that
new video is so good K carrat learning
MMD really really wow
Unleashed his talent even more
more
[Music]
yeah chy chy wrote to me like
oh maybe you don't need me anymore and
I'm like no don't worry
chy chy is scared for his
life no chy you're you're a freaking
goat
okay I I ask for different things from
you too don't worry you're still in
demand Jak you're both in
demand yeah I'm going to really
quickly um attempt to read through the
Frog Adventure super
[Music]
chats thanks for the membership
welcome so cute the thumnail is so
[\h__\h] cute I
can't I like this art so
much that's the one thing I'll give to
her she's [\h__\h] cute this this froggy
waa you have this as a sticker oh my God
this is the perfect thing to stick onto
things cuz it's like
tape you have to stick it
everywhere that's a perfect sticker this
is so genius making a sticker where
there's tape involved I might steal that
idea
someday it's amazing ja 47 Studio thanks
for the pinky
thank you so sweet of you thank you for
the Green Love FR Mandalore
[Music]
than but no please no frog legs no not
for me also not for froggy waa froggy
waa is not the type of animal to eat her
own kind she just like gummy
worms oh thank you 26 months come
down eating my T
as phantom3 56 looking for the
[Music]
top
thank
[Music]
Moog pink curse you foul and
fibian I returned from my real life job
to find my dear tento replac I will not
rest until she's returned to us
oh see see guys see how Nathan cotton
stayed
loyal why did you
not
H you were too
weak you gave into the
cuteness and the water pistol of a
little tiny frog
[Music]
a gun to your head we had this we had
this before it's a freaking water pistol
I mean yeah she she she may have water
boarded me into a coma with
it damn
it damn it it is dangerous okay whatever
T po D monkey Sanchez danar D froggy
fellow d things are just not adding up
are
[Music]
they tell starbs to the pinky how does a
frog light a fire with
kosine oh what does a frog do for fun Ki
Oh my God amazing pellar where did you
get these jokes
from it's
amazing I like them Kies than soon thank
you ah the tap tap froggy
people let me look it
up cute oh my
God holy [\h__\h] it's so
cute oh my God it's pastel and like the
art style cute I like it super frog
Mario than
soon oh my God stand back he frogged
ziply thanks for the red super chat and
a pinky hey FR could you tell Ki that
I've been looping her performance
constantly after the Fest vs got
released out of prison I think it's my
favorite performance of the Fest by far
I can't wait for the song to get
released properly absolute Banger PS you
merch is super cute the blush is way too
adorable and triggers my cute aggression
pretty badly so I try to be gentle when
I finally get my hands on it thank you
cute aggression it's a real problem in
this generation and Society yes yes yes
many people struggle with cute
aggression every day on a day-to-day
[Music]
basis feel free to squeeze the Frog when
you feel symptoms of cute
aggression she's not alive thus you can
squeeze her as much as you
want it's a constant struggle it's
really hard for me
to bubuki was going crazy at laas today
on Twitter oh
really who my PC just
lagged
oopsy play sad Sparks
Alexa don't squeeze the Frog protect the
[Music]
Frog you can do
both no was
me okay I'll go download more r
[Music]
okay okay anyway thank you please so
much thank you so much yeah you don't
have to wait much longer it's finally
time let's go this
week y y let's go I'm so excited too
finally people seem to be excited about
it people seem to be waiting for it this
is perfect
yay finally wa I think six
single I think it's my sixth
single cuz uh pineapple was not a single
it was a album
song Let's go thank you
Tippy I am a
[Music]
they love l shaped like other oh wow
fishing for bull frogs I know you can do
that than space frog P cute thank you I
like to see your
variations of frog names putting frog
into your your
name I appreciate it for
blood I'm coming for blood Ty soon to
talk thanks pinky froggy right to O I
even refuse to renew membership just to
not be a chicken and embrace being 100%
pure
tadpole I know it's just a dream but for
me kfy now means keep froggy waa
permanently also try some someday is a
frog game oh okay oh my God keep Frogg
per that is kind of
crazy that might be what you guys are
trying to say this whole
time when you say kfp and when you post
in the kfp
hashtag oh that game I think I've seen
it
before that's pretty oh my God that is
pretty nostalgic wait that's a
frog you guys know this game Zuma Z ma
it's a frog in the middle and he shoots
like these balls I guess you want to
it's like uh those games where you want
to have several of the same color next
to each other for points M and then
eliminate
them yeah he he seems to be Spitting
Fire no I might be wrong
though Frogger yeah I was thinking about
Frogger about playing it um in frog week
I know it's up the classic but the
classic classic the non like fake
versions and so of it felt like uh I
don't know there wouldn't be it wouldn't
be a very long
stream it would be a really short stream
and also I didn't know uh I think I
would have had to
use a
PS3 I think that was that the the latest
console where I could have played like a
more classic Frogger on I don't
know I was just like whatever I have a
lot of other good frog games I know frog
and I would have liked to play that too
you know I was really addicted to it as
a child I get it I get
it no but this way we still have games
in the future that we could play you
[Music]
know what do you mean PS3 has no games
what does that mean is that a meme
anyway where was I ult
than that was the end of those super
chats and I think I'm going to end it
there because I might just uh go grab
some food really quickly before it gets
too
[Music]
late including Tales of yeah yeah yeah
there are Tales of games on PS3 yeah
yeah yeah it was a meme from the early
PS3 days ah they just just didn't
release too many games
huh it do be like that sometimes M the
other day I saw saw like a comment about
like when I was just watching
videos about stuff I saw a comment where
it was like oh my God Nintendo is lucky
that uh Playstation or Sony hasn't tried
to make another handheld console like
the PSP in a long time because if they
tried with how good their Hardware
usually
is they would be kind of insane
competition
the yeah they're they're kind of Lucky
nintend is lucky that Sony is focusing
on like you know at home consoles the VA
exist I don't know I'm not a VA hater
also because I just didn't use it much I
I mostly had a PSP and I didn't get a v
until like like two years ago or so for
the sake of playing a tailes off game
didn't have a problem with
it Steam decks would ruin the VA but I
think place it Sony could perfect that
concept they could try again I I would
like them to to try
again but do we really need it when
there's a Nintendo only if they manag to
get better Hardware into their handheld
only then it would be worth it otherwise
let's just leave it to Nintendo I really
like the switch a lot of people love the
switch it's just genius having both in
one and yeah it may may have relatively
weak Hardware but let's see let's see
how that
changes if they bring out a
[Music]
successor yeah they have great
exclusives too oh
100% okay I'll see you guys tomorrow in
the member stream
um it will it will be something don't
worry you don't have to prepare anything
for it I think whatever it will be I
have an idea but I don't want to get
your hopes up yet so I'm not going to
say it I'll see you tomorrow okay for
the member stream thank you for having
um a good time with me listening to my
tangents even though it was really
uncomfortable and embarrassing for
me I will now go bath in shame and eat
something let's forget about everything
I said in this stream forever forever
forever never ever ever ever
ever yeah and in Germany we say
no thank you for
[Music]
watching we
bye-bye bye-bye have a nice day love
you take your meds
[Music]
oh wait let me see what are they
playing uh what's MAA doing what's
playing Holo X break ma is that a
this oh yeah was on archive
[Music]
I know should I I can't
decide okay Eclipse
time wait if it shows up it okay