foreign
[Music]
hello YouTube music weekend
I'm a phoenix who plays games with a
passion especially RPG games and
adventure games and party games yeah but
I also do sing a lot so today I want you
to listen to a couple of my original
songs okay
yeah
YouTube music weekend
um
yeah I have a couple of original songs
and you'll hopefully enjoy them very
much today so here at this digital
native stage on the YouTube music
weekend I will perform them for you
especially so enjoy and I'll bring you
through this little journey of kiwawa
discography disco disco
oh
[Music]
my God memories
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
[Music]
foreign
don't break I will never give up don't
break honeymoon
[Music]
I've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray if I go wrong what awaits me
[Music]
could you tell me please where I need to
go
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
yay
thank you that was
Alpha remix if you want to listen to the
proper version it's up on my YouTube
channel too let's go to the next song
lying down on the door they died and you
don't know don't know don't know what to
do hard to tell what's wrong what's
right yes or no don't know don't know
what to do
[Music]
it away don't forget don't forget what I
said
get out of your head life is only what
you make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
it let's get to it everybody's gonna
know your name
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
Don't Be Afraid just your heart keep
your head
[Applause]
[Music]
even when the place
[Applause]
[Music]
so don't be afraid just
like imagine
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
did you enjoy it
it's quite the bear quite the buff I
know I know but we're not done yet yes
this song was produced by Kira and the
next one
hustle is produced by Akita and Kiana
the dream combination here we go moving
to the next stage
oh yeah
I don't want to stop it yet playing
Russian roulette Yeah Boy as soon as I
saw you I knew it I got now got me
there's something special about you you
I know it's true
you know it I just can't resist you your
eyes are like a spell that I can break
through and that should scare me but I
don't know baby
[Music]
love hate all the same if you'll know
play that game imma look up up inside no
I can bite the feeling and I won't try
all the same if you know play the game
baby you'll decide if you want me to set
it up
[Music]
you got it cause lust is like attacks
and the way pain is so common your
problem I can solve it I'm Just a Fool
in Love know that this one then I'll cry
so you can save me I'm in two team and I
love the rice yeah I just can't resist
you feel as like a spell that I can
break through and that should scare me
but I don't know baby
eating me
you'll let me
let me love hate all the same if you
know by that game as I know I can bite
the feeling and I won't try all the same
if you'll know play the game baby you'll
decide
[Music]
got me breathless
night and day how can something so wrong
be making me feel so right
[Music]
I'm always coming back to you
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
I do
[Music]
hey
do you like it
thank you for enjoying my part of the
YouTube music weekend
thank you for listening I have a couple
more original songs that
um I think you would enjoy but this is
all I can do in 15 minutes pretty much
I'd really try to squeeze it in there
well if you want to hear more or see
more be sure to subscribe to my channel
to not miss anything and yeah thank you
for coming to listen also to all the kfp
members and all the newcomers who
haven't seen me before thank you very
much and have a nice YouTube music
weekend and in German we say
[Music]
and bye bye