[Music]
DET
H
[Music]
DET
OG
[Music]
DET
OG
[Music]
Oh
Ok
oh oh, is everyone here? Let's get together.
Ah, gathering, yes, gathering, ah, gathering, gathering, gathering, gathering, where,
hahahaha, Ah, Manekata, teacher, yes, teacher, no, not teacher, but not at all, yes, I just happened to be here. Are you all here? Is everyone there?  It
's all right, Mr. Wan, please take attendance. I
'll go then. I'll go from the white team's A.
Thank you very much for your space. I
'm Jako-senpai. Yes, I'm Hello. I
'm Tepa. Thank you very much. Ita-
tai.  Ii Ii Iru Nekanata-san wa
[Music]
Hamui-chan hai hai ah hai hai moomei cha yay hai ya nanai
tome
you
Kaikai Miame-chan Ame-
ame-chan
Okay, I'm going okay, okay, gogo,
gosh, the
members of Eko got confused on the phone call and turned into A.
Okay, okay, B's are heavens.
Choco-sensei, oh my goodness.
Rizu-chan is so cute,
please. Leader.  Yes, hello, I'm the leader ha
[Music]
Hello, yay, yay,
Dari, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, I'll do my best to flow up
[Music] I
'll do my best.
Kana, should I go? I think it's better to go. Ka-senpai is from today.
It's Raden-chan, but I'm a little behind her. I'm
sorry. My
junior, Goza, will be the second one.  I'm sorry, I
thought you came here to apologize, but I was
nervous about doing something like that, so what you said was correct,
and what Raden wrote was also a little confusing to me.
I'd like to cover it all, so I'd
like to ask for your help, but it seems like it
's gone, so uh, Raden-chan will be appearing in Holomen Hunting, but I'll be replacing her for a bit.  The battle is
still a secret, so I guess it's a secret what will happen
next. I'm looking forward to it. Will you be
wandering around alone? Will someone come?  I
don't know why, but I want to see him working hard all by himself. Maybe he's filming everyone by himself. He's doing his best, hitting me, hitting me. There
's a spy here.
What's going on here? It's really messed up.  There
's a matsuri senior who's acting like a spy.
There's a spy. He's leaving. He's
here in the waiting room of the white team. It's a classroom.
Everyone's waiting right now. Hey, hey, come on. It's
nice to have a competition. No one's here.  I'm here, mind
But it looks like we're all
gathered together. It's
great. We're glad. We're all there. We're all gathered
together. There's a sign that says, oh, that's
it. We can't put it anywhere, but we ca
n't open it.  I want to become a number. Is
this what it is
? How do I use it? It's
like holding a two-handed sign.
[Music]
That's it.
Ru, Polo Polo came to scout. It
looks like everyone is here. Hey, I'm
going to scout a little bit. I wonder
if I'll go scouting. Red team. I
wonder how everyone is feeling now. Everyone seems to be having fun.
Oh,
there were
a lot of them. [Laughs] The Gozaru-san were getting into a lot of trouble with each other,
right? Kirlo was all Riguro-san. Oh
no,
you and I were holding a signboard in your left hand.  I
can't take it anymore, but I can't take it off,
even though the signboard might be on it all day today.It's a
big mess and I can't take it
off.It's gone, so I can't take it off.It's
not just good, it's true,
but I can't take it off.What is this?  It's too bad, everyone is fixed. Seriously, it's
too much, but is it okay to hold it in a competition?
No, I think the inventory reset is built into the signboard, so
when Gozaru is infected,
maybe he'll have to use his left hand all the time.
I wonder if it's okay from the knowledge of Minecraft Minecraft As one of the creators, it looks like I'm going to be
debugged again.I'll do my best and do my best
as a debugger at the Minecraft Sports Day.I'll do my best this time as well.  It's
not
complicated, it's not
possible, it's not, it's true, it's true, it's terrible, it's true.Is it
true that there's a new Minecraft game?
Amazing, I'll see what happens in the next ad.  I can
hear it, but I can
hear it. I don't know. It's dangerous. We
don't know where the camera is, but
hey, I can hear it. I can hear it,
but it sounds like a senior. It's a misunderstanding.
What's the internal broadcast? Okay, then.  I
think I'm going to go. So
everyone, please. Aba is the first entrance announcement.
Everyone who came to the venue is not red, so I
'm going to go, I'm going to go, right? It's white. It's white.
That's Merle Meruru is red Merle is good
Merle
This is my friend Mel That's right there That's right there
Merle Merle
Meruru That's it
That group said you can go from this way too That group has
fallen I'm
coming from here now
[Music]
Tosasa-san is again this year.  Hey, you're a genius. We
're lined up beautifully. Let's do
our best. Let's do our best. Let's line up here.
Let's join together. Here with your mother.
Let's go here.
Can we stand together in 11 rows?
Yes, then please come in.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] Masu's most
powerful white.  Okay, lastly,
can I have the yellow group's mother call for me?
Next,
Mom, okay, you're hiding,
too. I'm in
trouble. Wait, it's
me, but I just realized it's me. I'm
sure the camera will follow this route.  nothing was prepared
Shinden White is
too serious.
[Laughs] Is
that what you mean
? There wasn't a white sign, so why don't you even hold the sign?  I would like to
ask you to give your greetings from the Sports Day. Hello
everyone! Nya.
Wow,
thank you so much for coming here. Thank you very much for taking the time out of your busy schedules.  I
'm sure the seniors and juniors helped each other and worked hard to practice until today, but since
today is the real event, I hope everyone will give it their all and
come out victorious.First
of all, everyone should have
fun and  Our goal is to win.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Thank you very much for your support
today. Thank you very much for your wishes.
Next, we received a message from Mr. Yago, the president of Cover Co., Ltd.
Yes, please look here.Thank
you for your hard work, everyone watching.It's a
sports day on the hippo table.When you say sports day, it's about the neck.It's
not in the program.I hope you're looking at it properly.In
today's sports day, we cooperated with each other.
Let's encourage each other and fight bravely until the end.
And as always,
thank you very much. Thank you very much
. Thank you very much. I hope you will pay attention to my efforts and support me.
Please take care of all the members.With this,
I will give my opening remarks.No
, I am injured.
[Music]
Mr. Kuoai Sensei Saruru, Channel 1.
Please come first. Keep up the good work.
Do your best.  That
's good. My
general outline is
definitely. Please, please,
please. Please do it. Please do your best. Thank you very much. I have a
problem with my ears. Goe
Shirogumi
[Music]  It's
okay, it's okay, big, it's
coming, it's coming, it's
dangerous, I can't hear what the teacher is saying. It's dangerous,
Sumo Hey,
good, good. I
think I can do it. Do your best. Good luck. Is it alright if I ask you to be the player-sensei?
Yes,
then,
please, Mr.  As players of Hololive, we have practiced good
sportsmanship as Hololive members.Do you
use the word Sensei Dodo?
November 4, 2023Representative of the Red TeamWhat is the virtue of the White Team?
Representative A Yellow Representative Haspels
[Applause]
[Music]
Yes, it's okay to say it. Thank you. I'm sorry for throwing bread.
Thank you very much. I
was shining.
[Music] This
is a special motion.  I'm
sorry for the inconvenience, but the
7 buff white team escapees are
contestants from each group. Please check the white group's contestant channel.
The sound quality of the rear sports day is  It's
a little bit real, so it's
not yet N I guess it's the first game of Home Hunting, only the people who enter the first game are like that. I see. I see. I'm going to the white team contestant's channel, so uh, American.  Chankaelanelisa
Yes,
yes Go,
please do your best Team
Fight
Player Channel No
[Music]
Good luck Good
luck Good luck Good luck Good
luck Good luck Good luck to you
[laughter]
I'm confused about both Japanese and English,
so I'm the third one.
Yes, that's right. Yes, that's cool. Yes, that's
cool. Yes, all three of us made it. I wonder if
we can all be runaways.
It's no good, but I'm not sure how complete it is. The white team is hunters, so the white team looks at the beginning. Ah, it looks like a hunter, so it looks like a grouper. I'm going to go and cheer for them. It's okay if we support each other.  fugitive  I wonder
if there will be an announcement about what group this will start from.I wonder if there will be an
announcement.I wonder if it will be there.I wonder if it will be there.I wonder if it will be there.Everyone
except the hunter team, which is now check.
Or 2, so maybe we're not the
same Hunter team. So
when you say Hunter team, do you mean the three Hunters,
or the white group of Hunters?
Which frame do you mean? It's not us yet.
First of all, I wrote red at first, and the rest of me is a
fugitive, so I only need one entry.Then I can
go to the other side.Here,
can I press it?This is a hunter.I ca
n't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't, I can't enter  We're
doing a lot of work, but I'm not doing a lot of work. We're
pretty noisy, so we've already
entered. Well, we'd better enter.
That means it's probably already on its own.  That's
what I thought. At first, with the power of God, I was able to do so. It's
okay if you don't press the button. It's okay.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'll excuse Sade's announcement. Kairoha-san,
Roboko-san, Kiame-san, Anekata-san.
Mr. Yuchoko, Mr. Azuki, and Mr. Azuki, I
would like to ask the contestants' channel of the Eshirogumi group.Is it the
other way around?The way we move is the other way around, or maybe it's the other
way around.  It
's not because everyone is running away, but the broadcaster is moving. I see, it's
okay if the broadcaster moves to the contestant channel.
What number is it? It's the same place, the white contest
channel.
Sorry for the inconvenience.  I'm
staying here because I'm not happy, so I
'm against Acha and others
today.
[Laughs] It's
difficult, but if I hear this, I can do it.
Well, I understand it perfectly now.
Well, wait a minute.
What I mean by that is that the red team is the hunter at first, and the white team all run away. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, but everyone is a contestant.
Well then,
that's what the white team's hunting is.  In the case of , the infected person and the
hunter will probably be separated.That's
right.
It looks like it's a
bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of the way
For
example, if a person from the red group is a hunter and the hunter is from the white group,
they will be targeted and run away.  It's
like I'm going to roll up and go, oh, I'm going to click. I'm going to be caught with a rope, so even if I'm already caught, I want to run away as fast as I can. Oh, I'm going to be
put in a cage, so I'm going to be thrown in. So I'm going
to South Korea. I'm going to South Korea.
Unexpectedly, the back of the cage is a hiding place because it can't get
out.Oh yeah, I'm a little anti-Ah, no one.On
the other hand, I'm going to go to the wide side of the opposite side of the cage, so
who's behind the cage?  I don't have any  It's the
same behind the pillar of the swing.
There's something I'm a little concerned about. I wonder
if that's what the staff is talking about right now. I
'm watching the text channel, and the
7 escapees in the white group are contestants, so it's probably the 2nd one.  That's right,
but I guess it's better to go there, because Bai-
chan didn't call me that by name.That's
right, that's right.That's why the
people from both the first and second hunting competitions
went over there.  Maybe it's better?  I'm
having a bit of a hard time thinking about it. That one is
better than that, but I was also called 'Kan', but I guess they haven't conveyed that to me. Ah-chan's is like that.
Yeah, that's what I see. I feel like it's something like that.  I'll
probably ask the announcer for a second, please.Thank you very much.It seems like
there's something for Laren-chan.  Someone was
called out earlier, but I guess they're still
going ahead with the idea of Raden-chan joining in. I
have a feeling that's the case, right? That's right. If
that's the case, it's
only for people who aren't really hunters.  I feel like I have to be on this channel right now,
but Amichi
has the power of God, the power of God, the power of God.  I
just asked him about it. Thank
you very much. Thank you very much.  I don't think
so. I
guess there are some materials that I don't think were there right now, and I'm
reading this right now and it
says that even if you're not a contestant, you can probably do it.  It
says "except for the contestants from other teams,"
so that's it. That's the confusion. I'm so excited.
[Laughs]
Even though I'm so excited, the staff is inputting information. So it's
rattling, rattling,
rattling. I
guess it's either of us
today.  It's a bit of a long wait, so it
's scheduled to be around 9 o'clock, but there
's an atmosphere that says maybe we're not pushing, so it's a nice atmosphere.
There's a little bit of time, so let's each take a break and
save some energy. Some of us are hungry, so let's
eat and relax.
Yes, it's long, so
this is the best part of the sports day, isn't it? That's right, it's the best part of the
sports day.  It's difficult garbage, right? It's
big garbage. It's different.
Don't say that. It's like a book. No, it's a thrill. It's a
real thrill. That's why it says "real thrill."  The
battle that came is real real thrill real
thrill An's Daigo To begin with,
it's an AB channel, so it's in its current form.  It
's like you're going to go to the other side. You
can just ignore the diagonal. It's okay, it's not okay, it's not okay.
[Music]
Suddenly,
there are 9 people. That's about it.
Thank you, thank
you, thank you. Thank
you. Thank you.
Thank you.  Yes, that's
true. What will happen? The channels will be separated, but we'll
do it together. The voices will
start suddenly, suddenly, suddenly, suddenly, they
will come.
Rouora
Protect the men, protect the members, in the back
[Music]
Don't hide and wait, it's dangerous! No way, people are
watching your back. I
'm not an anti, either. Let's protect
Machi
-senpai. It's dangerous. [Music]
Na-chan, the title will change, the title will change, the title will change,
Now, I'm going to show you how high I am. I'm
squatting, and I'm going to put out a little bit of 149 cm, and
let me make a little mistake. It
's 149 or less.
What about people who fail at this? The
perfect person is 149 cm or less, so I'm a
small person who says I'm 149 cm tall. I'm
sure you're 149 cm
tall, which is amazing.  It's weird, it's weird, it's dangerous, it's scary, it's weird, it's
weird, it's
dangerous, it's like I'm confident that the little guy won't run away anymore, what should I do?  I do
n't want to be caught. How can I catch you? How can I
get caught? Who is it? But catch me, catch me, catch me, oh, I can
go. Can someone say I can go? Who can
I go? Chacha, I can go, me,
catch me.  Well, I failed,
and I was
killed in the blink of an eye, but I was like, ``Let's see, senpai'' here,
and I was like, ``I wonder who it was that caught me too, and it
's over.''  It's
true that Anya seems to be wrong.
It's an awkward crackle
. There's a book that says there are 6 people. Oh yeah, I
'm going. Oh, wait a minute.
6 yen isn't here. Excuse me. Those eyes are
white here.  To all those who ran away from the group,
please move to the voice chat where the white group ABB was originally located.Thank you for your
hard work.
Welcome bye bye
Biver Ooo
Aoi This is a cheerful support.  That's
right, let's support each other. I
wonder if it's okay for those who have been arrested to stay like this. They've been arrested and are still being arrested. They can't get out yet. They can't get out. [Music] Let's do it.
Oh, I can't do it.
Oh, it's South
Korea. It's South Korea. Oh, there's a guy there too. He might not be able to come out until the start. Why don't we stay? Shall we take a picture? It's South Korea, it's a country. It
's South Korea.
Thank you for the photo.  The picture is being taken in South Korea
. My face is chained up in the grass.
It's really nice here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, right here, right here, right, right, right, right, right, right there, right, that's nice, okay, let's go,"  The
jailbreak has been reset.
Escape, get out.
[Applause]
This is clearly what it's like. I
feel like I should show it to the listeners as well. It's the
best shot, but even if you wait, I'm a
degozaru.  It's so
spacious, it looks like it was created by the infection mat,
but that's true, but in the end there were only 6 people there.  Oh
yeah, if you want to make
a seat, it's
okay, shotaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It's dangerous, I made it myself I went to the yellow team I'm
doing something like that right now Katsu Is it
okay? I'm back.  I'm back, I
'm back, I'm back, I'm back, and there
was an interview, so it seems like I went to the second game, too. I
interviewed him.
[Laughs] I'm
just confused, it's okay, I'm fine. I
'm laughing so hard.  or  It's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
, yeah, I was worried, but from the way the speech bubbles were just now, it
sounded like I was talking, but it
was blurry.  Mu-
senpai is walking around blowing,
let's do it, let's do it, let's go
, let's do it, let's do it, Shirotame,
Chirotame Shiro team, Chishithimushiro team
Shiro Shiro Ah, since it's a white team hunt, that
means we're not runaways, right?
Yeah, that's right, I want to run away as
much as possible.
Please, let's move on to the next escape.
[Music]
We're a well-behaved team,
so we're a well-behaved team. That's right
. That's right. Everyone was nice.
The white rice was lined up in the most beautiful way, and the
white rice was lined up in the most beautiful way.  Is it
white clear
? Is clear white clear? Yes, it's clear,
but it's true.
There's a gathering of resident toys, so it's
dangerous. It's dangerous, so I
guess the theme is "do your best, do your best."
Debut is from 2021 to 22.
Now that I'm older and pretty recent, I can't
fit in this Hollow, I think it's barely in Locks.
2 That's right. I wonder
if it's up to Holos.
Rocks is really running away,
but Love English
's 3rd generation is also the ID of the 3rd generation of I.
3rd period Unki
is 2 upolu I see. It's summer of 2020. It's not
hard to find it. Even if I
know your name, it's hard to find it.
But, do your best, do your best.If you struggle, you'll want to be
caught.There are people who want to be caught.I want to be caught.I feel like I'm
being chased.I'm so
happy.  It's not
gone. There were
still people waiting around. It's
okay. Is it okay? Just catch everyone regardless. You can
go. If you can, there's probably at least one Bob.
Short
bu. I'll take what I get for now.  There's
another hair on me, go touch, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
No, no, it's good, Goro Kids.No,
no, it's good, I'm saying,
but I'm sure I'm not a kid,
but I feel like I'm going to join.  I
'm sure about you, Anya
has been captured. It's true, Anya. It's
a scratch. Oh, it's a scratch. It's not a big sister. It was a big sister. Hey, unlucky fishing. I'm curious about this. I'm curious about this, but I
wonder if it's going to go downhill.  Isn't that a kid? Isn't that a kid? If he's not a kid, he
's not a kid
. He's got boobs. He's in the frame of a woman who's scratched. He's
going to get in. It's over. It's over. He's got
no choice but to run away.  All we have
to do is run, all we have to do is run away.Yes, we can run away.That's right, let's run away, then me and the group will get caught and let's catch them all.Yes, let's catch them all.If you can't figure it out after putting everyone in, just put them all in.  It
was quite difficult, like the question was logical. It's not consciousness. It's interesting. It
seems that so and so thinks. Surprisingly, it was true.
[Music]
was excuse me.
Thank you, thank you, but it might have been a big deal, but it was
already there, so yeah, that's true
, that kind of thing happens
sometimes, it's just bad luck.Now that I think about it, when it comes to kids, what happens
to them?  I
think I'm definitely a kid.I think I probably
look like a kid.My
face is being looked at a lot.Hello.I
definitely want to know the answer.I only know the senior from earlier.I
want to see a bar at the end.  No matter
who you want, you'll be targeted no matter who you are
. Senpai was completely included. He
was 6. Yeah, that's
right. Nana Karisa is like that same girl. Oh no, I
couldn't get that one.  It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay.
Because the training table for all the exercises is too easy.
Yes, there are some things that can happen, but it's
okay. That leader and Chiara
will cover for you. It's okay. It's
okay. I'm looking forward to it.  It's bad, you're fine,
everyone. I'll put everyone in, so I'll
put everyone in from one side to the other. Anyone who finds it
will have to peel off their arms. Use your grip strength,
please. It seems like it's moving. It looks like it's moving
[  music]
[Music]
Everyone, please go to Mr. Uji's voice chat. A
wasirknow
about
ONE.
[Music] Well, I
don't know.
[Music] It's
like this in pro wrestling.  I can't
find it. I'm in a
situation where I really want to do this. If I
open the door, slam it, and close it right away, I'll
be right in front of the closed door. If I do this, I'll be able to get in a lot.
[Laughs]
Hey
, it smells like earth. It smells like earth. It smells like earth.
What
do you say? It's
terrible. Wow, it's kind of heavy. Is it a little too close? I'm
in the room next to you.  It
's so cute, yeah, it's cute, it's
upright, oh yeah, yeah, that's it, that's
it, that's it, that's so
cute.
Yes, you can
sell it.This is really cute.The head is really
cute.The head
is very cute.The soldering is finished.Ah,
yellow.Yellow.Yellow.It's time to run.Run, let's
run.It's time to run.Do your best.  I'll try harder,
run away,
run away, run, run, run. I
want to go to Korea, but no,
no, no, no, only those who run away, only those who run away.  It's too
late to touch the runner, you're too eager to touch the runaway, and you're probably just entering on your own.Oh, you've already entered, I guess.  I'm going to make a mess of it, Kanata
Fresh, so I'm going to
go next to Anya.
It changes
[Music]
Ruru I
'm there too I'm there too Eh 460 Oh, catch me I
was ignored at all There's no way that's going to happen Wait a minute Captain,
but birth 158 Ugh I'm sorry just at the last minute Hey,
Oh safe, it's okay Oh,
hide it, hide it.
165 That's right, I feel like it's dangerous if you hide it, hide it, and
take charge of it.  It's
different to catch someone, but it's different.
[Music] No
one is going to catch me,
but I'm being honest. But I'm sorry for the people who tried to catch me. I'm
not being honest. I'm not being honest
. I'm not being honest when I scream.
Even though it's neat, it's neat and clean.
Various complaints are happening. There are also complaints.
Nice, nice, you didn't catch him, you caught him.
No, why?
[Applause]
[Laughter]
Yeah, I'm definitely a member. I haven't
been. So what's great about this is that you're
cute when you're a little self-aware. No,
what's going to happen? It's cute. It's
scary. You're so neat. You're you.  It's never going to change,
but it's definitely neat. That's a
great thing to do, run away, and
don't think you're going to get caught.  The
yellow was really strong. I
caught about yellow. It
was crazy. I caught it with this one. It was
n't a team. I ran away one more time. I
made an entry. Everyone did it. They all
did it at once.
So,
round,
escape,
go.  Run away, it's okay.When I
was an older sister, I wanted to be chosen as the group leader,
or because I was a sexy woman, but I
didn't care. Do
n't say that. I was
definitely not chosen because of my height.
Well, that's true, but the child who misunderstood me,
Kolka, misunderstood me, and
let me run a little too close.The cage
is too small.I really wanted to get out, but now I can
catch him.  Then, you
can't run away during the game, right? There's only a
little time left until the next game starts, right? The remaining
juniors have to do their best to show what they're going to do.
Yeah, that's what I mean, but there's a
possibility that they'll change it or it'll be completely different.I
want them to have it, but they
're saying, ``I want you to protect it.''  I
want to be protected when I say "Shin" and "I'm sorry",
right? Yes, I want to be protected, right? Yes, my
shoes are so hot, my
shoes are so tight. All my shoes are in a tight place. It's
creepy. This is definitely an expensive place.
It's a little creepy that the slope is about to overlap next to Xione Tepa, but somehow everyone is buried. Everyone is sandwiched between them, it's a real [ __ ]. It's cute. It's so cute that they're standing next to each other. It's so cute. Someone cute.  Me, line up next to me, ah, lyce,
reset,
start, maybe start over again,
oh,
ok, ok, ok, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh.
Oh, this has nothing to do with it, but your nipples are gone. That's a
lie. I worked so hard to make this book, but now it's
gone. I went to the trouble of chatting with Subaru and
asking how many nipples does Senpai have,
but it's only 2. It's actually 2.  There are other things besides that,
but it's not a book because it's like a bird does
n't exist because it's an egg.It's not a book, so that kind of thing
hasn't been captured.
2019, it's
so bad, it's so bad, it's not a
good year.
I cut it.
This is a bad job.
Run away, run away, run away. It
was scary. It's so
scary here. Tito, it's difficult.
If you have more than 3 songs, you
have the impression that you've put out quite a lot of music.
[Music]
It's hard for an artist to get caught by someone who's completely crazy, and to be caught by someone like that.  I'm
not a Claw, I'm not a
Myra, so you
see, I've been caught.  I'm
sure he hasn't been arrested yet, but
that's not the case. It's
very likely.
[Music]
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
I answered all the questions, but I ran away. I wonder if it was an
easy move. Thank you for your hard work.  Thank you for your hard work.
Just the three hunters stay here, and the
rest please move.
I understand. I'll do my best. Bye-
bye. I'll do my best. Is this okay here? Maybe it's here.
Hey, I've been arrested again
. I've been arrested again. I've been arrested. I've been arrested. I've been
arrested. It's South Korea. It's Korea.
No, I
'm at a loss. I'm at a loss. I'm
used to it. Let's put
this out. This is
it. Teruko-sensei is here.
[Music]
Tayo's in prison. I'm
sorry.
[Music]
But it's okay.
Hold on! I made a mistake. Wait a minute.
The mouse is
[Music]
Oh my god, I was just stroking it. And
that's what I was stroking.  I
was stroking it, but it hit
me [laughs] Hey, it's cute, yeah, it's facing down.  It's
true that I
woke up and was a contestant.It was
written that I was now entering the competition.  You're being
taken away automatically, you're
being taken away by disappearing people, pins,
do your best, do your best
[Music] A
dangerous white brawl
has begun. It's so
cute, I didn't realize it was
true. Was it taken away?
Was it a YouTube video?
Naru just took it, but look at
it, it's from, it's
coming, it's coming, it's starting, it's starting, is it starting?
My senpai
is hiding, but my senpai is
probably hiding, and I'm sure he's going to come in. He's hiding in a mess, oh,
senpai, he's making a big mistake. It
seems expensive, sure,
but
...
Alright, alright, it's fast. Three people have already
been caught.
[Music]
Goza
[Applause]
You're in the red. Do your
best. You're so,
so nice. You're so nice.
That's the best record, the best record.
Maybe it's the best record, but it's so messed up, it's so
amazing, it's gonna be 2 if it's not next time.
Haha,
ah, that's amazing That guy
from earlier is ah, what's going on? Wait a second, Choco-sensei
's photo is too good, isn't this?  It's
amazing, it's so good, it's so good, Rie is so good, I just took a picture right now, okay, let's get along and send this to Subaru.
Well, you caught it all the way at the end.Yes, at the
end, it was mostly blurry.The
face you were looking at was really heavy.When you
put aside your ears like this, it's surprisingly rare.  It's
a bit weird to hear that B-senpai has ears, but I
don't have an image of it.That
's right, I guess.They're all
long, and their thrusts aren't cheap.I wonder if it's
that kind of laziness, or maybe that kind of lameness.But
no, if I judge O-senpai, it's pretty lame.  It seems like there are
n't that many people, but Gozaru will do whatever it takes.
Except for Mio-chan, Kamio-chan,
or Miorando,
Mirala, it was a bonus stage in a sense. It's
true that I was able to do it.
Ne will do it for me.
Run away, run away, do your best, do your best, nice, let's
do your best, let's go, kyun nice, nice guy
[music] Ta-ran-ran After all, it was
a little hard to catch them when they were all gathered in a place, oh no, it's so
bad, hide it, hide it, don't hide it, don't hide it, hide it,
hide it, Chando-senpai
Hey, someone has been arrested. Aya
has been separated.
[Music]
Senpai, that's about 0 to 2 years old.
That's right, 4 years old.
Hey there,
stop in Korea, you can stop. I was
arrested and caught. It looked
like it was
going to be fun. It's
not. It's
erotic. I
'll protect you. It's
true. It's a blonde blonde.  It's
so bad, it's so
bad, it
's the same, I'm sorry, it's the same, it's the same, I
messed up but I'm
sorry, I'm bored, I'm bored, I'm bored at this time
[Music]
Hold on, you can catch me for a little while, it
's okay.  I
'm here, Senpai,
so sexy
[Music] I
'm here
[Music]
Nainai
Eko How many people were there? 13
Nice, Nice,
Nana, Nice, It was almost dangerous. It was dangerous
[Music]  That
was nice. I was
really a little
freaked out. I should have hid.
[Laughs] We
're all here. We're
back. We're back. We
moved on our own.
[Music] We're
falling. After all, who's winning now?  I do
n't know, I don't know, it seems like it's just a passing thing, I do
n't know. I wonder where the sexiness was judged.
Mume-senpai is sexy, oh yes,
yes.
This is sexy.
Senpai-senpai is the sexiest.
No. 1 Sexy No. 1 Seku No. 1 Sexy
Sexy Eh Here Sexy Is
n't Here Is It Possible? Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Kaela-san is here.
Oh, Kaela-san is sexy. Kaela-san is sexy. Sexy,
kaela, no, kaela.
Sexy is
[Music]  It
's cool, isn't it? It's a red color. It's not a comb, it's not a comb.
That's because the butt was glossy.
Hey, I saw your butt earlier,
but I was already Korean, so I
couldn't lie to you, so I guess it's sexy. Well then, do
n't make me look sexy. Is
n't it better if it wasn't sexy anymore?  I
wanted to be caught because I was sexy, but I
didn't know much about it. It's a shame. I didn't understand it at first. That's
true. I don't know what's going on. I hope
everyone does their best.  I
want everyone on the team to run all the way to the end.Yes, that's it, then it's
No White 20 Up,
yellow 25, white 20, red 15,
middle or 2 middle, we're going to liven it up at all.
Next venue, follow up! Let's
go up side Afro up fall I
don't want to fall I don't want to fall
[Music]
No
oh no that's bad because there's no senior Kia
English is
terrible
English English
Top second is coming, let's go, senior dream, let's
go, senior, let's go, what's
going on with the person? School School School's School School
Upside School
High School Class
Upside Camo Stage 5 Follow Up Stage Flow Up
Stage Rooftop  I
wonder what it is,
High Ground What is it?
Top Gogo Roof Top Gogolftorft
Yeah, let's go, ah, I see. It's almost like we're
on the roof.
Yeah, well, now it's interview time for all the contestants.
I see, I see.
Good luck, Roboco.  Senpai character Senpai Ah, really
[Music]
Do your best, try your best, try your best, but that's it, isn't it?
He doesn't talk at all, so I think we can go together. Ah, yeah, yeah, he's not
that serious.  I
didn't feel like I didn't use it.In fact, I'm really
grateful that Chiara's presence helped me.I'm thankful for
my passion.Today I looked up English.I
only looked up English for the people who would probably use it.Okay, I'll
stop here for
once.  I'm not using it, I'm using it,
but when I was taking a break, they explained it to
me, and I was like, oh, you're listening to me.  I
had a discussion with Mu-senpai about how to say steak, pork, and pork in English.When I asked him to grill it, he
told me what to grill.Good
luck Beef Fook
Chicken.  Ah, Beef Poku
Chicken, I forget chicken and pork,
so I have to shout this to my senior,
so it's beef, pork, chicken,
beef pork, chicken steak, steak, steak, steak, steak,
beef, beef, fire, beef,
beef, fire.
Fire Steak Steak Spicy Go
Eat Steak
Spicy Yes, I'm not
hungry. Someone said they were hungry. I'm hungry. Are you
hungry? It
's about 7:30. It's time for dinner.
No, that's not the case. Is that the case with the overseas group? Yes,
that's the case. It's different. It's time to go.
Senpai. Oh, it's
3:30 a.m. It's 3:30 a.m. Yes, it's raining in the morning.  It
's senpai, it's rain, it's not senpai, yes it's the middle of the night, it's the middle of
the night, Wow, it's hard for senpai to rain, but it's okay Good morning, sleep, it's so
late at night,
thank you, thank you
very much, senkyu, it's okay,
coffee length, I drank coffee, I drank coffee, corner,
nice coffee, nice coffee,
nice,
coffee cafe.  Minister of Caffeine
Minister of Caffeine Caffeine Caffeine
Power Let's Go Yay Yelets
Goashi English is nothing  A
great person told me that if I just said "let's go," everything would be fine.Indeed, I
believe in that great person and everything will be fine.Sui-
chan threw the trident, but
apparently only Sui-chan
has the creative authority.
Well, I heard that it can be used with that.It's
throwing a trident.Oh, maybe that's
it.Maybe it's something like that, but the
home hunting I did just now is more creative.
Editing in mode Yes, that's right.
Remnants of that remain, and I do things like
fly and throw the javelin by myself. I've
been holding it in my Anzurui cat for about three days now.
Trident is sneaky, isn't Trident?
Fighting with each other is no good, Mizuo-senpai. What are you
doing? It's okay, it's okay. It's
creative, so come up. This is no good.
What are you doing?
Or is it because Mizuo-senpai got his leg? He
says he's going to go up and do this. And I,
yeah, that's
true. It's true. I can't pick this up. I
can't pick this up. This is the remains of Sensei-senpai.  Well, I took a photo,
and now I'm reading out the stars
. I'm reading out the stars. Teruhiha-
chan's star reading is
showing up. She's becoming a troublesome
person. Please don't tell her. I'm really going to tell her.
Please
stop it, you can see it clearly.I put a little bit of dirt and grime
on my gypro.  I'm
still in shock. Please
do it first. I don't know
what to do. I don't know what to do
. I'll take a look at it later. I'll do the rest today.  I
'm going to buy papan-yaki papan. How to get the rest of it. I'm
going to buy it, but I'm really going to lick my indoor shoes. I don't know if you're
going to lick my indoor shoes. That's not it. It's not like you're going to lick me. I'm glad you're licking me.  It's
coming.
Najaja, I'll deliver cookies. Cookies.
Look, cookies. Cookies. Cookies.
Cookies. I want to deliver them to everyone.
I want to feed everyone at overseas stores too.
Yeah, that's true, that's true. I've
been telling the world a lot. I'm going to take a break from streaming
for about a month, and
then I'll go out for some training. Then I'll
give it to Karamui Ame-chan.
Presents Cookie Present Color
Cookie Cookie Color Should Kuki Come
Star Star
Oh Come Come Here Chi Chi Chi Chi Let's Go Robo
Ko Robo Ko-senpai Do your best Robo Ko-san do your best
Do your best! The fight is great! It's so good! You're so good at it
! Practice too. It's
not that fast.
Bi-san is really good. Why is
Gozayo-chan so good? Biji-san. Do your best! Robokoshinnoko is good.
Good, good, good.  Finally, it's time for number 2. Yo, nice, nice, yes,
nice, nice. It's all right, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Now that I've fixed the startup, what's going on now? It's
probably like touching a checkpoint, falling to death, and coming back. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
checkpoints are important. It's
true, Sui-chan and I are really anxious. That
's true, that's amazing.  It's so good, it's so
good, it's so good, it's so good, the
route is so solid, it's so good, it's so
good, it's so good everyone,
oh, the business, the business, it's so good
It's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's so good, it's
so good, it's colored in this remaining time, it's
true, Sui-chan,
keep up the good work, you're amazing, but you're in first place so fast,
ah, it's too good to be true, ah, check point,
Mr. Nice, wakose, papa.  But I've been steadily
catching up,
and I can go all the way to the top.  I'm
looking at the top, that's right, I'm just looking at it from the bottom. I'm
looking at the sign, which looks like it's around here.
It says that if you touch the infection sign, you can get infected. This is the
first time I've heard of that. Look at the infected person and click on the right button to
enter.  This is what it says, oh, it's going
to go up, it's going to go up, it's going to go up, it's true, it's
amazing, it's amazing, it's chasing me, it's
chasing me, I didn't know it was chasing me, and I didn't even know it now, but it
looks like it's pretty close up now.
Well, in the meantime, it
's amazing, it's true, we're all really floating, you know,
everyone's head is floating, right? Do your
best, do your best. You
can't see the politeness and niceness of the spectators, so it's okay. You can't really see it.
Fa it's true.  I'm reaching the goal, calm down.
[Music] That
pink one is sleepy.  Let's do our best,
just a little bit more, that's great, nice, nice, nice, that's awesome, that's awesome, do your best,
nice, that's awesome, do your best, Suisoi-san, wow, this place is so
expensive.  You look so cute even when you're throwing them away. I
wonder if Tsui-chan's stars are coming out. I'll do my
best to become a photographer with cute eyes.  Are
you sure you'll be able to do it? It's from the perspective of the fans
. It's
cool. It's steadily rising.  Oh,
pink is so difficult. I think I can
go. Just a little bit more time. Also,
do your best. Oh,
nice, nice, nice.
Everyone.
Finishing is nice
Nice GG good game is good game good
game I'm already clapping with all my might I
like this Everyone cleared it
Awesome
Raanda this is
oh I bet you're nervous Are you okay?Is the
screen etc.  Hey,
something strange is coming up on the screen. What is this? If there's a
chat setting or something, I wonder if there's a controller
or something. I do
n't know. What's coming out?
Okay, wait, I can't get off here. It
's a shift. I can
get off on a shift. Is it okay to go down on a shift? Yes, there
's a severed head flying around. It's a bit of a sticker. I'm
sure there's an infection here and there.  Are you
going back? It's back, it's back, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, so
good, tae, that's amazing. It's amazing that you're able to receive so much attention. There
's a mode called Spectator Mode that I didn't know about, and it's in that mode.
People who are in a cat's normal human state
can't see our heads.It's true that when they looked at us from below, they
couldn't see it, they couldn't see it, they
didn't notice it, that's why I thought it didn't
exist.  Well, I guess it doesn't get in the way.I see, it's
well done.I'm back.It's impossible to be
forced back.I've been writing one after another.I wonder if it's
better to make this an infected person after the game starts.I wonder if this is an entry.  but  It was
like when I was looking at it from the sky after I died. Do you mean separation? It
was like an out-of-body experience. Tanae Next Kiara
Senpai Yes, I support you, I
support you without. Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight,
here,
here, go go.  Go, let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, do your best, it feels good. Yo,
Kiara-senpai, wow, you're extremely accomplished. You're so
fast, you're the fastest.  I
was really practicing, it's good, it's
good, it's good, it's good, it's
fast, it's fast, I was doing something until the last minute. Hey, it's good, it's really good, it's really good, it's so good, it's so
good, it's
so good, it's so good, it's so
good.  Hey, great Chiara-senpai Chiara,
only one of us has already gone 70m It's
too fast, it's too fast! Ah, wow, wow, the
checkpoint is too smooth. We can't
go there. wow, it's so smooth.
Shortcut demon, I'm going to go there. I can
go to the sky. Wow, this is it. I'm going to go there. Chiara-senpai Super Gia is great. After all, the bird is a wonderful bird. It's a fast bird. It's fast. After all, flying in the sky is definitely a practice.  At that time, I was
really nervous, and
I said, ``
What should I do?'' No matter what I did, I didn't make any mistakes.  I've
come this far because of a mistake. That's
good. Which way are we going? That's it. I've
already decided on that one. Even the speed
is there. It's amazing. It's
too fast. It's too good to be true.
Nice. This is no longer the absolute number one. Below.  If you
fall here when you're back, you'll
be at a pretty low checkpoint,
so no, no, you're an old
man. It's difficult. It's so big, it's so amazing. You're in trouble,
Kia, do your best.
Wow, so cool, so amazing
! You're so genius and nice, Kia
-chan, you're such a genius. No way, you're so
nervous, you're so full of nerves, you're not nervous at all, you're
moving like you're not at all. You just
climbed up like that. You didn't even stop, nice and nice.
That's nice, that's
nice, that's good, that's too good, because we
haven't reached the 2nd and 3rd place goal yet.  I
got about 90 with my money, so I took a look. It looks
like I'm going to take a look. It's really fast.
Hey Gini. Oh, it's
true that you and Mr. Ago are competing against each other. Oh,
black is falling.
Black is amazing. That's what I thought. I died.  It's really difficult,
and the same goes for the sense of distance. I
really practiced this, so it's the result of all my hard work
. It looks like I practiced for a really long time yesterday.
That's amazing. There's only one person here.
So
Wing Undokki Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaamstersam or sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssololaryy-o-yel-chan-chan!  I
saw an amazing moment. It
was interrupted for a moment. It was an amazing battle.
However, since we
finished 12th, I think this
follow-up probably has the highest points.
If this is the point of flow up, the
white group's points are now 20 and the number 1
point has come out, so it's probably Ron number one.
Let's go
Hey, you haven't come back yet. You're back. You're
not back yet. Are you still interviewing
? No, it's not like that yet. The white team is the only one of our white team who is properly eavesdropping on both of them. Hey, let's go.  I
wonder if I should stand on the mountain in the mountain and become the mountain in the mountains. Oh yeah, that's right. It was a
high-level match. No, it
was amazing. I didn't make any mistakes. It
was really nice.
Nice, the white team is currently in first place.
Hey, the time is close, but white is 40 yellow, 38 and red is 37. Wow,
nice, nice, nice, nice. CM4, points yellow, 38, 37. Let's go, let's go. That's
great. Nice, wonderful. Nice, nice, nice. Nice, nice, nice.
Nice,
nice, this is going to happen with our princess bodyguard.  It looks like
Rile is going to Rile, right? There are things like protecting the general with a line of fangs, so that's
right.
There's a lot more to come. I'm
sure I have to do my best. The pressure is slowly building up. I'm going to do it, but I don't think I'll be able to resist. The pressure is
getting bigger.
Tanapu: It looks like it's going to be a long time ago, isn't it? I worked with Ramen-chan this time, so I don't know what will happen yet.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
Hello, I'm watching this.Okay, so here
's the interim announcement of the overall benefits.Click here for the 2nd overall
benefits.Yes,
that's 1, 40, and that kind of money, or
maybe 63 points,
white 52 points, that
or 3 points.  Kaa, we
moved to the venue for the next skill line in Lee Volume
[Music]
Let's jump from here. It was
announced that there was a score for that one.
What's up? A few came out. A few came out. White
got an overall score of 2 and 3. Yellow got
63. White 6 and Kia-chan are nice.
Good game, good
game, good game. Good game.  Nafanafa 2 people,
wow, 2 people wow, that
was amazing. I won't give
up. It's dangerous, I can't do it, it's too heavy. I'm doing my best, Chiara. Let's get on it. I'll ride it. I'll get on it later.
I'm the first one, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it, I don't want to do it.
Nice, nice, nice, that's cute. Nice, nice, nice, nice. Nice, nice,
nice. Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, and then you ride on top of me. I'm the one who rides like that
while holding the thing.
Wait until you're standing there. The general is on
top. Maybe the general is on top, so it
's the one that gets clicked. If you don't
enter and you've already entered, cancel. But
touch it one more time.
[Laughs]
General.
This is it.  I wonder if that person from my pair will come.I wonder if that
person from my pair will come.Is that
person there?Will he
come?If
the pair without one stays like this, I will...
Wandering around
everyone, it's better to prepare a rice ball,
eat it, put a
rice ball in it,
greedy rice ball [Music] Greed, I'm hungry, I want to do it, please release the naka daishou.
[Music] It's a
little aggressive, Akana-
sama, where are you here, but
where are you, everyone here?  It's
amazing because everyone is getting more and more Where are you? Where are you? Is it
okay to get off the target?
How do you stop?
Just press the same button again in the book.
Nice nice nice
nice
[Music]
Hey,
wait a minute,
did you go there in that outfit?
Yeah, he came in a suit. He looks strong. The
suit drawer is amazing, and he looks like a grassy guy.
It's strong
Yes, there are guardians It's too strong It's
okay I won't charge you a huge amount of money later It's okay It
may be Oyu
Senpai-senpai
Thank you Thank you very much I was able
to ride that I was able to ride that I was able to ride That seems to be the strongest
Thank you
very much for helping me as a pinch hitter.Also, thank you very much for coming, Ao-senpai.
Ka-senpai got on top of the senior who was riding on top of me. I
'll let you be my chair.
Thank you. I'm happy. I can ride on your ears. It's
fluffy. It's stuck in your butt.
That's right, the chocolate wire.  I've got a horn stuck in my head.
Captain, this is a horn. The
horn hurts. I don't
want it to hurt. It's better if we touch each other a little. Yo, I
feel like it's quite irritating. That's what Mio said.  I think it
's quite stimulating for you too. It's true that my senior is also
stimulating me with his horns. It's a painful thing.
Moshi Moshi. Thank you very much Neko Maokayu
for today. Thank you very
much. Thank you very much for joining us.
Spi Ichiban.  I'm afraid you're
going to be taken away because you've become a suspicious person.That
's not to say that I'm going to do that.I'm so
excited.You've taught me how to do it quickly.I'll
lead you to victory.  I
want to do it. It's
so cool. It's fun. Let's do our best.
Everyone in the white team.
We'll do it, we'll
do it. We'll do our best.
Yes, let's hear it at the end.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Costumes,
but hey, this is a strategy.  What do you do? I
wonder if all the white players are going to be upset. It seems like
if you get the most successful kill, you'll
get 1 point added, so the
opponent you can protect and probably attack is the enemy.  Let's
all focus on each other. It
seems like we should just wake up the guy who is approaching the general. If he's the
face-to-face
type, it would be better to stay close to him, but it's
okay for him to do it more and more. He's a weak person. I'm
sure.  That's right, I
want to beat up people who are weak.I can see it,
so maybe that person wants to kick me.At
first, stay close to the general and when you see 1 heart, charge.
Rather than being scared, I
think it's probably going to be a voice chat between Nemi and that pair, so I guess that's
right. There are so many voice
chats.
Well, I think there's probably a name at the bottom, so come to think of
it.  It seems like there is some real rice porridge in the area,
so you
can't get it without cooperating with everyone.You can't say you should protect it like that.That's right, the
general. Let's do our best by looking at the landmarks.
Let's do our best.
This is the target.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, if you find it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
if you're really going to win, then maybe if you're really
going to win, then it's probably going to be down.  Is it better for
people to
talk? If you're the one who speaks, it's okay. It
's okay.
[Music]
Yes.
Itothe
wrong
ITeamandIwaslikeI
Yes
[laughs]
thebodyknowH
meokayAllWhat
strategy
[music]
know
Allbasicallythrow
You
and
ATT SHI
ickMaybeistherea
SHIELDyouhaveto
equiptheSHIELDIhave
anything
currentlyIthink
thereaSHIELDIthink
justabookandyouHit
Peoplewiththeoris
theresupposedtobeI
seeanybody
SHIELD
SHIJA
okayWhodowethinkthe
weakestlinkis
WhoisitTRUEthatifwe
gothatweGETMORE
POINTSInoIDEarePart
OfThe
Game
YELLhere
wherewhere
meWhitekindharderto
RedYellowamongall
thewhiteShirts
hereapparentlyThey
havemoreHPTheyhave
moreHEARTSthanthe
othersIseewecould
alsoyouknowbully
Somebodyisthere
anybodyyouLonthink
gnagoleadersbecause
ofthemorePOINTSI
thinkifweMayHang
backandGetthepeople
inthebackofThe
crowdsWhotryingto
gettheleaderThey
mightnotnoticeusat
firstGivingUSthe
upperhandIknowmaybe
notgoodThisismy
first
timeokayIthinkagood
ideaWecangothe
unsuspectingOnes
I meanthePRWecame back
chance care
me
Knottingthe
horsesosorryIthe
onlypersonever
watchedSpiritNoI
loveSpiritwhereget
allmyIdeasfromis
thatCrazyNoNonotat
allSowrongIjustI
horse anywayiidhorseIam
ridingyouexactlyso
youaremoreofahorse
girlthanmerightnow
moreofaGirlhorseJA
SORIGHTIamaGirl
horseandyouarea
horsegirlYeahYouare
aGirlWhoisahorseand
Iamahorselovinggirl wholoves
younejnej
give
carotDoyoulike
carrotssugarcubesI
like
bothWhatdoyouprefer
IlikeIlikeboth
TogetherokayWho
faitemylittlepony
ponyRainbow
DASHOGOGOG
ient
Whatokay
[Music]
unspecokayOhGOcome
youcarefulokayWeONE
Iokaynicenicenice
niceSorryOhshootthe
GotUsokayokayokay
Whodidthatwejust
talkingabouther
beforeIRGetIRGetIR
IRsomeyou
okayREVENGEyouwant
REVENGEyes
yesareyouREVENGE
WORKINGNo
oneonemoreOhSHShe
USOhmygoshILost
EverythingisLOWokay
yourheartNo
NoIseeI
seegotohertoo
LLSorryno
okay
IknowgoingonRRunUS
WeforFokayifwecan
probablynotprobably
OFFNowAreyougetting
HerRokayscareHer
makeHer
ScaredYoushouldYou
ShouldBeafraidvery very
afraidgood
all
[Laughs]
sosorryIeventhinkI
waslikestaringatthe
screenIjustITellYou
Anythingthat
HappenedJustnowI
tellyouthat
happButwekilledlike
IthinkpeopleWealso
diedtcethatwasall
youthatwasAllYou
Killingandthatwas
all
NoKSon
USpeoplesaying
TE
DownWhat
isgoingtoGivingthe
PEPRESSUREWhat
is
AC
FWhyIS
F
doitagainWe
individualsAgain
of
whatIdidokaymakeI
gettherightTHE
PERFECT
[laughs]
horck
okayIgot
it
[music]
NokaybrokenNowCrush
allmyhes
DreamsI
obedient
Whatjust
[music]
kidding
FfnysohappyWEED
Togetherme
toohappythatIcan
bewithSomeoneWho
seemstoalsobejusta
little
deliriousSuper
deliriousIhaveno
ideaWhereIamright
now
NoIstreameddoing
Marathonstreamsfor
the daysI
knowICheckmyphone
likeIwonderlikeWhat
goingonlikelooks
likeNstreamingand
thenyouknowkindof
gettoitam
likeStillStillgreat
HaveAGlikeyou
knowfor
HOURIImadeAMaybeB
scheduleMOVEtoday
WhereIhadYouKnowMy
Oneofmylonger
streamshourseven
thenIEndat10andI
reallyfallASLEEP
earlylikeAgainstMy
WillIunderstandOh
YeahSoIkindofknew
thatlikeIwasgoingto
beabletosleepbutI
waslikegoingtotryI
needTry
TrymakesITWORK
[Music]
LetdothisThingI
STREAMbutIHlikeGO OUTIntoThe
WorldIfeelabit
TiredI
understanddefeat
your enemieslookat
allGetniceokayokay
okayokayNEXT
iswhoever
okayokayJumpJump
JumpJumpJumpOhnice
[Music]
okayIknowSSS
Swing
okay
[Music]
neveryou
ALSorryIYto
[Laughs]
around
backforback
forokay
somedidit
DidIcanreadnamegoil
IThowkills
you
killyou
K
[music] [
music]
kills
girlhorseeathorse
WORLDhorseeatgirl
eat
horseheTACusedhors
meatYesIdoRemember
ThatistruthTo
ThatI
knowI
know
okayTE
TEIloveWarRthemfor
melikeNoTheyvegan
TheyfineIknowwhat
thehethe
CREAMCRECREAME
CREAMpretendthatwe
OnTheRed
Team
AnotherItru
doIcomplhestI
thoughtBeLikeAROUND
THELASTGAMEIHowmany
roundsSsomeswichYou
tryingAgainyouwant
metryagainokay
okay ick cck
okay ick
horse
helpokayStandingthe
okayImakesurenoone
everstealsyouagain
thereyou
dockingokayokay
AgainIknownot
workingokayIdoIdo
itOhmynissIknownot
working
back
[Music] [
Laughter] [Applause] [
Music]
know
[Laughter] [
Laughter]
[Laughter]
[Music]
OhGod
okay okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okayokay [Music] [Laughter] okayrightccktil
SHIELD
okay
okaygirlThirstyHold
On
okayokay
okay
ONEWeTwookayokay
okayokay
wewegobackTurn
ReturnNousing
SHIELDIevenokayIcan
seeIcansee
okay
[Music]
okayHurtHurtUH okayHurtHurtUHnice
okayokayhur
[Laughter]
[Music]
kssokayoveryou
didohmy
godTeam
4okaywehavetobein
theLeadNowweGtobeWe
GotToBewinnersOhmy
GOnissaYouwereso
goodatdirectingUS
towardstowards
peopleNolike
SeriouslyYEIfeel
likeyouwereIfeel
likeIkilledjust
peoplethatalready
hadLOWHEARTSor
something
IHnoideaIwhatwas
doingyoucouldsmell
OUTDeaththatwaswe
just
finalized
We
FPS
hours
[Music]
May
WOWTeam
I
horseI
ACtohorseIcouldthe
horseMayMaybe
ITruthofLifeifyou
tellpeoplebugsyou
thensayitmorebutif
yourealizethat
nothingsandyou
just
youknowwhatiknew
thatMayDeepDownI
justItwasMy
PlanIdidwanttobethe
designatedHSEBrown
IthewordforlikeD
horsenotYouShould
Knowhorsegirl
horseIonly
speak
Ispeak
HUMANisH
sand
S
OH
rome
for
okaysupptogobackI
thinkIknowGdragUS
WeOUTIseeokaywehave
towait
forKOnlyKILeaveThe
Game
Oh
ohScared
CHANNEL
anyThat's right, it's important. Nice, nice,
strong and very strong. Yes, Ta-
san Roboco-san's pair was also
amazing. It was nice, super sleepy.
I got 3 kills.
Wow, you're doing a great job.
Wow, that's
nice, that's amazing. What do you think of this? It's pretty
good. I wonder if I'll even go there.  I
think I lost a lot of ground, but I think I made a comeback.I think I was able to make a comeback
in the second game
as well.I got about 26 kills,
so I guess I made a good comeback.Red was
also pretty strong, so it's okay.  Yes,
it's red, it
was strong, it was strong, it was amazing at first,
but I don't know what's going to happen, it's dangerous, I'm starting to get scared. Both the
princess and the princess are shaking, and today the princess is shaking in her thong.  I
'm shaking now, Bume-chan, let's
do our best, it's okay, it's okay, we can win, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, we can win, we can win.During
practice, I was dodged by the yellow team for about a minute and a half,
but yeah, yeah,
yeah.  Yeah, the part where they serve the food is
really weird, but it's a really meta reading,
but yeah, there was an update, and the
content of Holomen hunting has
changed quite a bit, so the menu is also one of a kind.  It
's possible that you're reading the mystery that Chang has changed.
That's possible. That's totally possible. I want to
win. I
want to win. If I've come this far, I've already
come. How far do I want to go?  Yo
Negonanere, yeah, I want to go, right? I'm
starting to get a little greedy.At first, I
felt like I was starting to feel like a nerd,
but I'm starting to see a victory.I wrap my arms around me.  I did
n't tear off my sleeves
just now.I just tore them off around my shoulders.I
can't tear them
off
any more.
You can't go too far, that's wild.
Take care of
yourself and get muscular. Muscles that you're proud of.
Come on, come on! Congratulations on your last 41 kills.  I was
blushing when Shigemiko-senpai came home.
How was it? The number
of kills was amazing.  I
defeated
it, and there were a lot of people like that. It
was amazing. That's amazing. That's why the
white group was amazing. Lastly, I would
like to thank you for the cat matata porridge.  Thank you for your feedback.
Thank you very much. It
was a pleasure to play with you all. I will continue to support the White Team.
Thank you.
Thank you. It disappeared in an instant. Thank you.
Thank you very much to the team's agent Oka.
Thank you, me and you too. We've had some shocking
kills, so it's
totally different. We worked hard. We did our best.
Thank you very much. It was really
fun to eat. It was really fun. It was
fun. It was fun. It was fun. But there
's a lot of pressure in the competition after this.
Yes, the pressure is different. Let's hope it's
okay. It's okay.  Everyone can do it, it's
okay, it
's okay, it looks like it's okay, you have to protect the princess, even
if you have the princess to protect you, even if you make a little
mistake, the princess will be able to make up for it,
right?In a world where pressure is dangerous and dangerous, it's dangerous.  I'm
going to do this and practice that.I'm already
climbing.Everyone is climbing the ivy.I'm in a hurry to climb the ivy.Even
now, I'm getting better at the ivy.I can do it.Oh, it's
difficult, isn't it?
When I asked you today, where did you go for a run? Yes, it
seems like the scores have been tallied,
so I'd like to take a look.
[Applause]
Hey, the red team scored 46 points, the
white team scored 46 points, and the yellow team
scored 23 points.I do
n't know what's going on with this.I wonder how the battle will turn
out.Okay, let's move on to the next one.Yes,
no, then next time.  Let
's all move to the competition venue for the race
[Applause] Let's
have fun,
Princess Mikata, do your best, do your best, do your best, I'll do my best, I
hope
everyone else can come as well,
knight.  I'll
do my best, I
'll do my best, Fat, I'll do my best. I
wasn't the VC of the team yet. I
wonder if everyone is doing their best right now. Pink, red, yellow, pink, yellow. Red is fine, but you don't have to worry too much.
But, oh, Princess Iris.  The princess is going,
the princess is flying. She doesn't say it herself. I don't know if she's
super cute or a mystery. I do
n't know. She's cute. She's a mystery. She
's naked. She's naked.  Is she
even naked? Naked naked princess!
Naked princess! It's so exposed! Let's enter Kanata Hime!
Okay, it's the princess, Hime Hime Hime. I'll do my best.
All of the princesses look like they're powerful. Now on all teams.
Why are we together?A
princess from a neighboring country has arrived.Let
's protect the neighboring princess.Hello, princess.Hello,
princess.Princesses, we
should look at each other's faces for a moment.  Don't go too
Thank you very much.
The meeting between the stinky princesses has begun.
Who will write the book? Thank you, please. It's
true. Yes, it's true.
Let's have a meaningful battle.  Let's
not
run. Don't run slowly. That's right. I
could do my best, but I've never run in my life. I
guess I've been living in a car all my life, and I've only been there once.  I've
never run before, so what kind of life is it like? Don't run, it's seriously
impossible. That's right, don't run. The princess is the strongest in our country. So
please, no, that's not the case.
Logically speaking, she's the strongest.She's so weak, yet
she's such a weak princess, but she's definitely the weakest.It's like she'll
crush me.Okay, first of all,
let's hear from the Red Team.The Red Team's Ehi is played by Tokoyami Toma, who plays the
cavalry role.  is Shion-tan
And it's blue and fluffy
and fluffy, and Moko-chanwa, so there are four of us, and
Fuwamoko is one of those two, so
yes, yes, thank you very much,
please, thank you very much.  I
'll do my best, I'll do my best. I
practiced till the end. That's
right, I'll do my best. I usually go to bed at 9 o'clock, but I practiced until 1 o'clock. No, it's true. It's really like 9 o'clock.
On days when I don't have anything to do, like 10 o'clock, I go to bed.Awesome.Amazing, then I
wake up really early.That's
right.I'm sure I'll do my
best.Okay, no, let's do my best.It's okay.I'll do my
best.
Yes, White Team Can you hear me?
So I'd like to start by introducing the players.
There's someone I don't know who I am, Princess.My
role is Hazu-chan,
Kai is yes, and Nanmu-chan
is yes.What do you think?The
enthusiasm is not so good, but those knights...
I think it's okay because you protect me. It's
okay. I
'm a guardian princess, so I
want to protect the three princesses this time.
Thank you, Princess. Azuki is so
cute, and Azuki is so cute.  I
'm a cute Mu-senpai. Are you okay? I'm like Ao.
No, I'm a Senpai too.
Please do your best in the performance. Hui-
hui, that's right. Lastly,
I would like to ask the Ki-gumi. The Ki-gumi is the Ki-gumi. Hini,
Iris.  The cavalry is at the summer color festival, and the knight is at
Hajime Ririka, or Hajime Ririka.  I'm
going to show you all the wonderful cooperation with Nee's useful knights. She's an
amazing Po Princess. She's already the fastest and the fastest. I
want the princess to take 1st place. I want her to steal 1st place. The
princess is true.  I'm the princess.
Yes, I have a fever. Please
do your best. Yes, thank you very much.
Please do your best. Please enter as well. Yes
, yes, that's it. It
will start as soon as the entries are finished. Let's
go, let's go, go to the wall.
Yes, yes, yes, it looks like it's okay. I'm full of motivation.
Subaru is also getting nervous.
In other words, Chinnesba is not a princess,
but she is a princess.
But after all, everyone has been
practicing so hard.  Yes, this is
nice. I'm so excited to see if I can
make it. Wow, stubbornness is the
first thing you'll need to stand on. Well then, next time, let's go. Um, I'm
here. I'll call out the names of the people on board.
Masu Carrion
Carrion Kineo cake
Okay, I worked hard and was nervous It
was a ride Did you understand the ride?
Member name Seisen He is a senior, my senpai Oh
Okay, I'm a senior Yuko English
Sorry, I'm also very reliable Good
time movement  Yeah, I'll stop when my name is called
Yeah, if you say stop name
Say stop name
Oh, I'll go from the right side Kamae Azusan M
Mei Kazama Azusan I'm sorry, I
can't go without it
O And next, let's all climb up Now Mumui-chan
Kazamaka this Azusan, but Mume-
chan Kazama ah this  Achanzu-chan, no, Mui-chan, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. You
might have waited to see if you understood this. All
you can hear is my voice.
Right? I see. Wait, I
understand. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Answer me what you're making. Wait,
open the book. Hey!  It's Luna, isn't it? The
possibility of Luna, Luna, Luna, Luna's
bond, as expected of Karuna.
Tonmuton, the latter is a special hamburger. Please
cut the special hamburger, meat, beef, potatoes, and carrots on a cutting board and grill them on a griddle.
Cut, cut, cut, lamb, lamb, lamb,
lamb, and then that's nice.  Let's
cut it, ok, ok, ok, the
rum is complete, rum is complete, Mio-san's
umm shibug, who came for ten
minutes, ok, let's
go, let's eat, let's take it.
It's red and yellow.
Red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red, red,
red.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm
going to defeat all three of them, and all three of them will be Snas
Nao.  Nice nice
Shishiora Ora, maybe I'll go, maybe I'll collapse.
Run, run, run, nice, nice, run, run, nice, nice, run, run,
run, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice,
dangerous, even if you get caught in the middle. And even if you're in danger, it's only 2. I'm really
surprised at how high you are.
There they come down like a triangle.  Mu-
chanmu-chan,
no, I'm glad. It
was fun, Senpai. You looked sad. If you fail, the next problem will probably take a lot of time.
Hey, let's practice.
There's a 3 second difference from the 3rd place
Bishi Jump Jump Punch I
can't stand it You're back You're so nice You're so
nice I'm with you all at the contestants I'm with you and I'm
Princess Hato-sama from Unsa.  Now that I know that, it's
true. It looks like I'm about to die. I have no choice but to quit. It
was TMT,
but I'm TMT. I'd
like to interview you.
Can you all hear me? No, I can't hear you, congratulations.
Well, congratulations.
By the way, see you, Knight Shion Tando. Did you
try it? You really practiced and
practiced. The four of you got together.
Yes, that's the result.  I'm so
happy, no, I'm so glad that it came out.It
was really quick, really quick.Oh, it
was quick, really
quick.That theme was Subaru after all.
Yes, that's right. I was making some chicks.
What's this? I'm curious as to what everyone was making. That's right. I
hope you'll take a look at the archives. So,
congratulations!
Congratulations, congratulations!
[Music] Let's
do our best in the last 2. I
'll do my best and go to the white team.
Okay, then I'd like to hear about the white team.
How was it?  I do
n't want to be so sloppy, but at the end,
when I was about to defeat Anocha, I
got caught in a sloppy fall.It seems
like there's something between Wave and Wave, but in reality, I'm caught between them.  I'll
leave it to you, so I
'm here. It's amazing. I'm glad I came in 2nd place. It's
amazing. I lost it. I
did my best.
Even though I had an accident, I was able to get into the car very well.
Who was the question? Who appeared? It was Luna. Ah,
Luna Luna, here too.
Kanaluna's bond. Well, it
was pinkish, so I was confused about Aku-tan,
but now I believe in Kanaluna's bond.
Thank you very much. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much
. Next,
I would like to talk to the Kigumi. Please give it a try.
How did you feel? I'm so disappointed
. I didn't know what to do, but at the end I was catching up. It was really amazing. I was
catching up. I was
catching up. I guessed my problem. I made a lot of mistakes.
Mom was trying her best.  Look, you
just did your best.The sports day is all about working hard until the end.There
's meaning in doing your best together.Of course, let's
all run to the end, aiming even higher.Mom, you
're beautiful.Do your best.  hey  What was
Tsuyoshi Ao? Lala and Ayappa.
Lapros. I showed them a few times. The last one
was porridge. It was porridge-senpai. It was definitely difficult.
How did you make the porridge?
Mom, I'll look at the archives later.
Neru.  Well, do your best. Good luck. It was
nice.
If it's not good, I'll stop for a moment. Hey, I said
yes. Now, let's take a look at the scores for the Koshi race.  I do
n't want to see it. I don't want to see it. I want to see it.
30 points. White team has 20 points. Yellow team
has 10 points. The red team has
caught up a bit. Maybe the
red team is coming. I don't want to see it. No, I don't know yet.
Yeah.  Well, I still do
n't know. So let's move on to the next
competitive winter race. It's
a bit dangerous. I understand. I
won't say that, but
hey, I'm
fine. It's a distant meaning, but it's okay.
Yes, I'll move on. It's okay again.
Uh, where? I was sent away without permission. Oh, I'm leaving without permission. I want to go home,
everyone. My
senior is doing some amazing cooking. It was very
fast. It was very fast. What was the book about?
What did you make? Lamb told me what I was making. Lamb
Lamb Lamb. It was Lambji. It was Kataram. Sheep Lamb. Sheep. I had the
lamb grilled. That's what that character is like.
Hamburger. This is what I practiced.  They
were teasing me because it was so long until practice, so I'm going
to wait until tomorrow. After this, I
wonder if the summer is going to be skipped. I see, the
contestants were attacked before Nodoka-chan's announcement.  The
previous technique is the first one to be surprised
at, it's a dangerous and easy-to-understand method. I'm
going to take care of my health and go to the flowers.
Well, it's
better to enter, right? You can enter and
get a book, so you open the book, choose whether you're the
all-rounder or the white runner, and come on, come on, come on, come
on.  It's coming, it's
coming. Is it okay? Let's right-click.
Ah, it's number 8 in the entry list.
What layer is Ame-chan in when it says "I'm mine?" It
seems like it's somewhere in the middle.
Memory Yeah, it's the leader's place, right? Yame-chan, 5th
floor, 5th number, 5th founder, hey, my chest is all over the place.
Okay, that's it. I see. I wonder if I've been able to enter with this. I've
done it, I've done it, I've
done it.
That's right,
that's right, oh, oh, that's amazing. My character contact number is blurry today. It
's
okay, I can do it. Don't be timid. I
'll do my
best. I'll do my best. I'm okay. It's okay. It's okay.  It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it
's
okay
[Music]
have ah ah ah ah ah I've been able to enter I'm done
ah but it's turned into 9 It's turned into
Nona
ah
ah ok
NNo
bebeJustJust
oh nice nice nice oh nice oh nice
oh  Good
Job Good Job
Nice Nice Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, or ah or is or is is or or is or or or or or or or or or or or, or or or or if you or I or I or you
if you are going to dive into this water you're going to dive into this water.It's the turn of the fly contestants to be on the first layer.
Teacher, the 3rd layer is Mumeha, the 4th layer is Noel, the
leader is okay, and the 5th layer is Amehaha, the
6th layer is
Kaerae, the 7th layer is Azusan, and finally,
Iroha, isn't it?  It's
true that people who are used to Minecraft are coming in. It
seems like they're going to liven things up even more. Let's
go
to bed. Let's go to bed.
Everyone in the white team could hear it.
Yeah, what do you think? Well,
who should I choose?
Well then, Iroha. When I
realized that I was an anchor, I
became an anchor. But I'm sure I'm fast-paced, so I'm
sure it'll work out. I trust you, so I'll do my best.
No, it's great, it's stubborn.  Okay
then, the white team, please take first place. I
hope you do your
best. Please do your best. Thank you for your hard work. I'll do
my best.
Okay then. Finally, I'll take the team Yaberi.
I just came back from picking flowers.Welcome back.Don't go
home.I'm about to go home.So when Nerisa
-chan was confused, I heard her
say ``open book, open book.''But I didn't get
it.Here, the
group leader gave an embarrassing response.  So,
okay, let's do our best. Wow, this is the luck of the water.
If you're at the bottom at first, you'll be able to go back. That's right. Let's do our best, try our best. Let's try our best. Let's try our best.
Oh, this is on the right, ah, I fell. I'm
doing my best here. The water is wow, wow,
wow. Ah,
no, no, no, but I'm
nervous. I've been practicing, so it's bad. It's
a little scary. It's starting to look like a
mental system.  It's okay, it's okay, Medi, do your best,
Medi, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, today I'm in
jail, I'll remember and do my best, it
's okay.  You
're working hard, you're really working hard. I'm
sure it's the best. It's the lightest one. At the end, you'll
laugh at the end. Well, once this is over, let's
go eat some delicious meat. Let's
talk to the chocolate and say, Azuki and the chocolate line.  Let's
do our best, let's do our best,
go-go-go-san, do our best, do our best, do our best, do
our best, let's calm down. I'll
be waiting for you. Come on.  Come
on, come on, come on, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's a nice catch, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's good, it's getting better, it's better, it's better, it's better, it's better. Leave it to Gogo, leave it to me, it's really good, it's really good, it's good, it's good, it's a good run, it's a fight against chocolate, it's calm, it's good.  There are
times like that, there are times like that,
there are times like that, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.  It's
okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's not at all, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, go, go, go, go, go, go,
wait here, help me I don't know what to do anymore
, I'm
stubborn,
oh wait, this bread.  Pan right,
left and right
Yo,
do your best,
stubborn
Hey, I'm sorry, do your best,
do your best, do your best,
Yo-chan disappears, dodge it
all too soon [Music] It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, try your best, it's okay  Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go
.  It's bad, it's
good, it's good, it's good, it's
good, it's
good, it's good, Kara-chan, do
your best.  Gogogogogo Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Yo, it's okay, husband,
yes, eat,
do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, nice, nice, nice, yes, do your best, do your best.
Hello, Iroha, Okay, let's wait, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, it's a good swim.  It
was a good run when I went, I was
nervous, I was so nervous, I was so
excited to do my best, so I did my best.
You're so nice, you're so
strong. You're strong after all. Hey, I
forgot to eat. It's
okay to have no problem. It's okay. I'm
hungry. I'm hungry. I'm
hungry. Let's eat as much as we can when we're done.
Hey, I forgot to eat. Nice
run, nice run. Nice run. Nice run. Nice run, nice run.
Degozaru,
yeah, nice Hihi, I want to eat meat, meat, I want to eat
meat, meat, let's go, meat, meat, yes, yes, yes,
my heart hurts. Thank you for your hard work.
I want Japanese sub-sub, I want to
eat, I want to eat, let's eat together, let's all eat together, let's eat
together, let's all eat together, let's eat shabu-shabu, shabu-shabu, it's
beautiful, it's cute, it's soothing, it's
cute, it's cute, let's go shabu-
shabu, let me leave it to you.  Take me,
take me,
take me, leave it all to Choco-
sensei, Choco-sensei chooses is berry,
good, super nice, yeah,
leave it to me, leave it to me,
even if I don't like you, I tried really hard, please, I persisted.
Good luck,
Tao, I'll be interviewing you, Aoh, White, and White, you did your best, Neha, you did your best, you did your best, you did your best. Well then, I want to be the anchor. Let's listen to Iroha again. Yeah, how was it? We'll be fine from the beginning to the end.
So we worked hard as a team and
got together. It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay. As a result, I
was passed and overtaken at various times,
but I was able to finish in 2nd place.  It
was a nice fight. It was a nice fight. It was a nice fight. Thank
you for your
hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your day off.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. You
did it! This is Kamaiha, who passed the pre-1st grade of the test. It was great! It was great!  It made
everyone cry. Some of them were
crying. They're very
sensitive. It was really good. I
thought I could get it. I tried my best. I
tried my best. I tried my best.  To be
honest, at first I was just having fun and was
just trying to do my best, but I
didn't expect it to happen.I didn't understand until the end.So I
asked everyone to gather in front of me for this ceremony.  It was my turn
to go to the front, and I
was the first one to go to school. I was
surprised to see there was a wall. Hello,
we were sealed away.
Now, let's go to the rattled throat that was closed in this school.
It's so
beautiful,
so
what's the point of practicing? It's just a bunch
of great kids,
after all. I feel like I ca
n't lose in a certain tonality.  It
seems that the colors of the team are very different.
Look at the volka, look at the volka, everyone is lined up and
holding a bread with a lot of volka in it.  It
's too much, but I'm
fine with proceeding. I
said yes, and the
ceremony will begin, but I didn't really know how things
were going this year or anything like that.
But yeah,
everyone worked really hard together and
did their best.It's amazing how close the competition is every year.It's
really worth watching, and I think it's amazing.It's
true.Everyone
had their own drama, or rather, there was some
drama, including practice.  That's what I
thought, but my
mom can't come in, so Mio-chan just
talked about it, so I'm
coming. That's a
nice line. After all, you said, ``You're strong, you've remodeled your mom, and you're amazing.'' All at once.
It's quiet now, but I
'm scared to feel like I'm in trouble.I guess it's okay.Okay,
everyone, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?  It's arrived, it's arrived.
So, before the closing ceremony, there
were a lot of voice chat changes due to the competition, but
everyone, please support me in that area.  I would
like to say a few words to A-chan and Nodo-chan who gave it
to me.Masuhai-chan and Nodo-chan meet
up.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much for your hard work.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.
Everyone's hard work and individuality
was overflowing, and it was the three organizers.
We were able to see all of your hard work, so we
were really moved by it. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the book Thank you very much
everyone
Thank you very much for your cooperation Thank you very much for your cooperation I
think it was fun for all three of you to participate, so please do your best until the end
Thank you very much Thank you very much
Thank you very much for your cooperation  So,
everyone, we are now going to begin the closing ceremony
. First of all, I would like to
give a greeting from the club. I would like to hear a greeting from Ms. Samiko, the actual chairperson of the sports
day. Yes, yes, everyone at this sports day. Did you
have fun? Did you enjoy it?  It
was fun, it was fun, it was fun, but it
was really good.
Thank you, everyone. Thank you very much. Every year, we've gotten really
busy, and thankfully
Hololive has gotten busier,
but still, we've all gathered together like this, and we've
all worked together.  I've already seen all of the cats
taking the initiative to call out to each other and help each other, and I'm
always so moved by how truly amazing it is.Thank
you so much for your cooperation.  Yeah
Thank you, thank
you, thank you very much for this. If you
could take this as an opportunity, I would appreciate it if you could say
thank you. I hope we can have more
interactions in the future, whether it's new members or the members of En and Kari.
Let's all make the Holo Live even more exciting.  I
think it's great, so I look forward to working with you in the future. It's
wonderful.
Thank you very much. Next, I'd
like to thank Mio-chan. Thank you to everyone who participated this year
and did a great job.
Yes, everyone is great,
and this year is also the end.Thank
you very much.Thank you
very much.Next Subaru, now Subaru as well.I've been in
touch with you for a while, and I've
seen many different aspects of the team.
However,
all the teams are already working hard, and I
think we'll see some good results this time
around.One of the things that everyone did together like this is that it's
going to be a big treasure.  I do
n't think so, so I
hope that you can make use of this bond in the future.It
was a lot of fun to watch.Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Finally, I
would like to announce the general benefits.The announcement of the special benefits will be the
number 1, then the number 100, and
finally the number 10.  I
would like to make an announcement on the sports day.
Now then, Mr. Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson,
please announce the scores. Yes, I'll
start by announcing from number 1. Yes,
then
please go ahead and see what you can see. Red team.  8 white group
8 oh yellow I want to wait and watch it, but what the heck,
it's on stream right now, but there's still a long line of people,
so
let's go ahead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I
don't
know. I've got everything. Yes, it's all about 100. Please, please, no, no, I'm going to go to the end. Everyone, please, please, please. Finally, about 10 announcements. Go ahead.
[Applause] What,
what, what?
8 white is
38 yellow is 106. It
was a little bit more. I
don't know. I
know it's frustrating.
Hey, Friendly Freeze Freeze
Friendly, yeah, and the 2nd place
was the white team with 138 points, but the 3rd place was the wooden team with 106 points.Well
done, everyone,
did a good job.Good job, good job.Good job, everyone.
Tane, when are you
going to give out the awards? Yes, there will be an awards ceremony this time.
Well, everyone, let's go to the yellow group. I'm Geo, who has the same medal. Well, first of
all, the representatives of the players and teachers of the yellow group.
Kana, Hasbe-chanbe-chan, please come to the front,
please come and win.Has, then, how about the third place medal?How
about bread?
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on that. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing!
Yes, it's Geo who won the silver medal for the white team.O-
chan-chan won the silver medal.I'm looking forward to it too.But I'm excited about the
medal.Congratulations to the
white team.
Congratulations,
congratulations, thank you,
congratulations, congratulations, and the red team won first place. I want to
see the big medal. I want to see the medal.
Thank you very much and congratulations.
[Applause] Sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
this is
the king this is this rai
or this is this rai and it disappeared
in a blink of an
eye. Even
though there were so many diamonds, they became beautiful in an instant.
Well then, I would like to
take this opportunity to say that Hololive Sports Day
2023 will be a nuisance.
Thank you, thank you, everyone.
Why do you want to take a commemorative photo?
Yes,
yes, I do
n't know what to do. Let's take it on that stand in the middle over there. Yes, please, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, okay, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, it's a game where you can't go back.  I'm afraid I'm
going to line up in the upper right corner. I'm going to
go in here or here. Yes, I'm going to go in here too. Can you
see me? I can go back.
Hey, where are you all? Ah, that's it, everyone. Hey, we're
not there yet. We've won. Sorry, sorry,
Lily. I've been waiting for you. Wait a minute, wait a minute, you stink, Sorry, sorry. That's fine. Yes, that's okay. I
haven't received it yet.  I'm so
happy that you're following me too.
I lost once, so I don't have a medal, but it's
really true. I'm hiding it.
That's not the case.
[Music]
If you do it, you won't get mad. Emiko. It's gone. It
's okay. That's
definitely the case. I
can't give you a medal.
Wait a minute, Mio-senpai. That's Mio-senpai.
Please give me a call, thank you. I'm
glad I was able to touch it.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
. Alright, everyone. I
wonder where I should look at that thing right in front of me.  I
wonder if I should look at Koro-san.Ro-san is flying like I'm looking at him.Ro-san is flying.Reaaaah, I wonder if I should look at the camera.It's
really in front of me.The cameraman.The
cameraman.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here.Here..
Yes, there's a
cameraman.
OK, everyone. Can you see it? I'm going to take a picture. The
photographer is very close to Meruru Towa-sama. I'm
sure he's hugging me.
Then let's go.
[Music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, who threw it? Who
threw it just now? Who threw it this year? It just happened that someone threw it. I
took it. Everyone is
throwing something. They're
throwing it again. Hey, hey, don't throw away your trash. Please take your trash home with you.
Thank you very much for coming over.
To all the listeners who watched the show, and to all the management staff who helped out behind the scenes,
thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.  There is
Thank
you. That's it. Well then, Hololive
Grand Sports Day 2023 will be the end.
Yes, see you again everyone. I
'm going to Deotsu Hololive. Yes, yes. Yes, I'm
going. Otsu Hololive. Oholive
[Music]
Live
Bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
[laughter]
[music]
oh
everytheSLE
[music]
[clap]
[laughter]
[music]
need
[Music]
byby
by
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
DET