[Music]
kelly's scared of halloween
is everyone too quiet for you guys or
should i turn them up louder
how's
i was muted thank you chad for letting
me know anyway ultra low latency
everything's
so should i explain what we're doing yes
please
please yep okay so and
we all have never played this game
before at least uh like
10 minutes before this unless we played
the 10 minutes before the stream
however i think i have grass crabs
crap grass scratches
and this is kind of similar to among us
and i didn't play it but coulda said
it's kind of also similar to dead by
daylight
right to me yeah in a way yeah
uh basically we are all children
and and then among us
wink wink is a secret neighbor like a
really old
dude scary dude that's always in the
screenshots from this game
uh but he's also uh shown as a child
at least in the beginning and until he
decides to just uh like show himself
so weird uh so we are trying to like we
are going into a big
big mansion and there's keys hidden
up over that mansion and we kids
try to find it and each kid by the way
has different skills
depending on which kid you choose so
the the old dudes eventually will try
to stop us from getting those keys
because once we get all the keys and
open all the locks to a certain door
then the kids win the game and i have a
feeling
that today in today's collab we will
never even once managed to open the door
but that's the spirit i get the feeling
that's pretty much how the game works oh
oh [\h__\h] oh okay
i'm on low power mode well
i'll be fine oh shoot thank you for
reminding me i should plug in my
my key movement yeah
yeah i think that's pretty much the game
it's kind of easy um
yeah there there will be an imposter
among us
wink wink and pasta among us
everybody
ah why minions
you're a yeah wait we're how are we
we're not gonna
mute ourselves like we didn't among us
because we realized it's not maybe
maybe not necessary however in the test
round ina
was the imposter and she was very quiet
so
maybe act as if you're a child
act like a child
is everyone ready to go into the first
round
keep it at 10 minutes or do you want
slightly longer
oh let's make 15 minutes if maybe
because i i think we need my time
especially my brain i just woke up
okay ready up i'll find i'll be the
detective
if watson will be oh wait watson are you
a detective i'm a detective but today
i'm using my fps skills for good oh
excellent then i guess i'll be the same
wow
cool ah kelly you gotta return to the
lobby oh yeah okay here we go um here's
the big orange game
ready
[Music]
here we go
nice i mustache the mustache too
okay cool
all right i'm good i want to help you
guys your flashlight oh yeah
quickly all right it's time to find the
we have six keys we have to try to open
this one
two three four five six yeah kelly i was
confused because there's like some doors
why are you in a desk you know some
doors you can open
with the key cards
why can't i why is it hold on what's
happening
take please
is
don't call her apex predator for nothing
hold on press e
oh no nothing in there huh what whoa
how could you mean girl don't throw that
pumpkin at me don't you do it
thanks chat hell yeah appreciate it
all right well you guys blame me okay i
am still learning the controls
so this will be interesting let's go
keep an eye on you cool
tell me that okay actually maybe nothing
what can i use this for the tailwind
oh god i know but i have this milk in my
what do i do with this milk
drink it okay how do i drink it calcium
calcium and
drink up cali i also want to drink cow's
milk
yeah i drink i drink then i throw the
carton goodbye
get away from me get
all right we have to find some keys
let's go find some keys lads
oh you just don't mean
[Music]
hello
okay that's drop and then throw as you
click
i'm trying to throw okay you press the
other button okay oh what's this
hey what did i do oh a key i found a key
oh oh oh open the door okay
hold on look here it is oh it
how do i know which door it goes to it's
right here right here right here right
here
isn't it try it right here okay oh wait
that's not going in the middle that's
for upstairs that's right upstairs oh
that's for upstairs okay
get away from me get away from me
let's go upstairs where are you i found
it
okay put it in pumpkin i'm not afraid to
use it
hello did you uh put it out oh
i dropped it i don't know how to play
the skin okay you press this
button got it nice i'm a gangster but
you all knew that all right here we go
oh okay and i guess you can't really use
it again huh okay that's oh
well we're opening doors
hello who's there who's that it's me
oh kelly hey you know what's going on
are you doing okay
on the way to number two okay on the way
to number two so if you find number two
i'll look
let go of me
i was on the second floor lads in front
of the uh
in front of the entrance to any of the
other rooms
you're me okay there's no hiding it
anymore i guess
oh what do you mean the apex predator so
you drill farm good eyes show it to us
your
sexy body wait what huh
oh
that's what i meant but also in the
practice round it was also uh watson
who was the only one who stayed alive
she died
yeah but i don't know i didn't know you
could get there oh
oh my god wow nice detective yeah
on the roof wow
no but big anime are you supposed to
find anything
i don't think it's this um
they're carrying us as always
of course sasuka
i was just impersonating
i can hear you
that's so weird watson oh my god
it's creepy just watching you gouda
especially as like a kid
like is she a kid or she is amelia
breaking the game where is she is she in
the roof somewhere she knows she's just
a chad and good at playing the game
she's glitched into the wall she's
amelia's breaking the game
are you hiding you're in this room
[Laughter]
i need some popcorn
let's see where watson is
what are you gonna do huh get a watson
hi hi hey hey throws wrestling you can't
go chairs
wait where are you come here let me try
and turn my chair at you
no all right your boy's gonna go get a
cold one everyone enjoy watching watch
the sleek girl
no wait why not watch our only hope
no no
i still want that cold one hold on just
a second
huh did you put them in your truck with
the candy
wait no you know that's a little
i'm gonna change my character i wanna be
the one who gets the clues
i'm gonna be the detective because we
need to
find those keys
okay return who should i i don't think i
was a very good detective i found one
key
uh but i wasn't really pleased with my
job so let's see
um is there any is there a kid that just
beats the [\h__\h] out of people
that's still playing too all right cool
you get to shoot them oh fps
can i can i hit someone with a baseball
bat
yeah yeah
that's a shame i think so there's a
character with a baseball bat but i
don't know if you can hit it i don't
know if you can actually hit the ah man
i wanted to i wanted to hurt that guy
okay well let's try my fps
and that's the counter strike what's the
inventor do not undergo
you make items like the milky way
we want to get into the basement yes
ah yeah what's our goal exactly yeah
there's
a door on the map and then you open the
big door with like the six blocks and
then you gotta
yeah let's chill ideally
that's a good idea let's stick together
this time
gang up on him yeah yeah get them
dog pile on it so with the scout you
only have 10 bullets
and you can only okay you can only
temporarily
go okay i'm gonna call it no it's amelia
all right and how do you uh how do you
press what buttons do you press to shoot
uh q and then
all right got it now q and then mouse
yeah got it okay
that's easy enough all right guys we're
sticking together right yeah yeah
i don't know i don't trust anybody
anymore i trust gouda
because it's very unlikely that gouda
got got to be
uh imposter again neighbor
i don't know apex predator
listen man what's this by the way i have
a
hint to a key it is in some
blow like oh i found it i found a key
oh cool nice a car key card oh okay nice
oh what's the key card dude i don't have
a pumpkin it should go up to the second
floor i think
yeah peacock open
i also have a card cool you can open the
other door over here
somewhere you can do that
okay hold on we can go up these stairs
oh there's a coffin looking place
what's in here is that anyway what's
this why can't we pick up useless items
what is that
to throw them i think you can throw them
how do i okay hold on
no wait no give me that sorry each key
card has a different number
uh-huh oh i found it too
what does this do you were like 1900
oh it's not kiara i hate kiara it was a
cat oh
oh no it's cali not i
[Laughter]
died
is
i think only like a certain character
can escape yeah
are you are you okay downstairs i'm
upstairs
okay then i'm downstairs
[Music]
oh no good you got to stay hidden
wait wait wait hold on wait hello
girl watch out i can build a gun
oh no oh no
i can't believe there are people who are
good at video games
wait what is the what is the goal now if
you're the last one
you got to get the keys yeah finally you
still have
all the keys yeah it's kind of awesome
you can only hold two things at a time
so it's like yeah well there's the one
character that can hold more than
items
[Music]
yes nowhere
go it's okay good you can carry the game
you can carry this game
you can win all by yourself i believe
i dropped my flashlight this is
i saw a few flashlights laying around
wait that
[Music]
oh you have to like speed around this oh
nice nice good yeah yeah yeah
there's keys they're not all up uh
you got this you got this
yeah don't say the number don't say the
number you know we'll find out where she
is
i don't like the inna is just humming
like so casually it's
really creepy what is this i don't need
this
oh wait yeah i do very creepy oh
wait what did i do super hot never mind
like not like actual key keys you can
find them in different places it doesn't
matter it doesn't have to be like
in a specific spot so wherever you are
you can't go find a key for the big door
huh and there's key cards and there's
keys
key cards are to open more rooms and the
keys are to open that
the big door that we need that we need
to open okay
you know i don't mean to alarm you but i
am now i now i'm carrying i am with you
by your arm
so please keep your distance
you can't stay in the garage the whole
time girl you can't stay in the garage
get out of the bathroom get out of the
bathroom
um uh he has bought directions i'm good
as bad with numbers
[Music]
what are you gonna do with that a nerf
gun
no oh does that work
you put it in the big door that's in the
main lobby oh god that's all the way
over here though
why did you just give away my location
watson what what do you mean
i didn't do anything i just said it goes
like it's my
god
[Music]
girl is carrying the whole game hello
that's difficult man that's difficult
camps in front of the door yeah
so we i think we if we all stay together
and we have like one person who does
like uh yeah
yeah i can be a good bait i can be good
a good distraction
that's about all i can do you wanna do
you wanna start over since we're not all
here it might be better for all here
yeah yeah hold on wait let me let me go
back to you though
i want to close my i want to test my how
do i get to you uh if you throw enough
items at the killer you can temporarily
kill the killer
oh no i didn't know that him down as
well not only the kids
okay spam throwing items at him and the
fling shots oh yeah
i want to actually use the slingshot
next time
i'm gonna do it temporarily
uh yeah yeah you kill him for just a
little bit
yeah i'm not sure how i feel about that
yo gangster what
we can play another round this is a lot
for one person and you guys are
getting yeah we can start over yeah okay
okay
is there like a leader lobby lobby
leader probably
yeah that's me um
that kid is really useful because you
kill him
oh that's op yo what the heck
with that did you just find the gun
all the way to the finish line
yeah do we have the option just leave
the house
go get the police
whoa looks like almost
what
[Music]
i died
oh no this is sad she's
[Music]
someone said my screams sound like uh
cleats or
shoes on a basketball court i don't know
how i feel about that
good at still trying to survive
you got to give up the ghost you just
threw them
[Music]
cabbages pumpkins
oh my god
you want this shark you're gonna have to
fight for it
okay there you go there
[Laughter]
[Music]
you can still save them yeah yeah yeah
yeah
um let's see i like i bet i can throw
pretty well so i'll be
i'll be this too what what are the match
rules maybe we can set it to like
because you guys said there is revive oh
um
what oh there's auto revive on yeah yeah
it's on it's on but we never realized
oh when you when you're naturally you
like fall and stuff and you yeah
you revive and you get missing i don't
think you're five yeah
okay okay okay okay
oh wait but one thing one thing we can
do is maybe
uh the number of locks maybe get them
down to five or so okay
okay that would be good five cool things
um yeah and the character that godot was
playing is pretty op
if anybody oh then i wanted to play i
went to the inventor to build
guns inventory oh you have to build
stuff right
yes but you find it's really easy to
find the stuff to build oh okay
i'll be i'll be an adventure kid then
maybe we should also turn off key cards
so we can go straight to the keys
ah yeah yeah
we'll see how it goes okay i think that
makes it a bit easier for us to win
because other than that i think we were
it was impossible for us to win
yeah wait question if yeah if there's a
neighbor but they're an
inventor does that mean they're uh
i am they can shoot the kids with their
phone
cool i want to shoot some kids though
i mean i want to shoot these kids
it's [\h__\h] up this is
something else i'm a killer but i
actually don't like ballistics you all
in the chat chill out
chill out i now everyone who knows me
knows i don't like guns all right listen
oh can you turn up yeah yeah okay okay
thank you
[Music]
that's kind of a good idea i should have
thought about that before
now so it'll make it easier to hide then
because we won't be able to see
yeah yeah yeah yeah wait how come chat
is saying in-game voice chat is it
because it's proximity based is that why
you guys are saying that
oh possibly what
correct use um
yeah proximity based uh voice chat and
stuff ah it is proximity that would be
cool
you can try that if you guys want that
maybe next time
i'm going in this room okay what does
that mean
the closer you are to somebody the
louder they are
and then the further away they are oh
you hurt me i accidentally threw my
flashlight
[Music]
i don't know how to play this game how
do i switch objects what's the button to
switch
to one and two wait okay hold on two
oh okay so this is the glue
what does it do it's all sticky and on
the ground i'm gonna leave that alone
come with me here yes it's milk yeah
okay wait where did you go okay
i'm gonna stay with you wait what if you
are the what if you are the imposter
trust me by the way i have a i have a
photograph again
of uh where the key might do
switch items oh okay it should be i
could have played
a lower lower cupboard not one like this
in a low one like a tv cupboard oh let's
see
what's this fine hey hang on money can i
eat it
like power oh cool yeah where are you
why do you want to see me what's in
sauce
i'm quiet
usually she isn't so quiet yes
mine is suspicious i would say
me yeah
no yeah no yeah
i am she's kind of quiet i'm a kid i'm
just a little
innocent kid oh i see walton hello
eyes on watson wouldn't i have attacked
you guys already if i was the
yellow um
[Laughter]
what's this dude oh you can jump
is that another flashlight there was a
lot of flashlights yeah oh in case you
lose yours i guess
[Music]
whoa what's going on
why are you guys so suspicious of me i
didn't do anything
exactly yo there was a snacks in here
like oh that's how she's fishes she's
trying to lure us
hold on hold on cut his snacks are you
talking what's this is it a candy bar
hold on trick or treat
not my feet what the hell is that what
the hell is that
what i heard a bag there's a walking
pumpkin
in the clown it's cali
oh yeah
[Music]
what the door blocks the door what are
you talking about i didn't do anything
oh god you guys are suss for thinking
i'm suss
um you can also be the clown and the
clown can transform into
a little snake the clown can transform
into other eyes
that's not good that's not great
is anybody a key no
no no
i'm in the garden and i'm about to die
thank you everyone for being with me it
was fun but i'm about to die goodbye
sayonara
[Music]
i'm working on it
i'm still alive i'm still alive
[Music]
how many years do i have i have two
actually why are you so quiet
kelly i'm searching
we're so close to death because i love
that that's it
that's it oh i see i see how i don't
know how to grab people in this game
i know i i pressed a bunch of buttons
basically we don't need the key cards we
only knew the what what is that
what is that surprise [\h__\h]
money oh that's not money
[Laughter]
who is still alive besides me
[Music]
hello i am
where is everyone
where'd you guys go
[Music]
how about that i don't know about that
i'm mixing up all the all the buttons
what's happening by the way i already
got two keys so
you know with the carrot oh come on
doing she saved the game
there's some nice music playing
oh oh yeah radio
where's your voice it's creepy
i don't know who you're gonna
hang on it's real dark
i wonder why it's so dark in here are
you lost callie
no i'm i'm fine
someone already here
oh i don't like it why do i hear sounds
oh
okay i don't need my i don't need my
flashlight oh
it's sneaky
what is this sound what
[Laughter]
that's a shame here why can't i find any
keys
oh do you even lift bro oh the the curl
the curl marks where the key is
oh wait who is the grove there we go
uh-oh no no
oh
i don't like that
oh my god where do i go i'm alive
you doing all right i don't want that
yes i think
killer is not very good at the game
apparently
i think the killers are really bad at
video games that's probably
that's probably who it is the one that's
the worst games out of everyone this is
very bad too because they're always lost
now protect me wait where's the where's
the
ah
lead me to do meanwhile killer you
the thing the thing i like this all
right
you know what are you riding on you're
writing on something on my screen
i am i don't know
what you gonna do with that killer
oh wait one last one
a good question i don't know what it is
it's actually a super nintendo no no no
yeah right what does it do
bananas
suddenly intrigued would be nice if i
had a flashlight
oh well that's just the brakes
sometimes there's a few places where
they're scattered around oh thank you
for the tip
i appreciate that here we go found one
yes yes
okay no problem
a nice house it is a nice huge house
there's a hole in the floor
oh
[Applause]
come here today
yeah i have it now i have it
you gotta kill her good luck what can
you kill death
yeah exactly see that's that's it isn't
it
the killer instincts finally come out
punch punch punch punch
clutch watch right now
i'm only a little bad at video games
okay turn on your in-game audio
all right okay
okay voice chat on always on
let's test it out oh you guys are
echoing try to
talk in game okay hello
hello can you hear me let me see if i
can turn up your volume because it's
pretty low hold on
ah it is really bad quality it's pretty
bad but
i mean hello at least i can hear you
guys but still
oh hello oh yeah i hear you
so bad it's so bad it's so quiet sounds
like we're talking through tin cans to
each other just stick to this
but it gives us a retro effect really
fancy retro effect
yeah it's pretty bad pretty bad quality
wow oh yeah maybe maybe
just for fun you guys want to try it
okay
it's scuffed but we can try yeah just
one round one round one round how about
it lads let's go
okay i'm gonna turn off the names for
the maymay all right oh yeah good idea
15 minutes key card off uh all good
how do we turn off the legs wait i'm
gonna see something
oh
i also don't hear her head bob intensity
let's see how do we turn off the names
it doesn't automatically oh it does it
automatically all right cool yeah i said
it
sick
we don't hear you in the uh in the game
wait that guy's going okay
she's going to fix it i think discord
uh would like to let us know that they
liked it when discord quality was on
i'm not surprised i'm not surprised
really
[Laughter]
no like actually discord yeah
bitcoin's in the chat wait what
the [\h__\h] what
discord's in the chat what i discord
listen we're doing this for the
experience
a discord like the real discord is in
the chat
it had a check mark next to his name so
i assume so
if people say audio they will appreciate
the score
more they say they forgive us
is almost ready okay
[Music]
it's cool in game audio right now
cut if it
however if it's the real one thank you
for blessing us
with our presents thank you but other
than that yourself
one piece
oh she's restarting the game i'mma
restarting the game
okay
no problem
what what is everyone uh going to dress
up for halloween i mean for me and cali
halloween is kind of over budget
yeah i'm just covered really what are
you dressed up as
dressed up as a what
i'm a dinosaur cool i want to be a nurse
because it's the opposite of what i am
right
i'd be afraid if i saw callie in the
hospital
yeah with good reason that's a very good
reason
discord discord came to my chat as well
oh my god
discord come to my chat
come say hello to my deadbeats discord
why is discord uh
watching our stream
who knows i couldn't figure out how to
do the thing where you
when you show everyone's big faces
kind of difficult because you maybe plug
that into discord options so i don't
have to use other applications
could you please i have some good ideas
i'm a good inventor or how you call that
i can make some i can send you some good
ideas i'll i'll send you
an email discord
[Laughter]
let's talk business discord let's do
some business
i'm a businesswoman wink
wink but other than that thank you for
your services discord
thanks dude i really appreciate it
for real though why is this card
watching why not who knows
we're having fun we're spending the best
halloween ever with us
i just realized kiara sounds the same in
the game
chat and she doesn't disclose that
what the heck does that mean bad or good
i don't know but it's why is it yeah the
quality sounds about the same
they really i'm supposed to sound good
on this card at least now when i bought
my new microphone
don't tell me it sounds shitty on
discord like maybe
like one of those mic uh megaphone
things
i bought a 400 microphone okay 400 or
500 whatever
don't tell me it sounds like a
walkie-talkie
maybe maybe it's my brain remembering
how your old mic sounds
i think that's what it is
four hundred dollars well spent no
worries
hey what's
maybe we should just do maybe we should
do discord again yeah
yeah okay yeah i think it's a sign it
was fun while it lasted
everyone appreciate this chord yeah yeah
discord well let's see
off this
back to the still muted on this hello
homie there we go
oh there we go oh my ears in the end
you can always rely on discord of course
always rely on this court
sorry everyone ready was wicked
yeah oh sorry i'm an idiot hold on yeah
we're going
bam i'm with her let's party
so loud that's pretty loud turn the
audio down
oh yeah it's kind of dumb because i had
to turn it up because everyone's voices
are so quiet and now it's like blasting
over here
bye i wanna be the imposter
i don't wanna be the impossible all
right guys i think if we spread out
if we spread out it'll be better good
idea
[Music]
hang on e is
oh my god the room's changed oh yeah
huh that's a thing that happens in this
game
everything changed whoa
wait what whoa what is that
hey you're looking for keys right just
the key
whoop wait who's quiet watson is
suspicious cool
last time what's up we start the game
[Music]
okay stay together okay okay hey i'm
here too i'm normal i stay together
hi normal oh money
[Music]
hi are you normal no you're not no
ah
only the killer would have recommended
that we split up
what can i say i'm attracted to death
death and i are meant to be
listen either i'm killing folks or i'm
getting killed that's how it always goes
every game
[Laughter]
in a dedicated relationship with death i
am
i wish there was a way to really step up
yeah
why is anyone surprised okay one two
down
monkey down
don't touch me okay
no not dead sensei with death you silly
willies
what is that it'd be weird to make it
weird
getting rich
hello
ah
turning off the names makes it a totally
different experience
oh mike oh my god what is the killer
guys watson's the killer
i can tell
what does kiara look like she's the one
with like the
the pig heels
oh
oh my god oh no no go escape escape
run run he's after you he's opening the
door he's coming after you up the stairs
now he's a child again that looks just
like you
look at him
[Music]
i got no chance against amelia
you're all dead oh yeah yeah it's up to
you again you got to carry the game
i tried
well i was up against the top fps player
out of halloween amelia what then what
sun
i can't wink with this expression we
both fling shots
this is a hard game for anyone who isn't
the neighbor wait
she's gonna say we suck i heard it
coming up
i agree i concur with that statement
is there any way to make it less keys
make it easier for you guys
oh we can get to three keys do you want
the three yes
but put the time limit to 10 minutes
okay 10 minutes three keys
no names yes speed run yeah let's speed
run this bad boy
that's my secret right now hold on i
want to beat you and then you win i want
to be this guy he holds a lot of things
all right
you said spread out because you were
there
before i knew i was here
because she did an amazing job
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
i can hold many things give me that so
we are standing up but we're not
splitting up
we are splitting up at least okay
it's only three keys now
okay money what does the money even do
it makes you rich i buy stuff yeah
oh what does the hammer do
are you cool i'm cool are you cool i'm
cool are you cool
i'm i'm cool i'm chilling are you sure
yeah all right i'll go i'll go with you
then this would have been the perfect
time for me to kill you
are you sure are you sure you're not
gonna you're not gonna i don't like the
way you're saying that homie
listen man i got a reason why
someone broke a pot
who do i who can i trust
did i check that before
someone approaching oh who's that
someone approaching
who is you is that cat why are you
calling us awfully
i'm chilling yeah girl is quiet huh
uh-oh i see you i found a gear wow
don't waste your don't waste your rocks
don't waste your eyes yeah waste your
rocks waste your rocks waste your life
oh it's girl why would he be wasting my
rugs
wait what oh god
stop it
i'll throw my things at the killer
i would like to but hold on i don't know
how to play the game
i just don't know how to play my
flashlight's gone
oh can you make things with this
what this shot's not reloading here what
do the gears do
no they don't you only have 10. where's
kiara
i don't know how to build things in this
game
i'm useless now i got a lot of peace
after me uh oh no i lost my pumpkin
what's in my hand
oh no i tried to throw it and i
sucked help i don't have anything what
am i stuck on
gosh darn it i thought i was going to be
the hero
and then i went and then i realized i
don't know how to play the game
i'll get them next time i'll get them
next time i think my channel is the
official spectator channel everyone
[Music]
where is that i think one of us seems to
be a detective to make it easier
oh yeah uh someone should be attacked
oh i watched that happen no my gosh
[Music]
how do you escape
is there an option to just go call the
police
i know i said that before but really why
can we not just call the police
please can i lose one
huh nice nice
you're good at this game why can't i
find any keys
who's still alive besides being inna
kelly right
no i was first together
yup as i said dedicated relationship
with death no one's surprised
it's too bad can i see something i know
how that
feels oh what's that i have a dedicated
relationship with that
deaf as well cool very dedicated
uh-huh i heard that's the word upon the
street
i have two bananas now yeah what are you
gonna do i'm just
not throwing the phone die
oh yeah yeah yeah try it
girls i am dangerous again
i can fight again yes
a certain november a
[Laughter]
i don't think she saw you
wait do i want to run away from yes
because you totally get away from there
probably running is the best option
i think nothing don't worry about it
wait the crowd
that doesn't mark the key anymore is it
because i went too far away
possibly uh i think yeah
if you get the key oh
[Music]
oh no you gotta throw something at him
wait i thought i thought already
he threw the key oh yeah i found another
one but he grabbed the key from somebody
yo there's another he dropped it you
dropped it in the garage
i'm cheating you dropped it in the
garage
i meant to throw it because i didn't
want to hold on to it oh yeah
oh i don't want to see what happens when
you win oh yeah
it's curious huh
okay well i cheated and i told you where
it is
someone be bait someone be bait
yeah uh callie's gotta stop backseat
from from the grave
callie's gonna shut up no beth see
gaming from the grave
who's this who's this cute little tyke
come here
oh my god i hate that so much dude oh no
where's the last key kiddos
that was so gangster he was such a
gangster
[Music]
oh my gosh okay let me do a go oh jeez
right you did your best it's fine i feel
like we got the hang of it now
yeah yeah you're pretty decent at it
i think uh one no
because it's a
in 15 minutes it's half past like half
an hour before kelly's
oh yeah one then oh yeah
one more okay yeah let's make it one to
remember leds
i thought i meant to leave one person so
they could win i thought there was two
people left
my back i didn't mean me and you it's
okay oh my god no i watched myself who
was the imposter
gura okay okay cause at some point she
was talking as if she was
one of us that's big brain
[Laughter]
oh waiting on you oh sorry i was looking
at characters all right
let's see oh cool okay i'll
i'll be adventure kid all right
okay let's go
who is it yeah why is he so creepy
i don't get it perfectly sculpted stash
perfectly symmetrical
all right here we go
totally different
maybe not because now we have to find
our way around
it's not different
oh it's kiara by the way what huh
what huh
[Music]
get away from me i mean i'm i'm not i'm
clear
it's not me really get away from me why
are you following me
oh are you normal we stick together
who are you uh this is me amelia jumping
okay all right i think everyone in here
three of us stick together we can
i can uh shoot whoever the wait who's
that
i come in peace tell me if you find
gears you guys
if you guys find gears tell me
okay oh gears yeah
general area maybe it'll be okay
where's my flashlight i'll follow you up
soon
okay i'm going to follow you guys too
you guys seem safe
where'd everyone go where's kiara she's
uh somehow missing out
[Music]
hello are you guys outside
hey who's that oh you scared
i trust you
oh i can jump you press spacebar to jump
i just figured that out
i don't like this this is too crowded
i'm out of here
hey i'm just proud because i can't
girl i'm fine i promise you i'm fine
okay kiara's here we all know it's tiara
let's help each other out tell me where
the gears are
let's make some guns
guys this way come on this way okay
i'm just giving you a chance to win this
game at least
one time oh my gosh definitely uh
i dropped my flashlight there we're good
okay
the front door let's see oh maybe we can
find stuff to build things here
um what what is that what is that where
is the music coming from
oh my god i don't like it
where are you guys
yo the jackpot i'm lost who's following
me
oh i can almost ah man i hope i can make
the gun soon
where am i back in here
where am i
god
oh hi people nice how
about this where are you
going how do we get to you i don't know
oh man i don't have anything to help you
someone was here
well we are really high up i don't know
hey there you guys are i found you
the kiara's gonna be the main door if
you guys bring stuff we can kill her
there's a crowbar and any gears up here
i wonder
can i make this jump camera
nope that is the answer to that question
oh wait i can help you
what you can get
i think we have enough to win but we
just need to get to the door all right
i'll be bait i can beat
a distraction
uh-oh wait why wait wait
what oh
[Music]
uh
can i take hold on we're safe here we're
safe here do you guys see any gears
i had a lot of gears i wanted to drop if
i dropped them
i just have to get back no
hang on tell me if you find any gears
you guys hey we're all alive can you
believe this
i got a gun you have a gun oh sick okay
i'll do the bait
let me be the bait why am i so anxious
to be the bait i just want to be useful
where is everyone wait where'd you guys
go where'd you guys go
[Music]
mmm
nice nice one more i heard a noise
left click left click put your key on
the oh okay
how come how come we have two blue keys
oh is it not a red key
and a yellow key yeah yeah
i'm gonna be useful and i remember we're
gonna die sort of
oh wait oh wait okay
oh wait we're still not back yet
i'm sorry she died
oh i think she died somewhere around
here
what you doing callie waiting to be bait
okay
oh no do we have all the
no keys got the red key all right let me
pick up something to hit her
also has a gun that's not great news
that's just not great news to be honest
well i'm ready to fight i'm ready to
brawl
oh mark's the key who is alive
oh we only have a million and 45. all
right
hey hey
hi hey i'm trying to figure out how to
get up
die you monster you don't belong in this
world okay
i i am running what's up
what's up
wait why is it making noise like that
what what everybody wait
here i can throw this i'll throw this at
him and then you can grab the key
a girl okay
[Music]
okay she's still she's still outside
don't tell them
you sucker
wait what's the plan here oh
whoa
nice cool okay perfect okay oh do i need
to get the blue okay
we already used the blue one yellow one
yeah you have 30 something i don't think
we'll be able to get it in time
yeah there's no way to find the last key
darn there's only one key though unless
uh
there is you haven't go go go we have
both
i only saw one there was only one i did
not think i was there's only three keys
and you guys did
we can get more time when we open it
no that's so anti-climactic
i can't believe that i thought i was
actually like
i was pretty close to dying at some
point so
at two points i think well not bad
oh from the first second that that it
was me
you're so obvious you're so obvious just
just the way that you are
you're just obviously the king was just
like you can hear the smile
yep from here to smile when you're
trying to deceive us
but i i really didn't think like i was
thinking if i'm gonna be the imposter
i'm definitely gonna
die and this will be the only game that
you're gonna be able to open the door
but i did it did all of us get to be the
killer once the neighbor
yay that's kind of awesome yeah i think
everyone did once oh yeah
oh nice that's lucky
gross and everyone won everyone won when
they were the killer
oh yeah yeah i don't think the kids ever
watched
definitely yeah yeah that was fun
everyone should try to get the clown
more often yeah the clown was super fun
to play
oh my god being the objects is so funny
good
yeah basically everyone had a win we are
all winning
yes yeah everyone's a winner i'm glad
it's the perfect timing to end but cali
i think you have something to announce
i do my new song is premiering in 30
minutes
30 minutes oh yay and then there's a
party there's a party after that where
we're gonna make drinks i haven't
figured out what we're gonna make yet
but i bought a bunch of stuff
and if you guys go on my twitter you can
see the ingredients i bought if you want
to buy your own similar ingredients so
we can all make drinks together and
celebrate halloween
[Music]
thanks guys thank you guys how about you
guys do you have any do you have any
other announcements
friends i'm making food
[Music]
the only announcement i have is i have a
legendary
collab with marin senpai coming up next
over so who knows what's going to happen
cali are you jealous if i sleep over at
madden senpai's place
no i'm happy for you uh-oh
what do you want it's cool
it's your life i just want to make it
clear we're just friends okay as are we
so i don't see the problem
nope not last time i checked that's not
what the ouija board says
oh what what ouija board
that's making it weird some of the
ancient ones i believe
[Music]
okay whatever anything else anyone wants
to mention
uh i have uh i'm gonna post a video in a
little bit
uh because kelly is is uh gonna give you
guys the last piece of candy to the
halloween scavenger hunt puzzle
yep yeah and i'm gonna post the video
after
her stream on twitter and you guys can
see the final piece
yes the final piece thanks
for like organizing this super cute
event scavenger hunt
thank you thank you thank you guys for
helping me
thank you amelia halloween happy
halloween
happy halloween yay
thanks for watching thanks guys it was
fun yeah
see you real soon bye bye see ya