[Music]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
bye-bye's movies
thank you
[Music]
oh welcome
to
a stream
hello
I'm so big help was made me smaller
[Laughter]
I brought back the head
um
it's very big
we have a potato bat no
no potato chips bag
I don't have many Zelda assets for
streaming wink wink
I don't I I don't know why
I don't have many hmm how come
[Music]
and blue made me a new one wait what
blue last time blue made something like
I guess right before the stream and I
did that holy [\h__\h] wait I didn't see it
and I didn't use it and it was just for
like one stream or so so then you know
there's no reason to ever use it again
wait that stuff looks good blue you
little [\h__\h]
oh my God
what okay I have to use that I gotta go
change
[Laughter]
wow thank you guys for telling me I
wouldn't have noticed oh my God
[Music]
I'm gonna be playing uh
with no not the usual gaming layout
because the game is beautiful right so
one should show all of that off
[Music]
so there's a hood
uh
uh there's so many oh my God
let's download all of it
must support the local alpaca
I mean blue isn't really local for me
blue lives I think Far Far Away adopt I
doubt blue is an Austrian alpaca
it's not very local
but I am in support of any kfp creator
oh shh what have we got should I do Hood
offer on I'm gonna try on but
Hood items are often a bit difficult
[Music]
um
I'll try I'll try let's try it's gonna
be a bit tricky
um okay
a new item
I'm I
putting on some clothes can you please
please look away
give the lady some privacy
unlike you know with Gordon Ramsay I've
been watching hotels hell right I've
noticed the pattern
in almost every episode he shows
his butt of
like he would get in a in the shower of
a hotel room
and get naked like show his bare ass and
I'm like what
is is this like maybe also in other
shows is this like one of his things
I was shocked
and embarrassed
and also I mean if he doesn't show his
ass he often just shows his like upper
his naked upper body which is I guess
still okay but
man
it's like they
actually film them every time from the
back when he uh goes into a shower
they really always have to show that
oh okay we got the
where is it ah
let's see if I can
oh
wait how do I put something ah
ah
it's one moment please what the [\h__\h] is
that
what the [\h__\h] is that
oh okay okay things are things have been
changed and they're a little bit more
confusing oh
interesting
hmm
oh
no I don't know
oh oh
I found
a useful new pinpoint but eh
wait wait wait wait wait
reset
no no oh [\h__\h]
so how are you guys doing today huh
I know what the [\h__\h]
oh
look can I lock this
yeah okay there's a lock locking
function
doing very well playing the game oh I
hope you guys I hope a lot of you guys
are ahead of me
because we're playing two times this
week
you know
oh yes perfect perfect
[Music]
it's difficult trying to
um
got these two too oh
Maybe
maybe only the sword separately could be
useful without the back of the hood
because the hood wobbles in the back
oh well whatever let me add
ah
wait uh
in that
oh
ah
I got the the hood front to stick
perfectly though okay
one more
that cute stick
is uh
oh well I hope we won't be fighting that
much with sticks especially if we got
a fancy sword
on our backs oh sure
my show
um
[Music]
that shit's huge what a huge stick
my arm's small okay whatever it's gotta
work like this
yeah
okay
okay I think if I'm done dressing up
[Music]
um
where am I
[Music]
foreign
moves around like that I I I I I can't
figure that one out yet without taking
more time
like that I got the front perfectly it's
like sticking perfectly
maybe if the if the stick covers up the
sword anyway maybe it's better without
the back for now
next time I'll try to
I'll try to no no hood version
okay
looks great right it does blue thank you
ah thank you for the asset looks so good
my hair's a little bit uh
sorry perfectionist kicking in I want to
do one more
one more fix
let's see how perfect I can get it one
more one more try
hey hey
[Music]
oh my God it's so cute and why am I like
dark
link though why
see now the hair doesn't clip anymore
and it's like perfectly centered
I think I never had a hood so perfectly
on top of my body before come on
eyes perfect and my stick
hey
thank you so much I love it I love it
but why darkling
mmm
oh yeah it's a chicken gluteus steak I
see the glue now
ah because like you do you put stick
things together with with glue in the
game right yeah yeah yeah yeah
I hope we can get that off afterwards
I'm not sure if we can
also well done I've I've never opened up
the game yet because I heard there's a
cut scene
um that we might want to hear
there you go
I might want to see yeah fancy cutscene
I have also not spoiled myself yet uh
from you know my favorite Zelda tuber
so I really I I know the breath of the
wild story I've watched as I said many
times before a hundred percent I'm gonna
say a hundred I really mean a hundred
percent very thoroughly plate
um breath of the wild playthrough
four times mm-hmm
so
I I think I know the game but I've never
played it myself
so that'll be interesting let's hope the
audience find from the get-go
I hear it you should hear it too
turn it up
do you do yeah the Kodak seats too all
hundred of the or the how many was there
more than 100 but he was really pissed
because you'd get poop in exchange
you hear this right
oh wait it's crackling for sure this
should do the trick
Legend of Zelda
here's of the kingdom here we go
footsteps and a loading screen ah there
we go oh
yeah that's on the first trailer isn't
it
Adele is so cute on that one that really
gave some people hopes that this strange
Bloom keeps getting thicker you might
even be able to play her or with her
or her English voice
uh
I prefer her German voice
damn
we've been descending for a while now
these tunnels are deeper than I thought
I'll make it louder what could be down
here
Zelda princess of Hyrule
doesn't need introduction
I'll be moving right away
oh oh I want to go back
link has something called your attention
yes I need to check if there's an item
up there
whatever it is we can play plan to look
at is on our way back up let's continue
this there will be no back out there you
won't be
reply go back out come on I know it okay
I'm following oh is there something
there now okay sorry thankfully you walk
so slow beneath Hyrule Castle oh is this
right after breath of the wild ends and
then we're checking out right away like
the next day if everything's okay or
it's just like many years later I guess
we'll find out well pretty
but you scared should I put your cape on
the ground so you can go over this
milady
some time has passed Full Hearts Max is
sweet oh I didn't know this isn't
falling out after coming into contact
with the Gloom drifting through these
Caverns
though here it seems almost Misty and
not concentrated enough to harm us
well keep going
from beneath Hyrule Castle thanks blank
we do not know what rates below so we
need to be ready for anything
but
I know I'll be okay with you link ah
then you guys should mystery Stay
Together Forever
foreshadowing
oh yeah damn so many hearts I probably
will never get so many highs in this
play for will I
will be difficult to get all of them
okay so far the controls are okay
but are there more press for crouching
uh-huh
um if I press plus it will always show
me this that's so nice put away with b x
jump I could jump whoa
yeah and some cello games you can not
jump yourself you can alright you can
only jump when there's something to jump
on
guys
I'm crafting increases yourself making
it easier to sneak up on Frozen animals
or in Zelda
oh awesome surprise
I never imagined this was all deep
beneath Harbor Castle
yeah me neither
when I was a child I asked my father if
there was anything below the castle he
told me there was though seeing it for
ourselves or even discussing the matter
was forbidden
it was forbidden well obviously you're
hiding like skeletons and all kinds of
crazy [\h__\h] down there
no one in our family knew anything more
than that
hmm
would that maybe be good if I put the
chat bottom left
is that okay too for now maybe
should I go first oh link
what
the master the master sword
oh it's glowing
my monster stick ain't glowing
it must be sensing something
I know we had a reason for concern ever
since the end of the calamity
the castle has fallen into neglect
but I never could have imagined anything
like these tunnels were hiding here
ah you must be careful as we move deeper
okay
careful careful careful
oh this is scary I don't know I don't
want to know what's behind this
oh scary
the seller of
Hyrule Castle
what are those eggs
dragon eggs or so it looks like could be
Dragon x
what I've never
oh this is how it feels oh wait I got
full stamina
if she walks so slowly I think I can
just climb uh and still be like
as fast as she is what are you looking
at
[Laughter]
these are ruins from an ancient
civilization
oh shika Maybe
wait something's written here might
these ruins be from the Zone I add the
other ones heard of those too
all right uh let me continue climbing
and
wait for me I'm just practicing my
climbing skills
what physics are against me
what are you looking at now
you should look at it from other angles
she's taking pictures
whoa
can we take a selfie too oh
these carvings I'm sure there's an eye
origin I've seen designs like this in my
studies
are said to have lived long ago in the
time of earliest Legend the earliest
Legend of Zelda is our day in the first
Zelda game hmm aren't they
they possess god-like powers and had a
prosperous civilization in the sky
oh oh I saw some speculations and I do
also wonder and would be excited if it's
true that this has maybe some connection
with the Legend of Zelda A Skyward Sword
that fully on our Channel too it would
be nice if there was a connection
um
I mean it would make so much sense to
connect something like that because it's
also playing in the sky maybe we see
groose's uh
uh uh future family
they possession many history books tell
us about its own eye but none give us
the full picture much is still unknown
about them
[Music]
es come out of eggs
maybe there are some donuts in these
eggs
in these eggs
those eggs
XXX oh oh my is that so nice when they
look funky
wow it's like when the museum means it's
a museum day
me and dada on the museum date
what's gonna happen I
finally the war is over and me and Zelda
can just live a normal happy life just
like we're supposed to girlfriend
boyfriend
let's take a selfie come on let's take a
selfie I'm gonna put it in our album
lovey-dovey album
is this what the sonai looked like they
seem so different than us and such large
ears
how did the ruins from a civilization in
the sky end up here beneath the castle
and why was it not allowed to come down
here that's the real question
it looks like the path ahead goes even
deeper let's continue link
I hope you're uploading all of those
pictures automatically onto an online
Drive
because I don't think you're gonna
make it out of here life
that's just my assumption
Zelda cloud
surely they have a chica
produced Cloud right the Chica Cloud wow
I want to swing my sword but he jumped
well my lightsaber
monsters down here uh please give me a
tutorial on how to fight because I don't
know do I have like an arrow because
there's up so high
[Music]
do you don't have to save me for the
bats
it's bad
of course I'm not hurt I have the must
sword I have Full Hearts full stamina
she's so worried women
whoa It's mirrors wow
oh
our left side is good people right side
as bad people almost at the royal family
being attacked include stories of a
Great War fought long ago it was a
conflict between Allied tribes and
someone only ever referred to as the
Demon King where's the Demon King Ghana
I have heard that often Demon King but
what is it possible do these murals
depict the same Legend
oh that's really cool
this is similar to the statues we saw
earlier looks like Yoda
and these figures look like hylians
mm-hmm
we're praying to them depiction
certainly suggests that the zonai
descended from the heavens
[Music]
it is said that my ancestors the first
of hyrule's royal family
born from a union with Gods who had
descended from the heavens
the first one is that the one we signed
a trailer
murals tell a similar
and if they are accurate others
in the middle they must have forged a
relationship with the hylians of that
time
oh
why does she sound so freaked out he
seems to be stealing something of
incredible it's an evil airpod
wait no those are the tears of the
Kingdom
[Music]
well thank god of the lines aren't you
happy you didn't learn [\h__\h]
and a fierce battle against him um
fiercer than the one that you just
witnessed of me fighting him in the
previous game he really does
get rotated
that one's rotated on the bottom right
oh he's gone
amazing you must be the Great War
recorded in the Royal histories
this is the imprisoning war and the
events that led up to it wow
free such a nerd
[Laughter]
intention of
poora is so cute
I've been seeing you that all the time
should we blow it up looks like
this well no problem let's just blow it
up
carefully of course
that's probably like is behind that is a
big solution like a big
spoiler
link let's keep moving deeper and we'll
only get to see it like at the end of
the game
and we'll be like oh I wish I would have
seen this at the beginning of the game
because then we would have had a
shortcut and everything would have been
so much easier we would have understood
from the beginning like obviously
everything all the answers are behind
this
where are my bums
yeah moving deeper on ah no problem man
it won't be dangerous
I mean don't even don't even pay
attention to the uh yeah yeah so this
becoming more and more to this [\h__\h]
taking shape slowly at least that's what
it feels like to me
uh is that like you sure about this
I can't tell you how excited I am
the mirrors down here their images
support so much of what historians have
written about
uh yeah oh all right I guess I go it's
like fainting if when we walk into it so
I guess we're still good
go away go away
Dark Matter going
one of these things mean I want to
translate
let's talk some more before you die or
so I find myself wondering how did this
area come to be so forgotten why was our
history left hidden here
I guess it must be hiding a dark dark
secret
did the royal family in those ancient
times want this place and these morals
to remain secret and out of sight I
guess it's like there's like a spoiler
alert
spoiler you will die
you should not know the future
because then you will act differently
and change the future we don't want that
um
oh God so many stairs yesterday when I
was hiking somewhere around the end
there was also like endless [\h__\h]
stairs and I was already dead
although the stairs are really the worst
thing of the whole hiking day
oh the music is going crazy
all back up
um
please listen to me
I can't take the feeling that I'm
missing something here why would anyone
want to keep this a whole area secret I
it can't be because of what's shown in
those mirrors
yeah it's a really loud night club down
there you don't want to go there no no
no no no whoa
that's a cool nightclub
oh [\h__\h]
whoa
oh [\h__\h] that's what they've been hiding
in their basement
that's crazy
she looks possessed to me
I don't think so
what is this place
I know give me a cutscene
not yet let's continue but we must be
extremely careful
now is there gonna be a fight
hmm
what is that
actually my new hairstyle of my casual
outfit looks a bit like uh hers
short a little bit fluffy with braids
oh
what the [\h__\h] one tier of the Kingdom
cute it's an airpod
stick it in your ear
creepy creepy creepy creepy
is that
gun on dorbs mummy form zombie form oh
God scary wait wait wait for it
[Music]
[Applause]
leaving me at exactly
Darkness
shattered so easily against my power
cannot save you from me
[Music]
carries that fragile sword I think
louder
that was all you could do
have you
no one name
what have we unleashed would this also
have happened if we wouldn't have gone
down there
oh
um um
um
oh
we [\h__\h] it up
looking
oh
and he falls down
oh like she stays there
[Applause]
this is like a Gandalf moment
oh
[Music]
come on
that part would I think generally that
scene we saw in the trailer but not that
part where she disappears we only saw
her falling right
I think
teleporting I don't remember that
the creepy hand
sprayed out of The Adams Family
oh
interesting opening
of course she doesn't die but
she's in big trouble
yeah and the master sword apparently
useless
that's why we're working with glue now
putting together sticks and stones
to fight evil
improving our technology oh and even
improving our arm
we now have a bionic arm
super glue and duct tape yeah just super
glue and duct taped and lost the sword
back together strengthen it like that
wow we got fancy tattoos now but still
no nipples
I think that's the biggest problem
we're Nike and small he looks so small
looks like a child
ew he's got like
funky nails
are those stick on nails like they look
like stick on nails
hello
I've heard a great deal about you from
Zelda oh
okay
why am I I got stripped of my heart
why did I get stripped off my clothes
your arm however was beyond saving I had
to replace it unless the injury endanger
you further can we do that with watoto
as well
oh
is it shattered too
who was talking to me by the way when I
was like watching the game a million
times I was watching it in German so
this voice maybe it's familiar to you
guys but it's not familiar to me is it a
familiar Voice or no
I really prefer German zeldado you guys
should listen to German Zelda
Neil not familiar okay let's go let's go
link
just stop saving the world in the end it
always leads to this kind of stuff maybe
that's the problem
yeah I kind of want to play it in German
I could change it but you know
they can't master sword wow the sword
that seals the darkness its sacred power
has been diminished after being ravaged
by the Gloom beneath Hyrule Castle who
would have thought that the master sword
doesn't ever tell the game you work so
hard to get to and it's always like like
depicted as like the strongest sword you
could ever get immediately gets like
destroyed so easily like this and all
its value is suddenly just
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh man
uh I can never fight for the master
sword proudly ever again
laughs
trash oh he still uses it
was weapon attack with you a quick
weapon but why okay
that is so somewhat usable maybe better
than a stick even who knows
wow
wait wow
it's really nice to see this in person
being controlled by myself
kind of stuff
the Wheels of Time
we also tell him and this do I put my
hand on it
he gets it
he's not as dumb as I thought he was
it was pretty obvious but even then
often it's not enough
oh
look behind you
thanks for the uh pinky no I didn't see
it no
no idea probably won't get to see it for
a while
or use it for a while
turning
the wheels are turning
this to me
reminds me of
Super Mario 64.
the best level oh can't do anything here
actually oh okay okay okay
just like Super Mario 64.
huh
yeah quite pretty but I mean where
exactly in these ruins are we like are
we even deeper now or
I failed to jump
nice climbing this is a motion
uh tutorial I think
let's jump again Charlie
[Music]
oh wait it's not as shallow as I thought
yeah we're fine we're fine we're gonna
break our thingies
and never Jam they really want me to
practice the jump hook
Landing is one even from a great height
will prevent you from taking fall damage
even if it's just a puddle I'm gonna
take you by your word now
um
yeah nice Turtle there's a chest
Minecraft physics yeah
what's inside
oh pants
or leggings and a skirt
archaic archive are our cry leg wear
simple classic like where they're one
worn and showing their age but they've
still got a few good years left in them
it can be a bit cumbersome to have to
tie the straps oh
open inventory of plus ah okay
oh it looks different
without the leggings it's just a skirt
what
oh didn't it say pants I guess there's
maybe pants inside I love it when skirts
come with pants
um so sewn into them especially in Asia
I feel like I see that way more often
than in western clothing shops but that
is so convenient because
I like wearing skirts but the wind is
not on my side let me tell you that oh
pretty
pretty oh we're gonna see a beautiful
view probably past the shadow
I mean okay it's mostly clouds I thought
we were going to see more of the
landscape
it's an idea we don't know if there's
water down there either and we don't
have our paraglider with us so I think
he's gone insane
that's insane like should we climb up
can we climb up there if I wanted to
[Laughter]
foreign
do I even want to try
it don't doesn't he normally oh
grab hold on to things
are these anti-climbing mechanisms
no you really can't tell
okay
can't climb wide surfaces huh
what white surfaces specifically anyway
backflip now it turns forward
and what now ah okay there's water thank
God
oh
ah there are pants inside
is that a flying snake
[Music]
the dragon is it a dragon
well
[Music]
hit it
hey the legend of zeld the tears of the
Kingdom yay
[Music]
accelerate hold our
[Applause]
[Music]
fun
nice
exciting opening that Free Fall must
have felt really good for him
this is some fake leaves
damn
dragon
what's he doing
he's thinking he's safe up there for me
unlike the other dragons that were
killed in breath of the Wild
but now I am also in the Sky High up
here
you're not safe from me here
As Long As I Got
this stick
which is probably totally better
wooden branches such as this are pretty
common but it's surprisingly well
balanced oh really it doesn't do much
damage but can serve as a weapon is the
two
how much damage it does I want to see it
in comparison with my master sword
press and hold equip or take out a
weapon from your inventory
uh-huh okay
it's strong
[\h__\h] three branches stronger
double the damage uh better take a
couple with me then
how much inventory do I have let's say
we have to pick up everything right
Skye's room is a common mushroom that
grows nutrisons guy Islands eat it to
restore health
we have to pick up everything to be
ready for everything what was that sound
oh wait I have another one uh uh uh wait
uh
all right can my master sword also
completely break I hope I hope not it's
like an ancient
an ancient oh tree branch a stronger one
or what
Parts Soldier construct horn
and a Zone I charge I've heard of this
you just don't forget don't you
side in the in a demo
ooh Sky's rooms I hate mushrooms
I need mushrooms this is my last resort
what my master sword
my master sword is my last resort
suffocation
no breathing don't give a [\h__\h] if I cut
my arm because he really cut his arm
bleeding
oh
I have a pre-branch I have an apple
um apple tree branch
could really stick them together but I
don't have the glue yet why do I go
first how do I run
oh that was blasted I was thinking maybe
I can run with our
oh oh that looks so a little bit like a
sword a wooden stick oh
a tree branch with an added grip
wonderful
nice last window this is a beautiful
hash patio patio patio
never tree branch can never have enough
tree branches
um
Alan say it's a sword this is like a
stick with a
oh with a handle hello
oh I can't hit you
what are you cleaning personal
a broom
[Music]
uh we're gonna fight now or
I killed you kind of killed why it's
weird you're cute you're like a lizard
[Music]
link I have waited for you Princess
Zelda left something for you in my care
oh the phone
does it still have the pictures this is
the pure iPad I am told it is an
invaluable tool that will provide you
with Direction
[Music]
the eye is so cool
I like this design
I should sell that for
the switch like exactly that
oh Zelda sounds princess Zelda's priced
device it has a variety of features that
are essential for adventure
use the features of the pure pad with
minus okay
I received it from Princess Zelda I have
now passed it on to you where did you
when when where
how
what the [\h__\h]
in the past maybe because she trapped
probably right she probably that's my
assumption trail to the past and this
thing is ancient so even though
okay so there's like this
um
different
timelines of the time and she traveled
to the past and then she gave it to this
thing and yep even though I just saw her
in a few in the future or in a current
time yeah yeah yeah
that's just a theory a game theory
my records indicate that princess Zella
is waiting at the location right on this
map that's a lie that must be a lie my
message has been delivered where am I
we stand in the garden of time oh Garden
of time
got enough time
is this a raised part of the Hyrule
castle and it's
Heaven haven't haven't we like walked in
this before in a different Zelda game I
don't know
could that be it
like part of the you know
that would be nice that would be cool
no
Corona Garden the Temple of Time is
visible from ear
it was used in the distant past many
rights and ceremonies of the Kingdom
were held there
Temple of time but no more now it is a
lonely place no one visits
or sad
oh there's never a bot over there on the
right side
find Princess Zelda okay I touch
does it activate
something
what does it do ah
oh a bridge
wow
fascinating that is high tech
I also like that they use the eggs still
here
um as decoration which in my opinion
really means this is obviously all still
Hyrule Castle parts
because we saw it inside the ruins
was this
oh
you call this vases the vases of
tears of the Kingdom
come back my baby is a fret well
understandable I'm sorry I'm just you
know getting uh nostalgic pots yeah pots
must be prone you know
hello you seem new here wait you you'll
go oh wait this is the front view
do you intend to use that as a weapon
against the soldier construct
[Music]
Soldier constructs are those of us given
strict orders to protect this land
the zonai who created us directed them
to eliminate trespassers they will
consider you a trespasser you must treat
them as a serious threat
oh
allow me to offer unsolicited advice
it is crucial to maintain a proper
distance and Target your opponents
swinging haphazardly
will not yield results
thank you I did pretty well without
logging on but that helps definitely in
the future
you may now practice targeting on me if
you want it are you sure
but please do not actually what do you
mean oh only targeting you're lucky are
you good it's good you said that because
I would have attacked you to
okay I can Target you it's kind of like
you're asking for me to attack you
though
I feel like you want me to
but you're so cute
well I didn't
treat carefully around any Soldier
construct you see our creator gave them
strict orders to protect this land
okay
okay so um I will not I will not hit you
so cute
for a weapon oh yeah I kind of already
did that by accident
where do I go now
jump down here or what
I guess so
what do you call
hook I suppose how convenient that
there's always a puddle of water
a puddle of water where there's a place
to jump
if I was a better streamer I would have
attempted to
cat stands Prague
oh
that is oh
yeah no not the mushrooms
mushroom you heard nature weren't you
supposed to protect this place
I think you failed
yeah good argument right
I don't see you're protecting it I saw
you hurting it I'll tell your boss where
is your manager I want to speak to your
manager oh I can't carry anymore we're
already full really
there's a funky verb
looks like a
like a falcon or something like that why
I wonder if we can shoot those later and
then roast them probably right
I kind of lost track of where is front
whatever front means
you can cook basically anything right
where am I supposed to go
this game is so open
was this the water yeah
oh there's some more of those
light thingies
[Music]
I like to go hiking in here
it's very beautiful hiking in like an
ancient old ruined setting like this
I wonder where you could do something
like where I wonder where you could go
hiking but in this kind of like
environment
oh
[Music]
maybe in Italy or Greece
definitely in Greece
but yeah when I was looking at like
vacation spots in Greece
some islands they're like more for
hiking
but you kind of need to First rent a car
and then go to like somewhat close to
the hiking spots
and I don't even have a license so I
would normally not go to that kind of
place but
maybe sometime in the future
oh this old one had a donut charge in it
must be buses maybe but it's kind of
like I don't know it doesn't
feel so smart to me to assume because
Grace has a lot of islands and to assume
oh I will go here oh God I'll surely be
fine with a bus
um
who knows that there's really buses to
go anywhere I saw also that you could if
you have a license again you could also
just rent like bikes I saw some people
do that
oh my mom you know she has like a lot of
veggies in her garden her big big ass
Garden
and she gave my brother
a glass of like spicy pepper sauce that
she made
thankfully she didn't bring me any
because I would not have been able to
eat that
but she brought us yesterday so what I
did yesterday on my day off was I woke
up I went hiking I came back I quickly
climbed what
I quickly cleaned some more of my
apartment for like another hour until my
mom came and I already started cleaning
like the day before and I went to Ikea
and I bought this and that right
um but yeah I was cleaning like crazy
my brother when he entered my apartment
he was like oh you cleaned
he immediately noticed that I cleaned
yeah and I cleaned like a lot of stuff
that had to be like thrown out I washed
old uh old clothes that were peed on by
my cats you know
I talked about it in my member's dream
yeah this and that
and
uh my mom arrived I was still
frantically cleaning so I was like I
started when she arrived I started
vacuum cleaning the whole apartment
but she came over because she had a
um
wait
she had a
job interview today don't worry
uh she didn't really want the job so and
she failed so she's happy
yeah and uh
whoa It's why
oh no no set everything on fire when I
do this
oh I should try cooking here maybe
don't throw that [\h__\h] throw it
don't want it
I'm starting a forest fire it'll be fine
yeah so she came over and uh she brought
some self-made noodles because that's
her new favorite thing now
she got a a noodle machine makes herself
fresh noodles every day
let's learn how to cook
wait can I can I
if I do this can I take out the fire
no stop the fire B
thank you and it looks like it's new
like it never burned ah this one's gone
okay how to cook so I I think in the
previous game you just put everything in
your hand and then you throw it onto the
tray
sorry
so I don't know how about we combine
mushrooms with pepper
uh hold
oh yeah he holds it the same way
is that a good combination
or should I not like mix it
[Music]
um
well
I will mix it and return to the game and
then oh will it make the [\h__\h]
oh
[Applause]
why am I so excited I heard this like a
million times I love it so good that
they kept it
I could
okay
[Music]
it heals more than hearts that I have
maybe didn't need to put so many
ingredients in hmm
oh we made a spicy fruit and I didn't
throw in any fruit I purposefully didn't
throw anything well there you go you
don't even have the frozen fruit if you
want something with fruit
um that is weird
to check a meals ingredients selected
from your inventory and then select
recipe late uh
food
ah check recipe okay could I like remake
it like a like a shortcut then I see
I see this is the thing I meant with
they got like recipe cards now it's
really cute
to remind you how you made it I guess
let's just make
uh a small mushroom dish
mushroom skirt okay okay that works we
just need like smaller food now
um one more
no no don't eat hold and I guess we can
put an apple in there
[Music]
I'm cooking let me cook
oh
I don't know what it is but this cooking
sound is this makes me happy
you get me though don't you
let's make I know let's make
spicy Apple
skewer so that would be nice
things are happening
oh
simmered fruit wow that that actually
heals a lot
oh
more
I've I already collected so much food
oh
it does I don't know I don't know if it
looks I wouldn't eat it but
just today one of the hotels hell
episodes I saw
um gosh what was that from
I think it was supposed to be Mexican
food
uh some kind of fruit on the skewer with
like a Mexican spicy
sauce is that an actual thing that they
eat
the way they made it sounds good but I
just don't like spicy food
it was really cute it was the episode
where the the one of the pantry chefs
the pantry chefs Chef who was kind of
like quirky and dorky but cute but
really motivated and happy
um he on his off time has like a food
truck and big hotel does even though
it's like a pretty supposed to be an
upscale one doesn't have a [\h__\h]
breakfast to offer at all so in the
morning he goes out to The Food Market
the farmer's market and he finds the the
pantry Chef uh with his own food truck
and then tastes his food which is like
quesadillas
boobs hello can we kill them they're
probably too fast and they make like
quesadillas and
um
and and some cool drinks and all that
and then he's like yo your food is like
any better than anything I ate in the
hotel and he's so happy and like oh my
God who knows if it really was that good
I think maybe he just said it for the
sake of you know the program oh they're
not they're not bothered by me huh now
he is
wait
[\h__\h] I I didn't want to hit him anyway
no no I wouldn't hurt a bird
and I can find them no way
no way is that a clock
uh riddle oh no it doesn't
oh no yeah and and then so they
basically they create a breakfast menu
with all those uh Mexican food items and
they let the the pantry Chef become the
breakfast Chef you know
all right let's do this
amazing
I'm amazed at the fact that it actually
hit them sheesh they were positioned in
the wrong way long stick a long stick
fashion from a tree branch I was able to
pick that up I thought I couldn't ah
yeah okay
um wait
no wait uh here here
this drop the tree branch and pick up
the long stick yeah
Diaz
a
these birds are so funny
what is the which direction should I go
well I should take a look at the map
like more often this is the first time
I'm looking at the map at the bottom
it's behind me maybe I should go
somewhere else so you guys see the map
too do you guys want to see the map
maybe I go here actually
and the chat girls
here
top right is also empty so I think you
guys could go there
what is that
what is that other Island over there
God super freaking out what the [\h__\h] is
that it's like a a railway
I want to go to that Island
this Temple that's the
the sky Temple thingy
that they said no one ever visits so we
should go there right
[Music]
at the temple time
almost at him because he runs into me
[Applause]
[Music]
yo those birds are really easy to hit
damn poor Birds you're stupid for their
own good and some Enemy No not enemy
friends
that one over there is an enemy let me
take care of them first
so far I'm having fun but I have a hinge
that
I will
have to or be motivated and and
[Music]
um
what's the word pushed not pushed but
like
it will be recommended to play some of
this off screen
to get I don't know a stock of food and
all that oh toasty Sky mushroom
a hinge hunch
incentivized exactly
because it's a big [\h__\h] game right
and there's so much you can do
now I wonder if you pretty much follow
the objectives but but don't like speed
run it just play normally casually how
many hours it will take you
I mean can you already tell because it's
the first day and no anybody who
finished the game already obviously
speed speed skimmed through it so
um
if you play it normally I wonder how
long it takes if it takes longer than my
Fire Emblem playthrough
I think obviously not as a streamer but
as a normal player the longer the better
for this kind of game I mean you can
play it shorter shorter but if you want
to have more fun of the game
and enjoy it then it's better if it
lasts longer right because it takes ages
until a new Zelda comes out
saw a one hour 30 Speed Run already holy
[\h__\h] no thank you I'm not gonna I don't
even have the skills to speed run it
like that
[Music]
um
chocolate
yeah open the Wild game so enjoy it
slowly but for a streamer
since I'm a streamer I don't want to
waste 200 hours on the end so
maybe I'll play some off-screen
you where was the dead cute when I say
cute it's not that cute
um
oh I had not noticed before that you
were unfamiliar to me my apologies
I'm on my task is to explain anything
that visitors might require knowledge of
you may have questions about this place
please rest assured then the construct
can answer them
they're so cute
I recall that your question was about
roasting food I roast ingredients by
placing them besides the fire
all right let me put my kfp chickens
besides the fire let's just sit down
it's it's safe it might be a bit warm
but
you want to stay close to the fire
otherwise you will catch a cold
[Music]
trust me trust me
nah you won't get cooked you won't get
roasted don't worry about it no
I do not eat but I'm given to understand
that it improves the taste
I will create those roasted ingredients
in order to enhance their nutritional
value
do you have ingredients I invite you to
use this fire to roast them okay so I
just put them on the ground
is what you're saying
I have a
chair
should I put the raw meat down now let's
just
hold hold hold
um back and then drop oh just leave them
for a while
oh that one's catching on fire that's
not good
uh is it oh no that's good but the other
one I picked up too early maybe
is this one roasting
can I push it
I think he was in the wrong spot
no no okay it works for one of them
I'm just gonna throw it I guess straight
into the fire
ooh okay I think that works yeah and
then okay
I thought I just had to place them next
to the fire all right bye bye thank you
construct that's a weird name I want to
give you a proper name because you guys
are cute I want to name you like Billy
Billy or
um
Jimmy
when in doubt name it Jimmy
all right let's see what's up there
can I take these flowers no
okay
it's an adventure
[Music]
broken
different from I think uh
uh switching in the middle of the battle
that's what I was not looking forward to
foreign
[Music]
yeah okay no problem I got so many uh
tree branches that I have to use up
anyway
[Music]
okay I'm getting the hang of it oh he
has like a somewhat proper looking sword
let me take that and that oh
yeah right because I was fighting it
um raise your shield with ZL
a rusty Broad Sword
five damn wow he automatically equips it
oh
wait oh no uh no don't don't throw
cancel fro
with how
that wasn't that r ah it said l
ah wait oh wait is he didn't people say
Zelda uh link is left-handed
but his wait when you're left-handed
don't you hold
the sword on the left hand
foreign
what happened why was left-handed not
good anymore I would have liked some
Lefty representation
[Music]
I I didn't try to cut off your eggs or
anything no no no no
[Laughter]
hmm
what uh out of context quote Oh [\h__\h]
we're not allowed to enter
cross his legs
that door will open only to those with
sufficient power
I'm sorry
I did not intend
it was I that spoke to you earlier oh
that arm originally belonged to me
I am wrong a cute furry
[Music]
source of the right arm
oh my right arm
forgive me for appearing to you in this
manner
ah because you're lacking one now I no
longer have a physical
form and no physical Harmony verb
in any case that arm should allow you to
open this door
seems to have lost the power to do so
is that what's up no is that what that
was you might be able to restore it but
you would need to enter a place filled
with sacred light
uh-huh
of course
why not visit the shrines on this island
oh first shrine
his ears are so cute
[Music]
shrines
sure they are
[Music]
you really sure it better be the key
also I would like a shirt like sometime
soon
the closed door
my adventure log okay all right so we go
over there
um
how do we get there let's see
can I jump from here no oh yeah
oh that was fun
no fall damage
there's a Togo around somewhere where I
want to find it
can I use that now oh
attack
enemies from afar ZR and then R2 release
oh okay okay cool cool cool cool cool
Five Arrows all right what should we
shoot
oh there's motion control
[Music]
you'll see I mean that was a nice shot
but that was my first shot let's see how
my
how my aim is generally in the game but
I think the motion control is actually
gonna be what I'll be using
seems to be easier to get like a an
accurate shot on a
on a smaller Target
oh this thing I wanna can you ride this
I want to try it
oh what's that over there
good for position
um
not bad I must say the motion controls
we open
oh we open and find a Secrets all night
out yeah we don't know yet what's it
good for
eign
wonderful
it's coming together oh
wait oh yeah I can climb I forgot haha
restroom not the mushroom it's the
restroom
and down
and jump
I'm still I'm still learning the basics
still getting used to it
oh
uh we might be learning soon
how to move this stuff to create a
bridge over there oh
[\h__\h]
is that gonna be like a a red I saw that
in the trailer I think
shrine
let's go
it has hands it's a stone with hands
oh okay heads is hands too
my first shrine
[Music]
it's a shrine
I will figure this one out
I will use up all my brain power and not
asking for help shrine
it's a shrine
trust me I got the big brains
I'll prove it to you cause I'm a gamer
girl yeah yeah yeah
hi
anyone talk okay so you've made it here
this is the shrine of light long ago I
felt these places with light that purges
evil
I believed this light will restore an
ability your right arm has lost
now then extend your hand
which one the fake one
oh the music
[Music]
oh what's that
who's that
[Music]
Ultra hand oh grab and move upstairs
there we go now we have them we can
rotate them get rotated
and stick them to uh sticking we can
already stick to the glue
this is the ultra
Ultra hand ability
it allows you to move objects freely and
attach them to other objects with it you
will be able to build a great number of
things really anything you can imagine
well here we go we get this one before
before the basic breath of the Wild
Things
hmm
use ultra hand and receive the blessing
from the shrine
I hope it's easy
tutorial Shrine usability activate the
ability in your right hand
what a l
oh oh oh there's also motion control
grab
rotate
what
ah
uh well physics right it will fall down
nicely anyway
surely
and now
that was not what I wanted is there
a ladder
um
uh
vertical there we go hey
okay
[Music]
we must do it again
horizontal vertical oh this one's longer
oh we have to stick them together first
yeah okay wait
please don't fall down
okay
I might we might even be able to do it
without sticking them together
well I don't know how do you stick them
together ah
wait uh
uh
uh I want it higher yeah oh okay
uh uh wait let's uh
no no why is it so why is it so diagonal
well
I'll try it
uh it's stuck together but
it's not exactly where at all how I
wanted it but okay
I think you guys know how I wanted it
but it's okay well I'll figure this one
out
uh first bring it up higher
uh
we can also turn it like this yeah yeah
yeah yeah
why is it such a
why do I have to move it by such big
like distances you know what I mean
there's no like more I guess if I turn
my own body I can turn it a bit more
exact
that worked
[Music]
and now I know how to rush how to Dash
oh
okay what is all this stuff
ah do we have to stick these things
together
to do what what exactly are we making
what are we making oh there's a there's
a rail ah I'm making a platform for
myself
[\h__\h] why did I do that
well it was already broken anyway
um
wait oh God how ugh I don't know ah
let's make it flat
oh
leave it on the ground but why are these
These are chained
I guess I guess no for now we can just
attach this
to
this platform right and then just try to
hang it into the rail
right
maybe I should stand on that then how do
I make it move let's just start moving
without it without me right away let me
better stand on it
can I do this what can I raise it while
I'm standing on it
no I don't think so
what what uh
this should work
ah no like this
what's up
oh I don't know what the rest of the
things were for but hey
[Music]
could you have used the other things too
this was the most obvious solution I
think
good enough yeah
yay first try of course first try
you'll have well what
you have done well to reach this place
we offered a slide that will cleanse you
of evil
pretty
cleanse me yes
let's go
cleanse my skin I want to be beautiful
chocolate while I say that while I'm
eating chocolate
mmm
oh
I'm Gonna Change
[Music]
light of blessing or one
um
a crystal that glows with a light that
purges ancient evil and purifies with
its Radiance wow
May the light of blessing Grant you the
strength you seek
bye bye
you gotta kick me out of here now
yeah
is this a loading screen
safe Skydive when you need to die from
the sky to the surface ah
never mind
I think it said land in deep water
hi I didn't
you did very well cutting through that
Shrine and He restored an ability this
is wonderful if you visited and complete
two more shrines you should be able to
open the door or two
really I thought this was like a long
Quest
you may want to Mark the shrines in the
distance with pins then you'll never
lose track of where they are are there a
couple more in like reachable distance
the Pura pad office offers you a very
useful scope it's quite handy don't try
a 360 no scope though
a 18 what
the sculpt and pins view distant things
and mark them with pins
um press R okay
oh
do I see a shrine
that's a shrine
that's that's really cool that you like
look at things and it knows what you
want to Mark not the thing behind it or
not the thing in front of it but like
pretty much it knows
that's the shrine that we're going to
um
and
zoom out no
Ah that's another one nice okay
let's go to those
how far which one is closer
um
maybe the red one
how do I get there
I you could you could probably can you
because it's open world so I'm guessing
you can just jump down all of these
islands and go straight to like the
bottom ground
um
but like if I'm a beginner and I do that
by accident how do I go back up
you went for blue
you can but I'd recommend blue ones oh
okay
try it
oh is it actually not possible it won't
let me ah okay so it forces me to go for
this kind of tutorial oh very nice as a
beginner I'm I'm glad
okay
I think I understand the path
aha now we built a bridge
uh technology
the zonai and tashika will be proud of
me
uh oh no this is not raged I have to
stick it together
what attach
nice
and brown is this long enough
please don't drop it
it's hard to see if it's long enough
oh
yeah that was just about enough
perfect
can I
can I like jump and pick yeah jump and
pick
where was I going this way
so far you know this game has been like
pretty calm the atmosphere very calm
it's very relaxing right now
I like me some action for the sake of
stream
but it's okay it's okay
I'm enjoying it
the gluing has a comical sound effect I
generally think the gluing itself the
fact that it's possible is kind of dorky
wait what are you doing here
I see that they're still at work even
now ah those ones we originally created
the concerts to assist in our endeavors
all of us were fond of them I never
imagined they would continue to carry
out their assigned tasks to this day oh
that is some determination to your job
I agree I like the glue I mean it's
helpful but it's dorky
the fact that their labor no longer
serves any purpose yet they perform it
still it is disquieting to me
oh do you have a purpose they told me
how to roast things I mean I may have
been able to know it without them as
well
can a woodchuck chuck
can I chop whoa
oh will they regrow
today we grow
whoa cool
I'm Animal Crossing now
did you get how I used it as a verb
oh my I should just chop these ones
whoa
so I know that the wood and the fire
stone you can make a fire in the game
but is there anything else you can make
with wood I don't remember
you would think there would be more
things
or maybe you can make arrows with wood
who knows
don't cut them all
too late almost too late
Oh you mean this oh
wait this is like a boat
why is there boat here is an example of
what you can do
sorry I trapped too much too many of
your trees
see you guys forward face it head on
Pardon Me I Was absorbed in my wood
cutting are you here for wood cutting
too
wood cutting is the practice of chopping
down trees to create logs logs can be
combined to assemble platforms uh you
can also chart them down to bake further
wood Lumber has many uses that is why I
come here daily to chuck wood
and yet I still find it difficult to
trap them down in the intended Direction
really
cute that is why you may have heard me
muttering to myself fix your gaze
forward face it head on ah I apologize I
have been rambling for some time
there's an ax I no longer need that you
already took good luck with wood cutting
oh has it grown so late already I must
have failed to notice the time Bell I
will rest for today
all day rest too even though they're
robots do they really need rest
oh
[Music]
oh God now it looks like a helmet I
could put it on
so is that a hint for me to make
something useful
I don't know what is that
over there
let's go there
uh oh wait
ah
well I would prefer like a flat platform
do I have to use the oh wait I can
insert maybe
um oh this is how are you back to
working
still haven't found the shirt yet did I
miss it
let's oh I got
can't believe
come on
okay
um
I wanna
use this
I guess oh here's the end of the rail by
the way
for ax is here do they break too
I'm guessing I have to make it a bit
longer
um
[Music]
wait stop rolling
there we go perfect
oh
is this good that looks good
that's what they want me to do right
no no
it's gonna be longer
I'll fall down
uh go up
why was it too short really
really
and this looks like a yeah see it it
should work I just had it
no no no
oh
that is completely on me still being uh
confused of my controls
[Laughter]
[Music]
I just wanted to climb on it
it's okay practice makes perfect
even though my Woodbridge was already so
perfect
but soon I quickly made another one
Ah that's left this way
this way
uh
oh it canceled on its own dangerous
I felt like I had no balance
good that I didn't fall off
okay
what is this thing
it's floating
can I climb on it you guys said light
surfaces I can't clamp up okay
it's like well Magic
this is
you can't answer it either can I move it
oh I can
what do you mean I can move it where
would I move it to
[Music]
me what
what
but if Florida doesn't sound so is it
like wherever I leave it it will float
I can use it as a bridge I guess
I haven't been on this island yet so
maybe they want me to use it here
um
like here can I make this jump you guys
said I cannot really
fall down right oh
[Music]
it looks kind of far
is it really supposed to be used this
way it's probably supposed to be used
over there
that looks a bit closer
like this
I know no no
yes yes yes
how about this now
[Music]
yeah
hey
I thought so oh
is this our shirt Maybe
and a donut charge
[Music]
Amber
no shirt yet
[Music]
um
I will continue to run around naked no
problem
it's not like we're not enjoying this we
worry
are we
okay
[Music]
okay a shrine
grind Tron oh another fire we could cook
some more is this a friendly one that's
a friendly one what are you doing here
let's teach me how to shoot actually I
know how to do it I'm not even gonna
bother you then
okay but let's try
oh [\h__\h] oh no no no no no no no
goodbye
uh
how do I shoot
wait what I just have to let go
and not one hit not one hit
eh
maybe if it's a headshot yeah
they're running so fast
[Laughter]
oh man cute
running around like headless chickens so
cute oh
ah wait
oh
[Laughter]
cute
all right let's cook some more we
haven't even taken a single damage yet
but
I shall cook some more
anything that came out of that no
okay
wait I can't cook on this can I I can
only roast it ah
you guys taught me how to fix that thank
you
well I'll only I'll only do it with one
I don't want to waste it
um
[Music]
how do you like it guys medium rare rare
wow oh that looks good I don't know how
it got that pattern because it was not
on the grill but sure
yummy
okay
what's up
more arrows
but the bow can break too right so
another bow would be nice too oh Amber
I lost track where am I going this way
medium breath medium well medium rare
nowadays oh what happened
[Music]
what made you change your mind
adulthood
don't worry I won't kill you I'll have
to keep some of you alive so you guys
can oh I can cook here
so you guys can we procreate re make
babies
my next batch will also be tasty pardon
me for not noticing you I was absorbed
in preparing my next meal I do not
recall having you haven't seen you
before today I must doubly apologize for
my intentiveness it is the duty yeah you
may post these questions are you
interested in my cooking
no I'm not uneducated in cooking
no actually I already know that I think
thanks though can I cook in your pot
oh no nevermind I think is time even
passing right now
[Music]
did we skip nighttime by being in the
shrine
because it looked like maybe night time
was on its way
but it really wasn't it is it does
I mean I see 15 15 became 15 30.
oh and now 35 okay okay okay
I don't wanna I don't like night time
I don't want it to be night time
wait a mom I'm going away from the blue
one again
gotta uh be careful to not lose track
of where I'm trying to go it looks where
where the [\h__\h] are we
ah over the big water and then we'll be
there and I guess we can oh oh oh oh
yeah I'm confused too
um oh
oh oh oh nice shot
oh No Just attack
okay let's go
[\h__\h]
get up get up
[Music]
hi soul face
oh I like the battle music who is there
someone on the other side
[Music]
finally it's eating food time
okay ah wait ah I'm gonna keep on
pressing the the Y button to fight but
he doesn't automatically take a weapon
huh when he loses his other one uh yeah
are we done
hey back to calm we're good
arrested shield and some other funky
stuff
yeah it was all right wait ah it's not
over I was just gonna ask because uh
battle music because it doesn't end
Oh wow was that a one shot
there it ends and the chest opens
that was fun
I I panicked through some items but no
that was totally on purpose and opal
oh
I would like my aspect do I have another
one no oh this one is like I don't know
magical mystical
it's got some glow around it
I think right now the ax is the best
weapon I can have
the most weapon-like weapon
powerful weapon
mass of Destruction
I wanna pick up the loot from that mob
that I shut down there we go oh there's
a flower here oh stambulb
wait is that is that leak or is it uh
garlic or is it
spring onion it looks like everything
[\h__\h]
where did you hear that
I want my first product but I don't
really see anything that looks like a
cork
riddle
is there really one here
I didn't hear anything
oh there's a boat up there still no
wait I think I hear it
was that was that the bird that was the
Kodak I'm so unsure
that
that oh no oh no nighttime I wanna sleep
scary aren't there more enemies around
when it's night time
oh wait my friend is there now
interesting shall we talk with him
I love this view of the Temple of Time
it always took a moment to appreciate it
whenever I passed by here the garden of
time was quiet the only sound to be
heard was the time bell ringing in the
mornings and evenings
foreign
it was as if the whole place changed at
its time especially at night when the
sound signaled the emergence of
fireflies those were glorious times
oh
I guess fireflies also an item I could
get at night
which could be useful for
certain things but no
no
[Music]
try now
I think you know this kind of game like
breath of the wild and tears of the
Kingdom it's probably pretty normal and
inevitable to lose track of time right
my stone ax is badly damaged oh no what
is that
I didn't see the water I need to reach
my friend are you
Collins
I love the Kodak voices stamina's room
hi I'm too cute you got a big backpack
yeah
this is
[Music]
me
ant
that's a friend yeah
ah I can make you something to get over
to him
[Music]
I'm so tired more
I don't even know how you can ever get
up on your feet with that big ass
backpack it's okay can I move you too
yes I can
wait I'll make you something
can I wait can I stick you directly to
this please
no way
no that's too cruel come on
sorry buddy you'll have to bear with me
for a little bit here
yeah that that could work
bye bye I'll go over there too to
release you I think should I
it's a little bit of a
[Laughter]
h
you can't release himself can he
I'm gonna help you buddy don't worry
[Music]
uh I wanted
yeah straight attached
and then yeah this isn't too bad this is
kind of crap thing I guess it's not too
bad
oh but now if I put it here it won't
move
I don't want it to like
float away without me
there we go
but how do I get back though afterwards
I was so close to my Shrine where's this
on the on the way anyway
that's one Shrine is that the blue one
so
hurt you
how do I unattach uh on Stick wait
foreign
[Music]
wait I'll help you
one more step
there should I attach you to your friend
I'd like to give you something but
here's all my hand yeah you poop
thanks
what is that can I cook with this too
where am I now or fireflies
uh oh no it leads back I guess
yeah
I have to wait uh snake
sneak
will I catch them
no
[Music]
sneak and run
oh
that one is kind of there
you would not believe your eyes oh
I got pretty high up and it was actually
still possible all right then
I hear frog
what are you doing
oh
don't fly away
oh no
is broken do I have another one oh [\h__\h]
uh
ah no
I have to sword can I not break it with
the wooden stick at all
no
man
um
drop it
okay that was not high enough
oh wait
ah yay
was there nothing inside
yeah just the arrow one Arrow such a
huge box for one Arrow
sure makes sense
all right uh
this shall I use that I don't really
need it do I
[Music]
because it goes down on its own anyway
doesn't it
let's try actually I could use the same
thing I think and maybe for going back
up because I mean up there
because that's kind of
yeah
difficult without some wind from
that Coral Cliff or whatever
wait uh
hook it in
and now we're good to go oh
I've got
took me ages to get to the shrine but
we're finally here
fun fun fun fun
nice connections oh do I want more of
these fireflies
nah
away
ah that would have been useful to get
over the lake huh but why is it over
there on the other Islands
can I find us another solution here
maybe just make a platform with
uh wait
just make a platform with the
um
normal logs and then use my color please
to create wind
maybe that works too
because that's a huge Lake
wait there is one here
two actually
wonderful and is that a it's a it's a
baseball bat and it will show
uh
ow [\h__\h] you
what does this one do I know that a lot
of them have like different uses
like they can they can ice enemies
freeze them
this one is unusable in the state but
applying a bit of Elemental stimulation
will change its form
all right let's make a bow
it's kind of stormy isn't it oh there's
there's fish oh my gosh collect some
fish it immediately distracted
swim Away really fast I'm not good at
swimming yet
um
I got one ancient hour one that looks
really tasty actually
I don't see any any others oh wait
there's one there
yes
beautiful connect
[Music]
where do I could respawn on the side
okay good good good I didn't I didn't
pay attention to my stamina this is what
happens when you lose stamina when
you're in the water I see but at least
we passed the night now I'm happy about
that I was wondering if you can use
these leaves no okay that would have
been useful though
uh I should probably eat
let's eat some yummy food
my mushroom skealer
and
okay
let's
uh
I mean if if just like with the food you
could also quickly
recreate these things as long as you
have the materials nearby that would be
nice can you do that
also I don't have an ax so I can't make
more wood goddammit
oh this is why it's so windy here
because I they want they're nice and
they're giving me some wings
get the ability later all right see it's
going there automatically
they've purposefully made it so windy to
make it easy for me
ah this is nice
making my own boat
going across the river catching my own
fish
aha speaking of Ahoy did you guys see
that oh yeah now I have an ax I guess
did you guys see that no
a new guests were announced for our
concerts now it's a Japanese guys so we
have free ID guests now and three
Japanese guests did you see the Japanese
guys sorry suicide Senpai so let's say
bye and my name is senpai
yeah
so the ones who already had a ticket
are hopefully even more hyped now
will be big big big hype hopefully
pulling the heavy weights for that
concert
yeah
[Music]
we will have a lot of fun streaming it
together as a group that too yeah
ah
I wonder
how do you do that like can't you do
like a backwards jump maybe only if
you're focused on the enemy
ah there you go
yeah
wooden stick
ah okay
ding dong
what are you ding-dong for as like
morning time now
anyway we should go to the shrine go go
go go
and go time to prove our brain power
once again
I want to wear these upcoming many
tickets came from though they actually
weren't sold out of seats uh well yeah
uh well
be happy be happy that they're they
added new ones
oh my God
this game Auto saves I assume oh I
actually don't know I guess so
hopefully
don't want to lose all my progress right
but yeah you know
new tickets wait did they also with the
ID ones I think they added new tickets
right and then did they also do the same
for the Japan member announcements
oh
so you've made it here not then extend
your right hand
oh they did
oh another chance for you guys oh oh no
it's the same batch
same bags of new tickets ah but they're
already gone again right I would assume
[Music]
oh wait another uh uh oh attached
something to an equipped weapon or
Shield to enhance it you can undo the
fusion but that will destroy whatever
has been attached ah okay
this is the fusibility
it allows you to view something nearby
to your weapon or Shield thereby
enhancing it
Why not pick up that sword just ahead
and Infuse a nearby object to it use
fuse and receive the blessing from the
shrine
okay
oh
what quickly set an ability press and
hold and select oh okay
but that's a sword
no wait I equip it Rusty Claymore oh 200
sword uh am I attaching I can't I can't
carry it am I attaching this big ass
Stone
uh let me think
let's drop this
and then
so stupid
that is so stupid but now I can break
for this wall
wow okay oh
I'd be a little bit more careful link
you're standing right there where all
the dangerous Boulders will fall on you
I guess he doesn't care about that
oh which way do I go
is this extra
oh
ah
ah I see gonna take a couple of them for
myself for later use thank you
thank you thank you I should be able to
do it with one hit surely
okay
we take the old wooden bow attach
material to arrows attachment
wait keep both drawn press and hold up
and then select okay
I shall try uh no way uh how to Arrow
again this one
oh wait uh
wait stand back I don't want to like set
it on fire maybe it does that
automatically
uh oh wow
come on hit
that worked perfectly let me take all of
these with me now we have burning arrows
fire embryos let's go I like that
that is uh an attachment
then I appreciate
what do you get this does seem I know it
is not extra I guess I would have needed
the key
eventually
wait could I not have put my arrow
into this fire
probably too right that that could have
worked as well
I see but we wanted to learn how it
works with those items
oh we got so many extra fire flower
thingy items that's nice very generous
what do we do here
oh it's a fight
oh okay
uh why are there so many leaves there
you want me to burn him
you want me to burn out
wait don't throw it
in your bed
ah I don't want to die okay get out of
here get out of here what do they want
me to do oh it takes another one
did he stick the stone to the stone
what is he doing ah what is he doing
yeah walking to the fire yeah
oh no it already burnt
okay I'll just fight you normally then
uh
really
all right my weapon's pretty big
constructible
a bow used by Captain construct yata
it's all guys I need to learn I need to
learn uh combat okay
Captain construct horn well
uh should I break this
ouch
what's up here
are there some hidden
weapons here
um
[Music]
how convenient what is this
did I set this on fire
all right uh
let me drop we still have some of this
I'll take
this long stick with me might come in
handy I don't know what that is though
what is that
ah attach this to it like four I can get
like a four new weapon
uh
no wait ah
the arrow
s
can I add a second one too no I'm
guessing not okay we have a cool weapon
for another time
not for today
ah there's even more materials here I
needed another another photo
oh well
Spike add to Shield that's also
cool idea let me do that why not
um
no
confused
to
oh no uh
yeah
wow
my back is very protected now
[Laughter]
sick good idea
and and we come out here even stronger
the power of fusion amazing
you have done well to reach this place
we offer these lights that will cleanse
you of evil
kill
foreign
[Music]
yeah I won't read it all the time only
the first couple times
I think no
I know that there's a [\h__\h] ton of
shrines
okay let's get out of here and go to the
last Shrine up here which is probably
the end of the tutorial
I got healed too
May the light of blessing Grant you the
strength you seek
say a letter in the other shrine
on our way
I guess is it just
over there on the right side on the east
side
let's check the map
link yeah
I came because there is something I
failed to give you
how could you fail it's not your job for
thousands of years let's take it
what was that
what is that
cute accessory energy cell a gift from
amazonai construct designed to be worn
on a belt it can power the night devices
when I have just given you is an energy
cell cell it is required to make use of
the tools known as stonite devices
I cannot demonstrate its utility because
there are no deny devices right here
thank you
however I have Associates on the other
side of that cave system
they can teach you how to use this
go for a cave
I hope that energy seller provided is
useful to you
we will see if it is
let me check the map as I wanted to all
right yeah it's on the complete opposite
no problemo
more enemies that is a problem
oh they're fighting can't
self-destruction
oh where are those arrows coming from oh
I wonder
a shot
let me test my new weapon
how much damage does he do
like none
yeah that's
um very unfortunate I don't want my loot
to fall off a cliff
I'm not gonna jump down there to get it
even
wait where is that cave out here
holy [\h__\h] that's what is that oh no wait
it's another
I see
alarm alarm
oh I think that weapon is pretty strong
damn
oh he's got a bunk stick on fire
can I take
no no melee weapons for me that's okay
is that even
like strong a board gaster
I mean throw something away
oh it's also on fire why is it also on
fire
an upwind is that what you call it
if I have my paraglider now
I could fly with that
oh mine is even I wasn't fire not
anymore
what's that what is that was that was
that was that I can cook here there's a
chest I almost run by the chairs an
updraft ah
okay you jump
is this where my shirt is
or did I completely miss the shirt
oh a soldier Reaper
what do I do with this master sword by
the way I can't drop it okay
this one's actually weak
wait it's mine
enough
is my attachment gone
oh
no
it burns off no
oh man okay we gotta cook
um but like not two big things because I
still have so little HP uh ooh let's
make something live
oh hold hold
and then there's maybe that's just some
Veggie dish probably
steamed mushrooms lots of refills my
stamina
[Applause]
okay
and how about
fish
hold and with mushrooms always mushrooms
because there's so many mushrooms I
guess I will have to grow fond of
mushrooms in this game
what does this become
fish and mushroom skeeler a simple dish
made by cooking skewered fresh fish
fresh fish
alongside Fragrant Mushroom nice free
Hearts perfect
um
I guess I should make something out of
this too huh
if does this give me speed
does it heal me too or do I add
something let's see
the more I add the longer it will
give me speed right
Hasty oh here's me too tasty mushroom
skewer speed up for four minutes okay
because I added four mushrooms
low level movement speed boost
what let's cook some more
I will need that so I don't spend a
million years walking everywhere meat
and mushroom skirt nice
the food makes me hungry I had already
lunch and breakfast today though I had
for lunch I had the remaining noodles
that my mom made last night because she
brought noodles right and I said I
wanted something with asparagus so she
was so nice to cook something with
chicken and asparagus pasta
[Music]
um
it was really good the noodles are
really good it almost makes me wanna get
uh
uh a noodle machine myself
should I add another one yeah
oh my God spicy pepper steak wow even
with cold resistance ah the peppers give
cold resistance
oh
interesting
when will I get my first heart
attachment huh
I would like some hearts
which ingredient for heat resistance I
don't know yet
we'll find out some sometimes stream
heart attachments
ah wait maybe we can make a fish with a
pepper
a fish with a bear Oh Yes sounds
wonderful
after I finish the tutorial Maybe
spicy pepper Seafood ooh spicy fish
spicy oh spicy
um
the other things oh no
I'll cook one more thing
just uh some
steamed veggies and
fruits yeah
now
oh wait a summer fish I want to catch
um I don't want to startle them
nice
okay let's go through this mysterious
cave
oh Discovery this Gallery Channel you
and me
[Music]
abcory Channel
close enough what the lyrics
he's wink he's eyeballs can I cook those
two kind of sounds disgusting
ah
oh no it doesn't seem to work wait what
do you what's the better weapon for that
um
never mind oh we got Rockstar oh we can
add that to a cooking salt very
important
I don't know how we could even cook
until now without salt what the [\h__\h] is
that
it's a frog
am I even supposed to find it
friend
oh it's dead now what
is it
hey wait it looks so mystical
oh wait I got something fancy out of it
bubble gem bubble Jam
strange question by defeating bubble
frogs and caves ah so these are always
in caves
will entice me to collect even more what
the [\h__\h] was that
I love that you can pick up your arrows
again
I'll be with the chest in a moment let
me just take a look
nice oh plant finally with this one can
make our own fire right
he
oh and with this here we have to break
it like we did before
start a fire today
on your own independently because you're
an independent woman don't stop don't
stop just go on your own way
is anyone playing alongside with me
while I'm playing
surely there are some of you aren't
there because the release date
me I am
oh oh somebody holy [\h__\h]
how far are you guys
how many hours in how many how many
products
close let's go
oh cute it matches with my skirt
you're the same part as me oh you're
trying to do that purposefully keep up
with me or
is that not the actual intention
90 hours they post it
I don't have time so I'm barely ahead of
you that's fine you know as long as you
you know don't fall behind
no problem with that is there
easy clap oh wait can I do the same yeah
okay
I can do the same with these Stones too
the full we got a rampy Ruby Ruby Ruby
I know how to say it I know Ruby Ruby
Ruby
uh wait we were here now we go here okay
what's going on why is there such so
much fog what's this oh
wake up teach me
the rats were crossing to the other side
of broken transportation is on hold
indefinitely
this is ordinarily where we send
resources across the river the only
Silver Lining is that the donai devices
are undamaged
seems you don't know about them they are
Necessities around here allow me to
explain the green thing is called a
donut device
I thought you meant our friend rarufu up
there rahu Raul
uh the one you see here is a fan you can
produce wind on demand oh my second so
these are like more high-tech
attachments
they are self-evidently useful we have a
variety of donut devices full of
multi-multitudinous purposes
require energy ah but does it like
reload when I use it once
yeah I have one perhaps a refreshed
explanation is an order an energy cell
stores the energy required to use zonai
devices
its energy will replenish automatically
while solar devices are not in use aha
there we go
its capacity is not unlimited use the
energy contained within wisely otherwise
you may run out at in Opportunity
opportune moment
ah I I remember seeing it in a video
the I think there's like a stamina bar
for the donut device yeah
[Music]
I wish this Tech existed for real
batteries what you mean the real real
charging
after not using it or I think it would
be really useful
but some devices you don't see how much
battery there is left I wish you could
actually see it maybe even on the
battery if you open up the compartment
and just look at the battery
that would be useful because especially
uh doesn't everybody have like
some random lost batteries lying around
somewhere and you don't know if they're
charged or not but most of the time
they're not and you try them out you go
through them and you have no idea if
they're working
to go every single one of them and then
you don't throw them away because you're
smart you just keep them where they are
Sam you go through them again
hmm
yeah well I actually don't I haven't
dealt with batteries for a million times
a million years so
actually I can't really relate anymore
pardon the long explanation it does not
change our need for a raft so my devices
are extremely useful think relatively
and you will find many ways to employ
them okay
yeah
I'll try
I'll give it a try let me just see
what's around here first
um
wait
I go from other side there's another one
should I talk to the other one too
whoa
roundhouse smash
nothing okay
okay
if we make it over there
then oh the shrine is all the way up
there oh
okay
but it seems to be the oh wait a second
seems to be the preferred method of uh
Transportation but
I want to look at this first was this
stuff oh
can I like make my own stairs here stand
on one move the other one
instead of row
where does it go though
where does that go
I don't know I want to go should I go
there
an island right across
it
add the lower one at that one oh
oh maybe we should go there let's make
some stairs okay
sorry
scary scary all right
uh
oh wait it's the wrong one
oh and how
how
ah grab
no no no no uh
want to move it kind of out of the way
well it's not really out of the way
that's oh okay
no okay I sound like I sneezed
I can't grab that why
ideally we want to be able to come back
up with the same stairs without changing
them too much
[Music]
I can't move that
thank you so much I didn't sneeze though
but thank you
well my hope will be fine who's coming
back up here
what the [\h__\h] are you doing stop it
oh no uh
leaving him no opportunity to fight back
I don't see [\h__\h] now where am I
ah
it's got quite the range huh I'm
creating wind with this paddle huh
oh let's go
I'll take that
I didn't even leave him room for one hit
I'm getting better
I think
I only want to go up here there's
something up there isn't there
um
Charlie borrow one of my platforms
foreign
[Music]
why is it Amber in here give me
something more fancy look a
disappointing chests man
I wish I could move it while on it but
of course that would be too easy
gamer Sims
it's really a thing trust me
oh I attached it even
don't float up
look at moved up
candle double jump please
good
I'm gonna go back now
I'm trusting you link to always hold on
you know
do not disappoint me
that's so scary
okay wonderful
it's going into the
dangerous dangerous
void
okay okay
let's make a boat
uh yeah grab
I'll even make it with free logs wow big
boat big space
last but not least
does this have to be like rotated I
assume so
um
I would think so
like this
wonderful
I think it's ready does it need like one
of those
wind uh
[Music]
sales
I can turn it on right can I how do I
turn it on
how do I turn it on
Beat It
oh
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah
an electric boat a moto boat
very fast 10 out of 10.
would make again would build again can I
turn it up too
ah
easy yeah okay okay okay oh not bad not
bad
oh not really I wouldn't quite call it a
speed boat yet
but you guys are free to use it
if you want I made you a boat
Scottdale oh are you going this
direction it is very late to travel this
mountain path is especially rugged you
must take your environment into account
when traveling I have developed
guidelines for traveling this mountain
path shall I tell you them
very well fire is a crucial tool when
traveling the mountain path a fire can
be used to either cook or warm yourself
I'm not going to ask those questions
I know that
but thank you for trying to help me
[Music]
teaching me how to start a fire today
um
still a bit wobbly with the controls
but we're getting there I think
hopefully
how the hero wow we're doing I don't
know how am I doing you guys can tell me
tell us
don't forget to fuse those weapons
and I don't want to use them all okay
I'll love this one fuse with
fuse can I fuse I can't use those two
can I
um what would I fuse them with
ah
no not amiibo no no no no no I don't
have a single amiibo
oh does that work
oh I mean at least it has a pointy uh
a pointy end a pointy
a pointy
a pointy finish
and more reach yeah
pretty strong tool I think yeah I made a
spare
point to tip yeah that's what I was
looking for thank you ooh
can I make a bomb
because I don't know how to can I even
point my weapon downwards
uh
this one doesn't even work for that does
it
I can jump and hit ah don't oh
[Music]
no but I need the Big Stone wait
uh no
yeah like this
is that enough strength uh
oh nice oh God dizzy dizzy
hey thank you and I learned something
new thanks to you guys I should have
given me a tutorial for that
charge
[Music]
Dawn
[\h__\h]
[Music]
Ed me
what the [\h__\h] is but you see me I didn't
know someone like you could see the
children of the forest
him
go ahead
all my friends are having lots of
different places too you should keep an
eye out while you wonder
I'm gonna do my best if you guys like
know that there's one around you're
welcome to tell me like hey there's a
Kodak here
hopefully it will be easy for me to find
where where
I gotta climb oh no
oh
nice
there's a quarter behind me technically
okay only if it's like really close by
tell me because I don't think I want to
make an effort to
um
like backtrack and that will probably
distract us
too often too long
if there's no good reward especially
which I guess
oh we could find out about
by now but
frog is the Frog gone
okay now
I think he's gone
he's gone behind you right now
stop going stalking Kodak
am I even going towards the shrine right
now where am I going
I went up to a higher Island now I guess
where am I
who
well we are slowly but surely
exploring everything
huh
oh no okay uh uh wait how do I take
another I know I have
[\h__\h]
how do I go to
how do I go to a Bose
oh that's Shields
no no
oh
[Music]
hold book ah aim the ball okay one
second
oh
I want to eat
all my meals have like too much
I'll just eat the apple
yeah that will be fine uh okay so I'm
holding okay
oh
God
[\h__\h] hell
don't die oh
the wings he created actually saved my
ass
no more fishy oh
foreign
[Music]
where do I even respawn
eh
last safe
huh almost had him I was too Reckless I
thought I could do it God damn it
hopefully not too far away
oh no that feels close
I think
oh yeah I see the X where I died can I
why is there an X
is there things I need to pick up or
just to remind me you died here don't
die here again
surprising took this long ah I take that
as a compliment of my skills
but this time I'll do it smarter
I'll do some damage from the distance
or maybe I could attach something too
yeah
oh
he's almost dead ah okay one died I
think
[Music]
you get him go get him that one's pretty
strong I think the other one also died
all right good I'm gonna come here to
challenge me
[Music]
did you see that Dodge guys and I broke
his paws baby
[Music]
she's got it's got a barrel oh no tattoo
action no but that was that was much
better see I learned out of my mistakes
it may take some some attempts but the
I'm getting there
let's drop this take this a solid Reaper
that's solid uh actually maybe we should
attach
so this solid Reba has seven attack
let's fuse
ah wait this ah this is the one I
already used a few zone why does it not
show
[Music]
Oh you mean the stick has been fused a
lot I don't get it
check the recipe on the inventory blue
items are already good ah okay okay
I guess we can refuse this I would like
to fuse it the other way around but I'm
too lazy to do that
plus two at least
I want to take the other things too but
I got no space okay
some stuff still here
oh
[Music]
no
noise I like shooting of arrows
I think I'll be doing that a lot gotta
get good with my aim
okay seems like most of the time when
you get out of these chests is this
these gems
oh Minecart
oh
we've had so much that's cool
okay
fuse the minecart
can you do that
oh wait I don't want to put this into
this oh does it start now it won't start
okay
you can't fuse it [\h__\h]
what
okay
uh
I was hoping that if you already have it
like roughly in the position it would
position itself for you but that should
work right
where does it even go
are we going further away from where we
want to go oh Discovery Channel
oh [\h__\h] it's so dark
I want that
yeah okay
okay
stop now maybe we can go back to
I guess if I stick uh the bright Bloom
sleep seeds to one of my weapons
it will act as like a torch
you're probably gonna tell me that
aren't you
I know I get it I get it
should I do that
but they're all they all have
attachments
um
[Music]
I'll can I the the attach this
all right I can
overplace this anyway
uh
-huh
I'm confused Pro f r
why would I throw
wait how do I do this again
fuse to Shield oh
actually
good idea wow
are you genius
oh wait go ahead
while throwing up
should I just throw these seeds
wait which way do we go anyway this way
fun
oh oh because it's a seat oh my God that
is so useful
I had the same rhythm
so night
ancients extracted energy from it and
refined it for crafting of weapons and
armor whoa
foreign
[\h__\h]
no
better get as much as we can right here
while we're here
hey
Hammer more useful yeah this is supposed
to be a hammer right what I have now
DIY hammer
can I take them back
no
do they disappear
oh there's more
oh they're mining
they're playing Minecraft I did by the
way
um request for Minecraft dungeons and
Minecraft Legends and I did just get
permission for it too but I don't know
if I would want to play it right away
when we just started this ongoing series
I'll I'll think about it
but I was interested in it because you
know I always liked the adventure part
of Minecraft and those games kind of
like do exactly that
I don't want me to use you tonight
excuse me
it's all night is already slated for
processing it would pose difficulties
for me if you took it yourself
it's a unique mineral that can be mined
far beneath the land below there are
Trace deposits of it on this island as
well but they are limited to this cave
our society flourished by processing
this substance into other materials
by cementing in the furnace it is
thereby converted into materials with
useful properties
a few such materials will be ready for
your review shortly wait one moment for
my review
Minecraft dance is essentially the Apple
for kids
then that's what I should have played
when I was a kid and not actual Diablo
you like my my my Cape my hat thank you
it's made by blue I'm also very happy
with it without it I would be so naked
thank you for your patience I will now
explain what sorts of materials The Ore
can be processed into whoa whoa
do not charges
this occasionally solidify into a form
known as crystallized charges
converting tonight into other useful
materials is the way of called what I
can't read is this way in this way it's
called processing
crystallized charges are solidified form
of tonight charges we mainly use them as
a raw materials material in the
construction of energy cells
you need anything else
I guess
um
[Music]
okay well you'll give them you'll give
them to me like oh exchange at four
that's all night material and you'll do
it for me I can't do it myself okay I
think I appreciate that I don't want to
do everything by myself
I guess I'll take a couple of each
I suppose that would be good I don't
know which one I actually need
don't they know I'm the hero they should
give me the stuff for free
[Music]
um
five two
these are the ones on my belt right
maybe not they didn't fill up
on it
all right
oh that was I was a wall right there
Now remind this on my own then you won't
mind right
I guess I'll eventually figure out what
is what exactly and how to use it
but now I'll just take it
and
it will probably come in handy
eventually what do you have
why do you have this is a Minecraft
station ex excavated resources can be
transported from here
could it be that you have forgotten to
bring donai capsules
uh I think so
you have forgotten yours or perhaps you
may not even know what I mean the night
capsules are a convenient mean uh means
of carrying portable zonai devices it is
unfortunate that you seem to have none I
will lend you a few spares thank you ah
wait
oh my God
ah
[Music]
these are like
yeah the ones I can carry with me
the ones I just see on the ground can I
like
transform them into carryable ones
the device cannot be put back in caps
okay think carefully before deploying
one of your approach okay okay
very interesting
this is a cool place too so is this like
the only place of this sort uh in the
whole map or just in this area
you'll get a lot
nice nice
because it shouldn't be holding me back
right
Bonk
okay I guess I'll be using one of my
charges
no okay how do I
how do I
huh
uh-huh
it's time
for us
to go to the next place with um
oh
there we go
that'll do oh perfect well
bunk bye guys thanks for
all the cool stuff
oh where'd that want to go is that
really what happens with a waterfall
if it's like in the sky
does it just evaporates so suddenly I
think I just saw a really hard Edge
behind the bubbles okay there's a really
hard Edge
behind the bubbles that makes it look
not so pretty
that's how I write yeah yeah Skye
there's actually a [\h__\h] ton of
waterfalls up there that's how rain is
created
the time bow that sounds from the Temple
of time and that's where that came from
being said a set time each morning and
evening
along with the constructs we woke to the
sound of the bell sound of the music
when we heard it in the evening we knew
it was time to rest it also played its
part in our traditional ceremonies in a
way it was this place speeding hard the
sight of the temple and the sound of the
Bell still found memories in me
mmm
good for you
I'm glad you can like relive so many
memories here traveling with me
indirectly
sound like you're having a good time
taking off the ding dong
[Music]
alrighty we shall use the Gata machine
that's a time it was a gun to game after
all Zelda has finally come to this point
to give up against all the other games
that use the gacha system
Zelda uh finally
has given up and it's it's come this far
unfortunately
hmm okay what do I put in here tell me
[Music]
device dispenser operation confirmed on
track to meet today's sunai capsule
production Target
oh do you want to use the device
dispenser
it's eating my taxes ask did you watch
the corner whole talk episode because we
mentioned you
[Music]
we were talking about you
I wonder if you know
I'm having big troubles breathing today
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
Mike Tyson's a bucket damn you're right
Mike Tyson's ass loves me
what an honor
no I don't have my window open
uh
yes this is a gacha dispenser it
produces tonight capsules by per
converting certain resources
the resources it accepts are things such
as construct horns ah internet charges
oh
you can process resources that you hold
by dropping them into the receptacle it
is similar to using a cooking pot no
okay we're good thank you
let me do it let me do it
um
horns
these ones and the charges
uh not these things right
and you should sell Improvement
hmm
ah these ones oops I'm blind I got 35.
wow
yeah but I shouldn't use all of them
right what is that does this have any
other use yeah increase attack power
okay I'll just use a couple of these
then
oh
[\h__\h]
I was back soon but I mean oh well
[\h__\h] is that I mean I mean uh well
[Music]
um
it's fine right it's not another big
drama
this is so so I don't know cute dorky
stupid oh lots of fans was this a new
one
a flame emitter
shoots fire
portable pot oh cool
then I don't have to make wait do you
have to make the fire for the pot or
does it work on its own
is there anything I didn't get that I
still could get I wonder
No need no fire yay cool okay I think I
heard a clock
oh ah there you are
I don't know if I want to help you
mmm
yeah okay
and how there's no Minecart
got it
am I blind don't have to make my oh
there it is
can I just use the one I got over there
what do you think I said
all right
look at that
clock
it sounds stupid if I say it like that
sorry yeah I'm moving then you must be
able to see me be gentle okay I'm a real
pickle I was traveling with someone and
God support yeah I know I know I know
I was already working on it
my friend is sending up a smoke signal
can't wait to catch up I'm so tired
though see I know I know all of that
already I could read your mind
he's so cute I don't even have to stick
you uh to it I just no way
what if I drop him
are you scared
no let's not even try I'll leave it to
other people to try
you're safe here maybe I'll join you
can I join you
what else is here
I applies
where where am I
um
ah
island is connected um I could I could
join him
foreign
let's go together
oh [\h__\h]
yeah I want to crouch but the
dad got rid of the
you can crucify a club I think I've
already seen some hints of the terrible
things that you could do
it's it scares me
a bunk no hey
hey why am I going back no
oh
oops uh wait
just drop you
want that
you good buddy I know that was a bit
scary but I got you I got you I'm
delivering you safely to you friend yeah
done now give me your poop
two times even
the the other ones just give a single
one do you skip two or so because it
takes more effort to herself
why guys why aren't you terrified it is
actually their poop
I know it
ah so night
arrows
can he not just do a single hit with
this weapon is he incapable of that
now he did
okay
I think I'll take
my Minecart and bring it up here
yeah what is this ah
turned over Minecart okay
I don't want to create a new one even
though we could
so
we're saving time with this
I tried to dash while holding one
yeah I would expect that you wouldn't be
able to do that
no
that's not quite the direction I want
you in
but nice that it does kind of
put it
where it needs to be let's go
[Music]
up we go oh is that snow
uh oh
wait I didn't see that
what
is
all the way up up
[Music]
um yeah
is the Croc saved oh yeah
cool
so that's a shortcut
Oops stop that
all right wait
you can get rid of that now why does it
still show that it doesn't show that I
died just now in the sky I guess I
wasn't really dying huh wait I got those
Towers now
good
ah
it's like a single Tower and this big
arena
what is that
it's scary it's probably gonna shoot me
it's like those
machines from breath of the wild but
they look different it looks dangerous
okay but uh how do I get the oh where am
I oh okay
this way
should
now wait do I have to go up oh that
looks slippery oh and it's
eh it's also [\h__\h] cold really
I already took damage what the [\h__\h]
maybe inside is not so
bad
yeah discovery
you gotta teach me about the peppers huh
I do not care
I know I know about the pepper
the pepperoni do I have no more
pepperoni
no okay can I take these pepperoni
oh thank you
I guess since I need to eat anyway but I
want to make like a smaller dish
let's just make babyloni alone
maybe pepperoni on a skewer
no I don't know the origin is the origin
hot summer
oh wow spicy salted Peppers sauteed wait
this gets colder is this I am that's
what I need
but is it cold in here too
doesn't seem that cold
yeah okay see in this case I know where
the meme came from oh
sweet
welcoming committee
oh there's two paths
he's the Frog
are you dead
are you pretty dead
you're really dead now nope
[\h__\h]
damn it wait if I would have killed the
bunny really fast I would have gotten
something uh too because I think in
I saw that one in breath of the Wild
no they get groupies right
yeah
no that was like gone in an instance
I didn't expect it at all I didn't know
they could jump out of the frogs
mmm
anyway was this path better than the
other one I know we're just back in the
beginning
okay
no stonks for me how many stunks wait do
I have any stunks no I have zero stunks
when do I get rupees where do I get
rupees
foreign
a bit slower
over here
God damn it why two two jelly
thanks for the red super chat choo choo
it didn't give me a super chant I was
Bamboozled into kissing the choo choo
didn't even deserve the choo choo
should I talk to him wait what the [\h__\h]
was that
whoa whoa whoa oh
oh no I don't wanna I don't wanna
oh yeah these weapons are more effective
on these enemies right
it's just like the
the weapons you got in breath of the
wild from those
specific enemies there forgot what
they're called I don't even know what
they're called in English the guardians
or whatever
so it's the same thing no not the vocal
blings no no the ones in the shrines and
all that
um
the soldier constructs and Captain
Constructor only doing their duty to
protect the garden of time at the time
it was sadly necessary to protect our
land from Invaders
I'm terribly sorry for any Friday post
to you now oh no problem I've been
having fun with them
and they serve the purpose of being my
personal tutorial
foreign
you can make those weapons by combining
two drops with weapons
Nanny yeah that's what I'm doing you
know
anyway
maybe oh I think dong
ah [\h__\h]
I need that meat bird meat very very
good for my health
need bird meat
Shrine is up there but
I don't see myself
climbing up there huh oh are they gonna
attack him
no
oh
thanks for the help man
well they that's collateral damage they
didn't even want to help him I think
flame and Mr Club you kidding me
oh wait this thing's pretty much broken
let's take this
noise
it has his work
gosh it's so bright here [\h__\h]
you can learn tonight to other monsters
to invite
yeah
yeah I've seen that it was the second
time I saw that
hands I think they didn't have those in
breath of the wild right now they're
back
with uh
tears of the Kingdom
I hear the Frog again
where's the Frog
I already saw me
ah wait
let's burn him again oh yeah
foreign
if you want to get that one [\h__\h]
aren't they rare this is the second time
in a row that I got one of those
I feel like they would be rare well
maybe they're not
cool
oh wait bomb
if I shoot an arrow
we have a bomb
oopsie
or possibly even just uh the bombs [\h__\h]
huh oh yeah
holy [\h__\h]
as a little bit Overkill
oh
fire arrow
oh chest
probably just never Amber or something
like that
call it
okay okay
oh but these ones don't re immediately
respawn like the ones in the other tell
the games
I'm so happy that bomb flowers are back
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is that
absolutely disgusting
typical Gordon Ramsay reaction
absolutely
rat what's this word
Rands Rand
foreign
HP what the [\h__\h]
yeah are you supposed to fight this
thing
my cold resistance is running out too I
know it doesn't matter in here I think
but
rancid oh yeah it's got a weak point
oh
ah oh
ah we're learning about weak points on
enemies now wonderful
come on show it to me show it to me
again
do you need to be penetrated a couple of
times to show it or uh
oh there we go
wait I don't want to use my uh
[Music]
nice
yay a like like Stone
a like like Stone
a strange round Stone from a like like
made of crystallized inner fluids
it's a good ingredient for elixirs
oh
the name of the enemies yeah yeah I get
that this weird name though
that's kind of our
biggest coolest enemy that we've met so
far
mm-hmm
[Music]
good practice for the future
lucky likey mean lucky me lucky lucky
oh no one liking
oh wait my bow broke
[Music]
nice oh I think the attachment broke
let's just break it for now
[Music]
oh
it showed it to me before I shot did not
oh flaming Mr Shields
eh how is that useful
[Music]
it does sometimes it opens up
maybe if you're like super close to it
or
[Music]
oh
a flame emitter
a flamethrower when I block
um
well uh shush
only carry free Shields
all right we're done here
going out to the cold again [\h__\h]
um
I could eat something like that but see
now I don't want to eat it because it
heals so much
well we might have to
buy this one
as longer cold resistance too
I could eat just the peppers too but
[Music]
um
or do you even get oh cold resistance
just by eating nah you don't do you
RPG disease do not hoard Islands okay
you will have to tell me that a couple
of times
ah
you buy guys
I don't know
[Music]
I also should put on some sunscreen
because it feels like their Sun would be
terrible here
whoa what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh
all right I was using the The Shield by
accident uh because I think I was when
was I was trying to focus on the enemy I
can't [\h__\h] say
the ground it's too bright what the [\h__\h]
I can't see the textures and [\h__\h]
brightness setting the goal
this is too much
perfect though okay the the fire
emitting Shield I found use for it
see you later Burbs
need sunglasses yeah
[\h__\h]
I think this was also an issue in graph
of the wild a little bit but it's like
even brighter I think a little bit
brighter on my screen that it is
actually
on a normal
uh screen just a tiny bit though because
on my other screen it looks a little bit
less only a tiny bit but I still can't
see [\h__\h] ah
wait wait wait wait wait I need to go up
here uh
got it
how do you get up
was this place too
it's hard to see how to get up when I
can't see structures
on the ground
you have to go here first
because there's a little path here where
I can climb
snow blender this is a good detail are
you you mean it's actually like good and
realistic I guess so
wait how do I not use the shield huh
what wait oh wait it's because I don't
even have a weapon equipped is it
ah
free Hearts I need more
well I think it's okay to die
sometimes in this game
the last safe was pretty close by I
think oh yeah no it's right here they
even gave me peppers
all right
let's try again
like oh
oh
that was close
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] hell uh I got confused with
everything
[Music]
foreign
what I suddenly forgot how to equip a
weapon
there's too many controls
you're strong
yeah
I have a weapon
[Music]
interesting
the texture is like still pixily
like a square ice
plates on top of each other
they don't notice me yet
okay
wanna come down here maybe
no
I'm scared come down here I don't want
to fight up there
please no
please
hmm
well whatever
you going
ah
what let's heal
foreign
[Music]
God like time stops when you what the
[\h__\h]
with my Things fall down
time stops when you eat you can think
comfortably slowly about everything
uh
uh let's drop this one
oh did I drop it
there we go
okay
oh I'm dying let's go that looks fancier
than my other Treasure Chest no maybe
it's just because it's so bright here
okay we did that mushrooms are good for
you no
I hate mushrooms
you could eat a fish
I need to get some food
collect more food
okay wow
where do I go
how do I get up there
from the other side Maybe
I don't think I can climb I mean I
haven't even tried I'm just assuming I
guess
speaking of food
got me a rubber drumstick wow very good
very good
oh wait there's a chest here
you have to like
uh melt things around it'll explode it
or
can I throw this also
I will I I just drag it oh yeah right
that's right I started in breath of the
Wild
Amber
okay let's go run my cold resistance is
running out again
first
it doesn't really look like really
there's any axes on the right side
either
oh wait here
maybe I can go behind the waterfall and
then on the right side looks like I can
climb there
see I can go behind it
yeah yeah
but that's a long way to climb
maybe I'll use one of my stamina items
so laggy did you get the output I don't
really feel like it's laggy is it
maybe that's just my stream
and I mean I installed it before a
couple hours before the stream so
probably most recent
okay no lag
I think this is the intended path yeah
because I can climb relatively easily
too
it was
this place
I could cook here
oh
maybe I will
hey
so how's this work I put Flint there
just on there
do I need the wood too
probably
ah no I do I have to hit it huh
point my ah try
a trip
my flame emitting Shield is coming in
handy okay but I don't have much to cook
right I have my
have my chicken drumstick and my some of
my Peppers ah some mushrooms
let's cook this
okay
Peppers
um don't know how much longer will be
in this area but
and then let's make a chicken maybe a
spicy chicken
or some breading would be even better oh
and that turns into the drumstick turns
into a steak hmm
it says chicken steak but it looks like
just like the other steaks
foreign
about that
oh my cold resistance running out
a mistake
in that situation that is incredibly
funny to me
fruit and mushroom mix on it wait
there's no culture systems
then I put a
what
oh
uh all right I can cook this
what does this turn into
oh oh it's just a stem bulb so I'm still
not really sure what it is it's probably
well
maybe it's a fantasy vegetable it's a
mix of a garlic and a spring onion
why do you always have such cute asset
spots because I have such cute viewers
who do this stuff for me
thanks to you guys
the thumbnail also like every time I
play a Zelda game
the cute fan art did you guys notice it
Blends in nicely doesn't it so you could
have thought maybe that it's actually
uh
the actual official artwork
I know I was humming but to me
ah actually to me for a moment it sounds
like a Japanese Hair Commercial
but I guess you're singing
is he doing that one
am I not being cold because I'm right
next to the fire
so that's something new
is that why I made that fancy sound holy
[\h__\h] seven hearts
I don't want to make something so
overpowered
I was trying to make something with the
rush rooms
[\h__\h]
I made a critical food but I wanted a
rushing effect I see there now I got it
oh why did it get rid of it
weird
okay uh
five thirty three minutes seven I don't
know how long I still need here
okay
because I like that
Shrine is right here oh some more
peppers
let's go the first train
[Music]
link really rocks the Unga Bunga outfit
it does
anything looks good on links somehow he
could be wearing anything cool
guten back it's like gluten tag
German Shrine German Shrine so I will
excel at it
yeah even the Garuda outfit
you know what's my one of my favorite uh
Zelda outfits
the breath of the Wild
uh winter uniform
the winter clothes for her
I love it
actually that might be my favorite Zelda
outfit overall
you Advanced a lot did I
it's been four hours almost
so you've made it here now then extend
your right hand
sure sure handshaking
and it looks so comfying
um
yeah the tutorial is long
[Music]
as said move up ah yeah I've seen that
in the Gameplay trailer
um
this is the ascendability it lets you
travel through what's directly above you
to ascend free with an emerge on top of
it can I not go down to
only up
you'll find it quite useful and all
sorts of places and situations yeah I
could have used it now like to go up
here
use a send and receive the blessing from
the shrine
okay
it's not called decent true true true do
I get a decent pill
wait so like here
it's like this is such a weird ability
okay
[Music]
oh okay
why is there a salon one here their
chest
[Music]
Diana I needed one actually perfect
foreign
for this game so true
[Music]
my shield broke uh wait a second
oh
can I attack with the
with the shield well wait
no ice let's just burn the boxes
ah only so that I can get up I thought
there was something behind makes sense
ah press a with Shield up uh-huh okay
okay let me test it ah so I wonder if
that would have worked against the boxes
maybe not
[Music]
another chest
oh I should no wait
no
so I have one last [\h__\h] Bill
so give me the good one
[Music]
the best asset I
you know what I realized though
I'm saying but um do you know those
controller hands
I tried to attach them again today in
hindsight I wouldn't have needed them I
guess but
the controller hands that they end
literally at the cuffs
and if I would attach it like around my
boobies you would have always seen that
they cut off at the Cuffs so ah and
maybe I should just extend it myself
because the the controller itself I
really like it it looks really cool
what I do here
my sauce
oh oh I cut it
uh
press a mid air
whoa what was that Shields
while holding a shield and then press A1
in what situation do you do that if you
try to Shield server The Shield feels to
something that will get in the way
you'll fall uh-huh
uh what am I doing uh
ah even these kind of thin surfaces
wonderful
[Music]
but that one's moving
there's no problem
is it because the other one's too far
away
what
fast fast
if your new also will have control if I
can tell you no I wasn't planning on
adding that because all the other things
I want already take up many slots and I
thought I don't want to use up a slot
for controller hands
if I can just put up a PNG and it will
look just as good even if it's not
animated but still
I don't I don't think it's worth it I
think I said this before
other things like hairstyles or
even I don't know expressions or so
seem more worth it for me
hmm that was the last one so I go down
you can attach it no no not yet but
maybe in the future
free blessings
oh yeah glasses too now but glasses is
kind of dorky I mean I liked it for
example in my bag reveal I bought the
the wobbliness of the glasses added a
comedic effect to it that I really like
uh generally I think sometimes that's
actually good
if it's a little bit scuffed it looks
cute
I see you've restored some power to that
new arm of yours
the door into the Temple of Time should
now open for you
can I get a shortcut can you like
teleport me there oh man
um
[Music]
what what confusing
can I not make just like without healing
just the cold resistance
man
okay
uh
over here
that's pretty close
I could drop into the water here but
will that be too cold
but I do have cold resistance let's try
cold okay uh
yeah I mean I thought so but testing uh
for science was necessary
sometimes it's better to experience
things yourself so that you don't do it
again so it's like burnt into your brain
right so now I won't do it again
foreign
here
a chest time oh no it's not just I
opened that if there was one how'd I get
up here
use what I just learned
there we go is she a snowboard oh that
would be fun
oh is that I never got your machine over
there
it's not the same one right
yo fluffy cute pants I mean
with those shoes and the pads it kind of
looks ridiculous what I'm wearing on top
and look like very short legged
I said
I'm what the [\h__\h]
did did he grow smaller
since breath of the Wild
oh wait ah
now let's try the other one
so jump and then
what was it
I would this and then
and then X right
oh
and then no when [\h__\h] hmm
jump and then
a jump and then Shield
[\h__\h] what
no jump Shield a what
what no Shield jump a
what are you focusing on
[Music]
yeah that is so cool here we go there's
our 1080 snowboarding because they just
don't release 1080 snowboarding even
though they teased me with it but
finally I got a like a little bit of an
a makeup for it
so much fun
I want to find like a bigger slope
sometime
[\h__\h] what are you what are you doing
no climb up there
[\h__\h] what's up there anyway
only there's a chest
it was the gotcha machine
yeah hi
it is a complete
unusual to receive businesses
well I mean I might use it
um I mean no actually no I don't really
need anything
[Music]
what's this thing doing here
what is it
hey
activate it
[Music]
can I use it
this one's for good I can get gliders
out of this
for real I could get different things
refused to Shield what no way
that's how you do gliders in this game
are there no normal gliders
what am I doing
there is there must be
[Music]
if you think the shield doesn't
what
a way
to fly farther try balancing in the
center of the wing
harness as the night button can harness
the lift to ride the wind
what harnessed lift what
we've got a couple of them
like this one's is it usable
oh [\h__\h] uh maybe not
oh there's one down there too oh I'm
supposed to fly over there
ah
well I must be able to use them if
they're lying around like this
and we use a different weapon
how do I do this
they slide
do it
uh
left it onto the rails next to it
isn't that one on the rail
mom should I start from
like here
oh
oh okay I don't have to uh activate it
this is scary
oh
my god oh no no not this way
that is very interesting
and dangerous but fun
such a weird way to travel
but it's it's
I like how they thought of like
different ways of traveling you get the
paraglider yeah but also you have this
here if you want
now how do we like
uh maybe jumped into the water
can you roll when you raise the ground
[\h__\h]
wasted
[Music]
where do we start from the
flying area
what
oh yeah okay
did I
does this mean I did the gacha
no okay
you gotta do it again
more flying yeah
fun I like that
wonder how often it will be there when
we could actually make use of it
properly
and how often we'll rely on our own
paraglider or like why would we even use
this if we have a paraglider with us
hmm
questions questions questions
my pants today
did I do I have my pants
ah I I have them I'm just not wearing
them thank God
I wouldn't have liked to go back
okay
so
what am I doing
this time
I will land better yeah okay
[Music]
I am a bird
I'm Like a Bird
only fly away I don't know Emma Zelda is
I don't know where my princess is
I'm like a bird oh my God why is it
flying so weird now
if I stand in the front oh it does go
downwards if I stand in the front
[Music]
oh dear oh dear let's not crash
oh
almost almost had a perfect Landing I
wanted to land right here
um
this sand
it's like somebody
goes through it with a rake
thank you for the raid hello
I wish I could have shown you a really
cool Landing man
all right open the time
Tower whatever
what's in here
oh
the closed door complete oh it's a big
airpod
pretty
yellow Edition
memory
time to eat chocolate
oh
this is now
It's Just Happening Now
no
oh she's crying she got crying marks on
her
cheeks because she cried so much about
losing me
she blessing my arm too
like the shrines do
you not want to talk to her
[Music]
some neighbors drilling here what the
[\h__\h]
it's 8pm
okay sometimes I also drilled after 8 PM
but still
so what exactly happened now
I got a arm upgrade what
one step closer to regenerating our arm
a recall
ah reverse an objects movement I saw
that yeah yeah until it goes back to
where it was which really reminded me of
ah
when was that game where we used that
yeah entropy Center exactly
because we had the same
basically yeah the same
uh thing but we could rewind and then I
think also
backwind
portal free app we like to call it
portal free
backwind upwind uh
front wind
whatever you would call that
huh
link chooses not to talk on purpose well
he might be saving energy or something
or he's just trying to be cool
um I don't know maybe he's trying to
seem mysterious because that's somehow
supposedly attractive
Maybe
hmm
ah recall the ability to reverse the
movement of an object Through Time
and we get that in the times one
and Zelda has vanished as well
use your size and it's a mystery even to
me perhaps it was a sort of echo one
that reflects her sheer will
that you've now been given this ability
no doubt it will true prove important
can we we run this real well rewind
these time Wheels
yeah
what does it do
isn't it is it even Ray one is it
it's rewinding so slow
and now
I know was that useless
Maybe
climb it okay
but when
ah
what
wow Genie
genius
amazing
hello
wait don't you like let me choose like
if I want
help or stamina or something like that
miles upon me was it do
open a door
will this kill me
can I only open this if I have like a
certain amount of Hearts this will kill
me
I think this is a bit uh
not so smart app
yeah
at least it doesn't really kill me
this door stands as a test of your own
overall vitality
you'll remain in a weakened state
you're not yet strong enough to open it
I am indeed on the weekend it is Friday
evening it's the weekend
[Music]
but there's one more Shrine on this
island there you can get another
blessing oh do I need couldn't you have
tell me that before do I need four
hearts for this
if you add that to the other blessings
you receive that shrines and offer them
all to the goddess you might just find
your way forward ah she takes those
Shrine thingies and she gives me
health I guess
Pura pan yeah yeah you showing me the
shrine
oh it lasts me wait
from now on it does huh
you see all the blue marks on your map
uh yeah there's the shrines
you can travel instantly to any of them
I suggest the one at the bottom of the
map use the quick travel function to
reach that area quickly you'll find the
last of these islands shrines around
there somewhere awesome thank you
shrines are also UPS okay but the one
that he put in there are not
or the one that the one that he put
there uh what
what what man
I thought map was minus ah
oh now it doesn't automatically go to
here are the patrons she took
um
here the room of Awakening
the last tutorial Shrine I thought I was
done I wasn't
wait room off Awakening that's where I
started out today
oh my oh my
oh my oh my oh my
I'm really assuming that I have to start
here but
I don't know if that's true
Ascent first I went I need to wait where
here
ah what's this one oh the map is on here
now too
oh
swimming for walls
no uh
uh wait uh
uh
uh where am I going
haha
where does Disney is this where we
walked through
no
I'm mixing up things in my head
the shrine
nachoya
nachos
natural shrine
oh hi there you want to talk
this is a crystal Refinery I can take
your crystallized charges and use them
to produce energy Wells what the [\h__\h] is
that
and energy well can increase the
capacity of the energy cell
you're carrying
this increased capacity will allow you
to use Zone devices for longer periods
ah
like the battery size I'll get more of
them
I can produce these energy Wells for you
if you bring me crystallized charges
very uh confusing but
I guess
100.
what the [\h__\h]
whatever not like I wanted it anyway
hmm
[Music]
yeah 100 for one charge
there's like what 10 total that you can
get throughout the whole game
[Music]
the ability to rewind nacho Yash run
wait
I'm gonna drown
now everyone now
I thought I could make the jump
um
can we do it like faster
is there a speed up button
[Music]
I I
will there be another one
hey chance
oh wait what
is it because I'm on it
what
this is not cold in here
oh [\h__\h] l
I am for rolly confused
look
what
happened
okay
wait now you're too fast
oh my God bounce bounce is so bouncy
oh
okay
a bit
unnecessarily
dramatic huh
I am the master of drama
I can create drama out of thin air
10 arrows really
okay oh
um
what
do I just have to meet
or do they have to meet at the bottom
what
I'll just wait
won't that work
ah I can't move while I do this
hey
but I don't ever only have to rewind it
don't I also have to kind of stop it
hmm no
wait what
yeah stay
stick it together
at least that one near me they met
well I don't know
oh oh I okay I could have made a mistake
there too because I could have rewinded
the other one and then it would have
gone the opposite direction right but
this way it was like going with it
okay okay okay
so Dad hundred percent uh yeah my brain
is able to keep up with that easy
I have 100 awareness of what's going on
always at all times
[Music]
so do speedrunners have to go through
all of this the whole tutorial first
because they have to do all shrines
otherwise they don't they're not allowed
to jump off the
Island
yeah oh damn that's triggering
all this beginner [\h__\h] let's see
[Music]
can we teleport
back
up here no
is there another alcohol there's another
thingy
no
but I I like this this is fun let's do
it
we only have to fly straight anyway so
let's stand straight
in the middle straight in the middle
yeah let's go maybe fly a little bit
lower where is that huh wait
we're up so high what the [\h__\h]
oh
looks like a Pokemon Arena gym up there
or like a soccer football should I jump
into the water
if I fly somewhere else
will it scold me
I'll just
I'll try to go for the water but this is
hard to guess where I am
um
what about now
yeah looks good looks good
hey wonderful Big Splash
now just don't drown uh
that's maybe Big Challenge
[Music]
a bit
that was funny I could have eaten some
kind of stamina food buns
okay we are back again time to test our
strength after getting one heart
added to our maximum Heights
I feel a little bit better about eating
all the food in my inventory
thanks for the membership
[Music]
egg
what's egg in Korean
[Music]
I know apple is sagua but I don't know
what egg
wait do I have to do this again
oh
really
can they stop trailing for [\h__\h] sake
get him
ah
I didn't pay attention
nah
okay
also thank you for the
membership
hi
give me
give me give me give me give me give me
a heart container
extreme heart container till the end of
the day give me give me give me a hard
container that is the title of my second
single Buddha
[Music]
heart content
container
yeah heart container hot container looks
pretty
does it have the same design as in
breath of the wild I wonder
a rare item that restores some of the
life force you lost to the Gloom
increasing your maximum number of Hearts
by wow
go and bring peace to the world okay
let me in
[Music]
is he okay
what's this is that sweat
he's like sweating as if he's like
raining from his body
but I can thank you
oh good
I see you have managed to open the door
you haven't fully recovered yet but that
is to be expected
we're almost Beyond saving
[Music]
by visiting the shrines
and receiving Their Blessings
have mitigated some of the corruption's
effects
all our time together has been brief
so happy that
finally met
[Music]
hmm
you are exactly as Zelda said
[Music]
the music
I've done everything I can for her
now it is up to you
[Music]
he gone
forever
but you're my hand
[Music]
huh
look at my weird ass weapons
sorry ridiculous
oh it healed me
we did that and now
huh
I'm gonna rewind them okay
[Music]
can I dive
here
[Music]
noise
I thought it
I thought it might be too far away
I guess in that way we also can decent
same thing
[Music]
tell me that there's uh my paraglide and
that
shoe box
no
oh no
[Music]
you're doing great angel thank you man
the gasp
[Music]
will this one recover more Master Sword
a little bit
[Music]
yeah yeah do it do it don't think so
much about it just do it
oh
how much
oh we're rewinding it uh-huh
we're not improving it we're running oh
is this the place where they took like
screenshots and I compared where she is
or so figured out where she is or this
is the same place what I don't know is
this the the one scene everybody freaked
out about
[Music]
your home
she's like what the [\h__\h] that is called
you got scammed oh
oh no it's chilling up here
you're a friendly right
um
[Music]
spicy flute
ah link save me fight me
link you must find me you must find me
any hints
could if you can talk to me like this
but give me some hint
oh yeah the clouds are gone now we're
done at the tutorial yeah and now they
want me to just jump down here
where would I be landing in the over
there
[Music]
what a absolutely ridiculous thing to do
what if I land on the lily pad
[Applause]
we did it we're not dead don't do this
in real life yep
spiral Kingdom
we're down on the ground yay yay
we exiled the Exile
we are back in breath of the wild oh
what what's the word I want to say
not venue not area uh grounds uh
territory that's the word I'm looking
for
okay it's nice beautiful wow
fresh grass on my under my legs under my
feet sees Dazzle fruit oh
break it to unleash it that's like
sparkles oh is it like that's a blind
really it's blind I thought it would be
too paralyze or maybe it's the same
thing
can I get a horse
what is that down there
ah the way so open the only thing she
said is find me what the [\h__\h] do I do
oh that looks cute over there
hey where'd I go
angel
s
okay
can't jump on that
could actually I want to surf
uh wait
hey even without snow I can do that
that's so much fun I saw you can make
cards too
sorry boob I need your your beautiful
tasty juicy fresh meat
oh dear
you can attack me right should I try to
it's my first bucklands
basically chickens
there's free should I try to find them
oh there's like explosive
mmm
all right how do we tackle this
is that not even like too far away
oh [\h__\h]
I keep on accidentally pressing that
yummy
go back please
don't purposefully alert them please
the opposite of stuff
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
well that was easy
shut up
[\h__\h] give me a fire again
[Music]
aimedoko
aim don't go for real I wasn't even
moving
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh you almost got me
is it dead yeah
I'm getting all my arrows back because
he sent me a couple too
nice I didn't even use the explosive
barrels tattoo
sunbellium Dillion
fruit
Shield Rusty Shield
let's climb up there
that was my first bulk blend
was it a crit really my first Bucklin uh
Camp about Goblin a buck box
yeah
those bastards still around Bugaboo
he's gonna
I love how good I still uses that
every time she gets a chance she said it
against coyote too I was so proud
I taught her that
oh wait I can make a car
I see this as a motivation to make a car
Hyrule restoration materials uses
materials to catch for all your Billy
needs come find us if you'd like a dream
home what
what can I get a house
a hotel car
um I think I'm like my first car now
uh
how do I should I place this below to
not make the car too low
it's gonna place the wheels like
properly does that make sense
good idea oh my God I know how to build
a car I'm such a mechanic yeah no not
attaching actually wait that works
just one in the middle I think also
works
that might work better so it doesn't
really
interfere with the wheels we were I
guess I don't know that works so how
many wheels do we want there's four
uh
one here oh
I think no
it's for minimum what
mm-hmm not it
laughs
wrong place
was too close
holy [\h__\h] they're like thrilling
endlessly can you guys hear that only
when I talk probably
[\h__\h] annoying
that's what it is
you don't hear it okay good I hear it
I got some big drilling to do
and
that will not
roll properly
okay Dad could work
text with glue like that how does it
even spin
and then wait
what
I attached one of my donut thing is
right
but which one
the turbo the fan
I guess the fan
if I leave this car somewhere
will I be able to find it again
or like does it eventually despawn
oh what happened to the tire yeah you're
right
there's a despawn I hope not
I'm even making walls for it
wow
I gotta keep on doing that
so I get protected you know
when there's people shooting at me at
least from two sides I'll be protected
oh [\h__\h]
uh
[\h__\h]
ah what the [\h__\h] is this [\h__\h]
all right
see what a pain in the ass how many
times are we gonna be dealing with this
[\h__\h] I want to go back to horses
horsepower is best part what the [\h__\h]
horsepower is best power
uh
okay I mean come on
now okay it doesn't get any more perfect
than this see it's already driving on
its own
it's a muscle car
a beautiful muscle car
I know I'm insisting on these walls
anyway there we go wow
yes
if I make something It's gotta be built
properly
oh yeah I'm basically building a house
on wheels
ah
well as long as it's straight I'm happy
with that
a wagon
I'll get i'll guess y'all all right uh
ah
I can't will you eventually get like a
tool to control where the car actually
goes like an actual wheel
because otherwise I have to keep on
repositioning it
where are you going
all right we're going this way
[\h__\h] it's getting dark
if I would have walked
would I have reached the the goal by now
yeah a steering wheel
uh
yeah yeah okay well [\h__\h] making cars in
the future maybe at least afterwards we
can continue driving with it if we want
to go somewhere else
[Music]
let's go go cargo
no
me now
huh
sorry
what you're telling me the effort was
for nothing
you don't want this kind of stuff
I thought it was maybe the path
oh man
I guess if I put more Wheels
and more
um
not Wheels
more wind machines
well how about if it's just a super
simple structure
see we're doing this now to understand
building
also the night was really short then
okay
do not disappoint me
you moved for a moment what the [\h__\h]
is it the ground
my Mr ground
[Applause]
the bottom
and maybe now I can remove the bottom
plank now that I have the the wheels
positioned at a good height anyway
good call
mm-hmm
no
oh the fan
you think it's the fan
[Music]
ah well the fact that it's rolling back
is maybe already a good sign
but it's working would it have also
worked with all the other stuffs
attached to it
let's go let's go no time to waste
oh don't don't go into where all the
enemies are
well almost bonked into the tree
hi Fox
where'd you go
squeal
all right
it drops nuts not meat
oh oh there's one of those big boys I'm
too scared to fight those
what the [\h__\h] do I do with this car
wait we're not quite there
I'm just
reposition it
wait wait
wait
I'll never build a car again
these are all experiences that have to
be made you know
[Music]
uh
hmm wait and sorry
don't don't
think about it
my bong speak
um
oh it tastes like a weird tower there
no no no no no no
no
[Laughter]
oh
what the [\h__\h] are this thing ah a day
for building they drop things like this
to build or
what this is for
what
ah
ah to rewind then go back up yeah yeah
try it right right right you know what
[\h__\h] the car
walking on the top
I don't care about it anymore like what
you're supposed to go in there
to the kingdom of Hyrule but there's
like a
there's like a big
Camp enemy account
or is it not enemy wait it's not enemies
Maybe
I parked my car somewhere over there
because there's free parking there
no way what you recognize me
yeah link Mr Link
is that really you where have you been
no I've seen you since Princess Zelda
since you've seen you or princess Ella
since you went under the castle to
investigate the glue could you tell me
how long ago that was I mean if you
remember it then maybe not that long ago
and that's when the castle Rose into the
air everyone's been so worried about the
both of you prior has barely slept she's
been trying to figure out where you two
went
ah at the moment Pierre should be in
that building with a telescope
please hurry there now she'll want to
know that you're all right
exciting when what if she aged like a
million years whoa
foreign
was there something else here
[Music]
um
pink where have you been this whole time
we hoped you'd come back soon but then
you didn't know you have where's
Princess Ella you didn't bring her with
you whatever happened please go to talk
to Pure first and foremost she's up in a
research lab that's on the north side of
our fort
okay I like the music here
[Music]
oh
dabs
I said morning hey hey oh have you been
don't answer that tell me later for now
you should hurry and go talk to Pura
she's been in a tasty ever since you
wonder princess have disappeared she's
in the building with the telescope yeah
yeah yeah
wait they got a little um balloon thingy
I'm using crispy
oh oh this is a shop or is it take for
free
what do you think you're doing
don't touch any of it without your
permission I'll get and you'll you I'll
get in trouble if you do okay so it's
okay for you
oh is there someone sleeping up there
what yeah what who's talking
pray
it's like a melting
some melted pistachio
this is me in the summer
oof
okay
sushi in there
[Music]
other ghosts was this
oh
some guides
[Music]
oh this kid you can make this slide too
huh
wait what how am I gonna ah
here
that is
foreign
okay now where have you been
you're not a ghost are you linky
hey did they even that looks interesting
a question
[Music]
hey
what exactly happened did she age a
little bit
since last game
wasn't she like really childish looking
tiny
she aged up huh
so when you and Princess Zelda go
beneath Hyrule Castle
you discover a mysterious mummy
only reanimates yeah no no
thanks will Rica then Zelda falls into a
fissure and vanishes this would be a
good recap for Sunday must have been
when the castle Rose and the ruins fell
yeah then later you wake up on a sky
island saved by the arm that was stuck
to the mummy yeah
get the poorer pad from an unusual
creature
yeah and learn that your new arm
belonged to someone named raru yeah
the master sword disappears yeah
and hear the princess's boys
and find your way here I mean
interesting that they like recap it like
this
because you know link can't I mean is
their way of having link tell it to her
but in the end we already all all just
did that normally I feel like in a lot
of games they were just like
skip this whole conversation and just do
a black
fade in and out or out and in and then
be like ah whoa I see that's what
happened here
so that would have been fine but okay
huh
then
what are you saying you came from up
there
yes how do you met I think that's what
the first king of Hyrule was did
are they one of the same
so much of this doesn't make sense yet
but I'm certain that Mommy you found
another Castle must be related to the
upheaval
the castle rising up the ruins falling
down from the sky The Mummy must be
connected to it somehow
and then there's the most important
detail of all you sure that you heard
the princess speak to you and she gave
you a clear message to find her that
truly was the princess then that means
she's alive maybe she's trapped beneath
the castle and needs help
that settles it I know you only just
returned link but I need you to meet
with with the search party up by Hiro
Castle they've been searching tirelessly
for you too oh
the captain in charge of the search is
named hotz work with him to find the
princess as quickly as you can
I know that Mommy may still be lurking
somewhere around there which is
concerning to say the least but we have
more immediate problems to deal with
right now I'm counting on your linking
um
oh we got characters to look at oh
is there old uh like breath of the wild
form yeah she was so tiny cute wow this
she grew a lot in this time maybe maybe
she used some science on herself
yeah she was so cute
the highest Authority on Ancient
technology she has served princess
zella's family for much of her life and
has worked with the princess to research
its own eyes civilization most recently
they started an investigation into the
outbreak of Gloom she has used herself
as a test subject in her experiments
despite being over a century in age she
reversed her age into the extreme
reverse
and I should look like a child not to
wait um
wait what what wait
huh
are you uh one
ah
you mean when she was so tiny is when
she reversed it extremely and now she
just grew back normally into her current
form
or so or reversed the the super
reversing
I don't
whatever doesn't matter
to the kingdom of Hyrule complete yay
the new objective so really they make me
go there right now already
oh
that is kind of like
feels intimidating to me
[Music]
thinking right now we played five hours
I need to read super chats it's 9pm
maybe I ended here would be a good spot
to end whoa
can we see the search party
no where are they
I don't see many enemies but maybe you
just can't see them from here I don't
see any at all
good spot right maybe I'll just play
this bgm in the background because it's
really nice oh
that's an old machine thingy
[Music]
but let me just explore this Village a
little bit more
and then we'll end it just so we see
what's around here
so those balloon things that fell from
the sky are called sooner devices
there's still so much we don't know
about them but trust my boss PIRA to
take a thing we know so little about
internet or something useful she's the
sharpest person in Hyrule a creative
genius
yeah I like her
my favorite breath of the wild
characters I like um I would say Pura
and that Desert Princess
nope
oh sorry I'm busy at the moment so a lot
to talk to you between swings you never
know when monsters will pop up so I take
my training seriously you might have
noticed but your sword handles
differently so it's wise to try
different types to get used to the view
yeah
nothing to do with them being small
[Laughter]
no
that's that's a coincidence
um
they have like their own little pond in
here is there feces
on ceiling
useless Pond if there's no finish in
here
it's basically useless wait they got
horsey look at the horsey can I have
um what is that really you link if we're
turned it's such a relief to see that
you say oh let me introduce myself I'm
grounded
head of the monster controls crew it's
our job to keep the monsters at Bay as
best as we can through Hyrule but aside
from that we've been assisting in the
search for Princess Zelda whose
whereabouts are unknown I'm glad you've
returned safely but I am Gravely
concerned about the princes I'm holding
out hope that the monster control crew
brings back good news they're searching
the castle for her now
[Music]
Pierre has given us orders to search for
ruly around the Hyrule Castle
I'm still dripping so much the dripping
is so exaggerated
[Music]
Zelda so it seems the best starting
point in the search anyway pure enlisted
uh our monster control crew to help out
so yeah that's what we're doing
we've joined the search link who I can
keep our forces on standby and not send
extra people here if you head to the
castle you'll run into holes and the
advanced party who will probably just be
super surprised to see you
[Music]
uh it's pretty
oh so you're linked this link that I
keep hearing about you look really tough
I'd like to teach you you to teach me
about combat when all this is done
I'm glad you have put you in safely but
I am greatly concerned about the
princess I'm holding out hope that the
monster control yeah okay
is that where I find that oh
that's why you gave me this Hood
it oh wait I don't have money
I can't buy it anyway
[Music]
can you can I sell things
that's why I'm oh that's why I'm Dark
Link
because he soon becomes darkling hmm
are you the shopkeeper hey welcome it's
your first time at my store right
it's the only place to shop here and
look out Landing I know it looks a
little fun together but I stock a nice
selection of goods I run a store back in
my hometown so I hope you'll support my
place here
bye bye stuff
how much will they get for when what do
I even want to sell I don't really have
um
I feel like I need ah wait I can sell
for crafting are they for selling
I remember now
the old Pals were for selling and this
one's still the rubies
oh
Ah
that's how you make money
[Music]
oh yeah
what else should I sell
I don't know about the rest
um they can be used for crafting but now
having money is good
monster Parts really
[Music]
good enough for now you got planted down
yeah 3 is 70. so again sorry is it worth
buying this or do I get something like
this soon anyway
maybe the hood
or
oh I think I could
um almost afford everything
as well
[Music]
let's get the tunic
you make me happy too
whoa
I got 240 left
[Music]
highly unhooked
ah can you upgrade uh armor too I forgot
if that was possible
oh
yeah looking good
nice
ah
oh
ah oh
should I help you I can do that better
than you
for me it takes one chop and it's like
gone
are you building something
[Music]
yeah nice Village did I see everything
interesting now
I guess you could go up all the way to
the top here
I should build an elevator
enough
oh
please
this is
[Music]
can I not
iced what are you doing this that's what
when you get the paraglider
not a whole nap
okay
then I think I'm happy for now
I'll keep this running
on the side
and I'll read super chantos
thanks guys for watching so far make
sure to catch up uh because on Sunday
we'll play some more
yeah
uh I'll start even an hour earlier on
Sunday
because it's weekend I thought you guys
would like to wake up an hour early hey
um
and then tomorrow is good at collab in
the late evening around this time
actually or one hour later I think or or
this time not sure
what the hell charge your phone
do it
do it do it
yeah we're gonna play a little game that
I randomly found when I was going for
like game permissions
I was like oh where's this looks like a
fun Co-op game hmm
so I think we'll all see it for the
first time tomorrow but yeah got a
little game prepared
for good and me
hopefully it will be fun
yeah thank you for the stream yeah no
thank you I had fun I I am not as
intimidated
uh uh generally of the game anymore I
mean some of the clowns
like if there's like groups that's a bit
scary and I think later on with like
more difficult enemies like the the in
German they called uh those horsey men
loins
I know what they're called in
uh German in English
uh but those are particularly scary
Aya
yeah I finished the tutorial
hmm
it didn't even feel like a tutorial
yeah it was definitely very well
implemented I I enjoyed that too I think
they did a good job at the tutorial I
think
even as a
as someone who played breath of the wild
you learned things there because you got
all those new tools
but will we get the old tools as well I
think I saw them being used in
maybe in some maybe I don't know do you
get the autos
[Music]
would be kind of a lot of tools if you
get those two but without them
um
no thank you lil
[Music]
oh you thought they removed Shield
surfing
the ultra hand is basically an upgraded
magnetism
okay if they removed all the old tools
[Music]
yeah interesting at least I feel like it
would be like too much tools if you have
all the although
yeah there's not really much more space
there's like two more things you can put
there and
two of them are taken up by not really
tool things like amiibo on the map
so the other things the other things
might not even be
like real tools either
interesting
can't think of any of the runes that you
get in breath of the wild that didn't
get replaced here really oh okay
well well kind of refreshing maybe I and
I I guess then I understand why they
came up with some weird tools because
they wanted to make like completely new
tools overall and so they have to
completely do something completely new
um that's not the old tools so they
would come up with weird stuff like
gluing things together
[Music]
hmm
new gimmicks
all new gimmicks
yeah yeah cause like a lot of stuff is
like the same right like the graphic and
generally the the whole engine and
everything
there's so much that's the same
that if you keep really everything the
same
and just change the story hmm yeah that
would would have maybe been a bit
disappointing so some things are
switched up
yeah amiibo what the hell I guess it's
like a constant uh promotion
advertisement slot because you
constantly when you try to switch your
tool get reminded that amiibos exist
because I heard that back in the day
uh with like I guess what like we the
wee times amiibos were released more
and nowadays they don't release many
amoebas anymore so it's not used as much
anymore but they still exist
but I've never had one because like back
then when it was more popular I guess we
just
I don't know didn't have money or
interest or use for it uh mainly for
Spanish
Wii U and 3DS was the amiibo heyday
yeah I heard that they were like more
common earlier on and now it's like what
what's an amiibo
[Music]
look kind of nice I just don't collect
figure wings I
I'm not interested in that so
um
oh I just noticed they don't do the ding
dong down here because the time Tower is
not here huh
the new link one yeah I think I saw it
yeah they make cool figures and then the
fact that it has a function in game in
theory I think that's a good argument to
buy it but I just don't really care for
figurines
um
I wish that there's card versions
instead of figures oh you want to
collect cards instead well at least they
would be cheaper you know
they had all of the amoebas but like
five well that's a lot probably right
the only figure I care about is the
Kiana figure
ah
still not on sale right
mysterious mysterious
you can still not buy a single Kiara
figure right
and then there's like free of Cali
right
fell the relaxed time and her like uh
chibi one
and her big one though can you not
actually get all of them already
hmm
good smile please
please
I don't know I don't really get updates
about that I don't know what what's
happening I don't know what's the
planned release date or so
I have no idea
[Music]
yeah
gaguda has a couple too good on Cali um
okay let's move over to the office
oh my God I want to hear the the
beautiful Zelda music
[Music]
are still great prototypes and I
feel like I saw maybe I'm imagining but
I feel like I saw a color
one
maybe not
I'm not sure
maybe I'm just like maybe my brain is
like Auto filling the colors in
that's it
not yet I swear I saw a color one too
right yeah
hahaha
big chocolate
wait
patience
cute
I like my hood
[Music]
the color prototype of the pop-up parade
and the oh yeah okay maybe that's the
one I saw
[Music]
yeah
keep the game running game a lot
[Music]
where do I read
help help
[Music]
I finished
the members super chats
[Music]
rebroadcast I will show down
Hotline Miami
okay
are you broken
got you
yeah
[Music]
I saw and the other day you know this is
this K-Pop song that's like it got
really popular and like also viral as a
like a tick tock sound I think
the the cupid song
[Music]
yeah that song from 50 50. I randomly
stumbled upon a really good
version
and I sent it to Kura and was like oh my
God
this sounds so good listen to it sounds
exactly like you
and I think she would like the song too
and I have an idea like if if we want to
do karaoke but our voice just is [\h__\h]
dead we can just play these AI covers
you stumbled upon it too probably
because of me algorithm told me to watch
the videos that I watch in case you guys
are curious
listen to this
it's like
like she's literally
is is literally her it's so good
[Music]
yeah yeah it is indeed also like scary
hmm
but this one is just quality
is this like is it
I don't know
you didn't see anything
right it sounds like her
it does sound like her
[Music]
it's a cute song too
hmm
[Music]
ah I saw the Spanish pecora one too I
think
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
but that one I feel like it wasn't as
good as this gouda one hmm
[Music]
oh I'm not using it I don't plan on
learning how to use it no
um
no no no no
a pickle one yeah and I think yeah
somebody made something with me a while
ago
I think
the Spanish pickle was so funny uh
[Music]
we don't talk about Spanish people
okay okay let's move on although
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] the whole stream I just couldn't
breathe well man what the hell
it's not fair
why
but I had fun anyway me me me
I'm kind of scared though how long the
game will be it's intimidating
real intimidating
[Music]
how long is it well we don't don't
really know
40 to 50 hours like breath of the Wild
um
now try to do some stuff off screen
zaldo
fun with zaldo was zaldo Zelda
pretty moms yay thank you
legend of zeldo
[Music]
you can adjust the line face on how much
side so yeah yeah I wonder I mean I
don't want a speed run it though because
it's like a beautiful game with so much
detail and so many things to do
I really don't wanna
try to speed through it I feel like I
want to appreciate the game
um
so I hope you guys stay with me through
this adventure from now on
um
you crito
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
even when I do some stuff off screen I
think it will be mostly like collecting
stuff maybe doing side quests
or so but I will I won't like uh
continue the main quest
I think
[Music]
making it often answers like Amazon oh
yeah I don't I don't I feel
we'll see how it goes I generally I
don't wanna
um
go over the main quest privately I want
there to be at least some kind of
connection some string that goes through
the whole playthrough that you can
follow
um
is that how I'ma played it
I'll stay forever don't understand the
game you don't need to try to complete
it I guess you'll become kibaba before
you do or maybe change GTA 6.
I don't think so it won't be longer than
Fire Emblem and it will be more like
variation and more action than Fire
Emblem I think
[Music]
as a stream game I think it would be
better at least
than five emblem
looks more it's more like I don't know
interesting to stream to watch Maybe
hmm
generally
if I don't run around in a big open
field for too long
okay where's this phone that I'm looking
for here
the re-broadcast
foreign
[Music]
whoa since joining kfb I'm happy that
there are karaoke broadcasts on my
birthday ah and I didn't see last time I
would like to thank my ever enthusiastic
tento kfp for that welcome for the warm
welcome oh that was perfectly timed yeah
on your birthday and it was even
pre-broadcasted at a fitting time for
like Asian time zones
um
happy birthday thank you
it's late by now but still
thank you so much for spending your time
with kfb and with me even on your
birthday thank you and I hope you
enjoyed it I sang some Korean songs too
so that was hopefully special to you
thank you very much for the support and
I hope you will spend your next birthday
with us too
um
oh like you don't have to be there on
your birthday in the Stream but if you
would still be around every once in a
while that would be cool
[Music]
thanks for the pinky only for my goddess
Austin her Divine voice I do I get up
this early bird choice
thank you for the rebroadcast God is
awesome but didn't you watch the the
first one too
[Music]
you guys force yourself
to get up like really [\h__\h] early in
the morning for the rebroadcast even
though you already saw the the original
one
you guys
guys sweet like what you don't even have
to do that at all you already saw all of
that
even better the second time really
it was worth watching toys
oh man
yeah and
Last Resort in abiti where to go good
doesn't feel that same I love your
singing thank you
for like getting up at like six or seven
a.m or so for that man what
thank you for the support
so sweet
[Music]
laughs
I forced myself to watch the first one
is just good
oh at a really late time for you right
you know you didn't have to
I told you I would rebroadcast it at a
better time
[Music]
thank you though thank you love your
setlist thank you I try to mix it up you
know
and and have some songs that I feel like
you guys would know because generally I
think I understand it's more fun if it's
songs that you know
so you know
but of course people have different
tastes so now everyone's gonna be happy
oh
um
thank you I'm glad that you guys enjoy
it
um
your alarm for the morning wonderful
want to hear you sing anything whether I
know it or not
thank you
you love me unconditionally huh
[Music]
you watch my rebreakers out of reflex I
was like ah okay while we're streaming
oh I saw this before but oh well
my my mouse is like moving automatically
I can't help but click on the thumbnail
ah I'm watching oh oh well I guess I'll
watch I'll keep watching all right uh
that code actually sent a follow-up
Pinky
some of your chickens volunteered for
the early shift lava I have another
pinky on behalf of their devoted early
shift Jenkins
Yumi is Right rather loved
oh yeah we were just talking about it
you guys
voluntarily getting up so early thank
you
[Music]
so supportive so sweet
thank you very much
you want to explain to the pinky I love
you mini inks too thank you Jacob Duncan
flaming behind flaming pants thank you
um
John
thanks for listening in I appreciate it
[Music]
snow lip little party
a whole novel
like Muslim I love most tickets
Anime boy dancing
and Han
humpback
more Muslim appreciators nice
I just got back Miss muscle stream yeah
you did
have fun catching up Unwritten birds
dinosaurs
[Music]
next is a showdown Idol Showdown
hello
[Music]
one to two moms what the [\h__\h] why
why
pay and then you get it in one to two
months what the [\h__\h]
why
what kind of scam is that
hey oof
that's ridiculous
that's actually ridiculous
[Music]
maybe you can borrow someone else's
coffee
for that time yeah or can you ask for a
refund and buy it somewhere else
I feel like some people might finish
their game after a week and then you can
get theirs and you're still earlier
yeah refund and then get digitally
I always buy digitally since I started
streaming
because I just want the game right away
don't have time to order games all the
time nah
[Music]
um
same
it's the the age of digital stuff you
know
thank you
I'm glad you like the voice lines thank
you so much
Jackson FB donkey soon can't focus soon
pinky I think I'm currently watching
very late at night on my vacation in
Japan oh it's a very beautiful country
with great culture all and also my first
time going it's much different than
Ireland
ah you came from Ireland have a great
stream thank you very much
oh vacation I wonder how long you're
staying and maybe by now you're already
back anyway
[Music]
thank you
which island Ireland
I Ireland
[Music]
you know why I think I realized I
understood why my cats have been like
meowing like crazy these days
at least at night I think I figured it
out
[Music]
because I had the window open in the
living room
uh for several days even at night and I
think sometimes the light was there on
as well and yesterday at night I saw
I was so disgusted like a million tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny flies
all Gathering up on the ceiling
at around all the lights
and at one time when I went to check
what the hell's movie was meowing at I
saw that she was like up there on the
wall right on on the on the climbing
thing is meowing at the wall and then I
didn't see it yet at that point but
there it was probably because of the
Flies
um
no those are not like regular flies like
only [\h__\h] tiniest lies you wouldn't
even be able to get them with a fly
catcher
but I feel like those have been like
annoying them and I reckon I I I saw
them yesterday
for the first time
no so I have to buy something to kill
them
when during the day I didn't see them
they probably only like gather really
when
I have the light on and then they gather
there don't know where they are now
they're not in my room
hello
this movie has entered the room
[Music]
she flops down demands
pet pets
you gotta come up here if you want Peter
pads
[Music]
all right
gotcha I got you
oh she's so cute
[Music]
how you doing
let me smell you
[Music]
her butt's a bit wet a new stuff I knew
something was wrong
[\h__\h]
I know that's why I tried to smell her
because I was wondering where the smell
came from
that's a problem with fluffy cats
don't worry I didn't stick my face into
the butt it was my arm that touched it a
little bit don't get the wrong idea
gonna wash my arm afterwards
hmm
ah
go can I I don't wanna I don't wanna
leave the
you guys are gonna leave if I leave now
it's just a little bit
hmm
her butt fluff was a bit wet
that's it's okay
it's okay
no it's okay
you don't have to smell it anyway it's
not so bad I really don't smell it
anymore and don't smell it anymore
it's okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
you don't smell anyway what do you care
oh
it's okay
that's nasty no
[Music]
God damn it well
I will give chonkers a hug on my way if
I find her
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
mmm
she is so fat
yeah of course I I washed my arm it's
wet
oh
[Music]
I just can't get enough of their
softness man
she's so fluffy
[Music]
oh
you know yesterday night I had a sad
moment
because I have um
we're living pretty far away but I have
like another couple of friends
I mean like a boyfriend girlfriend
couple
who I like
um so supportive so sweet some of my
bestest friends I just don't meet them
much
but whenever I see them they're like so
much fun to be around
and they also have two cats
yeah I had I always third wheel it's so
weird but uh it's interesting because
they're all like different
that all the couples they kind of
function differently
yeah and um they also have two cats
and I once slept over
at their own place so I know their their
cats they're really fluffy and sweet and
very cuddly
and they're also like sister cats
but apparently they they were already
really old
15 years at this point now
and one of them apparently just died
uh like had a million of health issues
and was made to sleep no and I heard
about it from my friend
oh
what happened
scary
oh scary I'm saving the village right no
nothing can attack me in the Villas
right this sounds so scary wait what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] this is so scary yeah
it's getting red
here first we have to see this
oh [\h__\h] like moons rise
why is she saying that as if she's like
the cult leader and she's making it
happen
shines upon the land
the English spirits of slain monsters
return to flesh
foreign
can I go back to the Happy music now
yeah
I think so
oh
wow
what a flute
the memberships wow
thank you thank you
[Music]
yeah it's just to respawn the enemies
but it's scary
very dramatic
right
yeah anyway I was saying that the cats
one of the cats died and she told me
about it and it was so sad oh my God
I wasn't worried about the other cat but
apparently the other cat is Fun the
thing is though
like sometimes I say when one of when
you have like two pets and one of them
dies
then the other one was very used to the
presence of the other pet
well uh or sometimes be very distraught
by it
so but she said that
um the other cat for now seems fine it's
been a couple days it's been a week or
so but the other cat is fine since
but the other cat is just as old she
says that the health issues are fine now
but they're being careful
but man
imagine thank God my cats are so so
young I don't think I can
I could function if one of them dies I
would probably be
like oh
not functionable for
months Maybe
[Music]
um
not feel so bad for the remaining cut
too
[Music]
so I tried to like you know talk with my
friend about it and cheer them up into
them you know
I can imagine how rough it would be
but my cats are like what now five four
five years
oh yeah probably something around that
so I hope they will also live at least
15 years
um you gotta keep them healthy
[Music]
please live as long as you can
um
your Phoenix cats
[Music]
uh anyway where was I uh Aya flashy Fox
don't know if you're back to Ireland by
now but I hope you're enjoying Japan
make the most out of it yeah don't don't
spend too much time watching streams
while you're on vacation okay maybe just
to fall asleep at night okay
mm-hmm
lore preserved
gotta get more cats now yeah yeah yeah
eventually I think like now I'm not
ready but I think when they get a bit
older I want to stagger
I want to get more cats so I can stagger
that no cats will ever be alone hmm
but then I I will always be like
experiencing cat deaths at some point in
my life
oh man
then get a new cat to cheer me up oh man
optimal cat deployment order
I have like eight cats damn ideal that's
that's ideal
genetically modified cats to live as
long as African how long
do rats live what a [\h__\h] would an
African parrot live longer than a cat
that's not fair
the game shouldn't come and started
engineering
80 [\h__\h] years
why
the parents generally live that long
what
well other birds don't live that long
normally do they
foreign
must be like the one exception or so
holy [\h__\h]
damn what
African grays are special whoa
grandparents and a parrot for a very
long time damn imagine having to listen
to a parrot going like
[Music]
like for 80 [\h__\h] years
I mean sometimes you know I see some
videos of like cute birds bathing and
doing cute stuff
just jumping on your finger and all that
cute cute but oh
imagine hearing that for your whole life
oh my God
one of your cats could say good morning
I feel like
smoothie sometimes really meows in a way
that it sounds like she's saying
something
I noticed that the other day
yeah yeah she's adopting adapting
speech
you say Kiki every day well it's my
freaking cup catchphrase I have to
[Music]
anyway uh temperature engineering Joseph
or a Loma donation
foreign
that's what I'm saying
let's see girls yay
[Music]
free Sunday what do you mean free Sunday
oh yeah seagulls there's so many
seagulls in Rome I took so many pictures
of them remember
are you here now are you spending your
evening with your friend
mine mine mine ah free Sunday you can
enter museums for free I didn't even
know that damn yeah
sorry I forgot sending the restaurants
but maybe you were able to go to that
one that I told you on stream anyway
hmm
[Music]
first on it first Sunday of the month so
not every Sunday oh you're lucky
free museum Night in Paris tomorrow oh
wow wow
too bad I'm not in Paris
I don't like I normally don't go to
museums though even when I'm like
uh traveling somewhere in a new city
I I actually I don't go to uh
museums much
no free ones in Austria I I think
there's probably some something like
that maybe
foreign
no not too nerdy I just feel like um
[Music]
well it depends on the museum really
depends on what they have if it's just
like art
that's not interesting to me
because well
it's just
I don't know going for a room with art
on the walls oh no man
hmm can just look at Art online on the
internet
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah other stuff
like dinosaurs or so yeah maybe that's
I don't really I probably wouldn't aim
for that either but that would be more
interesting yeah
[Music]
art in person it's different
yeah I could like act as if I'm like
sophisticated and stand in front of a
picture and be like
this [\h__\h] is so deep it really like
cleanses my soul yeah I could I could
but deep inside I knew it was just
bullshitting myself
[Laughter]
but if I want to feel sophisticated like
that
yeah then I would do that yeah for
whatever reason
[Music]
yeah somewhat of an artist myself
nah no hate against museums if you enjoy
that cool but I just personally I feel
like I would not be able to appreciate
it much
[Music]
Mabel
Mabel Mabel
[Music]
no history is cool history Museum's cool
I um
I visited some
historic museums in the past
also in Austria
those are cool
like stuff where I also learn about the
history
that I really appreciate
I went to
uh
there's like a shots come up thingy like
a lots of like treasure from
Royal
Austrian families or so
yeah and and like there was like
millions of beautiful
decorated and golden and silver and all
that kind of stuff plates and uh
cutleries and all that and like
depending on the time and on who's it
from it has like different patterns you
know blah blah blah you know very
interesting yeah
now that sounded really oh it looked it
looked really impressive especially when
it all was set up on the big table
um
uh yeah yeah the Imperial one that's the
one mm-hmm
and then there was a [\h__\h] Museum that
one was a bit special
um there's this this Empress to see that
austrians beloved Empress [\h__\h]
um however she committed suicide right
um she had a very like tragic life
so there's this museum for her
um where you can like learn about her
story and you go for these rooms and you
learn about it history everywhere
written on the roles and you see the
dress and all that
[Music]
ah
yeah yeah there was a
cartoon cartoon oh I know wait yeah okay
she was assassinated but she was also
depressed
she was very depressed that's probably
why I just mixed up and thought she was
maybe
she took her life but no
um
yeah yeah no she had a very very tragic
life you know hmm
[Music]
her son I am her son committed suicide
uh
CC
[Music]
the new Zelda was a very different
breath of the world no no
no I didn't and that's maybe a good
thing since I mean it's connected it's a
sequel so you want it to be connected
and feel like you're in the same world
wasn't she very loved by the public yeah
yeah she definitely was
[Music]
I bought like a
a necklace from her one that she would
always wear
I mean okay it's not the same but it's
inspired by her
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah yeah there's some famous movies
yeah yeah I am
I don't think I watched the most famous
one though with Romi Schneider I don't
think I've ever watched that one
I think I I'm too young movie too old I
wasn't
really if I wasn't
in this Dimension at that time or I was
too young
why am I on you stick by the way
you don't want to be on my stick I'm
just experimenting trying to figure out
this this gluing function you know
I'm still learning you're my
experimental object
you volunteered you forgot that you
volunteered um
How Could You Forget
weird
I I have your vocal
voluntation voluntaryation
agreement yeah
yeah
next time I'll
have you write it down
[Music]
what what well what what what what
anyway
artist and UI logo designer here I've
been watching you since your enw so I
was very happy when you made your when
we made your inclusion for the game I
hope you enjoy kikiriki Also hi Kelly
I saw like during the stream I was like
hmm the Kiana thing I don't know how to
use it also looks not so spectacular but
then later I saw on Twitter people sent
it to me
um that apparently if the opponent and
you both have the Kiara
uh collab
and then you reflect a projectile and
they do it at the same time then it
creates this like huge
even full of that looks crazy
and people were like nerfed it's crazy
but they said no apparently they keep it
and the thing is though I think you can
keep it because like when is this gonna
happen like on accident like in a normal
battle you don't do it on purpose when
you don't make it happen on purpose
I feel like when will it happen come on
both will have to have the kiwao collab
both will have to have the thingy ready
at the same time and then you will have
to purposefully like if you see the
other person using their Kiara collab
why would you shoot a projectile
[Music]
when you know it's gonna be
um
blocked any or sent back anyway
if you understand the game
then
generally that's why I think that it's
kind of from my point of view a week
uh
what are they called
a week
whatever
skill whatever
because
when you see it when you know the game a
little bit assist yeah then
how hard is it to not send the
projectile and just uh attack normally
most of the time people don't seem to be
using their projectile anyway that much
so
[Music]
it's it's not that helpful from my
understanding y'all
maybe okay maybe only against botan
but yeah then that's that's not that
helpful is it
[Music]
um
if anything Kiara shouldn't be nerfed
should be improved to block not only
projectiles no maybe uh reflex
projectiles but block other attacks you
don't have to
reflect everything
[Music]
oh a fire Aura yeah so you can't get too
close or so ah yeah okay a fire order
would be really good because then you
can't get too close to close and then
maybe you think oh I should shoot a
projectile and then boom but that only
really works once too don't you think
because then you know all right reflects
projectiles so then you don't do it
again and then you just wait
[Music]
I don't know
it doesn't really force them it only
forces them once until they understand
and they'll never do it again I don't
know I don't know I don't know much
about the game anyway in the end so I
shouldn't be the one making
um
bringing up ideas
making demands I leave it up to the
developers and the fans that are like
deeply into the game
um
yeah yeah I don't know what I'm talking
about anyway yeah
[Music]
hey
thank you for the support see you all
right
the guy Nicholas dungeon ssrb duncast
thank you for the pinky
I play and Love Actually Ariza right now
just because of you oh wow Tales of
arise I enjoyed too only because you got
me into it but I bet you would enjoy
Western RPGs too
yeah I mean it depends yeah which one
but I don't doubt that either
I even got people to buy lost epic AKA
topic
I'm like
perfect for sponsorships you know this
is just proof once again
hmm
you got tepic you should have gotten
yourself lost epic God damn it
[Music]
you got me to buy hola Miami damn really
so influential I'm such an influencer
hmm
I am a tea thank you yes
uh oh thank you also one of the deaths
so many deaths that say hello in these
streams Brutus salad dancing ate thanks
for two pinkies
now I have to watch the third movie I
heard that by the way attention previous
subject was obviously a joke uh love
your streams no matter what games you
play or movies you watch Breath of the
wild is easy until you walk up to an
enemy that kills you in one hit sounds
like the crafting will be fun this time
though
yeah so far I'm in a crafting like the
car for example it takes endless time so
like I feel like why
why would I do this
um
the only time where I feel like I would
do it is when I make a boat to get over
a huge Lake
um
I don't know you'll get faster at it
really
[Music]
you got better Wheels later
oh steering wheels too
okay
okay I know until then
difficult
you got a power that saves your designs
um
yeah we'll see
we'll see
[Music]
but
oh it's it's not
hopefully it's not like always necessary
to do it
because it takes up time
but yeah so far I'm fine um I had fun
today for sure thank you
are you playing too
on your own why are you just watching
Wawa
that's car the car was
it was basically asking me to build it
with the wheels and all that right in
front of my eyes
ah you made it the story Parts I guess
that's also one solution
to watching my streams without getting
spoiled
your first car was worse
[Music]
thanks for the gift memberships 20.
oh thank you
so money
so many new members
yay thank you so much
oh where was on animals
thank you
I won't give you up either
I'm Never Gonna Let You Down
I hope you are dancing like thank you
soon
thank you oh thank you light we keep
Tunes thanks for the rest of the chat
you're my first and best so I ain't
going anywhere if I disappear it's only
work related
[Music]
I know you've been around for so long
Wicked Tunes thank you
thank you you're the best
[Music]
I love your Untouchable thank you eagle
look also
ah thank you it's seeing your name makes
me feel so nostalgic because every time
I say your name I think of the early
days where we played Don't Starve
Together
of the myth crew
that's so nostalgic you want to teach
Dad
um
yeah they were cool
having our own characters self-made no
sponsorship
wasn't that like yesterday
nah it doesn't feel like listen
yesterday it feels like a he's just a
girl
oh yeah Cali wanted to die but like she
couldn't do herself
and I was burning things up
I think
I had no idea what the others were doing
uh
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
and another pinky I can't see colors
anymore red
a beautiful
vibrant red Super Chat
[Music]
it was a fun mess you made a good enough
joke you know was dying laughing did I
I don't remember how do you remember
that
[Music]
oh
I was Rising her Insanity raising her
sanity
I wouldn't say that I want to go back to
those times though
because
I think back then I still felt very
distant from
everybody and now I feel much closer so
I feel like those are good old times but
these are a good better newer times
[Music]
so true so true
um
looking for the top donation Pro Hero
thank you
thank you for all the super chats guys
very hectic first year
the heck thing I would say the first
half year was hectic
and difficult
rough
not the whole the whole year was rough
though I can say that
rough
scuffed
uh stressful
depressing
times
[Music]
when times go by fast though
yeah I'm glad I
uh
was able to
persevere
through all the bad times
like even even in my second year last
year
there were
um
last year
in some ways last year was worse than
the first year for me personally but
it's like a lot of things that I
can't even
like really talk about much
it's more like behind the scenes things
um
oh but I also persevered for that
and hopefully this year 2023
so far hasn't been too bad
so I hope that
it will continue knock on wood
are those things any better now
uh yeah yeah partially I mean
um
some things
have improved
yeah
I'm I'm good
started off of a bang that is true
starting off basically pretty much with
the
3D reveals very exciting
and we had a big concert and now we're
having another big concert this time our
own
en concert
[Music]
now I'm working on an album like
generally the year is looking good but
you never know what happens
what can happen to
make things more difficult we're
challenging
[Music]
has come so far
yeah I mean yeah we've done a lot of
things
I just
I know I feel like things have calmed
down so much and I really hope
oh we can grow bigger
I need
I need more en members I need more
collaboration partners and all that
so uh
that's something I feel like that has
been
Maybe
[Music]
dragging
us down maybe a bit
an EU Branch I don't need a whole EU
branch no
[Music]
I don't think that's necessary or even
smart
like an EU branch makes no sense because
in the end they'll probably just end up
speaking English anyway
unless you have like I guess maybe like
an eel Branch made up with like five
members one speaks mainly French one
speaks mainly Spanish one speaks mainly
German one speaks mainly Greek or so
whatever
uh and so on
and and yeah so they all speak English
when they collab and so on but when they
do their own streams they speak their
own languages that would be funny
interesting what the hell that would go
though
Greek YouTuber
Spanish would be not only good for the
Europeans though yeah
would be good for lots of people because
lots of people speak and understand
Spanish yeah
please do that well I can't it's not my
decision and all that uh and I kind of
doubt that that would ever happen it's a
bit of a risky idea and concept
[Music]
um
whole gen in Spanish would just work
[Music]
I guess not really something that would
interest me because I don't understand
Spanish
um
[Music]
would you say you really want a new
member or not I remember you talking
about worrying about the time slots
oh I mean at least one would be nice I
guess
um
just to meet up I want someone to go on
vacations with me
I want someone to travel Europe with me
no
what happens if they add an European
member and then the one European member
they add is like someone I don't get
along with that would be [\h__\h] too
though
that would be unfortunate
[Music]
I will
have to make myself likeable
don't know who think this
um
well what do I know I know nothing but
you know it's okay it's okay
I don't know
if I never get another European member
that's okay too because I'll continue
having my slot for myself there's
there's a good side to it and a bad side
to it I can see the positive in any
situation oh you know yeah
okay
[Music]
let's read Hotline Miami superchata
check out Jim Tracy thanks for the pinky
ah major congratulations on favorite
night finally hitting 1 million views
that's usually one of my favorite songs
of yours and deserves all the success it
gets now on to 2 million and further oh
two two mil FIFA night
huh equanite is cursed by the algorithm
but I'm just happy finally all my
originals reached 1 million
thank you guys for streaming and I know
a couple of you were trying to stream it
for the past forever
eternity
endlessly thank you I know it must have
been the hard battle
[Music]
hmm
thank you especially with YouTube making
it really difficult to stream things
purposefully
yeah it's a complicated complicated
science well thanks for trying Jim Tracy
thank you so much also for celebrating
favorite night
I listen to it almost every day thank
you
but now that we have everything on one
million I don't mind you guys like you
know you can
um change your focus to not streaming on
YouTube but streaming on Spotify Etc
um because I don't know I don't use
Spotify and all these other
um there's other
programs but having my numbers go up my
streaming my monthly streaming numbers
and all that go up a little bit more
over there is probably also very
beneficial for my future creation budget
hmm
yeah
anything really honestly as long as you
listen somewhere in some way
I think it will help my statistics
somehow
yeah
[Music]
that's [\h__\h] us
[\h__\h] North I've brought it up like a
million times with staff since two years
ago since hinatoli
just let's just ignore its existence
okay
I can't it seems like I can't get rid of
it I brought it up a million times
[Music]
it's a [\h__\h] parasite I swear to God
like it it literally is
[Music]
don't get it to one million no
don't click on it
ban it outside out of your brains you
shouldn't even be knowing about it
don't give it free promotion
yeah the fake Kiana who the [\h__\h] is it
makes me so mad like I don't know if
there's like a proper normal artist
behind that if they did that on purpose
or not
if they did it on purpose and [\h__\h] them
if not then [\h__\h] the whatever bot or so
put it there
I don't understand how that happens
I understand it
but it's ridiculous
it's ridiculous
[Music]
there's someone I don't know for like
the beginning of my music releases
there's a parasite
someone put their song with my name but
a different like picture so obviously a
different artist
and a different song too I think but
it's like always if you look for Attack
music it will always be in that
takatashikira music category thingy
and sometimes I think it also was on
Amazon music showing up like that under
my songs
I don't know if it's that easy to do
that then
like anyone could do that right
then there must be a way to get rid of
it too like what the hell
oh well whatever I don't have the energy
for this anymore
quiet wolves
oh and thank you quite wolf
glad you liked the voice back
thank you thank you
uh Hildegard thank you
[Music]
Mundo
I read this
asake
or
[Music]
um
I think that's it
spaghetti and blankets thank you for the
pinky hey boss I don't know often Super
Chat I usually prefer to make bad jokes
in chat but I figured it's my birthday
so I should treat myself to be honest
there is so much I want to tell you I
could write an essay about why you're my
Oshi just know that I will always
support you
thank you so much that's very sweet
happy belated birthday
are you here now
where's my spaghetti friend
did you spill your spaghetti yet
oh see you
in Vegas what is it like because of your
birthday you're in Vegas for a couple
days or so
why are you always in Vegas and you just
proudly like to tell people I'm in Vegas
Vegas
wait isn't it in the middle of the day
what are you doing
all right now
relaxing first
Vegas is not a place you go to to relax
normally is it
that is an interesting choice I mean I'm
sure there's like
ways to relax in Vegas
probably
city that never sleeps
for gambling I guess okay it's too early
okay I get them
maybe gambling is relaxing to you
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay go to them in
the night
lots to do here oh yeah it looks like a
it seems like a fun place with lots of
exciting activities party party lots of
crazy buildings and hotels
um
then enjoy your time there
and oh don't spend too much time with my
streams
you should be enjoying your birthday
vacation happy belated birthday
congratulations thank you for the
support
thank you soon
bye guys bye guys
if you win big money
invest some of it into kfp will you
if it's your membership or you know
paying your salary
[Music]
will give back to back to the people
[Laughter]
just kidding you can do it what you want
not just a suggestion
but don't don't go crazy okay don't do
anything Reckless like don't lose all
your money that's oof
oof be careful please
not even your lottery winnings or save
of course not
[Music]
5K super
yeah treat yourself
um
gamble responsibly
um or don't gamble at all
ideally
ideally toilet paper thanks for the
pinky I'm really hyped that you're
playing one of my favorite games
oh hello Miami
thank you I'm glad you uh and many
others were able to enjoy that
so many Hotline Miami fans I was
surprised
it was a lot of fun and I think I got so
much better
over time too
so I'm looking forward to playing the
second one at some point hopefully you
will be there as well my dear toilet
paper
what a weird name to have
thank you so much for the support thank
you
so impressed by how good you got
you really showcase your gaming skills
in the second stream
thank you I need like some classic black
shades
to put on to look cooler in these
moments because my normal sunglasses
that I have in my casual outfit I feel
like they don't quite have that effect
of coolness
yeah I need those like in the Emoji
one of those is what I need
[Music]
I made this account while on the
porcelain
ah
and you were like huh what should I name
my account looks at toilet paper that's
it that's what I want to go for
[Music]
well good that you didn't name it
something else that you were looking at
um
and another one thanks for the pinky
Unity chat yo gotta drop this pinky I'm
just so happy seeing you play invite to
the bgm I love the stream your reaction
to the song was very similar to mine
back in the day except that I didn't
shout it's like favorite night and like
2015. yeah yeah yeah
the museum was really good and I saw cow
carrot uploaded a remix of me singing
fever night over Hotline Miami
soundtrack did you see it guys
it sounded really good
it fit really well hmm
somehow Cocker's channel has turned into
a music channel because the past videos
are all music related what happened Kyle
Garrett what happened
yeah but music really good I enjoyed it
thank you Unity
check Lily aspects of the rise of a chat
today marks my second year of membership
I'm free at last from the confining
bucket wow I just wanted to say thank
you kilal for two amazing years with
lots of smiles and laughter it's been an
incredible journey and I'm super excited
for your new album thank
my first album yeah I'm working on it I
need to record songs actually that's
what I should be doing tomorrow probably
the earlier the better
um
yeah
I'll do my best thank you Lily for the
long-term support very happy you're part
of kfp for such a long time
and I hope you will like the album when
it comes out
I'm doing my best
if you liked my previous songs
until now then I think you will like the
album as well
generally because
[Music]
um I'm trying to
basically
give it the Wawa flavor
that I have established so far
something new sounding should be in
there too but generally should be Wawa
flavored yeah
yeah thank you so much
some more
of my few
European and in this case even Norway
viewers wow
sheesh
cute girl from Norway
um
[Laughter]
you gang what's up you gang rise Like a
Phoenix
oh apparently you're a vision is this
weekend I had no idea because I really
don't follow Eurovision song contest at
all
I don't think I will be watching any of
it I didn't watch it last time I'm not
gonna watch it this time
um
but yeah apparently it's happening
tomorrow
[Music]
I'm not in it unfortunately imagine I
was in it then I would tell you guys to
watch it but now I don't care yeah
[Music]
the German nominee that I lost probably
oh
checked out like a list of the not the
the one that finally made it but like
there were like several ones who made it
through one round right
I saw that
yeah yeah
[Music]
um oh was that the Austrian ones no I
think it was the German ones
no why would no watch exactly
I like that philosophy
yeah I really don't care much about
Eurovision I watched it live in my whole
life maybe once
when I was much younger and I just
happened to have a TV and all that and
there was nothing better on the TV
and that's a long time ago
so
yeah yeah but in Europe it's usually a
really hot thing
I know outside Europe you guys maybe
don't really get it
but in Europe it's really hype
don't let the Eurovision 2024 people see
this moment yep yep yeah let's keep this
secret if I get
a chance to be in Eurovision then of
course we're gonna tell the story of how
much I love Eurovision song contest
and how I watch it every year and always
dream of being in the Eurovision song
contest
since I was small I dreamed of it
remember your lines chickens remember
them the script follow the script
[Music]
laughs
delete this spot I'll ban everyone who
re-uploads it
[Music]
hey
what was I
um
Mamma Mia watch along I love them but I
don't think I want to do a lot long on
it
sample thank you for the Super Chat and
happy third birthday you are Sunshine
three years old
[Music]
congratulations
thank you for your long-lasting support
as well your third freaking birthday man
damn
[Music]
thanks for always being here and being
the Way You Are
human extension May believe that action
mode arcade dance
[Music]
monkey junction Rainier wolfcastle
Junction Canada in seventh reduction but
diving double Jones Duncan I am a tea
thank you
[Music]
foreign
what's that animal called again in your
picture
we weasel weasel am I saying something
in German or English I don't even know
anymore
you don't know what it means
you are you are a fraction
[Music]
pole cat
what that's called a pole cat
that's a weird name
cat that stands up like a pole
[Music]
pole cat
what's pulled a pole cat is mere wait is
meerkat and Polecat the same thing
cut from Poland
[Music]
um
let me Google
Polo cat why do I call oh okay it's a
common name for Sarah most elite species
oh okay
is polka the same as a ferret
the polka is an ancestor of the domestic
ferret but exactly where and when the
ferrets were domesticated are so
uncertain oh so well basically yes
pocket is basically a ferret
hey cute when they stand up they have
like a hunched back
so cute
the pictures
is that your profile picture because you
have one or oh it's your nickname
because of Polo so people started
calling you pole cat oh and that's so
cute
such a cute nickname
long boy is cute
they do have kind of a kitty face that's
adorable
wait then what is a a weasel
ah
it's like the shape is similar but the
colors are very different we weasel
versus Polo cat
what's the difference is it smaller
oh
[Music]
that's the same family of course pole
cats are more masculine and ferrets
though ferrets typically grow larger
also based on their head sizes you can
see the friends
finally ferrets enjoy social Lifestyles
while pole cats prefer a solitary
existence who
interesting I wonder what tirzu would
say about the the most most holiday
because there's 60 species of badges
other skunks Martin's mink minks ferrets
toads whistle is there a tearsville
video on this let me Google
must tell must what must mustelids
no
I was telling it there's no video on
this
ah what's [\h__\h]
hey then he didn't make a video about
them
yet
[\h__\h]
I should do a must-havely day
tier list
[Music]
yeah we went to animal
facts
like the video yourself I don't know
[\h__\h] about them
that's why I watch his videos tell me
about them
they're op are you sure really
maybe you have to make the video Sam
where was I oh
I hear a human extension May believe
a Rainier wolf Castle dances
watching stream Canada
Jones Junction
location
they're death machines I somehow can't
believe that they look too cute
but I have a double transaction I wait
every time
[Music]
again I underestimated the gamer of Ian
when I expected you to quickly abandon
this title it's okay I thought so too
can't wait to see what super implausible
game Choice you'll make next only to
have a bloody good time with it are
there any genres besides horror that you
usually refuse to touch
FPS right
um
[Music]
like at least like the typical
FPS games oh
I guess I also don't really play racing
games but not because I don't like them
I just also don't feel like they would
be good content
and I'm not like particularly interested
in interested in them I guess I'm like
neutral towards them
[Music]
my rhythm games I tried before but
it's it's rough if it's not something
like trombone champ
[Music]
which is that even a premium game
have you cleaned your butt
um
you better have cleaned your butt
yeah you probably did she's she's
generally a very clean cat
she claims herself all the time my cats
clean themselves all the time like any
other cat but yeah it is
oh yeah and sports games like FIFA [\h__\h]
who cares about
I don't think I don't think you guys
want that as a stream on my channel
anyway
hmm
okay dance of Hyrule that would be cute
my brain is mush
anyway thank you Flappy boy
very much for watching and I know for
now there might not be so many new
surprising choices because now I'm busy
with Zelda
foreign
okay it's been almost seven hours now
maybe I should end it
I'm bored
I I I'm weirdly bored I normally don't
have this feeling
but I'm just bored
oh
same
and maybe we should just
go different ways guys
for today
[Music]
the whole day no the whole dance has
been like
like a like a sloth
probably because I used up so much
energy yesterday
like what the hell I was
I didn't even tell my whole day but I I
I woke up right I went hiking
we hiked for like three hours
and then uh I went I heard it back home
I cleaned everything I was running up
and down up and down to like the garbage
room and into the uh Cellar and all that
trying to get everything look decent
then my mom arrives and I clean
continuously I continue to clean
then my brother arrives I stop cleaning
uh I did everything I did laundry I did
dishes I did everything everything I did
the guest uh room I did the living room
and then we go buy groceries
then my mom cooks but until then
still like socializing using up all my
freaking energy I was so tired
and I was so tired already at like 9 00
pm
and my mom was still like
my mom doesn't stop she's a freaking
wonderful when you put a person in front
of her or to her on the phone
she will never stop talking
um
she's even better at tangenting than me
oh I see
the game
has paused itself
actually the switch turned itself off
which is a good timing
I suppose
yeah that's why I escaped her fangs
eventually I had to oh
yeah and then I slivered my way into my
bedroom finally finally
sleep oh it felt like three days and one
day
um
oh yeah
normally like okay I either have days
where I use a lot of mental capacity or
I use a lot of physical capacity but
yesterday I used both to the absolute
maximum but the hiking was fun and after
the hiking we we got some ice cream too
like gelato
that was really good after hiking it
wasn't even that hot but it was good
weather and after hiking it just felt
like the greatest reward ever
um
no
very nice very nice indium
a treat of the long adventure
we plan another hiking ah maybe we were
talking about because my friends that
couple I went with uh BFF and RBF right
they they're very motivated to do things
they were talking about other
uh hiking trails
and I thank you I don't know
I was like yeah sure I guess
but also how about a picnic and also how
about just going to a lake and all that
you know I don't have to go hiking again
and again and again
we're gonna mix it up
you know
but it was nice like for once
there was like uh what's it in English
[Music]
ramson's Buck Rams
what's more they're also called wild
garlic what the [\h__\h] it's not garlic
though
bear a leak
Rams and buck Rams what's more common to
say
yeah Bella because what I'm trying to
but like throughout our hiking trail
there was a [\h__\h] ton of that everywhere
she was basically free to take but I
think it was probably already like too
old to really use it for cooking
never heard of it before
here it's like extremely common and we
make a pasta sauce out of it often
because we just have so much of it loads
and loads and loads and loads of it
it's really good though I love the taste
of it it's one of my favorite
um pasta sauces
to eat
it's not spicy no
it's not spicy unless you add a lot of
pepper to it or so I guess
yeah it's a really strong herb I guess
it has similarity to garlic somehow and
taste but I never felt like that it's
like super girl like yeah I guess it's
super garlic
oh maybe I should put it on a baguette
oh Bella bucket
yeah herb butter yeah yeah but normally
I ate it with a pasta noodles so good
and then there's always the season
where it grows everywhere endlessly
and people go to pick it because it's
like everywhere for free in like local
uh forests everywhere
it's the in the photo that I uploaded
the white flowers all of that is that
and that was just like one little spot
um
I think people would go there a little
bit earlier to like pick a lot for
themselves
but now my friend my BFF she was saying
uh I don't know if she wasn't even sure
herself but she was saying is probably
too late because at this point when it's
like already having these flowers and
all that then it tastes
bitter maybe or so
hmm
oh yeah it also has similarities to
another plant in in looks in visuals
that is very dangerous
very toxic very poisonous if you eat
that instead so gotta be careful but I
feel like it's so obvious from the smell
if you are in front of this herb you
will smell it
I smelled it it smelled so good
so I don't even understand how you can
pick the wrong one maybe only if it
grows right next to the other one Mike
looking like mixed into that like a half
half mix
then that's dangerous gotta be careful
hmm
it's similar to mushrooms then I I guess
a lot of things you pick in the forest
you just gotta be careful with
if you pick it yourself when I cook it
be careful
yeah yeah
um
anyway so I'm gonna end here thank you
guys for watching I'll see you tomorrow
with Google on my channel
and then more Zelda if you're interested
on Sundays
hope we will get very far on Sunday as
well yeah thank you
good night guys and in Germany
I'm gonna figure out what to do about
food now
still have leftovers from yesterday even
though I ate them for lunch but I have
to cook my hello fresh stuff otherwise
it's Gonna Be Blood
hmm what'd I do what I do what I do I'll
think about it bye bye
love you guys thank you so much for
watching
[Music]
foreign