[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
thanks
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I'll be right there one second
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay okay
[Music]
are you ready for more Luigi
we do it
yes
oh
why am I not moving oh
move move move
there you go hello
default pose
is shy
hello
sorry for the delay I was you know I
woke up an hour before the Stream
because very tired this too and then I
was gonna go to the supermarket to buy a
sandwich or so for later
and um well
then I was in front of the supermarket
and realized oh [\h__\h] it's uh a holiday
uh so I had to go somewhere else but
everything that was open was only like
software you have to wait until they
cook something for you
so I I got myself like a like a Pokeball
and some spring rolls and then
speedily ate them or half of it before
the Stream
so now I have some more spring rolls for
later
at least
when I get hungry because that was the
original intention to get something for
uh snacking when I get hungry in the
Stream and
um I was more thinking of something like
a sandwich but okay uh the spring rolls
were
nice and now I got like free free left
over but they don't give enough sauce so
now I'm out of sauce and I'm planning to
eat the rest with
with um
tonkatsu sauce I don't know if that fits
um
I only have tonkatsu sauce and
and some
uh mustard
if I had to choose between those I feel
like tonkatsu sauce will be better
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
religious holiday I think
you say it doesn't celebrate as a
holiday yeah we do we do we do I think
it's like a probably a Catholic holiday
or so I think
yeah yeah All Saints stay
um
why is Animal Crossing on the first uh
like what is it in the order in which
games got updated because I just had an
update but I don't even have Animal
Crossing installed why does it go first
place
why
is in my physical system
oh
oh that's one of the very few hey I
watched a video
oh
two years from the official release date
of the game
it's been not more than two years
definitely okay like I need to start
buying more games in physical versions
because
points and [\h__\h] and then with the points
I mean it's really honestly I don't know
if it's really worth it because you
really need to get a lot of points to
get anything good from it
but normally you know I do digital
because like I play so many games and
like I mix them up I don't play like one
game for one month I mix it up for the
purpose of a stream so
uh I need to get the games fast you know
and sometimes I don't plan a week ahead
sometimes I do more spontaneously
[Music]
but I get enough physical
although I would say if I guess space
like not not actual physical space but
only space on the on the switch
I guess but no physical space
I'm available
well it's a reference to
what's been happening in the game
in case you did not understand
did you understand if you watched
yesterday's stream then you understood
um
so I got iced tea I got water I got hot
tea see I'm back to these long streams
where I prepare a full [\h__\h] jug of
tea with honey and all that so that I'm
ready for the endurance
and snacks I got everything I got I got
Savory snacks I got sweet snacks I got
it all I got it all
right it has
with my chest area
[Laughter]
um
okay well sound is being [\h__\h] weird
and sound captured
am I sure but of course I am like
there's a there's a device in the game
that's called
reboot or so what was it me poop
baby poop
what what else could it was 100 V boob
right yeah
my memory would not fool me like that a
virtual bull that was I mean that's
pretty much it
[Laughter]
oh all We Believe
I'm taking my show where the [\h__\h] is the
logo didn't I place the logo here
yesterday
that's not it
go
oh it disappeared do you guys want full
screen
do you do you do you say
yeah
okay
okay if that's what you want
who am I to take that away from you is
it filling up the screen oh my God it is
unbelievable
I need to figure out what to put you
guys up
um the hashtags okay
[Music]
you
showed me that yesterday
story
for okay yesterday we played four hours
31 minutes
felt like more than that let's see how
far we got today
oh
it's not Halloween anymore guys how sad
oh Vivo okay well oopsie
[Music]
Okay so
okay well
I'm a people
yeah okay so
let's game again there we go need to
clean the popcorn popcorn is always you
know a big hassle after
uh a movie surely cleaning that [\h__\h] up
is not the most fun activity
ah oh I wonder oh yeah wait
I wonder if I get something special
oh
because we're still missing some of
those musical notes right
Maybe
hi
if I get rid of all of them do I get
something special probably not
hello
bring me the trumpet whatever that was
oh sorry [\h__\h] off ha
nothing special what's up with that
[Music]
where the musical notes
higher places
how do I get to the higher places hmm
well let me just let me just get rid of
them
all this
no
wow what's up
can you
go away
told [\h__\h] obnoxious man uh all right
I got rid of everything
um
[Music]
I feel like there must be a way of
getting what we need
oh yeah yeah
told you
it is
uh uh wait no it's it's not it's all
right no that's not right it's it's I
will not say what it is
you know what it is
well maybe in here or something no we
have something with the wigs no
maybe let's go
hmm
like something
oh
let's go
[Applause]
are you still here
oh get him get him
oh my God
he was in the way
wow that's slow motion oh
oh oh that felt so special but
I'm I was actually not looking for that
I was looking for
um
I was looking for like a musical note
but whatever I guess hmm
maybe I need to shoot toad somewhere
specific maybe the painting
no
let's go
ah okay
[Music]
yeah
what do these things do again
I swear
and now
look I just fixed the piano that's it
what
oh
[Music]
everything yeah
I mean I did
um
[Laughter]
could you guys get used to this hmm
I I did I did uh not get all of them yet
though right how many are we missing I
didn't look
behind the painting can I look behind
the video
well I think the one that's in this room
we already got so there probably won't
be more
oh yeah
where's your smile but I can cope I
could cases
I thought so
um
which one to clear this thing
why why
can I not just move on
you miss my face oh
[Music]
oh I
interesting interesting
[Music]
ah I do have eyes somewhere in my
resource folder
[Music]
wait oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's not a pnd
it's not a painting
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
this is how I feel
okay well look at my eyes my eyes are up
here guys
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
my window won't open anymore what's the
what's the shortcut to open a minimized
window that just does not want to open
anymore you guys truly know a solution
for that
I like clicked double and now it doesn't
want to open anymore I could play
through OBS I guess
out tab really
oh I'll stop
oh
wow
no
F4
for me
[Music]
Windows Windows button what's with the
Windows button
when and up
Windows and oh
it doesn't want to okay I'll just close
it once it's just a game capture it's
not like I'm closing the game itself
[Music]
oh I see there it comes
stupid game capture software
sure
pleasure okay
have we like checked everything in here
told is like so in the way
I think we checked everything in here
right
[Music]
my eyes
my eyes are
jpegboozled I thought it was gonna be a
PNG anyway whatever I'll need all the
musical notes
foreign
[Music]
but hey it's good that we came back to
this point where we did come to yeah
yeah because uh this way I got an extra
musical note that I didn't get last time
that's why you had a PNG for it
did I I I did it didn't die
yeah but it's okay this way we don't
need it
foreign
we've talked to you last time about this
but I guess we'll talk about it again
oh
[Music]
you've managed to find one of your
friends how many does that leave though
I see two toads and Princess Peach ah
I'm your big brother too he's still
captured also what about your face I I
feel like something's missing today do
we need to rescue your face as well
you're fine oh yeah I mean I guess yeah
you have your eyes that's all you really
need I suppose seems like there's a bit
more work to do wouldn't you say well
good luck
bye-bye
so where where are we supposed to go now
we got we got a button right
let's insert the button oh yeah
[Laughter]
oh
number six so oh yeah oh yeah so we go
to number six castle Mac fries what kind
of place is this
foreign
[Music]
I can't shoot up there though hmm
could have skipped straight to nine yeah
yeah surely if I turned it around I
could have gone to nine
that's how it works
oh
did you see the shock in my eyes guys
this is like a themed restaurant or
um
oh thank God they don't come to life
that would have been terrifying got one
more
[Music]
[Applause]
go get us go get him not in the fire
yeah
it's good that I'm playing this two days
in a row because this way I have all the
practice
didn't forget anything from yesterday
oh
bunny
can we do the oh
the carpet thing again no okay
suck
oh bunny
perception of depth
you know in German oh [\h__\h]
in German uh one thing one word to call
boobies boobies is uh
depth
um
uh plots like cooking pots you know
that's when I when I say depth I can't
really say that word so it feels like
I'm saying that
but like in Austrian dialect because we
say oh she has some nice uh uh that's
that's
I think I think that's what we say
Alex yeah like jugs I guess yeah yeah
is that not sauce to you there's like a
there's like a maybe maybe wait
foreign
that looks like something would stick to
that doesn't it
a duck like ah you guys are so smart
nope
nothing all right let's go oh
[Music]
what is this what is this place
more popcorn there's so much
entertainment in this
in this hotel damn I wonder why is it
not so popular
because people
people don't are not able to write good
reviews after they stayed here because
they're dead
oh
um
honestly in like Las Vegas
I feel like they would have some some
hotels like this right where they have
some really weird exaggerated
entertainment how do I get over there
probably with Queens you know
oh yes yes uh how do we get Luigi again
like this because there's isn't
it sounds like a
something I can get through eh but
there's a chest over there well anyway I
can definitely only go through here with
Luigi for now
but I can't get to the chest what's with
the chest oh no never mind
never mind I got it
I'm talking about this chest oh you guys
didn't even see it because my chest was
there oh
oh I stopped moving why is that
I got so many chests
nice
oh you don't see what I'm doing here at
all
okay how do we actually like how do we
get guiji
like completely disappear
is there like a way to do that
come on
maybe I just have to
walk over here once and then oh yeah
double tap oh yeah but okay see this is
also one way of doing it
and if we go behind here it's it's
awfully quiet here there's no music this
is awkward
[\h__\h]
do I have to hold it I'm I'm guessing I
have to hold it but wait
oh now the music starts
can I
yeah whatever
oh oopsie
sorry I'm back
[Applause]
[Music]
now
we need you
I like the Medieval music oh
foreign
[Music]
that has a lot of potential to be spooky
armor stuff in my vacuum cleaner
not realistic
oh oh oh hey there were some mice in
there and I immediately flashed them
nice
[Music]
what is that
greasy
and
cannot see okay
Kirby vacuum ah
I see maybe this yeah was like created
created after studying how Kirby sucks
things
oh interesting
and they took like I know part of
Kirby's DNA to create this vacuum
cleaner oh
damn
wow
[Music]
oh oh should I shoot something with this
oh
of course they are in there that makes a
lot of sense okay let me shoot the other
one too so
get to another chest do you see this
chest and this one this one you see
okay it does not want to break
wow wow
wow Mommy
what is going on here hmm trash can
hello hello are you alive sir let me
shoot you
hey wow
bullying the statues
you already had a nosebleed today
um
[Music]
I hit him with that what's his weapon in
the way let me let me let me let me let
me let me let me do it with this
hey no way I missed it he should be able
to be defeated right
I will not let this stand and have my
honor be
there we go
cannot escape the wrath of
Luigi and kiwawa
okay let's go down I guess I don't know
Gucci
no of course not
I can get
a plunger on top of uh Luigi
hey yo wait I'm supposed to do something
here but what is it because like I can't
get for any of the doors
um
oh
where is she
where did you see the poem up there hey
yeah my eyes are down here
oh wait how to make um
how to make
wait
um
please write something again
[Music]
say something
I want to make you
blue
there we go
now now right again one more one more
[Music]
mama
you've got the power wow
[Music]
nice to see you here wow you're up so
early respect
damn promo have you played this game
before I need to know
what I'm supposed to do right now
I can't open these
maybe I went for the wrong way
[Music]
maybe here I can go through
no
left door I mean in there okay not not
here but like oh
[Music]
Mommy Mommy okay that was
nice but not where
I needed to really go
that was some good big money though you
know
oh
[\h__\h] cutscene
unbelievable
yeah number one he got number one we
haven't been to number one before
really
oh
he's like come and get it all right all
right I'm into medieval Role Play Let's
Go
let's do it
I'll be ambulance
my favorite
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh wow what the [\h__\h] why is he so strong
there we go beautiful you called
earlier that's your best nights
I'm disappointed
I am disappointed can I take the knife
oh
not as like a shooty weapon I Wanna Get
rid of these boys though what do I shoot
at them
ah I should have thrown the ghosts at
these things
all right then and maybe they'll maybe
they'll hunt me later Crow
oh so many
oh
I got one more one more
foreign
why am I so terrified of these burps
they're like
Evil dark versions of verbs the crows no
no no
no no no
oh [\h__\h]
I thought I was getting a Golden Crown
like uh daenerys's brother
a Golden Crown for a king oh interesting
well well well if this isn't perfect for
our boy guiji
foreign
I guess I'm staying like this so forever
now guys
I don't see any problems with this
nice chest thank you
I should see that coming
baby if my eyes were a little bit higher
I would have I would have seen that
coming a little bit earlier
unfortunate
some damage must be taken sometimes to
learn and to become stronger
okay
ducky oh
is there wine in here
oh no tomatoes oh
oh a heart oh
I can get behind this is not a real
Barrel no it is okay but it does not
have a left wall
Barrel only has right side walls
it
thank you
he actually smoked me
what what are we doing here am I pulling
away from you
shit's laughing me oh for real
um
[Music]
but I guess that was quite like a
gentleman slapping me like
like how gentlemen fight right there was
a [\h__\h] golden golden boy
he's more important he's more important
[Music]
okay okay where's the other one
I see I see you you're right there now
you're in there
[Laughter]
thank you
he barely had any money with him
boys aren't money Lads yeah I just know
this there's no money
in the banana stand
what the [\h__\h] so disappointing
did I just take damage from slipping on
a banana
really
oh
okay let's continue
now that we're not being bothered
anymore
okay
[Music]
oh
a key to my heart
imagine yeah dying on the banana imagine
I had one HP left and I would die from
that
if anyone ever had that happen
accidentally to them by playing this
game then I feel very sorry for them
oh
[\h__\h] almost burnt my tongue that was hot
a door I guess so I was like wondering
why is there
oh
that's pretty fun this is the money boy
right he's not pooping
[Applause]
[Music]
don't let him go don't let him go
the money the gold Barrel
[Music]
ah there we go oh
very satisfying as always
huh
more that's the that's the money I just
lost yeah
well that seems to be it okay
okay
thanks for the hint guys
one more door
uh-huh
oh there's a there's a sword thingy up
there we need to get there oh
suddenly
Casper
how do I get up did I really
did these [\h__\h]
no
oh oh that's what what the key was for
that door okay I thought it was just a
normal door ah know if I want to go in
yet no
no
terrifying
I have a Dylan
all right there must be um
Michelle
oh
huh it looked like yeah I can go there
from here
okay that was hard to see without that
looking for The Gap
okay and is there something there no
no
I don't think I can go higher
you like my new face
thank you that's so flattering I'm happy
you like it
let's go
I did my best with the makeup today I
tried to
look a little bit fresh you know
yeah what the [\h__\h] yeah
all right
all right can go eat your Golder
like here
no
all right but she can go easily through
here
my mouth
well my mouth
um
don't don't don't you see him don't you
see it what is this stuff
oh
is that like wrong ones and and the
right ones
foreign
traps
by the way I made the music a bit louder
it felt quiet is it okay
or is it too loud now
oh
that was scripted all according to
keikaku
what the [\h__\h] is that Spider-Man
web spider
yeah Nani
oh
fire
can I take that fire
and
what
um I was thinking maybe I'm supposed to
burn them
the spider web here but oh wait a second
oh
I see I think I understand now
I am supposed to burn it but first like
this cannot shoot
cannot shoot fire
just by vacuum cleaning it I guess okay
okay
oh and then ah
but I'm wondering there was like another
door it wasn't there in the previous
room I feel like am I missing out on
something we'll just check it out later
foreign
number one of Luigi's Mansion oh
very medieval
a
[Music]
huh
what
oh wait
wow the music is
challenging
oh
[Music]
jab bring me this stuff thank you
oh
can we go together
I'm guessing not
I'm just gonna go with guiji in case
because maybe there's something I can
only do with him down here
or should I not
I can bring
Luigi
down here too no
and down we go
what happened what happened what do you
mean what happened
why are you guys so worried about me
it's just me
ow
[Applause]
hey poor collegiene you should not be
worried about me you should be worried
about Guinea
yeah I did was that just what was that
for
[Music]
me the money
all right do they keep on respawning
because I feel like oh they do
endless rat's bum
how to get that thing there
foreign
[Music]
do we really want to do that
no Luigi no no no
no
[Music]
I don't know I do not know maybe
a green she cannot use it
well let's just go to the oh
I can't well maybe I really needed to
um
go to the other room first
attack
ah okay let me try
[Music]
oh yeah
oh what is this
[\h__\h] rats
now the camera is so far what is this
hmm
okay Luigi come down please
I need your brains and I need to look at
this situation a little bit closer it's
a door oh
[\h__\h] rats okay
dangerous
dangerous we will send our best friend
oh
oh but there's water here
can I
can I oh God uh
what do we do about you guys what do we
know about you
[Music]
oh where's this come from
was that always there I didn't see it
oh
and no more
no more violence I have fought but this
is not falling down there's another one
okay
[Music]
what do you mean you can't see my face I
can see my face very clearly
[Music]
wow
foreign
[Music]
you think that's funny
you'll think that's funny
I have a head
so insulting
okay where where go next
can I fall down here oh yo
oh yeah
oh
paper boat
huh
interesting okay well I guess we saw
well we needed to see in this room
I don't see it
oh I'll see like an entrance to another
but you know what I will
use the
purple blue red light again
just in case
[Music]
okay no I don't see anything
I'm so rich now
am I
I guess
[Music]
wait so we got the key right on it did
we and what's happening
oh
[Music]
troublemakers
yeah you're just babies
no match for me
ister my sardo
the mice are a match for me
[Music]
[\h__\h] all right here we go we got the
key for the door
wow
oh
spin spin the thing on the wall wait
okay a fish
sword doesn't come down
can I spin something else
at this thing
what
[Music]
that one wait
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
thank you I was wondering about that one
I didn't see that oh
[Applause]
okay is the fish coming again no damn it
no more fish for me
oh
well but if I let it go yeah it opens
again well I mean for now we probably
just for looking around we just need one
of us here
[Music]
it's okay I'm more into chicken anyway
more of a chicken kind of person oh wow
let's see ah well now I understand
even though there's Gates
this is not a job for green jeans
that's a job for Luigi
[Music]
hello
oh
hey hey hey hey
I thought oh my God this was the end of
me
how much time do I have
foreign
[Music]
whoa
that was terrifying thank you Luigi for
saving Luigi's life
[Music]
terrifying oh the eyes
I don't know if I tell Kelly about these
eyes watching me she's gonna just rip
them out that would be nice
Callie will take care of it yeah did you
guys watch the the Halloween episode two
oh [\h__\h] why did I do that
um I don't know which pool I should do
it
rip rip what out the eyes of that thing
watching me
Michelle
what's this doing
oh
it do be a puzzle and I think I'm doing
it
not right
[\h__\h] wait okay I understand I understand
ah
first we get it like oh I don't know
[\h__\h]
I think it has to be in the same
position
like here okay and then
and then
no wait no
not quite
um
yeah wait so basically when I look up
and one is look down I think
all right
no way yes
oh God thank God
but I have to go with uh
I think
did you almost slip
can I go down with Gucci
oh I can't oh
easy comfy
yeah
um anyway about the Halloween thing
it's really cool I like that fauna was
in charge of a project like this seems
to be her thing I'm happy for her
I I honestly I didn't really know like
how how it would turn out like I got my
lines but with some
some low-key instructions
but I didn't see the art or anything
before or hear the others voices
so it's a bit difficult to like
you know adjust yourself when you have
nothing to adjust yourself to
um
yeah but Bae I think Bay did an
incredible job at sounding
like
she's like part of the story
Cali too Iris with me we were just kind
of like I don't know mood makers
so thankfully
just uh messing around a bit was good
enough I guess
oh what did that do
oh I don't trust this
[Music]
is
it's just Tomatoes what am I supposed to
these Tomatoes shoot though
the knights what
yeah me and Iris I was just doing iris's
hair while Bae was having a problem with
being watched and then Cali took care of
it very nice of her
very protective very yandere though
Kelly
terrifying absolutely terrifying I I'm
stuck
I'm stuck
[\h__\h]
I am stuck how did I get here when I got
stuck now
why am I stopped
stop wait I I know now how to do it
though
but I need to go
so glitch is gonna pull this thing
right
oh my God sorry
I thought I could like pull it with me
I guess maybe I have to suck it
expect that you know
okay
oh
oh oh oh it stops there okay uh
but there is ah
I was like
there's no cards here but we can we can
imagine
[Music]
imagination
brutal absolutely brutal
[Music]
blood there's only one left where are
you dude
so do you guys want to see my normal
face again
if you want to
yeah I know yeah
yeah yeah
all right I'm happy you say that wow
hi
do you remember this face
[Music]
my other face will haunt you at night
hello I'm back oh
okay it's hard to see where it's
actually going for but I think I'm right
in the middle of it
uh
give me give me the helmet no
go into place
I can't take this
oh
no more Bubba where's people
[Laughter]
[Music]
same person
just a different face you know
that hurts him too
yes
yo this wall is so sauce
hmm
oh
okay I think Luigi you have to come
now
okay
what's this
oh well
oh
this King
really like some to have some pictures
of himself around here huh
we're almost
[Music]
foreign
could it be that the the game kind of
speeds up with like boss fights after
you do the first piano dance
[Music]
because first we did a couple of floors
it took us like five hours to do to get
to one first proper boss
but we still have to rescue so many
friends and I wonder if it doesn't speed
up then how would that work but it seems
like that's what it's doing okay how do
we fight here
what do I do Olivia oh
he's coming for me oh
okay
um not sure maybe when the arrow follows
me it doesn't follow me though
um
[Music]
oh what do I do
holy [\h__\h]
oh
wait when he charges you can see the
there's like a Blanche spot
on his chest out 20.
[Applause]
oh
you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
game over
I thought when
I'm scared I'm scared to try it wait no
he doesn't yeah
[Music]
yeah I got bones to revive me but maybe
oh thank God
[Music]
I want the horsey tool s
yeah he stuck his head up but uh I still
didn't get him with the with the Flash
am I just supposed to like suck directly
oh that was only for like a tiny moment
though
plunged into the chest I wanted to do
that but that's also like a tiny moment
it's holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
no
no way
[Music]
Ash I need to get the heart
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
and I can think of my strategy okay he's
going for it
I think no he's going for this
oh
[Music]
no why
why let's get it
what
[Music]
I don't like this fight
okay what
ah
he's annoying as [\h__\h]
okay but I figured it out
fast
food
[Music]
okay come here come here
also okay
[Applause]
okay now now you whip out the horse
let's see what you got now oh okay
easy
hey what do you think about your cake
now
doesn't look so cool anymore now let's
see it yes
[Music]
don't worry you'll be deliberated
afterwards
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay the fight was um it took a while to
really get going
but eventually eventually we got it
[Music]
I have to say though yeah like I I tried
those things but just not in the right
moment I guess and then I was like okay
I guess that doesn't work
um okay
well we did it
[Music]
number one
time
[Music]
but it's okay oh can we like go over
there no okay okay
it's fine oh they left some tip money
thank you
[\h__\h] hello
[Music]
dude I like this music
a book will get a pretty good ending in
this game
look at my money oh this leads here oh
but wait was there no door here I guess
not
okay come with me
I'm going to
continue
[Music]
I feel like
I missed a lot of those secret swords
but oh well
my relatives oh yeah once again once
again
thank you Jello man
oh wait maybe if I get rid of all the
lights do I get something
nope
it turns on again magical fire
wait
the rooms are the grayed out I haven't
been to those yet how to
how do I
[Music]
have been here
light the fire ah are there any
oh I don't see like a
wait this one
can I take that off
maybe not lower is it lower floor I like
it light like
I think I tried that already
oh
what
I heard something there I think yeah
yeah oh
[Music]
we're summoning a knight
ow okay so you have a crown but no heads
to wear the crown so give it to me
ah okay I thought you know this is not
quite what I expected
but okay
at least one of those
let's go
go next go next
well next go next
uh
open the door please
oh [\h__\h] I'm like right behind it okay
sword Gem of the night sitting down uh
it's okay I mean what do we even get for
getting those gems nothing that I'm
really necessarily
[Music]
oh yeah
it's okay
cash oh yeah it's okay
oh yeah oh yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
a higher rank of completion yeah
I don't need no needs no names oh yeah
number one is
the grand Lobby yeah why did we get that
one we've been there before
oh
yum yum yum yum yum
I guess we'll go there anyway
they didn't have like a painting though
we couldn't save any toad or so hmm
let me take a set
that was a seven
Nana
oh
see I ride the seven always with like a
a line in the middle
I feel like that you know holy [\h__\h] look
at it you can understand it I would
think it was a one
and it's way more easy to see and
differentiate
if it has that minus in between but
um
I did that like that's how I wrote some
numbers before I've been from Japan
um
or somewhere else and like
someone looked at it and they were like
what is this I don't know this number
what is this supposed to mean I didn't
they didn't even see it as a number
I
I was surprised that some people don't
even recognize it when it has the line
there
isn't that weird
like what is this that's the thing I was
in Australia huh
no
that's definitely not just a thing in
Australia
oh yeah and there's two different ways
to write a four too yeah um
I write the open version usually
not the closed one
oh actually I'm curious now
I want to ask you guys let me do a poll
let me do a pull I'm gonna do a pull
um
uh
[Music]
what is this
huh
what is that
it's not even
huh
what's that q a but I can't are you guys
able to send in a question
how does this work
oh
how do I look at the questions
apparently there's like a list
somewhere how do I look at the list
[Laughter]
I I I I I I closed hyper chat but wait
now I'm curious I don't know take a look
at that
um
oh wow why do I look at this
I literally don't know where
foreign
I will be not answering your questions
but
can I do a normal yeah okay a normal
poll is possible do you write the seven
with the middle stroke or not
with without
now this is the real question asking
Google questions here
tell me tell me
[Music]
hmm
my question what was your question
oh
wow
it's quite 50 50 but more without yeah
I feel like it's more clear
with the stroke
um
foreign
[Music]
looks like a one if I do it
okay so without actually won that one
okay how about
[Laughter]
do you
ride your four uh for open at the top or
closed open closed
mm-hmm
that's the next question and then I
thought of one more
I have one more I have one more
um
I like the way the floor looks
but I do always write it open
valuable data yeah we're doing um
science
this is for science oh open gang open
gang is winning by far
that's interesting or how
mm-hmm okay last question
do you write your
Zeds
with a little strong or not
with no
none
um
only the small or big one
um or Capital One or
only when writing
um
in cursive
font or or or the other way around I
guess
okay
[Music]
set set
dead yeah dead
apparently it's not said like that you
say no I
I think I for me
the Capital One
I definitely always ride it with that
with a stroke if it's like the beginning
of a word I don't know actually hmm I
think
it depends I think for me it depends on
what mood I am in only the Capital One
um yeah maybe it is really only the
Capital One
[Music]
questions okay sorry sorry I've I felt
like a scientist
I wanted to do some science
very much
yay surprise speed up wow
Krista
one more flower here one more
oh
oh wait there's like a
um
I saw a trash can
or something like it
there there
it's in the room
sides baby
huh
oh so many flowers
is this the apocalypse floor or what's
going on here
where their very own Botanical Garden
but it's like supposed to look like the
Apocalypse
it's a cool look honestly honestly a
Botanical Garden like this would be
really cool
but if they make it so that it it really
looks like just a building that has been
abandoned
and turned into a beautiful
flower garden by Nature
just because it was better that would be
really cool what
what was that
Flats
use light on the flower
okie dokie
but only on those ones right
so far there's like
nothing going on here hmm
wait charge let go
[Music]
money raining down on me
oh oh all the [\h__\h] rats yeah
yeah got him
got him
okay and then okay door door time
hello
oh interesting
too easy
no no no no
it's not gonna be that easy
I will first walk around because I know
I can't just take it that easily can I
huh
nice
[Music]
um
mm-hmm
What if I
just go up first is that possible
don't go okay you're forcing me yeah
yeah okay priorities
eight
oh
oh you found back
give back
I need that
oh no stairs
[Music]
um I'm gonna get a heart attack trying
to climb those stairs
oh
slowly but surely 15 years later Luigi
Mario which is his full name eventually
reached the top however
he had several heart attacks while doing
so oh
thankfully he had enough dog bones to
revive himself each time
but now that he reached the top
because he had to buy so many dog bones
he's now [\h__\h] broke no no
no no ready
oh oh okay
pretty wow magical oh
oh
here we have a new oh
a new function
that's the first
wow
pineapples oh
sick
should we go here we have to I think oh
hello
oh pretty flower
we're over 19 900.
close again oh that's a pretty flower
I got myself a new plant by the way but
one of my older plants who have been
surviving for quite a long time
died
no not quite I I think they're still
Chad still
they're still transport to survive but
it's currently being like attacked by
some kind of
tiny tiny spider bug a red spider bug
it's called like spinman in German
and I I ordered
some
something that should get rid of it
but I hope it comes in time so I can
still save it because I really like that
plan hmm
I really liked that one
oh goity
seems like a death sentence no
no that is actually I had one plant you
know that was like really really dead at
some point but I revived it okay it
actually like I cut off
every single one of the leaves because
they were dry as [\h__\h] and like Beyond
life and and you know
so I actually ended up saving it my mom
was so delighted to see that yeah
was there money okay
so I think I should be able to save this
one too
no no no no no for real she was
delighted
yeah turning my thumb green yeah you
know I didn't notice like with this
plant oh I didn't know this fast enough
because like first I thought it was just
drying because of lack of water but then
I realized it was because of the um
those weird
bugs or insects yeah
so I'm a bit late with trying to rescue
it
but I will rescue
oh wait I could just open it normally
oh
[Music]
nah
why is it just empty
so yeah
yeah pray for my plant do that
what
okay
huh
oh I just have to get rid of all this
[\h__\h] okay
easy ah what do I see
ya
we can get over to oh yeah it's over 20
000. yeah
we're [\h__\h] Rich baby
yes yes we are
there we go
oh
you're getting high on those flowers
yeah
can't get enough of me
[Music]
[Applause]
what's going on I had him [\h__\h]
go away
oh
worst performance of takanashi kiwawa
today
[Music]
here we go
[Applause]
oh yeah
okay finally
where's performance so far
so many
flower pink flower petals uh
[Music]
see I think now my outfit is very
fitting today with the flowers in my
hair
is
[Music]
foreign
snake
dangerous snake
oh
that's for guiji oh
oh that's for me
what about this stuff
will that go away yeah okay okay
and that's where guiji comes out of oh
indeed
[Music]
makes me crab the Beauty and the
allergies ah you got allergies for like
flower stuff oh man
that's unfortunate I don't
I don't suffer of any of that thankfully
now
can I tell you a story one more I think
I didn't tell you that from yesterday uh
from the the karaoke I went to
[Music]
uh
oh some you know I told you that other
people would um put in songs and when I
I know the song I would also run to the
front to sing it right so
put in
a song that I thought I knew
I'm stuck
where the [\h__\h] am I stop
it was something with Rhapsody okay and
I thought that when they said it my mind
since it's an anime convention went
straight to aozona Rhapsody you know yay
[Music]
that's what I thought so the moment I
heard that I ran to the front
took a microphone got excited and
suddenly Bohemian Rhapsody starts
playing and I'm like oh well this is
embarrassing I am gonna just stay here I
guess
because it would be too embarrassing to
get to Club so I stayed and you know I
mean I've heard this song before so
I I tried my best to act as if all of
this was on purpose and I I totally knew
it was Bohemian Rhapsody and I sang it I
sang it together with like one or two
more people that were there in front
with me
see they were mostly carrying the song
while I was just acting as if I knew it
really well
man I thought it was gonna be hours
around the rap Studio I love that song I
mean Bohemian Rhapsody is cool too but
not what I expected
yeah maybe now I never sang it at
karaoke before in in like an archive
maybe now I'm ready for it next time
next time
I was one of the Bohemian Rhapsody remix
Time yeah
[Music]
apples
oh wow that's easy
well what are you gonna do about this
huh
am I supposed to wait there's a this
thing here
[Music]
supposed to walk in the park man can I
go no
why I want to
let me go
maybe from the other side
oh
I wonder if people noticed
that I thought it was gonna be a
different song
but I think the Acoustics were pretty
bad in general so
um
it was hard to hear
when several people were singing at the
same time it was hard to hear like who's
who's actually singing properly so I
think we could I think I kept up the
facade pretty well
I was just slightly bad at the song
that's it that's it
now some parts I was a pretty decent at
though like the parts that you hear all
the time
oh oh
I have to smack that toilet do I
yeah
okay water is dangerous for Luigi but
don't worry I got you
let's smack the sink too
or blacklighted no okay
oh or the bathtub
wow
and the sink
it's bathroom I feel sorry
I want a bathroom like this
what's up here what's what's what's up
with this
I feel like I should be able to get rid
of the leaves here maybe not
okay
wheel on bottom left by table
don't lift my table
um when we first have to fight something
's bathroom is this what it looks like
oh yeah oh yeah
where are you
where I am
[Music]
got him got him
Ah that's that was convenient
Nani oh
back
oh his friend woke up oh [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
oh wait he's oh [\h__\h] he's got all the
leaves oh
[Music]
um
[\h__\h] oh that's yeah bye
I'm gonna die I might die I might die
oh oh thank God thank god oh thank God
how many [\h__\h] leaves are you gonna
leave
[Music]
wake me up can't wake up Wake Me Up
Inside can't wake up
oh maybe oh blowing the [\h__\h] white
makes no sense
all right
oh
I need to get behind him
[Music]
a leaf blower not Leaf sucker but all
the other leaves I was able to suck
oh
foreign
[Music]
was working too
what
how do I get up there
[Music]
I have an idea
no
I was gonna hold on to it
[Music]
foreign
just brings it back
and sucking gets rid of it
[Music]
huh no
pushing in on the schedule
huh wait Boba why
what is that
foreign
[Music]
I'm doing a big confused
I don't know
I don't know but uh
that one's sparkling why is that so
sparkly
but anyway at least this path is open
now maybe maybe I couldn't do anything
there maybe it's like from outside
something I have to do
I did suspectly oh hello more pineapples
all right uh
out of here oh dear
oh
okay
thank God all the health man I need to
buy bones can I do it like uh without
coming to him wasn't there something
about that
I don't need anything I want to I want
to buy
it
lab
return to lab
but when I returned to this place do I
have to start from the bottom of the
floor
tissue
no
we'll see we'll see
ah
oh
takes you back to where you were that
would be nice because I feel like
maybe that really was that way I feel
like you may have mentioned that I know
I can get to him like from anywhere at
least
by the gold bone
that's all I really wanted oh look at
this on the top right oh he's so happy
that he's in a safe place now
foreign
[Music]
looks like it yeah wow easy
I'm so obsessed about that part down
there
[Music]
why is it so sparkly
maybe just stream Sparks a little bit
too much okay
[Music]
I jumped I literally jumped man
spooky game after all can't help it
it was to be expected I'm sure you guys
also get lots of jump scares in in this
game right right
yes you do
well yeah
why is this empty again
wait this is a different room right
oh
God can I oh
that is amazing
let's go
the bed what about the bed there's no
way
yeah you can see the springs
uh I wanna do this in a real hotel room
oh
a chance dropped from the sky
this is a good room can I take this
thing everywhere this would be very
useful I think against that huge plant
this this feels good
[Music]
oh look at this
is how it felt in GTA four five four
five four
to use the rail gun and stuff like that
oh
the power
can I get this one too
oh oh yeah oh yeah
let's do explore
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
yeah baby
oh I see something I feel like I saw
something
what about this oh
another door
it should have been possible in all
rooms at least on this floor
okay
[Music]
yeah okay let's see
can we go for these no not this okay but
what about this hole
is this only a lucky hole
you go there I go here can Luigi look no
what is this hole for I guess it's just
decoration from the aftermath
um
oh
[Music]
it's something oh
where are we going
okay and then
this one
slimy oh boy
nice coins ghetto
and just like that we're back up to uh
20 000. hmm
ICA
that's it that's it that's it
can we take this I wonder
my heart my heart
[Music]
um
I was like
okay okay okay
[Music]
for a moment I thought I was gonna like
Panic so hard and fail
no no no we're good we're good we're
good
oh can can we
can we think
the grass is back
can I
can I go with this no I don't think so
oh no
I need a smaller one maybe yeah to shoot
the bigger one oh [\h__\h] now
[Music]
I was gonna shoot the bigger ones well I
missed uh
what else can I shoot with
you know what I'll just do it like this
hey
and the big one doesn't work on the big
one too
[Music]
all right
let's go
oh hello
uh can we it's better to switch to him I
think
yeah yeah
oh yeah right this game you can play uh
in in Co-op right local co-op and
someone can play guichi right
[Music]
and no one else is here to play with so
sad yes oh yes
huh
very sad this one there
I feel like
there's more to this room
[Music]
foreign
okay I need to check
in the cracks of my walls
if there are some golden spiders in real
life Wow
maybe in Australia is this like a thing
in Australia that I
did not know well
any Australians in the chat where you at
Aussie Bros
where you at
ask Bae oh
I I did ask her about the snack box and
she said it arrived like yesterday
so uh it's uh will be reviewed soon I'm
so glad
about you know it was lost or something
or or the Austrian Australian Customs
just straight up said no no no thank you
but
oh
my God
well
yeah I think
um when she reviews it
I will be there too
that's my plan yeah we talked about what
time works best so
I'll be there to explain the snacks and
um oh a rubber duck but we're done
come here no
hmm
snack lore
yeah I'm excited to see her reactions
and see what she thinks of it because to
me most of those snacks are really
really really really delicious
I love them
Rabbi Subaru
calling her baymore since the Halloween
episode well I mean the Halloween
episodes the the Halloween thing
scripted so if I said Bay in there then
that's because it was scripted
huh
and I'm like
move this
yeah
did I just surprise myself
did you recover yeah oh there you go I'm
not sure if our eyes were taken I think
it was just the the audience's eyes
don't you think
or did you guys interpret it the that's
as Cali also took mine and iris's eyes
[Music]
I did not I was not aware of that
well that's um
sheesh I have to have a talk with Kelly
[Music]
oh
yeah okay
nice nice
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] Birds
I'm gonna get you I'm Gonna Get You
yeah
oh
sad
well your controls wow oh chest up there
interesting room
[Music]
all right we're going in I don't know
why we were able to look through it
first
that's why
oh I'm glitch you can't go through that
right
[Music]
maybe I can roll something down really
something heavy
oh
black light oh apparently you can just
skip that room
oh
I'm not gonna skip it though I want to
go inside anyway
oh
I see a flower Crystal thing here oh did
I just start the boss fight
oh yeah
oh
no never mind that's how it happens ah
oh well thank you okay so that was
necessary thank you thankfully we didn't
waste uh endless amounts of time on
figuring out how to open this
okay
um interesting
[Music]
bounce cute
finally Luigi can jump like properly
that's a skill dad
I was waiting for it
can we get much higher
yes we can I'm sure of surely of surely
we can
but what about
I would say we move this thing
oh yeah I guess it only moves there
I thought I could move it to the other
side
uh-huh
I like the glowy things here it's pretty
thanks
that's the room that we were looking at
from
in that cutscene
oh oh
froggy Wawa is real one piece is real
good
guys
everything is real if you want it to be
imagine
can we get in there
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
big money on the floor right there
I'll just leave let's get that one and
now people should be able to enter right
or leave
and so now we can leave
uh here I am again with the puns
yesterday I was even better at that um
I didn't even see the snake
I thought it was just like a spider
running around oh oh [\h__\h] I fell down
okay
[Music]
wow
that is way now there's a hole there
right there
[Music]
oh
I heard wait
I was I was like
a ghost and now I understand why this
thing is swinging constantly
how do I wake this ghost up
oh
okay
anyway
one second
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah okay I guess that's okay
huh
was that all all for Gucci
hmm
bye-bye
[Music]
ah I have to be above
I think so above him
that would be weird if that's the only
way to do it but okay I'll try
let's just try to leave he'll probably
wake up when we leave or so and then be
like surprised you can't leave oh
huh no he was not doing that
we'll figure it out or maybe the answer
will be given to us right away
see now I can't go back because doggo
does not want me to go back
yeah do you like this game yes I do very
much
it's my kind of game
wow that was close
like I have trouble playing a lot of
other Mario games
but this one
is is like on my level
beautiful
nice nice nice
okay wait ah how do I get there
how do I get over there
oh
can I swim there swing there no I can
only swing sideways
[Music]
maybe I'll figure it out later after the
boss is defeated
excuse me can I have a thing
I see her we're gonna open it by
probably
sucking from both sides
[Music]
I saw the windows yeah yeah there's
money there no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
damn
why so clumsy
[Music]
oops where is it now now here comes the
fight against the gardener right oh I
should not take the hearts now
[Applause]
don't eat me I'm green so I'm a plant
just like you you want me to believe me
eat eat Mario
oh
[Applause]
okay I see so when it does that I
probably have to like cut it
oh
out
[Applause]
well maybe there's more to it oh right
now okay
okay trying to stop that blunt I'll be
too late probably will I oh no there we
go not too late they give me a lot of
time
okay that's that's pretty easy
oh
that's manageable and while he goes
looking for it
I don't see this
is
much easier than or not easier but like
faster to recognize what's what I need
to do
supposed to
[Music]
eat
here
yeah
no no no no no no no no no
how did I get him to eat that though
[Applause]
maybe I stand here hello I'm here
hey
[Music]
okay okay here we go here we go here we
go here we go here we go here we go why
am I running around the ghost I can
probably run through the ghosts
thank you
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
okay one more probably
we're doing now same thing
not changing your pattern okay okay fine
with me
yeah I'm here I'm here come sniff me
sniff me
yeah faster
ice
[Music]
balance for lunch
love veggies
thank you fauna
thank you very much for this
sponsored lunch Danke Schoen
another boss has been defeated
this bus was really easy yeah cause like
I even like a few times many times I I
got hit by the by his plan but it didn't
do any damage
so it feels like it's very hard to die
in this fight
what is this for
um
can I use this for something
here
yeah
more do you need more
oh there we go
ah you're helping me reach this thing
thank you that was actually necessary
[Music]
okay now I wanna eat the one of my one
of my
um spring rolls
I think
they gave me like
um
[Music]
Seafood Spring Rolls I don't know
somehow it tastes like it but they're
okay
she's gonna eat one don't worry
[Music]
oh
Victory spring roll yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh wow
now I make tea
cup number two
[Music]
it's been
a half hours and this is just my second
tea cup
what's up with Dad
[Music]
I guess there's not so much dialogue
this time so
oh
there's lots to talk and therefore my
voice
dies slowly only slowly for sure
oh this joke is so heavy
my arms are such noodle arms man
[Music]
I always like this Victory music that
you get after defeating a boss is happy
music
[Music]
actually I want one more Victory World
but this one I have to eat now I'm
really out of um the proper sauce I have
to eat a little tonkatsu sauce let me
try
I think it should be you all right
[Music]
is like something you normally eat with
um
tonkatsu so if this is really Seafood
will it really fit
it's all right hmm
now I feel like I'm eating tonkatsu
h
[Music]
it tastes like chocolate
it tastes like tonkatsu because my brain
is so wired to tonkatsu when I when I
have the flavor of the tonkatsu in my
mouth the tonkatsu the sauce yeah
come on
[Music]
[Applause]
no
mm-hmm
oh yeah let's go traditional job
[Music]
so wait before we go
there's several things here Dad
um
we need to take a close look at
combining now
[Music]
that was so dramatic to the music
okay
[Laughter]
surprised this is the first time that
happened
[Music]
oh no get me back
to the music
more Victory music
oh how do we get to where that money was
outside I wonder
that's not the only thing
I wanted to look at so
in my mind
uh
it's a bit annoying that I have to run
through all the rooms again
oh man
[Music]
left side of the plant
at the bottom you mean
wait wait wait so uh I think above
above there is where the crystal was but
my nose is running
my nose running
oh God uh oh
well that's new
that is new okay
um but it's not really
glitching out
um
not so amazing unless there's still
something more to this
no
or does that lead me to a room
no I think that was that but hey we
didn't go here before so okay cool
yeah
going captain
ah funny
uh
ah another flower up there
huh
sassy flower okay
still have to get higher yeah
[Music]
almost there I think
cat hairs do that no it's not because of
the cat hairs
aha
I have to go through here again as well
okay that still doesn't work
High
eh
why do I have to do all of this again
also what was that
what was that
oh
I love the flowers on your hair thank
you
they're very fitting right now to where
we are in the game I would say
that was all planned I totally knew that
we were gonna come here
I thought the way this was not the red
space
plot space slots
what about this door
can I open this door
platforming Luigi
so
[Music]
um
hey
[Music]
I died I went to
towards the camera
rigged
okay what about this ghost
what
did I know your name
[Music]
I I wanna know how do I get this ghost
to wake up
Maybe
maybe if we shake it like this
[Music]
no more sleepy time you lazy ass ghost
okay
[Music]
and shattering slow motion
oh yeah
[Music]
okay that brought in a good amount of
money
and was very satisfying to finish off
nice yoga Tana
okay so my job here is done I think
I was just chilling yeah
yeah all the ghosts here are evil we
have to take care of all of them cannot
let a single one Escape
oh you know what that over there
how
[Laughter]
there must be a secret path here oh
girl can be on the first but oh when I
was thinking from there but maybe not
necessarily
maybe I could just suck it we
yeah from the big flower okay okay
I was thinking I have to find a secret
path no okay
okay
I'll show two things
the
Jewel
how do I get the jewel then
wait wait
that looks like bones
like uh
backbones of someone
I'm guessing it's connected to another
room that leads outside where all the
other money is oh almost fell down
on it
[Music]
uh-huh
yes yes yes
this is how you go outside
get those coins and
um
yay
oh and can we go forever no
well what about uh
I guess that's just a different floor
right the the the rooms on the map that
look like
um
you know a little bit grayed out I guess
that's just
uh I'm from a different store okay okay
then I think we're done here pretty much
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's not scared of height anymore
I guess so
my job here is done
nice oh
um then where's the elevator around here
but you didn't do anything that's
that's true
I know you're trying to be funny and
mean but I definitely did a lot here and
I want the credit for it credit where
credit is due
hmm
all right
I wonder how far we are in terms of like
percentage in the game like how much
more hours
can anyone like
you
oh yeah does someone know is there like
uh you know when I look up like how long
is this game it gives me the length of
games but can I also like like input
like a chapter and it tells me
how far I am in the game
two more hours
and one third done 60 done hi
Hi friend
eight more floors one six seven eight
yeah I guess so
but there might be like shorter floors
and longer floors so I'm not sure how
how that how much that really means
um foreign
well we'll definitely play a little bit
more like one or two or three hours
one third for full collectible but maybe
two thirds were just a playful okay
interesting
um I didn't did I not press anything
where are we going we got eight right
paranormal Productions
[Music]
no I think I don't know we could until
refinish it today
I don't know if I were to finish it
today how much longer would it take what
do you think
roughly
I I kind of want to cook later so I
don't think I want to go too long
freaking hours four to five hours
okay in theory I could do it but I don't
think I will force it but then the next
episode will be so short ah
well then let's try to go I guess for a
little bit more completion
content from this game
oh
well this looks like a small floor from
the map that I saw
I wonder is this like a museum like a
what
Museum
foreign
yet because I feel like
wait the key is right there
help
oh
wow give me the key wow
foreign
[Music]
maybe not yet
oh
that is like um the strikers League
whatever soccer game from Mario right I
played that when I was younger I think
on the GameCube
that's probably just an Evolution's
Mansion game that is also
also the soccer game no
I think so there's Donkey Kong and so on
and the logo looks like it my wrist
track is right
this is absolutely unrelated I think
right what that never seen these
characters before
doesn't look like Mario what is this
punch out
what is that
Nintendo
let me look it up
[Music]
huh
punch out
why did why is that here
Little Mac is in Smash Bros what is that
hey here we go same deaths
n-e-s Punch Out Mike Tyson's puncher
what Super Punch Out doc Lewis is punch
out oh there's a couple of these games
they're really old
same devs okay so these are all
um or some of the games that these devs
worked on okay
um
these depths specifically and what is
this on the left side
it looks like Gengar from Pokemon
somehow like a really dark scary poster
I know
I should play Punch Out
oh what what is that
uh it does you agree
I mean it has a lot of spikes at the top
it's weird there's definitely
some reference to it
surprise there's no one who knows it for
sure
Mario is the referee in punch out
really
probably Bowser
hmm I want to look it up if someone like
finds out they're the real
you know reference let me know also on
it
this one looks like I can open it
wait
[Music]
nice
hair here I'm playing punch out right
now are the other one's openable I don't
think so yeah I only saw the the clips
on the side
foreign
[Music]
oh was this necessary hey it came back
did it spawn there because I didn't I
was not watching
foreign
I don't think it's working maybe we need
a key for the key
keyception
oh
what is that what is that some penguin
what game is that
and the fourth one what's is that is it
a Mario game about feet
we need to learn more oh oh
that didn't go very far I think
just generic picks oh yeah I guess they
could also do the original mix
[Music]
okay
oh
secret openings oh
Luigi can go there
[Applause]
okay one out of six
let's try to find
couple more so we can get some more
content as I said hey
[Music]
I heard feet
you came at the right time against no
you actually missed the V boo bird the
legendary reboot takanasiki booger
yeah you missed out big time
[Music]
I'm curious I don't want to move on too
fast no I'm not
I'm not even halfway for the game
really
actually scream so much
I'm in shock
okay well then let's move on but do I
not need the key
that's what I thought huh
baby wait so I let the electricity go
but it didn't go very far
foreign
is this a bug what's going on with the
ropes
what is this
are you guys okay are the ropes okay
calm down
see now they're chill
oh
okay the physics here a little bit
confused
oh thank you
I'm missing something there maybe
this helicopter maybe I need to yeah
yeah yeah yeah
there's something here
oh
so does not give me the key but
but get a little special something
and now
not enough
oh wait maybe just
oh no so matted
can guiji go into the TV well he can't
even step up there that's the thing
[Music]
if only we could just lift our goddamn
leg
bye
it's something to do with the cable I
think with the electricity
so let me take a look at that
or maybe we just do it stronger
and then it will go further oh no never
mind
oh
little nightmares
TVs are evil did you not watch My Stream
Luigi
no don't go inside
[Music]
never mind maybe it was good
I guess this is a different kind of
world
um
look at the physics from the Ralph
ah okay
all right
now oh yeah I know it was something with
the TV and the cable but I guess it was
not the cable it was just I powered it I
guess by doing that
and connected it there we go
okay
[Music]
is this um
is this are you also in the midlife
crisis trying to make a movie like a
certain someone
director of the finest films I'm
destined for how could I lose it I'm a
puny worthless movie director that's all
even the Sparkle from this beautiful
button turn this down nothing but adult
shoe
Luigi it's got a feeling for him oh
bright red megaphone where are those
I would give anything to be able to hold
my dear sweet megaphone again
megaphone
all right we'll find it
but I have a feeling he won't be any any
more thankful and grateful
not just easily
give me what I want
ooh bunny carpet
huh
foreign
did I take it okay
can we destroy the gorilla
really
you oh my God
this is why I'm a cat lady you little
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you almost killed me
ah money you think I'll forgive you
because you give me all that money
oh [\h__\h] baby style
oh
Bubba poor Bubba
Bubba oh
movie sets
okay somewhere in the movie sets maybe
there's the red megaphone but of course
it's not gonna be the first one we enter
um
wow
dramatic but nothing's going on
we need some some actors
wow oh
that was it like for the room like
basically just had to turn the TV on
wait a second
I mean that might have really just been
all I needed to do but uh I will
go through and clean up a little bit
a multi-room puzzle
[Music]
diet Diamonds and Pearls
are a Luigi's best friend and yo what's
up with all that money down there
hello hello Keep It Coming yeah
what
oh wait can I just
I can't go in here huh
now I can oh can I
um
no I can
I can't see anything though but I guess
I already took all the money that was in
here mostly
okay
are there like stairs
well
no
so I'm guessing I can't reach the top
uh-huh
y'all
okay so yeah it really seems like the
only thing that was necessary for now
was turning on the
TV
oh God
yeah yeah
I know megaphone but I I look anyway
foreign
this is what I came here for right
Mario is the plumber and Luigi is the
the cleaner wait what is actually is is
he also just a plumber like as an
official job description
because I guess he wears the same kind
of clothes and all that
but judging by Luigi's mansion He seems
more like uh
in charge of the cleaning
after the plumbing
they're both just plumbers okay
I think I think he kind of changed his
career path though
okay
all right can I can I do something with
the light
surely I can
how can I know
we never do see Mario Plumbing
he does go
like part of his job
Luigi
I think we're good
okay let's go to the room next here
oh
[Music]
spooky and spooky music is a spooky set
oh
[Music]
pumpkin happy Halloween
pumpkin soup you know what I want to eat
pumpkin soup tonight
I got myself some pumpkin soup powder
which of course just not as good as like
the real deal the fresh
stuff but oh well
I should go to restaurants more but I
know when I'm alone I just don't
feel like it's
going to the restaurant alone in Japan I
did that all the time
but in in Austria I never do that I feel
in Japan I feel more more comfortable
with going alone I don't know why
well
together
what if we throw the ball into the well
can't
I must
more commented to go alone
I think so I think in Japan a lot of
people go eating alone after work or so
hmm
so
[Music]
um
only rarely do I get to go with friends
to a restaurant because like everyone's
busy everyone's so tasty although
recently
um an old work colleague
was like contacting me because she wants
first of all she loves my cats and wants
to see my cats again she used to take
care of my cats like a little bit
and uh and she actually is a like
kind of interested in Japan too but
she's not like a very obvious and open
weave Like Me Maybe
[Music]
um
yeah and she she said that she wants to
go to Japan maybe like me with a working
holiday Visa
so
she wants to meet up
at a cafe to talk about stuff and get my
advice and stuff I'm like okay I guess
yeah sure why not
I I need to get out more anyway
yeah
oh water
what does this do oh
ah smoke machine
or some money that's why it was not
working it was all jammed in there
yeah I got experience but I'm not sure
what I'm supposed to tell her
no I think actually no she might have
she might just want to go for
um tourism steak
I guess I can tell her some places but I
don't think I can tell her something
like much more interesting than what you
can find on Google
uh
in terms of where to go
also I haven't really
partaken
interesting activities much
while I was living in uh Japan
at least
most of the time
I've seen some places but also kind of
lacking I kind of want to see more too
but next time I'm in Japan I wanna make
use of the time and go do some touristic
stuff yeah because did you see did you
see on Senpai I saw her tweet she's like
uh tweeting from fujisan Fuji mountain
never been to fujisan I only saw fujisan
from a distance
but looks
really beautiful
really exhausting though I think
probably
oh dear oh dear you're a big spider
I can drive up Midway you mean with the
uh
that despite it will be gone probably
when I go back huh almost there
oh
Santa
[Music]
coin okay wait so what I can
I can um
oh wait ah Luigi
you do the thing and I go up I think
unless I hope it doesn't have to be the
other way around
a hollow hiking trip to Mount Fuji oh
that sounds kind of a [\h__\h]
sounds fun
I fell down of course I did
did
oh he didn't take any damage from that
be careful be careful be careful oh
there's a oh God
a tape over there okay
oh oh that helps a little bit I guess
[Music]
but that's really difficult to
like see where you are
oh man
can we get it on the next try
okay
um
ah
[Music]
a
turn
oh God
am I in the middle
what now
oh
okay okay that's all I need up here
right hopefully
I think so going down
you can stop now
okay but it's an ice cube was there like
fire somewhere
I didn't break from the fall
oh
maybe the the heat from my light skin
melted
no
oh I'll think about that later
yeah there's a gem inside I want that
I wanted that away oh tell me why ain't
nothing done now tell me
[Music]
foreign
looks like you know it's supposed to
film some mice or something oh wait
there is the microphone trapped in some
spider Libs
shouldn't be too much of a problem but
can we like become small
and get that
tape please thank you
a sound
hello hello
yeah Gucci to be honest we could just
stay there I don't care no
no
this is the money
what do you mean
make yourself than that before I think
oh there we go there we go
what about the coins though do they not
work
I think they don't all right
let us think the hammer can I use them
big ass hammer
Maybe
or
hmm
no wait I can probably just plunge it
give me a second I'm just I'm just you
know
we shall trying to clean up a little bit
first
[Music]
movie
oh was I supposed to be there with guiji
and oh there will be a big spider
[Music]
that is that is a good movie man oh God
it's alive is it what is
oh
[Music]
I thought it was alive
because things like also even really
dangerous music playing
hmm we're good
oh
huh
oh do I need help from Mario
on it camera
why is it closed
can I only open it when I'm in the movie
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
hammer no
so I'm guessing I actually can't
do anything here
right now I'm missing something oh
okay
not late
now to wait
not who don't
oh we turned on the TV
we have one more room to check anyway so
so [\h__\h] spiders
[Music]
the ice ain't melting yet though
oh
a little city Village
movie set okay
[Music]
let's turn on the TV
fire extinguisher I need not a fire
extinguisher I need the opposite for my
ice cube
I don't think
the fire extinguisher helps and I
probably couldn't even bring it to the
other room it might be so in the same
room
what is that
what
are you are you a child ghost
because you're chilling in the basket
you're so small baby ghost I'm sorry to
hurt you I'm sorry
that's the first goals we find in the
sets I wonder are there no other ghosts
hidden in the other
sets up
wait if we cast the one in the Ice Cube
then we only have one more left in this
in this uh floor that's actually the
furthest we ever got and with the extras
hey yo
thing
let me explore first before going back
first we're looking everyone properly
[Music]
[\h__\h] ouch what to do and in what order
and
how to solve this riddle
oh
it was an ET reference but The Ghost and
the in the bicycle
I never watched that
is
let's see
what's with this
can I open the door
no wait
oh
I can't but I will not be able to look
at what's inside there's some money here
though
um
okay
the bike scene is Iconic
oh
I'm going to go through here
sorry guys I think I'm a bit more boring
than yesterday
you talked so much yesterday now today
I'm not that talkative it seems
I'm just chilling but I'm having a good
time
with the game
it's okay
you've been really cute today oh
there were bubbles here last time I
stepped on it but why
why were there bubbles
um
thank you chat thank you
okay
yeah
fire extinguishers why
okay did I turn this on yet there you go
oh see I didn't do that in the other two
sets oh
I have to connect the movies by doing
something there but hmm
oh
quit I can't move with Luigi for some
reason
I can move oh oh the helmets
no stop no
can we do the other way around
did I have to do this with Luigi because
that seems kind of
um
difficult oh
[Music]
I have to be clingy oh there we go
oh [\h__\h] one more
yes yes
[Applause]
can lose his hat too come on yes yes oh
surprise
[Music]
squeegee the best Ghostbuster ever to be
alive
wait let me get the money
[Music]
okay invisible
what you gonna do
oh
got him
how does it feel to be the ground
pounded one yeah
[Music]
come at me bro
come at me
you're almost dead
I mean I guess you're a ghost so you're
already dead but now you're really dead
this movie seems to be done
right
give me that give me that
oh
it's still burning though is nobody
gonna like take care of that
I'll bring the Ice Cube here can I
[Music]
it would be nice if I could
but it's not burning anymore if I go
back into the movie do I have to fight
again
Alicia how to bring
Ice Cube
can't
is there a different way to enter that
set
through the ceiling
ah teleport are you Ryan
uh this one
ah
this way I can take it but the other way
I can't hmm
I don't know what to think about that
okay I guess Luigi has to do that
lookie looking
oh
God
oh well it killed me too but
air
nice
I think
well another one must be in one of the
movie sets also
ah
the lights are on on the ones I haven't
solved yet is that the thing because the
blue one is not
um glowing
and the blue one feels like I really
like finished it
let's see
over there
and let's see what happens
ah see I was looking for nothing was
happening probably because Luigi was not
on the set
oh
Game of Thrones after green tea
oh oh [\h__\h]
where are the enemies
I have to go up there
am I missing something for this to
actually work properly
you need water
[Music]
um
well let me let me look into this one
a lot of bucket oh yeah
[Music]
but what do I need water for oh
mm-hmm
attack
and uh a paper boat
okay but oh was that was the bucket in
the other room
it's a soccer ball here can that help me
I wonder
anything here that
seems helpful maybe the mask I don't
know
oh yeah [\h__\h] I forgot to shoot the
camera
Windows Movie Maker
starting right
action
huh what are you doing action
oh spooky oh that looks completely
different wow the filters are on
um
look
don't fall into the water you'll die
don't jump
okay let's fight oh
she wants something
what does she want
something I don't have I guess
maybe the soccer ball
the other duck we did see we did see a
duck come
um
okay
so she's a duck collector
where was the duck or was it just in
this big room
oh wait I think what's it in here I
might be wrong
take a bucket of water
and what she wants to duck
oh okay
bucket in the director room oh okay
bucket
ah okay okay
why does she want the bucket
is that here
take this
I'll turn on the movie Guinea and you do
your best I I
believe in you
I know you can do it
surprise
[Applause]
shocking like the first time I saw you
bucket
is this what you want
nope
what
about
hey
I don't think bucket before the ghost
really
but that's lame
I don't know
because then she lifts it up and there's
water inside I guess
[Music]
it's so scary
thank you
uh
uh we we got it we're doing bring this
to apparently
um
apparently
to the
The Game of Thrones room
don't worry dude I'll make your movies a
big success
we've got Hollywood at Hollywood
Hollywood actors here like literally
Mario is being being acted by Chris
Pratt which is acted by me but that to
me means that
it's a Hollywood movie
Hollywood movie
when is the Hollywood movie Hollywood
movie is that Mario will be a Hollywood
movie
wait wrong room maybe I don't know I
hope oh
I hope it belongs here
being made in Hollywood
but it's it's animated can an animated
movie ever be made in Hollywood
oh oh [\h__\h]
don't attack me
what it's made I guess okay an animation
studio in in Hollywood
come back
I'll go up first whatever I don't know
which one is more important
oh
Mommy
is this part important for the movie
because I guess there's fire yeah but
it's by the web okay let me fight you
guys first thank you for waiting for me
yourself
where are you going
helmet for safety but it's not really
helping you stay safe is it
maybe you should rethink that a little
bit
maybe it's safer to not get close to
Gucci at all
where are you where are you huh you're
scared you're spooked by Guinea
you're not in the frame
come in here
ah these amateur actors I swear
[Applause]
it's just a side character I guess it's
okay
okay so well
It's Not Over
no this is just I guess the constant
state of this movie set I guess
okay
I think I know what to do because the
fire is out now but I have to bring it
down in order you know it has to
be turned off in order to bring it down
but probably I bring it to the fire set
turn on the fire and then bring it to
the spider set
right
foreign
[Music]
I wish it was burning already now like
a bit annoying that I have to turn on
the movie first but okay
oh my soul
door is gonna explode it's middle door
is going to explode don't be surprised
there we go oh [\h__\h]
you died for a good cause
I don't always have to suck it huh
okay
keep on burning keep on burning
thank you
now we go here this land and then we
should be open
but since we got a five out of six
um
of the rewards I really want to get the
sixth one so I will not leave this floor
without getting that one
okay
don't turn off the light please
oh my God
it burnt the spider just by having that
thing lying on the ground there easy
speed run
oh [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] are we still doing this
oh [\h__\h]
did I [\h__\h] it up
what if I isn't it free already
[\h__\h] I can only do it in the movie
that was by accident
but oh [\h__\h] see the spider is not here
anymore then I wonder what was banging
against the
the wall of the box
was that
[Music]
was that I wonder
here we go we got it I hope he's happy
about it
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
right there
I didn't notice until now but your face
you have some nice features
and your bills not bad not like that
tiny red plumber that I've seen before
I sent him home when he came to the
audition right away
all right you have the little special
something oh yes you're looking good
that green is beautiful on you I see all
the baking Superstars ah my creativity
is shaking up all the dust in church in
July
come come let's start shooting where's
my crew places everyone take you places
Godzilla oh
because I'm being okay I'm not that big
can I get much bigger oh [\h__\h]
happens Luigi
can you believe him oh
foreign
[Music]
not very convincing oh that one's
convincing
no I'm confident
[Music]
all right interesting
obviously that doesn't work does it
oh
fire oh oh [\h__\h] give me that
oh my God
can I push you into the water is that
what we're doing oh no he doesn't care
about that huh
[Music]
all right
I see I see I see
oh
there we go
[Music]
excellent X let's keep it up yeah yeah
what choice do I have he's legit trying
to kill me
I'm gonna slip on the [\h__\h] guys
oh oh oh it's green oh
holy [\h__\h] he's strong
oh my God
okay
what what did I do wrong
absolutely [\h__\h] 40 damage and don't you
wow
[Music]
I don't know
it's not funny you little [\h__\h]
I'm dying here you think that's funny
okay okay let's be more careful
okay here we go
[Music]
I can't I'm not strong enough
go go
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
hey y'all
just taking ridiculous amount of time
I don't wanna be
[Music]
wanna be a kid
I don't want to
[Music]
go here
I'm gonna go for Gucci oh man poor Luigi
okay
yeah wow it's much faster now but now
he's starting to work against me oh yeah
basically
oh that Panda controller would have been
even more helpful here probably
hell yeah
this is our this is I guess
it's still art
are you at the castle
ah he's happy is that the last piece of
um
is it the last collectible maybe inside
inside that it has the same shape please
no no I don't want that I want the last
collectible
[Music]
please please please please please
oh maybe in there
huh
maybe he'll give it to me there
is a K-Pop song that's like some called
something like that number nine
a very old one though
good job Luigi thanks for the help man
you've been doing a great job
do you know the song
foreign
[Music]
oh hello I never entered this room
before wasn't it was I able to enter
before
he's so motivated
[Music]
wow he won't mind right
holy [\h__\h]
there's an evil evil owl on the on the
on that board in front of him
cute
give me that give me that
one more one more
I [\h__\h] up
oh yeah
[Music]
just one one US dollar not worth it
mama's baby picture
um embarrassing yeah oh
okay dude tell me where is my last
special collectible thing tell me
no I can never rest otherwise I helped
you you helped me please
[Music]
I know you already gave me something
not in that room
okay
okay so like he's just chilling here huh
talk to him maybe my thumb is almost
complete Almost Do Not Disturb me now to
editing process requires my absolute
intention okay
I got that phone on the wall wow so
professional okay
where is the last one
don't catch this ghost why
I mean that wasn't possible anyway
um
bad ending
we dodged a bullet really
sure
you don't need to catch him if you're
looking you'll be able to see the
complete movie at the end of the game
cool
there'll be an empty space Oh I don't
care about that that's okay I don't care
more about the movie then
somebody said throw this into the well
so
that's what I'm trying
is this really how I get it just drop it
oh I don't know how to drop things
I thought you just drop it
I can only throw it
the bucket I didn't throw it I pushed
the same button but I didn't throw it
just because it was too heavy I think
this thing will just fly off
only in the movie uh okay wow
I'll try in the movie then
um
wait the camera is going it's gone
though I can't
uh make the movie
yeah I can't I can't drop it is this
really how I get the last tape
maybe fermented
[Music]
if this is
all I need to do then it is really
difficult to get this tape what the hell
oh
man
try jumping
what what do you mean try jump oh
it's in no
well well
well well is it too late
for something else
maybe something here though
there's nothing really here
oh
yeah camera didn't work anymore maybe
the camera was okay
is uh is there still a camera right here
there's no camera right here
entrance room search there okay thank
you
someone who also actually knows
what I'm what I mean thank you
[Music]
where could it be
Cana
I got the one from this room though if
that's what you mean
foreign
I got the helicopter one yeah if that's
the one you mean
[Music]
um
foreign
carpet
what's with this carpet
that's what I was hoping for oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
all of them
that's the first time we collected all
gems in the room in the floor
I feel like they were easier in this
Florida I wasn't even trying that hard
yeah very nice too thank you for telling
me that one
and completionist oh
you little [\h__\h]
you're pretty dumb actually that's a
Pokemon that looks like just one
mm-hmm
why are you acting so high and mighty
oh you want to be in a movie
what
are you going
wait
wait Luigi Run
faster
don't go
do I have to find her in the stupid
movie sets now
oh my God
yeah glammy out
back on nickel
um
dark chocolate can show me where it went
well it's not up here
okay okay okay
it went into
oh this one up
I'm surprised it didn't go into the one
with the Box yeah
that would have been very cat-like
[Music]
oh more
what's that
[\h__\h]
I sucked up some stupid items
I don't want to play golf either okay
I know what I said I need a hobby
but golf is not going to be the one
I swear
let me get the little shits here
[Music]
no no no
wow
[Music]
I I see a pattern now like the ones that
wear a hat
you have to make a shock wave
the ones who have like a
a mask or or something like that you
have to suck it away from them
[Music]
the ones who have like a huge ass
Shields I guess you can try plunging
them yeah yeah
okay okay wait but where's the cat uh
[Music]
-huh what you doing in there I'm playing
hide and seek with me
thank you oh that's cute
Alex I can't even be mad oh baby
and she's not in here now is she
[Music]
what wow
uh
does she not like the good one to be
there
huh maybe I'm not supposed to bring him
out at all
I thought I was being smart
[Music]
I can't I can't get there
it didn't look like she went in here but
okay I guess she kind of did she was but
no she was behind the house
but okay okay if that's okay if that's
okay then
does this work
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh God we're making another
movie now it seems why you want me to
get up there
come on come down
[Music]
thank you
speak angry cattle why are you so
like you happy
hey hello
[Music]
cat what
do you want from me
[Music]
foreign
let her sneak on me okay
[Music]
cat must come to you
all right is it a problem that collegi
is here
I I'm here ready to be sneaked on okay
[Applause]
[Music]
stop it
wait I need the money I can't waste all
this money
[Laughter]
[Music]
the right moment
timing baby
he's oh we got one tail of the cat dear
Lord
that looks painful
but it only has three tails and not like
nine tails that would be
actually you know what I prefer free
dance
playing with Nine Lives of this cat I
don't think I have the patience for it
no don't
move
problems getting up there are you gonna
please sneak up on me if I am
really really
I fell down there already several times
she knows my weak spot
on
[Music]
what are you gonna do
okay you're gonna come down now though
right
that's it
oh Mama Mia where did she go this time
well she did she go one floor below
oh my God
so which one are we in eight
ah
why
[Music]
trash can
what I do what did I do when this
happens
huh
oh
would I know that
but okay
back to new everything is normal again
that's the first time something like
that happened what
why
oh we're almost at 30
000.
I turned off tips yeah I guess I did
because I have yoga
I got you the little lips wisps I guess
so
okay [\h__\h] ropes
why why is everyone out to get me right
now huh
wow
[Music]
they can't get enough of me
they want to get to know the bee booba
I heard the cat
they probably don't like the cat either
let's be real
right
[Music]
seven
I suppose
not the garden seats um
that place is huge I have to go all the
way up again
um
would you cuddle it okay
I'll catch it it's a ghost
if it wasn't I would
oh interesting
wow
oh
well that was really just because I was
looking for the
for the cat oh
I'm happy with that
yoroshide
wait there oh
that what was that there are no
footsteps here
foreign
[Music]
how did I miss that
come on
yeah
I think I missed one though did I
that's okay
yeah so
I have a feeling she's not actually oh
never mind she's here I just didn't see
her in the previous room
what the [\h__\h]
those are not the kind of bees that I
like
[Music]
but easy easy
it's like you come back to the rooms and
you know
some different kind of ghosts are
waiting for you
trying to
take your mind of what you're actually
supposed to do
all right so unfortunately I cannot
climb like that
I wish there was a shortcut there's no
shortcut right
I didn't make such a
genius thing that would have helped me
oh the cat just jumped over there didn't
it
[Music]
what does that mean she's in the other
room or
guestries she's in the other room
but there are no footsteps here
but the cabinet was open
already
my
it's open
no I don't know
oh never mind I can still open it even
further
[Music]
this time she
is in the bed
[Music]
all right let me get the the can I get
the blanket yeah
huh
if at least the room was still in the
states that I left it at like cleaned up
this would be a little bit helpful now
it gives me OCD and it makes me want to
clean everything all over again
wait no she no she completely left I
think she went a floor higher never mind
then did she
[Music]
even she went higher or she's in here
okay
now this is
real ghost busting feels like
phasmophobia we're looking for LA ghoste
come little kitty kitty where are you
where are you at did I go too far is she
not actually anywhere here
[Music]
she's still in the room oh man okay
I know it looked like she may have left
already
hi
these flowers
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] you
that
naha
go for it go for it
oh sorry go for it
those are the stages I keep on freaking
her out maybe
what
[Music]
what see
how about here
what
are you
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I waited too long okay
I hate this uh
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
you can't really turn around unless I I
hold the controller really
really weirdly but hey
[Music]
I mean the timing is kind of hard to get
right back
[Music]
I hate this [\h__\h] cat
s
[Music]
you suck
foreign
literally Luigi's game everything's
green and I say Mario I'm so sorry
I feel like this is like dog propaganda
they're trying to make cats look really
bad with this game developers would
definitely not cat people
they were dog people they wanted the
whole world to know that
same voice actor oh really
oh
what was that
she's not here
she ain't here did she go to the very
top
um
[Music]
foreign
do they really have to
room again but this is not the red
bathroom right there was another one
wasn't there you don't mean this one
oh
gotcha
but she only had one HP left maybe it
ends here
yeah
[Music]
one HP and one tail
blood artist not that one oh God damn it
a Sakura that when I was
and so I did not go too far
man
I like her tracks are anywhere here
either
wait this is not the Sakura room I'm so
confused or is it and I just got rid of
the petals already
no
foreign
by this cat
but it can't make me a dog person I stay
true to my
love for cats
can't change that
[Music]
oh
wait that's interesting
[Music]
okay what
I hate you
[Music]
oh
my God
if she
continues going to all these bathrooms
I'm going to forcefully give her a
[\h__\h] bath
and we all know cats will enjoy that can
you let go of me like what the [\h__\h]
all right
interesting interesting
em what should I know that was also kind
of a first
[Applause]
Banks to death yeah but with its tongue
um I see something there
interesting
oh the Watermelons are back
oh
yeah
oh yeah
is she purring is she is she being cute
that little [\h__\h] okay we're gonna turn
on the water that's it that's it you're
getting a bath
how you like
[Music]
you liked it how you like that yeah
I don't give a [\h__\h]
[Music]
too early
so slow
it looks like it's about just happened
I don't wanna get hurt
I finally found a cat I hate yeah
no you are not allowed to leave
a nice money number
we're not done
you're a k-less cat now oh
it threw up the
like a hairball threw up the button nice
finally
we got that's over
button nine like nine lives yeah yeah I
was thinking like maybe that's
there's a specific reason why day
decided to put
the cat
in connection with the button number
nine
Cuban news
[Music]
I thought you could just um teleport me
down
you know
okay
bandana
it didn't have nine tails though it
should have had nine tails then
that would have been more fitting
oh well
I'm I shouldn't be complaining
three lives was enough
oh Lord
no I did not want to do that six more
times
[Music]
Batman Scatman
that was one of the songs they played in
the after party
[Music]
I'm like for real oh yeah for real yeah
oh it's a fun song but
um
oh yeah
wow okay
unnatural History Museum
interesting
what does that mean
s
yeah
imagine that was her original song
that's a dog bone I just realized I'm
not a dog bone a dog a bone a bone in
general
we are extra spooked this time
why why what are you expecting to find
here Luigi
are you scared of History
oh
foreign
[Music]
we don't want that to come back to life
huh
smash it with something
got something please
oh this one too oh maybe this bone
this one's a small one no
oh
[Music]
what
I go
ah yeah first collectible
I wonder what the position means because
I guess it's just a color but why
wouldn't they put the first one you can
find here
on the first spot hmm
it confuses me did I miss something is
there another one like right here right
in front of the elevator oh God look at
that maybe there is because I can make
that thing move up there
but I don't know if that has any meaning
but I mean look at that
can I do something can I bring it down
foreign
I want to rip it up off the ceiling
and then get something from it
I don't think so
um oh
I mean
I'm so close to Greatness
am I onto something or not eggs
there's one egg missing
where's the egg
okay whatever I don't care
you can stop now
shoot something at that
um
when I find something
I need a lot of oh dark dark light I
need a lot of things to shoot right now
oh
huh
or maybe for the egg
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
if only it was that easy in life
kill a few bats and
they throw money at you
okay I would like to open that please
but so yeah yeah number two see what
that one goes right next to the red one
so I wonder if the first one is really
like the the one that's hanging on the
ceiling
because that would be positioned
even earlier than
the table but maybe that has nothing to
do with that
I'll figure it out
after
first one is always from a ghost oh
really
oh
scary oh look at that there's another
one here
I really need something to oh
piggy bank
I can't do it with a plunger
I need something to
shoot
I I hate the beds I hate that
[Laughter]
okay are we done now
we're done
oh
pineapple trees
they look like big slender pineapples
looks like a spooky scene yeah the the
way they light up the
dinosaur in the back is
pretty spooky
okay
oh see this one I cannot uh suck in but
I don't think it will help me destroy
things maybe I'll find something in the
big room
we'll figure it out I will not let all
these glass cases
just stay
intact
you know me
finally
another one of my friends
oh
[Music]
yeah maybe we can crash everything with
toads later
oh toad is that how we're gonna make use
of you afterwards are you the one are
you the one
hello oh hello oh
yeah that was to be expected
no
is destroyed I don't think
oh it's it's we still have a chance
we can still save toad right
oh oh that's scary it's not even like an
actual ghost oh
okay
that is probably not the right timing
ah but while it eats that one maybe we
were supposed to shoot the next one
uh is that so
ah should I get going to be faster with
that but no it looks like this
okay
this is
because we're doing the same thing
I need another egg
one egg will not do the trick but okay
I'll get it started
another one please
can you
well hmm I need another
oh Luigi thanks for taking the hit
oh
no egg
[Music]
use green she has a bait okay
wait wait wait wait
[Music]
well the bait was destroyed so fast
ah [\h__\h]
no well I mean if we clear all the eggs
once maybe we get double eggs now I
don't know no so one egg
can I throw Luigi
let him eat Luigi okay
do you would you like to take a bite
it's going deep
trust me
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
okay we're not playing games anymore
Blazers
um can we take take him
[Music]
any eggs oh
I got some health back
okay yeah eat him eat him
oh no
[Music]
okay we can use these things
if only he eats uh or maybe that's not
necessary uh I don't know
oh [\h__\h] oh he's stuck he got stuck by
gooey cheese
[Music]
couldn't switch back
maybe when he's stuck on Luigi I tried
to get his tail oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh
foreign
I'm a bit clueless right now
come on come on
well I definitely need to throw
something at him but in what moment
I wonder because
so far
oh God
in that moment
but oh oh that was still all time I
thought it was too late and then did
that do any damage
or did it just like stun him for a
moment [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
um [\h__\h]
the heart the hearts can I please get
them
whoa
whoa he got me with the tail but at the
same time I got oh
more please
um maybe one of these will drop a heart
no they did it before
okay let's focus on attacking again yeah
bye I run so slow
oh
yes so didn't do damage I really am not
sure
oh [\h__\h] oh it goes so far
oh God oh God run run run run run run
run run run run run run run run run run
run
oh there's so hard I can't reach it
I wish it was gonna hurt me
[Laughter]
[Music]
shut up
foreign
there's no damage though
this is really intense yeah
I was doing damage okay
that was tough
that was really tough
a stone age ghost survived until now
it's time to find peace
you've been alive oh wait too long
oh
please go easy on me
let's see what can we do with him
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God at least glitchy is a good
bait he's too Unga Bunga to realize that
guiji is the bait oh God
[Music]
okay I knew that was the moment but
previously I was stunned so I couldn't
do anything
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah feel free to go for him
Porky
foreign
here he comes
[Music]
one more
how kind of you to give me the heart
oh here we go
good good timing good timing
I was a bit too close for comfort but
we're good
[Applause]
[Music]
yes we're talking about
toe this free
oh I need really a massage tomorrow
I'm gonna get a massage tomorrow that's
my goal tomorrow is my day off I'm so
excited to get a massage
I think there's so much pain man it's
crazy
this is just my life I've accepted it
but it's not not very comfortable
hi blue toads
[Music]
oh oh you have an elevator fan yeah
that's good helpful
[Music]
now may I please use you since I am
saved you
yeah you didn't can I use you for some
Shenanigans ah you've managed to say
you've never told another side character
that we don't give a [\h__\h] about and
might as well just left dead but okay
you may have wasted some time but it was
necessary for Content so shout out to
the elevator and I'll make sure he stays
safe and sound in the lab
possibly be necessary though right to
use toad for that stuff because
then what if someone forgets it and just
sends toad away and then it's too late
for
um crushing everything
[Music]
let me see if it works with him anyway
can I use the bones do you have two
large bones
okay but let me try it like this first
[Music]
you can follow me and we're probably
faster this way okay take it back next
piggy bank
destroy
okay
yeah yeah you better make yourself
useful
so happy
fill it I hear no complaints
oh that looks good toad
that looks good that's perfect for your
round heads oh
what you doing in there
Tony you're not helping
where is he
can can I can he escape if I ignore him
for too long or does he just run around
forever that's the first one ah so what
somebody said about the first one always
being a ghost is true it was however not
in the same order as like you know like
walking in and this is the first or so
um
but okay nice
thank you Jello man
you're really feeling
like part of this aren't you I'm happy
yeah I mean
I mean telecast is useful useful times
but guiji is always by my side always
when I need him oh [\h__\h] sorry that was a
miss
and but the bad thing is I can't throw
Luigi in
they both have the good sides
tell rodactyl that's what it is damn you
got some dinosaur knowledge huh
oh [\h__\h]
just how could I miss
I'm initially missing but maybe it's not
enough impact
yeah is this one unshootable
I think this one's untouchable
I definitely
um got it several times
even even if I get it it's just a pearls
or whatever
we already did that okay let's shoot you
let's let's shoot you at the
flying dinosaur
[Music]
AKA
the first version of a phoenix
[Music]
thing
not that one it must be in the big room
right probably
but I'll check with the slide
I'm just missing one
completionist Chihuahua
let me try one last time
it would it could not possibly Miss
oh I think
that doesn't mean
empty case this one or which one because
I've been aiming with my
dark light at all of these
what
do you mean
[Music]
the dino egg I already got one there
like uh
who's this
mmm
oh
[Music]
ah he's so excited about it cute okay
you guys don't think it's here
[Music]
bounce into the Moon
did you kill money uh you mean the movie
guy no I didn't kill him
[Music]
he seems all right
I don't think he deserves to be killed
[Music]
there's nothing here
which one do you mean
this one
we got this one complete
[\h__\h] I can't stop myself
I just can't stop myself
yay
wait uh one last thing I guess
come on
[Music]
what nothing nothing spawns from that
really
oh wow that's uh disappointing
I'm so disappointed
nothing they're not even particles of
the eggshell
hmm that feels like a bug oh oh they do
be watching
something by the way does that ending
imply that Cali even took her own eyes
because you didn't see her eyes anymore
at the end right
[Music]
she loves Bales a little bit too much oh
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
now then Luigi you still need to find
uh one more Toad Princess Peach and
Mario we're halfway there good luck does
this mean I'm actually halfway through
the game though but [\h__\h]
I only managed to save one toad per
stream this is not this can't be real I
might it must be like a speed run like
in the last
two hours or so when you finally get
everyone at once or so
[Music]
I played
what four hours last time and now it's
been 4 hours 44 today no I played I
played at least four and a half last
time huh
four and a half today
that's like nine hours
game said it was 12 hours
so after three hours
[Music]
but that's not halfway through that's
one third
[Music]
hmm I extended the gameplay with the
with the gems huh
[Music]
am I slowing myself down
is it really halfway through or more
like I mean maybe it's considered
halfway there if I plan to get the rest
of the gems but if I don't plan on doing
that then I
I'm like one third left Maybe
Sunday
I probably have more than enough time to
go for another like five hours or so
halfway through the store for only story
uh-huh
what does that mean
s streams are always longer yeah yeah
um
thankfully you're not getting the booze
yeah no I'm not
good for your [\h__\h] booze no I'm not
gonna even try those that was a pain in
the ass
last time
gonna make one more tea
there's no time to make dinner yeah yeah
I mean it's just 9 P.M
um so that's no problem
no problem there
[Music]
um
I got like one blue my playthrough
yeah it's only the first one
me too
they're cute but
no no thank you they feel so unnecessary
I'm sure
[Music]
I'm only drinking cherry tea today
charity huh
[Music]
you think it's a good place
I'm going to find without paying of gold
are you mean the bullfinder
I don't I mean
don't feel the need to do that
[Music]
for me yeah no booze and no booze
oh
two-thirds should I apply more
how many super chats do I have to read I
wonder is it so much
like I will read them but I don't think
it's that many is it
[Music]
uh-huh
I don't think it's many it's a couple
streams but not not many super chats I
think
the the promo Tony stream had the most
hmm
maybe maybe one more floor yeah just
just in case
oh one more because some of you guys are
giving me mixed feelings about how far I
am
oh B2
Bala works
that's below our
our safe Point what could be there
I guess a lot of like
water
so no guiji maybe what's a boiler not
baller I read baller but that makes
sense
boilerworks makes money more sense and
more according to my
vision
don't be so stupid
oh
it's like the wild west the music
oh the keys right there a a key is right
there
interesting atmosphere down here
feels hot whoa
[Music]
a duck duck
duck duck
goose
[Music]
what's in here can I go oh this does it
have to be Guinea
I guess I can't go there
uh okay
what about here this looks like
something
Maybe
oh oh I don't know what that is
something here what's what's all those
stuff here [\h__\h] is that fire
oh what
what
hey
good that I went back there
and good that I had Luigi red a guiji
right there
the elevator
hmm
I want
it's raining money again
more
we'll find my way up there somehow oh
what's your job no
maybe we can be friends a holiday howdy
howdy
how are you doing how how how are you
going
oh
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
thank God that wasn't going she's
standing right there what is that accent
I don't know
I don't know how to make a howdy accent
I wish I knew
okay go into this one's for you
huh
oh
um I thought that it leads up there
[Music]
[Laughter]
is that uncomfortable for you Luigi hmm
oh wait oh
wow going easy can pass through again
okay so I was really thinking this
this Mass people Luigi yeah okay
from this point of view it looked like
there was some kind of like
uh something blocking it there oh oh
[Music]
like to the top ever or to the key
hmm
well we'll figure it out we'll figure it
out
that was Halloween well how on Halloween
itself I was just streaming and not
really doing
anything
[Music]
besides that
how was your Halloween guys
try the pipe again oh you're thinking ah
I might go somewhere else you think
was I changed something
I didn't really change something
I played jigsaws
too old to trick or treat
well I hope you guys watched uh
the
the Ahmad bales
trick or treat don't trick-or-treat uh
Halloween VR thingy stream yeah it was
too late for me but um
yeah
[Music]
yeah like uh I think they asked like who
wants to participate around the time
where uh I was just done with the
with the uh promo Tony VR stream and was
feeling absolutely exhausted from that I
don't want to do too many of those VR
streams
um and even from desktop I don't know it
was too late like
that and also I had plans as you know I
went to Convention
so busy busy weekend overall I was
already
mentally exhausted so I didn't want to
add any more onto it but
yeah you guys should watch the archive
they put a lot of work into it so go go
go go
if you didn't watch it yet
they I thought originally like when they
were saying oh we're doing like a like
an escape room kind of thing I was
thinking
um they meant like
oh
I was thinking they meant
um
like like a like an already existing
escape room VR game
but then I realized
later afterwards no they made it on
their own they came up with their own
puzzles right that's so cool big respect
the hole to the left yeah I've been
through this one
and I I just was like blowing into this
one but
oh
I'm stuck
why was I even able to stop the tube
here and then turn it on again what does
that do for me
gooey
does not like this that's understandable
huh
[Music]
enter pipe try again
why am I trying again
wow
I don't know
ah
huh
what
open
which way
do we need both of us for that oh oh
okay okay oh wait I just can't
that's ah hello
oh no go through go through
that should lead to the key right right
yeah and how do we get to the
collectible huh
what
take key that looks like I could go to
the left side
oh
[Music]
all the way on the right side that one
interesting interesting choice of
positioning
okay finally that took me weirdly
ah he leaves it there
sometimes I automatically assume he just
brings it to me in my inventory when I
get rid of him but no
second time
here
got the key
bright enlightening Heat
we are being greeted by
ghosts
having just some casual fun together
right just just casual
[Music]
no no okay don't sit there
that one's gone
and now you hi
turn off the banjo I want to hear more
of the banjo
okay
oh yeah calm banjo
bucket
bucket that just for uh dissolves into
some pieces of paper okay so I changed
something here I changed something there
I don't know what that does
but I'll just change everything
let's see how Luigi takes that
oh oh oh oh oh oh now they're all turned
on
okay that was a mistake
oh wait no this one I turned on now too
huh oh well never mind no okay
the right side with that one
oh
that was that one
turn that one off
oh no there's three left
maybe I can turn them off like on the
bottom here can I go down no
well that's weird
oh
foreign
no maybe not not that one but do the
other ones turn off I didn't pay
attention if I turn into the other side
oh sorry
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay
hi
oh bucket of money
huh
do this
which
opens the door
oh that's wow what needs such a secure
safety door
what could that be
yeah
oh okay
[Music]
I understand that not something a normal
person random person should be able to
enter okay
true
does every Hotel
have such a huge sewage system below it
not normal right
I mean like every Big Hotel
no right
no my mommy
water and I don't think I get any wishes
out of that hmm what happened what does
this do
we will
oh
stop the wee what no I think that it was
just right that one time
[Music]
let's go up all the chest ah
I'll figure out how to get to the chest
oh wait I think I know how
now I want to do it
get guiji or sell
all right
get crazy to turn it while I'm already
on it and then I think
[Music]
yes yes
okay
oh wow oh so shiny
let me check
is there something special here no oh
wait should I have
[Music]
what is this can I get up there do I
need Luigi here I hope not
we'll go up now and see
let's get rid of Luigi now
oh oh hi no
what wow are you raising the water level
oh oh oh yes he is
[Music]
like a Titanic kind of moment
don't go help help don't just dance on
the water what the [\h__\h] get us out of
here oh thank you thank you thank you
yeah
how are you wet
oh thank God
what what oh hello
can yourself into a real mess there
Luigi good news though the Poltergeist
has been tested in depths up to I forget
really deep what important is it's
waterproof but I'm not waterproof but
because that ghost used to switch to
control the water levels your path is
blocked I think you could walk along the
sewer Waterway and reach the switch give
it a try you've got to return the water
to its original levels and go after that
ghost hmm
I will try my best yeah Luigi isn't
waterproof either we have a problem
going to will just die instantly and I
will die momentarily
[Music]
what did that do
oh
a poster is not a good way to hide that
amount of money also we're over 30 000
. oh
oh that's chill oh but okay
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no it's all up there oh bring it down
that's fun I Wanna Be Luigi right now
just want to chill take a break and just
chill as if I'm in the pool I'll just
imagine
this is the the best life Luis you can
possibly have right now
even the music
it's so chill I kind of want to send
Luigi up there but oh
I don't know how to get off of the
duck
well let me try again
let me try again
oh
how
it is okay so Gucci I know there's a lot
of water but trust me bro
[Music]
okay okay
um
[Music]
and the last one
oh
Don't Touch the Water
okay thank you and that was all
can go easy get on the duck too
do we want to try that
no okay
all right but then how do we open that
gate over there
orange ball oh [\h__\h]
I did not even register that
hmm
oh wait there's even more there yeah
I'm coming
[Music]
what part two
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
shh I found it I did not see the bump
there what the [\h__\h]
uh
okay I have to be a bit more careful
here
I underestimated the situation
go back
and um
and now
you have to do something
that will turn off that I was hoping for
that good
oh [\h__\h] it's a piranha
it has yet to notice me I think [\h__\h]
that was the wrong one how do I get to
the middle
like this one is on this one
it is
we have to do it again
bounce
don't get caught thank you
let's bring it over here
oh oh wow wow wow
I don't like this kind of underground uh
switch levels in jrpgs either you know
like in I think in Tales of Symphonia
they had one like this
and in every other like Taste of
Hysteria they had one too I don't like
them at all
they tend to be bad why are they in
every [\h__\h] game
they're just depressing
I like that he's like chilling on this
rubber duck but still
because that's what's expected no I
don't expect
[Music]
what
you're telling me my HP was this low
oh
[Music]
what I didn't lose a bone though
oh
what was that oh I guess the spikes just
killed my rubber duck okay
not not me
oh [\h__\h] oh oh God no okay
[Music]
I don't like this
oh well
let's open up this [\h__\h] again
okay and and Gucci
oh don't touch them
uh which way which way which way
where did Glizzy go ah there okay uh
Dexter
what oh that's where I came from
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay next next
oh it's pulling me in it's pulling me in
wow
go back a little bit
and now now we're ready you know just
for safety I wanted to make sure
okay
oh no
oh wait wait oh there's like I could get
off here but I guess I don't have to
oh
okay it came out of the top one
and now go for this one
and we come out in the middle and
there's something to pull there okay
okay
hi
if there are any collectibles
in this level I don't plan on getting
any of them
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait I don't know what I'm doing
wait wait wait why I'm going so fast
uh-huh
what just exploded
what do you do you do
that okay stay
wait did the greasy die
the platform there to like possibly
revive him did he die because I can't
switch to him
oh
how did that happen
I thought he was safe here
oh okay
oh I went too far oh oh man well I mean
huh
wait what did I eat what am I
what what am I looking well I already
pulled the thing that I pulled there but
what did that do
I guess I can go back now right and go
to the left side
oh it was just for money okay
oh [\h__\h]
uh whatever
uh uh wait no no no no
this would be a lot more fun if uh I was
playing it co-op with a real person
like this is the point where I would
really like that
someone wants to play with me any
volunteers
this would be so much less tedious
okay
oh
can I not throw the oh plungers
yeah I can't okay
there's a lot of money down there
here we go no no bouncing oh [\h__\h] sharks
uh
wait
are you following me
um can you not oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
um I don't like this oh they [\h__\h] up
nice
too much thinking I have to look at so
many things here I don't like it
uh
oh no no go back go back go back
the heart I want the heart I'm too late
for the heart but do I need to get off
here anyway I don't know
oh
[Music]
let me look around
the last one we were in the Maldives oh
thank you
can I get the heart
that's where they ended up yeah
so far okay I think I have to
um
maybe get off momentarily or or not
oh [\h__\h]
lots of water here
[Music]
maybe I do have to get off momentarily
and turn off the water there
[\h__\h] sake
nah it's so annoying
I want to blow that thing away but I
can't I have to bounce
it away
but then it bounces me
no
okay let's see if real Luigi can help
here
yes that's what I was supposed to do
now
oh oh oh oh oh
[Music]
that's not the same ghost oh that's a
difference look behind
oh
that was easy because that guiji was
right there
thank you
s too
[Music]
boy boy
ice
get his tail nah
the other one let's get rid of the red
one now just a purple one left I think
[Music]
yay that sitting night there is US isn't
it
he says
you got something to hide don't you
what is it
nah
nothing
apparently nothing oh slip of slippery
Danger
throw it on the night
Okay so we're not being disturbed by
them anymore so now we can turn this
around
and will that bring the water levels
down
what did that do
I don't even know what that is but we
can revive guiji right here
yay
but that doesn't get us very far
oh
hype Direction
oh oh
I was hoping for the water
levels to change right here but
ah
what if I go now can I go right up yeah
okay okay
[Music]
Aha and then I wanna I want this one to
go
up
Maybe
when I go back and then I change this
one to the right side but then I didn't
even try to go to the left side
can I even I don't know
we'll see if we're missing something but
this seems right
[Applause]
and with the big red button
maybe this is for the water levels
must be
ah
couldn't
open
[Music]
treasure
yeah
yes
oh he's gonna notice though isn't he
he's gonna be mad
good job
good good job Gucci all right the water
is back to how it works go back to where
you came from and get after the mechanic
ghost
all right uh go back to where I came
from you say
[Music]
from which path
down here can I just walk now
enough
It's never enough
hi Luigi
you're finally safe here
I know it must be traumatizing
you have a what's what do you call a
a water phobia for 4B what's the
professional word
the right term for that
Hydro hydrophobia
[Music]
what what what what what
break the brick wall break well oh that
one
with
um with what
um
can I move
or can I just plunge it
no plunging allowed
this thing no
how about I can I just go behind it with
guichi
oh oh no there's a water puddle there
see
it I mean can
I spine
unmovable
floaty
it looks so weak though ah why can't I
not aim lower
you really thought that that would do
enough damage
did you
see you
of course not
[Music]
are we even talking about the same wall
I'll see
also I
think how do I get these coins out of
the floaty
[Music]
oh well
painting
oh I can't pick it up though really
whatever I don't care about those
Secrets here I told you
oh maybe the watermelon though oh
watermelon oh I can't bring it through
here okay put the door closed the moment
I entered
huh
what it
now I can leave but I need to lower the
water level even more I think
[Music]
what
a couple of wall again
oh this one
chair but
how to get the chair
should I
huh
Maybe
get something from mama here is there
something there it's for later
what's going on
ow what the [\h__\h] oh it's the shark
ah they're like acting as if they can't
just
survive without water oh
all right I'll fight you guys
I'll be part of it gladly
it's safe again no Sharky's here give me
another heart
no sharks it's a no Shark Zone no fish
nothing
foreign
these planks though I think I can get
rid of these planks especially now
oh
not that there was anything important
behind it oh hi
a lot of money here though it's good
that we went back
no gula
[Music]
what about this bucket by the way
is it actually necessary to come back
here
[Music]
that feels a little bit
annoying doesn't it
here let me Spawn you here
still wet or
I want to go through here no
no
[\h__\h]
why not there's no water left
don't be don't be so sensitive
why
oh what yeah okay explain that to me
[Music]
I spawned him a million times
how come
it did not work until now
okay I see some water here but and now
now I can just walk just fine what's up
with that
also I really start to feel like we
really just have to walk back normally
they make us like
look at everything again
how it looks without the water
oh hey see chest I would have missed out
on those oh
[Music]
well oh [\h__\h] I have to like throw
something into his mouth Maybe
soccer ball
how about that oh my God
what
yeah good old mimic
mimic
he's not mimicking me
oh
interesting anyway how the [\h__\h] do I
fight him
do you want some rubber duckies
can't give those to you hmm
mimics mimic objects
are you really a Jared for Japan well
I've seen these definitely in other JRP
juice yes
I think even in tails off games oh let
me do it again
um
I was not sure what to do yeah okay let
me get the other ball again wait for me
dude
that was the next thing I was gonna try
foreign
yeah I think I remember in one like old
I think maybe even in terms of Symphonia
there were
um
monsters like this
at least some tales of symphony I think
I remembered um
thank you
hola crabs
no crabs where is them
where's the promised crab hmm
I have to save the piggy
well
Luigi can you get the pinky yeah
[Music]
yeah I know narrow in here not much
space but
they got the piggy we got some alone
time with the piggy
okay moving on
um
speed run
I'm just gonna ignore everything as I
can
Mouse
this one I can break as well
that wall over there but I honestly
don't know
out
I don't know why no one that's another
path
if I was really supposed to go back this
way or if
this is the wrong way
it's kind of weird that it makes me go
back that makes me feel like it's wrong
Fire Emblem doesn't have mimics
boy huh
I am here now
[Music]
guiji take a look please
oh
if I turn it there
do I get to the other side oh
I have to get there
this room will be used later well I'm
using it now I want them on the
collectible
hmm
oh
I didn't see I thought I could change
the direction here
but wait
now
there we go or is it is it though
yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh hey yo
where's this room
[Music]
secret storage room
oh slice of pizza
[Music]
that's the banjo that has been playing
in the background all this time
there's even more pipes
what the [\h__\h] was that what the [\h__\h]
controller vibrating
[Music]
okay which pipe do I go through maybe
this one
yeah
okay
[Music]
Pizza where I'm
I would love to have a pizza right now
salami pizza or tuna Hawaii I don't care
after the after party when I was waiting
for
um my ride to come and pick me up I was
waiting outside because it was inside it
was too loud and too hot so
I was just waiting outside chilling
and they were like
two congoers
behind me
eating some 2 am fresh pizza
and they gave me one piece for free but
nothing to do it they were like a little
bit drunk
maybe they wouldn't even have given it
to me
if they
oh if they weren't drunk I think I think
them being drunk probably made them more
open to sharing their Pizza
but that 2 am fresh hot salami pizza was
exactly what I needed and was
like it came from heaven
it was amazing
and I was so so so
excited and happy and hyped and grateful
I can't believe that a stranger
would just give me
Pizza like that yeah to the high-end
pizza and it was a fresh one not a cold
one
I don't know where they got that pizza
from but Hallelujah bless you
I need to go get food now
yeah go get yourself
on it
why why is it possible for me to close
it again oh no okay I'm opening it okay
okay
less strangers with pizza I am
they were quite nice even though one of
them was way too drunk
I hate drunk people but they gave me
Pizza
I literally didn't do anything I didn't
even talk to them I just I was just
sitting on the pavement and waiting so
nice
didn't Mama tell you to tell you not to
take food to those changes I thought it
was safe in that moment
um
same
nice and they were eating the pizza
themselves so
I think that one was fine
can't say no to 2 A.M Pizza
you go with friends well General yeah oh
wow we're fighting that oh no oh no
[Music]
oh there
you're [\h__\h] kidding me oh
how do we fight this dude
I don't wanna be on here can I do it
from above here oh he just chose when I
am up here
oh there's oh [\h__\h] oh there's a bar
oh
hi
[Music]
oh God I was thinking of like throwing
it at him but they go and explode way
too fast
[Music]
I guess
oh [\h__\h]
okay
what what is the how do you fight this
guy do I really have to be in the pool
[Music]
okay
spikes yeah I guess he can get spikes
too right
if I can get hurt by the spikes surely
he can too
just [\h__\h] the bums
I think I will only hurt myself on those
oh God oh God oh no
this is not gonna go away
what
[Music]
wow
come on come on
oh god oh man
[Music]
well at least he's waiting right at the
bomb
quick get the heart get the heart no I
know I don't know
and now and now
what what
it's like a Bowser fight
uh okay and and now I go there or what
how long is he gonna wait for me
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I got
[Music]
I Gotta Wear
[\h__\h] okay now we're back in the water I
suppose
okay okay
it's right in front of you dude
[Applause]
what
does he know that it's right in front of
him okay smart AI
well what are we doing
what is it what is he doing
oh
[Music]
that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] slaps are so [\h__\h]
rude no
[Music]
no no no no no no
oh he makes me mad he makes me so mad
ah you set watch yourself
what about the bump give me a new bomb
Oh
oh never mind don't need the bomb
oh oh oh oh
I'm faster this time so we should be
good
[Music]
okay
let's get back I I'm really confused
about this fight but it's going okay
besides the [\h__\h] slaps which are
[\h__\h] rude and I don't know what he's
doing when he's doing that
I get confused like ah out of the panic
like which direction should I go oh yeah
bye
[Music]
what are we gonna do dude oh God uh
uh well it hit me did it hit him it did
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I got him anyway
the pain in the ass this bastard is
a lot of pain in the ass man never give
up they'll never give up what are you
doing
[Music]
come here
no
thanks
is the moment [\h__\h]
what a stupid fight
yeah touch it touch it
[Music]
oh yeah oh double
wait wait
oh no why
why how can you mess that one up oh he's
doing it again
how did I not suck him properly I got it
I don't know I got it oh my God oh my
God oh it's so far away he's so far
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off me
okay
this is it
you little [\h__\h] I'm so mad
[Music]
so painful oh give me the hearts that's
so rude
why did you have to send them
yeah I'm feeling the same way man
I'm gonna disappear and they're so close
to the spikes it's not even worth it
uh
but what did he like throw an elevator
thing down there or no
huh
[Laughter]
at least he was defeated ah worst pool
party ever absolutely
terrible not fun zero out of ten will
not do again will not come to your
stupid pool party again
not even any hot dogs or
what do you eat at pool parties
ice cream
I hear something like shiny sounding
anyway I'm I suppose I have to pull this
[Music]
ah barbecue Pizza
oh [\h__\h] man
you're making me hungry
I have one more one more spring roll
which number is this
[Music]
that was really
annoying
[Music]
oh he has like all of his living stuff
down here and he just had it in the
water
fridge is empty
this is empty too
oh oh don't touch it
oh
hmm why is all this so empty
what about the shower curtain she takes
a shower here
under the
pipe I guess okay
I mean why not I hope it's fresh water
like clean water
it looks pretty clean
nothing here here
huh
so weird
it looks like clean water I mean I
wouldn't drink it but showering I guess
he's a ghost who doesn't give any shits
okay what about this red pipe that
bothers me it looks like I could get up
there
oh good all right no we're done here we
have the elevator thingy
[Music]
um
Cletus was his name but
wait how do I get out of here where's
the exit
hmm
[Music]
was there an exit at the bottom
I entered from the bottom what
I'm blind
concentration is
no
uh here well I mean you can't see the
door unless you look at the map again
yeah
banjo music
oh oh okay that's fine I think this is
the exit to the
elevator was it oh
that there's so much backtracking on
this
level uh but maybe that's just me maybe
I'm imagining
that's why you have the map
that's why I have you guys
[Music]
and how many more floors
oh yeah oh yeah baby oh only five more
or six because the the number ten we
didn't even look at yet
but yeah I think
I will go there
and then
you know just leave the elevator and
then it should save so
yeah I'll continue on Sunday
foreign
[Music]
what is this room
this floor
[Music]
oh
I've seen this one is this the one of
the sands
where the sand is like everywhere and
you can like endlessly oh
look
yeah okay
no no
lots of sand we will have to learn to
accept and love and cherish sand next
time I guess
20 minutes and vacuuming yay
that is
perfect for people of OCD
lots of panic on Sunday yeah really
is it gonna get more difficult
oh [\h__\h]
yeah I will read some super chats but
first I need to I need a little another
little Idol meeting break
uh for two minutes and then I'll be back
and read you guys some super chats um
so uh please wait
um
okay okay you did great boss thank you
it was fun I mean um some levels were
kind of more tedious than before but we
also got like full collectibles on two
floors now it's fun
um I'm looking forward to the sad level
next time my least favorite ones this
time though were definitely the the
switch system place that we just went
through and the the planned level I
didn't like that one that much either
but um those are so far in terms of like
both streams my least favorite ones were
those two same same
ah I mean
the plant one at least looks nice
and it's less annoying than the sewage
one still
plant one I don't know why it made me
mad I guess just because
the rooms are small
and you have to go up and down
yeah I don't know oh
and then the fact that you had to hunt
the cats down through the whole thing
again it's pretty annoying
dinosaur one was cool yeah
dinosaur one was fine the movie one was
fine
um the middle age medieval one was fine
they were good
did like the prehistorical yeah because
they also the ghost
um boss the the dinosaur boss
even though it took me a while to like
figure it out at least it was like
quite different from the other bosses in
in terms of visuals
very very
big dinosaur attack wow
that's cool
boss having the stream this is the last
one hmm I guess was it was it maybe it
was huh
movie floor had some nice gimmicks in
the end yeah
um but generally like okay even if the
sewage system was annoying maybe that
was also partially because it was the
last level we did today and after it's
been six hours now after six hours maybe
it's just time to
stop because that's when
we lose our interest perhaps
um
oh because it's a similar level yeah the
[\h__\h] floaty physics
uh I can't wrap my brain around it in in
such a
quick manner while being watched and
being pressured and under stress
so
yeah
screw sewer and water levels yeah
[\h__\h] that
okay so little intermission and I'll be
right back
see you in my office
foreign
oh was there no music here did I turn it
off
it was like a really low-key sound from
the game I think
oh well you could have imagined for
blood
no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
I'm alive still breathing
ah stream for blood
for blood is good
okay
are we going to use the Halloween office
still I guess why not huh
it's still like
I still feel
like it's more that season than
Christmas at least
uh or like winter season it's not
Winters yet so
oh
man is
excited to take down the decorations
it's not really decorations it's a crazy
[\h__\h] out there that is trying to get in
and kill me
help I'm the one who should be asking
for help not the girl outside
oh
ah they usually actually hmm
I think during winter time like actual
like really really winter time I'll be
using my my Shrine with the snow a bit
more
um
Ballroom I don't use that much either
huh
I could use that every once in a while
and my kitchen haven't used the kitchen
in a while I haven't been doing cooking
streams
anyway
oh you superchatos
when he's on bgm and let me turn off the
game
[Music]
you missed them any plan for cooking
students
um
not really
not really yeah
I know I like them too but
your voice acting on the Halloween
episode was amazing you think so
it was hard I feel like maybe like in
hindsight now that I look at it like
incomplete with everyone else
it feels like we're we're looking
totally different like worlds and scenes
I don't know me and Iris versus Bales
and Kelly
uh like we we're in a totally different
vibe and atmosphere
so if we were
but I mean but that's that's not
necessarily like a mistake I guess
because that's just what our lines were
like we were just you know I mean
bantering minding our own business and I
guess ignoring Bale's worries Kelly's
taking care of it so
at multiple takes yeah I send like
multiple takes but
and there were like some instructions
like
like only like very little instructions
I think
I feel like there were some
I always had something else
oh sure
oh
I mean look at it
oh yeah no not really sometimes it would
say like in Brackets call Kiana
confidently let's do this girls
but besides that no not really any
well but I just I don't know I
interpreted most of my things to be more
like light-hearted
I think my my lines were light-hearted
like
me my character in the story was
light-hearted
and just chilling
yeah we were oblivious yeah yeah yeah
we're just we're not worried about
anything
or maybe we were evil and that's why we
didn't give a [\h__\h] we were the ones
watching and maybe we were really like
Gonna Hurt Bales I don't know
um
who knows but it was a cool story and
yeah as I said before I think Bales was
like damn like she had such a serious
tone the whole time oh this is cool
um cool cool bales
Bales Bells Bells Bells balls balls
males males Bells boobs
foreign
saved from last year but if you guys
want to make some new ones yeah we can
do it again
we can make some new Chihuahua balls
yeah
so I need to look for music
um
all right some chill Cafe music I like
to use this one
I love that hashtag oh yeah wasn't it
really just Kiana's balls
was it
that's so direct so straightforward
you sound a little bit out of the
weather oh I'm not but I just didn't
really have much to talk about today I
guess
because I I talked about everything
yesterday it was a long stream
but I'm not under the weather at all
at the moment at least I'm feeling fine
foreign
[Music]
oh speaking of hashtags people are
misusing KF props so I'm thinking of
taking it out of my description again I
thought of putting it there because I
thought it was pretty obvious okay of
props is for props but people have been
using it for normal fan art and now it's
hard to find the props so I'm gonna
delete it right now but then how do we
how do we let people know
about the props
damn it
yeah
well I mean the people that make perhaps
sometimes they know the
the tag already I guess but I was hoping
that some some new people maybe find it
and you know feel like making some props
but all right well we'll just keep it a
secret
[Music]
no because it was right next to the art
hashtag and and it says fan art a
hashtag Arts of ashes and Cave props and
you know props are some kind of fan art
so
huh the thing is when I put cave props
in there I have zero letters left
and I already like tried to squeeze it
down as much as I can so I can't write
props
is hashtag props I can't do that there's
no space and I already tried to get rid
of other things okay Arsenal would not
make a difference I think put it up the
kfp memes
wow
I mean that also is just there with no
explanation then
it would make more sense under fan art
in my opinion
and yeah I need more space I could if I
get rid of the Japanese
um description I could do that but that
one is already so basic and
squeezed in
so whatever we're just not gonna have
cave props for now
oh
ah
this is new
hey yo I was like looking at my Twitter
profile and on the right side you know
you have the you might like suggestion
and I got a suggestion for a new blue
refraction blue reflection Game Twitter
account
for the new blue perfect actually I
can't say it game they have a cute
design for the main girl
oh
she's pretty young
she got cool horns
nice art
blue reflection oh
cool she's like
she looks edgy
[Music]
damn
I should check that out maybe you should
yeah yeah the artist has worked on
Atelier games before nowadays not
anymore but he used to do a lot of the
Atelier designs back in the day
foreign
well you just wait in in like one or two
months you'll be wishing that I don't
play your pictures anymore
all that you're getting from me
[Music]
it's on tweet with um
the little dolls on top of a monitor in
in some office are killed
[Music]
get off of off of
I need to get off of Twitter
[Music]
where do I need to start reading a super
chants
foreign
[Music]
it's really not that much I think I
think little nightmares is the next one
yeah I
think that's the right one okay
[Music]
there we go
let me take a fruit candy I think
yeah Rocky Wawa reads her own Super
chats that's the only good thing about
her
and cruise Duncan Cruise usual room
five months bye bye it says I miss
you're not gonna say her name she who
shall not be named
that was fast
let me just make it so that we have a
good visual for that
[Music]
the hands are big
too big
oh yeah that's better
better
enjoy the usual room
and Jenkins monkey thank you for the
pinky welcome back Kiana last week there
was a cute little
named with a guy who claimed to have
eaten you I pretended to be her survived
but deep down I knew he would come back
anyways I love you from wait no boss I
meant kiwawa
[Music]
I don't know if this one is genuine
you stumbled over your words a little
bit
foreign
explain then what is the explanation hmm
tell me
try it was muscle memory
you would not have that in your muscle
memory if you wouldn't have supported
that [\h__\h]
in that one week
[Music]
you you were not you didn't have to you
could have been a lurker
uh
two moms usual room
[Music]
bye bye
[Laughter]
Crystal how could you guys get fooled by
that
it was even see through
pink
huh
that Kuma
what the [\h__\h]
you are
you all right come here show yourself
um
don't you want to say hi in the chat hmm
where are you
why are you okay for arm
time out
no more chat for you
Dr Frank and sakanashi
why did you change your name like that
because you can't you turned back into
the beach so you became Frankenstein
how's that work
and I know it's your Halloween costume I
guess wait I get it now
foreign
[Music]
welcome back thank you
I am back so you guys better be nice to
me
[Music]
Sean Eon and danke Schoenberg
foreign
thank you for the pinky
what can I say except yesterday I said
it was my birthday potential as a
belated birthday wish can I please ask
you for one more year of you shining for
us
I'm very glad I found my new friends
among king of peeps woofieu champion
you're cute
are you so cute
[Music]
you're having a let's go to some good
words congratulations
it's a little bit late but
doesn't matter right
I I am glad you're part of kfb thank you
for your sweet sweet kindness thank you
soon please continue supporting and of
course I'll do my best to make your wish
come true
I'll try
as hard as I can
to survive
don't you keep on going
yeah
Brandon Duncan Monica is a Sim thank you
soon
happy
happy birthday Monica you little [\h__\h]
that's what you wanted to hear right
[Music]
thank you
I know you changed the way you write it
but I know it's you you still have the
same profile picture and the can at the
end just gives it away so easily
looking for the top dog you shouldn't
hear the god dangashion Super Snake
Mario thank you for the pinky hi girl
I'm glad to have you back my beautiful
Majestic Phoenix
I miss you something strange happened
while you were gone I became a frog but
thankfully I'm back to a snake again
wait shouldn't I be a chicken I'm not
sure anymore help
yeah you are a chicken you're just a
very long chicken that can swallow very
big objects that are bigger than
yourself
but you are a chicken
you must be otherwise you would not be
able to work at kfp
um
long chicken
long boy chicken
stretched out
and very very flexible chicken
recipes
[Music]
foreign
battle
black Fortune if if anything at the
latest after Fatal Frame I don't owe you
[\h__\h]
then to go down question thank you for
the pinky hey territory it was my
birthday last week but there was some
weird frog streaming on your channel
uh-huh tell me about that
so I decided to wait and see if you will
come back also congrats on the long
awaited formatology stream and you pull
me into camera
um come on
person did amazing thank you yeah
Emma apparently had fun using that
camera system I I think you know making
use of the the studio that she made
she's surely
happy about it um not only her but
everyone who worked on the studio
yeah
especially seafoam boy
probably always very happy to see
that being shown up because like it's so
such a waste to just you know have the
winter area and show it once have the
Halloween area show it once and then
it's over you know so I'm glad I could
show pull more around but maybe maybe
we'll use the winter area again this
year and just upgrade it a little bit
who knows hmm
yeah it hasn't been used much only like
basically for one stream I mean I used
it for like a kalaoka stream after it
was used in the the group collab
yeah
but that's pretty much it isn't it
yeah yeah they should be used more than
once
um
they look so good it's only
it only sucks that we are so [\h__\h]
exhausting
I wonder why it was so especially
exhausting for me last time like the the
headset was hurting so much on my head
more than usual it's weird
uh oh yeah and Belinda first
delicious
and good choice on waiting until I'm
back yeah
crispy chicken not a frog always been a
chicken
thank you Sharon looking for the top
donkey shin you need to chat down
because your nightmare Duncan Jacob 47
ounce thank you soon I'll see you
laughing thank you Tracy Duncan thank
you
korean's 18 thank you
congratulations on beating the game your
talented Phoenix with Pro Gamer skills
it's appreciated that you go out of your
way to play scary games just for us
well well nightmares little nightmares
were still totally fine acceptable
compared to stuff like Outlast so I'm
good I'm good it was okay then with some
scary moments but
it was harmless
compared to stuff like Outlets yeah
and they're good thank you soon episode
[Music]
oh yeah actually I post latest fire for
public into the schedule this week did
you see that will be public
we're gonna try to clear with the last
character and I guess that will lead us
to a general clear of the game so I
don't know it's just like playing it
publicly I was thinking oh I need one
more one more game for this week
what should I do and then
somehow I just felt like playing
slightest fire
[Music]
no no no it's on purpose
yeah
I haven't played it in a couple days
though
[Music]
but yum will be fun I think
wait what the [\h__\h] why did I forget
Martin why did I forget about
putting that Portal game into my
schedule am I stupid
you guys didn't tell me about it it's
coming out on the third isn't it
the entropy Center
on the 2nd of November hey yo what the
[\h__\h] wait wait I think I'm changing
slaves
oh
well that's interesting I forgot about
that completely I was like last week I
was telling myself okay next week we're
gonna play the entropy Center
and then when I was making the schedule
I completely forgot
uh let me look at my schedule so
Fatal Frame first days let us buy our
Friday huh
well I already have final frame plans of
um Elena so I'm not changing that but
okay slay the Spire will not be played
publicly this week maybe next week
Maybe next week then okay
um it will be entropy Center I hope I
don't forget let me put it in my Google
schedule at least
watching item
s
[Music]
but then ah the entropy Center
isn't it kind of too early for you guys
I kind of wanted like a lot of people to
be able to watch but it really just
depends on like um
when I start
oh there was always gonna be someone who
can't watch it well 10 days EST I would
say in general is not too bad
PST will be suffering though wait is it
really 10 a.m Eastern because you guys
told me my EST times were wrong half of
them
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah wait yeah is it what
what is it at 9am
that one was right only that one was
right okay
well okay I'll I'll keep keep at the
same time because
um
I oh yeah I think I wanted to sleep
early on that day
fix my schedule a little bit and also
just be able to you know chill and cook
later so
it will be an early stream
[Music]
and then if you come to watch that I
might have some
keys for you
for my audience
okay
yeah so don't buy it yet just yet
because you if you're planning on buying
it don't buy it yet because you might
get a key from me
okay so next stream that we're gonna
read is
um
do you no that has no super chats of me
the chicken stream
ing
cute art
uh cute
don't quote me like that out of context
thank you for the pinky some random guys
telling me their PS4 with the new Quad
for a hundred dollars let's go
is that a good price I guess so I mean
PS4 is no PS5 but
what's a normal like reselling
secondhand reselling price of a PS4
sounds okay right
well congratulations Sanji Sean
congratulations I hope you're enjoying
code code
the fish right now on your PS4
um don't get it too slimy it might hurt
the PS4 and you won't be able to play
games anymore
you should put the card in a frying pan
or in a baking tray in the oven not
necessarily on the PS4
maybe add some seasoning to it
yeah or give it to a cat
[Music]
yeah you sent the pinky so and I guess
your PS4 was called now costed 150
dollars not 100 dollars
was it worth it I think it was worth it
trying to do thanks for the pinky Kiana
if you broke your bones in a terrible
monster fighting accident and were left
immobilized immobilized immobilized in a
full body cast I'll be your generic
poorly written caretaker former rival
who had to show you their loveness as a
bonus I will sign the costume I was like
what are you talking about until
the middle of the Super Chat I see this
is reference to my to my genius
storylines that I come up with that are
very very riveting and hard grasping and
tear
inducing
um
[Music]
do you want an autograph I don't think
you should be signing my cast I think
you actually need an autograph for me
because
my stories I'm like I'm I'm the next
um
J.R.R Tolkien
I am you just don't know it yet
for the pinky planning a trip to Europe
and we'll be traveling to Germany and
Austria oh do you have any
recommendations and must goes it will be
around the end of April will be my first
time to Austria love food sizing and
castles although that's perfect
did you
like the fact that you chose Austria was
that influenced by you being a fan of me
because then
I could be like a tourism Ambassador
because I don't think you would be the
first one who came to Austria because of
me yeah
I'm
I'm like an ambassador
hell yeah
but they they don't even know I exist
Austria doesn't [\h__\h] know I exist
to be honest probably like the the whole
um Eurovision song on this thing is not
really gonna work out either because I'm
I don't really like I tried you may have
seen I tried contacting
and like getting someone's attention but
like on my own it's not really something
I can get really far with like they
didn't like reply to me
and um
yeah I I I tried to
um get management behind this by telling
them the absolute insane numbers that
we'll be watching the program
and then you know get them to help me
but nothing really came out of that and
I'm kind of like I don't wanna I have so
many things on my mind and and so many
things to take care of that I can't
keep on running after all these things
in the hopes that eventually
um
you know I'll get
something some answers or so
um so I don't think that will be
happening which is uh too bad because I
feel like the goal was never about
winning the goal was to get
um my name and homologous name out there
and just make
um a topic which I think would have
totally worked and you know your
original song contest is made for these
kind of wacky contestants The Wacky
contestants
often they do pretty good even
um yeah
I would have liked to do it totally I
would have been very motivated to do it
but now I think it's too late
Austria has still not
um
announced
who their contestant is or how they're
choosing them this year
but I think it's too late
and they don't seem to be aware of me
and I don't know how to make them aware
of me
I don't have the connections to make
them aware of me
I'm angry because
I
let's be real like
um
it's difficult now that like the sea
thing has
um
toned down a lot
foreign
getting a big audience like a new
audience is very difficult
when growing process is very slow
uh
if I don't get to be on something big
something on TV or some kind of other
big promotion
yeah it won't grow much more and much
faster so I was I was thinking this
would be like one really really big
chance
and I don't know what else
I could possibly do
to get something like that I need a
scandal
hmm
I don't know man
I obviously I think about that kind of
stuff because I have to
I'm an Entertainer and I make my living
from it so
think about this kind of stuff
I could try to venture out of it and go
like try out streaming on Twitch but did
that help the girls who tried it already
I don't know
have you guys noticed
the whole live girls who tried streaming
on Twitch
them getting a new big audience I I
doubt it right
[Music]
um
so well it's difficult it's so difficult
because we're like in a niche
it's a niche what we're doing
it's not for everyone
[Music]
tick tock
um
I don't have the
mental capacity for that I think at the
moment but
um if I get that motion capture to work
and it looks somewhat decent then I
might try yeah
to do some like dancing stuff
oh yeah yeah I think Marian said fine
yeah she got some reach from that surely
but then again I I still have this
opinion that even if you get famous
within tick tock
Tick Tock users mostly don't care enough
to check out your other social media
some maybe do but not such a big amount
so at least that's what I know and
no
[Music]
Mr Beast video
yeah yeah yeah emphasis on the Creator
on the individual clip yeah
what
[Music]
your ideas are getting out of hand
do a collab with a big YouTuber
who
and what kind of collab
[Music]
um
as if PewDiePie would care about a
collab with me why me why me when it
could be I don't know Cali or so
don't tendons so I don't wanna I don't
know
[Music]
because it's Swedish and it's close to
Austria
don't think
that is a good argument
[Music]
yeah he's in Japan now
he lives in Japan now
he's hanging out with the cool
living in Japan kids I saw that
um
Valkyrie wanted to collab with peckwell
yeah whatever happened with that
I wonder if there's any progress with
that
is there
like tried contacting each other
hmm
[Music]
anyway let's read super jazz
yeah
uh
is
a difficult thing a lot of this has to
do with luck
you know being picked up from the right
person or like right TV or whatever
at the right time
stuff like you know
I'm being mentioned in Korean news you
know stuff like that that's just luck
and a really weird way of gaining a lot
of new fans and a big new audience
opening some doors
foreign
[Music]
but wasn't that the reason why like the
original
the original
the origin
no not really like her being featured
but like something about
her name because they like mixed
something up or so and then people got
curious and they looked into Amelia
Watson and they found her alive and all
that
uh yeah I don't know the exact details
but I think that was something like that
and when I say news I don't mean TV I
mean more like I think written news I
think like articles
um
[Music]
yeah that was just one of those things
like
it's just it's so random and it's luck
and you've got the right people who are
open to that kind of content
hmm
I thought am I was on the Evening News
see something like that would be cool
though I wanna
fight like if if if I were to step out
there into like a media where a lot of
normies would watch me I know it opens
the door to a lot of like
um
normy's hating on YouTubers and me or so
but it would also open the door to a lot
of possible new viewers and eyes and all
that because people like streamers in
general nobody has a problem of
streamers in general streamers are for
everyone they just need to be made aware
of YouTubers and and me and be open for
that so
I don't know I feel like especially if
it was like
maybe a German TV show or so and and
they would be made aware of that an
Austrian girl made it in a big way to
being company and it's now the the
biggest YouTuber in Europe
Maybe
you know that that's like if you
announce it like that and you introduce
me like that then you already like start
off by giving me a cool image and then
maybe normies they look at me and
they're like oh she's not a loser she's
actually doing pretty cool that's
interesting maybe we should support you
know I don't know
of course not everyone will be into it
but you have to try to venture out a
little bit if you want growth
[Music]
I need to be more of a normie I would
say
but I think I'm quite the Normie
don't I seem pretty normal to you um
I'm pretty normal
what
why am I not normal
why am I not normal what makes me not
normal
besides my looks
oh
is it just my looks well that's
discriminating
we can get
beyond that we can we can get people to
look beyond that if they just listen for
a moment
what I I'm so normal compared to
like a lot of other weebs I'm very
normal
laughs
[Laughter]
hardcore I don't fan not anymore I know
I talk about items and stuff but I don't
you know I don't listen to idle music
anymore I don't go to idle concerts
anymore
so like think back on my memories of
that but I don't I'm not an idol otaku
anymore
that is the truth my favorite Idol
groups have all graduated they don't
make music anymore and yeah
when I talk about them I usually talk
about what they used to be and what I
used to do
[Music]
whatever whatever
what is normal anyway that is the right
question to ask
[Music]
what about K-pop Idols oh that my
interest for KFA vitals is really just
superficial I don't even know the names
of all twice members
even though I like their music so much I
really just listen to the music every
now and then and nowadays A lot of
people listen to K-pop even though
they're not like
you know super into Korea or whatever
K-pop has become very mainstream
[Music]
foreign
for the first time oh I think I saw a
picture got plenty of piano fan merch
too artist Ali are the best they had a
lot of koala fan stuff oh man thank you
all for going out to look for that kind
of stuff in Austrian conventions there's
usually just one one single move
one single booth that does that
and has whole life merchandise
oh now I'm starting to feel a little bit
insulted black virgin
that's like years ago and that one extra
year was kind of just actually to close
a chapter
that last working holiday year the
purpose was to close a chapter in my
life so
I don't know man
um
I feel like on the Spectrum from Nomi to
weaboo
I'm closer to Normie than I am the real
book
whatever
Moon frog dance
for the rest of the chat hello my also
just want to say I had a had my birthday
last Thursday the Elena drawing collab
was a great birthday gift love the
artwork you did really happy to spend
another year of my birthday with you in
kfp
thank you
um
yeah
well happy belated birthday
happy belated birthday
foreign
congratulations
I'm a little bit
angry
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday dear DD happy
birthday to you
um
are you here Gingy
[Music]
happy birthday Cindy probably sleeping
are you sleeping I'm gonna visit you I'm
gonna come to you in your dreams I'm
gonna haunt you
speak Kiwa wine your dreams
I'm gonna
cut you open while you're alive and
feast on that sweet sweet chicken meat
[Music]
um
there you are oh thank you my vacation
with mama doing you know I made one
realization my mommy reminded me
she was like Chihuahua
uh our room is like you know just one
room right I'm like yeah but we have to
invest and and then she's like oh I'll
bring you earbuds and I'm like what
and just like because I snore and I'm
like oh [\h__\h]
she didn't want me to say this but
I completely forgot but like she snores
like insanely loudly like I remember
when I still slept in the same roof
under the same roof as my mommy
oh doors had to be closed
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] and hotel rooms are small beds
are closed and yeah earbuds are they're
uncomfortable and they probably won't
help much [\h__\h]
when I realized that I understood that I
will be [\h__\h] tired throughout those
days in
in our trip I will not be able to sleep
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
no I don't snore at all I've Been Told
but many people I don't know
I mean
last time I slept with someone together
in one room was
[Music]
um
Cali
and she did not I think I even asked her
she didn't say I snored nothing she
didn't hear anything
um
maybe only oh oh yeah Elena too later
too yeah they didn't say anything either
if I snowed in maybe only if I had like
a cold like a
big nose problem
well I'm a two yeah maybe I'm it was I I
might have been the lightest it doesn't
matter all of them did not mention I was
snoring
so yeah [\h__\h] I have the problem is like
I I
I have I'm a light sleeper I wake up so
easily and I only fall asleep when
everything is like dead quiet I can not
even sleep like it even bothered me the
other day when I was able to hear the
um
the what do you call it the lift them
what's left on in English from my
bathroom
[Music]
that kept me awake the ventilation yeah
the ventilation from my bathroom
now I had to get up and close the all
the doors so that I wouldn't hear it
[Music]
um
really light sleeper I mean I can fall
asleep
um while I watch TV though weirdly
enough
yeah but there's certain things that
bother me I guess and certain things
that don't bother me TV is fine because
it turns into white noise at some point
it's relaxing
but someone's snoring really loudly is
gonna take all my sleep from me oh man
I forgot if I remembered I would have
booked two different rooms
so [\h__\h]
I wonder if melatonin can help me I feel
like even even then it's gonna be rough
I'll just won't I won't be sleeping
Let's Jam that's for sure
oh it's too late to get separate rooms
it will be extra expensive I'm paying it
all I don't know I'll try my best to
survive
earplugs they're uncomfortable though I
feel like they'll bother me so much and
I I can't sleep well when I have
something on my head
or in my ears
no it's still the same place
yeah well I guess I'll try it here but
um
maybe I'll buy noise
um canceling earphones
but I think they will
like be uncomfortable like I'm a side
sleeper so it will be uncomfortable to
wear them while I'm sleeping
uh
[\h__\h]
oh when I say earbuds I mean just
something you put in your ear to not
hear [\h__\h]
not something that makes music
I'm Loki considering booking another
place like a really cheap ass
shitty place for myself
cheapest I can find
[Music]
[\h__\h]
yeah it's that bad
oh
well
I'll have to think about that
[Music]
oh man
it's just a few hours at night but I
need my sleep otherwise I can't function
anyway thank you GD
thanks for reminding me of that
oh I'll have fun at work good luck
celebrities
[Music]
thank you what's for dinner today
um
I think it was something Mexican
um I forgot what it's called
something with beans
black beans and
um rice
and what else am I putting in there I
forgot
and they gave me no no not burritos but
you could probably fill it into a
burrito but they also gave like tortilla
chips to eat the bean rice stuff with
the totalias tortillas no not tortillas
the crackers chips those chips nachos
nachos
yes
I don't know what it's called again
[Music]
but yeah
I hope it's not spicy
[Music]
yeah um I don't know what it's gonna be
but it looks fairly easy it's a one pot
um recipe
[Music]
tortilla
Martin ate done kitchen for the pinky
thank you I must admit something I
submitted undertale for your gift oh
although it's possible other people also
just did the same I wonder
but yeah you might have been
um the reason why I got that
okay no need to like you know admit it
it's like fine it helps me
I might really play it sometime
I'm not like really um against it didn't
think they would pick it I'm glad they
picked some games because I would say
that's one of my biggest costs uh that I
can't [\h__\h] write off
even though it's a work cost work
related cost
so getting games for free is helpful
thank you
[Music]
oh thank you thank you for the support
yeah breaks or brow bread I don't know
how to say that thank you thank you
has anyone told you your Japanese sounds
more fluently like no no one
not like in particular not compared to
any other time but thank you do you
think so
maybe you were saying that because you
watched me on the official Channel
um yeah yeah at least for that one we
were talking Japanese for like I don't
know two hours so
talking for that long kind of
yeah
gets me back into my game
is there any way to gift Steam games to
talents I don't think so I guess not
I mean oh maybe what you could do
because we accept letters
I wonder perhaps putting a steam card
gift code into a
letter just a code written on a letter
probably could even work
but it would probably arrive like half a
year later
how long are steam Keys uh how long do
they work I'm not sure
it's a genius idea huh
called inspires before it gets there six
months ah yeah I think you know I get
steam codes from from janma and I think
I read that it's like what three months
or how long is it maybe six months is
the expiration date but maybe it depends
maybe you can get some long lasting ones
oh
[Music]
what's geology
oh
thanks for the code right I think so
gift one should be permanent
well
I think there was an expiration date on
the ones I got from General when she
buys them from me
but anyway I mean you're welcome to look
into that
um
for the pinky my mother works as a
cleaning lady so I asked her about the
whole pre-cleaning thing and she
confirmed that most people at least
clean clear out their homes a bit to
make it easier to clean up so I would
say you're good on the front
um
I I think they would appreciate
that yeah
um like at least not having like a
million things scattered all over
because then the cleaning lady will have
to ask for the cleaning staff we'll have
to ask all the time hey where should I
put this where should I put this where
where this does this go and then you're
basically cleaning together at that
point so what did you get the cleaning
person for right so uh that's why I
tried to get the Clutter away first
[Music]
um
no it's not directly gift into my
account
it's steam cards from from the
convenience store
anyway
[Music]
thank you
spending time thank you for the rest of
the chat here's my paycheck buzz you got
some excellent loot I love my robot
little box oh what you have one
did you tell me before the Kato seem to
enjoy it as well did you get a new one
because you get one just now
like recently oh
tell me about it see there's barely
anyone that can do this kind of cat talk
especially not um robot little bugs talk
with
I've noticed I forget to look at my app
to see how full the
the tank the tank is
do forget that huh
but I feel like it's not very accurate
either when it says like so and so many
percent doesn't feel very accurate I was
considering getting one but then I
realized I didn't have a cat
get yourself a cat first
oh so let's keep when you got yourself
one for real from the same brand maybe
even the little box the famous One
nice I'm happy for you that is I think a
really good investment
[Music]
can push a notification
um I don't know if it can do that
it can do a lot of things though
ah take a 14 hour flight to go home with
it and shipping costs
well you should buy it once you're
settled
wherever you're settled
it was a cheaper one but it still helps
no no
[Music]
um
dog owners will never have this luxury
uh well I mean
well if you mean taking the dog out to
do their business outside you don't have
to do that right I've seen people like
literally lay out those light blue
pads all over the [\h__\h] apartment
yeah I've visited
house a house before of someone who kept
several small dogs
not AME
but someone in Japan
and because I know that person or the
family never takes out their dogs for a
walk which
kind of feels like animal abuse but what
do I know
um but like literally never literally
never the whole apartment is filled with
those pads
they always go inside on those pads
yeah and like
most of their dogs were in cages in the
small house for most of the time like
no
I I've been there for a while and they
would not let out certain dogs for weeks
or months
which really
made me question
how the [\h__\h]
can you keep dogs and then so many if
you're if you just gonna keep them in
the cage I don't like having cats or
dogs in the cage I mean for dogs I guess
like at night
some people do that and it makes more
sense than with a cat right I don't I
don't have a dog so I don't know but
yeah I guess I guess it's okay to put
like dogs or even like sleeping in their
cages right but even during the day what
the [\h__\h]
like not letting them out ever
[Music]
yeah yeah dogs like to sleep in crates
yeah I get that I get that but that was
not just that that was like constantly
just living in the cage like as if it's
like a like a shelter
[Music]
um
that dog was like extremely stinky and
traumatized
from like I think I I would assume like
from before like the life they had
before they were adopted or so probably
but this one was not better I would say
every time I would walk by that dog
because they kept that dog in a cage
outside
their house like in the
path to the house you know
every time I would walk by they would
like bark so aggressively
they were like so terrified
of me
and the the dog was like so stinky that
I could smell the dog from
10 meters away
I really felt so sorry for that dog
[Music]
it was not a particularly big cage
um
[Music]
now I don't know that's years ago so I
don't know probably
the dog is probably dead by now
it's so sad it made me really sad too
oh
you work huh you want to shoot at an
animal shelter
sorry sorry sorry
the thing is I I felt like I was not
really in the position to like tell them
how to keep their dogs because they were
supposedly dog breeders
not very active ones
at that but like it seemed like it was
maybe their original occupation or so
[Music]
it's weird because they were really good
really nice people
but I never understood the way they kept
their dogs
yeah
there was one dog that I bonded with a
lot and they would let that dog outside
uh the cage within the house but it was
quite the big dog
but I loved I loved that dog so much and
and she was so happy
sweet dog
and since I knew they never let that dog
outside
I asked to take the dog for a walk once
it was so difficult first of all I never
you know walked a dog before I think
and second of all since the dog that
never gets to go on a walk they were
like really really pulling
so it was so hard to control it was
exhausting
it took a lot of strength the dog was
walking me yeah
but she was so cute I love that dog so
much she made me so happy because that
was at a time where I was really really
really the only
um that was way before my working
holiday when I lived in Japan before
that many years before and I was
I'm kind of depressed and was going for
a really rough time
um and yeah the dog was like every time
I saw the dog I got happy and you know
it gave me
strength that toggle
yeah so I appreciate Douglas for being
such bright sunshines
right they give you so much happiness
because they just they just
their whole aura
is happiness
but it was a bigger dog so you know my
thing is I like I like big dogs but
small dogs they freak me out
they so young
they have big eyes and they look like
their eyes are gonna pop out and they
they are weird they're shaky and
they're weird
I like big dogs
I like big dogs and I cannot lie I don't
like small dogs please no they're so
cute but please don't bother me with
them
I mean people who like small dogs
totally cool and they're cute and all
but I don't I just don't no no no no
um
yeah
crazy Bubba
I'm so funny
uh I I I I I
um I like hearing Bubba in the back of
Amazon's streams every time I hear Bubba
bark
it makes me happy
[Laughter]
I like the yapping it's very cute
I like hearing
Bubba
but
being touched by Bubba
[Music]
or licked by Bubba
you must want to fight fam because we
love all dogs
[Music]
I'm in danger
Chuckles I'm in danger
I am not making any friends here huh
touched by bubbles of godsend
I just want some love yeah yeah yeah
yeah and he will not get it from me
because he has AME and he has Ina and
you know does not need me
it's greedy
so greedy wanting love from everyone
I I I I I I I like the cuddliness and
the happiness of dogs
come on come on don't be full
hmm
[Music]
the cats were a pleasure though
where one side here
One's next RPG long streaming game the
next long streaming game will be in
Pokemon
starts this month
yeah you should know that you know that
and now I'm just kind of trying to
bridge
to that point
I mean actually I
don't know for sure
if we will be able to play it I'm just
assuming
if not then I'll have to find something
else
I will find something
not confirmed
favorite Pokemon from the New Gen I love
all
cute the new Pokemon that were
introduced besides the starters
to me so far all were meh
but I mean they're okay
but nah
oh we went into 5 11 to Tails wow
Fireball yet yes Tails I'm not 100 sure
yet but we'll see
Pokemon Fire Emblem yes
um let's go uh Max Drinker thank you
recently finished 100 entails of the
rest oh presented
what does it mean to 100 Tales of our
eyes holy [\h__\h]
what did you do did you do all side
quests and stuff too damn
I had a great time and I thought I
should tell the Ambassador love you
students and you're burning salt cheers
thank you
wow nice I wonder if you picked it up
because of me or just in general your
tails off fan
but really cool ah collect all hoodles
oh
food was very important
okay I'll get to it
I think I will easily finish it once I
have the steam deck
I really just I don't the thing is like
when I feel like Tales of playing a
Tales of arise I don't I never feel like
playing it on my PC you know I want to
play it comfortably in my bed
but I have it on Steam
so
right I played it on Steam as far as I
remember
um so you know I I'm I really want to
play on my steam deck in my bed like now
that I'm not streaming it if I could
stream it I would have finished it a
million years ago on stream but yeah
I uh
[Music]
was it PS4 what what
huh
[Music]
I don't know there wasn't reason why I
did not like play it
yeah the PS5 arrived way later so it's
not that it was not because uh uh
five
maybe it was PS4 nah
I feel like I played on Steam
oh maybe it was PS4
[Music]
maybe I'll play it on PS4 I said playing
on PS4 I said I said so
oh
what
I must have mixed something up what the
[\h__\h]
okay I'm confused um anyway good job
I'll finish it within this year I
promise
especially long tonight when I woke up
and looked at myself in the mirror I
found that I had become a bucket that
had never happened to me in a whole year
at kfp I hope I at least look
mouth-watering have a great Saturday so
today hmm
you look
juicy
juicy butt juicy chicken butt yum yum
yum
thank you for being a member for so long
and supporting me for so long now your
bucket but it's not over yet
so
stay tight continue watching
yeah
stay delicious thank you so much
I will haven't watched got because I
haven't finished the books yet I wonder
if he will ever finish those
I watched an interview of him and yeah
he seems to be working on it
um
[Music]
done with the Chit Chat super chats
mm-hmm
you started for 10 years but he just
finished
painting a book and released it so hey
there's hope he's getting things crossed
off on his list
right
four blood
super chattels really quick before I go
because it's
um half past uh 11 and I need to cook
[Music]
he's just procrastinating
how do you know you have cameras
installed in his home
and even if he is then you know I don't
think he's doing it on purpose he
probably just really needs like you know
inspiration like you know writer's block
is a serious thing and you don't want to
just like
write whatever and throw it out there
just for the sake of throwing it out
there
and yeah Game of Thrones is one of those
kind of like big universes where you
have to think about all kinds of
storylines intertwining and so many
characters and their backstories it's
not an easy thing to write
um
oh yeah and he writes very slowly and
yeah he's a perfectionist yeah and
just in general like I I had the same
thing with art like every artist can
agree that there is also an art block
thing and
just sometimes you just you just can't
be creative
and I feel like for writing that's even
more a thing and even more difficult
[Music]
so I know for fans it's really rough to
wait
oh but well it is what it is
um
[Music]
15 years of right block well it's not
like he was not doing anything in those
15 years
I don't know I haven't been following it
so closely like I got into Game of
Thrones when the show came out like a
few seasons in
so I haven't been following the process
that much but I mean he was working on
stuff like element ring too right
another thing surely so
and what do we know what he's doing
behind the scenes he surely has been
trying to write things and then maybe
scrap scraps them again and stuff
and also he must have like a lot of
pressure and expectations on him
um
and that's difficult to work with too
thank you for the rest of the chat blood
Super Chat for lady Kiara since pretty
concert I really love your performance
of the song glad to finally have your
cover happy Halloween and also
congratulations to our Challenger
reached 2 million oh yeah right thank
you guys for listening to Heart
Challenger and for listening to four
blocks thank you
happy Halloween and thank you Skye I'm
glad you liked the cover you probably
did and thanks for the blood blood for
the blood Phoenix
thank you
Jacob 47 ounce for the rest of the test
as well for blood hype yay thank you for
supporting the cover yeah
I hope you all are enjoying it I really
really like this properly produced
version I think it sounds really really
good
[Music]
it's a freaking banger
so please continue listening to it
[Music]
thank you James Jackson thank you so
much
[Music]
evil dance
at how good this is here's my blood take
it all
if you give it to me so easily then I
don't even have to come for your blood
huh
then the song makes no sense don't give
it to me don't offer it to me
the the song will be useless
I have to comfort it on my own
I'm coming for blood
[Music]
let me fight for it
let me take what belongs to me
thank you though
[Music]
thanks for the pinky yo mate amazing for
blood cover we know it's a bloody Ripper
but damn I'll be living this together
with your other songs you should as you
should thank you so much I think it fits
right in there in the kiwawa music
playlist
um
it matches well especially like with
Sparks I think hell yeah
thank you for listening
Jim Tracy fans with a pinky absolutely
fantastic cover the Envy is great and
you absolutely rocked it thank you thank
you glad you enjoyed it
you know I would I wanted to implement
um 3D so I asked orina like is it
possible to somehow implement the 3D
scenes and yeah
um I wanted the the move from the
A Chorus included for sure
um just made sure that that was in there
yeah it's
um
not like definitely not the focus of it
but yeah you know the thing is like I I
commissioned art for it and then mixing
that with that was difficult I had like
to think about
if that even works well together so we
had to find a compromise but if you want
to see me dancing well you can just
watch the archive of my pretty birthday
the one the mastered version if anything
while you're at it
thank you
soon
celery beans thank you thank you for the
pinky holy you and Kayla worked up some
blood magic of Discovery I really like
the rendition of format during the
concert but boy this was really
something else and that outfit is just
absolutely emotori hot hot thank you for
the cover yeah it's a good design right
when I was thinking of who I want to get
um to draw me some art for four blood I
was looking for an artist that has
a style that's not so cute but more on
the edgy side and Bebe was perfect for
it yeah
I found
[Music]
um my choice pretty fast pretty easily
yeah
and baby designed some cool outfit
as well
it's quite edgy it kind of has like
scene golf
check out the anime convention vibes
yeah I like what they came up with
[Music]
yeah that's um as close to emotori as
you will ever get possibly
so enjoy it even has a lip piercing
damn girl what a rebel she's such a
rebel that koala is such a rebel music
[Music]
um
foreign
what did I say
[Music]
and did I not say tongue piercing
what did I say
what's that tongue piercing I said live
what the [\h__\h] I'm
I'm confused I don't even have lips
oopsie I mean tongue piercing it looks
very painful
bruh
I love the way baby draws eyes it's so
pretty oh I like it I really like the
art
um
okay okay I'm done reading those thank
you very much and that was the last one
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you guys thank you
I am going to cook something now I guess
hopefully
it will be easy
and fast
thank you for watching today we'll
finish lunch's Mansion free on Sunday
and don't forget I'm changing it's like
to spy her to entropy Center
unfortunately I messed up
um foreign
a week later and yeah tomorrow I want to
get a massage yes
massage and
I was gonna do something else too I
forgot
them
[Music]
I'm not gonna put out an updated
schedule nah you guys will see you guys
know you guys know and everyone else
will see when the time comes
shopping
is it the place of the cats um no
that place does not exist anymore I
think
I was told the last time that
you know they're leaving the country
I wonder what it was hmm oh well didn't
you say you want to sleep early
ah today not necessarily not so
important
[Music]
anyway thank you so much
oh Luigi
I'm hooked on the game
oh man
I'll miss Luigi I can't wait until
Sunday Luigi
[Music]
bye bye
another half hours wow even longer than
yesterday damn
[Music]
foreign