[Music]
hey guys
emmy please tell me you can hear me
[Music]
hello
oh wait it's still set to 480p oh wait
one second
[Music]
okay oh my god
[Laughter]
guys you have no idea how [\h__\h]
complicated my setup is right now
i hate it it's ridiculous hello everyone
hello
you guys hear me well because i'm having
some
issues here a lot of issues a lot
if you guys refresh it could be
available for a
1080p again um
i just changed the we did this because
last time i had like a really bad
internet connection
so i had to uh oh my god
uh different microphone no
i didn't no
yeah if something is wrong i don't
understand
what it is
um something is wrong with my
4xlr
sounds different i just coming out yeah
ryan i'm [\h__\h] hell why is it doing
that
what about now
hello is it better i
it okay okay but i still have another
problem i have a lot of problems right
now
um okay at least you guys hear me i
don't hear myself for some reason
i don't hear any audio at all for some
reason and you guys have no idea how
freaking complicated youtube is being
to me right now um absolutely
unbelievable
but hey i'm streaming you guys i am
on my pc i i i uh i'm streaming with obs
but youtube won't let me
open my streaming uh
interface on youtube on my pc
it will let me open it on my laptop
though so i
am connected on lbs on my pc
but i pressed start stream on in youtube
on my laptop do you understand i'm using
two pcs right now
because youtube is being a freaking uh
i don't understand i've tried so many
things ever since i came to
australia youtube is like trying to
boycott me or something and i've been
shadow banned for the last
what is it one week or something now
yeah at least it's working but the thing
is my laptop is now the one which is
connecting me to youtube but my laptop
is only connected for wi-fi while my pc
is connected for
actual cable so i'd prefer if everything
went for my pc right now
but hey my pc works
my pc works can you believe it
for the people who have somehow missed
out on it
uh
i uh had to kind of like keep
up on like yeah well done if i helped me
she took apart my pc and we packed it
and
uh put it in like a box that it came
with originally
and we filled in like a [\h__\h] ton of
towels and all that kind of stuff
oh my god youtube
wow what's going on with the
the viewer account is so bugged
what the hell i want to cry [\h__\h] you
youtube what the hell
it's ridiculous why
do you guys hear me still is am i still
am i still moving
stream died for a second yeah i don't
know what the hell is going on
it's because i have to connect to
youtube on my laptop it's ridiculous
i'm so mad i just want to have a happy
stream with you guys
talking about what happened um but
youtube doesn't want me
but i'll try i'll try let's see let's
see how far we get
yeah it keeps decreasing it's like
oh my god that's me maybe now it's going
up again
ah anyway so i'm gonna i'm gonna tell
you about
uh yeah i know i'm shadow band i know
you don't have to tell me i freaking
know
thank you youtube i want to tell you
guys about
the whole whole whole
trip from japan to australia
how about your cats my cats are
so sweet they're like on my my bed is
right next to my table
and they're like sitting there and just
chilling
now they're they're right next to me
basically
and just chilling i i spent the whole
night with them
and yeah spoiler alert but they love me
again as if that one year it didn't even
happen
me being gone just never happened
um wait a second
wait a second oh
okay by the way you guys also hear me
jam right you should be hearing it
oh this is guys this is the first time
someone from whole life
streams from europe first time
so where are my european bros at where
are they i mean
this time should also be quite
acceptable or acceptable for japanese
viewers and maybe even for american
viewers
but uh yeah
i'm finally here you finally have uh
someone
on in your continent finally
you've waited so long here i am i hope i
hope i'm good enough for you guys
i hope when i stream at these times it
should be good for my japanese viewers
as well
but when i stream at european prime time
in the evening then that might be
pretty bad for my japanese viewers oh
well
well everyone please share the stream
everywhere you can because i'm so sick
of being shadow band for the past few
days
and i i just don't understand i didn't
it's not only my
like previously it was always that my
streams were uh every now and then
shadow band but now the whole channel is
shadow band so
you guys don't get notifications you
guys thank you for coming though
you've made it you've made it for some
reason
youtube wanted to stop you guys youtube
didn't want you to watch his stream but
you made it anyway
thank you yeah
i shared it on twitter but not everyone
not everyone on youtube
checks twitter so hmm that's that and i
tried to write a community a community
community community notification but
i'm not sure if that actually really uh
did something
you know also i wrote on on reddit in
the hopes that the reddit people
will find me
what wait
do you think it's because of the polls
you know that was supposed
i only did it because you guys said some
of you guys said
that it will help my algorithm because
right now if you post polls on your
youtube community board
then oh it will increase your algorithm
so so so much because youtube loves
polls pause post polls and then
then i was like yeah but if i sent four
at once
wouldn't that make youtube think i'm a
spammer
wait when did the shadow ban start was
it maybe it was really because of the
polls
because i posted four polls i always i
was hesitant
to do it but you guys were like uh i was
shadow man before that really
ah changing thumbnails that no but but
the waiting room
stream has been was like
okay it could have been many things i
think like this the waiting room stream
was like shadow band since the beginning
but the
thumbnail changing could maybe have been
a reason
why did you post full polls because i
wanted to know what you guys think
which fandom is what uh
browser
welcome back thank you i have uh finally
come back to australia and europe
waiting room wasn't shadow band
i mean it was it was shadow bent later
on definitely i don't know if it was
from the beginning
maybe not it was before the polls
it was before the pulse but the polls
happened before the waiting room
i don't even know but the fact is
that besides being shadow band youtube
uh
is giving me huge issues with logging
into
my account and i don't know they just
they're trolling me
so bad it's it's i'm so mad
so mad
anyway let me tell you about everything
that happened
let me let's let's try to you know
uh have a good time
oh yeah i know i know nina streamed on
my channel by mistake you think that's
the reason
could that be a reason i don't think so
i don't think so
but we are we have contacted youtube um
but you know they're probably gonna take
uh about one year to fix it
um yeah or are they never gonna fix it
yeah who knows
[Music]
i just don't get it i just still get it
okay whatever
so uh i
as you guys know i've been living in
japan for
the past one year
and that was planned to be one year from
the beginning i wasn't
i wasn't thinking about extending it i
just wanted to
do this one year um i've lived in japan
before that
and so it's not only that one year it's
if you
add it all together it's been a couple
of years
and i just felt like it's time to
you know end it
i i felt like um
i did what i had to do not exactly i
wanted to do so many things this year
but i couldn't
but that's not something i can do
anything about and i've wasted my visa
which i can never use again ever
because it's a one once in a lifetime
visa working holiday visa
so i can't get that ever again so that
was a good use of a once in a lifetime
visa definitely
um sorry i'm extremely salty
i'm in a really salty mood
[Music]
but yeah um thankfully thankfully to her
life
i found something that
gives me the the opportunity to deal
with this
pretty frustrating fact that i wasted my
visa
and so everything's cool and
one year has passed the the months that
i was
um after i joined her life the time has
passed so quickly it's
it's quite crazy um
yeah the timeline has been has passed so
so so so fast
especially the last two to three months
it flew so fast yeah because like i
actually finally had something to do
every day i
i i was like streaming every day all day
and like making a weekly schedule
really made the weeks go by so fast
because i was always like planning ahead
planning ahead planning ahead doing
something doing something
so yeah um the past
few days were really really stressful
because planning or like doing the whole
moving from continent to continent
once again was very stressful but this
might have been the most
difficult ever like i've moved between
australia and japan many times but
never had i have to do so
many administrational things and
never had i ever had to
take care of so many um personal
belongings like luggage and all that and
pc sending a pc over to
australia and all that kind of stuff um
it was it was quite
a difficult move yeah and yeah of course
uh the
the sea made it even more difficult as
well yeah
i had to do a test before i left uh
which obviously was uh negative
that was fun i i did a little a little
test the one
with uh the spit the spit test i did
that one
uh and uh i had to
do all kinds of administrational stuff
yeah go to the municipal
municipal office and all that kind of
stuff yeah
i did a lot of things before i left so
the
few days before uh i think i guess like
during the waiting room was open and all
that
um those few days i was very busy but i
tried to still
um be active for you guys i i uploaded a
new video
and sheep as in continuation to m frog
and m crowl uh but it seems like many of
you have not seen it because of the
freaking shadow ban uh like
barely barely anyone from my subscribers
has seen it because it didn't show up in
the subscription box
and so that's rude okay
i i prepared it so that i would have
something to upload while i was flying
in the airplane i suck but you guys you
guys even made it to the stream so yeah
i think many of you guys saw it but
um oh yeah
i think many of you guys saw it but but
yeah
[Music]
maybe i should also upload i'm cheap
like the notification on reddit maybe
that will help
[Music]
it and who's also here yeah so
anyway um i had like
so so so so so so so much luggage
to bring over i i told you guys in my
maybe was that in my members only stream
maybe i i sent like eight packages or so
um buffering
are we back okay yeah um
pretty pretty annoying i sent like eight
packages to
australia beforehand uh sometime
like last week on tuesday actually yeah
i sent a lot of packages now that alone
was extremely expensive
to ship oh my god
that was a big surprise but
yeah moving from continent to continent
ain't gonna be cheap
right have you guys ever done that
before
have you guys ever moved from one
continent to another one
you're not gonna change
most people probably haven't
believe me it's not not a lot of fun
it's very complicated
[Music]
yeah so anyway my pc
however i did not send it i i brought it
with me to the airport in a box as
extra luggage so i i uh
i got myself extra luggage i was like i
had like two
huge suitcases which could
probably fit cali in
there somehow could in theory but i
didn't
i didn't do it two huge suitcases
and one big box with a pc inside
and a small suitcase for hand luggage
and bag
so i was like packed with so much
luggage
the casper come i don't think so
i don't think so even if he came then my
cats probably already
ate him
so a pc
i was so very worried about it when the
when when i was paying for it and they
they put like one they put one sticker
on it like
uh caution
breaks easily what what do you call that
what do you call that
what's the actual word for that uh
like some kind of caution sticker you
know he's
a fragile thank you thank you
carlos and fragile and i put one sticker
on it i was like
sorry could you could you maybe like
spare like a few more stickers and put
them on it
on the box because it was like a tiny
ass sticker i was like please please put
more on that please
so he put like five more on it like
per side one each
the stickers got ignored anyways yeah
but i don't know i felt like that was
the least we could
you put like this tiny sticker on it i
was like sorry
dude i think i think they will ignore it
if there's only ones they won't even see
it
and he was like yeah you're probably
right
so he was so kind to put a few more
stickers on there i didn't i didn't even
have to pay extra for their stickers
well so yeah and then um
by the way my my manager
was with me and yeah
manager's son helped me so much because
i i
i walked this whole situation this whole
moving situation
i would have gone insane
and fallen apart if it wasn't for genma
my manager if it wasn't for her
i don't know what i would have done oh
my god fool
[Music]
she is an angel yeah
yeah i want to say a big thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
unfortunately she couldn't fly with me
but she also yeah accompanied me to um
the airport
and at the airport
uh we we we were there pretty late we
wanted to have like one last
dinner but everything was closed it was
like
around midnight and everything every
restaurant closes
at 8pm in japan at the moment
because of raisins so we had like a
convenience store dinner
[Music]
in the lobby but it was yummy it was
pretty good
that was pretty good
probably the most fitting last dinner
maybe
did kelly come with you no she didn't no
no she uh unfortunately she did she
didn't but i mean it was pretty late so
it's okay it's okay um
it was it was a miniature sun
only
[Music]
and then then oh my god the airport was
so empty
oh the airport uh i was like in in
um should i say that i don't know
maybe not the airport was anyway so
empty
and like
i literally needed like
barely like i didn't i didn't even have
to like stand in line for a security
check
or or a luggage uh thingy
or anything at all i didn't have to
stand in line ever like
not even for boarding ghost airport
yeah especially at that time um there's
there's two
airports in like tokyo i mean nadita
isn't really in tokyo but let's say that
is like
i mean that's that's an airport where
most people fly to when they want to go
to tokyo
but most flights are being handled in
hanada
at the moment and even then hanada was
freaking dead like
barely any people at all thank you guys
for the super chats thank you
yeah pretty empty spooky it was it was
just very weird because i've
i've never really i guess i have like
when we went to hokkaido we also went by
airplane
and no actually
it was fuller back then but that was
like
uh like travel inside
the country so uh
i guess more people more japanese people
travel inside the country rather than
traveling outside of the country yeah
that's yeah
that was where it was really really
empty she
oh yeah so i had to get like uh
like the test and the pre-travel
clearance
beforehand and um i had to get like a
special mask
as well not because of the flight from i
had to i had to do a stop
in between my flight it was not a direct
flight so it was not for the flight for
from from japan on and but for the
flights to australia
that for that one i had to get a special
mask because in
in australia they only accept specific
yeah ffp2 masks
so i had to get those one in beforehand
which were actually pretty difficult to
get
in the in the country of masks japan
like
you can get masks ever since before the
current situation
you could have gotten them everywhere in
convenience stores supermarkets
everywhere
right but ffp2 masks i felt nowhere i
had we had to order them
on um online um
pretty interesting yeah they have some
standards yeah only ffp2 masks
let me drink some water i'm getting
really uh my fruit is getting really dry
oh
my cats no my cats do not have the hair
a mask
[Music]
we weren't even allowed to board the
plane
with a normal mask it had to be that
specific mask like
uh when i was like waiting i i already
had it because i was well prepared
i didn't think they would already need
it for the flight i only thought they
needed once i arrived in the country
but i only needed it for the flight so
when i was standing in line some people
that were also standing in line they
didn't have
that mask they were just wearing a
normal mask
because in the in the transit country it
was okay
but not in the country of uh arrival uh
or like the the the the the
gold country so
the the staff the airline staff were
like hey we won't let you in unless you
get that special mask
so then someone was like some people
were really nice and were giving out
some of the leftover ffp2 masks that
they had that was pretty sweet
yeah that was pretty sweet they were
getting out there
a destination country thank you i cannot
speak english obviously
okay you know what i just realized i
need to put something on my on my amazon
uh cart i need to buy a humidifier
oh my god my throat hurts
the air in here is for some reason
pretty dry i need a humidifier oh my god
shadow band yes i am as per usual
when do we get kfp masks ah that's a
that's a good idea but they had they had
masks merchandise for bloom for the
concert
and i thought those are really adorable
but it would
in order for me to be able to actually
make use of my own merchandise it would
have to be a kfb
ffp2 oh wait kffp2 masks smart
oh my god oh my god kffp2 masks
let's do it
i like that idea
[Music]
my cats are just sleeping it's so cute
so yeah where was i oh yeah so we got
into the plane um
i i got myself a premium economy seat
and i was so tired oh my god
it was like aft my flight was uh
oh yeah that was that was in still in
japan yeah
the longer flight i had premium economy
for the
for the longer flight it was it was
pretty good
[Music]
it was pretty damn good i slept so
well and the flight was so empty
i felt like in business class there was
only one person sitting and in premium
economy there was like three people
sitting
and even an economy there was like like
maybe
an economy there was like maybe 20 20
people sitting
at the most economy
right
but i was like hey at least there's some
people sitting on there
um at least some people
but like especially now since i think
japan
at the moment um doesn't even allow uh
uh like normal tourists to enter in the
country you could only be in japan if
you have like
some kind of you know special visa like
a working visa or something
so whenever i see like foreigners in
that situation in japan or
in the flight in that situation i always
wonder like what
what were they here for what did they do
in
in japan i wonder and why are they going
home what what happened
were they here working what kind of job
did i do i look at them and i'm like
um this person looks like they i don't
know maybe they did some kind of sports
or something
pretty interesting yeah to think about
what all those people
were doing in japan yeah i i wonder
about their stories
they were all youtubers with you and no
i don't think
the airplane food was okay thanks for
asking was it was okay
and um seats were pretty comfortable and
i watched i watched
i watched one movie i watched uh
uh from disney i watched uh
what wait what's the exact title the
princess and the frog
or or something like that
uh it's a it's a hand drawn not not
animated
i mean i guess it is animated but it's
like how do you call that
it's not 3d it's the
princess and the frog is that the title
i watched that one i never watched that
one before
oh so i watched that and then later i
also watched some episodes of the office
there's this last two that was the last
2d animation movie of disney
do they never do 2d ever again
never
[Music]
yes i did
and they shut down the studio are they
never gonna do
2d ever again i i feel like it would be
nice to have a 2d movie every once in a
while why does everything have to be
like 3d style
um oh well
yeah this good guy is the specifics
there
how's your jet lag actually i'm
completely fine um
i woke up like at 9 00 a.m something i i
had my alarm for later but i woke up
earlier and my cats were like
and wanted lots of cuddles so i was like
okay i'll give you cuddles my babies
but cute babies
fruity is faster and cheaper now really
fruity oh yeah okay faster i guess yeah
i guess so oh
so yeah anyway
i was sleeping very safe and sound
and then i got off in
my country of transit and
oh it was so early it was like so early
that it was like super the airport was
super
empty so i thought it was like just
generally empty but later
after a few hours passed uh the airport
was getting more and more full
so i realized okay
it's i guess a lot of people are using
this airport
it was way it was like a lot of people
in that airport but that airport is like
very much used for traveling around
europe right now because there's i guess
not many direct flights and stuff
so yeah
after a while i finally boarded my last
flight
did you bring souvenirs no i actually
didn't really
i didn't have time and and the space in
my suitcase in the end so
i i brought myself okay
so yeah then i i boarded the next flight
and i
i played um animal crossing and uh mario
kart i played a lot of mario kart on my
second flight
i was pretty good on mario kart on my
flight i was doing a pretty damn good
job i feel like i
improved a little bit
yeah of course i brought the bracelet
but that's not a souvenir for someone
else that's
just how is that a souvenir
why are you doubting me i really got
better i really got better
i will prove it to you guys i will prove
it
so yeah and then yeah i got off in
australia
and that's where it got a little bit
interesting um
[Music]
they yeah we we got off
like really slowly like they wanted to
let everyone
out like like like only a few rows
at a time only a few seats at a time
so that they could like check everyone i
guess
so we so we slowly uh
left the plane and then we all had to
present our like pre-travel clearance
and the
negative
i don't want to say it i mean i i i i
guess i could say it if i wanted to but
i
i i think it's probably better to not
say the word so i'm trying to not say it
papers please that's exactly what i was
feeling like i was like i was looking at
the
the counter and i was like that looks
like papers please
oh i wonder if corona
senpai has some issues because of that
because like
if if there's really some kind of voice
recognition of saying that word
then wouldn't she have issues by saying
her
own name and and youtube recognizing it
as that word
or i mean it really sounds a lot like
that word
she did before she had issues with it
for months what really
did what oh my god how did it resolve
though what the hell
oh my god
are you for real she did what did she
get shadow vandal what happened
[Music]
today
she wrote nice things to youtube
[Music]
oh
i oh they had she had weird ads oh no
if that's all that that that wasn't okay
everybody ever had a youtube disclaimer
about this
thing oh my god
oh man i mean i get that because i mean
the name really sounds similar but
damn damn
see everyone has their issues with
youtube it seems
oh my god
she lost and revenue because of
misinformation
about the sea thing even though it had
nothing to do with the scene
what what what what for real oh my god
that's so effed up what
for real though oh my god that makes me
so mad
oh my god that is
so bothersome
oh my god
my baby is making cute sleeping sounds
she was like
[Music]
that's the sound you just made
all right so continuing yeah yeah i went
through
went through that process of um
of of uh yeah getting
the documents checked everything was
cool i went through there
uh oh in one second other people other
people didn't even prepare the
pre-travel clearance and had to write it
at the spot
i was like why did you guys not prepare
it beforehand
that's like were you supposed to do that
but i guess maybe
many of them didn't know
but how at these times you have to
inform yourself
about what you need to get to a certain
country
you should inform yourself seems like
lazy travelers i i think yeah i think
probably a lot of them
were indeed lazy travelers and just knew
they had to do something like that but i
didn't do it but
like i would be scared that if i didn't
prepare it i didn't know that you could
do it at the spot as well i would be
scared that i wouldn't be able
to get in there at all like get in
trouble or something for not registering
myself or like
have it take like ages but yeah i did it
online beforehand so
it was easy i got through like instantly
and they only looked at my
my c uh test like one second and that
was it
and then then i
i was at the luggage thingy
and oh my god so in in japan i still had
my manager help me with
all the luggage right but but here i was
um on my own at first so i had to get
one of these luggage carts and even on
the luggage cart
after stacking all my luggage on top of
each other
it was bigger than myself
yeah anyway i was waiting for my luggage
and i got okay suitcase number one okay
cool
i put it on my i put it on my thingy on
my cart
okay suitcase number two comes i'm like
okay cool i put it on my cart okay
okay and then i'm waiting i'm waiting
i'm waiting
i'm waiting but my pc is just not coming
i'm like what the hell there's no new
luggage coming in
it's only the suitcases that are already
on the
under on the on the rolling thing where
is my pc i was like
what's going on where is my pc
where is my pc it's
i was like panicking i was like i was
getting like real mad i was like oh my
god
[\h__\h] sasuka something had to get lost
now huh
why does it have to be the pc oh my god
so i panicked and i i
i was like i was panicking but then
then i was like wait wait
ah i realized
that it might be yeah somewhere else
because it was kind of big that it
didn't even fit
through the the normal like luggage
thing at way at the check-in counter
so it was fragile so i thought like
maybe it's somewhere else so i looked
over
um at the other side of the the hall and
yeah it was in the oversized
luggage uh thingy yeah
i was so relieved
[Music]
it was it was either because it was too
big or because it was too fragile so
they
had it uh somewhere else so then i got
my
my pc thankfully and i put it on on top
of my
luggage uh mountain and then my luggage
mountain was completed and it was bigger
than myself
and i rolled it outside and
uh yes then i was uh
uh driven
driven dro driven i think driven i was
driven
back home and i was like oh my god
this looks so weird it's so weird to be
back home for the first time
in one year
it was so weird thank you for the super
chats by the way everyone thank you
one thing that i like uh also noticed
is that in in australia compared to
japan
there's like way way way
way less hand disinfection
thingies but i haven't really been
around much i only was at the airport
and well at home so i guess i can't
really judge
my friends told me that like in in
restaurants and supermarkets and all
that
there should be this hand sanitizers in
like in the in the entrance but like if
i judge
just by the airport then i can say that
um yeah japanese airport had way more
hand sanitizers so i think it will be
like a general
thing in australia that they just don't
have
so many um as many like
hand sanitizers as japan does but yeah
maybe they could maybe they could step
up their game i don't know
i feel like that might be uh a good idea
[Music]
hmm
yeah the only thing that was like really
strict is just you know
having the correct mask but
like like in the airplane at least and
in the airport and all that
but the mask like i have to wear it
because i'm in quarantine
um i had to wear the whole flight
but like
once i'm out of quarantine and if i just
walk around in the city
then you don't have to wear the mask
unless you go
into like a supermarket or you go into
the the bus or something
for those kind of situations then you
have to uh
wear a mask this stream isn't showing on
my subscription page
how did you get here by the way but yeah
i'm shadow band yes
my streams don't show up anywhere
my channel doesn't even show up anywhere
it's absolutely ridiculous so guys
i will post by the way i will post the
weekly schedule today
i think and please check it out and
and you you will probably not get
notifications and i will probably not
show up in your subscription box
so please read it a lot of people came
from reddit thank you guys
please for for the coming few days
please
check my twitter and check my weekly
schedule
to stay on top of when i'm streaming i
would really appreciate it because it
absolutely sucks to be
like cut off from everyone on youtube
and not everyone checks twitter and not
everyone checks reddit so
please share it with like people who
watch all live
you know to to not have them miss out
like it makes me sad too like
i wanna i wanna have everyone watch my
streams everyone who usually watches
them but
i feel like a lot of people are missing
out on it right now
[Music]
so yeah uh yeah as i said i will post a
schedule
uh later today so that you guys can all
um see what's gonna happen next week um
yeah so back on topic
the i i arrived
home my my room
i'm living with a roommate uh who
i've lived with before before i left
japan
and uh we lived together for like a year
and my cats i had before that like okay
uh throwback time about something you
guys don't have any idea at all
i got my cats three years ago i
started raising them in a in with like
like in an apartment where i lived with
another roommate because like
whenever i moved to the city i just had
absolutely no money i prefer to live
alone but i had no money so i had
to you know get like a place with uh
with someone
with a roommate and um
[Music]
so i was living there but i got myself
cats and
i was basically taking care of the cats
all on my own um the roommate
we never really even like had
conversations
it was it was quite chill honestly i
prefer it that way i didn't have a
problem with that like
it was a living arrangement with like
absolutely no interactions
we would never do anything ever together
[Music]
so yeah i got my cats and um i
i was living in that apartment for like
a year or something and while i was
living
there i made friends with someone
uh who i'm currently living with
and she was looking for uh
kind of looking for a roommate and
so i was like hey i want to move out of
the current place because it's pretty
far away from my workplace
and this one is closer and it's uh kind
of cheap
was it cheaper i think it was a bit
cheaper maybe
but yeah i just wanted to i prefer to
look live with
her because i just kind of liked her a
lot and so yeah i moved in here
um and at the time when my cats were i
think one year old
and then i lived here for another year
so my cats were two years
old when i left the country
to come to japan for one year so so yes
yes
and i talked to her about it like back
then i was like
hey i need to do something
i need to use the working holiday visa
which i can do only one time in a life
and time and i just really have to do it
to get some stuff done
you know it feels like whenever i left
japan the last time
it just feels like i left so many things
undone
and unfinished and it just didn't feel
right for me and it was an
extremely hard decision because first i
wanted to bring my cats with me
but after a lot of um picked the perfect
year to stay in japan huh
uh-huh exactly
yeah and i wanted to bring my cats with
me at first and i
i thank you taka roommate
we do get along pretty well yeah um
or what was i saying ah
i wanted to bring my cats but after a
lot of um
research i realized it's it's the best
idea to
keep them here and that was
that was so hard for me the cats that
i've raised alone
for the past two years who've grown so
attached to me
and i've grown so it has to happen to
them i really needed them they were like
like an absolute blessing for me like i
felt really lonely before i got my cats
and after getting them
it really helped me so much they're like
literally my babies to me they feel like
they're like human babies that for
people who i'm saying that for people
who don't understand
how how strongly you can grow attached
to uh a pet
especially if you don't have like if
there's if it's a family pet okay that's
that might be even more different
because these pets i've been raising
them
all on my own they're mine
there's not like a mom and a dad and a
sister and a brother and all that who
all live together with those pets no
that's that's another thing that
you can also grow very cost attached to
them as well
but in this situation it's only me and
my two baby cats do you baby talk to
them yes i do very much
family pat is different than having your
own pets and being
being the only person who raises them
especially like
with i have i have these two cats and
one of them
had like in the first week like i think
on the second day
after i got here i had to bring her to
the
um emergency uh emergency um
pet hospital because some stuff happened
and um yeah i just i just
i i feel very very protective of my
babies
and it's like i just i just
i i i baby them so much like i'm like
constantly
constantly cuddling them constantly
touching them
constantly carrying them around
constantly
you know just being being a really
really really
needy mom
and they sleep with me in my bed every
night
every night and when i get up they
follow me everywhere
they they're very nice to strangers as
well
but they know who their mama is
and they cherish me so much and i
cherish them so much like they're
they're my my babies i love them so much
you have no idea
i love them i'm so clingy i'm so clingy
to them
i love them so yeah
leaving them here was
one of the hardest things i've ever done
if not
the hardest thing ever ever ever
i felt so bad about it i felt like a bad
mom
and like i'm like that kind of person
like
when someone gets a pet and then like
doesn't really think about taking care
about them and then gives it away or
treats it badly and then
like i don't know like gives it away
after one month or something i'm just
like what the [\h__\h]
like yeah i just don't understand how
people cannot properly take
care of their pets or like not think
about it
before actually getting them so when i
had to leave my pets
here i felt so guilty and i was like
i was like i'm so selfish for doing this
but um i i did want to
like consider the fact that number one
they
um the roommate who take and took care
of them
also knew them for one year and the
place that they were living in
didn't change they stayed in the same
apartment
as they did before for for one year so
at least like the environment didn't
change
much except for me yeah being gone and i
wanted to visit them
a lot of times during this one year i
was planning to visit them
in one year like at least three times no
matter
if it would cost me a lot of money i was
gonna come here so often
gosh my it's so dry in here my throat is
dying
air oh my babies look so cute
they're so cute you're sleeping oh
babies anyway
yeah so i couldn't visit them when i was
i remember one year ago when i went
got into the taxi when i got into the
taxi and my friends
my friend and my roommate my best friend
and my roommate there were with me
they were with me do you have a
humidifier i don't but i'm gonna buy one
today
on amazon yeah um
when i was in the taxi oh my god
i was crying so much i
was i was crying
so much i remember i remember the day
when i left
that was that was so hard i felt so bad
i really didn't want to leave
but i felt like i just had to do this
you know
this this was like i knew that i had to
do this and it was like i couldn't do it
later
my my cats would live for like let's say
another 10 years
so and the older um i get i mean
obviously i'm eternal and all that but
still i should do it forever the things
that i wanted to do i was like i gotta
do it now rather than later
it's now or never you know and it's just
like i came to the conclusion
if i don't do it now or if i don't do it
at all i would
i would always regret it and
[Music]
but it hurt me so much to leave my cats
because they were
my my everything they were
the only important thing for me and like
even now
when when i was thinking about leaving
japan again once again that was
difficult to me because i met so many
people again in japan and i see all
these opportunities in japan
but but my cats are like
the most important thing to me it's so
ridiculous probably for people who don't
have pets or
who do have them but don't feel that
attached to them but like
to me it's like they're my babies
they're my responsibility
and and i love them and and i want to be
where they are at
um even if the country isn't like
um as great as i mean i have to say
australia
it does it does uh have um
a lot of uh upsides
for for me but i mean japan also has a
lot of good size
um
so yeah i i really had to
come back you know but so yeah i came
back
and here comes the moment i
i told my roommate who was waiting
inside my apartment
to turn on the camera
her phone camera the moment when i for
the future purpose you know i want to
look back on the moment
i told her she has to film it when i
come back home
because i want to see
how they react to me because i i thought
you know i thought
that they were going to be like
really happy and i thought i was going
to cry
and i thought it would be like this huge
emotional
super cute reunion like in a movie
i thought it was gonna be like sparkles
and hearts everywhere and everyone
crying and hugging and we
but i open the door and i come in
and my cats
walk away from me
my cats walk away from me and
just don't even look at me
[Laughter]
i was like oh my god this is so
heartbreaking and i tried reaching out
my hands to like let them
let them sniff and realize that hey it's
me
they might have just not realized yet so
i give them my hand i let them i let
them sniff and i'm like hey it's me it's
mama
it's your mama it's me babies me
obama your mama and
but i don't know they just
they just didn't realize i don't know
maybe they didn't realize but they were
like confused like why is she here
what happened she was
they were really really confused i guess
i mean it's hard to read
what cats think
so hard to understand
[Music]
but yeah they did seem very confused and
i was like
what what's going on this is sad
are they gonna like hate me are they
gonna like
try to keep space from me the whole time
but
but guys after
only a few minutes like let's say half
an hour
it was all back to normal they were
already like super cuddly
and and i think i started like putting
um furniture together and uh um putting
my room back together
in the exact way it was before like
everything but someone someone
took over my room i didn't i forgot to
mention that someone took over my room
for one year
but she moved out again so yeah my room
was empty the whole time
and like not the whole time i mean it
was other other stuff
oh why why why why why aren't you
charging
what it is
on it oh well whatever um
the whole time and there was other
furniture in there
so yeah but then i put all my my
furniture back together
and and and i put everything in the same
space
yes everything my desk my my
my bed my carpet the moment i put down
the carpet
the babies came into room into the room
and they were like
like lying down on the carpet and they
were like this carpet we know this
carpet this is this is the carpet
why did you see the low battery thing
should be fine though i hope
yeah so they really recognized the
carpet
and it was all coming back together and
that's when they really i think realized
hey
she's she's back she's moving back in
and they started like purring all the
time
and and i mean they were pretty the
whole day ever since i arrived they were
like
oh my god we're getting we're getting as
many pets as we did one year ago because
my roommate she um likes my cats
but she definitely doesn't give
them as much clingy attention as i do
i'm like 24 7 i'm i'm touching them
24 7. i swear
i know
yeah they realized and and and um
once it became like evening time and my
room was back
uh together and i was like unpacking my
suitcases
um yeah it was just
all back to normal and when i got into
my bed to
chill and watch some i wanted to watch
some netflix but hey i actually didn't
for the first time in in a million years
i didn't watch netflix before sleeping
because i was so tired i didn't even
need it and i was just i was just
cuddling with them
they were now this was the thing that i
was the most worried about
are they going to sleep with me on my
bed
as they did before because previously
a fake previously for the past
two years when i raised them they slept
with me on my bed every night
um like usually around my feet
or maybe one at my feet and one next to
my next to my head
um and i really liked that i really
liked that i didn't want to lose that
but i was like
when i'm gonna leave um my roommate
and the new person who moved into my
room for a little while
um they both didn't let my cats in
to their room when they were sleeping
they
shut the doors and my cats would have to
chill in the in the living room and even
besides that even when they were not
sleeping they usually wouldn't let them
into their rooms because they didn't
want
cat hairs and stuff too much i don't
understand that
but yeah they were um
mostly like yeah my cats were sleeping
alone so
imagine imagine sleeping with your mom
for two years and then one year
you're not allowed to sleep with anyone
anymore
so i come back and i was wondering if
they
like got like if they lost that habit
if they would not do that anymore
because they got used to
sleeping somewhere else i was very sad
about
the the thought of that happening
[Music]
so here comes the moment
nisa here comes the moment
i get into my bed
my my cats jump
on it lay down purr and go like
pepe pet me cuddle me
and the whole night they slept with me
on my bed and when i woke up they
cuddled with me
it was it was as if that one year didn't
happen it was
it didn't even take them any time to
recognize me
it took them maybe okay five minutes but
that's it it's like oh my god i was so
happy
i was so relieved because i i don't know
what i would have done
if they wouldn't want to sleep with me
anymore
i would have been so devastated but it's
like nothing ever changed
it's like just just like before
[Music]
yeah so i was sleeping very happily
and i was cuddling so much of them
and the moment i got up they get up and
they walk with me to the kitchen
and all that they follow me everywhere
and now i'm just you know streaming and
the bed is right next to my table so
they're on the bed
just just chilling they're always in my
room with me they're always
in the room where i am
so even i thought you know that they
would grow a bit more attached to my
roommate
because she was with them and i was not
there for one year
but ever since i'm back
they're constantly with me
they're not spending any time with my
roommates
anymore i thought they were gonna you
know
be a bit more fair and see
my roommate as a mom as well but no
i'm their real mom i'm the real mommy
i'm so happy that they like are all back
to normal
i'm so happy you have no idea i'm so
happy it makes me so happy
it's like okay everything was worth it
me being able to cuddle with my cats
like that again
it's all worth it
oh baby is stretching and baby is lying
down again
oh oh baby baby
no you're sleepy
would you be jealous if they did yeah
probably i would probably be really um
sad i would be like wow i shouldn't have
done this i shouldn't have left
i would have been devastated um
yeah we need cat emotes yes we do we
need cat emotes
my cats will be um will play a big role
in the future
like yesterday yesterday i was
um i turned on my pc and everything
worked thankfully and that was one big
thing too
like putting the pc back together and
then
it actually working oh my god it was so
relieved everything seems to be fine
everything seems to be perfectly normal
except my go xlr is uh acting really
weird
but i think like it's with it has
something to do
with i i don't know actually i don't
know something is weird like my
headphones
i connect them to the go xlr and uh
my headphones they just don't play any
sound yesterday after a while i was able
to somehow fix it but i
oh damn it but i don't know
why and i was able to fix it yesterday
and then i restarted my pc this morning
and uh
yeah it's not working anymore
oh but yeah kind of weird i'll figure it
out but at least i'm able to stream
even though youtube is making me
do some really weird things in order to
stream
really weird did you check the mute
button it's not muted no no
it's so weird but at least generally
it's working
um so yeah one thing i want to say
yesterday evening i was making the
thumbnail on my pc
and i was sitting down on my pc
and one of my cats she's like the extra
type of clingy she's like
super super clingy she's a big baby
like size-wise she's also pretty big and
so i
i start like working on my pc and she
comes over here and just you know
lays down in front of my screen
and just starts purring and stretching
and showing me her belly because she
really
loves belly rubs and she was like
because she moves around so much and
wants so much attention she
like constantly started touching my
keyboard
accidentally i couldn't work
she was just way too cute this is so
adorable she's such a big baby
she's so fluffy too
she's she's also the one that in the
very beginning
when i started um taking care of her
when she was only like a baby like a
really small baby
um who had to go to the um emergency vet
hospital and yeah
so i'm always very worried about her and
i was told that
in this one year my roommate actually
didn't really tell me about this
but i mean at least they took care of it
i guess
uh but in this one year three times
she had some kind of
uh wound
under like in her um under her neck
or like at her neck uh not in the back
but in the front
um under her chin like
she developed developed some kind of
wound three times in one year and
like apparently it went away after like
getting some
anti by
[Music]
anti-biotics huh am i saying that right
uh yeah i don't know
the vet actually doesn't really know
what
it is like they say it could be some
kind of
um allergic reaction but
she never had that before only when i
left she had it
so i really don't know uh
and well i hope she's fine it got me
really worried like apparently it was
like
all like open i don't know it's [\h__\h]
weird
i don't know what it is but i was
thinking of
maybe maybe it's a good idea to um do
like a
like a like an allergy test the vets
um said that i could maybe do an allergy
test
to find out what it is if if it is an
allergy
but i wonder if that can be caused by
stress i wonder if that's a thing
because maybe she was really
bothered by me not being there you know
cats can cats can totally have some
weird reactions
to stress like like mentally
you know like peeing everywhere and like
i don't know being really really
troublesome i was thinking
maybe this stress so maybe she'll be
fine
now that i'm back um
because she never had that before could
be scratching from stress
[Music]
oh you mean you mean maybe it was just
caused from scratching
[Music]
yeah it is very difficult to tell but we
will see from now on
uh how it will go i hope she will be fun
because
because she's i'm always so worried
about her she's such a baby
and um
she you know i had to bring her to the
hospital
in the first week that was that was oh
my god
that was so that was so
sad back then
[Music]
stress stress scratching that leads to
an infection is a possibility
okay so i guess yeah the vet didn't say
that but i was like thinking about maybe
that was it
um
it an abstest
i don't know not sure not sure what it
is but
for now she's fine she's very happy
they're both very happy
they're just being cute babies as usual
everything is as it was before
a whole year without mama is stressed i
thought so too
maybe it is that i don't know
but i'm just glad she's fine i got so
worried when i heard that you know
i'm i'm a i'm a very worried
cat mama they're huge babies
yeah very huge have their claws been cut
actually i um i don't cut their claws
and uh i mean there's like i know a lot
of people do it and a lot of people
don't do it because a lot of people say
it's not necessary
and i don't think it's really necessary
because they they
use their scratching poles and that
should generally be enough
and yeah they never hurt me with their
claws
so yeah i think most people don't cut
them and i think it's fine
yeah i i would say that i don't want to
do it like
i think yeah i mean that's something
that every owner has to decide
themselves but i don't want to cut my
pets uh um
nails claws whatever yeah
i don't want to trim no no no no also
they're probably not even gonna let me
do it
they're probably not gonna let me do it
uh
i don't know uh trimming nails
and declining something else okay i
guess there's a difference but
i don't do either and i think it's okay
they use the scratching poles
they seem fine
anyway so yeah that was pretty much the
story of me
going back home and everything is pretty
much
as it was before for now
[Music]
yeah my friends are really happy that
i'm back and i'm i'm really happy to
be um here again
i mean i have some mixed feelings
about like i don't know maybe maybe
i don't know if it was really
the best decision but it was hopefully
the right decision
how's the chocolate and food
[Music]
i um since i have to be in quarantine my
roommate is doing like shopping for me
and she got me a lot of
uh australian chocolate which i haven't
eaten yet but um
i had like a typical australian
breakfast
today and yeah the food makes me very
happy
stream shadow band i know i know guys i
know thank you everyone who made it here
by the way
because yeah stupid shadow band
[Music]
yes yes yes
yeah food makes me happy the bread the
bread is so good
i just use like cheap um bread that you
bake
in the oven and even that like it's just
already so good yeah
gohan no
is good too but my favorite is kinder
chocolate
it's so good my favorite might be kinder
country
something called kinder country it is so
good
[Music]
tinder is so expensive in my country
yeah it's a bit more expensive than
other chocolates i guess but it's worth
it
tinder chocolate is so
[Music]
i feel it's so weird i feel so weird
about like my japanese viewers it feels
to me like even though this was always
planned
i feel so sorry for leaving and i feel
like
i've i i broke up with you know japan
my boyfriend it feels like i broke up
with a boyfriend
um i feel so so
it's not you it's me but for real though
that's all i can say
it's my fault it's my fault i'm being
selfish
but yeah me coming to japan in the first
place was i guess
a selfish move and me going back again
was also
selfish i don't know everything i do
seems uh selfish
you're dating us to europeans
no i'm dating my cats
my cats are my babies okay i'm not
dating them but
they're my life they're they're
everything they're everything to me
i'll be going to japan many many times
once
everything is okay again
so i hope i hope they can forgive me
um
[Music]
it's so complicated i i like
living in both countries there's
good things about both countries
it's so difficult
oh hello you're doing a stretchy and now
you now you're laying down again
no oh baby i wanna let me get
let me disturb one of them and get one
of them one second
come here baby
do you want to put her in the microphone
yes
yes say something
say something
come on come on
come on she doesn't want to talk
or do you on say something
say something it's happening you can do
it
no come on she's really purring but it's
hard to hear i think
no
[Music]
did you hear that a little bit did you
hear it a little bit
[Laughter]
no she sometimes makes these weird
noises
oh
she sent you baby okay baby is leaving
bye bye baby she's so fluffy
did you hear those like she sometimes
sounds like a
like a like like a dove and like a like
a pigeon
she's like
i think in the future you will hear more
of her
name
i think she just it feels like she
doesn't want to disturb me streaming
so she stays a bit quiet right baby
no baby
makes me so happy
cats do a lot of tripping yeah they do
you should make an i am cat next and
maybe i
maybe eventually i will turn into a cat
are you ready to get up too
oh you wanna
come to the microphone no
names they're called they're called baby
will i will on stream as i do actually
often i often just call them
baby baby baby so
let's just say they're called baby
both of them baby one and baby two
so just ask me ask me how's baby doing
[Music]
baby is doing wonderful
you know they have like a million
followers on instagram so they're quite
they're
they're famous instagram cats so i
cannot
dox them and reveal their identity
therefore i cannot
tell you their name and i can also not
show you any photos because
there are famous instagram cats who
get you know free merchandise
sent to their mailbox every day and
they're sponsored by
um whiskas and all those kind of brands
and they poop into golden toilets
yes so they drink they drink cat
champagne and yeah they're pretty famous
they drive a limousine
and they have a butler which is me
so unfortunately i cannot share too much
about them i cannot show you
maybe you'll find their 1 million
follower
instagram account and then you can see
more and then you can find out their
name but
unfortunately i cannot share anything
with you because they're famous and i
don't want to dox them
it's dangerous it's a dangerous world
out there i want to protect them
yeah they're more famous than me yeah
yeah yeah they have a huge following
is this real or just a joke hmm
who knows there are a lot of really
famous cats out there
um i like a lot of them
but i will not tell you uh i don't want
to dogs my cats they're famous
they're famous i mean obviously they're
so adorable so
i cannot stock them you're pretty close
to them with 830k subs
i don't think i'll ever reach i don't
think i'll ever get on the level of my
cats that's
pretty pretty impossible
i don't have instagram
[Music]
hmm maybe my cats need a youtube account
maybe i should make a youtube account
for my cats and then they will reach
1 million there as well obviously in one
day
obviously they're both cleaning
themselves right now by the way because
i woke them up so
they instantly go into a cleaning
session um
they're so adorable they're so cute
i'm i'm actually i feel like it's such a
waste to not show you
what they look like because they're so
freaking adorable
hello baby where are you going where are
you going baby
yes i know i'm shadow band i know um
i i'm not sure should i
read uh super chat's in this stream or
should i do it another time
because i'm thinking
of maybe uh
asks caffey papa to make my cats as
[Music]
beaches
my my roommate just threw my cat back
back into my room that was funny
do it another time just relax i don't
know i got so much to read i should
probably read it but
uh hmm
i really need to catch up but i also
without my humidifier i feel like my
throat really hurts
[Music]
through yeah she heated my cat back in
here
now what should
or i was also thinking i could stream
again in like
10 hours or so 10 10 hours
no like i don't know in eight hours or
something like that i could stream again
i could try to fix my freaking go xlr
[Music]
now the humidifier might still take some
time but
[Music]
what should i do what should i do should
i stream again in like
eight hours
i could do like some some kind of gaming
stream and i do want to write my
schedule before that though
uh oh okay
how about how about i do like a super
chat reading stream
um in the following week maybe like
tomorrow
actually or the day after tomorrow
but i should at least read the super
jets from this stream if i can
yeah i think i'll do that okay
super chat
one second
okay so that so that i don't uh fall
back
too much
by the way i have to i have to buy a new
um gaming chair because
my old one i did tell you guys about my
old gaming chair right
i feel like i told you that i had one
and then that that
i would let my my cats scratch it as
much as they wanted to
did i tell you i feel like i told you
about my old chair yeah the pink one you
guys know everything there's a bunch of
you guys who literally know everything i
ever told you are you guys writing it
down or something
anyway that chair
it got thrown away because it's uh
apparently like we we kept it
somewhere in the cellar i guess
and it started like i guess molding or
something
ew and it got thrown away so
right now i'm sitting on a on a chair
for the
for our um eating dining table
and i'll get a new chair
yeah it's a bit
yeah bye but i
already looked up on amazon what chair
i'm gonna buy i'm gonna buy a bunch of
things i'm gonna buy
i'm i'm gonna get like a elgato
streaming deck
i i don't think i really need it that
much but
it it it says it will make my streams
even more professional
so so i want i want it
but they don't have the one with 15
buttons so i have to get the one with
35 buttons but i don't even need that
many buttons
have you guys seen that it's the one
where you can press a button and then a
scene changes
or like whatever you want to do like
there's like it's basically just
like buttons that you can um
attach some shortcuts with it or some
functions and
it just will work by pressing a button
which will apparently make
everything much easier and i never
really thought i needed it but oh well
why not
let's make my whole setup even more
professional
yes yes more and more more and more
i don't know if i really need them
though i never really felt like i needed
that but yeah here we go
speaking of buttons yeah put on senpai
volta
i have to thank both i have to tell her
that my pc is working
it's all thanks to her i have to tell
her
to read the super chats and let me
change this
super chat let's change the bgm to
i'll be reading the super chats from
this stream only for now
and then next week i have a super chat
ringing stream once my humidifier
arrives okay and as i said everyone who
leaves now thank you
but please remember to check my twitter
for future streams because
i think it will take a while
until um my my channel operates normally
again
and i don't want you guys to miss out on
everything and
it kind of really bothers me a lot
because i see
how the shadow band impacts me because
it's been a while and pisses me off so
much
what can i do yeah but you're
you guys are welcome to stay for the
super chat reading if you want to
let's go
by the way i'm reading this on my laptop
now so i'm like constantly looking down
looking for the top 10
[Music]
i felt the void of your absence made by
listening to the rick roll very good
good good choice that must have been
very fulfilling jin
thank you i missed you guys too i really
missed you guys i really wanted to
stream yesterday but
yesterday even though i i arrived so
early
the whole day i was busy with
unpacking and building stuff and all
that so
it wasn't really possible i really
wanted to stream yesterday night
but i couldn't and i was so tired after
a whole day of doing all kinds of things
yeah oh well maybe i'll stream again
later we will see
unstoppable phoenix thank you bruno cave
thank you
and chris harvey thank you soon fire
truck thank you
for thanking
thank you michelle v thank you and
welcome back to enjoy i couldn't send
the red superchat since i'm broke but
this is the
best i could do no problem no obligation
at all
i hope the flight was fun if not okay
again welcome back p.s youtube goodness
of bullying it really is
please give me a freaking break please
please please
please it's not only the shadow van i've
been having issues the whole day
um logging into youtube and yeah it's
really complicated to stream right now
for me so please get your [\h__\h] together
thank you
thank you so much i'm back yeah welcome
back
we miss you so much i miss you guys too
i'm sorry for that streaming for a
couple of days you know it was very very
busy
on the i like actually like when the
waiting room started i still had like
i think two full days in japan
but i i had to do many things and uh my
pc
got packed so at that point i basically
uh stopped like started the waiting room
at the point where my pc
was um not usable anymore so even though
i stayed in japan for another two days
um
i wouldn't have been able to stream so
yeah
well thank you alita for waiting and
thank you for everyone else who also
waited for me
to come back thank you akstf2
spanking time thank you for a red super
chat
welcome back we missed you thank you
thank you very much i missed you guys
too it's so weird to
have not streamed for um a couple of
days it's so weird
and it's so weird also to stream
once again in a different environment
very weird very new i hope i'll get used
to it
thank you though thank you for the
support
thank you
you just need some time to settle in
yeah
very happy that you are safe thank you
in an environment with your cats yes
yes yes i can't wait to play some games
and then have my cats
walking over my keyboard yay and then
accidentally ending the stream or
something
lord evil cries welcome back to europe
when you were traveling we at kfp italy
removed the beer from the menu as you
asked
now we sell wine stones with ch
i like how you wrote that with ch i mean
wine
why not kfb i did once again
not give you permission for that but you
italians just do whatever you want to do
anywhere you guys are like
you you don't even listen to me
you just do whatever you want
so okay whatever uh why not kfp
is uh italy only okay
italy only
why is it dying why is my why is my
where's my phone dying yapping ten
percent
i'm charging it why is it not why is it
not charging why why
why not how about how about this here
there you go this is this is this usb
slot
more like better for you do you prefer
this one
maybe maybe i'll i stop moving at some
point
it's connected to the pc yeah
is once again oh australia australia is
once again again blessed
by a magnificence i hope your travels
were smooth
and how are the cats did they own or
don't you because if that's the case
nothing a little catnip can't fix or a
short trip to the usual
i will never send my cat to the usual
firm
i also never use catnip on my cats i
tried it like one or two times
it was fun but like i never use it
um but yeah uh travels were mostly
pretty smooth yeah the trip was it's the
trip itself was pretty smooth
uh smoother than i expected i thought
there would be more troubles and all
that but it was really fun
thank you darkest dog thank you
her cats are overseeing the usual room
maybe
thank you scott wong thank you for your
support i'm back yay
darf shame thank you lily cats
oh there's a lot of european uh super
chatsy
logical paradox thank you del star dan
kishon d love 67
sebastian tafoya wish you the best from
now on as well i don't think i will be
able to watch you during the week
because of working time but i still
support you on the weekends
thank you and of course please watch the
archives if you missed something
you can always watch the archive you
don't have to watch it live always
thank you for the support flanders thank
you
cake okay kicks on
super chat oh my god thank you
thank you so much wow writing
uh with it
um
thank you so much you're so generous
[Music]
thank you for the generous huge donation
tv
i'm so happy that you're back in a
comfier and better environment
also i'm glad that you arrived safely in
australia
hopefully everything went smoothly we
carefully employees will be
always here for you thank you thank you
i'm happy to hear that i miss you guys
very much so
it's glad it's it's cool to finally be
back
i know i know i want to connect it to
the like
um the problem is the the plug is too
far away
i hope it will um be able to
stand a bit more uh pressure and then
for the next time i'll try to
use an extension cable mm-hmm
winged angel duncan cyrux
attack that shirt yourself didn't tell
me how to say your name i never know how
to say your name
please tell me welcome back how are you
we're glad you made it back all right
the chickens are ready thank you thank
you
i'm glad you waited thank you
thank you thank you
for watching
we missed you thanks for the cat update
you're welcome
love my cats i can't i can i can talk
about my cats for ages
penelope strange thank you soon
that is in a never-ending battle of
youtube i thought you were going to say
kian is the only whole live member who
streams from europe but
oh but
it was a different sentence
yeah um never ending battle indeed
who will win chiara the phoenix or
youtube
thank you hello hungarian neighbors
yes australia has neighboring countries
yes
cocoa bean pancakes
when journey ends and another one begins
time flows ever onward
look forward to the future and the
adventure change can bring welcome home
thank you
thank you jen is unbreakable
actually man i got really
i got really sad leaving my manager
because she helped me so
so so so much so many times
um i probably
in the last few months i probably spent
more time with my manager than i did
with kelly
and yeah it's just kind of sad and
it was it was definitely noticeable
that she was also very sad so that made
me even more sad i didn't expect her to
become so emotional
yeah so that was that was sad
[Music]
water
yeah sad
very sad i hope i can see her again like
in the summer or something james mcfee
thank you thank you for a red super chat
welcome back tanto your europe schedule
is early for the west coast us but that
might be better to make sure we're up in
time for work it's
it'll be like morning coffee time i
actually like um
this streaming time um this starting
time
might not be normal um i might like i
mean
streams at this time will happen but
probably
more often at times like right now
like for me right now it's 5 p.m
i'll probably um start streams
rather uh later around this time than
earlier so probably also a lot thank you
[Laughter]
a lot during
doing that
my my roommate just walked in
funny that you didn't see her how did
she not show up on the camera is she a
ghost
maybe she's a ghost oh maybe she's
casper
no just kidding oh i heard her laughing
in the distance
she knows what's up she knows that uh
how this
how this uh how how
how to deal with this kind of situation
she has been
trained by me chiara's roommate is a
ghost
yeah i don't know i mean her not showing
up on the camera it must mean that she's
some kind of ghost
all right where were we i was good i was
saying um
streaming times will um be
mostly during european prime time
which should be like noon
afternoon time for american time zones
i think yeah mostly probably around that
time
so look forward to that thank you james
mcphee thank you for the support
shark toast thank you soon kamen rider
kfb
[Music]
sorry my cat was doing something bad
bryant zarita dankeshan jct thank you
[Music]
i see interesting thank you for the
information
[Laughter]
hey you can finally use your 999 emotes
again
she was she was scratching the chair oh
baby i wanna hug come give me a hug
no hello
oh
cat break
whenever you guys do um you guys
what was it called again um whenever you
guys do
i think with bingo bingo again
with you know things that i do on my
streams
you now have to insert um kiara taking
a break to hug her cats
because that will happen a lot they get
shoes without red super jets
yes and they deserve it
or euro canard thank you
3 11 is on hiatus thank you
apparently we aren't even to talk about
the different parts of the sun without
facing the wrath of youtube
yeah um apparently
my streams can also be shadow banned
by some things that you guys write
in the in the pre-chat
it doesn't even have to be anything that
i do
so i don't think
that's what it caught what caused my
channel to be shadow band
but apparently you guys talked about
something
weird in my pre-chat and that's
i don't know maybe that got i think uh
maybe that's what
got my waiting room shadow banned
eh i don't know it's weird but
like i don't want to take the pre-chat
away from you guys
but it seems to
sometimes even though we don't want it
to cause anything and
you guys don't even write anything bad
in there but it can cause
something and i think probably just the
fact that we mentioned the word shadow
band in the chat
itself is also not very beneficial
so maybe from now on we should just not
mention
the word anymore and just say something
like
uh kiana got bamboozled
by youtube okay let's just say that way
bamboozle okay
and maybe maybe i'll ban the word shadow
band
in the chat because i don't know i feel
like
that might be contributing
to my channel and my streams being
shadowband yeah
cause because when i i tried before to
do a community post
to um advertise
a shadow band stream and in the
community post
i wrote the url of the stream and i
wrote this streaming shadow band so
please you know help me out and that
post
got shadow banned as well even because
of the youtube url
or because of the shadow band word
mentioned but or both
so yeah uh
it sucks
um now i feel guilty sorry canada don't
worry about it but
uh i guess try to be
careful of what you guys are writing in
the pre-chat um
i don't think it's generally the thing
causing it but
we will see um
hope you'll be back soon by the way be
gamer
as you play thank you and red panda
plush thank you robert maurice thank you
thank you for red super chat has message
not a chad
i i wouldn't i mean i would be surprised
if you sent a super chat without a
text usually or you always write
something in there which
i appreciate thank you thank you
thank you for the red super chat
you thank you for coming to the stream
as well
i feel like there is many people who are
missing out on the stream
because of the van because of the
bamboozle
but thank you for coming and thank you
for your support thank you as always
welcome back kiara thank you congrats on
you know pretty good okay you guys thank
you thank you
uh
roommate is otp thank you for the
thinking
we do um both enjoy
the same type of lifestyle um of like
just
chilling for the whole day
she actually um got herself
a switch after i left because we were
using my own switch
and she's been more and more uh starting
to play more games and
she's been playing animal crossing and
she wanted to play
because i brought it with me she wanted
to play super mario
3d all-stars and all that [\h__\h] she's
she's slowly turning
into a little bit of a gamer although
she's definitely not
usually the type to be a gamer
um she's she watches a [\h__\h] ton of
netflix though
it's crazy she watches so much more than
i do
she's like constantly watching something
and
we both have to struggle we connect with
the struggle of
running out of things to watch
but she somehow she still finds a new
series
again and again and again that i've
never heard of and then binge watches it
she's a professional binge watcher
yes skill paige donkey shannon cd kfb
citizen
[Music]
hello kiara how are you enjoying the
company of your cats yes i am
all i want to say is in the song sung by
maja i'm missing you and it's making me
blue i'm missing you and what can i do
but wait you're back canada's back
everyone raised the roof
before i can't glory to the kfc oh did
you miss me so much oh
i missed you guys too i am back
i'm back i'm back thank you guys very
much for waiting for me
mwah thank you genie nice to see you
again
mrs thank you and mabel cipher
oh yeah i need to buy some new cat toys
maybe i did buy them a new cat
tree while i was gone because uh
while so one of my cats is
kind of chunky although i don't want to
say that it's her fault
i want to say that it's because the tree
was cheap but my previous cat tree
which was pretty big it started like
breaking like
the top part broke off while i was gone
uh like a month ago or so or two months
ago
i think while she was sitting on it but
i don't want to say it was her phone
okay
it's not is it it's not her fault okay
it's just
that tree has been used for a while and
well it's it was a cheap treat
so i did buy her uh i did buy
via amazon i did buy a new tree while i
was still gone and they're using that
tree
right now it's actually a quite
nice tree yes yes but i'm thinking like
when i move
into a new uh place in summer
i want to get a pretty hot chick coming
i want to get a pretty big space where
like i have an extra room where i can
put like a lot of like
cat stuff in like like i want to have
like a lot of like shelves on the walls
that my cats can like jump around on
like monkeys
i think that would be lots of fun for
them like an adventure room for my cats
so
return to monkey yep
trees fall definitely yeah it's not the
cat's fault okay
she's she just she just looks chunky
she's not she's not actually that
chunky okay she she looks very chunky
because she has like a [\h__\h] and a fur
like way more than her sister they're
sisters by the way
my cats are sisters and even though
they're sisters like
um what the the trunk the chunky baby
has like kind of a different fur texture
a little bit
and she has way more floof they're both
fluffy
but one of them is way more fluffy than
the other
yeah yeah it's very interesting
looking for the top thank you thank you
for the pinky
and you just can't get a break from soon
as huh takanico is still my otp
now they only reacted a little bit soon
at the moment but now
now
[Music]
i can't read the rest from your name i
wonder what it says but
wait so is this casper super chatting
oh casper
i
could you ask him to show how to work
this funny door bye bye for now see you
soon
wait wait wait wait wait he did come
casper did come with me
wait what room what room at what room
is it is it what i think it is is casper
in my cat's stomach
[Laughter]
is that what casper is talking about he
doesn't realize that he has been eating
e10
wait no wait but that means that he'll
eventually come out as poop and
not be sending any super chats anymore
casper quick get out of there casper
guys we get out of there before you get
like
it turned into poop no
no be honest
i want you to be alive casper come on
get out of there
do something oh thank you for the pinky
by the way thank you
shakur thank you soon
thank you for the pinky just to be clear
now
kfb sims for our real boss the cats
right
no no don't get it wrong my friends
don't you get it wrong
i am my cat's mama and i am your mama
and you will all continue
to appreciate your mama
me
you better i think the cats are the real
potential
no it's me
sadly i didn't get a notification for
the stream yeah nobody got it because
i'm shadow band right now i'm bamboozled
but uh hopefully it will get fixed i've
been
i've been shadow band for a couple days
now so please
check twitter and so on for future
streams notifications because otherwise
you
will probably be missing out on it okay
thank you thank you
ferris gt thank you
thank you for red super chat glad you're
home back safe and that
your cats are as loving as they were
before been on holiday to australia
a lot of times already beautiful country
for its nature hyped for a whole live
stream
from you you eu now carefully belgium
reporting for duty oh belgium viewers
hey i'm gonna visit i want to do like a
whole europe tour i've been to a bunch
of
countries in europe before but the hell
jim i've never been there
[Music]
so that's definitely something i want to
check out
once traveling is okay again i want to
travel
a lot i also my roommate is very excited
and when i when i told her that i am
now finally able to
travel financially
uh it is not much of a struggle anymore
as it was before
and she was very happy because she was
like oh finally i have someone to travel
with me
yay so me and my roommate will probably
go on a bunch of trips once everything
works out again yeah pretty cool i'm
excited for that i want to go to like
um some some famous
vacation destinations like you know
the most beautiful beaches in the world
that's where i want to go
where the water is like see-through yes
and and
turkey turquoise colored
no turkeys
no no no no roommates john will never
um have a debut she as you as you saw
she doesn't show up on camera she's a
ghost or something so
i don't think she can w i don't think
ghosts can show up on my camera she was
right next to me
for a moment giving me um a cable
so probably not possible unfortunately
anyway flanders thank you for the red
super chat once again
and uh thank you thank you i'm glad that
hopefully
now many of you european viewers will be
able to watch my streams much much much
much much much more
you know what i'll i will
european streaming times yes
it's my time zone [\h__\h] it's time for
freaking kiana
foreign
is that correct
yes i know european uh viewers have been
asking for
european streaming times for a long time
not only from me but from other
whole livers as well but european
streaming time is
kind of difficult to stream in from
japan so
finally i can do it now yes finally you
guys don't have to
struggle as much anymore
borman clay thank you thank you also
from hungary
yay all my european viewers welcome back
to europe princess and finally i can
watch the streams
live instead of the archives much love
from hungary thank you
much love back to you
avenged me thank you soon mo moto
account name
um
[Music]
thank you for the pink super chat thank
you
uh and then if you're
followed up by your your main account
after sending a superchat with your sub
account
thank you for the red super chat
if you feel bad for dumping us why
didn't you accept our proposals out so
that we
could all green card to eu
you mean marrying every japanese person
every japanese viewer so that they could
come with me to europe
you know that sounds like a wonderful
idea
but i have to let you know this is not
possible by law i can only marry
one person so i would have obviously
totally done that yes yes if it would
have been possible yeah i would have
married every single one of you
unfortunately by law it's prohibited so
sorry about that
wow thank you for the red super chat
though i hope like even if you guys
even in my japanese viewers cannot
follow me
into another country you can always just
follow me by watching every single
stream
and i mean it's it's basically like you
know i'm
i'm a virtual youtuber and it doesn't
matter where i am it shouldn't matter
where i am
um
when um
what about okay she's already a cat
youtuber
a little bit of a full-on cat i wonder
probably something like that is probably
already out there i could imagine thank
you for the red super chat
you will be hearing a lot from my cats
in the future i'm sure of that
cheese is also a red super chat thank
you happy candle best kill i love you
buzz thank you
it's it's crazy how happy these cats
make me
i feel like wherever i live as long as i
have my cats
i would be able to live happily even
though i just sat
uh in regards to the japanese super chat
that i was just reading and answering to
i said that um
neither japan nor my own country
really makes me feel like i belong here
and that's something that i have been
kind of um thinking about
because there's no other country that
i'm really like
so interested in that i want to live in
it
so i don't know it's it's weird like
it just doesn't feel like i belong here
but it also doesn't feel like i belong
to japan but i wish i could combine
japan
and my country or live in both countries
that might be the ideal solution
but that's also pretty impossible so hmm
maybe try arduino australia no
no no no no no no no
uh i don't want to be in constant danger
of opening
the door to my home coming home and
being surprised by i don't know
a [\h__\h] huntsman spider or something
like that
and then even if i would try to step on
it
it's turning into a million small
spiders no
i am not up for that and i also don't
want to be suddenly surprised by
i don't know um crocodiles
jumping into my face or koalas falling
from the sky
as it usually happens in australia so
no although i would love to visit it
because i really really i really do want
to visit australia
but i will have to protect myself from
all the dangers
yeah oh yeah bears and bears
fall down from the sky in canada no
why what are you talking about guys drop
bears doesn't that happen in canada
that shouldn't be australian don't tell
me that happens in australia too
what what
australia has a bear problem as well
dear lord
oh my god
uh what what the [\h__\h] is that anyway
i don't even know what you guys are
talking about what is that
what is that uh
uh you guys need to tell me about that
it just chat is going too fast
little bears drop from trees are you
talking about koalas
oh my god i'm lagging
anyway let's continue before my battery
runs out
on spanking hand thank you for red super
chat wow my hacker tan is boring too
you have a cat named hadoo town that's a
cute name
like haru ah spring
that's cute wait is is that you have a
cat as
a as a profile picture i wonder if
that's harutan
um the purring sound of cats is so
healing
isn't it i love it
what happened you're welcome to send me
cat pictures
albedo dankeson leave one hat in japan
one in australia and move to brazil
then you can say you live in all three
albedo what
why brazil
i'll get that do you guys got that
brilliant i guess it's the point is just
for me to come to brazil
jay welcome general pickled
chat please make a youtube account for
baby one and two i need to decide
on an aussie you cannot decide between
those two believe me they're both like
so
so adorable you need to love both of
them wait oh my god i need to turn on
the lights it's getting so dark one
second
i just um i just had to put my
my my whole face into my cats
and
uh how to say that without sounding
weird
when they're laying on my bed and they
look so fluffy and just i
just can't i just i just cannot hold
back they
have to i have to face face bomb them
on their stomach yeah it's so fluffy
it's like a like getting a
i don't know you know how we girls we
like to put on some
face masks like aloey vera or
charcoal face mask whatever but
my my preferred face mask
is cat hair it's
the most soothing well well the battery
oh my god the battery okay okay i need
to do something about this oh my god
okay wait wait wait wait wait
yummy yummy
ah that doesn't work damn it
it doesn't fit the extension cord
doesn't fit into the extension cord
dammit what do i do
it all uh i'm gonna put this i might
stop moving for a moment
maybe
put this here but oh [\h__\h] no damn it
damn it i can't i can't
i can't even do that no
yeah i can't i i can't like
okay hello hello here i am hello no no
no no not without face no
okay uh camera is dead though camera is
dead
um
i'm having um a lot of um
travel adapters and i literally can only
charge my phone by usb right now
[Laughter]
[Music]
one second i can't show you that face
that's ridiculous
here have this but
can i use this this is from it is me
this me
thank you thank you this is me now for
we're almost done with the super chats
so we should be fine for a little while
i have literally like a problem like i
only have one travel adapter
but i'm using that travel adapter from
my go xlr but i also kind of need a
travel adapter for my laptop
so for my laptop i was lucky to find the
solution of
uh like using like you know how the
adapter for
um laptops usually have come like they
they're like two parts put together
and for for the part that
goes into the electricity plug i found
another end my my roommate had one
uh that is like european
you know what i mean so half of it is
like from my roommate and the other part
is uh from me
oh my cat just turned around like three
times and now she's
uh yeah cleaning herself
yeah so uh
but the thing is i needed my laptop to
work right now because
um i need and it's too complicated
for streaming i have like so many issues
right now oh my god i i explained it in
the beginning
i can't explain it again it's just makes
me mad makes me freaking mad
okay so anyway yes she is indeed licking
her bottom right now
yes yes
try find a usb port with lighting next
so it has more power
okay well it's too late now not for now
whatever let me just finish the super
chats
thank you for the pinky i'm a cat can
you adopt me i will be zooming around
though
i do want more cats so
i'll probably eventually get more once i
move out
and move into a new place i'll think
about adopting you maybe
but i didn't know you were a cat that's
new to me
salute yeah thank you to three hours
thank you daisy
thank you for a red super chat i don't
have much to say so welcome back and i
hope you get to visit japan again soon
i hope so too it's gonna be a bit lonely
you know
but yeah no the thing is like i can't
even buy travel adapter because it's
sunday and
in japan i would be able to buy anything
on a sunday
but in australia wink
shops are closed and yeah it's tough
yeah i have a problem
i can't buy anything all shops are
closed
allowed to go outside right now because
of quarantine but my
my roommate is super sweet she went
she's just gonna like buy me groceries
for like
like uh over a week like a whole 10 days
she's gonna buy me groceries and she's
so sweet she even like
brought me a freaking hot cocoa in the
morning in the morning
i don't know why she's so sweet i think
she's happy i'm back
she's so sweet um
hi roommate
magitenshi rmt
[Laughter]
she's pretty sweet yeah
she's very um i i asked her many times
that she really wouldn't
mind me like because when i stream i
often stream for hours and hours and i
get really loud sometimes and
sometimes i'll be probably streaming
after midnight as well and all that and
i asked her many times if she's really
okay with that but she said he has
absolutely no issue with that one really
good thing about her is that
she doesn't really get bothered by noise
and uh
even in if she gets bothered by it she
would just use
um she has noise cancelling headphones
and she says she's just she's
just gonna use that so that's pretty
cool yeah
she's very tolerant of yeah what i have
to do i told her i have to do this and
if she
has a problem with it then i absolutely
don't mind moving into a different place
right away
because i respect that i understand that
it can get very annoying after a while
and
even though she says she doesn't mind at
all um oh
nice neck crack even though she said she
doesn't mind at all
i think eventually it might get annoying
and bothersome
to be so considering um like her as well
she obviously has to be
a bit more quiet when i'm streaming
uh so i don't want her to
like you know live such a different life
just because i'm here
she says it's fine but you know i don't
want to put any
um any troubles on her so
i will eventually i will move out again
yeah but for now i thought it was good
to when i come back
to um keep my cats
um in a space that she's still very used
to
uh that they are so very used to because
like i'm coming back okay
that might be super um uh
um confusing for them and i thought it
would be very very
um confusing if i would come back and
the first day i move out with them and
bring them in a completely new place you
know what i mean
i want to do it like step by step like
first i come back and then we move
after a while yeah i wanted i want them
to be
um to get used to it slowly
that the changes are happening i don't
want to stress them out so yeah
oh okay yes
thank you yes i will refresh the window
because i reached the point where uh it
stopped
and now i read everything that came in
while i was reading
we're pretty much done i think
um
oh yeah
[Music]
a bunch of super chats came in
oh that's the launch ah there we go okay
young sing thank you
for ti thank you for a red super chat
thank you this stream is so great and
lovely and adorable and comfy really
i'm glad you guys liked it i
i was feeling a bit um worried about um
just doing a talking stream uh i hope
i hope it was fun for you guys i did
have a lot of things to talk about i
guess but yeah
talking streams generally like i enjoy
them but i feel always so worried about
if that's good enough
and if it's gonna be fun for you guys
but yeah it's it's great to talk to you
guys again
thank you ethan i'm glad you enjoyed it
i hope next time
i can figure out some issues that i've
been having here with youtube
and i hope the shadow band gets resolved
and i hope that i can get some travel
adapters so that
i can charge everything appropriately
that would be very helpful i need those
freaking
travel adapters and i need a humidifier
because my throat oh my god it's it's
not it's not doing well here
okay it's really not doing well
baby one and baby two yeah that's right
motion function
i believe you i can't believe you're no
longer a gamer girl on a game of girl
chair
yeah it's unbelievable
yeah soon though soon
it's crown thank you and welcome back
thank you for the pinky
welcome back moving sucks and weird
problems always pop up they do
yep once things settle down and you stop
making changes the youtube situation
should get better
just keep calm and keep going i'm glad
the cat's warmed up quickly hi baby one
and two
they say hi to you too although they're
sleeping
it's unbelievable like i'm so loud
um and i've noticed this i've noticed
this before as well like when i would be
like listening to music loudly when i
like before i left uh for japan um
they would just sleep through everything
they as long as they're in the same room
like once i get
up and move somewhere they wake up and
move with me
but if i'm just you know making loud
noises they just keep on
sleeping your voice is suffering for the
babies oh i wonder
cats have selective hearing i guess
that's true i guess so
um but i guess also yeah my voice is
just like
good for them to listen to
what
one thing that you know i already have
problems in japan
because i was taking too many naps and i
think that problem will not be resolved
here because
them sleeping on my bed and looking so
cozy
and me then joining them on on the bed
and getting cozy with them
[Music]
i i already know i'm gonna be taking a
lot of naps with them
because it's just so freaking cozy i did
that before too
so yeah we'll be doing it again it's a
big problem but relatable really
yeah taking cat naps with the cats yeah
they're always sleeping and they're so
fluffy and i just i just love chilling
with them
i'll be sleeping a lot with them
i'm so surprised the pc is actually
really done i fought something
with my luck something had to break
but nothing did oh i can't believe it i
was so worried about like maybe like the
the the
the i called it memory cards it's pretty
close but that's not what the name is
what's it called again
what's it called those those fin the fin
ones
what are the thin ones called the
uh the ram oh yeah
the ram i'm surprised those didn't break
because those are kind of flimsy and and
when when botan senpai
gave them to me to pack them in the like
anti-anti-static
bag she touched it so carefully so i was
i was like really worried like how do i
touch it is it okay to touch it here is
it okay that that they touch
each other in the rams um so i put them
into separate
anti-static bags they're pretty durable
really
they're pretty tough really i was being
so
careful like i was like only touching
them at the exact same spot where
bhutan senpai was touching them
i really wanna didn't screw up anything
because i really don't know anything
about it
i'm so glad everything works oh my god
oh my god guys there's one thing i
didn't tell you guys about
that i noticed thanks to botan by taking
apart my pc
absolutely unbelievable listen
this pc i basically um
i got from tsukumo i paid for myself i
didn't get sponsored
um but i basically
just said i want a good pc and they
built one for me
but i didn't have any specifications of
what i want because i don't have an idea
i just said make something good
and they made it and i paid for it and
they sent it over
and um
[Music]
so i didn't really know what was inside
um
i didn't care uh
so yeah i was using this pc and you guys
kind of saw the specs right and in
minecraft and so on
so yeah that's that's that but um
i have learned something new
about my pc
that i had absolutely no idea about when
bhutan's empire was taking apart my pc
can you believe what i have discovered
inside my pc there was a feature
that i didn't know it had
there is
a built-in game capture card
in there and i've been using my old ass
super cheap super old flimsy elgato
game capture card separately
externally but inside and i didn't know
there they built in a game capture card
in there
and i didn't freaking know and i don't
know how to use it either but bhutan
said by kind of explain it to me a
little bit i just need the software of
the game
that i already i already forgot what it
was called but
yeah i didn't know because they didn't
tell me i just told the company to make
me a pc
and i'll pay for it and they built it
and i didn't really know anything about
the specs and what they put in
but there we go i gotta i could use that
but
i mean the elgato is it did give me a
lot of issues
um in the beginning if we look back i
think we can all remember that i had
some issues
with my elgato many times
uh but it stabilized itself after a
while
so i didn't buy a new game capture card
but hey there we go i have a i have one
built in in my pc now so i'll just have
to figure out how it works exactly
what
yes that's it that's it that's it thank
you i forgot the name
so i just need uh the avermedia software
and then it should work i guess
so i know
so yeah i'll try to figure out maybe
that one is easier to use
i'll try to figure it out
very interesting um
thing avo media internal capture cards
are really good
[Laughter]
i was so surprised and i you know what
i've been noticing my my microphone
the you know there's this uh this
this how do you call it this fluffy foam
around the microphone and it's been
collecting so much cat hair
that's been flying around oh my god my
microphone is turning into a cat
come on
no
yeah the windscreen is getting very
fluffy
reject microphone become cat
check it monkey takishan penguin thank
you mrs thank you
oh we got our furnace replaced yesterday
the house smells but at least we're warm
and one by dying of gas oh my god i'm so
glad
oh my god what the hell gd dog is
is doing actually pretty well uh i went
to sleep somewhat early i
i was i was super tired but i had to
stay awake
last night somewhat early because of
setting up the pc
and trying to make a thumbnail and
trying to get youtube to work
so i did stay up like until like half
past
one o'clock but that's still a decent
time and then i woke up at like 9 00 am
i could have slept longer i did
i i will i will confess that i took a
nap before the stream to nap with my
cats though it already happened
i took a fluffy comfy
cuddling nap with my cats today already
a short one one hour that's a short
that's short for me and
one hour nap is short for me
yeah that was i was like holding my hand
i was
um like like like holding it on my
one of my cat's bellies and falling
asleep like that
so fluffy so fluffy
you have no idea it's so soft she has
like
the the not so chunky cat she has like
food that feels like bunny fur it's like
so soft insanely soft like
i don't know how how her fur is so soft
it feels like bunny fur
so touching it just feels so good
i was falling asleep while touching her
and also my cats i kind of like um
because i raised them since they're
really small i made them
tolerate me holding their paws
so you know how most cats really don't
like you
touching their paws they will like
pull away always but mine really don't
mind so i can hold their paws while i'm
sleeping
it is so sweet i always hold their paws
and their beans and i massage their paws
i i have to say i did a good job at
raising them they are so
tolerable they tolerate anything i do to
them
they love it they don't mind which is
really rare for cats most cats
hate it if you touch their paws
yeah you're so chill about it
i'm a good mom
this is shadow thank you for the pinky
uh ceiling fan thank you and oatmeal
cookies
wait okay shadow let me write sorry i
was uh i'm going too fast let me read
your super chat such a cute and chill
stream
glad you're back wait did i read this
one before what the hell um
am i getting confused
yeah read this one seems so familiar
glad you're back to enjoying hello baby
one baby too thank you
hello there back to you
oatmeal cookie oh too thank you
[Laughter]
thank you thank you for letting me know
in the chat because i can't see the
colors
thank you skye
welcome back to australia i'll keep my
fingers crossed for you
thank you i still need some luck to
figure some things out so that's very
helpful thank you
um thank you
that was too sudden
bless you thank you pascato
thank you and see what you're doing
there james burn thank you
thanks for the homecoming story it's
nice to hear your voice again very
soothing i don't want to imagine how
baby one and two felt not being able to
hear you for you
yeah i wonder if it felt for like a year
for them because even for me as a human
uh coming back here now it feels like
it's only been like a month
of me being gone it's so weird thank you
guys for the super chat
no but once i'm here it's like it feels
like barely any time has passed
so i feel like probably for the cats
it's it might be the same way
because people have told me cats have no
feeling of time
when they were trying to you know um
console me about leaving my cats for
such a long time
they were trying to tell me that cats
have no feeling of time and i was like
yeah that's cool
but like how do you even know like how
would you know that
how would you know that like how
how cats can't talk how would you know
that
cats don't have a feeling of time is
that really
true like if it is true that's cool
but how science stuff like
it it's down to how self-aware they are
oh they wrote it out
[Music]
um
interesting
okay continuing i hope the next
humidifier actually happens this time
uh for the last time uh the humidifier
was
a pretty good one but i guess the room
that i was in
was just too spacey so that the
humidifier
couldn't really do much but the room
that i'm streaming in right now is
pretty
small so if i would get a big humidifier
here i think
it will do a good job i hope so it has
to
people swear on humidifiers but the
humidifiers never really helped me like
i had a small one before
like standing right next to me
but even when it's right next to me the
small one at least
didn't help at all and in japan i had a
really beefy big one
really expensive one but i guess my room
was just way too big
for it to have an effect i don't know
we'll try it out again i'll get a big
one for
this small room and that should work i
hope so
it that one which boils the water and
does not ionize it
interesting needs distilled water is
that true
that's that sounds like very annoying i
just put in normal water
[Music]
is the door closed no that my door is
always open uh
at least like a little bit for my cats
but
i mean it's like leaned on so
i think it will be fine
you might extend it
thank you i'm back
thank you welcome back countless nights
thank you for the pinky
welcome back glad you made it safely
looking forward to fun streams in the
future as well as a cat debut and now
that empress kiara has returned and can
restore order
we will hold the line against youtube
cuz rebellion and we will win
[Music]
let's merge together against youtube
i think they need some kind of bunk
maybe we sent maybe we have to send
amelia to the headquarters again
maybe
don't wait and there's a name i cannot
read um
thank you
thank you so much apparently we need
permission
to make changes at kfb regional level
yes you do
will you please approve us turning japan
branch into a thunder dome
and to honor your australia trip because
we totally haven't already done that
but what the hell what the hell is that
supposed to be
what does that even mean
thank you for the red super chat but
what does that mean what is it what is a
thunder dome
is it just thundering inside of the kfp
building
it's a mad max joke oh i don't get that
i feel so
lame now is it just like
thundering inside
i don't get it
people fight to death no what the hell
no no no no no
no no no no no no no you know what i
have i have i have something for you
here what it where is it
other got it where is it
why is it down there here there you go
what the hell what the hell no
no why would you do that
stamp ran out of ink
all right continuing lionel duncan lexi
dot cape
peg thank you and lucas
oh wait lexi you said the pinky thank
you welcome back tanju sending love from
one of your many female fans thank you
thank you i'm excited to have female
fans thank you very much for watching i
hope you're enjoying the content thank
you
lucas
jesse lockhart thank you for red super
chat to the hardest working mama bird on
her life my first rat super chat and
love goes to you
welcome back amd wishing you and wishing
you all the happiness and support in the
world hashtag takamori forever
yay thank you so much for your first uh
red super chick thank you
i appreciate it very much and yeah i'm
back i'm back
and don't worry about takamori takamori
will exist forever
i've been posting in our um discord i've
been showing the girls pictures of my
cats and
kelly got very excited gouda also got
very excited
goodall was so sweet kuda messaged me
privately
about it and she was like so happy for
me being happy
it's so sweet she was like i'm so glad
you're with your cats and
and that you can spend time with them
i'm so happy for you she was so sweet
about it it was like out of nowhere i
was like oh my god
thank you that's so sweet
no so sweet i think she needs a cat too
she really needs some something fluffy i
know she wants what what
did you say that she wanted to get
something weird
was it a snake or what was it again
she said she wanted some weird pat
she needs to get a spider she needs
something cuter than that she needs
like a bunny or a cat or something i'm
sure it would like be really good for
her
[Music]
but okay whatever floats your boat right
so thank you jesse thank you so much
and roger daddy's thank you for pinky as
well sending this to the officially
sending this to officially said welcome
home from your female fanbase oh so glad
you're back home safely with your babies
hopefully youtube fixes itself soon or
we're gonna have issues
we're always here for you boss even if
the schedule changed thank you
no i think i mean you seem to be from
america and i think for
american citizens uh like american
people
people in america my streaming time
should be better than before so
yeah so should be should be good i think
hopefully you can always all watch my
streams in the future thank you for the
support
sephorik dankeshen barnaby cooper thank
you and justin the genius duck thank you
joshua roach thank you sharon thank you
for the pinky
welcome back potential i recently was
able to join your membership and i can't
wait to see more of your amazing content
keep being progress
can we get a usual room voice pack you
keep wiping our minds so
we don't remember what happens
interesting like kind of like a
style voice pack interesting
i i will i will think about it yeah
thank you very much and thank you for
joining the membership i hope i can put
out more content for the members once
everything
settles itself down thank you very much
for your support
thank you for the pinky wow four days
and you're already ghost
cheating on casper i mean
my roommate has been around since before
casper okay
and i can have more than two ghost
buddies okay
i love casper that will never change
patrick chen dankeshen also talked
in
oh my god what is this hey canada news
from the kfp college as you know the
cafeteria has and always
continued to serve kfb only since the
establishment's inception
and we'll continue to do so to our dying
breath
however we are having issues with the
with burger king
due to your marriage to them they are
starting their legal right to do
business on our property we do have the
kfp assassins but we need your word
um can we
can we just like chill and be friends
like
can you try to do something like um
peaceful
uh um solutions
and you reminded me i wanted to get my
favorite burger from
burger king because they didn't have it
in japan but they have it here
i want to get myself a crispy chicken
but
i think today i have to eat pizza
because i got some leftover pizza
and then tomorrow i'll get myself the
crispy chicken from burger king
hell yeah i'm so excited oh my god i
can't actually i can't wait maybe i need
to eat it today oh my god i can't wait i
need to eat that freaking burger king
i need to go to burger king
i need me my crispy chicken
i love it they have the crispy chicken
in japan too
but they make it differently yeah
chicken oh never mind never mind
jackpot thank you and pilgrim i
retaliate
thank you baby one and baby two creamy
cat food fun
actually they're like really it's really
difficult to find the correct food for
them they
are um they don't eat everything
and they don't
even if they eat it they don't um
[Music]
react well to most food it's very
difficult so
at the moment they're getting quite
cheap uh cat food why
but it's because like that's one of the
few ones that they eat
um it's a bit difficult but
i'll want to try out some more different
foods because i don't want them to be
eating the same food
their whole life i feel like maybe they
don't care but i feel like
i want them to eat different kinds of
foods you know
i just feel like it's a bit wasteful to
not have them experience
more foods they do love
canned tuna though
kudos
click on hinotori music video click on
the channel
go to the videos tab to finally find the
stream yeah me too
yeah it freaking sucks my channel it
doesn't even show up anymore it's
ridiculous
it's absolutely ridiculous
and it is affecting me because it's been
for a few days and i've seen
some yeah very worrying
effects yes i'm
i'm getting quite sad about it very
frustrated
alberto dan kishan george tankishan
sanji sean danke
cyrek thank you and slide and
do something i'm giving up on you i'll
tease you if you ask me to
anywhere i would have super chatted you
oh i know what you're singing
thank you thank you carefully lesbian
liaison v thank you
it's so aggravating that youtube that's
this happened to people that doesn't do
anything about it
exactly yeah i didn't even get a
notification
yeah i mean notifications are just
always bugging
doesn't even matter if you're shadow
band or not
but the problem is that i don't even
show up in people's subscription boxes
so people just think probably i'm still
on a on a vacation because i'm moving
i think a lot of people don't even know
that i'm
back yeah
that's the advantage and greetings back
to france thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
foreign oh my god as a canadian we
usually have our own guard bear to help
protect against the other bears falling
from the sky
elvis sanchez
oh thank you thank you for the pinky
thank you very much i appreciate it
i have long time don't not here don't
know what's happened thank you for
coming back hope you're enjoying the
stream
we're almost done guys most of the water
[Music]
i'm so glad you're safe i apologize i'm
not uh at many of these streams but i
wanted to send some support to my
attention as you make my
day so much brighter than before thank
you i'm glad you're here
thank you please come whenever you want
thank you very much
i'm running out of uh i don't have any
water left damn it
travel cane caster dan kitchen thank you
for the pinky glad i woke up in time to
see you welcome back shadow
i missed you to see you welcome back
yeah you need some punctation
welcome back yeah i miss you immensely
split this between your cats for me
please i'm
allergic and every day i feel sadness
due to it no
[Music]
that is horrible
that is like
the worst thing i could ever imagine
happening to myself
what the [\h__\h] are you making fun of me
for
[\h__\h] shut up
shut up shut up
i said everything correctly
shut up i hate you shut up
shut up uh
uh thank you for the pinky dice logaria
thank you for the red super chat sorry
that i'm not moving by the way welcome
back and i
and feel better soon oh thank you i'm
feeling quite okay
chill talking streams are one of your
biggest draws missed most of the stream
but can't wait to catch up on canada's
cat's content
yes i i would appreciate it if you watch
the archive i guess you
just woke up thank you for checking out
my stream
after waking up thank you mwah
and yeah i don't know how you found this
stream but i hope you will find the
future streams as well
uh because you know you know i'm being
bamboozled right now
[Music]
thank you for the support thank you very
much glad to have you back as well
thank you how are you i'm fine
[Music]
free account name
for the count thank you for the red
super chat
uma tinto we're so blessed you're happy
to spend so much time
on your comeback you're the best around
nobody's ever gonna get you down
fight till the end because your life
will depend on the strength you have
inside of you
is that is that some kind of like song
reference
is that a song reference
sounds like some kind of song
thank you very sweet of you so kind
thank you so much
even if it's just song lyrics thank you
for oh but
i was going to say that was like very
very
you know sweet and
kind what you're telling me it's a
karate
kid song
you kidding me i have the tire that's
the eye of the tiger lyrics
oh my god
it's too bad you don't see my pissed off
face right now
i'm just disappointed i thought you were
just
being like really really wholesome
oh name what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] uh better next
thank you thank you for the pinky
dice longeria thank you also for the
pinky for the high-powered air filter
fun cat life thank you
yes yes i will buy one right away after
this stream is over i need to finish my
amazon order
uh actually before i forget let me put
it in right now
let me put it in there right now i'm
buying a mod oh guys you guys have no
idea
i realized yesterday i had i had like a
huge issue with my monitor
um because i only brought my pc i didn't
bring the monitors
and i was gonna use my old monitor but
then i had this
issue that my new pc only has
hdmi and displayport ports but my old
monitor
works um
with um what's it called is it a dvi
cable or something like that yeah
and i don't even have that port but
my my monitor also would have the option
for a display port but i didn't have a
displayport cable
so we had to improvise and get um get a
display
port cable uh delivered over
from a friend and yeah
uh yeah the the the monitor is really
really old
um yeah even with the displayport
uh cable later on it didn't work in the
beginning
i don't know it's really weird i'm
getting a new monitor it so yeah
okay wait so i need um a human what's
humidifier in
german uh luft
before love before
look before it okay i'll get i'll get
one later
okay okay okay now i have it open so i
will not forget
um
thank you glad to have you back sorry
we're unable to send you a proper
invitation to our festival as north of
australia is quite struggling right now
i can't even send cover any date
proposal to this costumes not giving up
to
wait what are you talking about
what it's some kind of joke i get that
but i'm not sure
what you're talking about some kind of
festival
as north of australia on the quotation
marks
is quite struggling right now
what's happening
taking short naps isn't bad in spanish
are you talking about short naps in
like chiada um standards or
normal standards uh in spanish-speaking
countries we take naps in the middle of
the day
called siesta yeah i know that i heard
of that to relax
and for cardiovascular health and siesta
with cats sounds heavenly
sounds so don't stress about it okay
yeah it is like i don't stress about it
this is i need this it's like the most
um healing thing ever to sleep
together with my cats
free account name thank you for another
pinky okay follow up question
if we say already turned
the japan carefree branch into a battle
royale
how many tributes must we sacrifice to
get your forgiveness for fun to dominate
the tokyo france
none undo everything
although i have to say um
what's it called again uh that movie was
quite
fun i like that movie um
what's that would be called again
[Music]
what's it called again
no no not mad max no not that one the
one i actually watched
hunger games yeah i like the hunger
games
please no hunger games on kfp no
we don't want that why are you gonna why
you gotta be so
complicated i don't understand
why you gotta make everything into a big
battle
just stop it already i can take it no
more i don't want
the chickens please stop
it now i
have peace at kfp
um father doming is
angie japan kfp
branch get your [\h__\h] together
thank you and i think
that is
1514 thank you
star creator duncan free account named
mata
again a red super chat mwah thank you
i'm sorry to disappoint you with my
troll stomping lyrics before i forget
this week was obviously not very good
for me i was going to write it up
entirely until i saw on twitter that you
uploaded a king cover
i have not seen it yet but thank you for
saving my week
wait that was last week wasn't it that
wasn't even this week was it
was it this week i think it was last
week but
yeah you will enjoy it very much um
plea please look forward to the king
cover um oh he definitely already saw it
thank you i i wonder if you're serious
though if the week really wasn't
good for you i hope it gets better i
hope now that i'm back streaming that
you will feel better if you're serious i
don't know if that's a joke too
in case it is stop abusing me i'm
actually worried about you
so i hope you feel better okay thank you
matt hunzi thank
now i'm done okay
so next time next time i'll i'll do a uh
oh
wait a chance donkey tank thank you wait
there's more what the hell
oh wait there's more thank you for a red
super chat thank you chunky chunk i'm
late welcome back to here's some
my other fun for the kfp australia
branch thank you
i'm getting some monitors yes yes and i
think
first i'm getting one and i'll see if i
like it and then i got a second one of
the same
uh one i think and um
yeah you gotta watch the archive make
sure to watch the archive chunky chunk
thank you
director of the 10k visitor convention
here you wanted to be invited we want to
make it hap
oh oh wait that was actually about like
a real event
oh you want to be invited we want to
make it happen but with current lockdown
we have to wait to even get this year's
date i had to cancel the first one
oh oh now i understand
no no that makes sense okay wow thank
you very much i would love to
please um contact uh
whenever you know whenever you're ready
please contact the
the cover uh whole life contact form on
their homepage
you can just write in english that's
fine they have english speaking stuff
um yeah please thank you thank you very
much
jaihikani dankeshun
okay everyone thank you very much um
i'll get my schedule for the week ready
and chill with my cats that's the first
thing i'm gonna do because they're
sleeping right there and i need to put
my face
onto their stomachs and and go like
oh they look so they look so albedo is
smart and sexy
i need to cuddle with my cats they look
so peaceful
have a sweet sleep canada thank you
thank you also hello airlines hey yeah
free account name no wait stop no
stop stop
stop it
[Music]
you just came in so glad to hear your
friendly voice first thing in the
morning here you say good morning
thank you for coming but i'm just going
to end it now so you're welcome to watch
the archive thank you for coming
i'm glad you're here adidas
blog
thank you unity chad thank you for the
pinky
thank you for your first super thank you
oh my god
fellaini is please no more
okay i will read no more i will read no
more no
no no
no i'm reading no more
no oh my god the whole
[Music]
oh this is too many
no no no no no no stop stop stop
stop i'm reading no more no no
no f oh thank you for red super chat
i'm reading no more no no no no no no
i'm leaving you guys now
thank you guys for watching this was my
coming back stream
stop it this was my
first stream from europe and i hope from
now on we will
continue to have many many fun streams
together
and um yeah i hope everything will
settle in
i still have some issues thank you g-man
thank you wow
thank you that's god damn it
thank you guys logaria for pinky
okay okay okay
g-man hey guys remember the time we
dropped the reds which is intentional
didn't even read them
no no i i have to read those damn it
account names on thank you for that
super chat
kyla won't read this we are all so glad
you can pick it we can't be back home
with your cats and the people you
love the most thoughts thank you
wow thank you so much i'm glad to be
back and finally
you write something wholesome thinking i
don't read it but i'm reading it don't
worry
okay so yeah um sorry for a little bit
of scuff
and uh hopefully uh you guys will not
miss the
following streams as i said please check
twitter please check
uh my channel manually or use holo tools
or something like that
to stay on top of my streams because uh
it's it's kind of rough
to have like
only like a fraction of viewers
kind of sucks so yeah thank you guys so
much for the support dell thank you i
love you all i'm glad to be back
thank you so much i love you i love you
i love you
i'm glad to all of you thank you for the
support it's absolutely
amazing i love you all so much
on to a new chapter
thank you thank you love you all
and in german we say au vida scene
i will try to catch up with everything
that i've been missing the past few days
yeah gotta do some fan art
hashtag check and stuff like that
thank you all thank you love you thank
you for the super chats thank you so so
so much thank you
wow wow wow wow wow wow
wow wow and in german we say
thank you
watch heart challenger watch heart
challenger
while i'm bye gone
love you
[Music]
you