[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
oh I forgot
ah
ah sorry oh my
[Music]
god well you'll have to watch that for
at least in know five
minutes otherwise it's not worth
[Music]
it m golden Chet chick chick chick Chen
nugget
[Music]
B
I'm I say when you are
[Music]
ready no I say oh is that a dance move
cute I say when you're
[Music]
ready
da
[Music]
da da
da the
[Music]
H cussy hello K again
my throat is kind of rough today what
the
hell
hey I can put stuff on myself
[Music]
again I have a pink shotgun and I have a
little ouchie under my
eye you
see do you do you
hear the Beautiful clean
sound isn't it nice builds
character a cat scr scrud a HTI with a
shy
come no more noise after 3 years no
buzzing I don't think it was free years
of
buzzing no no no but it was definitely a
long time and with the with the goxlr it
didn't bother me so much because I was
able to filter it out uh in a way that
it didn't bother
me um
mostly but since I changed in order to
okay for everybody who was who's not on
Twitter everybody who doesn't know what
the hell I'm talking about
for a while now I heard this buzzing
sound every time I
speak and it was before I changed my
mixer but I thought you know back when I
start like I wasn't even so annoyed with
it first it was you guys pointing it out
and then I was like okay let's see what
I can do and then um I started out by
changing uh settings or also
changing um the XLR cable into a
completely new one cuz the mics are
connected with an XLR cable and then I
tried
um uh what did I try a different power
outlet different USB slot different this
and that and then I then I was like what
the maybe it's the mixer so I
switched the mixer but even though that
was an expensive thing to do it was no
difference if anything it was more
obvious to me now and more annoying and
it was actually making me go crazy
whenever I had my headphones on even
when I wasn't talking I still heard this
buzzing sound it was making me go crazy
yeah
uh oh it's like a
Tinus a tiny
tussy yeah and then even with the new
mixer I tried everything to get the
buzzing sound as unnoticeable as
possible
but a tiny what
[Music]
nail yeah but I couldn't really get it
gone completely it was still like I I
think for you guys it was less
noticeable than for me judging by what I
heard in the archive um but yeah and
then yesterday I absolutely lost it I
wanted to know the solution so I I asked
on Twitter and the allmighty all knowing
Twitter Community came to me with some
advices that were decent some that were
stupid uh only some mostly they were
decent
advice and then uh and then one that
pinpointed it I think other people were
also talking about interference but the
this one one comment pinpointed it in a
way by mentioning just try lifting your
XLR cable and see if it changes and it's
so simple but it worked let's go
other people were like change the
position of your microphone or maybe it
has to do with the gain because the sure
as sm7b the microphone that I use needs
a lot of gain um but yeah so you would
normally use a cloudlifter but if you
have a golr or a roadcast Duo you don't
really need the cloudlifter at all um I
don't even need to put that much gain on
but you know and yeah this and that I
thought I would have to we probably go
buy cloudlifter anyway but no the simple
thing of now it's not a bad cable
connection it's interference when it's
ly when the cable is lying on my table
so Let Me Maybe we can
actually do you hear this
now now I hear in my
ear uh the static buzzing sound it's not
even that bad right now but uh it's
there yeah you might have to turn it up
really loud in your ears it's there it's
there maybe I can make it
louder I don't know no it's not so bad
here well so what I did is just I hung
it up I changed my whole like position
of um oh it's beautiful no sound oh my
God it's so beautiful I was going crazy
um yeah I changed it so that the cable
didn't have to run across the um table
cuz I had my mixer on my right side and
my microphone on my left side so the
cable ran
across oh it's gone
holy it so
[Music]
nice
yeah oh my sanity like it got so bad
that I I I it was hard to sit on my
computer with the headphones
on without muting my
microphone yeah oh oh it feels good
feels
good
it feels
good so good so
[Music]
good now now we have to figure out uh
why GTA is in such an awkward solution
resolution why why what happened did I
do
this why is it so
Square we're going to finish the last D
but somebody said I only have like two
hours left of it so that's pretty good I
got so close to finishing but I didn't
want to force myself last time
so uh yeah we're going to do both today
I
guess but the the solution doesn't
change in the game did it I don't
remember that doesn't why is it
uh you thought I had more like 4 hours
but what the
how do I oh wait it's Graphics not
display
why why wouldn't it be
display uh is it
440 uh apply oh
yeah oh yeah oh
yeah that seems that seems
perfect let me move you guys my chat
chat here we go nine missions in two
hours you're laughing at me oh no games
yeah
yeah how dare you laugh at me like
that okay whoa that's threatening so
threatening it's kind of loud probably I
might have to lessen
it we're not getting to Gay Tony today
are we well maybe not so
what oh I should put piercings on my
face okay welcome back everybody it's
been a while cuz cuz I cancelled it I
think last time
right
[Music]
oh I don't remember uh I we're a
biker gang we're biker gang and the boss
dead right and I am now the
boss
uh and everybody's full of
something like that I don't know I
forgot how great this game is it's so
great I stand out so much should I make
myself
gray or at least
grayer oh oh maybe maybe like this
that's
nice do I blend it nicely I lowered my
saturation wow so good
do I look straight when I look here or
do I still look
[Laughter]
gay so funny I'm so funny no for real
though do I look
straight kanana the
gray with me bro
you n
okay oh
I have potato chips by the
way oh did I just activate
that okay but I have to hold myself back
to not eat everything right away just
salt flavor I just like simply salt
flavor I always go for salt
is feed them to the
screen here here here here H
wait does that sound like you ate
it
what are we doing what are we what's our
mission what are we like in right
now does it say
[Music]
anywhere I have no idea what I'm doing
but I guess we'll just go to some
letters the
J let's hit the
J we go to E why do we go to E why not
J you're you're
uh
alphabeto phobe you're
scared you're scared of the J the J J is
cool too okay Jay's
closer hit
the don't no more where's the exit
though H
wa I have no idea where I
am hello am I like
downstairs don't you lost I am lost I
shall be damned
too exit
oh
man man I found the exit slower than the
UK
[Laughter]
did I'm so
funny
I'm on
the um oh yeah I remembered how to get
on the bike let's go it's not really my
bike right don't I have a better bike
holy there's so many bikers B bike
b b
bik no I didn't have energy drink I had
orange juice and I had you know the
butter kind of bread with butter and
Nutella for
breakfast just a little while ago but I
I slept so
well I mean besides somehow having a lot
of back pain while I was
sleeping and having weird ass dreams the
only thing I really remember though
is my mom had like
a
um a a
tail I mean like a FL fluffy like like a
wolf wolf or fox tail more like a wolf
tail what the
uh and I'm like Mom what are
you why what why do you why did you why
did you put a tail what is that
what I was so
confused cuz the setting wasn't that she
actually grew one or so that she
naturally has it no the setting was I
was genuinely confused why she had it
but that was just a side side thing a
side quest in my dream story that was
up
yeah no she didn't have ears though only
the tail kind of weird not going to lie
it freaked me
out okay we're at the J I wonder what
this story
is me n what's going
on gentlemen Johnny you remember Ray
right how you doing how am I doing man
now it's got to be louder right oh God
if I tap back in I got the all over me I
got a boss who's a paranoid wreck and I
got a guy above me in the food chain
with a break
louder
wait like an overed
joke
wait things are great a subtitle sound
like to me but whatever so uh why
you here I heard your boys is having a
little internal dispute yeah where'd you
hear that from from Ashley you friends
with Ashley everybody's friends with
Ashley tough
guy H you know she's a good kid and all
a little messed up but you know she
needed a friend r they told us what
Brian is oh yeah where and how the hell
does he know all right don't go breaking
my bosss all right I talk to Brian a
half an hour ago and listen I understand
where you guys are coming from and on
one end I don't give a bunch of
Grease Monkeys want to having all our
gang bang be my guest you're all
adults what's what what what what's
going on I need Cal Billy's on the
inside I need a steady flow of
merchandise who is he again so it's in
my interest to see that you boys calm
things
down end this little squabble and get
back to
work drama mob mob boss Diamond guy see
you later bye
buddy so what do you think Johnny
Italian mob for I think that guy makes
my skin crawl but now that you mention
it so does Brian right now he's our
problem what does he ask us to do though
I was setting I was trying to a lot of
people headphones louder means too
much anymore anymore so so I'm going to
go pay Brian a visit and see just what
that fat fucker's problem is see you all
later mm
mhm
okay now let me turn on the subtitles
now I didn't want to do it right
now
um
subtitle
[Music]
uh um uh
sub ah why are they off why would I turn
them off makes no
sense
y potato chips y
y
guys guys I'm a
genius let me just tell you I'm a
genius double DLC damn I'm a
genius can we get to the second DLC
today we'll see oh hey I'm armored up
even I don't need to buy armor this
time I don't think I know how to play
this game anymore though oh my driving
comes naturally now
[Music]
soy
wow the pavement kind of like makes me
like forces me to stay on the side wow
so
go just need a little warm up yeah it's
my birthday Dusty e it's your birthday
we're going to party like it's your
birthday I'm going to shoot some people
let's go happy
birthday in your pants too and happy
birthday in your
[Music]
shoot this place is so far where are we
going I'm just following my
Navy na guys you want to hear something
unbelievable you're not going to believe
it you are not going to believe
[Music]
it should die this
go I'm covering them ah all right
right
right I what about what about here am I
good here but then I might cover up some
of the
subtitles but I didn't want to be on the
right side either because I don't want
to cover up the mic the phone it's
unbelievable I watched anime yesterday
several
episodes suddenly
something overcame me the feeling of
the desire to maybe possibly watch some
anime and thus I finished watching
Violet evergarden I watched like like
five or six episodes no probably
more until the
end and it was beautiful I cried so much
especially the episode where don't worry
I won't spoiler really the episode where
um she
writes letters and they won't for some
mother and they won't tell you what
she's writing until the end of the
episode like even you the
audience I cried so much it's like a
baby I think that was the most tear
inducing one for
me
[Music]
oh
M yeah that oh you guys know what I'm
talking about
huh yeah overall the anime was really
good it wasn't quite what I what I
expected I didn't think like every
episode would basically just be about
another like family or so that she
writes a letter for and but I I get it I
get I see what they're trying to do
they're like telling a story each time
how she changes someone's life and they
changed her life because one more and
more she learns about emotions and all
that and becomes more and more human
like right I get it right I get it yeah
have V got in yay let's
go you're happy aren't
you yeah and and just her learning how
to understand her own emotions and and
learning that she has emotions and how
to show them and that they're okay to
have and that it's normal to have and
this and that and that it's um okay to
go through what you have experienced
like
PTSD um like learning how to deal with
that and all that
yeah so it was it was good it was really
good and then I noticed like Netflix um
has like this Violet everun in
collection that kind of confuses me is
there anything new there like I think
there's two movies right and then
there's like
two weird collections that I don't
understand what that is but there's no
second season
right ah oh it's special
episodes
really a second movie is the ending
okay I don't know if you guys want to
watch them with me otherwise I'll just
watch them alone
probably cuz CU yeah I just started
watching the whole anime on my own it
was really good and yeah uh comfortable
convenient because it's just on Netflix
I can just watch it
there and yeah kill Annie of course K
cannot make anything lesser of a
masterpiece
C I need to
Goat yeah I liked it I liked it really
good wouldn't mind another that's true
that I like that too watching like 10
different animes First episodes with you
guys that was a good
idea so I
sorry for the
Tang Brian is protected in his safe
house I mean I wouldn't want to be in
prison or anything but I you know I I
take it Johnny the rat he looks
famili take up Brian for
dinner I guess it's the right time for
dinner I'm
hungry uh do we go
inside what gun do I
have where's my pink shotgun also oh the
the front is
[Music]
barricaded
can we enter from
here the back door Johnny's here hi do I
kill everybody or just one guy
oh
everybody
wait wait the
aim a aim
aim I've of You cover your ah why do you
reload like that you bastard Brian give
it up brother
give it up
for an
die already lost half of my
armor Brian but I'm warming
up get the down get down holy
why does it need to reload so often you
rip this G apart
[Music]
weak Fox Brian Brian Brian
Brian that sounds like the dog Brian
Brian can't look after himself I always
knew you were a trump you little
who's talking sometimes I don't know
who's talking they all sound so close to
my ears watch your ammo you're mine you
weasel
hi
where let me just look at your face
where are you little
girl boss never
die brother it's time I was just going
to check if anyone's left in here yep
yep se you ready for
this can you stop the trash talk good
night Brian stop stop stop it's so toxic
man hello we were your brothers Brian I
know they're upstairs but I'm just
checking I'm just I'm just
curious Brian you
little look out
the
damn son you surprised me last time I
checked there was no one
there where are you you anti-semitic
I got
you you're dead
man this house is up man di your
boo someone needs to take care of those
stairs ass how do you even get up there
jump or what to live
forever Brian Brian Brian Brian Brian
Brian oh get down I you a you little
what the hello calm down
please oh I see you weasel you
push
me I know I know Cube I don't want to
use it right now I feel more free
nice aim is Brian brother it's
time still alive got okay you're swore
an oath Johnny O funky wallpapers I'll
get out of
town the aim is so
like
you suddenly it asked me to save okay
that's so weird Tor what tor
I love the tutors let's
go okay I'm out of
here I'm out of here Jonathan where's
Brian halfway to hell my brother we
don't need to worry about that little
pull way good to know I'll stop looking
over my shoulder well until billy gets
out of prison at least stay in touch
ah h how do I get
down wait
what not
here I am so
confused it's so hard to walk through
doors and anything
really driving is not an issue but
walking walking that's a definite issue
oh hello bike that's not even my
bike
hey my back is still here y I have a
message what is this
message you should sleep in E Brian's
old apartment he won't be turning up
there again sure beats that old bed at
the club oh it's considered one of my
homes now
oh that feels really up
though all right let's go on a drive
are you ready long drive this don't you
love long
drives yeah especially with the bodies
are we just going to leave them
there I guess it's better than jumping
them and then having somebody find them
and then you
know people trying to find out what
happened to the
bodies music do no
I want
[Music]
silence here I am your
music isn't the silence just souping and
beautiful I love it it's h I'm enjoying
the
silence
sheesh so yeah now I now I don't know
maybe I'll watch more
anime
oh that's a what's that a side quest or
so depending on what I can find I just
want to watch anything that's like
easily accessible for me cuz I don't
have like any like anime subscription
thingies for like what what's it called
crunchy roll for
example I don't have that and I don't
want to like go for the trouble of
getting it in a different way so they do
have a lot on Netflix though yeah just
wonder if they have the good stuff
what what other do you guys know what
other good animes are on
Netflix one piece is on
Netflix until what episode like are
they are they on on um track like on on
updated
I'm not interested in
Rojo sorry about punk I don't little
witch Academia I watched that before
before I stopped watching
anyway okay so far all these titles
don't interest
me is spy family on there on
Netflix is it
really
yes no yes
no Kaku is also one that I watched
before I stopped watching anime
mhm I've seen
[Music]
it okay I have no idea what my happy
marriages oh
kakuru yeah kakuru is kind of crazy I
don't know if I would watch that
[Music]
nowadays I want to watch something like
ni Jo or working is there anything new
out there that's like that
just
just I watched that when I was younger
mhm M oh yeah I should watch Dragon Mage
that's one
of I can imagine it being up my alley
maybe a
Bui maybe I will I yeah I should watch
bii m
okay but Boi not on Netflix right Boi
and dragon M are they is any of those on
Netflix Love is War we tried that one
kaguya we tried that one and it didn't
speak to me at
all I don't
want
wormans I mean at least not on anime
like not this kind of
Roman
[Music]
I would have probably liked it when I
was younger but not now dub or sub just
sub so wait
what what did you say let me no let me
scroll in my chat no I can't scroll well
let me
scroll yeah yeah cringey that's what I
feel where you think you're going got to
hold up I'm talking to you all right
back off of him you stupid can't
you tell the difference between an arc
and one of my upstanding business
associates I'm sorry about here it's
impossible to find Good Help in this
city don't worry about it hey what up
Johnny Boy what talk to you girl let's
make it happen Captain I didn't think
you lost bikers got down with people
like Mar here well I don't have a crunch
subscription looking at the two of you
don't make no sense to me it's a crazy
City well this is crazy times Liz
there's a recession going on recession
and in this troubling econom you got to
make compromises I when the economy
up hey you clown you can
compromise nuts give me these for us
people always going to can't
communicate they're going to want even
more products when they lose their jobs
and ain't got nothing else okay I guess
all we got to worry about is the cops
taking us down then true that cat hey yo
eat let them know what it is you got got
to take some thieving snitching
and show them I'm a
but I ain't they
okay you are a but not their
okay I get that I get the
difference you guys going to go down
there and tear them
apart it is now get the out of
here okay
Ma she could have like a snack bar you
know
she seems like the type to have a snack
bar you know one of those like Japanese
style snack
bars I think we better take a cage on
this run can you get your people to
bring our bikes to the drop off
everybody respects her handle this
Johnny everybody takes her orders lead
the way
Johnny
sorry the the too expected has happened
what was all this with you I can't
stop eating the potato chips I thought
you could handle it I can't handle Focus
now I'll TR one cold female and I don't
want her thinking I'm a then I
guess you got to prove yourself no
pressure man go yourself
Johnny these people they love each other
so much everybody's so nice to each
other so titty this is one serious gun
Amigo this what they call a street
sweeper this this is what they call car
through any mother problem maker no
doubt guess thisy hit like shot it's a
shotgun right she's dishing out should
be interesting the pink problem I gave
it that name just now what's going on
why is our Point
here and why is there a Sky
rat I have to get
awesome
sky
Ah hell no what you support the sky rats
in this
city come on I didn't kill a
person it was a sky
rat
Sky I didn't do
anything I literally didn't do anything
so
Fair they hate on me they bully
me oh yeah part of my dream was
about
some
bullying I was like it was like a game I
was like
flying some machine I
think oh it's hard to
remember and and some
someone really H how do you say it had
it out for me really
wanted me to die or
so it's like specifically
me excuse me it's my P now we're going
the other side now I am make the
[Music]
decisions it was weird but the good
thing is because it was a game I
uh when when in big trouble I could
just press
Escape in my dream press escape and then
just uh get
out and hope that he would leave and
then I would log back
in and hope that he doesn't notice that
I'm back but I didn't get very far that
thing will always bother
me that
knife okay our problem is now that I
can't came from the wrong side I guess
um all right all right no not again shut
up I'll go from here and they want us
from the other side
right typical MMO experience
mhm but somebody really really
really has their eyes set on
you and it's so obsessed St
here
now that was a weird dream but at least
this time smoothie let me sleep through
yesterday too good girl Rush here okay
listen to me man you got to get out of
the way you're holding up traffic what's
the problem here what's going on is
somebody having a baby you don't got
change you're not going through those
are the rules I think she's having a
baby to him so just turn around and head
back I come back the exact change that
you need all right just let us through
please pay my bills and put food on the
table turn around I got some change
right here let's get this moving
all right this one's on us now move your
ass thanks guys doing great honey it's
okay no she's having a baby what did you
think what's going on
yeah no super chats because GTA that
little family didn't come through here 5
minutes
later it's good though cuz I'm still a
little bit behind I finished the
anniversary super chats though nearly
here the ship which one that
one uh o I have a weird gun
interesting get in
here oh you all oh do I have
something what's
that
uh oh there's so many
oh oh I wasn't supposed to do
that God damn Johnny all that gone
was get paid now no we ain't later on
[Music]
man wow but there's so many
people
going look where they're restarting me
bless is
a rush here
okay
amazing I'll still try to rocket
launcher at least for the the front cars
I can blow up the front cars right you
should think about a second
career these guys ain't going to know
what hit
them we just need the shipment okay
surprise oh
sorry is that my friend you Fook
the Convoy steal events
uh don't
[Laughter]
die
crazy okay okay maybe not supposed to be
done like
[Laughter]
this okay okay okay there's like really
close checkpoints we can try it every
way every way we want
to
but I'm losing
my I'm not getting back back my rocket
launcher munition am
I you have guns yeah but I just
wanted I don't
know if only he would run
faster okay okay okay we'll wait for the
van to pull up about sitting in little
booths and wearing uniforms that turns
guys into
we're about to see what we're made of
people we got to get that white
SH
now so do I not
shoot yeah yeah you're good to go you're
good go okay we wait for the mhm we wait
for the
van wait don't I recognize you
stop talking just let him through you
like let him
throughing okay okay and now we get it
in we kill him though first right
before like
now okay okay okay
okay
let me in let me in let me in let me in
let me in oh hey no hit yet no hit let's
go see me jump I was trying to jump over
that but I guess that that wasn't how it
works all right here we go I'm just
stealing the van I'm running away from
the police right for now for
now hey I'm already out of the circle
can I stay
here yeah
is is baby we we we what now are they
still do they need me oh I ditched my
friends
well I'll come back I'll try if they're
not already
dead does it
matter interesting car
though sorry guys I'm a little bit stuck
I'll take a little bit longer to come
back for your
rescue I'm already back hey are these my
friends
no get in here don't die I'm here I'm
here hey I'm giving you cover I'm giving
you cover is he is he in the car get in
how many more do I need to get get in oh
he's not a
friend okay uh is that is that all it
why is he why is he
leaving why did he
leave why did he
leave where did he
leave
dud get in again quick you idiot
Baka
M okay I lose the cops but there's still
blue over there there's still some
blue there's still some blue there or is
that the police now oh it's the
police he bought F was for reloading hey
why is he getting out again
what that's not on me that's on him he
went out of the car
twice oh my
God
oh yeah there we
go huh why did I confuse the game cuz I
I like it I think it happened at each
time when I drove through the
toall that was so
weird but that still shouldn't be a
reason for him to
leave h
it wasn't in the cut scene what is it
about sitting in Little Boots anding
uniforms I only need to bring one of
them with me whoever that was what about
the rest of the people made of people oh
we got to get that white oh normal
guy
okay uh normal guy
[Laughter]
no
AI
oh oh
man the dude in the booth is that the
only one we
[Music]
need yeah yeah you let me oh my
God
so can I shoot
you going to make me lose my mind give a
okay let's get
in oh the dead body is inside get
out
[Laughter]
also not the right way to do it okay
okay okay
okay they shot for the back oh maybe the
side doesn't have to be the
back should I kill them all it wasn't
really necessary last time it was just
Mark who was like not getting into the
freaking car doing so great honey you're
doing so great keep it up keep
up man you look good in that Booth CU
there's so much to shoot and eventually
it's like how can we do this with like
Free People Convoy nearly here we just
need the shipment
okay it happened again it's not driving
though go go go
Okay police
police why does he not get in trouble
for
that my might seems everybody to
come keep
moving I have an idea of this me when
they leave I'll shoot them with the
rocket
launcher ah
n good enough uh
okay you better hope you kill
me Nice Nice Shot Nice Shot is he dead
no I should have gotten Armor man
you all right there yeah man that's cool
oh oh oh oh got to be careful they're
shooting me from over
there okay can I oh sorry that's friend
right can I get in
now no
yikes
oh but those those don't seem so
dangerous
I'm getting in I'm getting in give a
get in to the get in
yeah yeah that's what I'm talking about
let's go don't get out anymore who is
that friend is that a friend no only
only ma is my
[Music]
friend only one sty should be easy
there's a car over there though just
I'll just wait a little bit cool good
work yeah
yeah see it's that simple uhoh you're
driving the wrong way buddy sure thing
Jonathan
sh I had it in me all this time Riders
are you a motorc like us and the angels
of death oh the car is so loud can
I have the voices
louder it's both sfx isn't it man car is
so loud we ride bikes we ride them hard
but the thing is we don't wear fancy
dresses or do pinky finger shakes or
anything like that so I ain't sure what
that makes us we're adults here Malcolm
allegedly Johnny Boy allegedly so let's
not let this descend into an argument
about the merits of good American
Machinery versus foreign Plastic
Fantastic crap or why you guys look like
rejects from a bondage club or why you
guys dress like the Republican Space
Rangers ouch anyway what I'm asking is
what's the deal with this music you put
out and the Branded clothing and
just part of our Vibe man why is
navigation telling me to go this way
when it's obviously
not you know we a complete subculture
like you guys used to be back in about
what 63 or something completely
lost if you ask me we've still got hard
man the Lost MC are still here we just
don't get on me TV and scream about MTV
sure you are whatever you say Johnny Boy
whatever you say
John an anime available on Netflix are
thinking of the USA version oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah it I know it might be very
different I know I asked you guys
but it might be very different for my
Austrian German
Netflix but I did see like when
scrolling through that there is a lot of
an on
there in
theory what does MTV oopsie what does
MTV even show
nowadays do they still have those shitty
shows that were somehow enjoyable for
some reason cringe cringe though from
back in the day like like MTV next and
all these like love themed
shows
it's still reality
TV oh okay do they have any of the
classics from back in a day still
running well now that's a fine little
Nest day to get us through a low point
in these here Global markets baby sure M
I'm just hoping and Pregnant stay out of
jail long enough to enjoy it no they
make a TV show about 16 and
Pregnant I feel like that's just going
to motivate some 16 year olds because
they want to get on
TV oh
no oh no they've had that one for ages
really Johnny did you get rid of that
stupid bike of yours and drive my V for
me yeah I did it handle like a piece of
I dumped it in the lock up you
mentioned if you're interested not in
the v baby but maybe I'm interested in
working the back of it they used to have
soon you know the birthday party show
for 16 year-olds now it's play a for 16
year olds man times have
[Laughter]
[Music]
changed
she from the birthday party
to man what
happened s 16 it's my time to shine s
[Music]
you know wouldn't MTV in theory by being
a music uh TV thingy the
perfect
uh TV channel to have like music
survival shows they should do
that that would be
already better than anything they have
now probably
what when did MTV have music survival
shows they never did not that I
know no
I involve actual effort
e you one
second CH
chica now all you got to do is walk to
are you home
free it's not in
yeah don't worry about my friend Johnny
H he's uh he's ugly but he don't
[Laughter]
bite
Andreas D Andreas why do I protect me
when you don't do nothing I was in in
the kitchen I was doing the I don't want
no excuses get the back in
the
kitchen is he her M Jesus
hey Johnny boy what's up you had a good
time the other day with those boys huh
men in their motorcycles sure why we
need to hit that Convoy so hard you know
all these bodies can't be good for your
business you don't think I could survive
out here if I wasn't dropping some
people H I'm the big boss
okay I mean I
respect the fact that people respect her
all right now you're starting to sound
like
Billy they're going to hate you because
you a woman in this Macho world
mhm they're going to hate you cuz you
from the island super people think
Latinos ain't wor in this
town when you the big boss and you me
this bodies got to come with it
okay I came up from a rough
background didn't tried to turn me out
when I was 14 years
old I fed him his balls oh let's go wow
just saying you should limit your
casualties when I ended that
I got a reputation in PR no man
touched me after
that nice nice I a't saying all men are
bad she's so proud them if I thought
that right
all
right okay okay go get my girl Mara she
just came in on the arios flight from
adios flight you think this an airline
called adios like nice again once the
have their party yeah it's fine
yeah yeah she'll love it
okay where
Andreas you missed a spot I miss
spot and get that spot off my
couch he really her M isn't
he
Andreas come
[Music]
BR you little
why is he not wearing a cute maid
outfit huh if she really wants to assert
dominance she should make him wear a
cute M
outfit
you
know you might not want to hear
this but devious
mates was a really really
entertaining TV
show it's like
um devious M was uh made from same
people who made um Desperate
Housewives and it's about like maids in
the really rich neighborhoods
experiencing a lot of crazy
from the rich
people and
then
yeah trying to survive that
it's just because you like mates
well I do like mates and they're all hot
as yeah they're hot as
but I like the criminal as ECT of
that
show the rich people are so
funny the rich
families in that
show oh I should buy armor before I go
to the next mission and I'll heal myself
here hot dog
please you should watch more up beaches
I do I generally
do and devious maid is like mostly funny
anyway there's some drama but they make
it mostly a funny show uh where is uh
closest armor oh not so bad not so bad
ikim
Masa
maua guys yesterday I had a feast maybe
it saw on Twitter some people thought I
cooked that I didn't cook it does it
look like I cooked it did I have to
clarify I cooked the thing I uploaded
later on but uh the Korean food was from
a
restaurant which my Korean
teacher uh suggested to me
before I was really good actually I was
uh surprised I was able to eat um more
than I thought I could my
[Music]
here
uh 5,000 five thousand I need a
big job okay I need one of the big jobs
so that I can afford this why do I
have so little
money I don't understand
uh I think the other things I don't
really
need like ammo I think I still have
enough
ammo
probably hey is an older Hospital wait
how much are they charging me for each
hospital visit for each like
failure of mine where's my where's my
bike did they take my
bike be let me
I know I'm
blind
it no way no way they charge me 20K each
time
nah nah then I wouldn't even be able to
afford my next
visit 1K well you guys don't seem to
really know what's the right answer
welcome to yeah I'm not talking about
real life yeah real life probably 20K
holy holy
[Music]
welcome to America honestly I don't
know how you guys even
survive
uh a health system like that I'm sorry
but like like who has that kind of money
huh so you just accept that you're sick
or or or have a broken leg or so or
rather die in the mountains after a
skiing accident or or birth your child
at home because the hospital is too
expensive how do you how
how have to get a sugar mommy sugar
daddy to stay
[Music]
alive
guys don't send me so many super chats
if you're in America you never know
what's going to
happen what was I talking about the
before
this yeah the the Korean food so my
favorite was I think the chap
CH which if I'm not wrong was the glass
noodles those are really
like the taste was really like you know
easy GS Ain usually this cute this is
going to be fun
heyab I don't know about you but the
America I believe in doesn't Deport hard
working young girls like this one yeah
well the only thing this girl works hard
out swall bags of coke and in a minute
blowing me so hey hold on your name
Marta
see coming with me keep your head down
on the bike let's
go where
we what do
we clear the area of
cops oh
what how did I do
that
how is that
normal that's a that doesn't shoot so
far
it
[Music]
yeah local
loal very
local can I blow this one up
somehow oh wait let me get
[Music]
the
yeah it came tumbling down so nicely so
[Music]
pretty I'm not even zooming in and still
getting all the hits Look At Me Nice
Shot uh who's left I don't see it what
are you saying just sit tight there we
go can we go
now or do I really have to kill
everybody sorry about the welcoming
party sweet cheeks but you got to stay
down we go
now I would like to go now can I what am
I going with like any
car let go
go locco Loco can we take the taxi get
in sit tight do you do we need to take
the
bike oh I have to kill everybody for
real for real
okay the
cleaner poor cleaner but where I don't
see them they're supposed to be there ah
there he
moved
and ah
him yeah okay go get Marta uh-huh well
we can take the bike honestly find some
Wheels oh three stars I think
escaping with the bike as them with the
car I
[Music]
think cuz I'm way more like
Dynamic what is she saying guys
translator notes
please there were no subtitles just now
what the
[Music]
hell boy
what she
[Music]
say go per no that was not per
right let's go Johnny Johnny boy hey
Johnny you're so
[Music]
fine
you drive she turned
finish okay oh we did it what that was
easy holy take the drag
meal to isab she's the drug mule isn't a
mule like an animal I'm taking your back
to
elizabeta that's you Marta you first
time Liberty City city
swingers listing all these things
Liberty City Liberty C Liberty City very
good you learn good I mean you're
learning very
well what did you
expect this this one thing I don't
understand wow nice graphic bugs when
you know the person doesn't understand
understand
you why do you keep on talking out loud
in the language that we don't
understand I don't do that either when
I'm like overseas and nobody gets
me no speaking do you realize we don't
understand oh my God you up
Jimmy feel the silence that mean I
understand still having a conversation
with yourself but why not in your brain
why why out loud like I will not
understand you anymore if you talk
more I do not
understand the same reason people talk
to themselves I guess and people who
talk to themselves out loud in public
are aren aren't they a little bit
locco uh isn't that a little bit
Lo
[Music]
yeah feeling
attacked I'm sorry but don't I never saw
someone speaking in public to
themselves who didn't seem kind of off
off at the same time filing a vlog yeah
that's YouTubers and there are also
local that's also local loco
loco okay here we
areas
Johny Bluetooth yeah yeah yeah that
keeps on confusing me nowadays
everybody's like talking to themselves
um like with on the phone but with like
a just an earpiece and you can't even
see that's really one techn thing that
has been invented that I don't like
because it confuses me is the person
talking to themselves because they're
crazy are they actually talking to me
are they on the phone I don't know what
where am I
going huh what's what's happening guys I
hatte it too yeah it's so
confusing I got some work for you and M
come see me
Liz oh yeah okay oh okay I wait I just
dropped off the lady that's what I did
she just disappeared and I'm not
supposed to go in okay
okay you wear earphones so you don't
look crazyy What's happen you mean with
a cable shut the
up
huh eat oh yeah she's pretty no no no no
no we got to go shit's got to get done
all right some other time then no I
don't think there's going to be another
time man shit's closing in all these
snitches all over the place you
hear that on your wire tap Andreas you
hear that maybe you guys should
uh get rid of him and sell this coke lat
huh you want us to take Marta off your
hands look after her until the Heat's
gone you ain't getting your hands on my
baby
girl you only got to worry about
yourself and selling that coke you don't
got to worry about about me and you
don't got to worry about her neither
okay okay come on let's do this yeah we
out I Amigos how she Bing me around I'm
the boss and you and anybody else who
shows up okay cuz that's the way I
roll roll that's the way I
roll
roll oh we got the gang let's
go
yay
uh how do I see my gang members H again
that crazy before that really wasn't on
me
man and now he's dooming hey aren't you
guys supposed to follow me I guess it's
not no it's not actually my
[Music]
gang tap it's not ah yeah okay I tried
that but I can't see it
go bu some like that it's because you
think there's something going
down they got more modern bikes too
I like your orange
bike wait what are we
ah I thought I was
here zooming to hide the same uhuh what
up kid got that package for you yeah is
she
Barbie what you been stepping on this
you
see p Punk like you looks like she could
be in the Barbie movie you do your job
and let us do whatever go ahead
girl
e please don't do drugs yeah it's good
so what you going to do good I'mma take
it for our own I don't think so well you
best change your mindset cuz this right
here is yeah
a you up now
yo you see what you did everything but
not my
bike bik
man how dare you
oh is dead is dead defend
this Sean from the cops what is this
what is this cam
what what what's how what's going on
what did I do why is the camera win how
do I undo it what did I press to make
the camera do like that
what the I don't want the news cam
why is it
cinematic v no ah I
don't oh V didn't
work
uh it doesn't say what the
press caps yeah that might have been
it
sh what who Am I who
am oh Japanese
keyboard wait I can't click anything in
when I Tab out nothing is
reacting H now it's reacting
okay's right on top of us uh uh what I'm
not actually driving uh
okay I think
no oh I am really not driving okay okay
holy that could have gone really
bad broke his car okay it's a party baby
it's a party in the
USA yeah the camera is still weird
unless I maybe that's on purp I'm sorry
you
friend maybe it's on
purpose every time I'm not pressing
right click it's just like that behind
we got on us I the I'm talking
about
well honestly to surprise I am not dead
in that situation man Des that
s diapers that ain't
right I know what it feels like to lose
a brother friend call me if you need no
no we redo this we are redoing it I'm
sorry that was a overall just a panicky
situation how did I live
right that was Michael Bay
directing Michael
B okay
uh
okay nice shot get closer I only have a
shotgun guys
broke down can't shoot that
far don't
you don't blow up so close to me holy
how am I continuously making it
blow up though that's
amazing you also shouldn't get so close
to me guys danger I'm a
danger danger zone here we go those CHS
need a mechanic do you guys in like na
or wherever out anywhere outside of
where I am you guys have a TV show like
vetan
D um where like there's
like
uh same
place
what
that's the same
place uh okay do you have
like a TV show that wasn't even my fault
where where where there's like
um we in a Time Loop where there's like
celebrities um and there's a big live
audience and then there a celebrities um
one by one coming in and they have to
say whether or not they believe that
uh some like
normal normal
person and claims they claim that they
bet that they can do something really
cool some specific skill you do you do
have the same program overseas over over
out of Europe out of Germany Austria oh
w w w w w
wow and then and then they try it like
live on TV and then and well they either
make it or they don't make
it do you have no not America has Got
Talent no no no no no no no no that's
not it it's like they would bet
something like I can guess I can guess
uh just by sniffing
blindfolded from which brand 15
different uh dog
thingies are uh-oh don't explode don't
explode don't
explode to stuff like that they come up
with these like super random
original um bets that they think they
can
do and it's it was like I don't know if
they still do this show because I
remember only seeing it like 15 years
ago maybe cop straight ahead
yeah do 100 flips in a minute exactly
like like all kinds of like whatever
they think they can do like something
special oh nice driving through
that and the celebrities there they're
just there I guess to get good views and
also to say I don't think you can do it
I think you can do it holy
wow G is really going to get expensive
now I did that
she
how do I still only have two stars for
[Music]
this my health was low should I get
armor before redoing this but I'm like
already like there right I can do it I
can do it problem with not having a car
is I don't have anything thing to give
me
cover yeah and it starts right away so I
can't get armor unless I like don't
choose the redo
option
yeah they were everywhere they were
everywhere no my goal isn't to
finish uh the game today wait I do
I my goal is to finish the game
today not
necessarily
fck be
careful
yeah byby don't blow up next to
me right now I have four stars now I
have four stars
so buit here we go
before it was just two stars a
bit a
b case of over steering If Ever I
[Music]
us anyway when I was younger I was
always thinking about what could I
possibly do to get on the
show what kind of skill what could I do
like I was actively thinking
up like ideas and thinking maybe I
should train this absurd skill or this
absurd skill I really wanted to be on
that
show but I never could think of anything
oh hi we got cops ahead yeah get
cops gone broke his car it was a
good show though but I think it ended
eventually because uh the the main guy
which
like the main MC who everybody knew the
show
for uh the
foras thas SC I think he got too old and
then he stopped doing the show I don't
think it's being done anymore was a
really good um concept though and the
other day I remembered the show and I
was just thinking
actually they got PID
I could see this concept working
for there we go for a vtuber seems like
these cops got us surrounded stream
plan
where I'm going to die look at my house
what do you how do I get off no I
pressed F but I'm staying on or what how
am I supposed to survive
this
what's with the
windows I
always okay thank you well nice car ooh
nice
car nice car hey okay oh my god oh we're
down to two
stars how am I supposed to
survive go go go go
go let me get a help offg please
let me get hot dog oh no m m I can't
reach a run run run drive drive why
where you stay why you stay Drive
drive
drive drive
idiot wait I I have nothing
[Applause]
left
what are we starting from the
beginning Mama
[Music]
Mia
I tried to take out the helicopter
it was too far away from a shitty
shotgun take out window oh we starting
here ah wait this one I hope these
things are insured we're stting here
wait we're full
health this the checkpoints are so nice
I even have a little bit of armor left
hey y
g they're so
nice that's a case of over steering If
Ever I saw one y you hungry M Dog yeah
they're nice of checkpoints
now you try to kill yourself I can't
reach that
helicopter a B right on top of bit
vamos vamos vamos
esos oh man leave us the alone
yeah okay here we
go we need you to get rid of behind us
this and okay now they really want
me to use high bombs oh okay uh how
[Applause]
again
okay uh uh is always on the
[Music]
left oh oh okay wow well
[Applause]
timed this is this is smooth
fun okay no need for any more for now I
think
oh I'll give you another one I think we
lost the last of the heat
boys yeah yeah how do they blow up
exactly when I want them to that's
fascinating one more to go Maniac Johnny
it's good it's
[Music]
good
y that was a wild ride Malcolm thanks
for making room on that pad always
space for you Johnny Boy and maybe we
should get us a room together at the
Jefferson Motel I heard you and your
brothers like that hardcore Hard Rock
bonding quit these flirtations B
all right right you got to take this
back Li right right yo catch you
around Johnny you want to kiss your
daddy whoa there peace out see you boys
later kiss see your
homies all right I took a few tries but
a lot of the failures were just like
cars exploding right next to me so I
can't even blame myself in my
opinion Johnny how it go do have some
bail money at least deal didn't happen
buyer got smart pigs got involved
friends are heading back with the
product things couldn't get much worse
here you know you know this is I was
quite sure though youare from me and for
a while okay see you all right yeah
that's good I need a I need El a bit
detox weird times call for weird
measures liist ala detox that's exactly
what I
need so if we don't go to Elizabeth beta
do we have something else not right now
apparently so I'll wait for a call
yeah oh bike orange bike how broken is
it
yeah yeah I don't think I can use that
looks pretty messed
up rest in pece bike Ashley Ashley what
is it this time hey Johnny boy it's
nothing I mean it's something but but it
ain't like you think I need you to meet
a friend of mine Ray bino it tellan name
what are you doing with him we're not
doing nothing Johnny not a good sign in
GTA I need you to meet him as all we're
over at Drilla in Little Italy can't
wait to see you baby baby she called me
baby all right I'm coming I'm on my way
if I ever find a way to get up there I
need the Legend of Zelda um thingy that
teleports me up there
yeah so anyway about that show
idea basically what I would say is like
maybe two judges or
so who you know try to guess whether or
not someone can make it and judge
everything and then like several
girls uh like four or
five showing off some absurd
skill like it it can even be like
totally made up like they would say like
I said as an example
sniff 15 different cat food uh
samples and try to
say which ones they
are yeah but I think in 3D this would
work better overall somebody could even
do like I don't know some some athletic
bet or so but you know what maybe I'll
bring this up to management and has like
a idea
for a 3D stream
actually can I get a car can I get a uh
car where am I maybe I take a taxi
honestly I maybe take a cab oh but
actually we also need to go to I'll go
to Ashley but first I go to weapons with
a taxi how do you call a taxi again e no
q
no
M oh hold e hey taxi I'll just take this
one
maybe and then do I press F long yeah
you got something I need please bring me
to where I need to go thank you I need
to go to
yeah I'm a genius thank you I know yeah
maybe maybe I'll bring it up surely they
would appreciate some ideas for like
game show type of 3D stream for like
every now and then they do that kind of
stuff so I think I think it's not
impossible Mr but then my condition for
me giving them the idea would be that I
would be included you should have
thought about being more forthcoming
earlier in our relationship as it
happens others in your fraternity are
not as loyal as you I don't know what
the you're talking about you're
about to see a close friend on the
witness stand time's up Johnny I'll
believe it when I see it you tight ass
prick adios we sell quality weapons and
we know how to use
them what do you think about my idea
guys
H I think it's quite genius
TB see you again I wouldn't even need to
be a judge I could think of some some
I'll I'll learn something just for
the sake of
this bye
you you better I'll take this
car buddy She's
mine sounds like would be super fun
sounds like
good I yelled but that's not really a
bet like what am I supposed to be
betting it has to be more than just the
yeling like
um
H I don't
know it could also be like I just saw on
Home Improvement sniffing different
types of wood and
guessing where it's from what kind of
wood it
is stuff like that you
know or I I don't know I don't remember
all these beds it's been a long
time burping the alphabet that could be
one here I guess it's not really
something I would doubt that you can do
Johnny I up I up real bad
you do I messed up baby promise you
won't be mad what did you do I'm an
addict I need help what the did you
do you must be Johnny who are you my
name is not important what is this your
woman ow de Ras he's got a gun guys okay
we need you to do us F they're so calm
what we need you to kidnap someone for
us why need you to kid well I'm not in
the kidnapping business dude and I'm not
in the dude business dude
you either do it or junky gets killed
not difficult decision even for a man
stuck in 196 why do finger gun when you
have real gun dude it's easy you grab
him deliver him to Warehouse of lampak
in ban industrial and this will pay off
her debts
well it pays off interest wonderful the
name of the man we want is Roman bik oh
he runs a cab business Roman hangs
around some backro gambling place on D
Street in shutler I got it what you find
him you take him Roman my man
now Ashley you got to stop
things up now you know how Roman
got kidnapped
a I I do remember that
vaguely now we'll get to see the other
side of the
story dude you busy I got something and
I don't need it getting around the
clubhouse I'll owe you brother what you
need Johnny I need to snatch some guy
name of uh Roman Bellic runs a cab firm
in debt to some Russians you down I'll
pay all right I'm up on y nor see you in
a minute okay why why let me into my car
please thank
you I need a hot dog too when I see one
oh there's clucking Bell
though let's go to clucking
Bell phasia
Latina
a what does that actually mean something
sounds like alcohol wait this clocking
Bell I think is
closed
what a bait how can you bait me like
that I need
H got take Roman to see some big
American tiitties is that is that what
I'm doing is that how we're going to
bait him hey Roman nice to meet you I'm
going to take you to see some big
American titties you in yeah let's
go actually was the downfall of
Johnny I can see that yeah
I can totally see
that no food's
Gohan maybe here that's a big street a
yeah hot
dog I'll take two of
those these small hot dog STS are so
cute m
yummy oh yeah yeah wait I want to go
back to the Korean food topic cuz I was
going to say I like the chap
CH and um the topoki was the first time
I ate
topoki the the kimab I ate before but
kimab I really
liked uh generally cuz like no Raw it's
like sushi but no raw fish so if you
guys ever see that in a Korean
restaurant or so it's not
Sushi I liked
it and uh uh I ate the
Jong with that has like it's like
noodles with uh like a
bean paste right got to go
here that one I was able to eat cuz it's
not spicy but flavor wise it wasn't
really my
thing uh it was like
very I don't know how to describe it but
uh it's just a very H mature
flavor feels like a very
mature not bitter but uh it's just
like not exactly my kind of thing Jam
[Music]
Yong
oh me I'm
sorry uh but uh what else uh the
generally we had like a lot of barbecue
so like
Bui in
several versions and just wrapped it in
the salad leaves I did that before
basically in Korea um but not with this
kind of meat it was a it was the the
tummy tummy stomach belly meat that was
like really fatty I didn't like that
when I ate it in in Korea because the
that meat I think it's a really
popular meat to eat in barbecue Korean
barbecue but I don't really like it cuz
it's like 90% fat it feels like yeah
pork belly
yeah
[Music]
mhm
not so much because I don't like it so
much
because I like the idea of like grilling
meat and then wrapping it in the
leaf the
salad Leaf yeah with some sauce and
whatever pork belly
slander I'm sorry I know it's Korean
soul food I
know I know that's why I feel so bad but
the other meats are
fine yeah
hell the rips I didn't try the rips
that's one of the few things we didn't
try Nice Rice rocket you got there come
with a fortune cookie as a matter of
fact it did understandable thank you
some 1950s looking who
preferred Rusty oil dripping junk to
Hightech Precision Machinery Rusty oil
dripping American junk please your
patriotism is making you ignant anyway
we going to go grab somebody what else
did I
have what else did I write down that I
have now know watch and learn my friend
let's go oh car car time the desserts
were so good but I wonder if the
desserts were actually something that's
common in Korea or if that was just
a thing of that restaurant cuz it was
absolutely genius we got to plan Johnny
Boy of course we got a plan we snatch
this guy deliver him to some
on the back I didn't eat alone sounds
simple as if you want Wing
presentation before every job you do you
you're running with the wrong Crow yeah
the to why you want snatch toi was fine
I'm doing this as a favor for I like the
must be a good friend texture oh it's
like that
isn't you know just m basically I'm
feeling but with a little bit of a spicy
sauce she ain't my old lady all right if
I understand correctly there's also
different sauces for
to she's a friend and she's in trouble I
believe in looking out for people youve
been close to you and your boys might
ride but you don't know nothing about
Brotherhood I think I know they talk so
much I think I would enjoy it more with
a different sauce maybe but this is
probably the most classic cookie
sauce it's just a bit spicy that's my
problem but I could eat it it's fine she
in trouble I don't know both maybe
it shut upar you know M I think you've
got unresolved women issues were you
close to your mother growing up yeah red
one most common I think so yeah Ain
kidnapping nobody because of my M it's
your lady us to do this think on that
son they served it on some type of like
fish though on top of it was toi with
some fish but I didn't eat the fish my
friend ate the
fish
so so I want to know Korean
Bros
uh spring wall for dessert filled with
fruit for example a banana is that
normal
and
kza filled with Apple for dessert is
that a thing you do it was genius it was
so good it was like actually so
good yeah it was so good and then it was
to with some vanilla sauce but I think
you could also top it with like cinnamon
and
sugar yeah then it's basically like an
Austrian dessert that we have the Apple
the Apple rattle
Apple yeah kza with apple filling and
spring rolls with banana filling it was
perfect guys just like a banana F uh uh
banana inside some like um
crunchy uh T dough
mhm it it fit perfectly honestly I love
that never have that in
Korea I wonder how they got the idea
maybe it was more of a Chinese
thing I don't know or their original
thing I really liked it uh also we had
this like kimy
B I think that's what it was called so
it was rice um a little bit spicy rice
because it's like kimchi mixed into rice
I
think Roman
Roman that was also quite spicy so I
didn't eat that much hurries up and
loses his money so we can snatch him
brother clock here Fri keep your
eyes where is
he I see a
taxi does he come out of a
taxi
Roman oh there he is let's get him hey I
feel so
bad hello hey man how you doing please
gentlemen the men and there just took my
money I can't get rubbed twice in one
day what do you want the shirt off my
back come on we're not rubbing you we're
taking you a chip
chubby get in there shut up shut your B
Ass
Up Man Poor Roman you're one in ban
fatty go to the warehouse no Roman no my
man uh one thing I wanted to eat all the
SLS in this city wear shitty track suits
man is he stuffed well it couldn't cuzz
I was already say something I can get
money I already ordered so much was I
don't know I some kind of uh what's it
called he money some cold noodles with
some spicy sauce but us also some
veggies and egg come full of unar 20s
right your man is like trying to
us I hope he know that you and me are
men of
yeah and that we'd find next time real
insulting it looks so good but spicy
sauce I wonder how
spicy don't cry to insult us Mr Roman
bellet I sure hope
not help I wish I could I wish I could R
now tell this gentleman what my kind of
people do to guys who try to buy their
way out just so you know who you're
dealing with Mr Bell this is one screwed
up dumb redneck
[Laughter]
I was
pushed I who the pushed that
bus pushed me get your ass back
here I swear to God threaten but don't
kill him what do you mean I'm I going I
what do you mean he got away how did h h
h that little why is I didn't
even good ending for
him how did a fat like that
get away from two young fit dudes like
us exactly yeah this has got to be kind
of just went to the police oh my
God good ending for Roman
Roman The Escape Artist man how do you
like bam Mr Bell some pals are waiting
for you there okay one more
time
yeah one more
time was anyway a a fun lunch with lots
of different food I love it because it's
like help me you can
Grill but then there's so many choices
of side dishes oh the the the the one
with the fried uh
veggies I really liked that one that had
a really like uh simple Mother
flavor not not spicy not weird I really
like that one you see I'm trying to
drive here you pop it you know
what I mean the fried veggies the yellow
looking thing man I just got me this
yeah is
vegetable and there were other twg Gams
but I like the yach
twg just shut this dude
up
TW very good yo I told you I like this
gun no no you little get in get in
how do I make him get in get in get in
get in get in fron but do not all you
little
FR get get in I'll shoot you dick
hell redo
redo run man is it because I just
stopped for like one second that that's
how he must have gotten out out of the
in at the toll booth because I had to
stop a little bit didn't go too well did
it no living hostage is one of the
prerequisites for a successful snatch in
a
yeah this is going what happened to my
sympathy I want to step off no sympathy
I have to finish a stupid
Mission I don't like it either but I
have
to let's just put him in the trunk
yeah God damn it at least I have like
full health and full armor so I don't
have to keep on buy you want a b
fatty okay how hard can it be to hold
him back from going like why not put it
in the the children lock or something
like that where they can't open the door
isn't that a
[Music]
thing
man surprised he wasn't in the trunk
right like there's so many better
options than
this
maybe you can't do it not in h old cars
didn't have it maybe okay well then you
kind of like tie his
arms tie his arms
but uhoh
you no no ran no no no no no no ran how
do get back in the car
I'm
sorry can I redo the Mission
[Laughter]
please a man man I just jacked that
that's your problem now guy too but I
guess we got to let him go I'll be
seeing the both of
you he still with
us it's different
ending
Yi please thank
you they have an ending for that yeah
how do you like he already ran away
though waai for you there okay do not
wreck the car that is also a bad ending
good to
[Music]
know no
so much for romance happy
ending so much for Roman's happy
ending no no no no no
no let's talk this
over let's play
bowling with
me I can show you my tricks are the
bowling
alley
I'll give you free taxi rides if you let
me go
you I promise you know uhoh no no no no
no no no you little get back in
here right now get in get in get in how
do you threaten him to get in get in get
in get in get in back here get
in get
in yeah
get in I did it I did it I did it I did
it he was sufficiently suffering can't
run next time lock the damn hostage up I
got a Le exactly don't worry about a t
you pull a stun like that again and it's
over for you bacon ass oh the the navi
is making me go extra rounds I'm sorry I
think I think it
is
yeah no no it's okay actually actually
it's
fine
Cy bacon
ass yeah yeah I'm happy I have more like
choices for next time I go to Korea now
so I know what to what I can what I
could eat although they probably make
all dishes a little bit more spicy than
they make them here I would assume I
would think they probably adjusted it a
little bit to the European tolerance of
spiciness try to another Korean cin not
just m it not just not just meat uh y y
what does that say yo ah it's already
gone yo yak yak what uh-oh he's going to
get get out again don't get out oh maybe
he doesn't want to
anymore maybe he understands now that he
must stay yakob yakop yakop yakop what's
yakop what is
that I just tried all the ones that
looked familiar to me that ah where
do I go that keep on being recommended
to me and they had a lot on the menu
so very very nice
healthy rice
uhhuh
hey I wonder if there's nons
spicy what was it
[Music]
Nong what was it the noodles that I
didn't get to try because they we
already ordered so much and they were
apparently spicy so I didn't really want
to order it anyway but next
time okay uh quick oh he's not getting
out he's not getting out Den I
nice he's intimidated maybe it's good
that it happened to us
before
okay I'm making you
hungry sorry go get yourself some food
regular not spicy is that what I'm
talking about
I already crushed his hope yeah I did
curtain
hone meat curtains are you saying that
to Lady Gaga in her meat
outfit that's the only thing I can think
of don't wreck the car H
the yeah the meat dress ew was that real
meat meat it was real meat right that
must have been so disgusting to wear
holy
who who chooses to wear some like I
mean I understand wanting to have some
shocking
value
but was she trying to send a message
with that anyway because I'm not sure if
that was really
effective like vegans were probably not
happy about that outfit
there must have been some message behind
it right right
hopefully what message with a bladder
problem
so this is Roman
Bellic such a tough guy e what is all
this F about he seems so friendly the
Russian guy Ashley square with you now
so do me a favor go easy on the fat man
go easy I've seen some of the bodies you
people Dro in the humbo easy Johnny you
saw the stands in the back seat
just wanted attention what happens to
this but wouldn't people say oh
waste of food and so on you not a good
look Lady Gaga not a good look
Johnny we should just I got
a with that outfit the the meat is
protecting her anyway we should just
throw her on the grill like that Grill
the
meat oh we can
like you know those pigs over campfire
if
we okay I stop I stop I'm sorry are
there any G offense I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so I just mean you
know like basically she's like a you
know I can rotate
her I'm so s those Russians have got
their guide you got lucky but you got to
control yourself Ashley the ice got you
into this
mess and you know what's the best thing
about me you call me okay a I'm I'm the
best thing about her that makes no sense
but that's actually
sweet okay I need a car without the cops
seeing it I would like a bike though I'm
a
biker that thing sir your
car I'm so sorry
that was a terrifying thing that I said
but I wasn't saying like let's roast
Lady Gaga no I'm just saying let's roast
all the meat on her like if it's already
attached on her I think it's asking us
to grill
her oh what's she going to do with that
food huh throw it away
huh
anyway Chuckles I'm in
danger
whoa I yeah I forgot about the weapon
discount but so far I only needed armor
anyway but the armor I guess is also
cheaper at his place but it's annoying
like I'm just annoying to call
them oh well I have a car I'm fine or
should I get a bike maybe I I'll get a
bike I'll get a
bike uh who
Terry Terry for Jerry Terry Terry for
the bike too clay for the
bike um bike ooh we have choices how
about
I say
stop stop oh it's the
hexer didn't we have it before though I
would have liked it to be something else
man my brother do you reckon you could
equip me with maybe hey police I'll be
out soon what the are they doing
they have some kind of God
complex sheesh too
realistic actually though some of the
recent cop footage cams that I saw the
cops were really surprisingly really
nice
though not all cops are
bad I saw some really nice
ones where they were handling the most
annoying ladies and men
ever you will sir here they are and they
were so sweet and respectful oh yeah
like one that I saw like I I can't
even that that one I really respected
there was like this what
teenager like 13 14 years old or so and
sorry this is really disturbing but she
killed her little three or four-year-old
brother or so and she was like I don't
know why I did that I don't
know and her mom was like so like
what the you know absolutely
lost all
her hope and the yeah they came to
arrest the girl and she was just crying
and
like I don't know what I did and why I
did that I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry well that won't change what the
you just did but the cop was
[Music]
so what are you like wow he handled it
like so well he wasn't like yelling at
her or
or
anything of course he was also not
praising her but he handled the
situation so
calmly professionally
yeah so there's good ones good good ones
thank
God
excuse
me how you
doing oh
oh I
win he was trying to drive through the
middle just like
[Music]
me sorry that was I know a disturbing
story
is very disturbing
indeed yeah it's real life man the
craziest happens in real life that
you would think it only happens in
movies or games but
no honestly GTA isn't even that
unrealistic huh
sadly apparently like I've never
experienced stuff like this
but it does happen stuff like this I
mean like stuff what happens in
GTA art imitates
life guys a question I noticed when I
was going through Netflix to find Violet
ever
Garden uh that there's like a an um a
continuation not a new season but like a
a
new story continuation sequel thingy for
Vikings is that good cuz I remember I
watched Vikings years ago when I was in
uh in Japan during the corona
times and I enjoyed the first couple
Seasons I didn't enjoy it when the dad
died whoever watched uh Vikings probably
knows I think his name was
Ragnar when he dies and only his
children are left over it's it it's kind
it kind of gets like really bad
yeah yeah now there's a new season not
new season not a new show and I didn't
know about that and I wonder if it's
[Music]
good yeah yeah it gets so bad
afterwards I'm not the only one who
thinks so that's why I stopped I didn't
watch the last what are you talking
about five episodes or so because it got
so frustratingly bad no we ain't we
ain't doing nothing I mean not at the
moment but but he's he's a friend he's
been to me and and we need you we need
you to do this for us all right I ain't
sleeping with him but you know you and
me broke up you was with that Lela girl
that's all over now baby you know that
man you got to get off damn drugs I know
I will I need you to do this for me yeah
the the wife is hot mm where is
hea righta is
hot
notag no no glad to see youing Ashley
says you want something Ashley oh good
kid you know man ice my day was cing Don
that was it I even missed the ex
people up y listen mm everything
you up don't do it oh yeah I know
about some diamonds yeah illegal what
his name
EV
Insurance ruins everything Wise from
Wise Guys for Wise Guys you understand
no tax man nothing got our names all
over right problem I can't be seen yet
all right let's just call it a it's PR
de well I imagine that happens quite
often with you Ray then maybe oh yeah
you like maybe I'll rewatch Vikings cuz
it's been too long like you too much
I'll tell you what you I don't want to
watch the ending you can buy yourself
some real friends yeah it just gets so
bad the ice is being held by a guy named
Gay Tony Gay Tony should be no problem
with that good
oh we're connecting the
DLCs
Johnny don't get too clever don't worry
I'm really stupid
anyway I can't get too
clever Jonathan what can I do for you
brother James we got to hook up in
broker might need some help all right
man I'll let the lost brotherhood over
there know you're coming they like
getting as dirty as the rest of us
appreciate it man a hook
up my gang members
finally tan CL I know I know sh
sh sh sh
sh potato chips the potato chips Arc is
here
again come on come on I love potato
chips where is my
gang hey what's up what's up your leader
is back stay behind
me that to the front of the pack Le the
back
yeah go away I'm leading now stay behind
we got some ice to take Johnny K let's
do this are those bars supposed to be
full are they like already really low on
HP or is that
just just how it's shown all right boys
all I know is that these diamonds are
being held by man town called where to
take them be a good profit G see if this
comes through so let's do it
yeah let's do it mayy down the line
there'll be an opportunity to rip off
the smug Guido who gave us the job in
the first place be careful guys
brother's L
forever be careful
guys stay behind me keep it up keep it
up yeah apparently they have XP I didn't
know that oh
nice oh careful careful careful
everybody every single one of them
crashes into it wow not very much brain
cell no cute cuddling it's like when
cats walk together and they walk so
close to each other that their tails
into twine you know that's
us but their tails are yet too
intertwine I don't think we want to see
them intertwining although we're going
straight to Gay Tony
so oh sorry
oopsie hey guys how you doing
so these are great they're great but uh
it's great Tony you had your head in the
oven Mr Tony I have what I tell you
perfect clarity beautiful Clarity well
cut in a shitload of carrots what do you
expect wait are we talking real diamonds
now gorgeous just like you we do the
hand over police and get out of here
this is too much ignore him he's
probably been up all night with some
bimbo
Tony you're a chef welome yeah I have
line and some kitchen how about I throw
that into the equation what's the price
look here's the money we agreed upon
last temp just give us the ice all right
all right here Tony can I hold
them
thanks oh we out of here come on
let's
go the and the about
okay well the quest definitely can be
can't be to kill
him take out Tony's
boy one
boy we can't kill them because they're
coming up right later in the DLC so
I'm killing someone in there but there's
surely plenty of people in there how do
I kill one of them you hor
F what about him like can I not shoot
him he's shooting at me oh
is my gang with me no am I alone am
I supposed to be
alone just kill them all
okay you're dead
man I it better be allowed
[Music]
okay how how did I still not get him in
this okay he stopped shooting very
good no you stop
now is Gay Tony also in there could I
shoot someone by like accident that I
shouldn't be shooting you or
me how was that cute the bus jumped come
on the the
oh dear oh dear oh
dear oh oh de oh de oh dear Mama
Mia oo pretty China
Town
uh what where's the limo a there it
looks so
short how did I not get
anyone cover me who am I shooting the
driver stay the away from
me fight me going for the tires oh
sorry collateral
[Music]
damage hello I'm running out of
ammo
oh that's the one I need
okay pick up the diamonds everybody's
dead sorry I know you said boy but I
killed the
[Music]
boys I got you that ice want me to bring
it back to the restaurant I know you
don't like me Johnny you have to get me
clipped Jesus probably got to have the
Wise Guys in E Co follow right now I
need you to split the hall up half a
trash can on herti street and the other
half a trash on Emerald my way are going
to go pick it up all subtle like uhhuh
sounds real dumb to me but if that's
what you want done I'll do it as long as
I get paid yeah so two locations one's
pretty close over
there um around that building I
think
call who are you calling
Ghostbusters sorry
okay I didn't even do anything but it
counted last
one take out
this no problem but
like I might have to shoot with
something
[Music]
else oh they're stuck in traffic cusa
that is a a big Kus police get out of
the
way I'm out of ammo oh now
pistol time uh m m why' we get the
police involved eh why have the why did
the police have to be there why are you
not
dead now you're dead right okay okay
[Music]
say
office everyone
[Music]
dancing da da da da actually I came here
on
purpose apparently we need SMG
ammo and we can buy arm let's
go and
SMG SMG SMG
SMG this I think no
[Music]
there all
right done Halloween M
time I don't
know I guess I'm already in Christmas
mood I shouldn't be
but but if you think about it holy
holy it's almost like September is
almost
over can you believe it that means then
the the the number will say
10 and you know Christmas is on the
number 12 that is so close
guys Christmas isn't as far away as you
think it
is
nice did you know 10 comes after 9: did
you know MAF checks
out yeah believe me what's going on baby
Trust
it's in the trash now and Ray better
hope a garbage truck doesn't come around
anytime soon Ray got any money for me
there ain't no money yet Ray's got to
sell this stuff before you get your cut
you'll be in touch sweets I love you
Johnny oh not enough you
don't okay
well got to wait for another
[Music]
mission some crazy missions today
really
[Music]
exciting always comes late like the 24th
the set but that is really late but
understandable when nothing else really
makes you feel like Christmas especially
when there's no
snow how can you feel like Christmas
snow walking around Christmas tree a
happy
holiday is now nobody going to call
there we go I was about to say n
r Ashley sends love Yeah christas bonus
oh yeah that was always like for each a
thing I was looking forward to Christmas
and there was a summer bonus too a
coffin you got that diamond money you're
going to have to work for it friend hope
you don't mind sweating a little
Handover is happening at the liberon
swey he walked away with half the bread
buddy CIA CIA got a north entrance of
the
liberoni all right it's pretty far but
today I'm I don't know I feel like
driving long distance I don't mind it I
might regret it after I see how much
time I have left with this
DLC but I just want to stay on my bike
all
day I want to ride my bicycle I want to
ride my bike I want to ride my
bicycle you're next to end it h you mean
I'm soon ending it oh y then the 2 hours
wasn't so Off 2 and a half now and I
wasted a lot of time
dying three more missions okay well not
bad we're not taking four hour okay I'm
going to jinx it
but the time has come don't worry we
still got another you'll
[Music]
see
steak yeah driving is good for Tangen
thing I wanted to tell you about
my Adventures yesterday AKA lazy day but
I watched anime and ate Maran
barbecue and lots of scien tisses
so now you
know did you
see us
p
first solo
concert Mama Mia it's happening oh my
God Picola
Picola
yeah I didn't expect that I was so
I was really
surprised and she's doing it in a really
big
Vue wow you doing a watchong I guess I
probably
will but I wonder what she will sing cuz
she doesn't have that many original
songs to fill a whole concert right
maybe she's still going to release them
because the concert is in
December beginning of December so
there's time enter the lonian am I
entering from the front
huh no probably
[Music]
not are we entering from here oopsie
that's why we stopped our bike there the
venu is actually like has bigger
capacity than our big Whole Life concert
guys oh there's a there's a vest there
just lying
there so maybe for
later we remember this race at me in
case I forgot my
own yeah I mean with every concert comes
a new outfit right it's usually the the
one that's in the main visuals from what
I've seen so far that's usually how it
goes are we going
down
oh
yeah yeah but I think the reason why
um it's bigger than
the whole life concerts thingy it's
because we need the venue with a
convention hall right right next to
it you
know so there's not many options we
talked about this before there's just
not many options for the exit door but
it says
Exit
I was look looking for the museum
okay yeah for the sake of having an expo
one must uh sacrifice a little bit of
capacity but of course whole life could
fill up so much more than that yeah you
got to keep an eye on this
jackass me I'm Not Dangerous there's so
much
healing
sheesh yeah she's feeling that alone
probably no problemo easily 15,000
capacity better than before yeah 15,000
come on let's get
inside gentlemen gentlemen pardon the
precautions you know how things are no
problem let's do this okay let's see the
Stu go Mory come over here Mor C whoa
whoa whoa whoa since we're having a
little show in tell let's see some money
of course no
problem there it is beautiful huh
unmarked bills no history no need to Lo
yeah I was thinking I was in this
building before but uh stff I wasn't
sure if I experienced it
with or with our current main guy Isaac
look at them gorgeous huh like condensed
money Isaac these are great so it was it
was the
Nico rest I remember the museum do
something stupid okay you let's get
the man come on oh it's going
down so okay
Escape Escape they
say wait who are my enemies you're my
enemy
right
is that a rifle that I have right now oh
hey stop it how many times do I have to
tell
you it's like a school
bell when the break is
over motherucker but this one just never
ends
oopsy okay easy easy easy
SMG
ammo I just bought so
much
oh out of my sight out of my
mind oh I'm running out of ammo on this
one too holy
leave this mess
behind I should sing this in K sometime
I didn't before
right H oh hi
you
you who else was
shooting I hear
ah this what you want slap that one on
the list I actually I I slapped a couple
on on on my list that I forgot about
last time I felt like so regretful I
sang so many songs how could I forget
these I I've noted them down a grenade
pick it
up why he not pick it up I want the free
grenade
H these what what did I say
oh cuz I have pipe bumps or are they
supposed to be
better I don't know about
that is said these wait where am I going
down oh
here this place is so
beautiful oh there's the will that still
be there after I'm done maybe I'll pick
it up for free cuz a a
free free armor I want it but I don't
need it right now sadly oh
bye-bye
oh nice
roll he's
styling Flex
thing nice one it didn't really do you
any good though would have been better
if you would have just
hidden door is not
again we worked hard for this cash SLI
lost M
Property I'll rip your head
off so the DLC is
honestly such such an
improvement over the main game I'll
H I'll I'll agree with
that like all the checkpoints being so
much better I'll try this
um oh where
go where did that
go you got to kill me or what G Tony is
even better apparently yeah
yay then I'm excited for
that last willing Testament I
always forget I can
zoom I can't see G
[Music]
dead they're so far oh got him oh he's
running we got a runner think quick
quick quick why you
reload he's getting
closer they're driving away over till I
say it is that's okay right we can have
let them drive away push
me come on come on come
on come on
try all you Kies are two pricks I I'll
just drive I don't have to kill them all
right but I I'll get the ammo if I kill
them all I get the ammo yay
oh
freebies I do okay
OH police
hello I think I'm done
now
[Music]
byebye
get
up no no no no no don't even think about
moving
no
a no if I reload I get my guns back
right right
right no no I want it
back I get it back
right but you have to restart the whole
mission oh that's okay
I mean it's just
uh huh why is everybody's reaction so
weird I see it's
just n hell
no you can't bring me there oh oh wait
what I have
nothing I have
nothing what am I going to
do oh this
ah okay okay oh oh I thought that's
where I was
now
damn whenever really had that happen
before I
think I might your oh we start here okay
no
problem no problem at least we have
everything
back oh is this like I don't have the
mission
yet
or huh
I don't have it yet
huh buy more
ammo I mean the uh the SMG has plenty
the rifle is lacking but I'm fine with
just the SMG and that'll pick up
everything at the
Museum oh I have to wait for the call
again call me please
no call me call me call me maybe hey I
just met you and this is crazy but I'll
kill some people cuz you're are
lazy yeah you got to give that girl
another chance you know you kids are
perfect for each other thanks for the
advice Ray I was thinking the same thing
about you and a coffin you got that
diamond money you're going to have to
work for it friend hope you don't mind
sweating a little easy I just shouldn't
have like bked
against I finny I would have bonked
again the
tree
against why did I Bonk the tree what did
you just drop out of your car hey no
littering trees strike when you least
expect it ah trees
[Music]
dangerous well yeah so
H this year solo
concerts TOA Senai
Pai who else had it this year was okai
last year or this
[Music]
year so
say
what say kind of goes for
her label I guess was last year I well
NEP Lao is not a solo concert but yeah
it's kind of I would consider it in the
same
[Music]
category K 2024
ha uh
no I highly doubt it but good for
everybody who gets a chance I'm curious
to see how pias will be that will be a
huge venue
she
shei been to the makani concert venue
before as
a audience for a
concert but
not not the I don't think I've been to
arak
before I know it
though it's going to be
big we're going to watch it online
though I don't think I'll go I mean I
would like to but I don't think
I I I mean I
don't I don't think I should go there in
person
right even if I tried this guys myself
um I don't think that's going to
work and if jenma finds out she's going
to kill
me not a good
[Music]
idea sh sh
we have PC's backstage pass I wonder if
that's possible but they don't even I
don't know I don't think they would do
that
no I don't think so I don't think they
would allow even that like for real Idol
concerts I know that like for hello
project and so on they will let like ex
members and so
on uh or just members who are in Hell
project but not part of this specific
concert they will let them in into the
con concert on like like second floor
seats for example but hey all right man
how's it going hey good to see you again
yeah likewise people behave let's hope
this goes a little better than before
yeah come on let's get
inside gentlemen gentle gentlem pardon
the precaution bner I got arrested at
like when I was already done with the
museum and left over here whoa whoa whoa
whoa they arrested me because I bonked
into a dream yeah that's what happens
that's why I
screamed yeah it's a bit different with
uh YouTubers
mhm all right all right I'll go the SMG
right
away oh going to it dropped
let sorry for hurting you I feel bad
don't with me anymore is that Nico
who I
hear wait I want to see him wait can I
see him you want some of this no I want
to see let me see
Ni you think you can with me this
is NI right I hear
him I'm
curious I'll help you Nico let me help
you oh hi are you shooting are you
trying to shoot me like you're so close
to me how can you
miss how bad are you at
shooting other side of my
[Music]
floor
oh reloading Oh
no just slowly menacingly walking closer
and
closer but so
calm I'm such a
pro oh there's a medkit there too but
now I still have full HP this place is
so so loser
friendly like a Terminator yeah it's the
Austrian roots in
me was there someone here
no we'll get this guy for you I like
this style honestly I I I really like
this style of just walking calmly and
shooting everyone in my way
I feel
it it suits
me okay already killed all the bottom
ones I guess I wouldn't want this ni
Bell coming for me
deranged oh checkpoint I I'm going out
here I yeah oh oh okay it was so close
a
on car blow them up all they will
can't run away and make Mission blow
them up you mean I should use my I only
have like two left on my rocket
launcher
ahhhh
I know I'm not taking cover oh
you are not going to drive away my
friends
o ah they did ah don't drive
this party ain't over till I
okay this part is over though I think oh
wait can't
see
I
hear
hell you're not getting back to R
boys okay got to go
fast oh at least the police is not on my
butt
yet let's go where are
they oh they're going to go over the
bridge I think that's what it looks like
although they could also
be
okay I understand
[Music]
though let's kill the
mafia uh got to go left I'm hurting you
down assho about next one
[Music]
left no more Tree in my way can't stop
me where are they oh here
I'm on your back oh I got your
tire I'm right behind
you I Won't Let You
[Music]
Escape oh they're
stuck n that's the problem when you're
not in a biker gang you need to you need
to be in a biker gang that's the only
real way to do crime brother Johnny bik
where are you man I need to give you
something very versatile on V what's up
wait
there L's the
cops okay I will
try oh by the way guys I said it before
kind of but I'll say it again next week
no
schedule for now I I'll just update you
guys all the time uh on
Twitter with my
plans I think I might stream uh FF zero
FF fer F zero FF zero on
Monday that I can tell you and on
Tuesday is
sharu collab stream I think on her
Channel pretty
sure
f99 yeah I want to race with you guys
you can try to get into my group I
wonder how difficult it
is like the groups are pretty big so I
would imagine that it's not as difficult
to get
in you you guys did it with fall guys
you guys did it with Mario
Kart and game is free as long as you
have a subscription to Nintendo
online oh yeah I know it is like a
tutorial I'll do that beforeand
hand you said tomorrow after ah tomorrow
tomorrow the day after tomorrow sorry I
mean
Monday tomorrow was balers gate right
balers gate oh let's go balers
gate The Ballad of Boulder's
Gate
tomorrow I think uh was it during the
daytime for me this time cuz we're
rotating so we should be back
to Good Time time for
Wawa in the middle of the day for me
kind of early for you
guys I think it's like decent for
EST not so decent for
PST yeah 9:00 a.m. EST isn't so bad EST
winning h
yeah we'll play uh I don't know how long
for me I can go long uh since it's in
the middle of the day for me but I don't
know about the others how long they feel
like
playing hi guys how are you
doing hey what do you got all the money
the diamonds can buy you mean all Ray
money Ray man all of them here
I so dumb yeah them I guess we're
rich then hold on to it brother you bet
your balls on
it he's so
done least good time for E
yeah yes yes
yes y I'm
happy he's fed up Johnny nikk you got
away with the money bring it to me what
the Nico said that dude that's
weird was kicking off I don't know
what happened to the money I just wanted
to get out with my life you better not
be pulling nothing Johnny or I'll stop
pulling your teeth you hear me I
like you Ray keep your sense of humor in
the face of An Almighty see you
around I have to stretch so much it's
like they were playing the goose game
Hong Hong Hong Hong
Hong and
voice AC
partip oh
really
cute oh I have a message You've Got Mail
meet me at ra dot dot dot who sent
that that's so
omnus I have an announcement
guys yesterday I was with my very
intelligent friend friend who studies
many things in
University and is overall very smart
okay she's she's smart like one of my
smartest friends
okay
yeah
and I asked her what does she think the
definition is without giving her
context I asked her what she thinks the
definition is of of
ignorance and she agreed with me guys
the first thing she said was basically
the thing that I thought it
was she said like I think what was it
um
like
purposely purposefully not on not trying
to understand blah BL blah blah you know
the discussion we had the other
day especially
purposefully yeah and I'm like oh you
know my viewers they totally
like disagreed with me and they were
like you know making me feel
like I knew
nothing I was shocked so bad that's what
I thought it was yay let's go yeah and I
told her you know when I looked it up on
Google actually it seems like chat was
correct but she was shocked too I was
shocked we were both shocked and I
genuinely think that in some
places maybe it's an Austrian thing or
maybe it's a a regional thing but I
think in some places it's uh really how
like it's being taught what it
means H yeah willful
ignorance but that's just what people
think it means to be
ignorant I thought so she thought
so I'm sure other people would agree
with me other friends well look who it
is hey how you doing tough guy what's
your
problem I told you not to get
clever I'm not that stupid it's just a
thing oh you got to be kidding start
walking
downstairs okay I'm
going that's
right
what the is going on here
hell stop that anything yet
nah burn him
again ah where's my stuff
you see genius over here would rather
get creme bruid before he dies hopefully
you ain't so stupid I love my stuff I
don't know what you're talking about
you
ooh what are you death where's
my stuff I don't know who do you
think you're bullshitting a
bullshitter that's his
[Laughter]
look you're going to have to cut that
out Ray it's not cool I
Ashley my friend and now I'm
going to you where's my
stuff off R oh let's
go
yeah drop the gun goon
no I'll cut him he doesn't care probably
no get get the up back up go ahead
go
ahead Billy was right about both these
back stabing fools I got guys in every
corner where you going to
go
oh we did it see you later see you later
alligator I'm going to go get the
Brothers oh it feels it feels like
a
finale's
go let's go go and meet Ashley all right
um Navi you're going to show me where to
go thank
you
yeah that's what I like to see
extreme
violence let's
[Music]
go oh I was looking at the
chat very good
Showdown
bye
[Music]
excuse me excuse
me the most recent um I know you guys
don't care but the most recent real of
Time episode was also really
good and
that Survival show result made me very
angry
Idol Survival show what the was
that but then one of the girls they
kicked out she immediately after the
episode aired posted a music video of a
kind of self-produced Lo more or less
part of it at least uh single and the
absolutely slays it's an absolute poop
and it's actually better than the debut
song from the actual group group from
the Survival
show so that's quite funny yudia you
know what I'm talking about and even
like the lyrics they're like roasting a
certain someone it feels
like good strategy yeah like she
prepared so well must The show must have
been like done for ages if she was ready
to uh able to prepare
that I think
um
like from what I've read the auditions
the first auditions were a year ago they
probably filmed for like half a year so
the show was probably over for half a
year and the rest was just them
preparing for their debut probably I
would assume so yeah yeah
yeah yeah cuz the the camp
uh the the training thingies they were
not that long right so oh Ash is calling
me I'm almost there as girl your friend
Ray ain't so friendly Johny K you're all
right I'm sorry sweets I think RAC some
guide that for you of course he is baby
thanks for the heads up may me outside
the house okay I'll be there if I'm
still walking oh what are all these red
signs they're hit before they get but I
thought I was supposed to get to Ashley
I have to do this first now are they
moving or are they staying
let's see yeah they're moving okay well
they're on the way to me huh so I'll
just I'll just let them get to
me yeah but the song from Gina I
genuinely like it I think she did great
and she has so much potential honestly
so wasted this one I really like
[Music]
Christina I I anticipated your arrival
oops
seec know more about family than you
Italian I really like Christina but like
the one that I really don't understand
and I was really surprised about was
Gina them not taking Gina let me explain
to you guys the one like out of all the
contestants there was one who was
already being trained by this company
that was making the Survival show
because she was
scouted she was scouted and then went to
like uh to the company to train for a
year
okay and she was getting really good and
she really had the skills like sometimes
they would still criticize her for not
being good enough considering the
training she went through I don't agree
with that though but yeah um she was so
qualified and she has the perfect Idol
looks she has a face that is like really
unique and pretty she may be young but
she doesn't look so young and it seems
like the age didn't bothered them anyway
cuz they added the other young
girl yeah and they make her go to the
very last round like I if I was in her
position I would
feel so over I get scouted by
this company I train for a year there
I'm like better than most other
contestants and then at the very end
probably just for the sake of drama in
the TV show uh you it's only YouTube but
you know just probably just for the sake
of the drama they kick her out they
don't take her for the final lineup I'm
like is it really worth it is that
really worth
it I don't think so because she would
have really been a great asset to the
group
really I'm not exaggerating here we go
I'm so shocked about this but wa oh
but I think it will be um a great
opportunity for her like people are
looking her up and finding
her track nobody you oh I
need armor
hotot oh
well she definitely got big exposure
yeah but now to keep this up you know if
you if you're an contestant of a
survival show like that and then it's
like over yeah people give you some
attention in the beginning but normally
it doesn't it doesn't stay the attention
the focus doesn't stay on you for that
long
sadly you boys better be more dangerous
than the last so it's really crucial
right
now I wish for the best for
her I think she's great she's still
honestly in my opinion a little bit
Young young for this industry but the
way she presents herself wow you
wouldn't think she's that
young the song was so mature and she
looks really mature sry she's great like
her singing is great oh hi don't die
don't die don't
[Music]
die a I I'm going to
die okay I did it uh go meet Ashley yeah
but first
um
Mazula
heal
myself how old is she she was like 13 at
the beginning of the Survival show by
now she's at least 14 if not going on 15
she is 14 going on
15 but she looks like
16 or
mhm yeah but the other 14 year old they
had she really looked like a 13-year-old
this one she didn't the one I'm talking
about the one that I like that I'm
surprised about not making it she didn't
really look like a 13-year-old at all
yeah yeah but generally I I do think
that if you're so young you shouldn't be
in the idle group like that especially
cuz they're making this idle group with
the goal of you know taking over
America I think
like that's that's supposed to be their
their goal try they want to market the
group to America English speaking
audience at least and I don't know like
it still feels
[Music]
very kids oriented like the song that
they
released it's kind
of I don't know doesn't really feel like
something an American audience would eat
up but you
know
the vibe they went with I just don't
think it is necessarily for an American
audience but we'll see we'll see we'll
see I need some food now
Gohan maybe on the way I can find
something do you think it will hit in
the US though I mean they'll they'll
certainly get their initial like big
views on the first single that they just
released the pre- debut
single but
I don't
know how the what the future will bring
for them I
I I don't think they'll do as well as
like twice for example or new jeans
even but I'll be happy if they prove me
wrong and new jeans isn't even meant to
what's going on I'm sorry be only for
America they just so happened to work so
well internationally me and
neither yeah always Korea for backup
plan Jim he ain't that wasn't the
purpose oh not
Jim this Angus is crippled and
Billy gone insane now Jim's dead Jim I
guess that's what they
call you got me I don't got you Crystal
got Got You Babe Johnny I'm going to
quit yeah and I'm an idiot believing in
your all this time it ain't
your fault it's my fault I'm a
I'm going to go to rehab
straighten myself out anyhow he he told
me you wouldn't get hurt I wouldn't have
done it otherwise yeah well why
shouldn't I kill you why bother I'd be
better off dead H but Johnny Ray ain't
the problem what are you talking about
are you telling me that a backstabbing
mob guy wants to kill me ain't the
problem
Billy see it's Billy Ray it turns out
that Billy was trying to poison him
against you and now apparently Billy's
going States he's going to he's going to
blame you I'm sorry well what now you
got to get someone to help you maybe
that
Congressman maybe we'll see H go on and
get out of here he's so done you're
speaking a foreign language to me now
lady now get the it's so
relatable like I don't know how Nico
didn't become like
this how do you not become like this
this is the only
realistic um character development just
being pissed
off that's the only way that makes
sense all right uh food uh guess we
didn't find food on the way but now we
got to find
it and Nico was just so focused on
Vengeance and all that it just I guess
he had a lot of
endurance but this seems so much more
realistic
stubs I'm not in the mood to do any
killing for the supposed Elite today
you're going to have to get your own
hands dirty stubs oh spare me the
lectures this is important Jonathan oh
important enough for me to come down
from my Ivory Tower and rub elbows With
You Blue Collar type on the wrong side
of the West River NS meet me at your
Clubhouse I drink single oh yeah Hot
Nuts
hell The Nut House oh the logo I just
realized
it's a nut in a like that
restraining
jacket great deals great deal wow the
nuts filled me up completely damn can't
believe nuts are so so
filling
s you little
shits you little
shits rich in protein and fats yeah they
might be good for you and have a lot of
nutrients but do they really fill your
hunger
m m surprisingly feeling I never
experienced it like that
okay back home
already I was just there but now I'm
healthy
again nice place you got here
Johnny not quite sure I that tie brings
me PTSD I think I like the smoking
policy what the do you want now is
that any way to treat a friend are we
friends I think so you've certainly seen
me naked no I haven't do you want to no
I haven't oh not
particularly now listen your friend Ray
I wish I had don't worry about him why
not apparently he and a lot of his
associates under some serious
observation and in the process of
imploding they'll either be dead or
inside within a month or so best thing
you can do stay away from him what about
Billy Gray yes well you've got a bit of
a problem there sport he's been talking
inside thinks he can help pin a major
drug dealing ring on you and your buddy
in the
chair thinks he's going into the witness
protection program and if he callers you
you'll do 15 years and he'll live in a
condo in Arizona well I don't doubt that
Mr stubs but he's on the inside yeah I
know and there's currently very large
walls and armed guards between me and
him yeah well you're a smart guy you'll
figure something something
out if you get into trouble you call me
when you get there I might have
something to help you with it good I'll
need he has such a fitting voice actor
why you doing this he sounds so Congress
Manny I was good for a
favor good for
favor
hold go to the prison okay hopefully we
don't stay there
[Music]
New
York
this
you nework
[Music]
actually fitting for Liberty
City this
song
[Music]
it's
shaby
bang
what all right prison prison is here oh
this thing oh yeah oh
scary
teil the Battle of gay waa exactly
that's what's
next we'll get into it
today
all Correctional
Facility it's called prison just say
what it is
clearly you're getting out of
here you enjoyed your time in the
state's care what a this is
KF Terry man we got to pay our friend
Billy a visit we've been talking bring
clay and bring all the Firepower
you got meet me at the Alder State
Correctional I'm waiting
KF Prisoners the last time K fed prison
ain't be easy what is this what's with
the camera
brother oh free weapons ter um what do I
want what do I
need she is do you have something
special not for these weapons man blame
Billy what
free
what
free fre what's the last
one where's the RPG
ammo rocket launcher no I need the ammo
is it the ammo when I buy it oh yeah
here we are oh
what rocket for rocket
launcher why is eight the
maximum n
oh yeah cuz I used that my last rocket
it was gone okay uh no need for
armor grenade launcher let's get that
too oh that can take quite a bit more 20
nice
um oh I think I need to go to idle
[Music]
meeting but I can take it a bit longer I
think do I need something else the M4 M4
M4 M4 M4 M4 and what's
M4 what's
M4 why do you think I understand that
when it's not really written there what
the hell is the M4 gray rifle why would
you say
M4 what gray they're all
gray carbine didn't we have this
discussion before don't call it
something that it's not called there how
am I supposed to know look at me you
know me you know I don't know
so this thing right okay okay okay
why would you assume that I know what
you're talking
about I have no idea man M4 what the
is an
M4 get the ak ak
ak what the is an
AK what about the pipe bomb I I don't
need them I already have so
many under the
M4 this
thing but it replaces something I
already have does it make it
better I don't think
so just some brothers having a good time
now we're
done
yeah don't take okay okay blow up the
prison oh we're going
big I'm about to introduce a pip bomb to
that gate yeah let's do a pipe bomb I
don't want to waste everything
already uh how we throw this
again like this okay just
one I don't know if I'm mentally ready
for this oh God oh God oh
God
um ter play Come With Me
yeah take cover you idiots what are you
doing oh my God ah don't run in front of
me I'm going to hurt
you no cover for the Wawa no need for
the
cover
okay you
okay
okay ah reload that's do
okay what
he's using a shitty shotgun you
so
shitty we're being raided
welcome we are doing the big one the big
of the the l s
damn
it's going down wow wow wow wow wow wow
how can you miss why does nobody really
get any hits except for
me terrible
teammates me oh there's a eight kit
there but I still don't need it kind of
too early would have preferred uh
another armor your time is
up but it shows that they're already
being
very kind Distributing these things are
they don't shoot me can they shoot me
you a an open like I can shoot them but
can they shoot
me I hope
not going in the
ground okay
okay head down there's a sniper on the
RO I ain't going to live by
your you got to kill me or what
apparently not yeah cuz I ran straight
through them I don't think I took any
damage let's
go I'm the only one who matters I'm the
only one taking the
shots calling the
shots
okay my back against the wall
nice slide sliding in style oh still
alive okay where are you still
alive how's that song Go Again the
Portal
song come on you think I give a
come the get the sniper sniper
sniper oh thank
you oh
this was a
[Music]
Triumph can these things blow up you
better hope probably not get some
cover
sorry Yik oh helicopters no what is
that normal well I can shoot them with
my oh w w whoa
whoa with my big launchers right I can't
see them
though
uh-oh oh I don't hear them anymore they
actually are gone
I down on you you're we
good Terry we are very good we're so in
let's
go it's a party in this prison let's
gock hey make your way to the prison
yard you're free everybody
free oh we're even picking up things now
during that scene nice helicopter is
here two
helicopters what a
deal okay they left the helicopters
which will make it actually easier to
deal with
them
idiots they got helmets will it be more
difficult to give them head shot
I flew off his his
helmet let's get this over with I don't
care what happens to me as long as we
get fil come on
oh come on you
uh am I
okay that's what you're looking for
shitthead stay the away I don't
think I'm okay oh there's armor over
there
you ask for
it I think I'm okay Mama push
me yeah B Lost MC yeah I'm glad I got
you
two uh they're not really huddling
together so I don't know are you friend
or F friend
right B there's so many I would shoot
something they were huddling together a
bit more but they're not where the
is Billy
Gray you're going in the
ground
oh
okay I'll rip yeah I see the body armor
boys it's like ah well we we'll be we'll
be fine we'll be fine we'll be
fine stop getting up you bastard lost
damn sh you ready for
this I'm still
alive I just lost all my armor but I
still have kind of full HP
so we're doing fine if I wasn't
constantly reloading what's
something's still alive there no
no I'm going to take out Billy bring the
around so we can out here all right
execute Billy what let me get the
armor
who's
sure come on wait that was a was that a
friend no right the I
don't think
so why is this one glowing red blue red
blue take
it okay uh not anymore oh are we going
it's not up where's where's the Big Red
over there let me pick up some
things are we going guys friends you
follow me
right
wrong there's no William the rules don't
apply to your kind you want to say
something besides that screw you
Johnny all right
goodbye that was easy
use a
pistol too late
now I would have liked to be that to be
a bit
more Pro
climatic was kind of antil climatic
climactic
climatic
bye-bye sorry for the intrusion we could
have had it easier without killing all
of you guys if you wouldn't have forced
our hands but you have forced our hands
that's why I use the pistol Alo it's
more eh would would it have been
different visiting hours are
over all right sorry I changed the route
on the
navigation good job me good job not so
much you guys our club but he sure as
ripped it apart I'll forgive him
the insults and injuries but I can't
forgive him that back treacherous
bastard you didn't say
him um can I just
ask that was our original boss
right
right Terry yeah play thanks for rolling
with me this gang is all the hell
right now but I'll Love You Brothers
until I die he could never be able to
take
son of a
ever you have people
behind yeah you don't with the new
[Music]
leader You're Not Safe not even in
prison turns
out that needed to be done going to
sleep good night need to be shut up see
you again maybe tomorrow years ago he
would have led the charge in Al and he
stay himself drugs sent that insane
was that the last mission or so like
almost
[Music]
last went smoothly first
try bab last nice phito
phito
hey
h maybe renovate this hole Maybe
get pink Johnny to please
get this guy we had fun
here yeah we
did but it's
over probably better to be over how the
did that happen you know how it
happens it's that up part of
people which means good is never good
enough I mean it wasn't enough we had to
be drug dealers we also had to be
Outlaws to be Maniacs to be psychos and
to be
greedy you know well that combination of
greed and up stupidity that works
well in the government not so good if
you're a crook huh ain't that
the
truth go
ahead let's put this place out of its
misery yeah do what you got to do come
on man let's get out of
here SMY hello thank you for letting me
sleep tonight last night maybe also
tonight stop blowing it up why did you
blow it up don't that's not necessary is
[Music]
it yeah you came to see the ending
huh this movie likes violence
smovie oh nice ending
music hiy you want to see
it it's over she didn't see
it cat is
here she probably was on a toilet again
if I'm correct with the
pattern Rockstar North that was the
first DLC of GTA 4 The Lost and the
Damned I think was the
title
yeah all right why no music is this a
bug is there supposed to be no music
here so
quiet n
it's probably a bug right oh I hear
train
sounds oh because I have the music
off oh maybe
yeah the oh fire I See
Fire Inside the crew house I See
Fire H
now on to the one that we're actually
most excited for Gay
Tony the blood of Gay
Tony but do we get some after
credits oh when they lose rights they
delete self delete the music H oh who
whoa whoa whoa you've completed the
story for the last okay Finish yeah I
got an achievement for finishing the
story
so
H am I just
done just post game now I just
leave I guess I just leave H okay well I
mean that um definitely like technically
better A lot better than main
game uh story was possibly also a bit
more easy to
comprehend and characters
were I mean some were the same but
generally the new ones I thought they
were okay was missing maybe some someone
really
iconic
but it was all right the biker theme I
like it's
funny uh and I like being on the bike
all the time I do like that they
improved a lot of things like
checkpoints and the fact that you can
like bring armor to you bring your bikes
to you and all that that's that's
cool so yeah good
[Music]
DLC but apparently Gay Tony is even
better oh the game just closed oh yeah
right I guess I have have to open it
again and let me tweet though that we
starting that we're done with um Lost
and
Damned
quote we
finished the lost and damned now
starting the Ballad of Gay
Tony let's see do we have some rainbow
emojis
yeah there we go there we
go now starting the Ballad of Gay
Tony Bolt let's make it bolt is Tony
Italian cuz I make I could make it
italic as
well I'll make it I'll make it italic
just because that way it's not
straight
perfect
nice wonderful people will find out that
we're doing that now all
right let me open the game
again actually good one h ha wait you
mean my tweet or my or the
DLC thanks for the membership gifts by
the way ziply and
Nathan thank you thank you thank you
change back to color oh should I make
myself like extra colorful I wish I
could make like a rainbow filter above
myself
um what can I
do
what if
I I can only get myself like a one one
color
unfortunately no rainbow I
think
oh oh no that's bad not
good
uh
unfortunate I'm just going to be no I
look pretty gay I mean look at
me I look like I'm going to um except
for the shotgun I look like I'm going
to a music
[Music]
festival
loud yellow arrich streamer
here we go Grand Theft
Auto the The Ballad of Gay Tony The
Ballad of Gay Tony let's go oh they're
pink it's pink
here tanos
Simi
oh
that look hey I would have liked to see
more of the opening it's sparkling it's
sparkling I love LC what's that let me
move yo I'm a wait wait CL member I'm
going to take these rookies downtown are
you with me hey what's your name son Lis
man I don't think that's such a good
idea yeah they said catching that pass
school championship football game was a
bad idea I broke my leg in 13 places but
I scored a touchdown and won the game
the world was built out of bad ideas my
friend this it's the heist the good
heist come
on the one that brought me so much money
the pe4 has been molded and is set to
explode in 60 seconds now listen people
we're your friends me and me brother
here why you telling them we're brothers
you idiot that's going to make it hard
for them to find us isn't it I'm trying
to be honest with these people we put
them through a lot today these
people your cause that shit's over
Island's not the only thing that's green
dollars are too now a that's going to
narrow the search ain't it the
needle out your arm then tell me what to
do I'll let you tell me what to do when
you stop shoving half of Olivia up your
nose every Saturday night
oh do not the with
us Michael say
Michael there is a
hi my brother watch this happened in the
main game and we're now seeing a
different POV stream
POV oh bling bling the ballot of gay man
everything's a little fuzzy and if you
think of anything else Mr Lopez sure
sure I'll give you a call
thanks Mr
Lopez well he made it out alive good for
him oh he's like really
stuttering what's that what's with this
cam
work
[Music]
hey oh feeling good feeling good
ew the tattoo I meant was you bony it's
me yeah there was a farm at the bank
place got robbed nothing to do with me I
I
swear um some anyway um listen I'm
coming so wake up you hear me wake
up sneo
oh such a good
mood yeah I'm sorry no I I was working
lat Johnny was there too yeah Mommy
don't be like that okay I'll be home
soon look I I got to go
okay he keeps on
walking oh oh
oh Tony Mr Tony Price is it
me whatever
whatever oh how are you I'm good boss
how are you wow nice apartment you look
terrible that's good cuz I am terrible
wretched what's wrong oh the
usual boyfriend thinks I'm a cash
machine one nightclub catering to the
Rich mindless crowd in the city with a
rich mindless crowd is suddenly poor and
Mindless another club catering to the
gay and decadent crowd with the gay and
decadent crowd suddenly think decadence
means buying outrageous new throw
cushions instead of getting loaded in a
bar and every half with part-time Hood
in this city thinking I know let's put
the squeeze on the club Owners they must
really really want to substitute my
inadequacies with their money because
after all they want to stay up all night
talking to morons because they
enjoy it it sounds pretty usual oh
thanks for the support hey that's what
I'm here for a boss yes you know if The
Bodyguard business partner thing doesn't
work out you should consider a career as
a life coach oh he's his
bodygard never mind did you speak to
Troy yeah he said he loves you but he
can't handle working the door at a gay
club anymore he says people are laughing
at him who's laughing at him I don't
know I think the little people who live
in his head one stuck in 1955 oh I love
those people and what's up with Des he
he says he saw you last night yeah and
you was holding court with that Chloe
Parker until 4:00 a.m. I was apparently
so my God 45 years old and I get my
kicks doing blow with 17-year-old kids
whose only claim to fame is that people
know better what their vagina looks like
than their face I should be sent to
prison shouldn't I yeah most definitely
what's this money did you rob your own
club Tony I just went to the bank for
you man I don't want it in the bank hey
Tony the door was open man it's easier
to get into your apartment than into
your nightclub yeah we have an no Guido
policy at the club here I ain't so sure
oh I love getting racially abused used
by a SPI yeah who's a Taco Tony
my business partner Lis gentlemen watch
your language we're in the great Melting
Pot we're not spicks or guidos or
we're proud Americans Luis this is Vince
and Roco relatives of Gracie credit is
to you and guess what we ain't here
about Gracie oh oh
oh
beautiful hey that's a start I guess we
don't have to beat you two lovers up
yeah good one see you later oh nice to
meet you
muscles don't you there
go who the were those two
T fine men of the cloth who the do
you think they are ancelotti goons I
borrowed money from way back never mind
amateurs okay so let's go just took back
what belonged them all right
then should have kept it in the
bank
okay
n just collecting that and he he seems
to have plenty of money I mean we need
to go to
Hercules
Hercules I loved that Disney movie back
in the day I was I was I think my
favorite one W pink roads
ah everything think's pink let's go I
love that come from don't tell me you've
been running a SK job I would think that
was my favorite you know me
transparency sometimes I wonder if you
brought me on as a partner just to share
the blame when the IRS comes knocking I
was investing in your industry and
Acumen don't look for anything Sinister
here that's what you say t but I'm kind
of suspicious Massachusetts maybe SE
that robbery made me paranoid and
maybe that's what you say p
Massachusetts p
um what was I saying oh yeah once what
was I think maybe now it would be
different than what you what you would
say like 10 years ago or so what was
your favorite Disney movie when you were
younger I think it was really Hercules
for me
because of the fun music and the story
was fun
too Aladin oh a lot of Aladin Lion King
a few
Hercules Stitch is that even disy Aladin
El so many elant wow okay why did you
did you guys all fall for the cute
[Music]
girl be honest
guys here we are Beauty and the Beast
Troy Jasmine she's she's gorgeous a very
important client is coming tonight we
need complete
discretion what the hell is Treasure
Planet don't tell military grade hey
this is serious G buy his next CD if
they know he'd rather be singing Cabaret
than rapping as if people buy CDs
anymore sure look I really need to talk
to blah blah blah Another Time Troy
we'll be at
masonet
okay masonet
9 I've never been to a gay club before
getting anxious or any really getting
anxious nightclub business is going to
forget the banks were the ones who
needed a bailout no
more I've been to one Club I think in
Japan I think you could considered a
club for my friend really
only because my friend was DJing there
it was really empty though and I felt
super
uncomfortable no it wasn't idle stuff it
was like I think a proper Club but no
people and just super
awkward yeah nobody was really partying
there
either the cover charge is such a
r that was I think the only time you can
try to impress the ladies with you're
dancing if you dance successful for a
lady you make get a surprise
oh you can get some shots at the bar or
you can go upstairs to the VIP area and
take part in this is like
Yakuza okay okay how do I dance do I
need to do something like a rhythm
game
for okay who do I dance to like maybe
her like she's she's it it will be hard
to keep up with her but F4 left shift to
start dancing oh God maybe I should have
asked for the oh God no wait what is
this sorry sorry she doesn't like it I
need instructions sorry sorry sorry give
me instu uh can't go back to see the
instructions
uh what what what do I I
do oh my head's in the
way the menual
colors yeah they're
nice Press buttons I don't I don't see
it oh just maybe just
anything what else can I
push I can just move my arms like this
oh it's going up though see hold hold
what hold a
button
oh
huh am I doing this right I press the
left Mouse button for that moment
hold uh hold
what ah I did it wrong how do I know if
I go left or right Mouse
[Music]
button learning it without the
instructions oh I don't know what I'm
doing I'm just pressing everything but
I'm doing it right
oh oh I did it I did it
hey maybe I have to be in
Rhythm I don't know what I'm
doing
looking kind of weird there
guys no pissed her off I did something
wrong can we keep on going ah it was
[Music]
reset still don't know what I'm doing
prepare to
sens what is she going to get
naked oh
[Music]
F no F doesn't work now I should have
done it earlier a why why why why I
don't
understand whatever it's fine
winning somehow I figured it out even
though I still don't know what I'm
doing yeah okay okay I'm filling it up
see hey and I win can we go back into
the grinding mode what now I filled it
up
it's
full what happens now my fingers are
getting
tired shouldn't it have switched
yeah I don't even know how to end it oh
did I glitch it oh she's she left
what what was all that
for
ah hi Tony told one of your friends
ising trouble out front can you go
helpie you know who it is I don't know
anything about it but take care of it
l is this a gay club doesn't feel so gay
inside we're going outside right this
way or that
way
TOA fit no I can
dance you know I
can oh this is a normal Club okay L is
my boy people say l is their boy girls
all say they're him I don't care
if yours damn mother you ain't coming in
not in them clothes not with that
attitude enjoy looking for a job in this
economic climate yeah yo
what the he tell this clipboard and
ear piece mother to back up
B back up what's the problem D you
asking me y relax go inside I got it
yeah relax go inside mommy you need to
go relax guys shut up okay jeez wow
downtown's really Chang you man you too
good to take money from me and enque now
you know it ain't even like that bro
okay you don't pay for in here okay
you just can't be looking like you came
from selling dope on the corner yeah I
mean especially the red
[Music]
outfit dress like that huh you see what
I mean come to think of it Lou what the
are you wearing huh what go home
and take a bath do nothing else put on
some clothes huh I had a complicated day
okay all right take some time off the
girls neck use night off
too yeah after that dancing ritual
gentl ni you got there they don't want
to see me anymore come
on thanks Tony I
guess the dancing was SI
really you think so get in Tony's car
all
right my car now oh nice car take your
friends back to
Northwood all right I don't know where
that
is uhhuh okay thinking about this how
many days a week you work those Corners
seven days junkies need junk rain sleep
or shine you ain't no Postman loc you're
a busher all those hours you'd make more
slinging meat at Burger Shot than r ring
a bit on them Corners
H okay like 5 he seems like such a
nice guy guy playing what's Q 76
he's got his they're going
to let you do at Burger Shop with an IQ
sub 80 they just about to let me was the
you see what I mean now they don't even
have dishes at Burger Shop all this
is pene they ain't another job in the
city for this dumb bastard to do hourly
wage considered and all you don't get no
working Burger Shot NE
if them ivy league can't
find work what you think R is meant to
do work them Corners man work them
Corners I you don't mean nothing man you
guys are better than this I don't want
any of us to go away again and come on
board with us we can start selling our
own product your connections man we'll
have the whole city on our I took my for
you once man I ain't going back there
you think I put in all this work to go
back
inside huh oh prison was the best thing
that happened to you L what you talking
about man before you went in there you
was a skinny little and now you
pumped up don't tell me that sugar daddy
of yours would have been interested in
the scrawny that went away little
L little L I'm oh yeah thank you so much
man never thought about being grateful
to you for signing me up to the fight
off hairy ass rapist day and night
exercise plan my pleasure
bro a okay damn so we came out of
prison now we're
[Music]
buff nice it's like a workout
program arrived here we
be thanks
l
l we'll be back same time next week yeah
see you on my
way mama
whoevers what does that
mean I'm kind of cold I want a cardigan
or something no wonder I'm cold I'm
sitting here in my bikini all the
time yeah wasn't whoever was ex like it
seemed kind of familiar to
[Music]
me but why would he call him them
eggs oh did he mean different kind of
eggs oh ah in combination with that
uh-huh maybe it's
MH okay
[Music]
okay
oh that's how
home looks
decent oh it looks
good way better what we had with like
Nico sleeping on the bed will save the
game and advanc Time by 6 hours his bed
is even
made sheesh who makes their bed I
don't yeah use wardrob to change clth
wow
[Music]
what 66% what's that mean c ahuh for
each Mission I get this will show you
score in whether you have achieved any
secondary auh so with no car damage I
would have gotten a check mark there and
my time took too
long you will be able to repeat missions
in per well that's new
n this is where GTA 5 got it from uhhuh
I don't remember this in GT
G5 press enter to view the target
score
430 ah and 10 ah come on I was 1%
over and even the time wasn't that much
okay well not a
hold so he wanted us to change clothes
right oh
Tony L yes it's me things go smooth at
the clubs made me wonder why I need you
around at all oh great I might just take
a vacation then come on I was kidding
the clubs fell apart without you bank
robbery on the news could have been an
opportunity for some thought it was a
radiator that I don't need any
press like that now was the way police
Tre an xcon in this town have it your
way see you soon no shoes on a bed tell
that to all those American sitcoms and
movies and whatever it pisses me off so
much when they you know lay on their bed
with their shoes or generally walk
around everywhere and their home with
their shoes like oh my God stop
Americans stop please stop so disgusting
take off your shoes
please
ew right mhm especially on your bed how
can you what do you even sleep with
shoes like if you love your shoes so
much you should go shower with your
shoes we do what we
want okay what are our
options oh I I mean kind of a weird
Patchwork suit but what else
uh-huh
uhuh what does he want from us probably
the suit right that that that's like a
suit underneath the jacket at
[Music]
least I guess
this I don't know what to think about
the suit does it look
cheap it does doesn't
it it's interesting but it looks
[Music]
cheap
y needs a good ironing can we go
shopping Well for now we got a deal with
what we got I
think yeah okay
I think W go idle
meeting can we watch
TV saki ooh speedball makes saki sick
help me someone hey what about my dead
parent
Souls oh is that Dragon Ball forget
about I don't know maon Dragon
Ball week for another episode of
Princess Robot bubblegum don't forget to
pick up the feature length film that
went straight to DVD the saga continues
in I think you'll enjoy this while
I'm I hope it's not
copyright all right see you in a
bit oh wait wait wait I tapped Out
Princess Robot publicum lxvi repress
Destiny Sparkle the action RPG oh
ah too many numbers and of course
trading cards uncensored manga and
collectible figurines for lonely people
to stick on their desks in L of friends
plus an assortment of other quality
branded merchandise to horny to fight
crime visit princess robbubble gum.com
[Music]
Rich guys make me so wet marry Rich it's
all that matters the season finale of
gold diggers of Liberty City is next
week Oh Daddy the competition gets stiff
on
CNT they back and their front two bimbos
four massive breasts two tiny brains
conjoined twins season 2 what happens
when one finds religion and the other
finds work as an exotic dancer find out
only on
CNT princess Rober Bubblegum
[Music]
it's okay it happens to a lot of guys
you never know what radiation exposure
can do to your statement oh this is so
embarrassing look please don't blog
about this baby because I never had this
happen
before Oh No Yes master get your ass
back down to the training facility I
know I'm late for the sexually arousing
training montage I was just um tending
the garden are you even listening to
[Music]
me I'm sorry I'm late Master you're not
just late you're filthy you have pin all
over your face you the pr again
in master why have you never told me
about my parents H you were abandoned
here by your ninja parents after they
died they killed themselves for reasons
we will discuss in a future episode
trust me but for now I just want you to
think of yourself as the chosen
one what the is
this I didn't order anime I had
lived by myself for many hundreds of
years yet I was prevented from being
near children after a bit of a
misunderstanding find a blue square
how's the TV program is it entertaining
and dis it was just an innocent swimming
it repeating already I raised you in the
traditional way instilled you with a
proper sense of A Woman's Place oh
CH Ching I trained you in the dark
art vital for Fighting Evil I made lots
of long- winded speeches that unced
goodies as the wind flows the spirit
departs but then what about memories
what are they his his forehead his head
is literally a butt then the still just
reads in the wind like the stars of The
Province ining howo they sound simply
ephemeral theyes dust in the hands of a
man without legs such are the ancestral
spirits that summon us all what what the
are you talking about master
concentrate focus on my Cod
philosophical jibber
jabber yes I think you understand now
you're nearly one with the sword yes
yeah soon you'll be ready for two swords
at once then you get pay
extra okay how do I know I'm destined to
be a great warrior and why do I always
have to wear such skimpy clothing for
training and why do I have to have a
cute teleporting animal sidekick who
never does anything useful
saki boy oh saki you made a mess you you
annoying turd why merchandising of
course off the making Warrior educ sorc
I know the story of this girl
ridiculously huge breath a hairless
vagina that you have no shame in
exposing Pencil Thin arms come on you're
ready for the final
test the final
test hi
what whoa
who wow wow she's so
good she doesn't even see it but she
still gets it ready for a final awkward
transformation
Montage oh it's sa Moon
W oo
oh she's turning into Robo girl oh oh
oh they're even
bigger oh nice that's a I love that X
ribbon calm the down you are the
only hope we have save your dead ninja
parent Soul came up with a moody
arms feminite androgenous sword wielding
teen boy defeat the alien Armada Loop
animation
prodction costs just like last time yes
only this time futurist Tokyo is not
under threat from the forces of Darkness
sounds like it's it was it was about to
Loop now and no the VA is fine it's fine
how do I stop watching under the threat
from the oh different channels face just
like that yeah well you know what I
don't turn a blind eye too blind people
with the seeing eye dogs they don't have
to to pick it up I mean I wish I could
poop in public without having to pick it
up I have what talking about listen I'm
sure it's covered in my next book
pre-order wow you guys are so
dramatic yeah great just what the world
needs another book about how to solve
conflict with a nail gun and a bad
temper ooh nail gun let's go the onion
volcano was too powerful and my parents
were burned alive another
anim
I'm a blind Samurai I'm unable to love
you're not exactly a samurai I am same
well didn't you picked out the wrong
costume shut up this outfit is easy to
make into a plastic doll okay well I
wanted to be a Ninja really but like I
mean your parents are ninjas and like
they did which is like even better so
like they made me into like this goddamn
Samurai like yeah well I'm a sex fantasy
for creeps oh
tell me about it anyway you want to hear
something that sucks okay the last thing
I saw was a man flipping shrimp tails
into his hat imagine that okay get your
mind around that flipping sh like on a
cruise ship forever for eternity
terrible what a strange way to go blind
well at least he won't be hard to find I
could help you get revenge on the shrimp
tosser who took your sight but it won't
be easy he has restaurants at strip
malls across the world what's your quest
visit the graveyard um I have to visit
the graveyard and pick up a carton of
Redwood lights on your way home remember
lights not Dem Menthol I am
jonesing
okay oh it's the
graveyard
a she's so
sad it's so sad this isn't the right
graveyard but it's the only one I could
find
o PE
time okay I'm just going to stand here
and look Moody okay fair enough you're
blind and you're dressed wrong shut the
up you're jealous come on
let's get out of here before anything
stupid what Asian culture is so much
better than America I totally love this
place I think I was Japanese in a past
life plus I have a tiny weenie what
oh no machine
alive this is it the final fight
sequence oh another
Montage help I'm poorly dubbed and we're
running out of funds for translation
this story makes no sense Haya
ha o i scratch you dead body freezer
Mod's telephone yes translation
problem
oh no uhoh monster monster Ry time this
is why we started right remember your
training submitting to bizarre male
fantasies of women in a completely non
misogynistic and sexually healthy way no
a part in training hey get out of there
well look just like okay I was told to
get out of there let's get out of there
oh very interesting program that they
have prepared for the TV
wow where do we need to go guys we have
to focus we have to do some stuff first
of all how about we go grab some armor
but no they're all so far away and I
don't even know what my mission is
somebody going to call me or
[Music]
what
moyi stick with a th oh I got a text
could do with some help masonet come by
doing Opening Our or I'll see you at The
Loft opening hours when is it's 11:25
now I doubt oh I doubt that they're
opening
now you can blink
now thank
God you'll watch that I won't even watch
episode six of Star Wars that is very
very
different and I just put it on to
entertain you guys while I'm
gone I did get a cardigan by the way an
invisible
cardigan oh hey the road is now again
green probably because a I'm sorry I'm
so
sorry I'm so sorry I apologize for my
terrible terrible
Behavior please forgive
me I was really trying to get out of the
way okay we did it now I'm going to buy
armor I don't know if we need it this
early in the
DLC but better safe than
sorry
[Music]
is it is it really so did they I'm I'm
not sure like is it is the game actually
less gray right
now it could very well
be wow
hallelujah how much later was the DLC
made
after
after the game the original game came
out sky looks Bluer to you as blue as
New York City skies get
yeah I've never even been there but I'm
just saying oh hey my chat actually
broke to the m one year two year one
year two year one year oh okay well they
definitely took in
the critique of the game if there even
was critique about that back then I'm CR
criticizing it now but I don't know if
that was a thing people didn't like back
in the day oh hey there's an
M my my home is blinking what why is it
blinking does that mean it's
urgent oh now it's not blinking
[Music]
anymore it was definitely a thing H the
te is here
okay are you okay can't see what do you
mean I mean it's pretty much visible
no you can see the map just open your
[Music]
eyes
right even if you don't need the armor
now eventually we'll use it up
eventually hey man this is a clean
business no trouble
hello wait I only have 500 bucks and
this cost 500 ooh
oh my o just now clip that and then put
it on one of those Star Wars monsters
thingies
animals I think I just sounded like um
not not not like uh what's it called
yeah I sounded like a Chewbacca just
[Music]
now a chewy Baka a wookie
okay we'll go to the Pink
[Music]
Tea ssy B chewy
Buck sh to do nice guy I got to do
got to tell you about last
night Chihuahua Chihuahua I'm not a
Chihuahua I'm
kiaha oh where the fu are you been
man yeah I came as soon as I could I
don't pay for as soon as I could sleep
with half the women in Liberty City no
doubt you think I don't know that you
think I like being like this then what's
wrong T I up good and proper I
work on gin night life 20 years I beat
everyone Mayors Rivals drugs everyone
and this time I up what' you do
I'm the only man in the history of this
town with the hottest gay and straight
clubs at the same time I'm about to lose
everything what are you talking about he
owns both I don't know if that idiot
Evan or or the economy or his
cocaine or the pills which I am not
taking anymore but this time I
up I've done a deal with the wrong devil
man I'm such an idiot things have been
bad before man you get us out of it I
fight you plant together we get out of
it sure but we've never been this
before hey yeah it kind of went down the
Made Me Gay Tony always be the king of
this town you are this town I sold a
business to two different people and
they each think they own the lot man
we're should I make it louder so
I'll go tell them they gave you the
money as a present if they don't like it
I take them to the special VIP room at
the bottom of the West River it's going
to be very crowded in the VIP room these
are not nice people and there's a lot of
them and right now you and me have to go
play nice with one of them so they don't
start sending rent a Goomba into the
club goom it's going to be okay man yeah
whatever don't send the go to the club
this blogger this nebish with internet
connection bad mouthing me all over town
do you know this guy the the
senator do I know him come on all right
who's the girl there wasn't a girl man
there shark a
girl what does he mean with the go ding
range
we doing something for Roco the who took
your money yes one of the joys of
getting old is being ordered around by
people below the age of consent in Utah
don't you mean it's one of the joys of
borrowing money you can't pay back he
can take my money blackmail me my armor
is
purple my armor bar me who goes to
jail me as an insecure brick but I
didn't think he wrote like that he
doesn't I love this think so at least
it's colorful it's pretty up Suburban
this just up my Alle muscles can be
confusing actually I almost like my
anime RPG almost got a yeah sure you
could call crazy Coke adct a type
you've been reading my love me profile
lonely old hasbin se's crazy cokehead
with bulging orange biceps enjoy your
youth Louise you don't appreciate it
until it's over oh yeah I'll look back
on these years of getting sh at and
helping you clean up puke as the best
times of my life you idiot if I
miss this meeting I'm to
Y I love potato
tips good
stuff that was a close one with the
police in
here mm golden
Pier
golf oh that the way he put down the
ball look kind of gay the and the F Tony
you got burrito breath you ain't
been eating Mexican again have you yo
rock you invested in the wrong clubs man
maybe split sides is more your Vibe oh
but boom I'm sure I would have found
that funny if I spoke SPI real shame
I'll have to ask my maid to translate
for me rock what do you need I need you
to help me get some information out of
this Union prick who's decided to get an
overinflated opinion of himself these
guys stuck in the 1970s or
something I like the way he dresses he's
right down there well that looks amazing
I've never seen a balling out a bowling
golfing thingy like this in real
life from
inside I'm going to get down there and
go talk to him only from the outside hit
him with some balls when I tell you to
huh you think you can do that for me
Louise looks cool so big yeah I'll give
it a
try I
go top
[Music]
gohm what we doing man we're keeping our
most important investor happy H it
already yeah but nothing moves ahh okay
where where is the hole
though H I don't know where the hole
is whatever let's
go wow pretty Dominic to be athlet that
didn't go very far bend the knees it's
all I'm supposed to hit the guy okay
ah all right is
he is
he oh now I see the bar on on next to
the map no let me do it again no can I
cancel wait I yeah hey ah let me do
it again when it's up there ah
I think I get it okay
that you have a one of those I thought
if it's like in the red that's that's
when it really goes where I wanted to go
thanks
man
okay
okay that's also too much juice
tacos for it's hard to guess how
much power they want Step Up be my
guest that that's also too much but
better oh what I hope you didn't miss
purpose there ah so
close Okay that was that was literally
on the
mark So if I aim for him properly and
then get the mark
[Music]
then toour championships that's for sure
you're my caddy
ah
you people is more suited to being
tatties it's hard to get to the bar
remember to
breathe yo okay that could be
it you going to tell me who's holding
out all right what a creative way of
torture ain't going to comply he's
working down Columbus Avenue you got
more than that I know so creative that's
it let me go
already no moving it no I know don't
Rocco have someone else to hit the
batting case for him the guy haven't you
I can't imagine he's got too many
friends just really change this is so
creative we're making a game out of
it
okay oh I got it pretty damn good
hey give me the rest of them you piece
of I hear Jack Duffy with the tww
might be with them okay now off
already this don't add up let me go no
we don't have enough yet where are you
going job at this place where'd you
learn to play golf L right here right
now needs more don't to be honest I
never fancied the game I find the
clothes you have to wear kind that's
pretty far the farther we the further we
go the closer the bar seems to go to the
top
M ah
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe you
no damn
it B the knees it's all the knees shut
up I will not bend the knee to you you
are not my
[Music]
king ah too
much domicans is meant to be
athletes
smoothly come on now enough for the
commentary also a little bit too much
maybe they'll be lenient you one of
those things for Shut Up N
hell I thought they you tacos for sport
it's I feel like it's kind of delayed oh
now I got it it's really delayed like
when I click doesn't like stop right
away wow right in the face o there's got
to be someone higher up that should have
left this comes from right up top some
on his skin he's in with the m so you
can't do
they know where I am I
wouldn't want to be you you think that
means to me
you action baby
I'm help
me much as it pains me we better get
down good that I got myself some
armor but the first mission can't be so
difficult
right down how much
down ah this level I think oh I'm scared
[Music]
scared uh uh uh I don't feel very
coveredby is that all I have that's I
don't I think I only have the pistol m m
this is not good this is not good this
is not good what a shitty position I'm
in and they're so
far okay okay okay calm stay calm and
then I can do it
your head is in the
way you don't want to
[Music]
be
um a get his feet
[Music]
oh but hey I can do it without taking
cover
that's
something they have shittier aim than me
that is for
sure he but look at my ammo look at my
ammo who who whoa whoaa I need to run in
there to get some
stuff sorry wa coming
through hey hey the
SMG hello pick it up hey
all right
hey let's
move
hey okay why am I doing that that's a
little bit too
much okay he's just chilling there in
his shoot with his hands on his
knees I
sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry o oh racing on the golf course
fun with the golf car where are we going
buddy that way oh that's a small
exit oh hey poor lady I feel bad for
her there goes my armor so armor was
definitely a good
idea oh gon is shooting
wow so proud oh
uh uh I'll go from
here hell
okay they're in front of me
now I wish I was the one shooting then
we would actually have a chance
uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh no don't be in front
of me
no we're yeah we
are we only got one behind us now thank
Moses but one's in front of us oh D they
messed up we might be in the clear yeah
that was very stupid of them ftic did
you see I can't shoot oh you to say
so oh
explosion how do we get into this
situation running away from monsters in
a golf cart I think you
got thanks for that dignity nice I think
we
lost what a nice ride we
have make me help us out
yeah that was a pleasant outing Rock
where's that P with you know what we
square square what you borrowed at those
point you even on the interest besides
I'm about to have to do all the messy
work on this guy myself but I I I told
you everything I'll see you girls
later
Jesus poor guy he's so bloody too let's
just head back to the
apartment
okay didn't hear him screaming I thought
it was my own for that guy like a back a
of crabs crabs are easy to get rid of
believe me on that one thank you for
sharing we're business part is we share
everything the emphasis is on business
bro you can keep your crabs to yourself
sorry man but I really got in this
here Lis Tony man you got to calm down
you're really pushing me yeah well if
you weren't out chasing tail this was a
Twan operation like it should be then
maybe things will be holding together
better oh I'm getting blamed for this
now oh of course whenever I come to the
clubs you ask me to run off on some
stupid errand like a chump you don't
ever let me into the serious and
you do deals without even telling me
until it comes time to protect your ass
from whoever you got your fat the day
from all right all right maybe I'm
taking you for granted I'll change I'll
be better yeah thank you but I don't
believe
it they've got
issues those two but they're kind of T
okay listen Lou would you mind
paying I know he's a bit of a schmuck
but we owe the man money and I don't
want him anywhere near the clubs I feel
you there t that guy is a social atom
bomb I'll go see him
h what's with cie oh paying more your
visit the golf accuracy I didn't get a
single check
mark
huh 50 52 what the
rude okay we have to go to
my and why why is this tea
blinking
is it because it's
like this says available so it's like
not a must or
so shall we go here but then first uh
maybe here should I take the golf
cart
n let's take a proper car this one looks
so nice that's a is that a m that's a
musle
car I think sorry Mister what the
up
maybe hell
[Music]
yeah let's go muscle
car pretty muscle
car I know a thing or two about muscle
cars I'm going to go grab more armor
that's the only Annoying Thing like
having to grab Armor after each freaking
Mission and you could say skill issue
but I'm just going to say say nah it's
not entirely on
me it's kind of
[Music]
annoying should I buy some other stuff I
don't really have the money for it yet
to be honest so maybe
not just don't get
[Music]
sh okay Mor
maybe we find food on the way should be
possible your gun is
showing oh cute looks like a taxi but
not
quite
ow ah man my driving is kind of off
right now I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm so
used to the bike
maybe oh nice car not so nice
anymore oh he met
he's
[Music]
angry what the hell cheat codes but you
don't get achievements ah you mean for
the armor I could get I could put in a
cheat actually that really makes me
think when I used to play games
privately I would totally
cheat when there was a option like in
games like GTA or Sims like I didn't
really play GTA but I would totally
cheat if I was playing this back in the
day definitely cheated in
Sims that
sucks probably would have cheated an AOE
too yeah but for streams you
know yeah everyone does it right
everyone cheats
but in streams it just feels like wrong
and also I mean it makes no sense y you
want to do something with it was funny
for a little bit in AOE too but it
definitely shouldn't be uh the norm is
going to be disappointed bro
okay if I cheat then the game isn't a
challenge anymore and you know too
[Music]
easy yeah
Amando Amando
[Music]
Watson yeah I played aoe2 on my
channel and actually seems like it's
making a
comeback
um cuz Mauna asked uh again
about the tournament thing that she was
planning which even more now makes me
think I should find
this this lady that seems to know her
things about
aoe2 and make her teach me but then is
kind of
unfair compared to the others who are
not letting themselves be taught but
like what can I do about they could let
themselves be taught as
well um I didn't pick up any
food there's no food down here huh it
looks really gray again dark and
gray no it's not
[Music]
unfair yeah I wonder how serious they're
going to take
it the the tournament itself but it
means I'll get back into AOE too a
little bit for a little while probably
hey yeah whatever come here give me some
love right here so what' you want don't
say you needed a favor I look like a
charity case to you can I ple the fif on
that
one that's funny you're funny yeah
you're funny he's got an
interesting face compared to his body of
a little girl and man you need calf
implants you and you know I'm guessing
just just from looking at you you ain't
exactly pack in a 10-in hose man me I
make girls
wice
WCE just to LEL with you for a minute
bro Tony owes you money the monkey
noises Ton's my boss and my friend so I
help you a little but if you mention my
host again I'll put you in the
ground Jesus Christ man you pent up come
on I didn't mean anything by it I
apologize right look let's re he's like
a childish version of that other
athletic dude from come
here give me a hug whoever that was
bruy oh well if it isn't my brother the
ghost what are you doing here bro and
who's this guy it's Lou it's Lis Lou
it's nice to see little brother Jesus
you look pale what somebody die
unfortunately not man what are you doing
here myy I my D my I'm thinking about
moving back
home you see I've been hearing some
stories about you getting somewhat uh
above yourself and I'm worried about you
don't worry about me man I'm fine okay
I'm going to be just fine Jesus
who is related man ought to be horse
whipped look at you you're you're you're
you're lumpy like a awful like a a big
pale mess and you're fat
bro you're
fat you my man you're you're you're
you're you're perfect yeah chiseled tan
handsome on the dream ticket maybe your
mom always warned me that you were a
lazy kid I bet you've been juicy Maybe
here's the reason why Brucey ends up
like that
happens no no
no yeah I smell it on you fear I smell
it on you guys too A lot of the time
back and your life just got fun again
come on Lou let's roll what an annoying
brother to have you better let your
friends know about me because kibuts
number
one yeah he's back back in town and this
time it's
kosher want to be you
wow an interesting character for sure
man will
you
oh we have what need done we some very
intense to handle yeah I'm hoping
you mean you got or red something like
that that's about as intense as I'm
willing to give red wow it's incredible
he looks like a man but he talks like a
is Brucey on steroids you're a business
guy so you should stick to your business
don't get involved in stuff that's
out of your lead because of very intense
syndrome that makes you
overcompensate but I like intense
characters on
you need me to take out the monster I'll
wh that on the dashboard and see
what you think of it yo yo you'll think
it suddenly got darker in here I'm
talking serious block the sun oh
what you talking about hold me
responsible for your inadequacy issues
after that huh oh oh don't take nothing
out bro keep it to yourself keep the
monster away from me and listen to what
I'm saying this comes from the
heart okay I don't want to see you
getting in over your head for a man of
your height it's easy to do wo w slow up
dog I think you're mistaken in your
impression of me I look like a civilian
to you you look like a lot of things bro
a lot of neurosis in one tiny package
kind of like an army knife without the
edge you think because of my lumpy
little brother that I don't swing on the
dark side hey I never said you w a s
don't you think of it might have seen
you on one of the never said you weren't
a swinger I done 3 years I se you
wouldn't even believe yeah I done 3
years helping to run
I seen you wouldn't believe hey how
many guys got the juice to get into some
Foreign Legion when they're
18 then we might as well drive through
the
drive-thru where are we going damn
it let me just hang here for a a little
bit de stuck
again that was too easy getting away
from those where are we actually
going though oh wait I was going the
right direction suck on your mama's
titty at that AG time bro and leave my
mama out of it things I saw over there
were insane dog insane i' tell you about
it but then I'd have to kill you right
here I could do it too with my beheads
wouldn't even think twice about it we're
talking about murder now I won't because
I like you yeah Special Forces don't
even begin to describe my special
sounds about right to me look I came
back here after the service and I
changed man I changed you think it's
easy sitting down at Econ 101 with youve
been icing fools I wouldn't know bro
still got my 4.0 didn't I go give it up
right here yeah good for you bro you
want to send me a resume so we can skip
all this personal history crap no okay
stop talking dude where we have
arrived get down to the docks okay I get
out of another car
too man I like the
car have I not been here
before hey you what the are you
doing here myy oh they
dude we told you we ain't in business
with you no more you're a ripoff
Merchant no more cooperation my friends
it's hostile takeover time hand it over
you Mor you prick you ripped
us off for the last time let's get these
oh
okay take out all of Mor's Rivals Helia
anything from Mory
K got to help my
homie
hey
wa n need the fu up there a he's
going to kill us uh yeah oh
out
of Mama
Mia
um that's not very very
nice thanks paramedics
but I want to redo
that please where do we restart is the
are the checkpoints good in this part of
the DLC as
well oh you what the are you doing
here
Mory mother
don't run in circles I thought that was
the best
strategy oh is this the RPG
guy
no the
peak out of
here or was it and he just switched
weapon
there it is he's up there get
him before we're dead okay let's go
ah of
boy I still want to pick up something
okay okay
[Music]
okay my hearing is gone come back
please don't shoot
me uh is the one the last one is the one
with the RPG right okay oh oh there's
more I don't feel I don't know if I can
survive
this especially since my friend isn't
even joining
me oh
he
oh
okay I got everyone on this
level what do you got oh got to get all
those nice weapons in the
beginning is this the right level
oh we clear was it him wait do I get it
do I get
it that just looks like a normal rifle
to me the jetty uh that means go down
right go to the jetty The Jetty The
Jetty Con on 1.5 million thank you
[Applause]
hey it has been a long long ride to come
to this point
um
God I am very proud of
myself oh no not the wobbly
Waters they ain't going to go nowhere
with one of these bomb let's do itue oh
we want us do sticky bomb all right is
this the one where I have to be like
close to them
[Music]
again I don't know how this
works launch man
I are they sticky those are sticky ones
right do whatever the they like to
do you're annoying nobody Ro yeah byby
go away go away go away me I think it's
stuck to them that's right angry Lopez
it I think I think can't I'm doing this
man but it doesn't go off what am I
doing
wrong arrow down button press down to
dat name nice one
you buy my
[Music]
health
goodby have to catch up you can't throw
that far I
[Music]
think wobbly wobbly wobbly wobbly wobbly
okay here we
go uh that did it stick no it didn't
stick
uh
I don't think that's ah why would I
even attempt oh that was dangerous why
did I make it blow up so close to me
holy
[Music]
genius W not so much genius after
all we have to catch
up
come
on hey oh no I don't think no I don't
think
so
hey take no come
[Music]
on
M blowing up all the fishies in the
water hey don't loose a f can I lose
this if
he drives off into the sunset with
Sunrise oh God he's so
[Music]
fast okay now it's a
chance that's definitely on
him uh
you
there beautiful knock up and I'll
bust on out of here
nice sticky bomb very helpful well not
that wobbly water it's so wobbly hey bro
I can't imagine you got much of our
business left now that we taking out all
your employees imagination isn't your
strong suit Louis let's leave the
logistics to me huh hey I'm more than
happy to leave everything to you war in
fact I don't want to be no part of any
of this correct me if I'm wrong but
you and Tony are business partners
aren't you sure well I own Tony EO I own
your ass as well get used to it hey no
one ows me bro oh I beg a
differ
no no no no no we don't play this game
not like that go bro you're going to get
out of my face now wo sure I am sure he
you did great I'm feeling real bullish
about you Lou real
bullish that doesn't sound so good hey
you come by soon we got some more
to
[Applause]
discuss yay do I get any check marks at
all oh two 11 head shots
oh
mhm back space oh there it is all
right okay enough B time
yeah it can't be that
hard to just stay on
land I'm going to
drown okay straight straight straight
straight straight straight straight
straight thank you why are there no lead
uh fences
Ledges over there H you're bound to fall
all right oh we're really low on health
we got no armor so
that's first thing is there any food
here like here a
soda probably not going to help much
take the potato
chips great deals great deals does it
like at least fill up a little bit thank
you very
much oh that's pretty much full health
I'll take
it oh wait there's a hot dog stand
there I know I'm pretty much full health
I don't
want to get anything else where are we
o pretty close to
the
Gabby get out this my
Camp unless you want to drive at me
I thought so where can I
take soda very feeling
surprisingly here we are thank you very
much yo I mean that oh my God these
taxis eight bucks wow that's so cheap
actually no
hey
idiot I wish taxi now now we that cheap
no all right not even Uber is very cheap
here
anymore see you later it's messed up
okay now we could go to the tea shall we
go to the tea to Tony he's available for
[Music]
us let's take an AV
cab did he stop for me thank you
yeah
I we drive this
direction there's just too much
inflation these
days too much also for trains I noticed
there's is one train in
Austria that you used to be oh my God oh
my
God oh my God used to be the cheapest it
oh not the okay okay
okay that's one way to blow up a
seagull
uh there's this one train that used to
be like the cheapest what what do you
want what do you
want what I didn't blow you up or was at
your
seagull oh
man life is not very nice to me
when hey he don't piss me up no
leave me
alone oh oh wait hey who is the police
shooting am I let me get out of
this oh my God what was happening they
will arrest him wow
really je that never
happened yeah am I dressed appropriately
now today
[Music]
wait let me tell about the Aus train in
a
minute oh my God
[Music]
romance Mor no my my no I I got the
money seriously that's not the issue I
Snee in your ear is there anything else
my team can do for you no we do events
parties anything you like just give it a
think all right bye-bye duality of kfb E
versus kazun mostly Gaz think about
what's up come on there's something I
got to take care of all right think
think
thanks
[Music]
Trevor Tony me of course of course my
business partner Mr Lopez YF Amir what
is up homie not much what is up pomy hey
you guys want to join us maybe for a a
bit of this or a bit of that ah we'd
love to but we got to go deal with some
business okay good good seeing you take
care huh oh W who W and if you ever want
to talk about franchising this place huh
just give me a call we will we
absolutely
will let's go I'm in the mood
baby good to see everybody in a good
mood bless you thank
you youf the
legend hey I should have picked up some
food in the club they must must have had
at least like fries or
nuts
something take Tony to Dragon heart
Plaza just in case in case this is some
sci-fi if I find food on the way
I'm taking it to be prepared what we
doing in Chinatown take a guess another
job for that Rocco oh yeah and moreon
proud of yours after what happened at
that driving range we still all that
pimply I did a lot of dumb things
in my life Lis but none of them were
dumber than borrowing from those bricks
really though some real I mean you're
still going out with heav this is
serious the Mafia even if we did
have the money to pay them back they
wouldn't take it they're going to ride
us into the ground but you don't have
the money do you to hey what about that
thing in London that going to pull us
through this didn't I tell you
London ain't happening and I wouldn't
travel to that to pun anytime soon if
you were thinking about it bro
thanks for keeping me in the loop again
can I get food here doesn't look like I
can
enter man I'll
D give me some of that al dante
please F
Toco did I miss something these are the
big streets there should be some
food over here there's like people
literally outside
there in the same place basically to put
cramp what about the
cramp how's the first DLC oh was fine it
was improvement over the main game in
some ways killed green
car green green and my I can't find food
I wish I could like pack a sandwich or
so just eat it whenever I wanted like
buy something from the supermarket or
so that area looks like there could be a
hot dog stand honestly over
here
no there must
be there must be some food here I'm
starving I can't keep on eating potato
chips all the
time
[Music]
H can't find the food when you really
need
it
sasuga what about here restaurant can't
be entered this looks like very
special
dimsum maybe in there
I didn't have those DUIs I'd step behind
the wheel right now you're a
menace I'm a menace of society yay
that's a compliment for
me
H maybe I'll give
up yeah I wish they would show like food
sources on the map like the little hot
dog
stands
h hey let me move you guys why are you
why are you over on my second monitor
anyway you should be I can't move
it there we go come on come on come over
here hold my hand follow me
[Music]
oopsie now you're closer to me now you
can whisper in my ear yeah your main
monitor material of course you are I
always try to have even though I have
fre monitors I still try to put like the
game and
chat
on uh one monitor in the
middle and then on my right monitor I
usually have
OBS left is actually mostly empty cuz I
feel like my microphone is there so I
don't like it's kind of in the way I
don't get a clear look to it anyway most
of the time I don't put anything there
and sometimes I have like Discord on my
right side in case I'm waiting for
something or
so for Hol talk it's a bit more
complicated cuz I need to look at
everything but I usually keep my
script in the middle my question script
cuz I need to memo memo I need to write
down
things but I also need to have my hand
on on Hol uh on OBS on the all the time
because I need to switch cameras and
stuff like that to make it look more
interesting a okay whatever no food then
at least we have full
armor
gum in that case I guess my brother is
in good hands you take care of
that seem the defition of differs in
your country the marketplace has a value
for everything and I guess that a
disloyal you bastard ain't wor to
me didn't we see this brother such are
the heady joys of consumer capitalism
the prev that's flaws are becoming
increasingly evident that's right I
forgot you little yellow people are
commies too huh both sides of the fence
you know I grew up watching your kind
getting killed on the TV hell of a show
I'm sure but perhaps the show wasn't as
much fun as the reality of that wall H
perhaps not now I bid you farewell sir
and don't do all that smack at once on
second thought you know go ahead
do boo watch you g a vending machine
inside here I apologize for our
Associates UNC manner I can only say
that our does it look so familiar one of
necessity not Felician please you must
be the famous Tony Prince uh notorious
maybe it's Luis Lopez my business
partner so nice of him to always
introduce me has led me to expect much
from this meeting ah yeah about that
Rocco has a tendency to promise more
than he can deliver that must have been
weaned too early yeah not weaned at
all as you can see we are already behind
schedule on this project we need you to
uh how do I put this to our things with
the planning department and to ease some
licensing troubles look we're not
lawyers okay we run nightclubs pretty
badly too we got enough trouble keeping
the licenses on our own clubs okay we
don't do licenses before I was being
polite Mr Lopez but I do not have to be
Mr Pelosi made it clear that you are not
in a position to choose who you help and
who you do not yeah well that kid got a
big mouth okay and he ain't in no
position to be writing checks for us
okay we are not going to be able to help
you period let's go to sorry to waste
your time Mr um you are not going
anywhere until we have an arrangement no
I'm afraid we are there is no
Arrangement you got a problem take it up
with your boy
Rocco me you are not negotiating
columninches and B tabs you insolent
we are serious
people really yeah really
oh what is wrong with you I was supposed
to be the irrational idiot with the
anger issues I got anger issues okay the
the guy threatens to shoot me cuz I
can't arrange the licis for him please
give me a break D oh
God they're coming for
us very interesting hey baby oh she's
rubbing her face against something nice
edges cats love edges oh
oh man what is that gun in my hand
what the is that I'm zeroed in on
him I've seen that before what's going
what what is this a P90 is it like
a is it like a rifle or like an SMG
what's it closer
to it won't
shoot
himg this is why I pay you to be it
won't shoot you ain't paying me enough
is it so silent that I don't even notice
it's
shooting the wall okay is it the wall
the wall man
there we
go that did indeed sound different from
others
[Music]
okay what it sounds so
funny oh I didn't know you can silence a
gun like this oh my God calm
down fop you
my happy
place and let me let me take cover like
kind of
here you can silence
anything you joking right I think I got
him I think I got them one too nice I
get extra for head shots right ooh
that's the the little gun again it's
nice to they bring new guns in both
DLCs
even cover my ass
thinking Ain going down who needs
cover except for me cuz I'm in whole
life oh more
armor just a little bit not F
would have preferred a first aid kit but
yeah
okay Stick by Me
bro's that's my buzzing my microphone
buzzing his back oh
[Music]
no uh where are we
going down I don't see any more enemies
you can hear it now right it was a joke
by the way it wasn't my
microphone he's still trying to
shoot what a fun gun P90 they call this
I I shall remember this it looks so
funny
too hey
grenade that should be fine right yeah
you you actually your St up
there it sounds sounds like
popcorn or I don't
know what are you even doing nothing
find a happy place find a happy place
what do we get into does it matter just
get us out of it I already found my
happy place it's whole
alive
Nice Shot SW nice move
baby can you take a look at the floor
below Lou I'm having a fit here I'll
check it
out oh another one wow okay really
really
generous what you wa what you waiting
what you waiting for you can come down
now come down Tony
[Music]
boy look at me holy I'm
good
hello can I enter move up to me oh I can
is there any secret here no
lame I'm cracked CS go shall we play CS
go
no Angry mother up or
down I would say down yeah I'll check
everything for you you're paying me good
I
hope
I hope he's paying me well oh there's
the oh you were right good brain whoever
said that
[Applause]
Candy by
me oh I'm at the
wall I'll get a drink once I clear this
area you angry
wow that took a lot of
me yeah that is realistic we take it
Psychopaths nobody will shoot me
while I take the soda
right they're going to kill us L I
wouldn't mind if they put another armor
here but no okay okay I will not stand
in front of people's shotguns and any
more at least not that close I
promise sounds like a good idea
right that's my
future goals
future resol resolution for the future
man move up more soda
wow yay look at all those balls cute is
there more of them
outside wait for Tony to exit the
building
okay oh what's this
car please what can you drive me to
the apartment I need to lie
down he's so dramatic
man okay
we did
it that was a delightful experience
can't believe we made it out of there
that was worse than spin class my
heart hey you need to look after
yourself I'm soak through I must lost
three PB in sweat yeah I'm going looking
for walking behind me nearly got us
killed when I get a hold of him you
won't do anything Lou You'll Play it
nice we can use this if we're smart we
were dumb enough to walk into the death
tra for the kid I doubt we're going to
pull brains out of our asses now I was
too close for conversation I got a
feeling we ain't the only ones will be
ripping him L God I need my pills don't
take that T I'm
serious a he's looking out for
him so sweet oh what did I get player
damage
[Music]
zero really
75 plot
armor whoa only got the armor damage
even that besides the one almost head
shot that I got I didn't really take
much yeah actually
true
[Music]
Pro
okay uh do we have a place to
go is is the m this just my home right
do they want me to go there it says
Mom's house mom's house should I go to
Mom's house first TR first I go to armor
house you really want that Austrian
train tangent huh ah Moy
Moy here comes the next mission hey
what's happening man who's this that's
Yousef air man who the guy who wants to
talk about franchising your clubs hey
those conversations are usually Tony's
Department well Mr Tony gave me your
number there are some other matters I
need to discuss before we get down to
the real hey if Tony gave you my
number then it's okay bro great come
hang out at my apartment it's right on
the middle Park prime location one of
the most exclusive in the city top
dollar you love it all right I'll
be by sometime just don't wait up
okay uh yeah okay
so Austria you know maybe you remember
it's shaped like a schnitzel right so
it's kind of wide right
and no no I don't want to buy the
grenade
oopsie you're thinking chicken leg Yeah
Yeah chicken leg schnitzel same thing
schnitzel land I I like to say schnitzel
because that's our
our
thing
mhm
and and and so there's like uh on the
top part of the Schnitzel that is not as
lengthy as the bottom part of the
Schnitzel uh there's on the right side
there is the capital Vienna and on the
left side there is a nice city that
borders to um Germany uh to like close
to Munich kind of um it's called sbur
yeah yeah m sbur is where mad was born
Vienna is where mad lived for a while
okay so they're like on on the edges of
Austria those
two okay understand so uh years ago many
many many many many many years
ago this company like we always had like
like normal Austrian trains right the
they're called o with the o with the two
dots on top so that you can't write it
if you don't have Austrian keyboard but
you could write o e BB instead we have
the UB B trains and I never wanted to
use trains cuz they were so expensive
and that was broke Tony I'm
talking L what's gotten into you why
haven't you been helping out at the
clubs you serious man I've been running
around this city getting shot at by
doing hit for
HH so we can keep these plac running
what else you expect me to be doing
standards have spped L we're dead
without this Revenue stream just keep an
eye on things
okay every night just talk to him and
he'll explain everything okay T but to
freed up relax enjoy
yourself okay wait but I'm going here
right
yeah and
so uh back in the day normal Trends too
expensive unless you have like some like
discount cards and this and that BL blah
blue didn't have that though but
suddenly out of nowhere this new train
company shows up in our country I don't
know where the hell they came from but
everybody was happy because they
offered this route between zburg and
Vienna with like several stops in
between that are pretty important stops
too like Lind for example I think M yeah
the vest buan I told you about the vest
ban before I think and they offered like
basically if you want to go from sburg
to
Vienna it was half the price than what
the Austrian trains UB would offer like
half crazy okay it was so cheap so
suddenly it was a nice way to get around
the country and I would say like so like
everybody made use of
it because it was just so much cheaper
and it was kind of comfortable and it
was also cool because you could buy the
tickets in the train um it was like a
pretty normal thing to do with this vest
ban while in the ubb trains you have to
have the ticket beforehand but it's just
more comfortable when you're like
stressed out right and you just have no
time to buy a ticket cuz you're already
running through the
train you can just buy it there and it
was a really nice train too like it
looked very very different compared to
all the other trains that we
have yeah and then it evolved so much
that because it was so popular they
added some more routes and they even
made a vest bus like a bus
version I think I never used it but I
think they made that mhm it was really
really popular so and for a while this
was like the best option to get around
the country at least in in that area
like the upper
schnitzel yeah and uh and then I haven't
the past years cuz I was in Japan and
all that I just haven't used trains
much but I
noticed the
price did not double no it kind of
tripled it's
now for some
reason more more
expensive like it it doesn't make sense
anymore to use it the vest
buan it's and this is I don't think this
is even inflation only it's more like
you know the I
think there's probably more reasons to
this why they increased their prices
prices insanely but now I can't
recommend it to you guys anymore if you
travel to Austria it's been this
happened though I don't know when but
like for many years it was fine
but this is a development over a long
long
time yeah privatized Transportation
moment yeah I think they probably at
some point probably themselves thought
hey we're so cheap we we can up our
prices a bit more like they'll still use
us and then I don't know what else
happened that they would go this far but
now it makes no sense now I don't want
to use the vest Buon
anymore it was still cheap when I was
there really are you
sure yeah but they lost their Monopoly
like why would they do
that part of it was probably
sh like un
un like not really in their
hands
but
man messed up really expensive
trains why are they so expensive man
man why is so
expensive why am I going
automatically
yeah how much are we talking I forgot
but it's like triple what it originally
was hello like really unreasonably
expensive
hello what was it what was it
um I don't know got to look it up hey
man hey what's up what's up so
glad you could make it man seriously
you're not a you shouldn't say
that
sir you okay bro no I'm fine man I got a
couple of upstairs hot ones not
sheep nice hey man you want to join in
no I'm cool man I'm cool yeah of course
oh to be honest anyway after I finish
with them they'll be out of commission
anyway I'll bang them to Pieces after I
finish with them they look like they've
been dragged through the desert
wow good for you man good for you listen
so um what' you want
you see this city I own it everything
seriously I DED that but one daying 60
skyscrapers man condos P houses luxury
apartments serious MH I tell you oh
man oh I love this song you know this
song oh
yeah
money hey you don't
dance
a city I run it I run everything I'll
show everyone I mean look at this
here this is a gold
phone great man that's
great B is doing bird
[Music]
dancing nice aquarium
nice game
thing so what do you say you going to
help me out Tony says you can handle
your myself maybe man what you is he an
oil Baron and to shut my father
up who I ain't killing your father man
no I know you're not I needed to get a
helicopter for him you know and I found
it w that scooter beautiful machine sexy
the company that built it they have a
display model on their boat and that
will shut him up you know so them I've
got good connections you know and uh pay
him the respect he deserves is that porn
playing up there bro no man that's real
women helicopter mission I'll be all
right as long as I'm not super pressured
like in the ending of the GTA you want
me to get you my helicopter and that'll
make you that happy you better be the
real deal
man you know I tell Tony that we work
together huh I'm going to make you both
very rich men we'll open up nightclubs
all around the world China Pakistan Tim
back to anywhere you
want you know what this means
you and I we are brothers we're
Partners great this one's much harder
really I'll get through it some business
I'll be fine
ladies prepare to
[Music]
suffer
okay uh what a
idiot get a boat from the
marina
minai
M and we're not taking that truck right
we need to proper car real car didn't I
leave my car on the other
side I'll take this one though that one
looks nice my
car
sparkly like that was probably my car
anyway is he a werewolf
how werewolf
vtuber definitely already exists I can
see
it Mercedes E-Class yeah looks like a
look a you look pretty normal car but
good like good quality normal basic
car how to describe cars by taka
nashiki what turn to the
right it's actually mayb I can tell you
one thing this is not a May
Maybach there was a time where I knew
nothing about cars and I found out about
Maybach and then I said okay I know
about this one car this is now my
favorite car this is the car I'll get
myself in the future and thus I know
this is not a
Maybach the one car I knew about was a
Maybach I don't think I'll ever get
myself one though too
expensive not worth it no I'll I'll for
getting a may I get a Tesla I think
they're
cheaper meres band on
crack my
bag why you saying it like that because
that's how you say it in German my
B and it just sounds
better don't get a Tesla okay okay
well remember I I wanted to get like
those classic cars
anyway the
oldies but like make it modern inside so
that it runs properly like a proper car
but the outside must look like a a nice
old classic
car make sure from newer plants I mean
like new
models n n well I mean I'm still very
very far away from getting a car so
that's the thing far in the history and
if I if it all if it gets to that
point nice why would I get a start for
that are the SE insured or
what did I have
insurance yeah once I get to the point
of getting closer to getting a car then
I'll don't worry I'll I'll do my
research or I'll ask my brother I don't
know I'll do my research and I'll I'll
think very thoroughly about
it but I don't need a car yet I mean
sometimes there's times definitely where
I feel like oh I wish I had a car or
someone who could just drive me
spontaneously to where I need to go
especially like I don't know if I need
to go to the vet for example cuz my cats
are freaking
heavy heart to
carry where was I supposed to go the
Mark is
gone it's called Uber no but there the
Ubers are also not that happy when they
need to
transport cats even if they're in the
boxes they're still like
uh any
boat which
boat it's
like uhhuh I can just take any boat
right I need of them okay well we'll
take this one although o that one looks
nicer oh
well
nice what was I
saying
oh yeah and also when the distance isn't
that long they're also like pissed it's
just also so
expensive it's so
expensive uers are so
expensive they're supposed to be cheap
they used to be cheap why are they also
so expensive now
man did I tell you about the one time
when I was kind of like stranded late at
night at the airport because of delays
and we I was forced to take an Uber and
they were like like those those
birds and and hyenas that come when
there's like dead animals on the
ground they like gather all around it
cuz they're like yeah vultures
vulture
taxis cuz they knew that all the trains
were done for the
night buses too there's nothing like
this not walkable cuz the airport is not
in reasonable distance to
anything so they knew they knew you need
a
taxi and they raised their prices I know
how much Uber normally costs from the
airport they raise it
like at least double if not
triple so expensive and we were like
disgusting like this is too expensive
this is too expensive hoping that if we
act like we don't need it
but we obviously do need it that they
would bring it down but
no Mama
Mia yeah especially cuz like when
there's high demand they can also up
their prices even more how do I get up
there do I just
like wait maybe
sideways 80 to leave the airport on the
taxi holy that's a
lot let's try to like jump over
smoothly ah
oh wow that surprisingly smooth baby the
Buzzard she will pick the bones of your
enemies
clean steal a chop should I be
stealthie nice music
I mean so far they can't see me but you
guys said this mission is difficult is
it difficult after I get the
chopper or until I get the chopper or
[Music]
both
oh they don't see me yet but I mean can
I not just
walk okay thank you for making the
decision easy on me
we
[Music]
got yeah
okay it has an
alarm get in okay how do we control a
chopper again uh man this is some
hard I'm not
sure uh are we going to take off is this
how I'm taking off oh there we
go
uh
uh um uh uh uh uh that's not it uh
numpad right there we go there we go
there we go where are we going oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
sh oh
[Music]
it's okay we'll just try again my man
hey YF the chopper took a little damage
you ain't going to be able to give it to
shut let me just do it again a
shame just redo it sexy time the mission
is called sexy
time when the bottom of the blade faces
what is the direction where you go
Buzz hey look at this nice restart spot
wasn't it night time
before hey my
health my health didn't reset did it was
it always just
low
he what about my
health got an undesirable on board
an undesirable on
board that sounded so
Irish we
have Mar Chopper looks like he's
shooting the
woman be nice to you
women
[Music]
okay stylistic Choice he ugly
just kiding just
kiding than for the lesson
Tony okay okay okay
okay just don't don't play too much with
that okay okay okay I can do it I can do
it
I think what blade are we talking
about uh this indicates your height
above sea level I think I'm too
high okay okay ah this this freaks me
out when that when I when I point
downwards that much it's like really bad
I lose control
quickly but he looking smooth
no just got to keep on
Switching so I don't go overboard and
over overseer hey I got it all right
homie now the guys you took it are some
inappropriate individuals these are some
Terror cell war criminal enabling
the real deal
take out the boat with all the guys on
board bro you sure it's the right thing
to do my brother over it take
out the boat do what you want me to
return now you
bastard destroy what do you mean
destroy fire oh fire the minig guns okay
okay
okay I saw something on my map but I was
just going there man okay I have Rockets
nice nice that beautiful yacht I already
have killed so many people like tell me
beforehand and I would just kill
everybody on there and then we could
keep the yacht wouldn't that be like so
much more like winning warning missile
lock detected oh sorry what what does
that mean oh
oh
okay that is um not uh well
aimed uh yeah
by how do I aim it oh oh sh oh oh
how do I aim
this it only shoots
forward uh uh
uh okay I ain't dying in this thing oh
no
think oh oh oh oh
oh help me life
[Applause]
fun we almost added we almost had it
shut
up
Lou
Lou I was getting the hang of it yeah
I was tacking oh we're starting from
here wow
yo thank you user friendly as okay
let's sink let's try to
stay like
straight uh uh
okay oh God not the boats
War okay oh yeah
okay
okay H go up go up go up okay fine fine
fine fine fine fine
motherucker oh
oh
okay okay okay
okay I'm losing balance I'm losing
balance I'm losing balance I'm losing
balance okay
um
[Applause]
this Bro
intense is that not enough yet how much
do they want fireworks
[Music]
byebye okay
they got some nice guns too not going to
lie sheesh I'm so powerful oh oh
War uh yeah no I
missed out this
controls the one thing they didn't fix
in the
DLC
could this hit
nah okay okay okay okay how many how
many
oh
ah missile in the water why Miss in Miss
in
the
and
launching it kind of goes upwards huh
let me try to get closer we
maybe
here I did it just spammed it at this
point yeah
yeah
okay not so bad only took me three tries
and the first one was kind of something
else Titanic
moment a the poor
yach sincerely we would have made more I
think if we would have just taken it for
ourselves or sold it after killing
everybody while I was on board that
would have been easy I've done more
difficult things take out leing armed
dealers hey those little
bolies they're tiny though how am I
going to
hit
yeah all all quite balanced right
now
oh
n wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait how the am I going to do that
okay it's hitting the water that's uh a
good sign oh
God uh aim
aim oh God oh God uh
uh I don't know what the I'm doing
H okay
okay uh uh
no I got one by accident yeah it felt
like something
[Applause]
happened like with those tiny targets I
doubt I can really hit them with the the
big
missiles I think going with
the should work
right first
person how do I search the first person
[Music]
again yeah cuz the missiles are not uh
Target seeking right not that I've
noticed at least
B yeah the checkpoints are super
generous
okay but I feel like I feel like I lose
like sight of where I
[Music]
am no go back to O OG oh
God yeah cuz I'm already used to this I
I don't I won't know like how high am I
where am
I I am using control uh a keyboard I
mean
yeah is there another like the little
guns are on shift but like is there also
one that I don't have to use the mouse
for the
missile you want to kill me
too
oh oh almost
got
no not F it's definitely not
F why are theirs Target
uh
finding mine are
not they're just little tiny
boats I'll try one
more and one
more and a few
more got to get get
closer War what is it with this
what the
how uh
uh
oh ah
stop
this is the most most difficult
part for
[Music]
sure shut up shut up shut up shut up
shut up
sh I was so close how did it still did
it hit him at all I wonder
[Music]
it's difficult to balance
difficult to balance the altitude
and the direction and
everything
oh I didn't realize I was so close to
the
water and another
one you can just lean the stick slightly
I want to make it with the keyboard I
don't want to switch
now where's my
R there it
is I'll try a few more times like
Dan
[Music]
okay
focus
ah that was
close
I don't
know go go go go go go go go
go
hell I can't spam the Rockets cuz my
hand has to switch over to the mouse
unless there's another button for the
rockets that I don't know about then I
could stay on the keyboard but now I
have both hands on the I have to have
both hands on the
keyboard I don't know
ah
oh okay okay
[Music]
okay all right all right all right all
right all
right where's my where's my
controller my man hey YF the chopper
took a little damage you ain't going to
be able to give it to your dad this is a
shame at least Papa cannot be
disappointed about the gift he knows
nothing about see you later that's
actually really
nice of him body would be really mad
oh
um I don't know if it will like
immediately recognize
it I rarely rarely use my
controller
[Music]
um okay got a PlayStation controller
right
here how do I
know that it's
recognized
[Music]
oh how do I ah ah
okay um
I don't know if it's like I don't think
it's
already it's a red light right
now it's red light nothing reacts either
[Music]
like not working
not working uh not
automatically what do I
do can I like close the game and restart
[Music]
here I might reset the checkpoint
maybe uh do I have another
one I know I'd like to go with this one
but it's not
reacting I I I got it connected directly
with the cable to the
PC h
oof oof oof oof oof oof oof oof
oof wait let me try the the other one uh
the other one the other one the other
[Music]
one a
try because this one's just razor I
think sometimes it doesn't work let me
try the real PlayStation
controller I think that usually works oh
but this one's a different
[Music]
cable
need
uh what's
this what's this what's this what I need
I just need the uh USB C
cable
found one not really meant not really
meant for this purpose
but maybe it will do the
[Music]
trick oh
ah it stole my
audio that's what happens with the
PlayStation controller oh but it's real
reacting it's reacting but it took my
audio one
second you little
you shitty little controller
uh okay it's back it's back it's back
audio
feve okay you guys got to help me though
uh sniper aim right
[Music]
stick I know I think I I flew once with
a controller in
oh in GTA 5 at
least what's back M it says A and B here
but I have a PlayStation controller it's
back Circle right yeah I think so and
then R to stay what's R R1 you mean or
the controll the right
control the right joystick
think
uh don't okay no triangle triangle is
band we'll just we'll just figure how do
I how do I stay up how do I uh uh how do
I how do I okay uh wait how do I how do
I how do I how do I how how do I how do
I how
do R2 R2 R2 to go
up okay okay okay okay ah okay yeah okay
okay easy easy easy easy easy easy and
how do I
shoot oh it ain't me going
now oh wow wow what a difference why is
my thingy my camera
dead don't worry guys I'm still
here okay this seems much
easier
I feel also much
faster but still I
wonder how far can we even go is there
like a cut off
point what a
boat okay
[Music]
wow come on you little do
[Applause]
that am I too high
oh whoa whoa
[Applause]
whoa
yeah
how how
how h
no how did I not get any
shots okay something about me control uh
uh putting in the controller makes my my
me stop moving for some
reason I'll figure it out that was just
the first try Okay that was just the
first
try I was hoping on
the on the missiles first because I seem
to be able to get really close to them
but
man go go go go go go go go go go go go
go no no no it'll be fine it'll be fine
I'm just getting used to it okay give me
some
time
warning I ain't
got I I still have problems like staying
in oh the right direction okay but that
was
[Music]
one okay
low
[Music]
oh okay oh no he flew fire fire
fire turn turn how do I do how do I do
like a normal like staying in position
turn where is
he okay just
one
R1 oh okay back
here I'm the unlu
on now I just got to try to stay above
water I did it told you I could do it
just need you know a little bit of warm
up hey those guys ain't r no more Yousef
I'm going to trust you that there was
bad news of course you can trust me man
we're brothers now Blood
Brothers cats out there
cats just bring the C to myip my best
boy ahed is waiting for there okay cheer
upen don't think about it nothing can go
wrong now together The Zo will build D
species you thought didn't exist no more
Sabertooth doos and women in Gold
cages name there everything to be happy
about dreams Amigo dreams I got keep on
dreaming okay you keep on dreaming
hallucinating one might say I'll stay
realistic where is his helip
Pad saber to Doos
yeah I'll fix the camera and disconnect
the controller once I'm out of
here nice
nice oh is that it
uh there's definitely a helip pad there
oh yeah that's that's it oh Landing H uh
uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh wait wait wait wait
uh okay
ah okay okay got it got it is that it is
that it okay okay
y you must be L smooth as butter up here
tell me about it bro you're a m right
useless board that crazy
some serious military great he
could have had all the gold in the world
but he's obsessed with what they want s
h i see he wants what he can't
have typical human
behavior
all right how how is my rating the time
is within the time okay what do you mean
boats destroyed for you how could I have
done
more should I have destroyed boats that
weren't part of that crew would you have
been
happy you did well
yeah honestly could have probably done
it like this uh in the finale of GTA
but just out of
spite I say
no cuz game can't force me to switch
away from my
keyboard after all the they put me
through you
know without checkpoints anywhere
anywhere really unbelievably
not very
nice maybe we'll do like maybe we'll do
like one more Mission then I'll read
some super
chats I don't
know my throat is feeling a little bit
tired but I just threw in a cough drop
so maybe it'll get
better yeah the fin the finale like they
don't have to have as many checkpoints
as this Mission just
now not asking for that bad but just uh
like one more please one just
one that's all I'm asking
for one checkpoint
Mani daxi I thank you my
man yeah this is balad of Gay Tony why
do I keep on stopping let me disconnect
the oh
show take me to lower e take me home
here we are thank you bro very
much why is my camera so broken
now stop freezing it's not that
cold yeah I yeated all the cables now no
more PlayStation
controller no more of that
nonsense
oh wait I know the song that's not
good but whatever I don't care I don't
care today
that's a real song
right he's
vibing she's a
man what's your problem man where's Tony
where's Tony where's Tony what's wrong
with hi Evan you're looking cut hi Evan
like a drink hi Evan if I wasn't
straight I'd ravage you right now Evan
where's ston you send me them here who
cares about Tony the man that's
what back on drugs what one would say he
refuses to get any work done and PS the
man's a wreck then break up with him for
the last time and off out of all of
our Lives please wow somebody's got his
sister's underwear on by
mistake EV
look steroid junky you a particular
okay I'm just going to admit
that now would you shut the up
before I shut you up now where's Tony
he's in the
bedroom okay why did he make that sign
with his hands oh is he out on drugs hey
Tony get up yeah piss off come on get up
man let's
go piss off I want to die okay man if
that's how you want it come
on water boarding let's go better great
come on
this way this he's stripping so much
he's like a
raincloud you said we had something to
take care of I I should have let
your parole officer put you back in
prison all those years ago you're a
degenerate what about me you guys can't
just leave me here I look so cute though
point oh off Evan I'm starting the
app be gone before there I am let's go
once again I'm froze
myself I'm
good you
hero oh wait wait wait wait what I
forgot something forgot what the the the
explosives explosives explosives no
what's wrong with you man you want a
nightclub not a teror Rocko's gone nuts
he's going to burn the clubs down for
insurance he's going to kill us
yeah he's gone crazy and you're running
around with some bombs okay what kind of
drugs do you want I hope they strong I
told him i' take care of his Union
problems for him no un yeah are that or
they kill me I wish you'd talk to me
about this first man okay blowing
up ain't exactly your side of the
business okay it's not your Forte what
do you care about the business you got
your head your head in the
clouds huh you think you're a big shot
you're a nothing and soon you're going
to be a dead nothing yeah no doubt boss
now where you going think I got guy to
get up Frankfurt Avenue for Liberty
electric okay what else the the the
transport workers guy is uh driving an
OU of service subway train through North
Holland I me to take the whole thing out
a subway train Jesus Christ please tell
me that's it the head of the LTA is out
of Fran International and it's priv a
jet hey you'll probably blow yourself up
as soon as you walk out the door you
ain't doing this I got to it's the only
way you can survive get out of my way
sorry as much as I'd like to right now
I'm not letting you kill yourself I
stopped moving again maybe it's a
sign okay but I look so
cute we knocked him out dony you're
a little piece of work you know
that
a decent wage of
kisses yes you do deserve a decent wage
of
kisses why the do I stop
moving the app must be
like updating or something what the
hell I can't yawn let me
yawn Justice for w was yawn let me yawn
why my body reject the yawns when I
really need to
yawn nice same color we color twinsies
cute oh hi I'm moving how long how long
until the
FBI will take me down
again ah now I got a nice comfortable
on that goes through through my veins
and my
[Music]
lungs all I need armor I probably
shouldn't do whatever we're doing
without armor
right yeah always the
armor don't forget the
armor when does Kiana get the tongue
update yo not that I really want that
tongue but you are asking the real
questions my man o nice
color yeah seems like turns out everyone
in Japanese Branch gets everything first
uh originally the plan was different
from what I've been told but seems like
plans have
changed but they're almost done they're
almost through so it's only a matter of
time till we get it I'm going did to I'm
that's for 3D you mean right that's
different cuz she like she used a wish
for
it mhm well then must be soon uhuh uhh
this place is going SC soon you
know I'm with you man the order makes
absolutely no sense but maybe maybe myth
maybe we'll get it
[Music]
sometime they said it was a gift what do
you mean it was a but what's going on
you mean the
3D the 3D Expressions were a gift to
her well then I'll ask for the gift as
[Music]
well there a prototype so it was free uh
okay sorry there's just certain things
that are not going according to
[Music]
plans just very very
confusing I'm not moving
again
H oh hi cat which cat that's chunky
wonky stretching her stuff strting her
stuff on my on my
carpet and expect other members to use
it soon uh soon uh I I haven't heard of
anything maybe in 2 years
yeah if it's about like Fred D uh
facial
[Music]
expressions it's about 3D right not 2D
cuz I was talking about 2D
[Music]
originally I used to be told that uh dad
has to be a wish as
well one of the 1 million or two million
wishes I don't know how that's
equivalent to a 3D outfit but you
know uh what are we doing here um I
guess I'll check
again what am I doing here do I climb up
here or what
what I'm on the mark ah stick bomb
sticky bomb right they were talking
about sticky bomb hey do I have to put
it up high or can it just be down
there oh wait am I controlling
this or does it go off on its
own on the base is this
enough wasn't enough but nobody suspects
me let me go out again but nobody's is
even concerned about what I just did
nobody cares on the base like is this
the base or this the base is this
okay oh hi
dude the crane is rigged to blow get
clear all right wait let me get into my
car first must have been the wind all
right let's
go
hey I feel kind of bad was that really
necessary did we really have to do that
holy out the way a lot of
collateral damage oh
no next Target is on and out of service
subway train intercepted at what
whatever okay
placing Bombs all around New York
City we're
letting ourselves
be the servant once again to do all the
work that we don't really want to
do you
man feel like in GTA 5 we had everything
better in
control
although I guess Nico also was more like
his own man than someone else's in the
DLCs were
like someone else's man oh I stopped
moving again I'm going to give up or we
could switch up but then I won't have
the um cute shotgun
anymore
Nico was also passed around yeah I mean
yeah look at that mint color
cute look what that looks like a lizard
that car literally look like looks like
a lizard I got something for
you oh a train
already wa wait wait
wait I
made
yo
that was on the last like little bit of
the
train so go next plane is taking up
5:30
okay I don't know if I can get that
there that fast do I have
to
I'm I'll try I'll try perfect aim that
was so
lucky that was my lucky
strike my lucky
[Music]
strike
one in a million m luy strike oh hey
there's an ad for the anime we watched
princess Rob with
bubblegum honestly the absurdness of
that that's pretty close to some really
absurd anime out
there there are some pretty absurd crazy
insane animes yeah
I I remember
one uh I don't even know how to describe
it I think it's pretty well known
but I don't I don't even remember it
well enough to describe
it the uh do something I think she was
called something
Chan
uh killed everything I think yeah toan
yeah
I want to delete that from my memory
please W I'm surprised you guys know
it
oh it's very famous but really old too
Zoomers wouldn't know
it Zoomers would not know it
oh yeah Bales asked
me something speaking of tum much but I
don't know maybe I should keep it a
secret cuz maybe it's like a secret
maybe she wants it to be a secret let me
keep it a secret then for
now you'll find
out
eventually speaking of tumors
yeah okay we have arrived at the airport
the airport though kind of
dangerous I have to put it on an
airplane but will they even let me
in Must Destroy the plane before it
takes off um this is not the kind of
place I can just enter normally
right do I should I drive in it into the
airport can I I can throw it out of the
car right yeah oh oh okay they didn't
care this one
not this one right but you'll get one
too oh well never mind
aim car it's leaving in 20 minutes but
that's in I don't know how long that is
in
in in oh yeah
by 3 minutes already
passed yeah
[Music]
where is it leading
me oh there's no way there's no
way but maybe it will leave slowly like
it can't take off that quickly
right sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh turn
back I
up I up
okay it's starting hopefully just
starting to
leave which one
uh this
one is it on he ain't taking off
today oh yeah but since he said that I
suppose it's on
right okay okay ah you got the thank God
that was a close
call but he didn't even look like he was
about to
move all
right let's get out of
here
four
four uh to that's a problem
D
um
four was that inevitable oh wait hey the
circle is there but it's not going to be
that
[Music]
easy
let me get this way Circle
bigger
[Music]
ah no what the hell is of all these
taxis my god really realistic I
guess
oh my circle's small two stars now oh
because oh yeah just because I'm in the
airport
right it's always like worst in the
right
just what are you
doing a
come I'm on I'm on fire I'm on
fire
hey no let me go let me go let me go let
me go let me go let me
go he stop I'm already
[Laughter]
dead no the police will have taken me
right if I
redo is it before I place all
the guns uh
bombs oh
up can't
wa a airport okay
9:15 all right
airport okay we're doing airport again
but my no no non uh weapons weapon nista
only have this did they take everything
else should I
reload
they I will not let them take all
my stuff
no no damn it D it 11
[Music]
okay
H what do you
mean ah God damn it
Mama you say I had
it I thought when you get taken by the
police you lose
everything oh but I was in front of the
police
station what's the look at these
guys
look at
them they're models they're they're all
the
same those over there were the same he's
same he's also the same Kat in
city that's a different
one but he looked
freaky so do I have to place all the
bombs again I'm
sorry I'm not feeling that right
now nah I don't feel that we'll do it
again next
time oh I don't feel
it I was going to end it
anyway y y
y maybe I'll do this part before next
stream let me switch
apps see if the other one lets me
move
uh fun time today
though got pretty far I would
say
uh even though I was messing
around
[Music]
yeah Tony seems quite fun yeah I like
um
okay I have switched into different
clothes oh small small small small small
small small
small where do we go up ah
so I happens
sometimes I lose control over
myself heated
myself where we go where do we
go I mean you know the shrine fits this
outfit but it's winter in my
Shrine so it doesn't really suit um
where could I go
[Music]
maybe
here yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah like last time where I said this is
the Yukata not kimono which is a lie
this Kim
this winter to me I I I tell you what
season it is and I
say it is summer for
now
H
H because I'm keeping the summer alive
with my new
swimsuit
yeah the turquoise one that I was
wearing it's not really new cuz I was
wearing it all time since I got the
outfit
Mizuki
Mizuki Mizuki
mukii
mizi so I actually um while
I'm while I'm
thinking of it yeah mind
oh uhhuh
so we finished the anniversary super
chats let's see what was right
after and we need some bgm but oh my god
oh I'm still like
so
fascinated delighted
by not hearing anything it makes me so
happy
oh oh my
god wow
[Music]
fascinating you hear your own oh man
that sucks thankfully I don't have that
but seems very rough to have
that oopsie uh
yeah at least we don't hear the that's
exactly what I'm talking about
yeah thank you for the stream thank you
I hope you enjoyed it yeah the guy
T and
now what was it after anniversary ah the
the collab the family field I'm sorry
guys that that one was kind of a little
bit scuffed here and there oh it was so
stressful it was so stressful uh to
control everything cuz I was I was
controlling the sound effects I was
trying to switch bgm each time but then
I was so difficult too because ah the
repeating and this and that and oh my
God and then switching to the uh to
updating the points and then
also uh updating the questions and
updating uh like the answers and
updating the the alarm I doing so many
things at
once
yeah
[Music]
mhm I was I
was just trying to make it interesting I
think it can be
improved to
eventually be used again as a
concept but yeah
anyway you know for our thumbnails for
all these collabs I
actually um I sent in our myth group
chat I sent like like 15 different
really good
myth uh full member fan arts that I have
collected over the months and over the
past year I was like hey you guys just
in case you need some thumbnail material
how about this and this and this and
this and I sent them all and they were
like oh my God thank you so much you got
all the good stuff I'm like yeah yeah
yeah yeah the collab ones I collect some
of them uh for like future purposes I
was like uh we might need this in the
future and hey we did cuz we needed five
different fan
arts yeah my folder comes in handy and
even save to them all of course with the
credit in the name in the file name
mhm the unusual quality of the funless
yeah I dug out all all my good myth
group fan arts dug them out out of my
own
archive this one was perfect for me
because I was like in the position to
take a selfie in this picture so it's
made for me I'm I really like the one
that Amma
used I think it just it just has and I
knew she would choose it I thought it
just had those am Vibes like looks like
something am would
choose
yeah the wow
archive uh let me put on some
music how about some
retro oh that's not as retro as I
thought it was going to
be that's fine though that's nice old
Pokemon city
bgm is what I named this one remember
this
one okay we're not really that many so
I'm not going to show the
window but here we
go second let me write it
down Super Chat super cat
reading tomorrow balers gate
apparently uh the na girls are not going
to stream at least that's what they said
last
time narissa are you watching are you
going to stream tomorrow the Baler
skate so it might just be me and kie
streaming oh hi Nisa no stream okay okay
send all the jail Birds to
me bring them to me no but I get it like
when I was when it was like 6:00 a.m.
for me last time for stream
start I was like oh I'm so glad I
don't have to stream cuz then I could
like you know it's just different when
you stream you really feel like you have
to be more entertaining and you have to
be focused on the chat as well and pay
attention to this and
that uh yeah and and be more active in
like voice chat in terms of talking
H this way it's a bit more
laidback laidback and just yeah better
if you're if you're so
tired ground Loop isolated yeah I heard
a lot of people were talking like
mentioning ground Loop isolators I don't
really I don't
really like know what it is I understand
what it helps for but I don't know what
it is really um but it doesn't seem like
I really need it at the moment
just be you and Cali yeah I think
[Music]
so yeah hanging up the
wires good enough apparently I I have to
fix myself
[Music]
again okay didn't see that you did not
see
that
no you did
[Music]
[Applause]
not thanks for the stream good night
byebye see you tomorrow maybe
maybe I can do a lot of the knoow of the
N you
cannot D Hood thank you dun for a pinky
oh rest your throat you say wow but I'm
just starting to
read a oh that's sweet
though thank you yada yada yada proud of
you thank you thank you oh wait that's
originally from from Evan zal though
[Music]
apparently this is original message for
future super
aha
ah Evan are you
here yeah yeah all these like super chat
deliveries for your third
parties
confusing you're the man like yeah Doug
hood is like the Robin Hood of
kfp okay not quite but
you know he's he's a
hero he's the he's the mar antonet of
kfp or I'm I'm the maranet of kfp really
but kfp super chat tensil
service wasn't she's not a villain
excuse me
it's hard to find the
right equivalent
okay what what what's your problem with
Maria tet she's she's slay okay she's a
queen everybody
dies everybody
[Music]
dies God damn it guys why why you got to
be like that why you got to take
everything apart with your beaks
eh
just just
[Music]
chillax May India tayor
and now you're coming here with the she
never said let them eat cake do you have
to ruin everything this is why we can't
have nice
things
man Flor John Danon Andy Joe Danon Sky
Danon king of waffles Danon
uh bottom thank you for the red super
chat but cake well SE said let them eat
NIS we she didn't go so what I won to
think she
[Music]
did thank you bottom for the worldless
red super chat and it's a triple oh baby
a triple holy
bottom
holy
why why won't you take the chance
to write something in that message I do
not
understand H why why are you okay like
I'm I want to like how can you donate so
much and then just leave it at that like
what we need to
talk thank you bottom you're not even
here now how how are my thank you words
ever going to reach
you thank
you thank you
soon thank you so much insane amount
of salary for me let's go let's go let's
go minus negative
[Music]
salary Mr empty block D kak brutal salad
than canny STS than voltage T random
collusion I had many collusions today
thank you for the pinky number one t
you're still on the board huh what was
that about I wasn't even participating
in the
game or are you calling me your number
one in general
H H what's this
about what is this
about are you just
being
flirty he you mean
collisions
collusion
wait what the is a collusion versus
a
[Music]
collision
cons I feel like I knew that
cuz I definitely heard it
before but it merged into one word in my
brain
oopsie okay I am separating it
again okay okay it's s separate again
okay no more no more confusion no more
misunderstanding should be different now
in my
brain hope it stays this way
but it's really too too similar like one
letter off U to I
Shish no longer shall these words
collude or Collide
exactly thank you random collusion for
also clearing up the confusion haha in
my brain about this
word even though you didn't even attempt
to do that g thanks for the pinky thanks
for the fun collab to celebrate myth's
thir year anniversary
cavia thank you for watching I'm I I I I
will take the praise but it wasn't so
good it could have been better I'll take
the the
fall
uh but you know I really wanted to
prepare something original I was
thinking of like games and this and that
but then again like games like game
games you know like uh computer games
for example are
just um not I don't know somehow these
kind of like game show type of games I
feel like they're better for
banter um and like talking in
between
yeah and you know you know I could have
pulled out like I don't know gartic
phone again but we did that with uh Ena
I knew that she was going to do like a
drawing inspire tied drawing style
stream so I didn't want to do GIC phone
um and yeah I don't know like what else
with five people there was wasn't much
choice that would have also fit in one
hour some other ideas um you know again
like uh the that Mario Party game that's
on PC that I played with
phon but I feel like for that I would
want a bit more than an
hour
could have done jackbox again but I feel
like we did jackbox so many times
already it's always fun but uh for once
I thought it's better if we don't do
jackbox Mario Kart is kind of boring for
such a special occasion you know it was
a special occasion so I thought we
needed something special and I was
thinking so hard about what to
do what could I
do it was still fun though thank thank
you and there may have been a lot of
complaints that the answers were too
biased there surely was some bias but
what do you expect what the but I
don't even think it was as much biased
as like everybody complained about just
going to say that because you
know you guys no need to feel bad about
it no I don't think it was that
biased like if it was really biased you
guys would have put me on Number One
Gamer I was just somewhere on the list
yeah but that doesn't I don't think
that's even that biased because I do
think like in terms of like it depends
on how you see the term
gamer cuz like I play a lot of different
kind of games on my channel and I play
long games you know like you you you can
see that as a qu quality as a trait of a
gamer you know so it's not weird not
completely weird for me to be up
there uh and then the other answers I
think weren't like that biased and takam
Modi even like generally it was biased
towards an i audience that is for sure
like the the couple questions for
example like generally a lot of the
questions just were member answers but I
told I said that in the beginning I
explained it was every time I would say
that like even before I explain a
question like just keep in mind ien fans
were pulled so mostly
yanish answers will be mentioned paab
Nashi was definitely biased I I I said
so myself on stream I said sorry this
last one is kind of
biased you guys couldn't hold back on
that
[Music]
one cuz that's not really a known ship
outside of you know the Pabon Nashi
fans the Kiwa and the way
fans I don't think I think yeah many
people were very surprised that that was
even a thing but we went to the males
and all that like it's kind of a thing
okay
okay it's kind of a thing
[Music]
yeah maybe it was a good way to let
people
know it was a good once in a lifetime
chance so let people know I'm a toi I'm
a to
do
uh yeah and exactly family food is not
food Feud is not about being correct and
people kept on like I thought it was
pretty well known even I knew what
Family Feud was about it's about not the
correct answer but what the majority
thinks and in this case the majority was
an Ian
audience that was mainly kfp but I told
you to not vote if you only watch me I
told you very severely and I think a lot
of you listened probably not everybody
but a lot of
[Music]
you yeah perception thing mhm but some
people just I I guess were upset that
what they thought was best wasn't on the
board well well
well then next time how about
participating in the
poll yeah the poll was a very last
minute
thing but you can change the result by
voting
so see even a lot of kfp didn't know
about it that's because it was really
last minute
yeah where was it Twitter no it wasn't
my pre- chat like I was discussing how
to do things in the pre- chat like
asking for
advice and then I figured it out and
then I was like I made a a Google form
with jma's
help and then I sent the the link into
the chat and then everybody just voted
and I cut it off after like a little bit
over 300
votes because I had to count it on my
own I didn't want it to be too many like
not counting it's not just counting it's
like genuinely looking at the
words and seeing if there's similar ones
Etc yeah
[Music]
someone even drummed up reinforcements
from a certain place before the for
who I did kind of tell you you could go
to other discords to tell them
quickly lunchbox where did lunchbox
go to the dead beats or
where
I don't think so I
mean don't they always say like we asked
100 people or so whatever 300 was plenty
it was just like a small joke game it's
not supposed to be that serious anyway
sometimes people take things way too
serious
anyway I don't think I should have cut
that I think that was
[Music]
fine oh Oh you mean like not the
question but the the actual yeah I
didn't know what to do because um I
don't
know it was very
like broad yeah the word animal was just
really broad but uh well
[Music]
well it is what it is um it was like the
top two answ so I thought I should keep
it
in I don't know why I got so many like
vague answers for that
question
animal what's a common vtuber theme
character Theme
animal it's so
vague that is so
vague but yeah you in generally when you
play Family Feud play as in like the
game the PlayStation game or so or
Ubisoft game you try to bring out vague
answers cuz usually the answers people
give are I feel like often quite vague
[Music]
really can't believe dog was not in the
top 10 because I don't even I wouldn't
say Doc either I don't think there are
that many okay now we have K and fuok
but outside of whole life I don't think
there's so many dogs dog
vtubers I don't I can't think of a
single dog vtuber outside of H
[Music]
life it's like foxes yeah Wolves
yeah no I barely know
anything surely there are maybe one or
[Music]
two but I can't think of any
anyway H where was I bottom did I give
no I wasn't there I was a
g Co sour Rex than cold tolin thank you
for the pinky happy F myth the the
reaper kulu's daughter a
megalon Mega more like small Odon a
phoenix and Bigfoot oh wait who's
Megalodon is like a big shark right how
is am a
Bigfoot
what huh or is or is g at the
Bigfoot is she
both it's a big shark right how is am a
Bigfoot because she's
elusive
nah what how what what part of her makes
her
Bigfoot never heard that example before
do your am reps huh am do seem like a
crypted you could see in the woods huh
no she
[Music]
doesn't what do you
guys
on Amma doesn't have big feet I saw them
remember when she sent me a a foot
selfie it wasn't really about the feet
but was about the
cables I think she she sent me a picture
like really early on about like some
cable management I know I think it was
about um like VR setup and her foot was
in
the in the in the
picture and I was like oh my God your
feet are so
[Music]
beautiful yeah did I talk about that on
a
panel nowhere
[Music]
else did you save that I don't think I
really have it anymore but I could
probably scroll scroll scroll through
the archive of our
conversations panel exclusive tangent
not exclusive anymore then ooh
[Music]
and I'm a team oh now my thing is here
it's not on my red side anymore got to
get used to it thank you Ma Chef
appreciate the cruise your name is too
long
okay done dny with the funny next is the
Nintendo Direct that's really short it's
only like a few just one pinky and a few
normal
ones
[Music]
um isn't that cute I wrote that with the
mouse because my pen wasn't
working my
Wacom pen so cute sometimes I don't
normally do simple
um uh uh thumbnails like this but
sometimes I think they're really
nice and eye catching
La sits La
sits smovie is here by the way exploring
the room that she has seen a million
times I thought you did it for
copyrighted well I mean yeah I can't use
the
logo I can't use a Nintendo Direct logo
so you know I had to like recreate it
but I wanted to draw it with my hand but
the pen wasn't working so I had to use
my mouse
I think it turned out quite nicely for
me using my
[Music]
mouse you heard the
meow I'm almost done baby
almost take a 47 hour t m a thanks for
the pinky I have to say I was not
expecting to get a watch long this time
since you were so busy yesterday so
thank you for the stream tento in a way
this is a looking to possible future
streams congrats on fre years s it's
been great having you here thank you
it's been great having
you yeah uh it was kind of spontaneous
because I heard the day before that it
was happening and I thought well
Nintendo Direct is
actually surprisingly always at a pretty
good time for me like I think 3 or 4:00
p.m. and it's comfortable and short and
I thought that there was going to be way
more excit exciting stuff but somehow
the previous Nintendo Direct was more
exciting yeah U but I think it was uh
fun nonetheless to just watch Nintendo
Direct together every every once in a
while I think it's
nice yeah I got I I don't know if I got
baited but I expected probably I'm
expecting it too early but I expected a
a new console announcement
[Music]
cuz people were hyping it up I thought
it was happening but I guess not they're
still like surely they're working on it
but they don't want to announce it yet
until last moment so that the Nintendo
switch still continues to sell well
right yeah so they're going to only
announce it when it's like really close
to the actual release
date
because they want the games that are now
still coming out in the ending
Spurt of the switch to sell well and
still get a bit more switch sales into
so yeah milking it yeah until the last
moment Christmas as well yeah so who
knows when it's coming
[Music]
but where is my T snowboarding what the
time to use
my my new insurance to sue them for
depriving me of 1080
[Music]
snowboarding how can it take so long
anyway it's an old
game the
I promise
he
promis man don't announce it so early
and get my hopes up if you're not going
to
[Music]
deliver oh where's my air today
guys where is
[Music]
it it's been more than a year since they
announced really has it been that
[Music]
long nah not that long right not a whole
year but definitely a long
time Beyond Good and Evil don't remind
me of Beyond Good and Evil cuz 1080
snowboarding is at least still
happening Beyond Good and Evil is not
ever happening and that's depressing as
f
Fu that's
like one of those games from my
childhood that I played the most and
enjoyed the
most so it would have meant so much to
me if there was a
sequel it would have been so hype
especially if it was during my whole
lifetime and I could stream it even more
[Music]
Ty never played the OG it's it was
really
good good GameCube
[Music]
game yeah they even have a
trailer well well
well oh no I didn't see a gameplay
preview yet I just saw like a screenshot
or so of uh the new Yakuza game game but
I'm excited cuz it's going to be out
early 2024 right February or
so wait wait wait wait why did I auto
correct Dragon's Dogma 2 into
Yakuza in my brain huh why is that the
same thing in my
[Music]
brain cuz the dragon
you I was thinking of
yeah
Yakuza uh I am so excited to play Yakuza
when it comes
out it's with Ichiban right I really
liked
Ichiban
so that is really hype looking forward
to
that and Kio wow All
Stars double
Trumble of course I'm going to play it
who doubted it why would you doubt it
oh well there's one aspect of it
that complicates it I don't know I
honestly don't
[Music]
know but probably can get around
it
I'll play it I want to play it I want to
play it I want to play it I want to play
it I want to play it I want to play it I
want to play
[Music]
it what do you mean M
can it will be fine I think so too oh
mik ire rea Ed to it ohuh oh was she
like watching the trailer on stream
[Music]
or the Harry Potter game is not new
anymore not not playing Harry Potter
[Music]
game
yeah
sorry guys that I was eating some of
potato chips
today I'm
sorry I know they crunching like I
wouldn't want to hear it I wouldn't want
to hear
it I'm so sorry I couldn't hold myself
back today I will work on my patience
and um discipline for the
future I deeply apologize
about my lack of
discipline on
this sad sad day of big
crunch it's my
fault I fully admit it's my fault for
giving into to the devil that is potato
chips even early
[Music]
on
was it potato chips or pum band it was
potato
chips they were
discounted they were minus
25%
[Music]
yeah they tasted even better because
they were
cheaper they were steel not stale they
wear steel not
[Music]
stale time for apology Twi it
longer yeah I mean I I'm I'm serious
though like I know I wouldn't want to
watch like hear somebody eating all the
time in a VOD or
stream
n so sorry but I really couldn't stop
myself like when you start you can't
stop you just can't
[Music]
stop at least at least I don't um like
what's it called schaten um you know
like
that it was just crunching but I I I
don't eat with my mouth open I don't
yeah smack and all
that that's really something I cannot
listen to
genuinely why am I talking about this I
just felt really
bad that I might have an issue with m
I watch Raina so I don't
care
[Laughter]
yeaha
[Music]
yeah I think Ena also smacks a little
bit it's okay it's okay you
know some
they don't have to change their their
[Music]
ways Lena and her
steak Yeah Lena does a lot of eating
streams but then you expect her to eat
right so that's
okay like her streams are literally
like meant to be eating streams but she
probably also eats when she's not doing
the eating
stream she's been on a steak
Quest man I need to C catch up with
[Music]
waya I I actually I I did write to her
recently for a reason um but not really
catching up with her like about random
stuff unfortunately she ordered a $40
steak and it was
mid uh I feel like generally if you
order something to deliver then it's
it's like chances are high that it's way
worse than if you ate it at the actual
restaurant so I would blame a lot of the
quality issues on
delivery like the fact that you don't
eat it at the
restaurant
mhm it gets cold and it's just I don't
know somehow less
enjoyable maybe they also don't I know
that's something I I wonder I would like
to know from restaurants if they make
something for delivery cook do they cook
it
differently than when they cook it for
the like people in the restaurant do
they make it uh like differently I
wonder right now this the trick is to
get it undercooked and cook it a bit at
home to heat it up oh I guess when it
comes to steaks you could do
[Music]
that good stretch feels good
man that is clever I'll go to Butcher
get it for a good price you mean an
uncooked steak I don't think
waya is going to do
that that sounds very unw
[Music]
like AST K
Sigma
Al and
P
M that's you oh my God
surprise all right
[Music]
uh no do you Super Chat Bowers gate
Babble
[Music]
gate I got to make another
thumbnail I'm keeping them like similar
though purposefully
wait what's going on
here
huh why is
there why is there what's with the
rainbows and pinkies in this one what
happened what
happened is it just because it was
[Music]
um ah for do you because of do you cuz
you couldn't Super Chat
there
oh Mak
[Music]
sense
okay crusty thanks for the pinky
congrats on the do you and
re-release wah I remember gushing over
the original MV and leaving a comment
because I loved how much your style of
music suits you but this proves to me
that you can that you actually can
improve on Perfection oh thank you wow
that's very nice of you oh spoofy is
like staring at me don't stare at me oh
oh I stared back and she came over here
um I even saw like I'm aside from uh you
know comments about oh Korean fits the
song I Saw messages that like my singing
is better in this version
too which I think is really just because
I sang the song already a million
times
so I'm just more used to
it I initiated petting time it seems so
she's like cuddling cuddling with my PC
right
now and also it's mixed by a different
person who certainly mixes they both mix
really well they both to
but you know it's a bit different um so
I don't
know
what what you
want come
here stop cuddling with my
cables come here stop just walking
behind my all my
[Music]
cables be
careful hey
hey oh yeah rubbing her face again
against everything
[Music]
hey come here come here come here why
does she go the exact opposite direction
of where I'm trying to lead her to
oh now she's getting closer and snap oh
I got her I CAU her oh what a rebel oh I
got her hi say hello say hello you don't
want to say hello okay that's fine but
you so
soft wow w
wow
wow anyway I hope uh my Korean views are
especially enjoying the do you Korean
version but if you guys can enjoy it too
that will will make me very happy as
well and I tried really hard to make the
lyrics
Sound uh like smooth and make them flow
well and pronounce them correctly um I
wonder how
how how good it sounds to a Korean
person I maybe I'll try singing it live
now at the
end I don't wouldn't mind singing
it took me a while to you know get
everything
down to a non-current person sound
influent
[Music]
natural
ah in in Japanese there's this word
called oi I wonder what it is in Korean
wait let me try to look it
[Music]
up
somehow it translates into like a
freiner like what the is
this what what the is this actually
no there's a just
OB no wait
what
is I think
AUM
AUM I don't know what the hell this
means that they just translated to
me what
[Music]
but younger generation D don't use oh
okay reach yeah let me see what is this
sometimes translators go a little bit
sentient and they
say crazy
things oh it was just giving like five
different ways of Translating that
word but in English it gets translated
as sloppy words flirtatious words
flirtatious words flirtatious words
flirtatious greetings three times flous
words but that's not really how I would
describe that word oi is like something
you say like a compliment even though
you don't mean
it like sucking up to no not even that
no just like a compliment that you don't
really
mean now flattery lip
[Music]
service or as they say sloppy words
flirtatious words flirtatious words
flous words Lous
greetings wait can we oh my God we can
be so
insan sloppy words flous words flous
words flous words flous
greetings wow I feel so and sink man she
loves me she loves
me I feel
love
my new audio stock lady
beloved TTS loves
me
[Laughter]
wait oh
[Music]
wait
[Laughter]
Kiara I love you she's very beautiful
and has a good personality I yearn for
you every day oh thank you oh my God
you're so sweet you don't have to say
that link oh my
God it's getting a little bit hot in
[Music]
here
it's true no
stop I mean I mean yeah I might be true
but I don't even know you that
well let's get to know each other better
oh okay yeah let's start small okay
let's start step by step from the
beginning
you know I we can't I you you're a TTS I
don't even know how to handle that you
know it's my first like I I never I
never got close to someone like you
before so we should go slowly and and
hopefully we can we can get to know each
other better like we could finish each
other's sandwiches for
example
I'll make you a
sandwich
really you'll make me a sandwich that is
so so sweet and kind of you to take care
of me like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow H would you also make some food for
my cats and take care of them when I
want to continue sleeping instead you
get up and make them
food I have no body but I will do my
best to help you so considerate
TTS maybe I should be your body maybe I
can give you my body
and we be we become
one wouldn't that be
wonderful yes let's
unite
unite let's combine okay let's combine
let's combine
I actually wrote g g it's like what they
say when they
combine the
meas
got all right see you later
TTS
ch
CH p p doesn't translate so well into
English sizzling why Sizzle what's
sizzling okay okay okay back to work
back to work sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry
spicy spicy
wow oh that's
satisfied thank you hum thank you for
two pinkies ending my birthday weekend
with a bang of Korean version of do you
it felt like a new song somehow and I
love it fantastic job happy anniversary
to you and do you sorry for theate
greeing I had to make sure I got your
limited Merch this time
oh
huh oh H what do you mean like was it
during this time that it came out
at this like hour thank you for three
years of charming my heart each day for
inspiring me to dream for me again
inspiring me to dream for me again and
fulfilling my life with precious
memories that I'll treasure daily I'm
proud to call you here he comes my Kami
oi and I'll continue to support and love
you wa thank you wow
ah oh I am I am flattered oh you were on
a budget ah you mean you had to do one
thing first and then the
other that is understandable always got
to have priorities it shows that you are
very mature to put these things in
order yeah thank you so much for the
support for listening to you know do you
my music once again glad you could enjoy
it as if it was a new song Happy bla
birthday for
sure Happ happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
pants to happy birthday
you
congratulations thank you for everything
I hope you stay as wonderful as you
are and can live your life to the
fullest while enjoying the wow every
day and I hope you'll enjoy the
merchandise when it arrives uh when is
the is the merch still it should yeah
wait anniversary merch definitely still
[Music]
selling we need we need pictures yo we
need
pictures I hope we can get pictures
before the sales are over and the CD
when is the when is this can you guys
tell me when does the CD start stop to
cell I want to put it in my
calendar you know October 2nd ooh okay
just so that I put out another
reminder Remind CD sales there we
go okay okay okay okay
6 p.m. jst
okay the thing
is I'm a bit busy during that time I
don't think I can do a cut out or
anything for that no
[Music]
no I'll just do a little bit of
promotion it's it's going to be
[Music]
fine I had jenma tell me uh about like
the streaming numbers and sales numbers
Etc but I can't really tell if that
was comparatively a good
amount she told me but I don't know if
it's a good
amount
H oh yeah yeah yeah in order to promote
it I could also just put out another one
of the
videos uh actually let me tell
I don't think they're working on the
next one
yet the first one's finished
though where where where is the Fred
where is the Fred
[Music]
ah wait when am I putting out the love
rush though that's going to be a little
bit close
actually when was
I love rush love love Rush ah o that's
kind of close that's not really
according to my
[Music]
plan eh I don't want to compare myself
to CI no thank
you that calls for depression
Arc
[Music]
H let's do
this hey I don't know but I don't tell
I'll tell him to work on tgw
anyway yeah it's okay it's
okay I'll just ask the music department
what they think although if it's a
negative answer then I don't want to
hear
it oh that's
[Music]
depressing where was I I yeah thank you
to get a kiss as well because it was two
pinkies so yeah hey hope you had a great
birthday hope you celebrate it yourself
you deserve
it
yeah but I was going to put out love
rush like on
Tuesday
and then putting out the next one like
so soon after that's like under a week
after if I upload it on October 1st or
2nd then it's kind of too close to each
other so either I I wait with love Rush
a little bit longer or and then put them
out on like first or
second I don't know yeah I don't want to
put the it has to be at least two weeks
apart for me in my
[Music]
opinion and love ver is finished tgw
hasn't even begun
apparently the artwork is done but I
don't think I don't think she started
working on the
[Music]
MV anyway anyway yeah I want each one of
them to have some time to to spread out
its
wings I I don't expect many views for
those mvs at
all uh so anything is fine but if they
could all eventually
gain like a little bit like 300 400 500k
then I would be happy
[Music]
already no stress
though in the end they're just there to
REM remind people of the album some who
missed out on
[Music]
it
retrospective yeah
hopefully yeah this way I think tgw and
retrospective can reach even more
people and they might really dig it cuz
putting things up on YouTube is just
giving people so much of an easier way
of accessing these
things
so yeah I think many people who missed
out on it might try listening to it
through
that uh Jacob 47 I thank you D and green
Wilder a
rainbow happy anniversary I know I'm
late but as usual most of you streams
are while I'm working my other job mhm
the videos you recorded for the
anniversary stream were amazing I was
especially a fan of the paragliding one
if you manage to handle that you might
actually be able to handle skydiving no
that's way more scary from my experience
skydiving was surprisingly less scary
than I expected because when you're more
than 3,000 ft above the ground your
brain is trouble really acknowledging
how high up you
are I don't know about that e but does
that mean you tried it
so I
don't
no looking at the ground so far below
almost just looked like it was a picture
rather than a distance I could fall and
get hurt from I understand that it may
not look like much anymore but my brain
would still know I'm in a
helicopter uh no so scary like what if I
but I mean wait I would I would be
flying with someone else strapped to me
again right then I don't have to be in
charge of pulling the the shoot right
that at least makes it a lot better in
my brain um as long as I'm strapped to
someone yeah but
yeah and then they'll probably push me
out of the helicopter even if I'm not
ready yet
cuz they can just push me out
no
no on the flip side bungee jumping oh
this person has tried it all bunge
jumping was genuinely terrifying the
first time because it was only 90 ft up
and I could tell by looking that I would
fall that distance in just a couple
seconds
yeah wait so you have tried those two
things but you haven't done paragliding
green Wilder that's is that what I'm
understanding then you should try
paragliding next go go go go go you in
Canada right I'm sure you have beautiful
views there aside from that point of
view it's fantastic actually I like how
point of view fits into the POV of what
we just talked
about POV of How High you're up and how
terrifying it is I've listened to the
album many times now and my favorite new
song is retrospective I don't get all
the talk about it being emo though I
don't usually read into to song lyrics
very much I just like the beeps and the
boops even from the first time I love
the sound thank you I also don't really
register lyrics much when I first hear
songs even after the 20th listen I might
still not really register the
lyrics yeah um but you know I think a
lot of people just uh because you guys
knew that it was something from my own
feelings you guys wanted to analy it and
thus you connected with it because you
just chose to understand the meaning of
the
song cuz I even introduced it to you
guys when I sung
it yeah yeah yeah yeah anyway green
Wilder that's actually insane that you
made all these experiences you seem like
a very
action what's the word action seeking
kind kind of person wow wow wow wow you
are maybe not green Wilder but the green
Wilder after
[Music]
all what even what even is Wilder is
that even a word you you must be green
Wilder fril Seeker adrenaline
junkie a wild one you are
sheesh well you go go paragliding and
then report back to
me thank you so much for the insane
support I don't think I want to try any
of
that
anytime
ever
but I mean never say no right but I
don't I don't see it in my future at the
moment no thank you for now for now for
now for now that's just feels crazy I
know I can
totally agree with it being safe like
I'm sure it's
safe but
still I
nah no I am a
chicken you know
that don't you use this against me or I
will cook
you into a
soup or I'll throw you into my chicken
Shredder mhm make you into
nuggets be
careful yes
ma'am thank you green Wilder mwah MW
mwah
mahke our Sav than for the red
oo thank you k for the amazing birthday
present today with the Korean version of
do you oh you're welcome it is my fourth
favorite in the album with fite being
number one and I hope another variation
of it is released in the future yeah I
mean I've done like anniversary things
every now and then um you know with h
toi and now do you uh don't see it as a
must thing that I do
but it's it's more about like whether or
not I I remember it and for he know it
was special because it was my first song
so I definitely wanted to do something
for hinotori and for do you I felt like
it was meant to
be to turn it into a Korean
version um right now I don't really have
the urge to
do anything
else but we'll see how I feel maybe next
year I'll pick up something that I want
to do with one of my
songs
maybe fite Japanese
version I could I could see that that
because that way it will like we could
do fever Knight City pop or something
like that in
Japanese I don't
[Music]
know
baby
I
[Music]
night give me that give me that
thing yeah I could do that even on my
own
yeah thank you our saves I'm I'm glad
that the you know the OG Classics are
still your favorites you know like doo
and fever night but that was your fourth
and your first I wonder what's in
between but thank you for listening to
my music so much I'm really glad that
you like it that much thank you thank
you it means a lot to
[Music]
me spank andhe another red one thank
you I I don't mean like ever for this
stream but just generally you sent so
many thank you ready for more chaos with
you and the Gang thanks for recommending
I follow pepo currently
out oh you're also checking up on Pepito
now are you me too me too it's always
nice to see updates about B maybe you
should give me updates to spanking time
about your CLE does your C CLE go out
your
C mine don't go out so I could not
update about
that
never I think it's
safer I like even when you live on the
countryside you hear about cats that
just don't come back at some point
because maybe something happened with
them maybe they did go out to one of the
few streets and then got driven over and
so on like it's so
scary it's so
scary no my cats don't go onto the
balcony
anymore I haven't let them out in a
while and when I do I I like hold
them or stay really really really
stalkerish close to
them yeah other animals that attack them
and so on yeah it's just scary I want to
give them the freedom because I don't
want them to be like stuck
within a certain amount of walls forever
for their whole life without seeing
anything um what what I think is good as
to give them like a
garden
right hopefully a big
Garden or just move a
lot move move houses Apartments a
lot I feel like my cats have already
seen a lot of different environments
honestly
they get something new to see every once
in a
while yeah yeah they don't get
[Music]
bored yeah they've moved a few
times yeah quite a
few even a house is enough they have
lots of place to run around yeah and I'm
sure sure they're fine with that but
then you know I really feel bad if if if
all they see for their whole life is
just most of their life it's just one
one environment I I hope they
can I hope I hope for all the cat out
owners out there they can show their
cats a little bit more of the world
somehow somehow
somewhere train them on the leash no my
smoothie refuses it
entirely it's so hard to get her on the
leash in the first place she already
knows what I'm doing after I did it once
and just it's just
impossible I didn't try on chunky wonky
yet though maybe she would accept it I
wonder yeah maybe next step for me is
buying a cat
stroller after the leash was rejected I
try cat stroller which looks also
[Laughter]
Crazy Cat backpack yeah
yeah I've seen cats rolls around
really the one like cat Instagram that I
follow she uh has used cats and her cats
looked really happy in it
so annoying to set up and stuff I think
at least like it's easier to put them in
there you just pick them up put them in
but you probably also have to leash them
if you put them in the so that they
don't just jump
out well well well well we'll bring the
cats around World Around the World
Around the World Around the World oh you
know one thing that I don't like about
the roadcast the new mixer that I have
is I can't do two effects for example at
the same time I used to be able with the
goar to do like megaphone and Reverb for
example or like Reverb and like change
my pitch Etc it doesn't seem to be a
thing yeah like it switches between I
can't do both that's really lame
honestly
H and
the old one the G lar just had more
variety of effect
[Music]
so I don't like it to be honest I don't
like
it I don't like
it but it seemed to
be kind of the best option besides gor's
alarm I looked at a lot of like reviews
of
Replacements I mean I could I maybe I'll
ask them if if it's somehow
possible or if they could add the
feature maybe it's possible and I don't
know about it but so far it doesn't look
[Music]
possible you like the way I sound well I
did play around a lot with the
um
the the settings of the you know BL blah
blue EQ and all that yeah I don't know
what I'm doing I was mostly playing
around with it to try to filter out the
buzzing so I just tried any setting that
reduced the
buzzing
white
Wawa white um white white white white
white why why white Wawa is with you
right here she loves you very much and
she misses you with all her heart choo
choo P
pill she's just stuck in the prison not
allowed to get out of of the usual room
yeah and SP I'm the G cretion Rowan come
for the pinky dear kada tomorrow is my
first birthday since I became kfp oh I'm
so happy and glad to meet you and become
kfp always thank you for everything oh I
saw Korean version of do thank you so
[Music]
much h
h n n
AO
noo a no it
[Music]
a okay
hey
hey thank you so much I'm glad you like
Korean version of doy you it's thanks to
the fans who created a Korean
[Music]
version
yeah I will try to sing it
afterwards my my throat hurts but I want
to sing it anyway also I you know you
use your throat differently when you
sing compared to when you talk they
say we'll see how that goes Nathan coton
thank you for the pinky oh wait actually
wait Rowan Rowan I didn't say happy
birthday thank
you s
you
[Music]
happy birthday now it's already too late
but you know better late than
never hopefully we can spend more
birthdays
[Music]
together that's that's that that was
it I
think right
yeah
hey I need to remember my Korean
vocabulary and all
that I feel so bad I feel so bad I'm
losing everything I'm losing my
marbles I'm losing
it h
[Music]
na C than on the pinky Ki is my col a
fiery Fury woman and the objectively
best choice of the
bunch
hey stop you really flatter me every
time stop it
now you cannot flatter me like that
no what am I supposed to do it's too
smooth thank you thank you I hate the
word fury though cuz I want to read it
as fiery especially cuz it's kind of the
same
meaning but it's not supposed to be said
like that
apparently I hate that word it froze me
off each
time e it's wait how do you say it
wait yeah yeah wait that's the thing
that's the thing you I it confuses me
see it's it confused me again like
apparently it is fiery uh but it looks
like Fury I don't know it froze me
off I hate it the Casual command d
d spam D ja D and
D let's get rid of
that
and
uh
where's my I made my own version of the
do You
lyrics where's my where's my where's my
Korean where's my Korean do where's my
Korean do I think I made
a a
Google Google
dock uh is that my draw yeah I want to
sing it
now
copy of there it is copy of do you kiaha
transcribed
[Music]
version yeah the dog is different from
what I
made and then I think Johnny sent me a
version of the Korean
version for do you Korean HH
what what did I just say I think Johnny
sent me a cut out okay version for the
Coran
version or did
he ah yes he did I think did he no no he
didn't he sent me an a capella version
you know like the the other one is going
to sound good too do you want to listen
to
it guess I got to use the OG
car should we listen to it
yes it's
opposite yeah let me put that in here
and then do
you do
[Music]
you
uh
[Music]
my Cara
version um
no uh do do where the freak
[Music]
here last time we heard a capella
version of one of my
songs made by my team it sounded really
cool let's hear
[Music]
this
girl you know it I just can't resist
you
[Music]
that's just what we do love hate all the
same if you know play that
game all the
[Music]
you do you
do don't ever fall you got
it just can't
[Music]
resist that's just what we do love hate
all the same if you know play that
game all the same if you know play that
game it right
now do you do you say you
[Music]
feel I'm always coming back to
[Applause]
[Music]
you you you feel the game we play Love
hat
[Music]
betray wow that's actually the first
time
oh the first time I listen to it too
wow wow it's so
[Music]
pretty man it really makes you believe
that I'm a good singer
so pretty yeah if
I what am I say oh yeah I would have
love to put the Korean version onto the
album if I would have really like you
know if I had it earlier like it was
kind of like a oh I can take my time
because the anniversary of do you isn't
until so it wasn't included if I I
didn't think of it if somebody would
have you know reminded me hey you could
put the Korean version on there too then
I would have done it but
yeah like maybe as a CD extra as well
together with the Sparks remix I think
it would have been a nice extra for the
CD
version oh well it's okay it's okay it's
okay it's okay no
need okay let's
sing
ah before I go I didn't read all super
chats but plenty so
before I
go let's sing let's try to sing I
haven't seen the lyrics in a while maybe
I'll stumble over the words
[Laughter]
again
version do
you
[Music]
oh
yeah playing
is this okay sorry I was checking the
audio volume should I make it
louder
yeah
[Music]
I just can't resist
[Applause]
[Music]
you love hate all the same if you know
play the
game
baby
now in theend
just don't ever let yourself
falling
[Music]
res love hate all the same if you know
play the H so
oh my high voice is so
[Music]
[Applause]
baby
[Music]
for coming back to
you
[Applause]
G we
play do you do
you
me game we play Love
hat
hey oh that really I really
strained my throat
there I couldn't sing the high parts
shinda shind
okay I can do better but at least I
nailed the Korean
hey
on uh what's the word Al anhe what how
do you say Al anhe in
English of
unhe at one goal first attempt
okay right off the
bat
where you read I was reading ragi yeah
but still the lyrics flow so fast so
it's difficult
okay a okay my throat really hurts
I got to go
coin
tomorrow gate
okay tomorrow bers skate
yes according to
schedule byebye I'm going to rest my
Thro now oh my God it's already past
midnight it's been eight hours wow wow
wow wow wow
okay and in German we say I'll Fe Us
in
byebye Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye Bye
by
[Music]
for