[Music]
[Music] It's
starting, it's
starting
So, it's almost time for the next live show.Today, I
appeared with very good BGM, but I hope you all like it.
How are you? Hey,
can you hear me? BGM
Too good I
didn't say this. I haven't
played this new type of BGM at the opening.
So today,
actually, Subaru, the
Tales of series so far, Tales.  I've been playing
Ob Symphonia and Tales of
Tiramisu, and I've
been asking people to let me play with them, but then I
received a call from someone who would be the official Tales of Arise ambassador, so today I'm
inviting them to become the official Tales of Arise ambassador.
Now, please appear.
I'm Mr. Kihara, who seems like an idiot.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I'm here. No, no, no, hello.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, I'm
sure the day will come when Subaru-senpai calls me Sensei. Sensei.  I guess I
'm a little nervous.
[Laughs]
Please. Today, I'm probably fine. I've
worked as an ambassador many times, so I
'm fine. As expected of you, I'm a teacher. Is the
volume okay? Is everyone
okay?  Is it okay? Let me
introduce myself, please. Yes,
Holo. Listen for Live English. This
is Takanashi and Chiara. Well, I've been liking health for a long time. I'm
glad that Bandai Namco noticed that, um, last year.  I'm really
happy.Last year, I
received a job and became the official English ambassador for Tales.
That's one of the reasons why I became a fan.So yeah, it's really been a big part of my life.It's been
quite a while since I started liking it, and I was really happy when I saw it.Tales is the
only way I can experience it.  It has a certain taste.
[Music] That's
right. Today, I'd
like to go a little bit simple. Let's talk about how we're going to go about it. But
first, let's go ahead and do some slides.
Moreover, I want to talk about my memories,
but let's talk
about them, after all, Subaru and Chiara, my
favorite Sinfonia,
who is my favorite?
Memories, memories, etc.
I was really
young when I did this, and in fact it was a
long time ago when I had a GameCube.  Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, for Christmas, my
mother bought a Continuation Sinfonia for my house and my brother in Japan,
and
my brother mainly played it, but
I participated in that battle, and yes,
yes, yes, yes, that same one.  It's a game that you can play together,
so I
fell in love with the story as you fought together, and also the way it looked.This
was the first time I had experienced an anime-like game, so I thought,
Wow, that's kind of cute.  It was
amazing to find out that there were so many other games like this, and it was the
first time I learned about them that I realized that
there were anime-like RPGs out there, so
even when my brother wasn't playing them, I played them myself.  I
played it for a little while, but I wasn't very good at games at the
time, so I
couldn't go all the way to the end by myself, but I
played it a lot with my brother, which was really
heartwarming.I
still remember what Subaru-senpai was like.  But, well,
there's a famous scene from Sinfonia, isn't it?
There's coffee in the lower right corner of this and this, right?
That scene really gave me goosebumps.
[Music] It's
not a bird, it's this, it's
this.  When I thought of the Clerk series, I
started thinking of something like this, but
then I
found out that that
coffee cup was being sold at that time.  When I
heard this from a listener, I was
confused and wondered if I should buy it.I think
it's
a mug, after all, but
Sinfonia is
what it is.Lloyd's is
good, and I like it because of the way it shines.I'm going to
make all kinds of things.
There's a scene where Lloyd is making up a story, and there's also Kratos' kindness, and there's a scene where Kratos asks Lloyd to be strong and healthy, and I love that line so much that I
still talk to my listeners often
while playing that RPG.  They talk.
Chan is cute, and the interaction between the two of them is great.
Lloyd Lloyd is also
quite childish, but
what he does is that of a hero after all. What
's more, it's like the warmth of this parent and child. What's so
amazing about Sinfonia is that you can't
touch it.  It was really wonderful, I really
liked that part,
so everyone's interaction was great, and
Shina was
really cute,
and the scenes with Shiko and Boruto made me
cry a lot,
so let's talk about it.  I
can't stop playing it, so I'm going to move on to the next one, but I also
played Tales
of the Abyss, which is wonderful, wonderful, wonderful. I have fond memories of Abyss,
Mr. Kihara. You know, Abyss is a console game that I
can originally play Abyss on.
Well, I've
been trying to do it quite recently, or rather in the last five years.Actually,
I've wanted to do it for a long time, but it's been
quite recently, but I feel like I haven't gotten to the end yet,
so please don't spoil it.
But I
know a little bit about Subaru's
first
Tales of series
was Abyss. It was Jiavis, but I'm not
sure if it came before that.  I feel like I'm about to
cry.
[Music]
No, but I don't want to spoil the story,
but Subaru is the first
character to express
this kind of strong
motherly feeling to a character. Please
stop it.  So this is the
first time I've
done a live commentary on an RPG,
and
every time I've watched it, I've
cried until my T-shirt is all messed up,
and I'm like, oh seriously, that was so good.And
every time, I ended up feeling deeply hurt, in a good way.
Afterwards,
there's something so moving about it, like looking at the sky. There's something so moving about it, like a moment of emptiness.
No, I understand that a lot.
When I'm done playing a game like Tellz, I feel like my life is over.
What should I do with this?  It's like that. I
think about a lot of things. It's the
same with Sinfonia, which is very easy to understand, and the
same thing with Abyss.
After the Tales series ends, the
world will become different. What is the world? I
think about all kinds of things and
soak in the appreciation.  It's not, but it's amazing and makes you think.
By the way, I don't think it's an
RPG. I
got Tiara in Sinfonia, but my
favorites
were 1 and 2, so I'd
love to see 1 and 2 in the future. I
like them.  Isn't that right? I wonder
who the members were. I
think I heard someone said they liked Xillia. Maybe Kirara,
maybe Chiara.
By the way, what's the point? I
especially like that Xillia. For some reason.  It
's really dark, I feel like Kinari Naka Terrace's games are
generally a bit brighter,
but in terms of the story, Xillia
suddenly gets dark in the second part,
and the system is amazing and different from usual.  The
story changes as you make your own choices. There are
n't that many, so it stands out. I
see. When there are quite a few branches, it
gets me excited. Yes, that's right. I
like the basic system of regular Tales,
but this one...  It was different from usual, so it
really stayed in my memory for a long time at home.Oh yeah, it's so
memorable.I
cried so much.I
cried so much.It's
not like I'm doing it for the sake of crying.Tears
don't feel good, but there's
something like that.Subaru has such feelings.  This Tales of
series is quite similar to Abyss and Symphonia.It's
okay.I'm sorry.Subaru
may just have too many memories of this Abyss.I'm
sorry, but if a sitting senior praises me like this,
I'll pick it up again.I have
no choice but to pick it up.Don't
stop.  No, I'll go next time, but yes.Let's
go.Next, let's go here.Yes,
which slide is that?Yes, that
has changed.Okay, today, I don't want to talk about that old
tennis game, but actually I
want to talk about Rise the video, so
for that purpose.  The official management team has already
checked Arise's understanding and prepared the guide just like we did.A
confirmation test.I have
n't done the test yet.Subaru.That's
why I'm here.Subaru
.  First of all, I explain to my seniors about Nemiryo Rise,
hoping that they will like it, and
then at the end, I have them take a test, but it's
about understanding, understanding,
understanding, it's okay,
two owl-like creatures.  It says "Let's join forces to take the Arise understanding test.
Yes, this
street is Ford, not that nameless one.
Hulu, but I think they said "Furu" in Japanese.
[Music]  It's
not Fururu, I see. She's really cute. Tales always has a mascot of some sort,
right?
Rise's mascot is Fururu, so
today I'm going to promote various things about Rise,
so please join us at the end.  Let's work together to
take a comprehension test and get a good score.I've
prepared it.As always, I'll do my best.Let's
do our best so that it sticks in my mind.Video
First of all, let's take a look at this and that.I
want you to play Arise.
There's a new video for RPG fans.Teacher,
if you haven't seen it, I'll watch it with you.It seems like this is the
first time in the world that a cat has been
streamed.This is the first video to be played, so let's
watch it together.  Professor
Sho: Okay, so I'll be quiet for a moment.Yes,
by the way, I'm
going to be talking about that Subaru aloud as usual, but the teacher will be watching over me.It
would be helpful if you could let me know.I'm sorry, this is my
daily life with sounds.Okay,
Oishio.First
of all, this is how it turned out.  This is how it turned
out. Well, let's take a look at it. It's the world's first introduction PV. Let's take a look at Arise. Here it is. How far can I take it to get my mind off it? Even so, I'll keep going to stop him.
Hey, that's good. I'm Lena.  You are the one who will
use the flaming sword to defeat all the Surds.The
promise is that we will work together for that purpose.I
want to fight.It's
so beautiful.I've
already made up my mind.It wo
n't end unless I give up.And
someday I'll be able to
tear down the wall.  The day will come, the
wall,
when I see your face, I can't let go
[Music]
I've been looking for you
I'll defeat you to set you free It's
not easy to get over it
But get over the pain  I'm sure the
day will come when we'll be able to understand each other.Even
if it's the last moment, I'll never give up.What happened?I've
decided to let you dream just a little longer.I
also
want to be with you more.  From the
other girls
Our journey
continues
Come on, it's time to Arise
[Music] Well then,
let's talk
[Laughs]
Girls are too fleeting, aren't they? I'm already a little
nervous, but
that blank girl is that pink.  Her hair
is pink. Ah, it's Shion. Her name is Shun-chan. Oh yeah, that's
right.
But she's quite different from our Shion-chan. She
has a personality and many other things. Moreover, she's
freed from slavery. Yes, this is a pretty serious story.  Actually, it
's a very, very painful story, but
before I get into the story, I
'd like to say something about the story.The
video I was playing just now is from the main game, and
most of the footage is from that game,
but at the very end.  There
was a video of the DLC, and now that new
bundle has
just come out, and
Delcy called Taser Rise Beyond Dawn is coming out, so a
new bundle type that combines the main game and DLC is
coming out, so it's
perfect now.  The timing is perfect. It's the best time
to start playing Arise.
Um, at this timing, I'm also getting access
to the new bundle version. Oh
yeah, it's
going to take a little longer until TNC comes out, but if I get Battle now, I'll be playing the main game
soon.  You can play the game, so
first of all, it's quite long, so enjoy it,
and maybe
by the time it comes out, you've already
finished playing the main game, so that's the best time.
Just at that time, some
new downloadable content will be released.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, I
see. [Music] At the right time, you can also enjoy the downloadable content as if it were a continuation. If you do it now, that's right. Yes, I think there were a lot of things that bothered me about that video I just saw,
so I'll start by saying that.  What kind of
game is Arise?I want to promote it in various ways,
so first of all, I'm curious about the characters.That
face covered in steel is amazing.That's the
main character.Maybe I'll see that slide next
time.  I think it's good.Maybe he's
sleeping a little later than me.However,
this white-haired person is the
main character, and he says, ``Alfen.'
'
Remember, it's
dominated by the neighboring star Lena.
Dana
is the name of the planet star Dana and Rena That's
right, I was wondering who their names were, but they're planet-type. That's
right, that's right, so those
are the two stars next to them.
I see,
Dana
lives a shabby life as a slave on a planet called Dana, and he
wears a tortoise made of iron that he can't take off, so that kind of
mask is like a proof of slavery, but that's
not the case.What's that there?  There are a lot of
them, but
not everyone wears them.In
fact, Alphen
has lost
his sense of pain.Yes, he doesn't feel that kind of pain.That's right.Also,
that's
fascinating, but
he also has memory loss.  I don't know where I was born, I
don't know why the Iron Tortoise is wearing it, I do
n't know why I lost Currency-kun, I don't know anything about myself.I
really don't know anything about myself.I don't
know anything.  Of course, I
don't care about my own suffering, but I
especially care about the other person's punishment.I don't
want anyone to suffer, and I get really
angry because of other people.This person is like that a lot.  What,
uh, I can work so hard for others,
or
rather, it's like I can't overlook a plan. That's why I
become so passionate. I
have a very, very good heart, so eventually I'm going to have a
big time to guide Dana, who wants to be a slave, to release her.  They
get caught up in a battle, and they say, Okay, let's free Dana,
so I see. Who's the
slave? That's right, that's the
main point of this story. Here's
how to use a sword.
Yes, seriously,
this thing is really cool. It
's a flame sword. Isn't the
sword
really cool? Moreover, this sword seemed special. When I
looked at it, it seemed so special.
How special is this? It's probably
better not to spoil it too much.
Okay, so next time, you'll
find out how to do it at the very beginning of the game.
No, but stop for a second. Let's
talk about Dana from Cat Slave Planet.  There were a lot of things, but I
thought the worldview was unique after all, so I'll leave it here. I
understand the worldview.
Since there's an anime, let's
take a look at that too, Professor.
Ok, okay, I'll be silent again.
Excuse me, please. OK, let's do
this, do this, do this, then do this. Well then, let's
understand the worldview of Tales of a Rise. Let's watch the anime together.
This is it. There's a
lot of water.
The water is so beautiful
[Music] It's
natural, isn't it? It's quite natural.
My stomach is pounding, but it's quite modern.
Vehicles are
protected by spirits, and the
land of Dana, which was surrounded by rich nature, has
suddenly come to an end.
Things and life dwell in it.  Exploiting spiritual power in every way.
That's what these 300-rank
Lena people have been doing in Dana. They're
pretty controlling.
Why did you save me?
[Music] The
life I was born with is what I
seek. Either way, we'll fight.  I have no choice
but to keep going, and if I have that flaming sword, I
can see some chance of victory.The
sword
is the key word after all.This
black, but only if you two are aligned.That's why I will
fight, I will fight
desperately to win the
world and
myself.
[Music]
Teacher, I
have a question.Do
you think the world can't be saved unless the two of us come together?That's right, it won't be possible unless these two, Shion and Alpen, live together.I'll spoil it too, so
tell me why.  I ca
n't do that. I'm curious, right? Sensei.
Shion-chan
is a 10-user. I guess that's right. Well, let's
take a look at Shion-chan a little bit. It just
came out, so it's serious.
But there's something about Shion-chan.  There was also another
woman who looked like a keyword, with amazing golden
hair, and for a moment I could see her Nekata, but she
was the heroine of Rise, and she had great
technical skills and
Japanese.  What do you say?
[Music] It's
life force, yes, yes. It
's from the noble planet Renner, which
controls Dana by 300 yen. It's from Lina.  5 bosses to control
This is Lord Rolls.
Bosses are called that in English, but
in Japanese they are
a bit
sharp.
During the game, you keep defeating them, but
in reality, Shion-chan
touched his skin.  All people
feel severe pain. First of all, if you
touch Shion-chan, it hurts a lot
. I
can't touch Shion-chan. Even if I wanted to hug Shun-chan, I
couldn't. That's the curse that
Alpine is involved in.  I don't have any sense of pain, so
this would be a good match.
Of course, that Shion is
a bit special, but that's true. But
yeah, uh, that prefecture, the
Flaming Sword,
just like I said earlier. I have to say something
spoiler.
Wait a minute, I
have to say this. I
feel like I saw something in the video just now. Since
Alphen
can now be touched, he
brings out a weapon from inside Shion-chan's body. Okay,
Shio.  Shion-chan's something is pulled out from her chest
. This is also the enormous spiritual power of the flame that was hidden inside Shion-chan's body.
That's
right. It's all made
with spirit arts. So, this is a prefecture created through spirit arts.  We're
going to take it out from inside Shion-chan, so
these two have to work as a pair.Oh,
I see. They
're stronger when they're together, but somehow when you
touch them, it hurts.
Is the cause of this curse of thorns?
The cause is,
yes, yes, yes, yes, it's so true. It's a
curse. I want to do something about it,
but I
can't do anything about it, so Kokoton
and Alphen's chance encounter led
to a 300-year-old curse.  An
opportunity has arisen to end the slave rule of the Lena people.
So, is this really an
invitation? Sensei, this is the
slave planet, Alpine, and the planet that it rules,
Lena, and the Lena star, Shion, joining hands.
Wow, what is this? It
's not the end of domination, but it's not a peaceful symbol,
but it's something like that. I
understand. I'm glad I understand. I wonder
if it's going to be a little bit more. I'm
a little curious.  So
Alpen is the only one that
comes into contact with Shion, right? That's
right.
Shion-chan is quite like that. When I
imagine it, she seems a little lonely,
but I'm used to it, so it
's already quite cold, especially at first.
About Shion-chan, she seemed a bit
strong-willed.By
the way, did you see that Shion also
has a gun?It wasn't
cool, but it was cool.It's
especially
good to use it like that when hitting flying enemies.  So, Shion
sells the flying enemy with Shion, then
goes up close to it in Alpine and cuts it.It's like that.It
's like that naturally, but yes, it's
right now, Shion.I'm
sure it's like this from around the chest.  In this
scene, I
thought the sword was coming out of a whirlpool of flames, but
apparently it was coming out of a baby, but it's a little different from that,
but it's because they don't feel pain.
Sensei: That's
a bit strange.  I already had other friends with me, so
let's see if they'll watch it too.My
explanation is a little lame, but I
'll do it.It's really easy to understand.Teacher, it's
really cool.I mean, I
thought the battle scenes were really cool.  I've
been watching it for a while now, and there's that one-on-
one fight scene. It's
amazing. It's not like that plane,
but the design of the flying thing is so
messed up. I don't know what it is, but I
really like it."  I
was looking at Subaru. Yes, there are some futuristic
parts.
Maybe in the next slide.
This
is Alpine and Shion's companion. The linen on the left
. This girl has actually been a member of the Resistance for a long time.  This
is a girl from Danajin who was active. I'll probably
move on to the next slide. Basically, this girl
can't use spiritual power and has fun, but she has learned
magic to resist Lena, and she can use
very,
very strong impact magic.
[Applause] He
's a party character who can use magic. He's a
magic character.
Look at
him. Ah, I see. He
's with Rimmel-chan. The
House of Councilors is so cute that in fact,
this is not a spoiler in the game, so I'll
say it.  That's why I
collect Fururu in the game.There are so many
different kinds of Fururu.That's why it's
good to collect a lot of Fururu.It's
really cute.I
also saw it at the Tokyo Game Show the other day.  There
was a huge Fururu
. Let's not talk about the Tokyo Game Show.
I couldn't go. I
wanted to go, but I'd like to see you at a game next time.
[Music]
Well, Law is on the right.  Law is a
slolier Seesorian in the land where morning never comes,
but he acts as a surveillance police that can be used by Rena. He is a
member of Dana, but he has joined Dena's organization on Rena's side and
serves Rena.  That's why the
craftsman is actually an enemy at first. He's in a
position like an enemy, but
Roan is good at close-range impact. He
uses super and quick impact. Yes, he adapts with one blow. He's
at the mercy of his own hands.  I'm
going to go with Baba Baba,
especially that target, and the
equipment is really messed up.If you
attack someone who is hard today, it
will break, so first
attack with a low attack.Yeah, break that equipment like this.After that,
everyone
goes to hear the story.  When you play, you can come up with a lot of strategies.There are
various positions depending on the character.Oh yeah, there
are quite a lot of strategies, but it's the
smartest way to do it like this.I see.That's what I'm good at.
Yes, the
next
Slider-chan
is on the right, but it's okay to be on the right.
Or it will be erased. The one on the right is Kisara-chan.
Kisara is originally a ruler, Rena-chan, and a
slave, Dana-chin.
There are some countries that coexist amicably and live together in good terms.That
's right.We're much closer together
than in other countries.I'm a Danazin
soldier who sympathizes with Shu-kun's ideology in Menancia and belongs to the SS.  If you
look at it, you can probably tell by the cat's equipment,
but he's Mr. Sohei, so he's a tank who is good at manipulating an extremely large household
built using Lena's technology to
protect his friends and fight
[laughter].  I was
wondering if this isn't a shield, but it's
like a character who can warp anywhere.I
think it's quite sacred in the character, but it
might be the first time, but he
fights mainly with a shield.  Okay, let's stand up,
push, push, and
burn. There's also a race,
but I
'm fighting mainly with a shield. It's
cool.
And what's on the right is this. I'm talking
about those five bosses.  Didn't I mention that there
seems to be a boss who is in charge of the 5 people? That's
right, this is a spoiler.
Even these people are lenient. It's written here,
so they're in a big position, but
even if they're having fun, they're interacting effectively. They're
conscientious.  Rinajin is a really nice person. Have you
been there? I wonder if you've already been there. He's
quite a
hobbyist,
artist, and
collector, and
people around him tend to see him as a strange person. When the time comes, he
uses a certain technique, and since he's a redactin, he
also uses spirit arts.  I can do a lot of things, but
I have a stick, and I
use it.It moves pretty fast, and it's
easy to use.The
clothes are pretty good, too.I feel kind of noble,
but there's that
one thing right now.  That's
right. Well, these two
are together. When they meet, they're together.
I see. They
're connected for some reason. They're
connected for some reason.
Hmm, that's probably true.  I
think it's better without it.That's amazing.I
feel like I'm trying to find the right line right now.But it's
difficult to understand.Even
though I'm giving spoilers, the level of explanation is quite high.So, it's
a little difficult for
me, too.  Sensei, please do as you wish, Sensei.It
's dangerous, but okay.For now, there
are six of us.These six
will be our party.The
six of us have
different origins, places of residence, etc.  Isn't it? We
all have different ways of thinking because of the techniques we can use, and
there are times when we get into quite a few fights. There
are six of us, all of whom have very different personalities, but I wonder how things will turn out at this party. I
wonder if they'll be able to get along.  Or will we be
able to fight together and achieve what we want
?But I don't know.Even
if we are in different positions, I think they will be able to do it to some extent.Well, that
's just a guess, but
there are some Dana people who serve Rena, and there are Dana people.
There are people who have been with Dana for a long time as part of the Dara group, and if we did it again, we would see
Lena and Dana together today, living happily together like this.There are
people who live in the country, so it's pretty obvious that
the reality is different depending on the character.It's
worth it.
Teacher, do you understand that the
reality we see is quite different, so our values ​​are also different,
but I do want you to do something good in that
regard?That's right, you're a genius, Subaru-senpai.
There's something I've never done before, but I've never done it
before. Is
there anyone among these characters that you're interested in?
Ah, good. I
fell in love with her too. I wonder what Tsukura-chan is really
like. This huge shield is so cool.
Well,
I actually have a small one and an 18-inch version of Perfume.It
's a
set of Perfume, so both of them
have a scent.It's a
little bit, but I'll tell you
next time we meet that I have such goods.  Please bring it to me.
[Laughter] I
think we should see more about [music] So let's
take a look at the video. Well then, I'd
like to take a look at the video, so let
me know when you're done. See you here.  A quick
farewell to Kihara and Hashibashi-sensei.
Now
let's watch Arise's battle together. Here it is.
[Music] It's
over.
[Music] I'll
finish it off now.
[Music]
Super stylish.
Be my opponent.  Yes,
but the
combos are amazing.
Subaru can also fight like this. It's
pretty dizzying.
[Music] It's
really crazy. It's
really crazy.
[Music] The
relationship between the two of them seems interesting.
[Music]
[Music] Did you
make it? Did you see it? Hey teacher. I
thought I should watch this one more time. It was
so
worth watching. Isn't it cool? It's cool. It
feels really good when a combo comes together.
That's one of the points.
Yes, actually, in previous Tales games it was
common to guard against enemy attacks,
but in Arise, everyone
but Kisara doesn't have guards, so
instead of that, there's that evasion button.
That
sake, the
dodge counter is the key to the fun, you know. It's a guard counter. Yeah, there
's a counter that I dodged.
Of course, Exora still has a lot to offer. Of course, you can block with that big shield,
but yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes.
So, let's talk about the basics.
Sorry, sorry,
but like my senior said, the combos look really fun, and this one too.
Yes, it's definitely a familiar system from Tales. It
's a fun system to hit with the kelp technique,
and what's more, it's a very fun system for me.  What I like about this
is that it was also in the video, and there
was a big scene where Shion-chan suddenly did something like this, right?
When it came to something like a combo technique, that's right,
that Peya technique, the
boost attack, the boost.  It's
called a strike, but this
is a pair technique in which you work with your friends.As you
work together with room techniques, boosts,
tag material strikes, etc., you
can have a fun battle at a very fast pace, and use this to defeat the
enemy.  I
think we'll be able to clear things up more and more.
[Music] That's
our image. It's okay, it's okay. Our compatibility is
gone. It's okay. You
can attack the combo and activate it with one button in the middle.
That's right, one button.  That's right, it
was in the bottom left, but in the bottom left, there
was an icon of that member, and if it was
glowing, it meant that this girl
could use this bazaar, for example, in the renewal, so I
sometimes put something like this in the middle of a battle.
For example, a
low punch
comes out, but if you use it at the right time,
that
equipment will break, so you
can use it at times like that.You can
use low to match the enemy with strong equipment, etc.The renewal is like
that, for example.
There are also techniques that can stop the enemy's spells. There are many such
techniques. If you use them at the right time
and use them together, it's really easy.
Does it mean that Subaru can easily
release this?I think everyone can use Subaru as well.There may have been parts
in other Tales games
where I thought the battles were a little difficult,
but Arise is really easy to
learn.  Even though I'm not very good at it, I
was able to do it, so I think it's easy to understand.It's very easy to understand,
and there are combo techniques and
techniques that I've seen in previous series, so it was really fun.  It
means that even people who are playing this kind of game for the first time and people who are unsure of what to do can easily pull off great tricks, right? Sensei.
That's right, do
n't give up. I'm
relieved, Sensei.
There's only one thing about Subaru that I can't feel at ease about.  What's more, I
can't feel at ease.That's the
understanding test that I'm about to take.I ca
n't feel at ease about this.Are you
ready?Senior, are you
able to manage your thoughts?
Please leave it to me, Sensei, for a moment, Subaru.Answer
without looking in my eyes.  I'll do it, OkOk.I
think Subaru-senpai can do it.Okay,
first of all, if you
have any questions, I can give you some hints.Okay,
so feel free to let me know.Let's
start with the first question.Which is the
correct combination?  Wow, I
got a test-like question.
Wait a minute. I
understand, so it's Alpine. She's
a slave and the lever is Shion-chan's. She
's a master, so this is 1. Is
it 1?
[Music]
[Laughter]
Just in case, one more thing.  To explain, Lena and Dana are
on neighboring planets, and it has
been 300 years since they invaded and ruled Dana. The
Confidence is
divided by five rulers of Rena called the Sharp,
Alpha and her friends.  He
will travel to various places and offer his support in the fight to liberate the Ordinances.I see.Does he have
high technological capabilities?It
says that he unilaterally invaded 7, but that's
true.I do
n't know how much I can say about that, though.
Don't worry, it says on that slide that the
number 7 is divided into five, and
each one is in
control.Teacher, it's
divided into five.Yes, yes, yes,
that's right.The next question is, what
are the terrible characteristics of Zion?
Which one is the right one? I do
n't have the qualifications. I can
use a gun. I
can use the power of termination. Or I
have a weak diet. I've come up with a rather delicate question.
This
must be a characteristic.
Is there really only two answers?
Which one is it
? Well, isn't it 2 or 3?
But somehow, I
don't remember if it was explained that it was the power of the spirit that can be used, but I definitely used 10, so yeah, that's
true.
Yes, Shin was
using a gun.  If you
call it with a boost attack and do a linked attack, it
will use tune, so it
will shoot down aerial attacks.Yes, I said that,
but yeah, there is no junior high school,
so we haven't met.The
world of Arise is
familiar to increase.  It's
not a spirit,
it's even Hoshino. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it; I can't read it; I can't read it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
feel like there was a slide like that where they ate a lot.Hmm, and Shion-
chan is Shion-chan's Jun
is the result of Rena's technical ability.Eh,
please say that again.Shion-
chan's gun is Rena's.  It was created by a very high level of
technical ability. I
wonder if only
Kokone-chan can use this. What's more, Rena people can use techniques using spiritual power. This is the power I want. I'm sorry. Do you understand? It's about the spiritual power of the stars and this problem.  It's like
a pixie or some kind of fairy spirit.
This is a trick.
Yes
yes. Sorry it was complicated.
Sai Shikamo Sensei's official
LINEstamp.
Popular release. It says a little.
Shion eats.
This person's question is just this.  Let's
stop that, Professor.
Now, maybe I just wanted to show you that. The
next question is, which one is wrong?
Yes, there are resistances other than Alfen among Danachin,
or Renachin's control
is 300.  The number of people who use it against a school that has been around for a long time or a school is
suddenly very common. There are still 7 Kisaras,
but they are satisfied with their lifestyle,
or they are
good at fighting and are the only one among their friends who
can use guard, or
Rimmel is Dalatin, but
attacks.
Good at magic Which one is wrong? Is
n't it a girl who is the only one who can use guard?
[Applause] It's nice that you
remember it.
No, everything else is correct. No, I
thought so, Mr. Ro-kun, it's fighting.  I
thought you were a really enthusiastic guy who didn't use the guard and got in. That's
right. It's certainly the result of the teacher's teachings. Ah,
good, good, no, wait, this.
There's an explanation. Teacher. I
'll explain everything in a bit.  I
think everyone has probably understood this by now,
but in this game,
only Kisara, who holds the vertical position, uses guard.The
exhilarating feeling of seeing through the enemy's attacks and countering them
is also recommended for those who have played DAYSoffar so far
[Music]
More and more  I was in the resistance,
so yes, Nanchin's rule has been going on for 300 years,
and there are a lot of other things that
I learned.Actually,
this
may have been more than a question.Ah, more than a question.Okay,
Professor, please
explain.  There's still that central Harim, who is
a master of Mochizuki, and who
protects the coexisting country of Menantian with a shield.This is a little bit of a
battle scene, isn't it?It's pretty cool.There's
something really moving about it, and that
's the only guard.  The one you can control
is Kisara who is holding a shield.
It looks like this. Yes, that's what it looks like. It's
really cool. It's
cool. Ah, it's fun. This feels good.
Well, once it's decided, it's
[Music] It's already
[Music] It
's fun. I basically do everything else.
In the Tales game, I
always left the magician character
to the computer, but
I tried using it once in a while.It's surprisingly
easy to use and fast, and the
magic is released at a fast pace.But I'm
sure Subaru has quite a bit of that, too.  I think Abyss and
Symphonia use Lloyd and Luke
all the time as
main characters.I think they basically use only the main characters,
but in Arise, I
felt like using other characters as well, so I
tried using them.  I think it would be a lot of fun if you did it.
Try using a lot of different characters. And what's
more, you're
asked to master familiar techniques.
Mazinken Shunji
Shion-chan, Heart Race,
Circle Resurrection,
Holy Dance Thunder Blade What is this?
This is like a high-claw
attack, is
n't it
? There are some familiar words in the limb selection.
Grand Dasher, the one where the soil becomes bar,
and I really like the one where the tiger says bar.  That's
probably why Subaru
Subaru is after all new human rights and what else?
Everybody used that Subaru a lot.
Which one did you use a lot for evasion? It
spins around and around.
What is that? It
spins around and around.  I
wonder if there's something like Rayquazan. Yes, Subaru's memorable technique is Rayquazan. Well, maybe there is. I thought there was something like cutting through the sky while spinning around, but there are so
many different things.  Yeah, I'm
sure there were some techniques, but I don't know if they were this one.I do
n't remember them, but there are a
lot of other techniques.I'm looking
forward to it.Yes, please try out all those characters and play.  Now I
want to play the game.Oh
, I've tried it, but
what should I play if I actually want to play it now
?
Thank you for the good question, teacher.The new
DLC is also included for 6,800 yen.  I
recommend the Rise Beyond edition that comes with + J Plus.It
will be released on November 9th, but pre-orders have already started.If you pre-
order now, you can immediately
download and
play the main game.As I said earlier,
make a pre-order now.
By the way,
as a bonus for early purchasers,
special costumes for Alpen and Shion will be
available from November 9th.You can see them on the next slide.They're
really cute.That's an
illustration to commemorate the release of Tenjo Balance.  I
think it happened
in the same game.It
's great to have a matching set.I seriously have a lifetime, but
every day
when I play, I go back to my whole life.It's
so cute.By
the way, my teacher
is already watching this stream.  I'm
sure there are quite a few people who have played Arise, bought Arise, or played Arise, but should those people
just look forward
to this new downloadable content
?
Hmm.  Well, I have a similar pattern.It
's not long before I can play CDLC's Beyond Down,
but I think it'll be coming soon in November.Here's the
new character that appeared at the end of the previous PV.  The
new story is the main one, and the
play time is
about 20 hours,
but there are also a lot of quests, and if you
load it up, it's even more than that.I'm really looking
forward to it coming November
9th.  It was released in 2017 and is DLC, but you can pre-order it and it
comes with the bonuses I mentioned earlier, so
please check it out. Yes, there is a lot of volume.
This cat is a new character. What a
new character. I'm
happy to see more characters.
Some people have already played the game.  Please
give it a try. There
are trailers and other things,
so please check it out when this stream is over. It's a
very mysterious, mysterious existence. It's a
mysterious existence. I'm seriously going to play
it.  I still
don't know much just by looking at him, but everyone is already
thinking about a lot of things.What kind of person is this person?Is
this a
child enemy or an ally?Is that a secret?Is
that okay?Well, well, well, I don't
know what to do about that.I don't know, I'm young.
Yes, that's right. I see. I'm looking forward to
it.
There's a [music] set, so I bought that set, and then I
went back and bought it
for 6,800 yen
+ tax. This set is genius.
Now is the time to play Arise.I
have no choice but to play Arise.And this is what it is.People who
have downloaded it
haven't played Arise yet.If you haven't played the main game yet, it's
best to play Arise first.  I guess.
Yes, of course that's what we're going to do now. It's not too late now. There are
spoilers, so please play the main part first. I
see, everyone.
By the way, I
wonder if there are quite a few of our listeners who have also completed Arise.  I
completed it during the distribution.I
played the whole thing from beginning to end,
but yeah, it's downloadable
content.It's pretty amazing when it's around 20 hours long.So, I'm looking
forward to the DLC.I'm sure
there are people who haven't played it yet.  Please play the main story and the
downloadable content.If you have already completed the main story,
please
enjoy the downloadable content.
[Music] I
really want to play it.It's
fun, the characters are really interesting, and it's so
cute that when I put it on, I fell in love with it.  I'm
sure there's a lot to look forward to, so I'm glad they've already done it. There hasn't
been much DLC in Tales so far, so I
can't wait for it to come out, but
I can't wait.  Until that day, I
will continue to watch Subaru-senpai's journey through Tales of Lies.First of all, the
main character who is lost and the
heroine who feels pain when touched are both
unique, and
I like that.  I think it's interesting to
look at historical stories about the liberation of slaves from various standpoints,
and the characters. I
think there are a lot of fascinating characters, so how do they
interact with each other?  I don't care about that, and after all, I
've heard that the gummies in Arise are amazing, so I'm pretty sure about the gummies, too.I've heard that
gummies are serious and fights are dangerous,
so the ocean is still there, and it
's still there, after all.
As for what happened, I'm really
curious about that part. Was Subaru really that interested in the gummies? It's
okay.
When they broadcast it on TV, everyone said it was funny because they couldn't wash it. What's so
funny about it?  When I heard that, the first
thing that came to mind was something like Arise's gummies are terrible.I
don't understand either, but I don't know
what they mean.Yes, yes, yes,
garbage is the best.We are
saved by gummies.  Well, I'm definitely looking forward to seeing what kind of gummies will come out.
Well, I'm sure there are. Well, let's
play a little bit and see how many
gummies there are. Well,
this is the story.  I'm starting to get curious about what will happen at the end,
so Subaru:
If I do it, I'd like to start enjoying the main part of the game.
[Music]
So that's all for today.
So,
Mr. Kihara, thank you very much for today. It
was a bit difficult to explain in Japanese, but I
feel like you understood it. It's amazing. That
Kirara, you
know, you say that because it's not Japanese. Kiara, you know,
she's originally Japanese.  That's the
second part, or rather, it turned out to be something I would normally buy.I
really don't like it, but it's amazing.The
characters speak in English,
so yeah, that's true.Thank you very much, teacher.  The
voice actors were really good. They were really good.
Seriously, but the seniors
will do it in Japanese. I'm sure they'll do it in Japanese. Thank you very much. It
was fun. I was able to appeal to today's seniors.
Thank you very much for your detailed explanation of the characters.
Thank you very much. Yes, that
's all for today.
So what should we do in the end?
Should I go out with you, Chiara-sensei? OK, I'll go with you.  Would you like to use it as a scaffold? Teacher, I'll
go then. I'll see you soon. See you,
bye.
Thank you very much.
[Music]