[Music]
Hello
hi sorry I'm
late as
usual Hello
[Music]
everyone, I'm at the beach. It's crazy, it's
really cool,
wow, it's
so beautiful wearing these summer clothes,
you guys look at
it. Come on, let's wait a minute, let's
move aside for a moment
[Music]
here,
now we're the theme  The theme is we're going to
the beach, guys, are you late or not, are you guys late? Why are you
late? The theme is we're going to
parties on the beach now, okay?
[Music]
OK? Today's plan is we're going to do karaoke
but short karaoke
OK, short karaoke only not
[Music]
G
but the gu  yes, here are some gu, unfortunately we
can't come. So it's like,
eh,
we'll make it, we'll have fun, be happy
together with the guests, okay, okay,
what do you sing, okay, First song,
First song, First song, Do you want to go to
war?  -war Tokopedia singing
is
a failure, let's sing
a relaxed song first okay, let's sing a Chill song
first
Okay Where is my mic Okay I'm ready I'm
ready I'm
ready manasan wahahah
okay we eh eh suddenly eh
suddenly on  E garden oh sorry sorry
sorry okay
okay I'll be right [Music
]
here夏き
[Music]
Riri [
Music] [
Music]
Kacang瞬 [Music] [Music] [Music
]
も君将来
[Music] の
夢き希望
[Music]
望 sing  How are you?
that's the performance from Koba with
R Ar
OK hang on
Yao give me the
title So the first one is
Ririka
singing the song
wisheng
Secret
B Secret
Base
[Music]
bye
Z let me explain let
me
[Music]
That's our first gu wait let
me  the and the super chat
not
Al next gu Who is it Who is it
Ririka is already here we call
her friend next time yes
we call her friend next time
yes wait let me
[Music]
okay I want to cry but no so there are
some parts that Rik should sing
we sing together but  In fact, why is
he just silent, okay, just sing to yourself
okay the next person is
Let Me Let Me Move here
First what
about Siho
okay
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] が ある ならり たい と
[Music]
う
[Applause]
レス守こで
[Music] [Music
]
首
[Music]
の靴
unas
[Music]
te
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
別
ぎ
k
[Music] I'm
getting gout again, aren't I? What's the reason for this?
I think it's better if not.  jumping
jumping yeah wait
Okay I'm done I'm done calibrating again
So I think it's it's song I need to
recalibrate
for song
yes enjoy
okay there was a
and we sang Romeo and
Cinderella by dorico
[Music]
every time you sing
guik not ke  the guest is hilarious, I
understand the name
too,
I don't think I want a song that's
slag first
okay I think this one e cute song cute
song
okay
yes wait where is it Okay I don't want to
jump up and down Okay I want to be jumping
jumping Okay let's
go bury
spai Happy birthday thank
[Applause]
[Music]
give me give
me
[Music]
て
chapter
[Music]
love
B [
Music]
love
[Music]
me [Music
]
胸
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Applause]
[Music]
chapter baby
baby
[Music]
set happy
birthday
[Music]
I love
that song sweet
Berry baby love what's the title baby
baby it's me
Gaga baby  gugu gaga baby sweet
Berry
[Music]
by in
OK, the reverb can't be turned on, I ca
n't really hear the reverb. OK, wait
a minute
[Music]
ah, it should be more reverb now, it's
better,
the sound should be a bit smaller, oh yeah, I'll
increase the calibration
bo yeah Yes just a moment have each song
our gaming calibration guys Come on yeah sor
[Music]
Sor
Well that's right again guys I'm
back to normal
OK next next gu is hmm This is it this is
it oh okay okay okay okay friends
now
friends friends Okay  let's go Next song
who suddenly appears from
under Anjay let's go Mami yes yes
yes Here's my favorite song
[Music]
nihekek
n right
[Music]
yes [Music] [Music] [Music] Kalauak [
Music]
[Music]
I'm
sorry
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] t yo yo
kor
Ah
[Music]
yes
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
wait is it my
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
part
worry just playing games I know that's
plastic and the plastic be
another morning
[Music]
comes just playing games I know that's
plastic
[Music]
to the to
another I'm just playing games I know
that's
plastic dance  the PL be
another morning
come
yeah click the mouse
baby wait the rivb the wait Let Me Let
Me hear my own
reverb let me hear my own reverb ah
check now the reverb is It's OK It's not
that much it's not that
less the reverb is
here  the reverb listen to
the damn That's a rivb Right
There
that was the song we
with no
n PL
[Music]
OK
next there is Bang Akim swear where
bangim Oh yes War times
bro eh is it okay if I do karaoke
War here I haven't asked tokpet
ih haven't asked tokpet
ih
Sis can sing
Warad really,
the song is ready
every 2pm.
Hands are calibrating
again.
[Music]
dah
dah I'm ready for the next song
yes okay Next song
is let's
see let's
[Music]
see I've grown up Mik I'm
now let's  see
M Wow, don't do this, let's go later, this is the
last one, just the last one,
basically
OK Next song is from the [ __ ] board
let's
go
I
[Music]
Black
I don't want to shake too much
ah let's go
[Music]
hak
[  Music]
崩
[Music]
to That's our bir
ha let's
go your way take your way
[Music]
yo
[Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
SH
rocker
Man he
[Music]
crazy
[Music  ]
[Music]
Black
Haj
maruno
Mat
[Music]
monat
[Music] I'm
tired, I don't want to jump a lot,
guys, that song is very
very loud to sing but very very fun to
[Music]
sing
okay  haha
let's
[Music]
go
だだ不世界
[Music]
な で 見え ない の
中先 だだ ない
[Music]
one two
世
[Music]
let隣 let's go h
の 町 から景 は た
め生きつくど世界
[Music] はくりる供 の頃 に は で も て
[Music
]
の
one two
[Music]
[Music  ]
で倒
[Music]
も沈 Oh Gama didn't send l2d so just chicken
yeah yeah guys
yeah Kim
[Music]
kimケ僕
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
let let's
go
yeay ko
Salamat Yes great thank
[Music]
youamp
amato Hi aligato
Mina dah dah eh the kobon k is gone
too wait I'm also gone
OK I'm back
yeah the four of them when put together what's the
funny thing about gaming comedy comedy what's the name
eh what's the group what's Citayam what's that time  Yes,
we forgot the point, huh
OK, hang on,
OK from pok
one one
[Music]
su
uppr one
two first opening
for for pokéon journeys
after the rain,
OK, next OK Oh, my
throat hurts, my th
is a b but
wait let me
[Music]
myali
[  Music]
[Music]
Okay I'm back Next song
Okay ah Next song yes okay This is it already
this is it okay this is it Let's go Let's go
Let's go Let's go
[Music]
Brother PP
ap
[Music]
I have a Pan I have an
apple apple pan I have a Pan I have
Pineapple Pineapple Pan apple pan
Pineapple
Pan Pineapple apple
pan
dance what the hell Gus Anjir
ple
[Music]
yo
I have a Uh I don't  know ah I have I
don't know I have an Apple I have a
Pineapple Apple Pineapple I have I don't
know Apple [
Music]
pineappleen Pineapple
Apple
pen Pineapple apple
[Music]
pan
ngapain
ragus wes
Jan
[Music]
dance with
me with
me no hazing
right
dog dog si
[Music]
good right
PP
PP from
pikaro
pikaro I have Ah okay okay okay
okay I will sing it again
l l no no Wor no The L
Ok
[Music]
Sor
P
[Music]
ap I have a Pan  I have an Apple uh apple
pan I have a Pan I have
Pineapple Oh Pineapple Pan apple pan
Pineapple
pan pan Pineapple apple
[Music]
pan P Pineapple apple pan dance
Time
[Music] [
Clapping] [
Music]
[Clapping  ]
[Music]
I have a pen I have a pen uh long
pen I have an Apple I have a
Pineapple Apple Pineapple long p Apple
[Music]
Pineapple Pineapple apple
pan pen Pineapple Apple
[Music]
p
Now I have the lyrics right
Thank you
okay, okay, great, ragus Thank you,
great, doubt BR set to
invite me to sing karaoke, what are
the silat, but this isn't
okay, Huh,
OK, continue
Eh
, this is it, isn't it?
Hmm
maate mate maate
maate
[Music]
maateate Where is it Where is
it Where where is it wa  wa wait
wait
ah wait
OK I want to sing this with with
this my lovely person senai but I need
to eh I need to censor her clothes
because
of I don't know my Manager told me so so
I need
to I need to  be right
need
Yes Yes I'm sorry guys my Manager told me so
so
yes it's complicated rbet Yes
it's complicated
Indeed it's
tommate
nah this this is what I
want this is what I mean okay okay
okay let's
go
all sorts of things
I think this ok this fine  Okay
sor because it's on my
channel Yes let's
[
Music] go [Music] u nak [Music]
ehaini [Music] [Music]
good [Music] [Music
]
め
[Music]
gone Where my hand Why It's like
that
[Music]
yeah
OK I'm back OK OK OK next oh wait
wait wait before that
eh that was ha
camaama ha cama
[Music]
from Where there is I'm jealous it's funny ma'am I'm not jealous
I'm afraid it'll be down on
youtubeak tahahak understand the point of
being told  I
follow next
Okay let's go this song is very
l let's
go
wait looking for the
lyrics there's no
lyrics Oh okay Here We
Go
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
indonesahayar
Dun masal come and go I'm
used to being alone
again  for
[Music]
daydreaming, various dreams will not
solve
the problem, dare to
break through all
the obstacles, dreams never stop, there
is still
your love here, the light comes and
the light shines on
your days, remove all the doubts
that cover the
heart, and the emotions of the eyes bring
the light of things that are  baru
it's your thank you for coming to my
[Music]
birthday ye ye ye
po love you love you
[Music]
to you're not gna say anything to your
son ​​It's your is my
birthday
No not even a
word
Bro are  you [ __ ] serious
What whatever Bro lame
lame What the heck
Man bye bye that next time I want to come
to your birthday
bye bro
okay the
was the
rain spell the
family
bobo
Yara
rain spell
[Music]
Bob thank you
okay we have  ah at the end of the event
so This is the last song Yes this is this is this will
be the last song
Why l song yeah You guys just listen yeah
you guys listen to this song like how
okay I'm not ready I'm not ready
forong
ready not ready
[Music  ]
ready really ugly dog ​​repeats ah
repeats
[Music]
lah what the
hell
[Music]
lah
serada
[Music]
how scary are you Wow
I understand more
[Music]
dong
[Music  ]
low blood
[Music]
for a moment
гототе
parad Dark
[Music]
paradтова
y
bir Thank you for
and I've told you even though Si Mel Mel
later we sing this song OK Then you
have to sing it the ngerok yang ngerok
basically
uh calm
down Yes
Okay that was the last song Okay t song
d t song D UN
Revel crazy that's called groll
Mang
grow UN
rvel
from
by
e kitaajim
okay
[ __ ] fuing
tired yes
Okay take note Okay screenshot
Okay Okay then I'm
done Eh  but I want to sing
this
[Music]
jam
Dadi Thank you Welcome To The
Stream Welcome To The Stream Thank you
for the Happy
[Music]
birthday No don't even don't
even you don't even say happy birth when
BR
pe
whatever whatever
[Music]
tut maat
yeah Ng
come on let's have fun war war
war W War W War those are the lyrics Kobo
makes the same bangakim and also the melody
ee Kobo makes Yes We Made It
together
[Music]
hang on
Wow, let's go, come on, come
on, come on, don't forget, guys
[Music]
Topet
Tokopedia every 2 pm check Tokopedia
on Tokopedia for any item, also check
Tokopedia Tokopedia is ready every hour
2 pm disk disk all items are available
[Music]
disk every 2 o'clock  afternoon, check
Tokopedia, enjoy scrolling looking for
mandil goods, check Tokopedia, uh,
War Tokopedia 121, don't forget War Tokopedia 121, come on, come on,
come on once again, let's close,
let's get you hooked on
the song and check Tokopedia, keep
war Tokopedia every time at 2 pm, check
Tokopedia Tokopedia goods  whatever,
check
Tokopedia W Tokopedia is ready every
hour of the afternoon, discounts, discounts on all items,
there are discounts, check
[Music]
out
every 2 pm, check Tokopedia at War
War Tokopedia, any item, also check
Tokopedia,
oh, where
is Kokopedia every 2 o'clock  afternoon
tokia tokia anything at
tokia Tokopedia is ready every
2pm Dis all items are in kag
[Music]
out Come on, what are you waiting for, check out
kanjangwopia
I'm
satisfied scrolling looking for
mandil goods check out Tokopedia
[Music]
Eh nah