[Music]
it's to just a thought within you wish
that road on now the wind begins and
ends tell and
goodbye I'll take a chance to see what
we could be the past and distant memor
to another world at last I'll Gras that
promise
life the highest over began so part of
plan I arve soldier in Far Land with the
hand with going go let it all melt away
in the white on the winds ofation flying
from all this world to see
though I makes you all decited hard to
hide it f numing days is numing
happiness something anyone can find
pushing on for is all that is
mine alone it's all so the so the thing
I TR before with the be B inside
[Music]
recalling all the days we met a place
that I've been LED and yet my world was
built of walls of endless
high but it Melody that Set Me Free this
worlding seem the best of me un
invisible for just one moment I can
find f f so unpleasant resentment the
more you told the inside of the binds
the stories of old burning through every
repage to learning to Envy the stage the
wild with the viol SM H the Bri cage on
wind of desperation flying for all this
world to see the one Mak to all the fite
it f it's hard to hide it been decided
for me numing tears and heartache sorrow
hate running endlessly through time
again still the FR under like I've
always
been my my home a place never now and
feel the
beo the full is divide the cold inside
the dice roll is dis spice it must have
a nice the gorgeous device to tricker
and Ty it's got a price playing it's R
the car that creat a heart nothing but
dead dond the SP the L your Wes they
never going to change Li myself reject
any all help on my chips fall hell Blood
Sweat can I stop the thoughts feing
nobody's waiting after all is set done
there's nowhere L run
get never thought i' beg the be talking
head got one but don't need nool
[Music]
our world is turning once again for that
reason I still sing and we shed so many
tears find out though I never did a
change a thing Le the BL crying feeling
like dying all became a part of me we
won't have to wait for long waiting from
Beyond with our cont me nothing pain is
numing happiness something anyone can
find pushing on for resolve that's truly
mine on the Wind of desperation flying
through all this world to see but I make
to Long f f start to hide I won't
let numing f is numing happy so you know
it's over worth fighting for every me to
an end it's than all be
gone your home is more than just a place
you're never Sai on the forward
something rewarding but your wers will
never be storing I'm ignoring the Lord
cuz I want to be
[Music]
more more more
than I'm
[Music]
hey un happppy work look got the like R
in for
[Music]
sing SL the me SC
get
[Music]
anything
I call
you
all got my
[Music]
down
day w
[Music]
Happ
you made that
[Music]
my my
not
[Music]
for down
hey you home can I get a
head let's go
[Music]
see and I my
eyes
[Music]
last
we don't know
you
[Music]
fire K yeah
to talking
all
on on the back
[Music]
wow I'm or
for
without talking all away
[Music]
k i me
why not go all the in
[Music]
day
aies the oh you know that
fore wow
[Music]
a
around around everyone says that love is
just like a
dream feel like a m from the he love is
feel
so just like that you know just how it
goes don't have stop but you already
know my got me more yeah I don't worry
about you good good good don't wor on me
I want to go and party don't let this
love in now I won't
pretend
love try
now
freet when you go kiss me I'm taking a
perfect
pict you're to me like a you got 1 2 1
so free so so so sweet go that
way yeah yeah keep going you
[Music]
know you
be to my Fe you be
[Music]
your mind the warm I want to go and
party don't let this love now I won
pretending
love I want to try it now now going 2 1
2 Qui when you kiss me I'm taking up
pict you're St to me like I
you got 1 2 one 2 three so so so sweet
go
way keep going you man
[Music]
I'm
going when you me I'm taking perfect
pi to me like a you guys
are free it t so so so sweet go away
keep going you know
[Music]
me where do you want to go just right
on F take to the time where I can
find
[Music]
you
foree
[Music]
fore
foree
for I have you
to in my
[Music]
life
for
[Music]
foree
fore speee
[Music]
in
spe foree
in my
[Music]
life fore
looking on in my life
[Music]
pil as pain contain my memory
stranger and if true here you are one
more story has down the the hor with the
SN in my hand Wonder L inside my heart
we can feel the Out Of Reach
[Music]
break go the story
T night and
me
my look
[Music]
at got to be more W store I'll find it
this days the selfle for the one find
the way the next take it B been done
remember when but feel like that first
time
again night back
[Music]
down keep on by many
you so long
[Music]
ago nothing CH stop if you're true
that's who you are one story The I want
to with my hand wonder inside my heart
feel out of creepy
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm let
your need to
[Music]
you be fing the
go
[Music]
oh
I you
[Music]
for
better me
[Applause]
you got
the there you go
you
[Music]
be better
he
[Music]
H part
P
you who is H get
[Music]
it's the
the it from out the way like a
Bop riding by well wondering when I'll
make let me stay here
[Music]
ring ring roses fall and round la la la
walking up and down fall I want to stay
here
forevering ring where I
there walking up down
[Music]
no my honey
Kiss
Part
[Music]
she but it
was just my
the golden sunl shows it's time to wake
up waiting
quietly shutting my eyes and my
face look me St
[Music]
it's
just very T the it come M way like a
Bop riding F
Well
for never me
stay
[Music]
here time to get this party started by
fire like the fire Bri or high as you
desire chasing all that we Aspire ring
out like war fire never ever have I ever
in a a dreamer take the chance and look
my lighter
[Music]
fire me out I'm out of seat to over kill
saddle stories wearing me down is the B
of the system break out give it
everything this is our time we're going
to
discover how New World keep the light
and fre
from fire fire W the fire high as you
desire now Beating Heart through the
flame of
the
[Music]
end
I time to get this F started fire fire
light the fire Bri highes you desire
tting all the we are far step to the
left two steps to the right step back to
where we started and then over again
step out of the circle break down we got
everything this is our time we're yours
to discover time to take us home so when
we
belong afraid us from
the to Paradise fire fire like the fire
fire highes you desire ignit beating
Hearts Dan through the FL of light so
all Dan through the end
time keeping
all through
the Rebellion
[Music]
as we get this party started fire fire
like the fire right or high as you
desire it's thing know that we Inspire
still be the fure of a story I know that
I can be for one of the only they tell
me that I'm crazy never let
stop I get this party started never ever
have I ever been a a dreamer fire fire
light the fire fire fire light the fire
night speeding heart jump into the G
my
I'm till the end of time
[Music]
Dan through the FL
of and all St we had through
the keep King all the world to the the
[Music]
to get this party started fire fire like
the fire High youire time to get this
party
started that's right I'm not just an I'm
a time
traveler what this
[Music]
one we
first I wonder what you think of me the
image was
set it was a perfect narrative but it's
time went by I forgot to hide the laugh
that came so naturally through lows and
highs I wonder why I ask beside you will
leave now no matter where around we are
we know with you I can count on mag
mag nothing can stop us now let's
go back time
go how said I know why you see when
you're here with
me
heart for every to see this mystery was
s immediately
[Music]
it's so
long since I laugh so hard I cried now
you came
along it happens almost every time that
I hear your voice the left no choice to
let you know where you me to me
spiraling time skipping through Tre
memories now no matter where when we're
from our friendship
Elementary is CL now you know nothing
can stop us
now way back time
go how should I know why you when you're
here with me W stop SC me
heart be
F forever to see this mystery was
me
weer what the future hold is not not not
for us to know yet it's gone gone gone
before we know
it s the
question we can make this second T last
forever now one
[Music]
another where
time should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock will stop
spinning
f for to
see that's right I'm not just a
detective I'm a time travel look at this
[Music]
[Applause]
I was B to tears I like 9,000 years if
back and for and com upup in like a knif
and then I saw it in your eyes and it
took me by surprise 10, BS B to my heart
to Li and I want you here right now you
know cuz I'm ready to let go get me
through the night somehow show me all
you know my lips are mystery one kiss
and you'll agree if you're down to get
familiarize and baby say right e r i s s
play with fire take me higher
clarify take me
higher burning up the Flor you got a v i
can't ignore in the sea of Embers
dancing wa until the
night The Best Is Yet To Come but you're
not like anyone I'm going to pass I'm
someone shining so bright the desent is
filling up the air and you're still
unaware that you're falling fast under
my smell baby it isn't fair when I'm
inside this illusion I am anyone and
everyone our logic Fades away tonight
you're say you're right r i s s a k blow
fire take me
higher glow fire take me higher
[Music]
take me higher in it's a game play with
fire say my
name play with fire say my name say my
name fire take me
higher take
me with fire take me high
w
[Music]
[Applause]
taking you up alone taking you up don't
don't me here the B the B taking
Bel we
go think they want it they want to get
we take them down down down I'm in the
borderline running no surprise you ain't
going to win but you can try told you
got no luck end up in my line up l l r
hide and scream already locked your
upful things you always play call me out
one hear anything a him start right on
your heart thr in the keys out shot
[Music]
down
never just we got
him you standing on the head so know me
unpredictable to for you don't know
where to go show you something real My
Level you never know how the the love
you
know in the
Lighty what run what right rushing in a
fanty want to be dis sure that you won't
out me it
out I fall now do it do it now
en see your guilty
heart we're not going to stop it
just standing on the Ed don't know me
unpredictable typal you got knowwhere to
go show you something real my know
you'll never know how the the
[Music]
love get down get like that like that
get down get down down down down me up
let go going up below you don't they
know it in the light ohmighty what's
wrong what's right with you right in the
night ohmighty come say nevering
the
again standing on the head know me I'm
predict you I know where to go show you
something here my never know you'll
never know has
aable
beautiful look at it look at Let Go Next
Level almost criminal as a it goes
[Music]
a