[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
frogy froggy
w
h frogy w was I only get
Clips
why what's a what's a froggy W stream I
did uh how about frog detective kada
even though froggy waa play it but let's
see oh I don't have sound a pengin okay
so beginning of stream what did she say
I even a frog like
me my
[Music]
hand
stop it
start the
stream start the stream I think she's
starting the stream
K is she is she what's she going to
do I'm for people who are just coming in
I'm trying to confirm what I was saying
in the beginning
[Music]
ah oh
ah is am I saying or I think maybe k k k
k or
so actually just one one
second okay
[Music]
perfect halfway through a little bit
more than halfway through the Frog week
we know you guys didn't really remember
either though you guys reminded me of AR
Ribbit therei but not of K
Kido okay we are going to play Silly
game silly game very silly game Spin
frog isn't the thumbnail genius I was
like scrolling for my
art you guys I'm so happy there's been a
lot of new new froggy waa art as well
and a lot of art of the cape as well
thank
youa yeah and thanks to that um actually
the the the froggy waa and the thumbnail
that's on the
copter is old really
old
actually
actually actually
[Music]
it's from I think last Last
Christmas I think
now now I don't have it at hand anymore
I
think do
[Music]
I it's it's really old and actually she
froggy one one is in that picture stuck
on like you know those top Christmas
decorations those like cones or whatever
like the stars she's supposed to be on
top of a
star let me show you the OG I want to
show you the OG cuz I edited it edited
it sounds
funny yeah there it is it is there it
is
look this was
OG and then I got rid of the star and I
was like M she's still like it looks
like she's grabbing onto something I
could make her grab onto the copter and
make her go
swo and it's so old is this
from
2022 2022 2 November
2022 see I I I think I'm mostly last in
last frog week I think I mostly used up
all of the well
usable frogi waa art for
thumbnails um I used up so many they're
so cute H but now I got a few more but I
recycled this one I don't think I used
this one before in the past for a
thumbnail and now I found a really good
use for
[Music]
it I'm so organized like I'm I'm I'm
this is like the one thing I'm really
organized with like there's so many
things where I'm like all over the place
and like really unorganized but when it
comes to fan art
um I I realized
early very early on in my time in H I
realized I might need to like save all
these fan arts and in the beginning we
still had way more fan art than now and
uh a lot of like the defic hello sorry
I'm like tanging in the beginning I'm
going to start in a moment
okay uh I was going to say um yeah I was
uh I was I was like starting to realize
oh we I should I should probably save
these and if I save them I should save
them with the Twitter name so I can
credit them properly even if I look back
on the art like a year later yeah so I
did that and now I have like every once
in a while you guys are probably also
surprised you're like huh this art looks
familiar but it's not recent where when
is this from right you guys probably
also are like isn't this like what or
you actually never have seen it before
cuz it's that old
I'm a genius de said remember to set set
to the shop for holo reference what what
does that
mean Holo say to the shop for holo
reference oh wait are you saying they
put a reference
into the shop into the
game what they put what
did they do that for
me did did they did they do that for me
am I not like the first to play this I'm
actually the one who requested this
game the de was in preat earlier and
said oh he's not here now they they are
not here now I don't know what who they
are are they not here now they were here
before cuz yeah I asked for pubs I was
like and I also like when we asked for
perms for a game they also ask for like
the the the reason or like the purpose
and the time frame and Etc and so I said
I want to play this for frog
week de de de and pre-at death not now
chat they are studio somewhere okay wait
they're not a member probably right I
need to look at the gray names probably
right sounds so
discriminating ah there you are there's
a bunch brother the game what did you do
that for me K
all w what did you do that for
me oh wow I just bought your merch set
cuz you got you got your patche I got
mine too let's
go let's
go wait um that's it that's exciting oh
oh [\h__\h] sorry but but I can start the
game
anyway right but these are always really
short right I can update
these are usually short
right great names man too yeah yeah yeah
yeah they do they do they do they
do
[Music]
updating oh there we
go oh but this scares me like the
console restarting means that my cap
game capture is restarting
too ah now I feel like I shouldn't have
done
that ah no why did I do there you go
there you go okay it's back it's
back I don't trust my game game capture
card ah I heard that sound CCH
okay let's let's go let's
Ste I see little a little bit of a
imperfection hold reference in the game
shop wonder how early I can reach that
double
double okay okay okay okay okay no did I
ever tell you the story of the clever
little frog and his wonderful invention
yes but please tell us again wait I know
this is this sound normal cuz I have
sound problems right now I hope this is
normal cuz it sounds like
it's like
wobbling you yeah yeah yeah but not
double now a ah sorry sorry I'm so get
all get I'm not used to streaming get
all I'm a stream
beginner sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
the merch yeah the merch square is too
big sorry I'm a stream beginner kid
please forgive me please buy my merch
actually my merch is not too small it's
h it's not too it's not too big it's too
small look at the
merch can
we dear de dear developer can we
Implement my merch in your game
shop ingame purchases
yosu
Kidd how about that let's do a little
tie
up okay I I hope the sound is um
supposed to be like this cuz my sound is
kind of messed up right now I
think I don't think this is normal
actually wait do you hear is like
wobbling one second let let me know if
you hear it in in two
seconds well you probably you do
probably you do yeah it's just
crackling okay H did I ever tell you the
story of the clever little so I'm
checking for an answer from the dev was
a serious
question what the clever did they say
something about implementing my merch in
their in-game
shop little frog in this wonderful
invention yes but please tell us
again damn it damn it damn it no reply
I'm getting left on r or left
onard oh that's
loud love it
though oh oh yeah right I remember from
the trailer it has this
French music wait French music on a frog
game
what seems on purpose oh clap clap clap
clap everybody
clap what is this cat doing here I like
it it's cute or is the studio is not
French is it
would be a funny coincidence oh oh what
is it's so cute you know with these frog
games I've been playing the art style of
all of them is always so Charming I love
[Music]
it I can sing
French I am fluent
yes so we have a garage is that the
shop wait
what wait what oh fastest time okay wait
I cannot press the garage thing I can't
press
it but I guess let's go wait my controll
is just not really working well is it no
wa ah wait it's it's it's ah it's it's
not the I was pressing the d-pad it's
not the d-pad
it's the X a b
y oh is this the ingame
shop Wing
colors
finish yeah there is there it is there
it is feing Strike freeding strike
freeding St tacle tacle tacle
tacle I think that's it pretty much I
mean you could you could think that
nature is maybe F
of oh I found it
immediately but I cannot afford
it cockpit
colors no those are those are normal I I
like the choices of colors though
oh I mean this was probably here before
already it's not for me right I like the
hats
cute cat go B cute cow
frog
C sorry u meme continuing from
yesterday coo trinkets a bare shelf
shelf is a fair shelf GTO has installed
a new shelf inside the Frog copter oh
wow we're
shelfing shelf nothing immediately fills
the heart with calm quiet like a nice
empty surface then why too does the
heart long to fill such spaces all
pickle heart m very
true very true but I don't have
anything okay ah thank you for the
reference cute you did it in a very
subtle way I can tell I appreciate that
that that is very sweet man if you ever
want to like you know um do something
with the kiaha just contact the the the
H life female I'm up for
it personally I'm up for it personally
personally I'm know about the
company okay let's do this I don't know
how um we're just going to spin oh
nature is f as colors and
penguin don't tell Kyla that we had your
color chicken
but you didn't want to get in trouble
with me huhm what does this mean I
wonder if you guys looked us up after
you got the permission request or if
somebody in your studio was already
already like kind of aware of Hol life
and they were like permission request
from Hol
life.com Whole Life channel Tak
youtube.com it was always there it was
always there massive Holan it was there
without my
influence that's actually even more
impressive
wow
wow I love you I love you can you make a
game about me we have we have lots of
Holo fan games can you make game about
me or horo
to do you take game
request you know H life fan games are
really popular these days they become
like number one on Steam
just it's a good good good way to go
yeah yeah
yeah and now you can you can pair up
with Hol live you as you maybe know as a
game developer and the Hol fan you may
know you can pair up like you kind of
you can even ask uh to like yeah put a
price tag on
it yeah we have a new fan game Revenue
system but any anyway not that you would
need it you're your own system uh your
own your own studio and yeah anyway so
yeah and let's properly play this and
touchdown H we made it BFF is that
supposed to be a frog sound
kiddo B what or is B someone's name you
can let go of my leg
now ah it is a frog's
name home we l ghetto look at him look
at him cute cute cute cute I mean
wonderfully done ghetto ghetto ghetto
ghetto is Japanese
for yeah throw throw up thing stuff
yeah actually B also sounds like barf
wait is this on purpose wait is this on
purpose because when you spin you throw
up so there's ghetto not quite but
ghetto
and B barf not quent but
[Music]
B is this so it's common slang for barf
it
is is intentional oh my
God I I realized that on my
own I'm not reaching
kid I know too
much H yeah okay okay sorry I'm focusing
too much on the chat
cuz I want to
see what what it
what if de makes game about froggy Wawa
now sorry sorry for the
pressure what's your who's your ooshi by
the
way who's your just kidding just kidding
don't say it don't actually do say it
but B tote in GIC
GIC
wait that's so I heard that
before GIC I heard that
before sorry I'm kind of in a funny
mood stairs at
you pressuring Le Celtic language m m m
ah let's just say the order of the
colors
mean so you put in only your
ooshies into the colors so I'm one of
them and goba too and F too and Kaa too
let's
go thank you oh my God I love you I'm
going to cry Where's My Cry
button there thank you so much thank you
and Ena Ina too
[Music]
yeah thank
you okay I'm gonna get my [\h__\h] together
now Tak is
over no no no it's
not so I had every faith in you thank
you B that's very generous of you now I
can only think of thrown up stuff thanks
to these names so are we going to test
this copter of yours you bet where
should we drive to drive copters fly but
it does seem like we're not in air we're
in water oopsie did the message change
how about that old Jetty over there
Jetty Jetty Jedi
Jedi
binging okay let's go chill
[Music]
music yes so music actually pretty loud
let me turn it down
uh so you can see it spins and we can
probably not even fit through if the
spin is like like
this yeah so too quiet
okay so we have to be
careful and go through these
passages in a way that when you know do
the spin
anything does not obstruct anything what
hit the bricks G there's no way we'll
fit through the Gap yes yeah that's what
I was saying I know G but I know
B I know there's no way we'll fit
through that Gap with these big old
Wings Skittle it looks that way B but
because we're spinning we can just slip
through when the fin bitang y y yep yep
y y y y like Fring a needle with another
needle that's spinning I do not
understand that but
okay
now let's
go a this is so cute this is so cute
YooHoo there we go and then one piece
the one piece is
real one piece I found the one piece oh
my frog I'm sly we made K maybe we
should have a rest now there'll be
plenty of time for that soon off to the
next training
Pond Pond I live in a pond that's
me
you
cute felt a little bit sick
there oh okay I I Wast a little bit of
time no hit yeah coins
yeah okay goal is to get enough coins to
buy the Phoenix
color and maybe maybe a nice
hat
yeah sounds like
a oh next I wonder how many there are
learning the ropes oh I I'll show you
the
ropes oh I don't need I'll show you
the what
frog chef hat if not we right I will
gladly wear the chef hat of of the Dead
kiar that I took off her body to prove
you all she's never coming
back is that what you want kind of
morbid not going to lie hey B it means
the world to me that you take a week off
work to test frog copter with me you're
so welcome kle don't mention it to be
honest I'd rather explode in this thing
with you than spend another day well
that's so titty in Mr yakamoto sandwich
shop if you would have continued to
spend another day there you they would
have probably turned you into a sandwich
so it's good that you escaped bless you
bow I hope it doesn't come to that KD
though that does remind me we are yet to
try out the spin faster mode with that
R spin faster hey that'll be helpful
when we're waiting around conver
conversely if things are going too fast
we can slow the FR up this's movement
speed down to a crawl with ZL oh I can't
stop spinning complet it can't stop
spinning completely though otherwise it
would fall out of the air so we are in
air the the the OV makes me oh
[Music]
God have two two hearts
no okay
no
no okay I should use the
no help oh I'm not made for spinning go
go go no wait oh oh wait it makes me I
thought I thought it makes the spin
slower no it makes me slower okay okay
okay okay okay okay I oh no it does make
what
what no wait what what I can't do it I
can't do it
no help me help me cheat cheat code
please start from slightly
above okay
what should I have gone through it
slower or faster I can't
comprehend
no no give me the controller I wish I
could spin faster with that uh move slow
slower Sor you retract that cuz it was
wrong oh but there's already the goal
here H I kind of want to redo it
n really bad I only have one HP
left
[Music]
I'm already so bad and this is this is
just the second one we didn't even
explode you passion I kind of did
explode once but let's not tell him that
that's a a different
[Music]
timeline it's going to be long yeah
maybe I can't reach the Phoenix
color
no the dev said before you're going to
Rachel I didn't think it would be maybe
is it just me cuz like from the first
from the beginning already suffering so
much I mean even if there was suffering
to be had either way was it supposed to
be this early this game is hard okay
okay
okay that's the spirit all right I mean
we appreciate a challenge don't we at
all okay don't don't don't judge me like
this game Don't Judge Me Oh I still got
three out of free coins though I thought
I would maybe get
less oh coronai played it this she you
say it took her 18 hour
18 to completed
right oh my
God oh my
God I'm going to get good not this one
exactly but similar one she played the
OG which this one is based on
oh
oh There was a Game Boy Advance game ah
we should not have put a tutorial
message there since it does not really
help this game can get hard we made it
look cute to counter balance the game
you honestly reeled me in with the
cuteness and I was just looking for frog
games that I didn't play at and I think
isn't this one like still pretty new as
well I think so I saw it like I saw it
recently somewhat
recently yeah and this frog copter it's
very nice to look at and actually very
comfortable All Things Considered but I
have to ask how are we
hovering good question what do you
consider new I don't know maybe in the
past one to two years oh it's actually
very
simple it's like think you know when you
put a drop of water on a hot pan and the
water does that little dance yeah I
guess then you tilt the pan and it
bounces
away oh yeah except in this metaphor
both the water and the pan are the Frog
cter oh and we're just a couple eggs
legs EGS eggs eggs along for the right
okay then all checks out already okay
I'm not ready I
know don't wait those [\h__\h] no I got I
got my life back do I get my life back
if I go back to the
beginning should I go slower
[Music]
but
okay maybe maybe I go slow no no no I'm
slow I'm too slow
then
[Music]
maybe
ah
wait I can do it Collision
[Music]
show no I didn't pay attention in the
end cuz I felt safe no but I I I got it
I got
it I got it all figured out I think I
think now now we're now we're
coptering don't lower your guard at any
cost oh okay I'd ask how the flying po
works too but you know oh that's
actually also very simple you know when
you drop an egg oh oh they they be
dropping a a lot of egg reference this
is the second egg that they're
mentioning kind of kind of sus kind of
sus but in this met metaphor the sky is
my kitchen floor and the egg is me and
you oh frogs being
eggs sounds also familiar eggs eggs eggs
and the eggshell is the imperious skin
of the Frog copter strong and true you
can't argue with
science
M great look at him
SP okay I have hope now I have hope to
be broke and
later can't have your hopes broken if
you don't have hopes in the first place
that's my problem I have hopes
now I
believe I believe too
much I should not be believing
maybe you have to go into things without
without hope without
positivity and then happy things will
make you happier even
more but sometimes you cannot solve
things unless you have
confidence difficult oh there's red
coins NY NY well you're right by my
calculations there are exactly six coins
and it doesn't seem like they belong to
anyone maybe we could use these coins to
buy new things from the garage
especially the whole life reference
things yeah like paint jobs or new hats
how are we going to grab them yeah it
might be tricky to drive the Frog copter
and grab coins at the same time perhaps
one of us should reach out and grab them
you've already been grabbing them so far
don't tell me I have to control it now
ah he's on
there no wait oh crumbs what do you mean
why are you there where were you until
now oh oh
no oh
[Music]
oh why do you need to grab
it oh
[\h__\h] no wait go
back grab thanks damn it I feel like I
could do it I could do it I I was so
close both times it's only at the end a
little bit now that I think about it I
think I probably could have just driven
into the coins to pick them up you know
just like we did in those other parts
exactly like why are you doing this but
I didn't want to rob you of a chance to
look cool of course you look exactly
like me in the
thumnail I'm going to kill my fro today
yeah thanks SK it was actually pretty
[Music]
fun 22 seconds eight under par what's
par is par the a average what's eight
what what what's
eight what's
[Music]
P golf term bar is the goal
no
no well whatever I have my own
goals that's
okay how the [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h] do you do
under under under that
HH our power is
higher okay B I've been thinking this is
the last test before I rubber stamped
the Frog copter what but it would feel
like a waste to just go home afterwards
maybe we could go on a little trip huh
yeah I really could do with taking a
break from our village let me think it
okay you're thinking about where we're
going after this ooh
oh this is Chill why is there so much
space okay okay uh
H okay here we go no no but it's
impossible I have to use the spin faster
or spin slower option but I don't know
which one is the way to go oh this one
was an easy section though there was
only one Narrow Path oh Plum town I
haven't been there in years what a great
idea let's set up camp and head off
first thing tomorrow barbecue time
[Music]
yeah yeah try speed running a level okay
okay I'll 12.8 on the par holy [\h__\h] but
yeah so you probably for Speed runers
somehow it should be possible you never
need the speed options the game can be
beat oh that hold up but I was about to
say that I feel like probably you could
if you're good if you have the good
timing and all that you could probably
go for the game with constantly pressing
the speed option I would imagine cuz
like how else do you get those times
what the hell for Speed Runners this has
got to be
possible but they say I don't have to
but then if if I don't then I certainly
will not reach the
par you can just use a glitch to
instantly
finish no no no I can't do that after
hearty fly
barbecue and an evening of reminiscing
about the old times the stage was set
for ghetto and B's adventure and froggy
waa they forgot about me but okay
skimming across the big pond to Plum
Town those Critters were out of the
training Pond what who's the Critter me
hey I have a question so there's two
frogs inside the tiny frog copter I
think it's probably bigger on the inside
and B is a toad for what it's worth okay
so
what
to I think I saw someone saying
something
funny like noticing German language
thing uh what was it a toad in German is
no not toad uh a turtle in German is
Shield which is Shield cro no not the
fry thing although that that was also
kind of
cute Shield told is turtle in German we
like German words don't
we uh wait did we
just wait did we do this
one yeah we did yeah we did yeah we did
Speedy not speedy not speedy not speedy
not not speedy oh my
god let's
go next
area Turtle cute so it confirms turtle
is
frog just like many other things turtle
frog dinosaur is also Frog as you saw I
can buy color now yeah but not the
Phoenix color I have to save the money
money you know or do you mean maybe
there's an inflation and one coin in the
in the maps is 10 coins in the shop or
what we'll check we'll check okay if my
calculations are correct this is the
right stream yeah guys you are right in
the right stream this is the right
stream welcome to the right
stream 10 10 times the charm Day St what
do you mean ah because it's already the
10th
[Music]
okay no
no holy [\h__\h] there's a coin there but
you can go no I'm not doing
[Music]
that I don't need that coin oh oh I can
get it with my tip no maybe not
uh do it I need to CL
it no let me
redo let me don't probably never going
to pull off the beginning ever again am
I no
[Music]
no let's go I
Cano chill oh
again
yo
[Music]
oh the golden one I don't know about the
golden one uh gold color sorry I'm color
blind no I can't no whatever go go go go
go go go go go go go go go
go yo I'm doing better though I got Full
Hearts Let's R plump down here we
go
W let's go it's my birthday happy
birthday oh I did get 20 coins from that
oh wait I'm getting way more coins than
I thought I'm getting oh inflation
inflation nice okay let's get Phoenix
color what is the German word for
pancake in in in German German it I
think people say p
which is basically
same
yeah but there's also flat pancakes AKA
creps but not quite creps there's a
difference but H we call them palach
chinking in Austria but I honestly don't
know how to even translate that directly
finish without taking a hit or quickly
will na be oh okay okay this time I have
actually didn't get hit let's
[Music]
go how many money I have P
chicken no it's kind of a weird
word Phoenix I could have F so you
s
you
you you
said
um I'm your number
one I'm I'm your number
one I getting tears in my
eye
because you
said unless any of these are references
to I'm your number
one let's go too bad she's dead too bad
she's
dead oh
where my
colors it's my colors it's
mine
fire three
houses that death is a real
one and that's literally my popsicle
sword
fir free houses this a million years
ago okay I love
[Music]
you this makes it so real like I mean
you know any of you
guys also you know but like when when I
this this like this is a moment where
like it hits me like I can play I can
just like ask for a random game you know
because it has frog in it and I I I I I
play game and then death in chat and
then Dev says they like Holo and then
Dev says W number one I'm going to
[Music]
cry
I need a
tissue
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I just kind of I think I need I
needed that
today and it came from a really
unexpected
source sorry it's happy tears it's
really happy
[Music]
tears you can see my
hand what the [\h__\h] happened I already
explained
[Music]
it it's happy
dears okay okay calm down calm down
calm
down thank you so much you made my
day chill chill chill do you remember
the festivals in Plum town do you think
they're still going surely because I'm
there oie do you as a reference to my
song no it's
not
o than for the memberships we got to get
them a membership we're going to get the
death a
membership oh yeah that was this time of
year right the food Vans were the
highlight of my summer as a toadlet
toadlet toadlet froglet I guess I guess
I was like is that a madeup word but
there's froglet so there's toadlet I
guess
cute ah you guys are so sweet a than
thank you thank you oh my god membership
let's go
frog
frog H music in the game we chicken out
and you never you chicken out and never
reached out you wanted H music in the
game I mean that would probably been
maybe difficult
cuz yeah cuz you you're yeah probably
that would have been difficult I I I
would assume because of copyright and
you uh this game being like you know not
under Holo label but still I appreciate
the f a
lot I still think about them most days
ready no let's
go
[Music]
yeah oh oh [\h__\h]
no do I have to go from ah above to
oh because it doesn't turn the other way
you always always turn that One
Direction and you know how much frogy wa
loves One Direction I actually don't I
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is
this what the [\h__\h] is
this
Fu okay here we go oh no
no
a this game is making me happy in all
kinds of
ways oh the music is so beautiful too
right now maybe it's good you didn't go
for Whole Life music I really like this
Vibe oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh first try
let's
go
much oh oh no no no I did
it
[Applause]
I did it let's
go
yeah that was so good that was so good I
got better I got better I got
better Pro Gamer did they get the
membership yet no at least a lot of
other people are getting happy today
too everybody gets me and you get a
membership and you get a membership and
you get a membership and you get and you
and and you and you and you and
you do you think that's where you get
your love for of food from yeah maybe I
just like the taste of food yeah we all
do don't we all
do k shimbo k
shimbo they may have a business account
oh do you do do you do you say Have A
Brand
account I mean sometimes it's really
just hard to get
them sometimes it really is just that
hard new things unlocked soothing Sunset
flight dead level that sounds very
nice it's a standard one where a very
small operation small small small but in
my heart
in my heart you're this
big because you make my heart
today go
beig not
small
big let's go wait this one let's
[Music]
go cute what is this the coyote over
what okay okay let's do this ready
steady
go
[Music]
okay no wait from
here no that was difficult I don't want
to oh
no it's getting really tight ah boys
Steven
ah hiy
stepen hello is this the way to Plum
Town sure I mean all streams lead to
Plum Town
eventually maybe so Plum toown maybe is
a a big lake yeah but why the rush why
not take it all in and see the
sights there is a heart over there H you
never know what you'll find of the
Beaten Track M oh man wait should we go
this
way would that make more sense I think
so
oh that was so unnecessary wa that was
so unnecessary wa I'll try
again of course y
It
Go
[Music]
y oh the music is really soothing indeed
yeah yeah we already talked Steven you
don't need to repeat yourself like
this return to Monkey waha no froggy
waha week not monkey waha
week yeah yeah yeah all right all there
special coins out my
[Music]
okay here we go we're going home boys
oh hey what's up
[Music]
uhoh
okay I feel like I could have done that
with full HP too going home today all of
this yeah yes we
are yes we are baby when is the monkey W
stre when I I feel like probably we
could easily put a monkey suit on this
model instead of a froggy suit the
music's lower quality was not intended
we accidentally converted it to MP3 Tes
twice and lost the originals and just
kind of roll of it it's fine I don't
really hear bad quality because I
just I can't really tell no can I
actually I mean maybe I maybe I
subconsciously noticed and just blamed
my my C capture
card or my current sound settings no it
really doesn't bother me I don't think
it would bother
anyone power Word level of deing hey
what the
[\h__\h] true death how can you lose the
originals
how fine
gem what's up with the
gem this the music is some fine gem is
that what you're saying I would agree
with
that are these tiny boats they're so
tiny hey now stepen just the heads up we
have a model boat race here every
weekend ah the boys are still out cuz
nobody really comes is that what these
things are called
boys really nothing nobody really comes
through here anymore I'd make a path
through for y'all but I think you'll
probably figure out a way pass him
quicker yeah sure bo boy uh boy ah in
German we say boy I think which I guess
is pretty much the same but we I think
we write it with
an maybe with an eye no maybe not I
don't
know w i don't say that I'm not Kiwa get
over it it's been 84 years anyway like
to say in the boat club I'm off to
finish making my new boat nice boat
maybe see you guys around such a cool
guy for real for real okay the
boys oh yeah I was like M can I really
already go turns out like I do it I do
it redo redo redo I want to redo redo
[Music]
I want to learn how to recreate that
sound wouldn't that be
[Music]
fun redo redo redo redo
redo I have so much legum again in my
throat now from
crying but it's it's been really watered
down my fum is way watered down these
days
hallelujah okay okay see I can do it I
knew
it yay woo wo that a close
one okay
uh I was chilling I was waiting do we go
from above I think we go from above a
sh well that that one's
tough that one's can you even make I
don't think you can make it can you
maybe U maybe that's just like uh use
your
tips why did I have to wait so long for
that one
[Music]
ehh yeah I don't think I'll go for it
this time cuz I already have the Phoenix
color so I'm already like done my goal
has been reached way earlier than I
[Music]
thought this is so relaxing too I really
like like
this what is this what is that what is
that
ah oh the heart wasn't there because I
was at full
HP now I know what that is uh
[Music]
okay what the [\h__\h]
man excuse me
what
huh
are you seeing this kfp are you guys
still trying to get them
[Music]
M
uh how how I guess slow down no but
didn't even
then
so are you seeing this are you seeing
this [\h__\h] this this
huh I'm going to get hurt and I'm going
to die a
[\h__\h] yummy follow the
[Music]
curve oh
man ah come on I fought
[Music]
you ready sty let's
go right
[Music]
move
okay and with that flow we go in one go
here we go oh yeah we're just moving
[Music]
through just let it
happen oh yeah she's feeling it with
Full Hearts
and like with no single care in the
world she's speeding through and now
here she goes she has free Hearts she
can do this with getting bonked it would
be no problem but can she do it without
no she cannot but that's okay we'll take
it as a
win oh or which direction will she
choose she will give up the coins
okay sometimes you have to measure your
chances of winning and losing and be
realistic about it she took two coins
with her anyway this one I think she'll
take from
below sometimes you got to look things
from the downside actually never mind
she changed her opinion because she was
wrong it's also important to admit that
you're
wrong to go further in life and mature
and Advance this is looking like a bunk
and it was indeed a bunk but she's happy
with her performance and she's reaching
the goal woohoo and she's celebrating
she's looking really
happy I just got l in my head cuz I
turned up the
earphones she made
it sure would be great if Mr yakam got
off my case and let me be creative with
my cooking ah let him cook let them
cook why won't they let them
cook she sh she's
go
that felt pretty good I think from the
POV of the death I think they made it in
a way that you should be able to go
through without even like stopping a
single time it should be possible and
that's probably the only way you get the
on par time so sometimes you just have
to believe the only important thing is
that within a narrow path you have to
find the right angle and follow the
stream like you know in a way that no
bunk of
course yeah but so it has to be possible
to do it without stopping and we saw it
here in action how the wa kept on moving
yeah eh we keep on trying to tell you
that you've been hitting below par which
is
good oh I'm not over part and Below
part ah wait if there's an X that means
I I I did do
it
oh
oh wait here I didn't do any of it oh my
God I'm losing my mind Hey but the last
one was
good wasn't the last one good
[Music]
I did do it on the part a few times okay
wait how much how much money do I have I
want to go shopping you can come back
and speed them later you you know me I
probably can't I probably not can't but
I mean I could but I need to spend a lot
of time with it okay I have I have only
37 coins no okay that's it's not enough
to buy
stuff can you only put one Hat on at a
time probably
right personally why is there a toad
head personally oh does it go on the
tips of the of the copter maybe even
personally I would love to have the cat
or the
dock U but the chef hat seems to be the
meta
that's a cockpit colors what what does
that ah the middle part
huh
not quite happy with what I got so far
[Music]
though
get chef hat is mandatory Chef makes you
instantly RN really okay let's go I'm
aiming for that here we go get Chef had
all the
way
yeah okay frogy waa would enjoy wearing
the de H the de hat the chef hat of her
dead
predecessor to make a
point hey look the Jenny is just over
there maybe I'm just I'm I'm I'm just
going go over there and set up a
campfire for tonight great idea I'll
just spin around and see you in a minute
wait you go in there look he's in the
beginning of the map he's not in the cop
[Music]
no no no no no
unacceptable look he's right there oh
did you see him how do you maybe I have
to wait
here didn't didn't feel right to go in
one
go go away go
away oh and with the tip
ah yep
yep Yap it Yap she Lov to Yap oh this
one is this one from the other
side maybe just a tip even yeah ah
[Music]
no I have a question for the Game
Dev when did you start developing this
game no
whatever when when did you start how
long how long did hold talk with
gamee let's go H talk with game
death which way do I
[Music]
go tra
tra no
I H talk wild gaming yeah I knew I knew
it I knew it I kind of knew it here I
get that Co at least to make up for it I
hope I'm not missing the answer they're
not green by now
right I made it took about 10 months
October
2021 did TW 10 months oh I guess yeah
it's been out for a while 10 20 20 2021
2021 did frogi Wawa exist at the
time a year after my
debut frog exist in
October not and frog did yeah
okay maybe subconsciously I planted the
Frog
seed in your
mind oh sorry I was just so happy I made
dead oh my god oh can I can I can
I oh my
God yo hi he's there already why was he
faster than me yeah I think she created
it pretty soon after M frog
M yeah
yeah that that really narrow path though
that was about the same narrowness of
the previous one where I was like that
is impossible and I did it I did it h
just some rocks no just a
box oh and some fireflies that does
sound pretty
cool where are the fireflies ah there
there if 10 million
fireflies go in my tummy tonight I think
I will blow up when I
sleep but I don't really care it was
worth it anyway I will eat all the
fireflies before I sleep
no that I can
eat frog
City yeah oh they're poisonous though I
forgot I
forgot they already TW oh they did ah to
tell me like oh hey there's that's maybe
that's why I was like oh yeah okay I'm
keeping this game for next year frog
week maybe I saw the tweet and was like
ah damn it I already planned out
everything frog games you must have been
waiting since last frog week
then I feel like I can remember seeing a
tweet like
that you must have been waiting like oh
my God when's next frog week when's next
Rock week when
when when play game of frog of me why
yeah you were really happy when you
said
sorry I gasped my own
spit that that makes me so happy that I
could like make someone happy who waited
so long for me to play their game oh my
God it was worth the wait right wait is
this a new one
yeah wait why am I I'm doing so well why
am I not getting de you have to lower
the bar why am I not getting the Speedy
eh Speedy Gonzalez why why why why what
the [\h__\h] is
this every day I beg for frog me too me
too I was begging every day I was in
that glass container may it be the bow
may it be the the other one aquarium
every day I was
begging to get out and kill
[Music]
her uh
the frogy
jar hey G what happens if we need to
spin the other way
oh that's a good point I hadn't really
planned for that can only spin one way I
guess if we Collide into something soft
enough to not damage the P paper mch
exterior but which was also bouncy
enough to trip out the
hysteric check on the onboard
microprocessor
what I figured
it might
cause totally original Mechanic it might
cause some kind of safe Mal function
where the Frog cter could operate at
negative polarity in free room wait so
are you saying that this just this
mechanism just starts from this level
because I feel like maybe at times I
already hit it softly enough that that
should have happened but it didn't
happen so now I'm
like how stop does it have to
[Music]
be got to test it out I need some
testing
grounds but where are we going to find
something as soft and bouncy as the oh
wait you oh you mean there's a specific
object ah I thought you can just hit any
wall okay M the spring over there
aha only special surfaces not
a I need to
sneeze
no no no no I'm good oh will fall into
the water okay okay I feel like we've
been in water all along
y i redo I can
[Music]
redo so
no too
close I would
do go next this is like Elden
ring no
whatever oh
okay no I don't like this no I don't
like this no no no no elen
p
no shut
[Music]
the what the
[\h__\h] why would I even want to switch
wait did it even switch there we go
there we go okay yeah yeah yeah this is
what I need yeah I don't think I was
switched last
time this is just like Elden ring yeah
it
is I
mean there do be some rage in both games
and and you know you you die and then
you retry so yeah I think I switched
twice mhm
it's an odd coincidence that you only
just mentioned the need for reversing
our spin Direction cuz it looks like we
might need need to make more of those
manuvers on the stream ahead I guess
life gives you a hint for stuff you need
to pay attention to it's just easy to
miss the hint as well you know cuz you
have to already be paying attention I'm
paying
attention I'm I'm paying attention I'm I
know I found I I
understood put those foolish and tourist
sure I'm very glad uh you're paying
attention okay thank
you I would like a refund though from
paying attention it's too
expensive oh oh thanks for the
coins did do you hear this smooth smooth
music oh it's time for a French snackbox
review
oh yeah now we're talking
oh oh my
God I
it no
no it was going so
well bye-bye
bye-bye
bye-bye here we
[Music]
go wait what am I doing is this right is
this right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah was
this
right no no
no cannot accept this
[Music]
outcome SM music smooth spin
smooth oh no that's not smooth why are
you here
now yeah all right time to switch
Direction here we go here we go here we
go watch this
oh oh
no did you see that oh [\h__\h] okay okay
okay okay oh oh okay
okay okay we need to be oh no I should
have committed I should have gone
through
anyway stop it we need to be
um what's the word parallel
parallel with the angle when we start
when we begin to go in slide slide like
I'm sliding into your DMs when I want
the PNG version of The Fan Art you
uploaded thank you very much apple
blossom
tea what is this okay think think
parallel think
parallel h
[Music]
no no my speeding
Gonzales is
gone what the [\h__\h] it scares me I want
to switch Direction ideally but it
shouldn't matter it shouldn't matter
what is
this okay oh you got to believe oh can I
do this what do you think guys I feel
like I
can she I got the big mommy I got the
big money in the bag let's
[Music]
go I'm so
happy I wonder if life is always giving
us hints but we only notice the really
obvious ones I think you're probably
right K gaming what do you think it's
saying now it's probably saying stop
bouncing around otherwise your brain
might fall out of your head no not my
brain not my one brain cell sure that
checks out yo that felt good that felt
so good yeah yeah it felt so satisfying
they let me
[Music]
cook it's bringing a tear to your gamer
eye can I lick your gamer
eye
yummy gamer
ey do not do this at home do not lick
each other's
eyes but it tastes salty I like
[Music]
yeah in Austria we like we like salty
things very much salt we love
[Laughter]
salt oh oh Sound Of Rain Sound of
Music I got all coins I got all coins
finally an X again
[Music]
yeah can I get the soundtrack please can
you send me that lowquality
MP3 just kidding you don't have to but
it's really nice it's really nice I want
to use it as a stream bgm ideally but
can only use bgm from games within the
stream where I'm streaming the game um
cuz copyright text and everything has to
be
[Music]
proper nearly there I think if we drive
for the night we'll get there by
Daybreak okay an all nighter let's do it
man I'm tired already we're just about
to start oh you uploaded them okay oh
[\h__\h] look listen
you hear the bunk
bunk oh I was like did you see my my
wing was inside the
wall but they forgive
me oh [\h__\h] I want to dance
tango to
[Music]
this sorry can I
redo see wait
eight bit drama get out of the way I
drum with my hands I don't even need the
sticks that you
use someone get me some Bongo assets
please thank
you man it B Dr I got nothing on
[Music]
me
[\h__\h] 8 bit drummer cover of Chima
yeah I he really liked the last one
which one which one was that was that
retrospective that he really
liked was it which one was it actually
I'm like I don't even remember CH
the I'm was tgw that that one that that
one he liked so much right he said like
it's like his top five of um whole life
songs which I'm
up very
honored yeah cuz he requested it
himself I would think you guys also were
requesting it but somehow I guess he
gets I guess he gets a lot of requests
so that why that's why he
didn't um he didn't get to do do it
until until that
[Music]
point yeah and like I'm
surprised that the
drums were harmonizing so well [\h__\h] what
am I doing the
tangent it sounded so good I think uh I
think he turned on some sound effect on
the drums too could that be so that they
sound a little bit different can you do
that like with the with a keyboard
keyboard uh piano keyboard that make the
pling pling sound you know what I
mean maybe yeah maybe he just put on a
reeverb or so but Reverb yeah electric
drums mhm is that what what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] de what the [\h__\h] was that
it's mean it's mean I was trying to
position
[Music]
myself how many levels does this game
have that's also a question question I
would like to have
[Music]
answered Phil Collins
what somebody said this is like
Spanish Spanish
guitar go into hint go into the Gap then
move out out and around the rock thanks
I would have known that
anyway no I I had a feeling now I'm just
chilling too much sorry sorry sorry
sorry
sorry we we we we we
we okay no I'm too chill I have to lock
yeah lock in gamer
brain
yeah yeah like I listen to other covers
from a with drummer oh I mean that's so
mean feel like I have to
wait because it pops up is it always the
same time like when the map starts does
do do they always have the same
[Music]
Rhythm
now okay yeah even with other songs I
mean it always sounds
cool but uh this one was like
particularly fitting which surprised me
because tgw is such a electronic
sound that I have felt like maybe drums
are you know is that what you meant is
that what you
meant I love that
[Music]
sound h
oh yeah I didn't get the first one oh
yeah I I want all the
[Music]
coins I'm going in yeah oh that feels so
nice it feels like I'm on a
canoe but I'm going that way with the
flow of the
[Music]
stream yeah okay well go [\h__\h] yourself
then oh from this side I
think now I'm going to redo it n
whatever going to redo it
I'm going to redo it The Vibes of this
game yeah the music with the art style
in combination and the fact that there's
frogs I mean that just makes it
[Music]
Superior oh yeah can she do it can she
do it in one go oh she's spinning she's
spinning like a crazy
frog let's go
no y y yeah she felt the
danger the danger
noodle no
no okay whatever should have gone
[Music]
through the boobies the booby trap it's
the booby trap in a literal
[Music]
sense oh oh oh oh I thought maybe I can
go back
no I should have gone full
[Music]
circle feels better anyway when things
go full circle
y you oh
oh should always be possible to go in
one floor what am I doing why am I so
waffly it was a technique guys it was a
technique that only professional
spiners oh
what can apply I can get it I can get it
without okay now we move on not wasted
some time but all is
fine um
this one's a fer but
okay you just turn on the
[Music]
blinker do not do do not do the puns
Wawa do not do them they're
[Music]
distracting why is this one this
color oh yeah full circle full circle
full
circle
oh I think it was just reflecting
[Music]
actually spinner
yeah in German that's an insult to
spinner spin is like oh you're crazy you
crazy
[Music]
person okay what what no that's so
mean heart
Challenger heart
restoration restor
ra what
the who who
whoa
what the [\h__\h] boy
boys the boys hold let the
boys out what I'm I'm thinking of a
girl's generation song n the [\h__\h] n me
the [\h__\h] this level is so
long oh my
[Music]
God end it
now yeah old one but how does it go it
doesn't go like who let the boys
out that's not how that girl generation
song goes ah bring the always out
something like Girl
Generation what
what we bring the boys
out my mind is too locked into the who
let the dogs
out
oh I'm too stuck on that Girls
Generation Can You Feel the
hit and then
and then what's the melody after that
that's where I'm like getting
stuck who who let the boys out
what that is that really the is that
really the lyrics
let let the
[Music]
boys go generation make you feel the
heat
okay
chill we're going to do this now cuz
even the bgm gave up on
me there it is but why I feel like the
boys show up in different
[Music]
timings it can't be the right surely
it's always the same timing when the
level starts you know what I mean like
it like it's like always the same Rhythm
it has to be but it feels like it's
not okay
[Music]
oh that one is so close in one
go all right all right all right all
right they have they do have their own
circle
[Music]
cycle you are ruining every speed
runner's
life why do they have their own cycle
but that explains why sometimes it works
and sometimes it
[Applause]
[Music]
doesn't that explains a lot it's not a
skill issue anymore it's a boy
issue W look at how small she
[Music]
goes and how stupid that Bonk sounds as
well it's okay I'll go with it because I
I do get a heart it's okay it's okay
it's okay I do get my
[Music]
heart refill
incoming oh my God oh my God that was so
close what the
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
okay what am I doing
what how was that forgiven I'm forgiv
I'm a villain I'm a oh
[Music]
no deserved deserved deserved deserved
deserved deserved
[Music]
deserved what the [\h__\h] what how I need
to spin the other way
death I need to spin the other
way no
huh what what what the [\h__\h] was did I
what
[Music]
D what the
[\h__\h]
I need can you coat in a bouncy pad
please just go for it
okay okay you are so
[Laughter]
[Music]
right
she damn she good she good good she's so
good she turned into monkey oh [\h__\h] oh
my God I need water Ed Ed Ed how did you
why did you bring up
Eden wow what made you say that I drink
I drink I drink and I think about
meaning of
life
[Music]
oh asking for the
death you can't see how my my cheeks
[Music]
go when are you FS on life
frog that's
all
yeah okay oh we're closer than I found I
think it's just over that Hill I
presumed we'd have heard the Bell Tower
by now B ha night night b
um I think I already asked this question
but I didn't see an answer how long is
this game can I finish
this how many levels are
there
Moss I got Moss for my sh
can I give to
am 60 to 70 level holy [\h__\h] I don't
think I can
know this is level there's no
number there's no number to the
level all
seven 67 sounds a bit
much for one quick
stream not going on the list no
I'll play again I'll play again we left
am out of the colors but found another
place for her the Moss am that's my
first shelf trinket some Moss balls that
promote a sense of well-being while
glowing ah some Moss balls that these
these ones promote a sense of well-being
while glowing gently they
glow sheesh microscopic Sports emitted
from this boss seem particular
particularly attracted to the Frog
copter exterior the resulting layer of
squashy
microscopic
sagum flum negates glancing collisions
with walls wait this actually does
something but it's easily scraped off
well suited to people who enjoyed
bumping into is it like an extra life
per
level but it's inside the copter I can't
see it I think I'm lagging
oh yeah I'm lagging a little bit wait
let me restart this
app it's
dying okay now it's
better so I think I got an extra life
now which
is am I allowed to
have like a bump bump excuse can I have
can I be
allowed
we are now in our first
town oh my God I think we can buy the sh
oh
really
POG lovely hats 100 yes we
can man I could I could buy some other
things but not the cat well I guess I'm
M the sh
H it looks
kute he's a
chef look he's a chef he's killed with
the chef had I'll give him that it looks
really good on him and he's not wearing
it like so stupidly like the Frog
detective yesterday in the middle of his
bumps no no no it covers his whole head
he just wears a big chef
[Music]
hat if he was using the small one from
from kiata then probably it would have
been in the middle of the bumps yeah all
right let's check out this
town what is this actually like a town
where I can like move around normally or
am I still speaking is this still a
challenge Rock detective slander oh it's
so
challenge okay Plum town is just up
ahead oh boy how exciting Che my beloved
yeah yeah yeah shouldn't I be your
beloved huh oh yeah music let's [\h__\h]
go the best music soundtrack I've ever
heard in my
life
what just stay calm and play the game
what the
[\h__\h] it
is over it's so
over
wait a moment what what am I doing what
am I actually doing somebody tell me
also what is this thing is that the plum
Mo what is
this did it actually work I don't
really I don't know if it worked it felt
overall a little bit weird unusual I
lost the heart though how does this work
how does this work
how does this
[Music]
work it works but it's not yeah I mean
but I don't even think it worked the
first time or did
[Music]
it maybe it did and I just got hit twice
in that
[Music]
moment no what the
[\h__\h] oh Sor I
did I think it might give you more
frames m
H when the circle fails you take a hit
aha so okay I get like yeah yeah
oh I see I see
now W that is very very very nice I
thought it only gives me like one free
bump oh this is
pretty this is
[Music]
nice yeah slow but steady don't go too
fast fast I like the reflection here oh
see how the frame saved my ass I think I
think it I was going to say maybe it's
like baby mode but considering how
difficult this game is probably going to
get considering all the levels it has I
think it's it's it's it's just like you
know
it's it's okay to use this right it's
been pretty helpful so
far now that I understand how it works y
see okay there it didn't work but I get
some hearts back
[Music]
yeah the amamos is my my lucky
charm oh I I like these Corners I kind
of got used to
them these kind of Corners these
circles oh and this as well yeah isn't
this a really nice level design
look at the reflection and the there was
a bench up there and now there's a light
up
there and
baby I adapted quicker than you
thought I'm a spin frog hey does
something feel a little off to you yeah
where are all the people m true where
are they there's no answer we just ask
the question and don't get an
answer okay
where are
they
who ah this makes it a lot
easier oh boy visitors welcome to F Town
Friends
dog
doggle I'm doing way better
yay hey did we miss the festival where
is
everyone there was a
festival ah yes oh well we haven't had a
festival about 20 years now Wow Wow
since I was a pup actually wow wow pleas
stop people C stop cing when then people
moved away wowow are there are there
food vs still here I can't read
anymore sorry Frank nobody really does
it anymore w w personally I kind of just
eat dog food wow oh no there's this one
cat that wants to start an ice cream
shop
W yeah hey yeah come on I'll show you
wow W better than nothing I suppose okay
ice cream oh he's he's spinning on my
helicopter
thing oh my God he's going to throw up
he's going to
BF cl cl cl cl
cl love the bgm right you see plumton
wasn't quite what the boys remembered it
to
be the world had moved on and Plum was
just kind of crumbling away like a plum
crumble h m is that a
dessert like an app Apple
crumble this is a bit of a depressing
story uh just like my life oh hush just
wait a minute it gets good again soon so
they met this cat called t a
cat that already uh cured my whole
depression yeah hearing about a cat
cured my depression so you are right it
gets better
immediately
oh okay ice cream giveaway wait are
these dots now all um pink does that
mean we kind of like are through one
chapter or so wait what is
this what is this colorful dot
above this one we don't have it here
what does this
mean can't yes I see do you
see do you see the cat it's staring at
us it has a
backpack New World new col ah so it's
kind of like I went for a chapter we
closed a chapter wow I'm so
proud I've come so
far the dog just St it's
cat hey h c visitors wow are you selling
your ice cream today w
I remember she's really
[Music]
shy can can you help me give out free
samples meow so that people W take me
seriously a business
on oh hey sure that sounds fun climb a
boly can you spin fast so I don't need
to look at anyone for too
long cute she's shaking now I have both
I have a dog and a cat does she really
need me to spin fast
though oh zero out of fourt what do you
mean was there a chance to give one out
now no right oh there you go take oh
cute yeah
cute oh
cute oh cute I did it
I gave ice cream to the
people what the [\h__\h] I deserve a bon for
that but that was
difficult thank you dear
Moss oh okay the dog can do it too all
right all right all right all right also
when you're there at those animals they
are
really uh they don't mind me bumping
into them apparently oh my God what the
[\h__\h] is it just me or is it really
actually spinning faster than
usual feel like they made my copter
faster oh my
god oh what what what the what what was
that can I get another
heart what is this I don't want to redo
this it is a bit faster
right Moss M
sauce H what is this what maybe what
maybe I go from
here
yeah there was a
frog hello fellow frog would you like to
take a
spin in my helicopter which is totally a
helicopter trust me what the hell what
the what is this
death this is very
Musashi oh my God so I'm almost ready
I'm almost
ready oh
oh
[Applause]
okay death death fou play
foul big Foul
Play
I could have avoided that if they
wouldn't have moved the camera away from
me
[Music]
certainly kind of
rude okay give ice cream did you give oh
okay okay okay okay yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
skiy oh oh take
[Music]
yes and here we go from the
top
uh-oh going from the
top yeah yeah okay okay looking
[Music]
amazing
sheesh I'm so good okay I deserve but
why did it have to happen after I
already got the heart oh wait I didn't
because I was at Full Hearts
yo
whatever
whatever I don't care I don't care at
all oh [\h__\h] oh sh oh
God no this one's so difficult holy [\h__\h]
okay be careful be careful be no
de what the [\h__\h]
de what the [\h__\h] at least I didn't die
this time but like you see what you have
done here do you
see I hear your eyes
open write this
down Mr defent yeah you see game def
[Applause]
hard you know what else is hard
my fist that will punch you in your
guts no I will
not I love I love
[Laughter]
[Music]
you my strong Hulk
fist
but
punch fuy W smash
abusive streamer
relationship I
redo I can indeed
redo oh wait I have to redo the
conversation too
oh
oh do it for til also try to touch the
last one further from the wall the last
one you mean another one that I didn't
see yet or the last one that I did see
further from the wall Yeah well yeah
well
well I may have been somewhat close to
the wall but it wouldn't happen if you
wouldn't like interrupt me like
this oh I could have skipped it
oh so generous
so
[Music]
generous okay
Mr be and one for you and one for you is
that Sakura
[Music]
trees sliding
FR like we're ice skating oh no oh no oh
no it's okay we'll get a heart what what
what am I
doing what am I doing ah now I'm going
to use up the heart
[Music]
already I'll take it I had to but then I
can't make any mistakes
here I'm
choking choking at least in a different
way from these past days I think I
prefer this kind of
choking okay I did it without taking any
more
damage
oh all right all right all right all
right okay here we are with Full
[Music]
Hearts wait yeah hook yourself in and oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh sh Okay Okay now what's
going to happen yo it continues to spin
though even in that
oh
I didn't get hurt this time but I
literally saw that it was continuing to
spin just saying that's not really fair
of
you try adding more
skill to the
control you little [\h__\h] you
little ity Bey tiny
[\h__\h]
are you saying skill issue but you're
saying it in a way that you're not
trying to blame me you're you're blaming
my
controller I see you're so
sweet
oh oh this is so pretty the cloes
hanging over the
[Music]
canal I did it guys and after I got the
heart I took no damage let's go I think
I might do one of those things you know
the smile here he
comes
breathtaking did we fall in love with
the
cat
understandable
cute
happy happy game Happy game clap clap
clap great job thank you than it all
I think so too like actually I'm getting
so good maybe this is my calling maybe I
found my
[Music]
calling and especially now that the cat
is
[Music]
involved okay at least I'm getting coins
in the recent
levels that's
[Music]
something now speed run
this
no
seriously what
good oh cat what did the cat always wear
that hat cute
frogs yes we are
frogs good observation Mrs kitty
cat I wonder if the if the Tilly is also
a pun on something like with the frog
names but I can't really think of
anything that it might be maybe it's the
name of one of the death scats that
would be cute the town is a hard part
the next World Forest this is where the
art like is really lovely
oh you're you're you're reeling you're
reeling me in you're reeling me in like
this like
this I said my controller skipped in I
would like to find a place to sell ice
cream forever you know
meow oh like a
restaurant yes meow ice cream restaurant
for
che I think that's more like a cafe but
okay okay let's take a good look for a
look for a good plots to set up shop
yeah skill issue with controller yeah it
was it was always the
controller oo oh this is
romantic the frog and the cat alone on
the
boat lovey
doy oh oh okay okay okay okay we're
still we're still in we're still in what
the
[\h__\h]
okay the
boat we passed it safely let's
go ah
[\h__\h] oh that's
beautiful what the I I have to go from
here I guess oh wait the music's
suddenly got
louder ah
ah I sent the cat spinning oh it got
louder again what is this is this me or
is this the game then is this my weird
sound settings I could totally blame
them you
know I want to redo I want to
redo maybe it gets louder every moment
her heart beats
faster
blame the game no I mean but like it
could really be
me and you guys hear the sound the way
it's current is currently messed up by
me yeah I think it's
me sorry game deaths for
misrepresenting your
sound yeah it's it's I think it's
me I I I I don't know maybe I'll
I need to fix my sound no it's me it's
me don't worry
ah but how is it more noticeable now
than before maybe it's this particular
type of music makes it more noticeable
thank
[Music]
you it's still beautiful even if it does
that wait what do I do what do I do what
do I do
here what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the what the
what what did I do I got to go from the
other side I can't force my way in there
on this
[Music]
[Applause]
side I need to
spin and look the other way
if I believe that I can spin my way
through this there is
nothing that I can
miss besides your
heart Mrs cat Mrs
Tilly
no okay now we go from here to
here wait where do you can I go under
that uh
plank yeah I must must be
able all
right frog bird
[Music]
moment whatever
whatever let's go again let's go
again
I'll do it over and over again if it
means I can spend more time with this
beautiful fluffy fuzzy kitty
cat and also she's throwing me off
emotionally and physically because she's
throwing off my frog cter balance now
that there's no dog on the other
side that's obviously the only reason
why I'm making mistakes right
[Music]
now okay I'll wait a little bit and
there we
go
easy SP spin SP Spin to
Win spin to win the lady's
heart yeah
yeah that's what I'm talking I'm I don't
have pain
patience I did not have the patience oh
[\h__\h] no no
no yes
yes are you calling her fat wait that
distracted
me I'll I'll oh I would have redone it
but okay somehow I survived that I was I
was kind of
purposefully pushing myself into that is
there a heart coming up or
[Music]
[Applause]
was the one from from Japan to Abu
Dhabi um you know I was I was in
business class and like frogs like me
usually
are um of course with takanashi ki's
money now that she's dead I can use all
her
[Music]
money and in business class they
obviously like they what the hell they
try to talk more with you and they they
try to
like make you feel like they care about
you and they call you by your name cuz
they have a list and
everything where your name
is on there oh God damn it I
need come on come on yeah
yeah okay sorry that was difficult
one Paris
social I don't know I wouldn't call it
par
social oh I guess last time I tried to
go uh back just backwards but now I'm
just going in a circle again which is
fine
too but it forces me to go here again H
well like buttering you up no not really
I don't really feel like she was
buttering me up but so I was like
sitting in my little
cubicle and before the flight takes off
already they come to your cubicle to
each person's cubicle there's several
cabin attendants that have like maybe I
don't know maybe five or 10 cubicles
that they are personally in charge of
doesn't mean that that cabin attendant
will always be the only
one takeing talking to you but
um yeah in the beginning at
least there's this
lady she comes up to me and I already
know what she wants because I'm used to
now
okay no I I'm I'm trying to flex because
it's not very uh often this was recently
I'm just getting lucky with business
class uh thanks to the company um and
and the certain occasions and in this
case they were saying oh because they
don't have premium
economy so we'll do you that favor
Takashi Kiana I'm like
okay so she comes to my cubicle and I
already know she wants to ask what I
want for fo later cuz there's already
like a fancy printed out
menu um that uh the cool thing with ety
hat I will say is they have dine on
demand you don't have to eat at the same
time as everybody what the [\h__\h] I was
kind of stuck
there um you can choose to eat whenever
you want and so they ask you like when
do you want to eat and um
there's a lot of
choices so they ask you what do you want
to eat and I choose my course but before
that she says my name she's
like wait Plum she's like with a really
nice
pronunciation she says my also very
German Austrian name Taki
Kiara which now for this purpose oh yeah
SAR let's say SAR of course because I'm
famous and I want to stay Anonymous I
don't want people to ask for my
autograph and all that so I of course I
check in as Sarah Gutenberg yeah you can
totally do that on airplanes too fly
Anonymous no you cannot but let's say
let's just say I uh flew in the plane as
Sarah Gutenberg
and if if you
were like English speaking or any other
language you would probably be like
unless you have a language as your first
language is kind of like German based
you would probably be like uh if you're
English you know English speaking You'
be like Sarah
Gutenberg most likely and I would know
mhm I I would understand you are
not speaking my
language but this lady she crouches down
she looks at her list she looks at me
and she says and and welcome on board
Miss Sarah
Gutenberg she says it so nicely and I
immediately I was
like you you pronounced that so well I
said that to her immediately cuz it
really stood out to me that it wasn't
just a good pronunciation it sounded
like she speaks German but I was like in
my head I was like no way but let's just
say you have a really good pronunciation
I'm surprised and then she's like yeah
because well because I'm Austrian and
I'm like what you're
Austrian and I think she like
purposefully um assigned herself to me
cuz I'm also Austrian she knew that I
was
Austrian and she told me that she was
Austrian after I um told her about the
pronunciation being so
good and now the reason why that
surprises me is because like it's ety
head Airways that's that's not an
Austrian Airline at
all but the crew I I noticed I talked to
her
later she told me cuz I I asked if
there's like if there's like her if
there's a lot of other foreigners
working for the airline and she said
yeah like pretty much
95% of the cabin attendants of the
airline are not from there they're from
all over the
world and it it kind of just happened
like that I think it's because just like
Emirates and so on there's certain
airlines that like get all the like
foreigners um because they have great
deals where they they pay for a like a
luxurious or somewhat luxurious
apartment she told me that they have a
pool and all that so that sounds
luxurious to me but in a video of
someone else who works for Emirates I
saw there was no pool and their
apartment was like but anyway they pay
on top of a real pretty good salary they
get like expenses
like of course their apartment paid and
all that and I asked her why does she
doesn't she work for Austrian Airlines
why does why didn't she consider that
and she said well first of all the pay
is way better with etad Airways than
with ausan Airlines but then also
because she didn't really intend to work
for an airline in the first place it
just kind of
happened n she so basically I'll just
tell this tangent and then we can move
on basically after she told me that like
we were vibing okay I was so happy and
like we decided to just speak German
instead and she was really nice I really
I really enjoyed talking to her we were
vibing and she was taking good care of
me and then um after a while I couldn't
sleep anymore so I got up to like blow
my nose and get a
snack so I went over there where the
cabin attendants are chilling and I saw
her and she's like oh so how you doing
how you feeling did you get some sleep
and I'm like nah not so much but you
know and we chitchat and I ask her all
about everything she asks me what I do
and I ask her like how many times have
you been to Japan and like this and that
why do you why didn't you work for Edy
had Airways and she told me out because
of a guy that she broke up one month
after she moved to uh Abu Dhabi for him
I'm like hey yo what the [\h__\h] and then
since then she's still been a cabin
attendant for 7even years and I'm like
oh wow I thought usually the the the how
to say turn over for cabin attendant is
was pretty bad cuz like it's really
exhausting I'm surprised you do it for
so long BL blah blue we talked so
much I really I
[Music]
really I really liked her so you're
saying she's single I don't know if she
was single no actually I think I
do yeah I think I I think we I think we
went to that point in the conversation I
think we got there she told me I think H
that there's like no no
time yeah did she have a crush mightbe a
little bit yeah she was very charming
and sweet and I don't know it's just
something about like randomly coming
across another Austrian that made me so
excited yeah
yeah so I'm just telling you had a nice
a
nice faithful meeting with a Austrian
and I was so close to asking her for her
number I didn't austrians are pretty
rare exactly like when I heard her
pronunciation I was thinking like maybe
she's German but there's no way she's
Austrian you know but she was Austrian
out of all the things there's there's a
couple countries where you could have a
you know a good German pronunciation
from the r Wawa oh she was I think she
was enjoying to talk to me
too yeah okay sorry about
that she was so
nice now I almost want to fly ety head
again just to meet her again but the
chances are really freaking
low cuz of how many
flights there are and how many flight
attendants there are but she did say
that she tries to get um ah assigned to
the flights that go from ababi to
Austria as much as she can although in
this case she was just in a flight from
Japan to abudhabi yeah but she told me
that they all live in Abu Dhabi of
course cuz that's where the airline is
based but she told me there's like
nothing to
do she told me there was nothing there's
nothing to do there like she gets kind
of bored that's her her problem she
feels kind of lonely that's what she
told
me like she feels like the one thing
about her job it's not so much that
being too exhausted from the flights and
all that is is the problem I mean that's
that is a fact that is a problem but she
doesn't feel like it's much of a problem
for her personally that was your
opening was
it she said there's not much to do
because I guess it's hot and all that so
besides like going to shopping malls and
going to the beach and going to the pool
what do you mean that was a
sign no it was
not you
guys she's into men okay she told me
about a
guy n k I didn't fumble I did
not can do
[Music]
never I don't know if I have give up
attitude there's a lot of times where I
feel like I really want to give up and I
really want to throw everything away but
then then my mind goes back to I can't I
can't I can't even if I want to because
I just don't want things to end this
way I want things to end in a more oh
not again in a more positive
way yeah um what was I saying though
yeah the the fact that you know there's
maybe not so many activities cuz of
shopping malls and that's the thing that
the ID members told me too about ID at
least in in
Jakarta
all like because it's so hot outside
there's like you know not much bearable
things you can do and a lot of people
they just like hang out in the malls all
the time and that's so interesting to me
cuz like the only time I hung out at M
was when I was a teenager and like I was
really excited about getting my pocket
money and not being in class anymore in
the afternoon or on the
weekend and then I go to the mall a
little bit to get a
smoothie and maybe buy a new accessory
or something like
that but besides that oh God yo what a
mean
Corner no I I've been I've been drinking
movies aggressively for many many years
feeling called out here T
really I think I a never give up mindset
doesn't mean you never think about
giving up is that you push forward
anyway yeah I mean that's
me that's me I used to live in Las Vegas
and it's the same there in the summers
oh I can imagine I I hear I hear it gets
very very
hot you got to consider that roads are
not built to be walkable so the moles
are kind of like this they're not built
to be walkable you mean they have no
sidewalk or
so I was actually pretty interested
you're from Abu Dhabi right I was pretty
interested when I uh when I was arriving
on the way to Japan when I was arriving
in Abu Dhabi I was paying quite a lot
attention to the outside I was looking
outside the window a lot and the zoning
the zoning was really interesting to me
because like it all seems like and she
told me the same thing it's like a still
if you think about it that way it's a
relatively new city they're still
building a lot and I see like these huge
squares of where in like one square
there's like a million okay not a
million but a few hundred or hundred
buildings houses big houses that are
completely dark no one lives not a
single house out of those 100 in that
one square where the street are making
it into a square are um like I it feels
like none of them are rented out and
then there's other squares which are
fully went which makes me feel like
probably they're all like made by the
government maybe and then they rent it
out in like chunks so that could it be
that there's like a lot of areas where
the whole area not a single person lives
there and it's just constantly
dark yeah built but not sold and they
when they sell it maybe they try to like
sell out certain areas first before they
start selling another area where then
only one person will be living in like a
100 house houses section or so that's
like Dubai too some pieces are just
empty and decaying decaying
[Music]
too it just looked kind of funny to me
from the air looking down because then
it was really noticeable that there will
be big chunks of houses there the nobody
has a light on so they're all
empty all nationals are entitled to land
who that's yeah I I heard about those
kind of laws that's pretty sick
[Music]
so a lot of Billings
are that's pretty
interesting yes this is it drop me off
here meow you Franks come over anytime
when it is finished she's so cute G
Tilly is giving me the cras what no okay
I'll keep her for myself then what the
hell but she does make good ice cream so
I guess that's a good train off how does
she do it without thums guys how does
she do it oh sorry
[Music]
as a marriage gift from the government
you get a house and land and stocks holy
[\h__\h] I mean
she when I was in Abu Dhabi I made a lot
of German
tourists I recently watched a video
about I think it was about Dubai but I
feel like that might be partially the
case in Abu Dhabi too about like certain
contract s like they really want people
to live there they really want people to
move there especially influencers they
give them like special contracts they
let them live there for free and they
let them pay like no basically no no
yeah they want people to live there so
bad like so bad but then the the
trade-off is you get to live there for
free you pay no taxes and all that as a
influencer but then when you make
content and all that that has to be all
positive all positive
you can only talk positive about your
experience
there what a deal I mean cuz you get to
live pretty luxuriously
too yeah yeah yeah yeah they also want
to keep all the locals in the country
instead of
[Music]
out
damn interesting interesting Logistics
interesting clap clap
clap but a lot of YouTubers do that I
feel like especially like German
speaking influencers and YouTubers are
very drawn to that
[Music]
auor or maybe it's my imagination but it
feels like a lot of Germans are going
there
they love they love the luxury AO boys
Stephen you're back let's
go coral island huh I feel like I played
that yeah all Steven what are you doing
here this is where the model boat
championships are being held in a couple
days I'm just here to test the course oh
more boats hey what would you guys say
to testing out the route H sure why not
all right I'm not a boat but I'm the
perfect test
I'm a game
tester I find
bugs all the time no just kidding I
honestly I never find bugs but maybe
it's just because the games I play
usually have no bugs it's just
yesterday was an exception what the
[\h__\h] oh h no let's redo
it find bug eat bug frogy W game
tester
[Music]
what Asian Asian beetles the ladybug
that I vacuum up what
oh what are you talking about real life
you're not talking about a game ride
you're talking about how I vacuumed up
beetles with the
stocking that's what you mean
[Music]
right yeah the
infestations
[Music]
yeah there's certain times in the year
where certain bugs are speaking of
bugs today I I met I'm a
be no what the [\h__\h] whatever what I
don't
care doesn't face me at
all what about the heart wait was I not
supposed to go here
first
and maybe you're supposed to go back and
done here yeah so I'm at amab
today I don't know
how but an Amma be actually not an I'm
is I'm a bumblebee or
be what do you think also what the hell
oh my
God am I going the right way wait what
was they so many paths what the hell
where is the right
way I like to think she's a bumblebee
I'm is just amab
bee am is Ami she's I mean Ami is pretty
chunky this is really confusing
me it was really confusing I don't know
where to go but okay I'll go this way it
has to be this way but
[Music]
then
what the
[\h__\h] to redo this anyway
[Music]
probably she's she's so chunky so I feel
like maybe she's a
bumblebee but and then
again she could also just be a normal
bee she called her
fat I still I still love the the picture
of the moment of frogi with AMI when Ami
is so small on my
nose but yeah so somehow I'm pretty sure
it was a bumblebee somehow a bumblebee
landed like on my territory yeah and my
cats noticed it first and it was it
didn't fly away it it was on the
ground seemingly stuck and I'm like what
the [\h__\h] and I I I the moment I noticed
I'm like go away go away Kos I don't
think you should touch the bee sounds
dangerous to
me so I I'm like go go go
sh
sh and I noticed the The Bean Is like
having troubles taking off it's like
making
these
noises and
vibrating but it's lifting up one leg
weirdly and I'm like what's what's
happening what is is wrong with this
Bean so I I was like observing it for
quite some
time it was
misbehaving it was kind of misbehaving
because it wasn't behaving the way a bee
should behave
yeah
amazing
amazing oh no what the what is
this huh
what was that def what was that explain
yourself yeah and while I was
watching um the bee and trying to keep
the cats away especially chunkers with
like she's she's normally a shy cat but
she's so brave when it comes to uh bugs
and stuff she would like like weasle
weasle weasle quickly weasel her way
over to the VG thinking she can like
take a punch punch punch or so but I'm
like no no go away go away don't touch
the be you might get yourself
hurt so I push her away and she like go
back and then again she's like Wile Wile
weasle weasle slowly weasel slowly
weasle and then Zoom fast weasel but
then I push her away again I'm like no
junkers bad junkers bad
junkers yeah she's hunting she's so
cute smie was also interested but
choners really wanted to sweat sweat
yeah choners really wanted to send the
SWAT team but I was really worried about
the bee I really wanted to help the
Bumblebee but I didn't know how and it
was kind of weird because the the wings
were definitely
intact but it was like kind of lifting
its leg the whole time and and like I
don't know it seemed stuck so I thought
maybe the leg was broken but they don't
have bones so I don't know how that
works but
I I waited a while and finally it was
able to like put its leg down and then
immediately it started it tried to take
off uh but then it couldn't it like
immediately fell it tries to take off
and then it doesn't get like high at all
it just falls down and tumbles and
stumbles again and tries again and again
and again I think something with the leg
was wrong because the the the wings
seemed fine but this whole time it was
like vibrating and the the fluffy butt
was like like
breathing vibrating and and pulsating I
was like wo I've never seen a bee and a
bumblebee so up close for so
long it was really really struggling and
I wanted to help but I was also scared
because
bumblebee so cute but touch I think is
dangerous I didn't see
a um a a uh a stingy stingy
thingy what you call it I didn't see now
the pokey pokey
thing maybe do they lose it's do
bumblebees lose its Pokey
thingy when they poked something
before
they die if also maybe maybe that's what
was
happening but maybe it's just not always
that
obviously like out there maybe maybe it
was just retracted I don't know but
maybe that's why I was dying I don't
know H it was weird I was really weird
and and we were all I was watching for
different reasons I guess than my cats
but we were all very interested I was
watching for like 15
minutes eventually it it waddled
[Music]
off I had to keep my cats away
actively not all Bumblebees are stingle
Oho some are eh sting is connected to
their inside so their insides go with it
when they sing
Oh it really makes you wonder why
Evolution over over time has not
improved the way their Body Works what
the
[Music]
hell anyway sorry for the tangent sorry
de sorry but you should probably you
probably you know my streams so you know
you
know Well Done boys you did a great job
guess what you're honorary model boat
club members now let's go and bumblebees
don't die from stinking only bees oh
yeah I feel like I heard something about
that that only only one particular type
dies from that and I guess that's just
the basic B
type oh thank you Stephen it's a dream
control
kid apparently they're not supposed to
sting humans our skin is too strong oh
they don't die if they sting all of oh
really wait does that apply to bees or
or also like bumblebee is that
cl cl
clap what level are we so far I don't
know we're in the the the the the town
chapter but it doesn't have numbers so
we're in colorful bunting
now
yeah let's
go Bumblebees are different to honeybees
unlike honeybees a bumblebee does not
die after stinging and can sting more
than one once similar to a
wasp they don't expect to die it's just
we're we're built to thick skin and so
when they pull back they accidentally RI
out I feel so bad now I feel so
guilty why have they not learned this
they need to write it down and pass it
down along the generations that you
should not sting a human because it will
hurt you and then we would all be much
happier we don't get stung by bees
anymore and they don't get hurt anymore
that's great that we met Steven again
and you got to eat all that ice
cream but I still feel strange about
being in Plum town again it doesn't feel
like it used to kiddo yeah it's like the
town Soul has gone to sleep kiddo like
have you noticed the bell tower isn't
Charming anymore oh that's because I I
took a break I'm I'm the Bell
chimer
ding sorry I went on vacation sorry
that was me my fault I didn't even leave
a a
notice sum Mustang for the
confusion
ah okay okay
okay oh too late restart I want to
restart steady let's go
oh okay
[Music]
okay
what life is not
fair spe is not
fair okay here we go frogy waa is
getting serious
again oh my God what the hell is that
can I redo
Sim stopping music yeah that's like my
favorite music
genre oh my God can you give me your
composer email
address oh come
[Music]
on I cuz audio doc has like everything
except proper Sims
Music I looked it up several times but I
just can't find something like Animal
Crossing music I can still find Animal
Crossing esque music at
least what how
explain
huh what the hell
man it's like BOS NOA yeah yeah so I
think I I I did get something before
that is kind of simses and that was
basically just bossan NOA
category it kind of gets pretty close
[Music]
yeah okay I know this one I can do I'm
capable of this one then this one gets
like really
questionable
oh yeah I did it but it's really
difficult okay okay okay okay okay ban
NOA is such a Vibe for
real for real for real I want bosan NOA
remixes of my
songs oh this is so
chill like I feel like you could have
gone a completely different direction of
the
bgm with the soundtrack and go like make
it really stressful wait I Gotta Go From
Here make it really stressful with like
your beat or some other like stressful
kind of music with a exciting beat and
BPM you could have done that and it
would have worked but it would have been
a very different vibe obviously oh it's
a
fox hey did I hear you guys talking
about the clock tower yes sir
we see the CLP Tower is as old as the
hills nobody remembers building
it but all we know is people stopped
coming to visit about the same time and
that the clock tower stopped CL chiming
I'm not a superstitious Fox but I feel
like that had something to do with it
that seems
plausible anyway how rude of me people
call me the mayor on account of the fact
that I am the mayor woo let's go
congratulations we don't get many
visitors these days but Joel tells me
you're causing some excitement with your
spinny FR topper
thing nice to meet you mayor Fox it's
called the frock copter
yeah we're here to
spin they all love my frog cter I think
in the future we will see a lot of
people using this as their choice of
movement especially when the sea levels
are rising and more and more cities are
getting
flooded is when this will be the
solution to all your
problems trust
[Music]
me
yeah checks out right
[Music]
yeah the moldes don't don't talk about
the mold Lees sinking that's so
[Music]
depressing fascinating hey do you think
you could show me some moves of that
froggy copter of yours it's a frog
copter not froggy copter but okay I like
it though I like
it suddenly the ocean Rising doesn't
seem too bad yeah we get to go with a
frog copter I mean that that sounds fun
thanks for the
pinky okay how about we do a tour of the
docks
fun is that a word oh here's a little
trick you got to grab these Keys that's
the only way to open the harbor
doors okay okay let's
go I I I can float no froggy waa cannot
swim very well yeah so
what I'm still a rock star I got my rock
moves and I don't need you and guess
what I'm having more fun and now that
you're
done I don't need you
tonight I'm all right I'm all
fine I'm
pink spitting bars yeah those were just
copied I didn't I didn't come up with
them
[Music]
I'm green no I'm
pink and edgy at that because with an
exclamation mark oh my
God an exclamation mark instead of the
eye makes everything so much
cooler so [\h__\h]
edgy oh [\h__\h] no I could have done it no
Dam it
I I kind of I don't know I don't know
what happened there I don't know that
was not big
[Music]
performance you know speaking of ladies
that uh are like so to say working for
me that I really like where am I
going remember the lady that I asked for
a
hug in the store
[Music]
I feel like in the in the three weeks
that I was
gone maybe she quit her job because I I
I can't seem to to see her
anymore maybe she was all just in my
head but there's a different lady now
that doesn't doesn't look quite is nice
to
me I missed the other lady
um I need to check I need to ask them if
she quit because it makes me really sad
if I can't see her anymore bring her
back bring her back wasn't a dream I
can't believe she like would just leave
me like that she should have told me if
she was gone in these three weeks she
would have known already that she was
quitting right and she should have told
me I think she would have told
me and maybe she's on vacation I don't
know but the new girl is definitely new
oh sorry but in the right hands it has
such a style and finesse hey thanks
mayor what my frog
copter it's time to wake up no I'm sure
she was
real I miss her I miss her I miss her
smile I miss
you new girls just don't nro's hugs just
don't hit the same I didn't try to hug
her
though wasn't she no that was a
different very nice lady from a
different store that lady was really
nice but I also kind of stopped seeing
her so yeah
she's probably busy with her
baby she she might have quit
actually oh I'm done I'm I'm in the
forest now that you said has a really
nice art
Aesthetics yeah looking forward to it
bye-bye cat I think I I'll I'll I'll try
to go a little bit through the forest I
might not finish
it but um going to check it out wait
wait that doesn't look like a forest hi
me
again okay one more one more to go grand
opening of 's ice cream restaurant me
now oh really okay well let's go to see
it this way frogs frog is capitalized
wow we're that
important look at her R cute
outfit the pink backpack and the pink
hat she's so French so
[Applause]
beautiful what is this other
path maybe for going back if you missed
a
[Music]
coin yeah going well so far oh oh
oh thank you Moss no
that sent me
spinning I'll accept it though I I could
have done without
that but I was cutting it a little bit
too close there I got stuck and I got
too far to
[Music]
retreat left or right uh I think or down
ah I think up
here oh God oh God no what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay no what the [\h__\h] I'm ready to
die guess I'll
die we've gotten so much better you say
that while I'm making all these mistakes
I kind of want to sacrifice myself but I
I I'll look I'll look further ahead to
see what's waiting for
[Music]
me oh [\h__\h] I went the wrong way it was
downwards
yeah it I may have been next to the
heart but you can only use it once I
[Music]
think but yeah at some point this is
just smooth
sailing in the beginning I was like how
the [\h__\h] do I do this but then you just
kind of ah what am I
doing we got to go from
here I guess you could go both
ways uh but yeah feels like once you get
the hang of it it's pretty chill I
wonder if it gets much more difficult
though are there still some some
pages where I lose a heart or
two and also you got to consider I'm
using the Moss
which she's
cooking
oh
feel like I'm I'm in a fee park right
now oh
[Music]
god oh I don't even need the heart feels
kind of
wasteful wow now which way do I go
though H we said this way I think wait
no can I
though I feel
like I know it has to be this way yeah
oh
what
what what no that that path is so weird
but then it makes sense once you reach
here it just makes
sense yeah you you're supposed to go
that way but I cannot seem to find my
way through it it's okay losing one
heart is
okay I wish it would have been
before I passed the heart though
think you're getting better of course I
[Music]
am praise me
more more oh that's it
chill really chill I thought this would
be a more stressful
game oh she's happy briefing
again say say boys I have a preposition
for you you know that Old Clock Tower
say no more mayor let's take a look oh
in the Frog copter what do you mean how
am I going to fix
[Music]
it I'm going up to the top of the tower
to take a look I got a lamp go to the
garage to equip okay can I have more
than one thing
equip this fox sounds like
to excuse me my my voice r repto is
limited oh there's another like an extra
level there
ah can I have
more than
one drink
it I
think bathing in uh life love wait is
that a love life
reference Bing in the warmth of this
lamp rejuvenates health slowly
oh naturally is as it is powered by the
rotational action of the Frog copter it
affects scale with
speed oh so if you spin faster you'll
get Hearts back
faster you can just like stay in the
same place then and load them up
no oh oh life love love that's a that's
a thing that people
say I don't know they they both sound
very good if I can only have one then I
don't I think I'll stay with the Moss
for Amy for Amy sake by the way I have
enough money to buy a new I can buy the
cat oh I become the
cat holy [\h__\h] guys but it's frog
week
this is amazing though if it wasn't frog
week I would do
it I a damn it I thought maybe the cat
will be on top of me or
something should we start cat
week cat for one level okay okay that
that seems
reasonable and then Japanese pun
incoming after the nickel i k to K I go
back to frog because it's the same word
it's just written differently but you
[Music]
know oh [\h__\h] it's
a you know and and
D maybe translated as pun but I think it
normally means um when you make like a
pun with like using the same
word a different word but like using you
know just like what I just
did ah what the hell is this
beginning okay okay okay
okay heavy breathing cat yeah word play
word play yeah yeah yeah yeah D is word
play basically yeah yeah yeah oh
no a cat themed week with cat
info yeah well I don't know we don't
want to do like too many personas oh I
mean I love that with
a but I think uh I'm fine with just
like one or two personas I kind of want
to do a crab
person I feel like I would be so cute
cuz I love crabs too and I am am crab am
crab
indeed yeah and I feel like it would
look so cute If instead of this green
suit I wear I wear red
suit I do be crappy often but I'm I also
just mean I am crab because I am Cancer
sign that reminds me you know I told you
right that I watch this like Channel you
going to make fun of me blah blah blah
is this channel is YouTube channel that
makes a lot of different kind of videos
but they're like all pretty like in
Japanese we would say
ruo YouTube content what am I doing what
the [\h__\h] man ah let me out of
here yeah the dating one and they have
like this dating show right where they
do like speed dating they they film
people speed dating there's a button in
the middle of the table and it lights up
red sometimes and the people can press
it if they don't like what they're
seated against which is quite often they
press the button quite often but anyway
like the newest
episode there was something really funny
there's this like pretty mature looking
lady um and she's paired with a I think
he said he was
18 and they definitely were not a match
they didn't look like a match at all and
they were not vibing but they were
having an interesting conversation
because of them being so different
and they uh somehow get into the topic
of whether or
not he might be an alpha male like she
asks him if he's an alpha male or or not
or like I think she was like you're not
an alpha male hor or something like
that and and then he's
like he's like nah I I don't really I
don't really care much but he's like you
know spiritual astronomical signs and
all that but I I was born in April and
like so
[Music]
funny he he didn't know what the word
Alpha meant he fought he just assumed it
was like one of those like what
something
rising star sign whatever I don't really
know these things at all either but it's
so funny because both both of these
words are just
stupid bless him yeah it's so good
though it's so good astrology for men
Alpha
better that's actually a good sign that
he doesn't know well like but like even
if you don't
know or if you don't care for
astrological not
astronomical did I say astronom
astrological right as astrological signs
and all that like I would still like I
don't know the meaning of them and I
don't care for them at
all but it's fun interesting how like
especially if you're young I feel like
you have higher chances of knowing what
Alpha and better male means than an
older person I feel like it's like kind
of like you know internet Zumer not
quite Zummer lingo but what is
this huh
[Music]
whatever I'm surprised that a younger
person doesn't know rather than let's
say someone who's like I don't know 60
or 50 I don't know
death what the [\h__\h]
Dev what the what what the [\h__\h]
Dev welcome to ah it's a bonus level
that's why it's like
this yeah but like no no blame of not
knowing that it's just the funny and I
like the conclusion of thinking it's an
astronomical thing astrological
as wait now I'm getting things mixed up
too wait
what I never heard of Alpha and better
until very recently you don't think it's
Millennial but he wasn't a millennial 18
is not being Millennial right 18 is
uh astronomy science astr okay
astrological then okay okay okay yeah
yeah yeah H they also they also have um
these videos where although no that's
Jubilee Jubilee is a very similar
Channel okay um but they have more like
videos that like debate things and they
they had a debate um like where it's
like five s no maybe three or four
astrological
people who work in astrology and then
five no four probably four
astronomical
people and they were debating you know
about their legit
legitimacy oh God all these words about
each other's jobs and um I'll go this
way thank you
bye and yeah it was really funny cuz
obviously like the science people you
know they know they're doing science but
the the non-science people they thought
they're doing science
[Music]
too I think you know as astrology is
nice to have in your life and if you
want to like you know have fun reading
your horoscopes and all that that's fine
that's fun like I I enjoy reading a
horoscope every once a
year but I I used to read it more
often um but like you have to read
realized it's
not uh science you know it's not science
it's
fun and I don't mind you
know somebody who
although it gets so confusing and so far
I made it when they're like what what
the [\h__\h] is this about rising and like
then they're two star signs why why are
you two star signs I don't
understand I don't get it that's too far
[Music]
h no yeah definitely harmless fun I
don't mind it well like holy [\h__\h] what
are you talking about I can follow you
to the point of saying the Cancer sign
is emotional I totally agree I am I am
so
emotional I agree with
that yeah but like yeah it's so funny to
me yeah the the like some people who
really into that stuff they're
immediately like um like first of all
they assume your star sign based on your
personality which I thought assuming
things was not cool but often they are
right interestingly and then they say oh
I can't date you because you're that
star sign H give it a try but I mean
they must have had a lot of bad
experiences with that with that star
sign
yeah I so so
funny that's also a case in these dating
show videos like they they'll ask each
other it's each star each other star
sign sometimes and then they're like oh
okay press the button beep sorry I'm I
cannot I cannot deal with you because
you are whatever a
Capricorn or [\h__\h] Taurus
ew uh sorry we're not compatible and
frog Pisces
[Laughter]
[Music]
ew I mean I have to agree like the
cancer things kind of apply to
me people are so judgmental everybody
says cancers are emotional and I mean
it's kind of
true kind of
true I was of a cancer for 5 years L she
became a cancer in the end
[Applause]
hey that's so
mean okay mayor fox says the clock tower
is in the middle of these Woods we're in
the woods
now I think now might be a good time to
crack out a small addition to the Frog
copter oh [\h__\h] what's happening really
also by the way we haven't seen those
like bouncy pads in a
while where did they go never feel my
good CH let me introduce you to my ultra
handling from C widget here all we got
to do is grab that little guy and all
will be revealed okay I can't
wait okay let's
go the death puts them in forgets about
them no more bouncy pads no more bouncy
pads for you WWA
no I often joke ask people about their
sign and they say you no matter what
they
say no J we kind of
did you forgot about him you forgot
forgot these here are grabby arms
oh interesting they look like bugs to me
oh they look great what do they do well
see K kinetic kinetic kinetic K kinetic
kinetic K kinetic kinetic right energy
is stored Within These spring loaded
foam doas and when we press a we can
release all that pent up energy
triggering a chain reaction of pulley
and
wheels effectively extending our reach
by several centimeters and capture
whatever objects are within the grabby
Arms Reach like coins okay we'll we'll
test it out but like that sounds
difficult we'll see we'll see kinetic
okay what is this it doesn't even go as
far as I thought it
would
ah oh wow
okay
interesting
interesting we'll see how that
goes yeah but I just want to say no hate
to people who believe in star signs and
all that generally as I said I I like I
enjoy it too a little bit is interesting
to me it's interesting to me to listen
to that
too I do think it's maybe a little bit
like a waste to rely on it too much and
like make make uh your love life too or
like your life decisions too dependent
on it
though you could be missing out on on a
really great love life
maybe depending too much on it but I
mean it's your life if you're having fun
with that then you do you you do you
yeah okay so I think this is the right
way maybe we should ask someone for
directions hey look there's a bee a be
sorry calm down wait the be is wearing a
chef hat too do you see it's h it's up
up up up up up up there can you
see oh but I'm not I said I will change
my my appearance
again but I didn't we could have both
been wearing the chef hat oh no hello be
do you know the way to the Old Clock
Tower
she's so
small
Wendy
oh it's just for that gate over
there I could open the gate for you but
I have to plant all these seedlings
before I'm done
here it could take
hours
small and why why don't you let us help
you we got these grabby arms now after
all well if you
[Music]
insist don't let the cat get too close
to you though it's it's so ready to swat
the [\h__\h] out of
you
okay okay where where do I put wait I'll
take the other one
[Music]
too I kind of don't know where to go
there's a lot of directions maybe it
doesn't matter Maybe we'll all go back
to the middle
eventually stay in the middle like you a
little what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] by the way my dear um two people in
the chat who just let me care a little
bit about
K-pop I've seen this new idle grip which
is also from hyve and it gives you the
vibe of new jeans people are talking
about oh my God how it gives you new
jeans
Vibes ah I'm not interested for now I
don't need another idle group in my
life and I don't know I watched like one
live
performance
yeah magnetic
something it ill it is that their
name um I don't know there there's like
apparently there's like two members or
so that are
13 holy [\h__\h] they're reaching like J-pop
levels of
youngness Too Young Too
Young yeah crazy I mean new jeans some
of the members also started out really
young I think but were they 13 I think
they were maybe 14 at
least
no they're cute though and yeah I
mean the song was not bad at
all Hy is spamming so much I think
they're they were part of this like um
Survival show
right pretty sure they had a survival
show that I did not watch why was I oh K
oh what the [\h__\h] somehow I thought I
could get through here in the middle I
did not
really look at the
stone did not
consciously register
it
okay yeah also wasn't
there those two people in the chat kind
to help me wasn't there a survival show
um do not Senpai told me about it
oh that's it nice that was not that was
not bad oh well I'm actually somewhat of
a celebrity
the CH you could say I make jam it's
it's a fine Jam you've been listen she
got bigger because she got more
confident I like jam and the finest of
all gems is my famous pedal gems and the
music you're listening to oh how
exciting anything to help a fellow chef
we do acknowledge that we're also a chef
we are oh well I'm more of a sandwich
folder still Chef still
Chef in the world's most boring sandwich
job a although you know maybe you need a
SSH up some time
oh oh the frog has found a liking in the
be sounds familiar get her get us out of
here I'm embarrassing
myself
cute I'm in
love Subway naming their
chefs Sandwich
Artist
stretch produce 4 no not that one no
there was another one where it was like
K-pop Style again but with Japanese
people only I think and L told me about
that and she told me that an X I think
an
x48
member and I no no hello project member
right but she told me there were some
people that she was like paying close
attention to um I don't know about it
the one that need no no no no ni was not
on that one no no no it's a very recent
one and I think they just finished up
and I think I think the group that came
out of that I think I just watched their
MV I didn't watch any of these survival
shows so I only watched um the one from
vich where I'm not happy with the result
though but they're fine like their new
song I like the new song from
vicha way more than their like first two
songs way
[Music]
more
you make me feel like I'm the only one
only only only only one only only only
only one only only only only one only
only only only
[Music]
onea you make me feel like I'm the only
one we like the that don't we # vul #
Yol yeah that one is
good I like it more than the previous
ones it's a
bear oh hello there I didn't see you com
in hello there boy you sure would be
great to meet the celebrity toarch of
Wendy the be on account of this being
her Jam Factory that I'm
exploring oh we just met her she seemed
cool probably not in love or anything no
I don't care about her at all you can
have
her now that you say it yes do be a
yellow
bear it's okay I think even with a red
shirt like you could get through because
the art style makes it look legally
distinct oh you think so that's great
ready let's go
woohoo goodbye
bear oh [\h__\h] oh
what is this
apples apples wait oh I can pass I
thought I
couldn't oh the apples are staying in
the
lane and I can go over the lane okay I
want to redo already because I didn't
even I thought I have to go around the
lane I thought I would Bonk myself on
the
[Music]
lane I'm so sorry guys for the
music I I I I I I'll I'll try to fix it
tomorrow but I already tried to and I
don't know what the hell is going on
they [\h__\h] up my
settings [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
Apple an apple a day does not keep the
doctor
[Music]
away until graduation maybe until
graduation of froggy waa yeah what am I
doing what am I doing what am I
doing
[Music]
actually right now it's
fine oh no now they're they're wobbled
again it do be wobbling sometimes
no okay the the Moss does not seem to
work for the apples okay oh [\h__\h] The
Coin Heart
Challenger oh oh
he n the [\h__\h] n the
Frog oh I've been missing out on a good
censorship there
huh I need the
Frog kind of sounds like the music gets
quieter when I
talk I don't think that's what it's
doing it's nice if you perceive it that
[Music]
way oh this is so nice it feels so
satisfying when you get a good
curve okay this
way I got to get all the coins I may not
be getting the no Hearts used and I may
not be getting the the Speedy Gonzalez
achievement but I've been getting the
coins pretty
constantly ever since I realized that
the X means I did get
it and that it's the only thing I can
manage to
[Music]
do the fact that you haven't raged quite
yet is incredible yeah this I'm just
chilling I'm really enjoying this this
is really relaxing to
me I think the music plays a big part
yeah and my scale I'm just that's
[Music]
good ah
n not so I'm playing it the way it's
intended oh hello again Wendy there was
a bear looking for you a little while a
little way back there you must have
quite a following for people to come
looking for you out
here yes well I'm a celebrity after
[Music]
all
c c
b
b 100 seconds
wow with over par yeah
[\h__\h] B be be no not s be I'm talking
about
bees guys
bees tranquil Sunset River wait we
should change back to
Frog who M
frog H hats right yeah yeah yeah we
could also
become the
toad but now I don't have that money
also he doesn't I mean they're pretty
similar doesn't make that much of a
difference here I'll just I'll just go
back to being
Chef wait actually actually I think I
kind of want to look at if I have enough
money I think I do I look at different
colors yeah like taco color or shark
color cuz Taco
color that might be that Ina purple with
like some yellow in it right
H let's take a look oh oh my God yeah
that is 100%
Ena by the way I already saw her new
outfit she showed me already when I was
at her
place it's really really
cute she has an outfit reveal uh I don't
know when exactly but she just announced
it right so it's coming in a few
days look forward to it I can afford one
more let's look at
[Music]
shark yeah I mean yeah that is that is
her color famee but I think the the
tacle one hits
harder yeah maybe I can get the penguin
to
later let's see let's let's try to get
the penguin Kyla want
to T
crumbles
[Music]
I nature for yeah yeah yeah true true we
have that one
[Music]
too
t or Taco Taco frog now it's not to
anymore
sorry Taco looks very much like her hair
mhm no I feel like I'm thinking more of
her uh clothes actually when I look at
this much like yours is a short I like
that the death took inspiration from the
designs not just the colors
mhmm exactly Taco
Taco cute hello again there oh there he
is he just missed weny again oh shoot
well maybe that's for the bear I think
if I actually met her in person I'd get
so excited I'd fall over into the river
like the silly old bear that I am well I
do say you should never meet your Heroes
I assume for a reason uh along those
lines also because I'm in love with her
and you should stay away from her
because I love
her well in light of that do you think
you could do me a
favor
not5 would you be willing to take this
ch money note over to Wendy to buy some
of your famous pedal Jem sure why
not I'll
[Music]
try
no okay we probably need two tries for
this now that I took damage so early oh
my God
what death death
Death I feel like I feel like um a
soccer football whatever player oh there
it is the switcher
rule calling for the
sheet shat
[Music]
shy red
C my leg is
broken ref
ref in English you say refere see I lost
all my [\h__\h] [\h__\h] that what the
[\h__\h] a she
[Music]
I'm acting like a oh my God what the
[\h__\h] is this acting like a a Austrian
very
Austrian
dude
um
um um okay here we go here we go here we
go here a what the [\h__\h] death death
death
Death wait no da da
da wait I can reload here I
forgot oh the time restarts too I think
what the [\h__\h] death
death wait I think there's something
about that um this cut
there I think they want me to put my tip
there and then do something but like I
don't know what the [\h__\h] you want from
me try using a high level
of you're
somebody I I think I know what to do I
think I know I think I know I think I
[Music]
know
level okay
okay what is this sudden Spike of
difficulty ah okay like like this and
then I don't [\h__\h] know no okay W I
kind of did it I don't know I think no
what the [\h__\h] that what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's the taco
color oh did you see how I returned
there but like what is this do I also
have to return there for a
moment I returned because I I thought
you know I can do a proper turn and then
like go in again more
[Music]
smoothly wait a moment turn around turn
turn turn turn turn turn turn turn turn
turn and then and then what the [\h__\h]
the what the what maybe I go faster
y
[Music]
n don't stop go
faster but then if I go faster it's been
faster not
good early stream
death death late stream
death you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] let me
read
I I don't
think it's
[Music]
possible clearly a death
issue don't talk to me don't even talk
to me
okay I have an idea how about we don't
speed up we slow down once we're around
the
corner so I do this
still and then oh but no that's not good
because like not only my speed slows
down it's my my wings
too I mean no the wings slowing down
would be what I want but not my speed
itself maybe I have another idea but
it's probably not going to
work
yeah oh what the [\h__\h] that's not what I
wanted to
do okay while we're at it what the hell
is going
on I don't
no
oh it's switched this is fine I enjoy
this music very
much I think I know wait no wrong wrong
wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong but I
would say like no no never
mind what this is like the most
difficult part in the
game what the
hell not even the powers of the ancient
ones can help me through this
situation what the [\h__\h] whatever we
we'll be losing Hearts we'll just
be losing hearts it's it's it's okay
whatever and then you think did I switch
I don't think I
did
yeah we
go
death death
Jama what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] you got to not stop but I tried
that in the
beginning I think going back here is
fine
but like otherwise how am I going to
even even when I'm
here it's not wide enough for me to do a
full
turn
oh you think I might need to use the
spring first no but it is the right
direction though is it not if you look
at it this way it's obviously the right
direction I hate my life right
[Music]
now with all this skill that I have
shown so far when you guys were saying
I'm so good
now there must be something inherently
wrong with this
level to suddenly [\h__\h] me
over frog me
over try using the
spring and go the opposite side okay
I'll try but that's not
in in
[Music]
intuitional or maybe it is no I feel
like you would normally like to go down
first but this could
work in another
[Music]
world wait the music stopped so
perfectly in that
moment until
[Music]
that's what I
mean okay so but then I I kind of have
to go this way you know oh oh oh I what
this it was so nice until that
[Music]
point I thought I could do
it and I did not
[Music]
stop skill
issue
what
whatever whatever man
whatever this this is also like I I I I
I need to make it through with two
hearts so that I can lose a heart there
too because I am
[Music]
lost this will be the end of
me and my journey with this
game what the hell what the what the
hell m
there's a malfunction located between
the computer
[Laughter]
and usual room
for eight months
goodbye goodbye
[Music]
sir you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no no no I'm giving my
notes in the case of My
Demise I will be giving my notes to
GAA I I I'm already going to redo it
what is this what is
this
[Music]
prob it's a tech
support it's a tech support ter what I
thought I thought that was original I
thought you came up with it on your
own with the purpose of roasting
[Music]
me oh my
God
a
death what's going
on what's going
on problem and chair not in
computer I don't know is this even the
way I mean I feel like we're getting
further starting in this
direction it ends here guys it has to
I can try to lock in here in in that
little little
space but I don't know man I don't know
I don't know I don't
know no I need the
coins I didn't
hesitate I don't hesitate that's not my
lifestyle
[Music]
how do you do
it like what no I I don't know what to
do there
I don't
know safe is at the towns we have to
speed yeah Go Go De you go play the game
right now go go you have about 5 minutes
until I lose my
shits Go De
go didn't you say you can like glitch
through it anyway and then you can like
speed speed your way to this
part but don't answer me now keep your
hands on your
controller what I can make the curve
but you cleared the game oh
wow well you are a
b seems easy easier for a bee than for a
frog cuz you can just fly
through oh [\h__\h] what am I
doing
[Music]
Dum just imagine ah that was kind of
close I think just imagine you're in
Venice I feel like that was kind of
[Music]
close no
no I'm not slowing down and I'm not
stopping lunchbox what do you know what
do you know about frog cup ing huh what
do you know about
spinning you know nothing about this
lifestyle I'm not
stopping I'm
[Music]
maneuvering
close I canot I
cannot why am I even why am I why I can
just like I've kind of committed to
getting all the coins that's my
[Music]
problem
okay no oh
sorry switch to good colors see if she
can spe
[Music]
the maybe the purple makes me into a
turtle kill me just kill
[Music]
me if you do the same but for the
original side okay let's
try let's
try but now I'm I'm like I don't
remember but maybe the
freshness but it's always
like
[Music]
okay shut up I did not stop no no no I
did not
mm- I if anything I I stopped because I
got hit if if that's what you mean but I
didn't stop while I was not stopping
when I wasn't stopped I I did not stop
until I
stopped start the outside when you enter
moving into the inside as you
turn
well that's not like like a lifechanging
advice okay I I
mean that's all you
got s on the
outside problem
de
[Music]
oh
man wait from left or from right what's
what's the meta
huh no it's impossible did you honestly
do it without getting hit I want to see
proof
proof proof or I'll make
you
no no go poof proof make it go
[Music]
poof that little bit where you move down
to grab the third coin is costing you
some time
mhm I'm trying right now so can't get
the coins without touching the wall
see see not just
me it's even somebody who cleared the
game okay
okay one two stay away stay
[Music]
away
try to reach it with like the tip of my
copter I
suppose I missed it and I still got
[Music]
hurt I missed
it a whatever I don't want the coins
anymore I'll trying maybe two more
times
[Music]
d
m
is it only on switch I think
so it was not on
Steam I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I I I went down a little bit for
the coin again I probably don't need to
go down but looks like I'm going to miss
it I know I can get hit once
um
but okay whatever let's move on even
though I almost had
it but then like okay as long as I still
have two hearts I then I can lose a
heart here and then we see what happens
next cuz uh yeah there's no way okay but
I can get for that tach whatever
I'm giving up on that
part because I need the
hearts I need them Hearts wait what
yeah like what is this de what's this
like what what
what what Dev explain did you make this
game because you want me to just cry
[Music]
HH I think that's a
bridge what
[Music]
what every de's dream is to make their o
she cry I see I see I see how it
[Music]
is what
death I I don't want the coins
anymore this level has broken
me oh my god wow look at all the
Maneuvers I can get those
[Music]
oh look at
that oh that that that feels
nice surprising that you did that for
the first time
there oh everything after that beginning
is is pretty mad
bow the first two
problems
uh
yeah that's fine oh the
oh oh another a
switch and here we
go and down I
suppose
all it still
[Music]
continuing that's
fine the
be oh what is this a
Bak money not what is this for uh when
you right you look a little sweaty
spaghetti yeah it became smaller
again oh well anyway it's from that bear
he's a big fan of yours and he really
wants to commission some of your petal
Jam is that
so what she she got biger again oh my
God okay [\h__\h] cute this Bee makes up
for
everything well if you'd like to see how
the magic happens then come right this
way
ah
cute
man the bee heals all all my problems
it's so late already I have to read
super
chats you have angered me
enough
death T POS and await your
destiny
now you're wet what you going to do what
you going to do about it
huh you going to you're going to what
you going to take a towel and dry
yourself huh huh oh you really you
really going to do that
huh yeah you better you better take that
towel dry yourself yeah
cuz if you stay wet you might catch a
cold and that really sucks cuz you're
going to be sneezing and you're going to
your nose going to be running you don't
want your nose to run you may be even
coughing and worst case you might get a
fever yeah
so better dry
yourself wait we're so close to another
world there's like a candy world there
oh
man yeah anyway it was a lot of fun I
did I did like really enjoy this this is
really chill too and some challenges as
you can see still await you if you get
to this
part oh but definitely worth taking a
look guys please check it out and get
those get those colors that I couldn't
get the Kaa and the the FAA
colors go check him out and show them to
me I want to see
yeah go give him some love because
they're a real Chad a real kfp Chad from
the Fire Emblem days yo yo we got to
support a fellow
kfp thank you so much you really made my
day and then you ruined it
no no that was great I really like this
game this like this definitely exceeded
my expectations has absolutely nothing
to do with uh the de being kfp no
no no it was really nice really I
thought it was uh just like a silly
silly silly
dorky game with like you know just SP to
win but yeah it was very chill
aesthetically pleasing some cute little
characters too and oh my God
frogs I just got back did she Rage Quit
well I'm
[Music]
quitting there may have been some rage
but it's because I have to read super
chats okay so happy to watch my o play I
still can't believe
[Music]
it thank you so much so sad we couldn't
get you a membership that's really weird
they send so many
memberships 200 218 members have
received a new membership in this
stream how how the hell did they not get
you
weird de
[Music]
account
look
look I'll just show off the colors one
more time for Japanese
[Music]
bro so
kiaha
color GA color Taco color and I wish I
could show you um this is Kyla color
can't see now and apparently is this
really fun color cuz like it's blue from
this point of
view it might be different I don't know
is this
really but these ones are definitely you
know
us yeah yes it's her dress oh okay okay
you guys got to show me some
screenshots they said there's more Holo
references to in level titles for
example did I miss one I didn't like
read all the titles
properly you're you're such a Holo otaku
oh my
God water are the
flowers I
mean avoid the Ju juy apples planting
seeds a grand opening unlock the unlock
the gates Moonlight Sonata colorful
bunting a grand out turn the T ice cream
give frog cup that comes to none of this
sounds really like a reference so far
war boys sing handing Downstream leaving
the Frog Pond burning your
stripes collect the coins Master
controls learn your ropes yeah no maybe
later maybe maybe later
on I got pretty far I got pretty into
it sound of rain is a reference to girls
last
tour
oh
Nar sound of the
rain I just thought a sound of
[Laughter]
music okay well that was a lot of fun
I'm gonna play this bgm in the
background while I read super
chatos thank you for your musical
contribution at least for this moment we
going
Poes I'm going to start reading the ones
from the concert that are so so many
yeah but guys play the game go buy the
game on switch if you have a switch go
go byy bye bye bye bye bye byy why would
you not buy it's
fun it's cute it's made by kfp
support go go go go go go I'm not
sponsored but like
hello bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
bye byee
bye by bye bye bye
bye bye bye byee bye bye
it's a really good song from idle group
cute I want to do bye byebye
sometime sometime in
Fredy thank you love
K thank you studio
somewhere
somewhere over the
rainbow there
a
kfp dad
loves the W
[Music]
dearly even if
secretly thank
you me is that you is that
you and you and
you wow thank you
guys me but it's not a
secret publicly love the
Wawa I'm also Wawa I'm froggy Wawa so
applies to me
too
okay let's let's be a little bit
efficient just a little bit just a
little
[Music]
bit
meow
[Music]
meow fubuki Sena is streaming at a weird
time she started at like 700 a.m. her
time the
hell hi
smoothie a you got cold ears I like to
squeeze
them
Carla
car
Cara Carla the Carla is is done now is
she
not yeah she's done I want to try
playing that game um sometime next week
the
new cool H Life
game I'll try next
[Music]
week
you
know you know when I um asked the usual
people AKA null ref and seafoam to work
on some Easter stuff and they were like
oh H yeah we can do it but it's actually
really stressful time right now cuz they
were working on this
game h
they are part of the crew for that game
and now they're done but they've been
working like simultaneously a little
little bit on my Easter stuff as
well but they told me it looks like all
should be okay should be fine but you
know I was trying to avoid scuff and all
that but can't promise I mean
considering how busy they were getting
that game ready for releasing
it um I don't no they say it's fine they
say they say it's it's going according
to
Kaku Oh What A Dream Team husk as
well husk and K what a dream
team is it really an Ian holiday collab
over this in the last
minute but I think there shouldn't
be well yeah there there's probably
going to be SC
there's probably going to be SC sadly Am
won't be part of it this time cuz she's
busy which makes me feel very
anxious but hopefully I can uh cuz like
you know um with VR there's always a lot
of troubleshooting even not about like
the games or so but even just like with
models and all that and tracking and
whatever um and Amed was always helping
with that
[Music]
well last time last time I also tried to
like be helpful of course and it's I
feel like I'm I'm her
trainee I feel like feel like a trainee
and she's my Superior and I'm being
schooled into the I don't know I'm
trying to say I in
German I saw she saying she might be
well I'm I think I can uh the people who
say they're participating they seem
pretty much set in
stone uh I could announce it like I
don't really mind announcing it shall I
announce it I shall announce it
um okay so this time it's ID and Ian
really grateful ID is joining even
though uh it's pretty it's going to be
pretty early for
them H okay stop it's going to be um me
as the host uh since we have an uneven
number of participants I'll just be the
host I will not be playing the games
that I thought of uh we have on the Ian
side a
kaimori sasuga always always up for some
fun stuff we have
quas
my yeah and we have um M Marino
mums let's go and we have bio the gamer
girl B currently getting like a VR model
approved or something I I hope it works
out I I I would hope that wouldn't be
like a cause of her having to drop out
uh I think it should be
fine and then we have f f again PR
anticipating just like last
[Music]
year and then on the ID side we have Ru
the
squel and we have o the zombie and we
have mun the
moon so it's uh including me it's nine
people but it'll be yeah eight
participants in the games I'm the
host for ID members and the rest is
members yeah yeah teams of two there may
be team a team game where I split
them into two teams but um they might be
able to choose their own teams I'm not
sure how we're going to do
it
yeah yeah yeah sounds like a very fun
collab
mhm I I hope so I'm a bit nervous about
it because these kind of things you know
always like VR VR is always like takes
so much
preparation uh but
yeah yeah pretty strong was it you think
so it'll be on Waba Channel I don't
think we'll have any other povs because
um we're going to be using the camera
system anyway cuz uh also like remember
last time when the eggs were all
scattered uh the egg search is I think
the only thing that we're like reusing
as a concept but this time we're going
to um scatter eggs apparently in like a
smaller studio so to
say and uh so then we can use the the
camera and somebody will be controlling
the camera and switch angles and all
that so we will not be using like last
time our like POV like handeld so to say
cameras which should overall be less
chaotic and all over the place
yeah I think I need to go idle meeting
really quickly and then I'll come back
but don't go people always leave when I
go on idle meeting why would you go
instead take this time to buy some merch
oh hi
smovie but yeah feel free to spread the
word I think the participants should
stay the same there's not really
anything I think that will go in between
anyway see you in a
[Music]
moment
a sorry chunkers had some something
stuck on her butt so I had to chase her
and cut it
off and she was zooming zooming around
like a crazy cat
[Music]
up a poop a poop the whoop a poop the
whoop it happens sometimes her butt is
very fluffy it happens actually really
rarely I didn't cut off her
tail I I cut off some part some little
bit of her fur of her butt
fur
you took one of my Gummy Worms no how
dare
you just one of the realities of having
a fluffy cutle yeah all kinds of stuff
gets stuck in there
F hairy butts are a
hindrance dingleberries
dingleberries sounds like a Willy Wonka
term
terminology
how much for cut
off
honestly like okay the parts that are
clean I feel like you you would want you
would want that cuz it's so
soft soft chunky wonky
hair princess fluffy
butt okay we're going to read super
chats we're going to be productive and
efficient whether you like it or not
after a little head crack
okay so so so wait let actually let me
answer only a question it's okay
to
Okay so
holer my best friend help me
out uh GAA streaming
list from
the waiting room which H turned into
something else later on okay and a
thumbnail perhaps would be good you know
today I cleaned
out my uh my download
folder I got rid of 50 GB worth of
data what about
[Music]
time sounds some fun right yep GB 50
GB well I
mean I have two discs that are 930 GB
total so 50 GB out of 930 * 2 isn't even
that
much but yeah that's why my download
folder always took like so long to uh to
load and was like like it just stops
loading it's it was like bugging
out no I don't want it to automatically
delete after 30 days because I have a
lot of stuff in the download folder that
I need as well that is just there
because I don't move it it's just there
but I need it but yeah yesterday I was
like no today I was deleting a lot of
stuff I was
uh
yeah good it felt
refreshing 50gb isn't that much yeah but
like honestly in data it was like over a
thousand
files so it was a lot it was a lot it's
just like a lot of smaller files
too
you can copy everything into a new
folder to deal with it latest faster
yeah I mean yeah but no I just I just
got rid of
it a good amount so that's good let's
go wait I forgot the super uh the the
the the thumbnail did I download it yeah
here it is another thing to go into my
download folder
okay it's from the waiting room while
you guys were watching the concert and
from the story time
afterwards here we go
sky7
[\h__\h] and thank you oh this was already
afterwards or what oh yeah oh the first
couple super chats already about the
performance andr D it all spankenheimer
[Music]
prises incredible performance tal
incredible singing incredible dancing
and a really good Japan lesson in the
middle we are blessed thank you yeah I
had fun coming up with the MC I was like
already thinking about future MC's if I
get the chance to do one again I was
like I I was I was getting some
epiphanies but I I wonder normally you
don't do MC's alone so you get paired up
of someone so it's like hm can I force
this idea onto
someone in the future I hope
so
yeah I I hope I can't be a little bit
creative in that
regards I like to be creative for
MC's especially now that everybody's
doing
waves now that the trend has been
set say SP you Spen thank you so much oh
blah that's what I do
now chunky chunk thank you for the red
CH on fire 10 out of 10 thank you so
much Kima definitely is a song that sets
people on
fire
especially
[Music]
kada let's set her on fire oh [\h__\h] she's
a phoenix I won't do
anything than you chunky
[Music]
chunk Cruz thank you for the
pinky I Shadow my knees from kneeling so
hard out of respect oh
dear I'm kidding of course but oh my God
were you amazing I love your new
original song and that performance of
Chloe was Stellar thank you for all your
hard work love you no it wasn't Stellar
we sang uh Wild Card are you
okay no uh yeah was great I agree we had
a good good time I'm I'm really happy
with the outcome I'm pretty satisfied
yeah
no thank you very much we going to be
watching it again and feeling all the
feelings again uh on Sunday
Sunday wild was amazing wild was
incredible thank you I kind of want to
put out a cover too but like the timing
was kind of difficult cuz I wanted to
put out uh an original song around the
Fest
and I feel like when when performing
wild card at the first end the only good
timing the best timing would be also to
put out the sound cover during
this and putting it out like 3 months
later or so it's kind of random well I
don't know maybe I'll end up doing it
still at some point like a proper
cover cuz um Dam K and Johnny you know
my angels they were saying they were
even saying they'll mix it for free for
me and I'm like what a deal like I can't
turn down deal like
that
yeah and maybe maybe I could just make a
a solo song cover of it so because I I
mean we performed it together at the
concert but you might be curious about
what it sounds like if I sing it all
alone then it's a different version then
then there's like a little bit of
difference to it which I think would be
nice
too yeah we'll see about it but for now
I need to release my original song which
I've been seeing MV
previews and they're looking pretty good
I mean kodu seems to be working on a
million things at once so he he's uh
doing his best rushing through it um but
it's looking good I asked him to include
more dancing scenes of my recordings cuz
I busted my ass recording with that
suit uh on the on a really tight time
schedule and now now I got an update
with uh n&b that has more dance scenes
it looks really
nice no wobbly likes no there's
definitely still wobbly legs
yeah but I I think if you just watch
it then you won't like focus on it like
me you might still notice but it's not
really like something that ruins
DV yeah we got a teaser perview for that
yeah I think I'll upload the teaser
after the
Easter the
Easter collab Easter stream maybe maybe
I'll even raid myself into it but I
don't know when the Easter stream
ends that's kind of like open-ended so
we'll see but it will be like
afterwards for the preview but the
preview really I mean you already heard
the song honestly the
preview so much of a preview a teaser
for the
song is more a teaser for the MV I guess
but even that there's not much to
see it's really just a small you know
like an a teaser to really just tease
you that the song is coming out soon
like a reminder like
hey this
exists I will now plant it into your
brain
again but I did get K to make another
like teaser um audio cuz like for
pineapple for the teaser for pineapple
as well the audio was like specifically
put together like some instrumental
parts put together specifically for the
teaser like it's not just you know the
teaser
cut without like it it's like cut and
then rearranged and like you know
adjusted a little bit
so he made that again really fast mhm
altered a little a little bit
Yeah so that it doesn't give away too
much but it also just uh gives you a
Vibe Vibe
check yeah so yeah look forward to it
and naan C on thanks for the red super
chat than
it hi atten seeing your performances for
this first concert I'm struck speechless
first concert what do you mean
first Oh you mean first of the four ah I
thought thirst for you like
what so I will share a sentiment from my
guilt Discord quote K will be underrated
until the day every person on the
internet follows her and I will support
you until that day comes thank
you a wait so you your guilt Discord did
you did you are they into Hol did
you did
you
what's the word infect
them sounds like a nice
Guild how me Devo no no I'm thinking
more of like online online mm RPGs you
did a watch s together oh
nice were they into H before or did you
kind of force them like hey watch this
with me or else you're going to be
kicked out of the
guild huh the hold of
virus don't give them don't give them
the flum
no I'm
tired [\h__\h] smie why are you coming
here reformed as h of Ah that's fun hi
smie are you are you also offering me a
a an interesting butt situation as a
present I don't need it okay
just need your fluffy
tail watch this girl I don't B showing
up on rating on
Monday
yeah or
else okay well thank you so much for the
sweet words naan I'm so happy you enjoy
the we're going to watch it again will
you be there or will you be square h
square is not very friend shaped should
be
round Kimmy
[Music]
pH thank you for the r Super Chat we
have skipped raids because of outfit
reveals and content a well I mean based
priorities so thank it all for the M
awesome job Wawa your moves always blow
us away it's always amazing seeing you
dance I never get tired of it and you
someh always exceed our expectations
love you
w thank you so much I tried to
exceed I was nervous about the
rap what's the word not reputation
R how you guys take the
song H I was really happy with how you
took it the reception yeah yeah
yeah really really relieved I
was cuz as I said like normally if
things went without
considering uh uh your
vision this type of song would have
probably not been next on my list of
releasing original songs and who knows
maybe I would have actually re uh
performed a album song I might have gone
for something like pineapple or sleep
talking to be
honest or tgw and I'm so sorry I know I
know I know I know especially with a
band retrospective would be
amazing but it's not the song I want to
in like if I get one solo song in this
big big concert which is a big
opportunity I I don't know if I would
want to choose a song that doesn't
necessarily represent my current musical
Direction I know a lot of people like
that John real like the kind of rock
metal whatever I know I know it's really
cool and I agree it would sound really
nice with a live
band yeah I was thinking of medley cuz
like uh Chloe for example did a medley
right um and that that I was like yeah
that that's actually kind of
smart but then again I also want you
guys to enjoy like the full song cuz the
full songs are amazing
too but yeah um so for me retrospective
is not really there in my my high
priorities because it's just like yeah
not my direction and not how I if I get
this one chance not how I want to
represent
myself it's pretty smart maybe one day
I'll also do a
[Music]
mly but then then each part is so short
and I'm like I wanted to hear more of
that
[Music]
M I know it just feels so
fast I don't
know if the medle could be a little bit
longer a little
bit but
yeah I wouldn't mind more songs like
Kima oh thank you um but I I I I want to
try also more like R&B is stuff like
sleep talking and I don't know this and
that I want to EXP expl within the K-pop
um
Vibe you're an amazing singer thank you
so much thank
you well anyway thank you m love you
[Music]
too I a beep thank you L for the pinky
oh K you are just amazing I feel so
proud to be P you really need something
special I'll never forget that
performance thank
you yeah pretty happy with
that looking forward to watching it with
you guys PO on the
weekend yeah little members only stream
my weekly members only
streams thank you so much for supporting
me
and shining brightly orange uh and
midst the
masses now you should be shining green
though jaob 47 than it all for the pinky
absolutely lovely first day you killer
with Kima ve Very sensual and cool
dancing looking forward to the MV and
then Chloe was not the dance partner I
was expecting but the song was amazing
and one of the coolest group songs for
of the night for me yeah it was an
unexpected pairing for me too to be
honest like when I first saw the the
pairs
or like not all of them are a pairs some
of them are bigger groups too right I
was
like a
do with Chloe who at the time I didn't
really have any connection with besides
the
pajamas yeah but I did take it as an
opportunity to get closer to her and I
did yeah we definitely grew closer
thanks to this thanks to being paired up
so
randomly oh could
origam yeah origami the origami kab was
really just like at the time I found out
we were going to do that so I was like
okay let's let's get closer then let's
do stuff together and then I invited her
to the origami
collaboration who knew pajamas can make
good
connections it's so when I think about
it it's so ridiculous but I I love
ridiculous ideas like these like you
know we were wearing the pajamas I asked
her to bring her pajama we were both
wearing the pajama even though you can't
even see that much of it just like the
the top the edge of the
sleeve you could see it a little bit
during the stream like something so
silly but I thought it's a nice detail
cuz the pajamas are that's the first
thing I felt like when I saw uh Chloe
stream I was like oh I have to same
pajamas we must be
friends yeah was the first thing that I
felt like connected so you know it's uh
it has emotional value to
me
yeah so I hope to meet her again and do
more stuff together
yeah she's so sweet
H and so thank you so much
Jacob song was amazing and one of the
coolest group songs of the night for me
yeah that was definitely one of the
cooler songs I I really wanted us to
leave a cool impression with the song
instead of like doing like a cutesy
Japanese songs which are great too I
love doing cutesy Japanese songs too but
I feel like I was just like kind of
already had this Vision that probably a
lot members are going to do cute
songs and we're going to balance it out
with a a cool song that you know is even
English
wow yeah because she was able to speak
like this in English I thought you know
this is the chance to do something that
nobody expects in a Ian uh Japan duet
unit usually for these unit songs
everybody's doing a j Japanese song so
that was the the thinking I had in my
one brain
cell I'm so happy she was up for it cuz
it is pretty difficult pretty difficult
I can
imagine the song itself also has like a
a couple of different difficult m
topl lines which is the the
[Music]
Melody and I saw a clip of Bales and
Mum Bales shot I watched Friends a
million times and I did not understand
what she was talking about in the
beginning like what is she what is she
on
about the friends move and then a
afterwards she said that they showed a
clip of you know the thing from friends
and I'm like
ah yeah you're
right you're kind of
right so in France if you've watched it
Ross uh tries to swear at who was it one
of the
girls and he does
this
wait hand to
he like Bonks his fists twice against
each
other
which in his mind seems to be an
insult close
enough and so we did that in our
Coro and Bs was really
like he does it to Monica a lot it's
like a middle fing yeah to him no nobody
else does that right except for us and
wild
card uh I watch Friends a million times
and I did not think of
that interesting very
interesting interesting
observation I mean when I say nobody
else does it I mean outside of friends I
mean being such a Zoomer right like a
lot of the time she would not think of
such things cuz it's kind of friends is
kind of Boomer
media but I guess a lot of dors picked
up on it cuz it's on on
Netflix well same for me I didn't watch
Friends for the first time until like
the recent years way after it was like
on actual
TV I don't even know if I was alive was
I
alive
new shows can't compete with the oldest
yeah there's so many good Classics
man Like Home Improvement and
chimed
man good
times and now I'm watching Witcher The
Witcher because I run out of shows
man it's good so far I like it I
finished the first episode at least
now I'm in the second episode
[Music]
now uh where was I ah man schneid thanks
for the pinky absolutely amazing
performances both for your new original
and the what with Chloe H you actually
managed to smuggle in two songs by you I
was like
yeah exactly I put K on the credits
twice and Johnny and money too I I think
I think it's the same team for both
songs I think my angels must have been
quite delighted by that getting a lot of
exposure for their songs and a lot of
people really lik wild card and I think
some people even thought it was an
original song why just because it's
English I don't
know was not an original song from me
but from my team indeed I guess because
it has a similar sound to Kima in a way
just because it's produced by the same
people and it's English so it makes you
think that like that sounds like
something I could probably release and
yeah true oh yeah also because a lot of
people never heard it before they're
like oh must be a new
song more people need to listen to K
songs they're really
boppy
yeah okay next um space wonderful thank
you for the red super chat
incredible performance W I love both
Cima and your duet with Chloe so much
your voice was so raw oh was it
raw ew raw I like it cooked and powerful
and your hips they give akis competition
oh I'm honored your dancing was out of
this world you were great my town oia
had so much fun thank you wow
I'm happy to hear that yeah my singing
too like
Kima even when I recorded Kima I feel
like I went out of my comfort zone I
mean when I recorded it for the single
release but out of my comfort zone
thanks to Mo being right there listening
in next to
me so that may have like whatever ever I
I
I learned so to say back then I tried to
apply during the performance as well I'm
glad you liked everything about it yeah
you remember did sound deeper than usual
with the key yeah there's some deepness
but not so deep that it's uncomfortable
for me so it's was pretty
perfect I really like it it's pretty
comfortable to sing oh I think ah there
there's some difficult Parts too though
yeah I'm going to sing more H sing talk
more about the song Etc when it releases
but thank you so
[Music]
much hello she's so
curious but thank you oh she keeps on
rubbing my leg
So
Soft for the red super chat you
absolutely kill it today your singing
and dancing is out of this world and I
can't wait a moment longer to be able to
watch your performances again super
excited as well for the release of your
new song and I'm pretty sure the frd MV
that goes with it yeah of course fredie
I feel like I have to make frd
mvs no it's coming out um next week on
the weekend
[Music]
h i I wanted to put it out earlier but
we still waiting on MV to finish and on
the art to finish and also then there
were some other song releases um dates
that I wanted to do where I was told oh
overlapping not so good I'm like
okay so it will probably be yeah on the
weekend pretty sure 100% but I'll
announce it properly soon
[Music]
TM
yeah no I don't want
to what do you mean plug it in the
waiting
[Music]
room on the same day I'm putting out a
teaser so I can't like link the waiting
room for the actual song yet I can link
the waiting room for the teaser I can do
that and I can say at the end oh my
teaser is coming up right after this
yeah but I I don't want to like you know
make it too much all about that cuz um
don't want to don't want to force myself
too much on I I'll I'll use it a little
bit perhaps as a reminder you know like
hey I'm putting on a song but I don't
want to like you know push too
much don't want to seem like uh
that's all I'm here for you know to
advertise stuff no no no no no I don't
don't want to do
that I I'll shill I'll shill the teaser
a little
bit make it as a payment for organizing
collab Yeah well yeah I mean I am
investing some money I don't know how
much they're charging
me I don't know I don't know how much
you're charging me to make the games and
the modeling and all that but uh yeah I
got to get something back out of
it get your froggy wa
merch there and Link is down there in
the
description H anyway thank you guys want
to follow
me thank you so much for the support oh
wait that wait I I was already at do
Jones
sorry sorry I was in the wrong line
thank you so much you too both of you
thank you for your kind words very very
supportive makes me feel like I want to
go right back out on
stage was crazy kind of
crazy kind of [\h__\h] crazy
big ass audience this time even bigger
than last time carpet ABS thanks for the
pinky incredible performances W you
really took your Coro to the next level
this time I'm super excited for kima's
release love you my Oshi and hope you
have a great time with all the girls
after this so funny you say that because
like the coral to me was easier than
others that I've done like I think
pineapple was more difficult for
me no I said this already Cima is
actually like I had a relatively easy
time to pick up the moves it's more
about the execution when you execute it
C cleanly
cleanly then I guess and big
bigly then it just yeah feels yeah I
guess
intense but I think this might also be
like you know a different choreography
style because this time it was a
different choreographer
um but like I feel like pineapple and
and doy you and so on like all my other
dances Sparks as well they just like
have so so so so so many moves in quick
succession tacked onto each other like
Bam Bam Bam Bam and that's like really
hard to learn and remember especially
cuz I always learn them alone at home
watching the reference
video uh and it's kind of different when
learning from a teacher step by step in
a good
pacing I like both ways because at least
when I learn it at home I can go at my
Pace but then I take too many breaks and
also it's like confusing yeah and I may
miss I may miss some
details but yeah so Kima I also learned
alone at home but it was generally
somehow easier to pick up because I feel
like there were less quick succession
different kind of moves stacked on top
each other but they still
seemed
pretty how to say
memorable and may I say I
actually like um for Fest you know I
basically get a choreo for free if I
don't already have one so that's why I
didn't ask my usual choreographer I was
like I can get a free choreo well I I'll
take that um but that means that I I had
to work with one of the choreographers
that cover works with but the one that
they assigned first and sent me a choreo
for I was
like it's not it I can I and then I
remembered um I remembered uh
when when I was like
rehearsing I think it was doy you for
Fest there were some dancers like help
helping me just like you know they were
just like I think they were there for
other choreographies like supervision
and all that but I had my own Cher right
so they didn't they didn't need to be
there but I saw like one of the
choreographers I was like hey what what
kind of stuff do you do and they showed
me their Twitter and not their Twitter
their Instagram I was like oh this is
this is the kind of choreographies I do
and I'm like oh oh that's pretty good
that's kind of like the kind of sty of
choreography that I'm interested
in but then later on when I asked for
like commission turns out they were
pretty expensive I was
like maybe
not but I knew that they were like you
know already kind of connected so I was
like I remember this one person can can
I ask for a corer from them specifically
cuz I feel like they could nail it
yeah and
then even though they already had
something created I they brought in the
new choreographer choreographer and then
based on the choreography that they
already had they uh
added different moves and all that like
put it together splice it together
remixed the Coro basically yeah got free
got it for free and then it turned more
into the kind of Coro that I like I
unfortunately don't I I feel like I
could make like a really simple Cora on
my own I've I kind of have have done
that before but for something like this
I want a more intricate one and that
still seems like something above my
skill level so I leave it to
choreographers to make the choreo um for
for me to
learn and they made something really
cool yeah I ended up quite satisfied
with it
no
no yeah I'm glad I found one one
choreographer in Japan that can I mean
there's surely more but I'm glad I found
one now that can do like the K-pop style
of
choreo CU I I know a lot of Japanese uh
choreographers who have a very JPY style
of Coro
making um and that's nice for Jpop songs
but for k songs I want the K-pop flavor
to
it yeah so pretty
satisfying I'm so tired what the
[\h__\h] not everyone tries dancing too much
that's also a thing like I like first I
I think uh what I got first was still
pretty
simplistic well same for wild card I was
like can we make this a bit more
difficult and like you know I think they
always start out making it like a
relatively simple Coral because you
know you know it's a lot it's a lot to
learn and take in but I was like can can
we make this more difficult
please so I think that's why I I think
BS was like oh what are these coros I
want to learn them yeah I I I
particularly in a very particular manner
supervised both the Chimera and wild
card Coro creation and gave very
particular references and all that like
I want this I want this and can you
change this move into a different move
I you
know to make it something that I think
is giving K-pop
Vibes so I think that's why they give
off a different vibe
also because different choreographers
made them
yeah
yeah no the ity crown was not my
idea wait I
think I may have given YY as a
reference I think I gave YY and black
pink as a
reference YY does the crown move a lot I
know
know and honestly my my usual
choreographer Kiana she also I think
does the crown move a lot like the crown
kind of hand even when it's not just two
sometimes she does it with one hand like
a this move
again it's pretty popular
somehow an anti FR oh I think I know
what you mean do do you mean the one how
do I explain this and the anti fragile
do you mean the one where I'm like kind
of like
angled and then I pull my hand down and
I you know what I
mean uh wa where where is
that keep
that
[Music]
insane no where was it oh the head roll
oh that's not what I meant true though
oh you're right you're right oh my
tongue came out you're right now you say
that yeah yeah yeah yeah there is a
there's a move in antifragile where they
do like a very similar move yeah yeah
yeah yeah you're
right no they definitely I didn't send
them a Le seraphim Coro but maybe they
you know took inspiration from all of
that they're so
good
yeah
fragile fragile
fragile okay sorry ATT too much where
was
I here I
think I think so was was it was it carpa
OBM did I read this like everybody is
like saying similar things so I'm
getting confused I think it was the
pinky right Carper are you here it's
okay we love
yo thank you I love you too I love Yap
chicken I think so I think
SOA really took theora to the next level
yeah yeah yeah I think I think so love
you my ocean hope you have a great time
of all the girls after this thank
you no I unfortunately I did not have a
great time with the girls after this
though I just
died I just kind of died in my hotel
room I mean in the on the first day
after that I had to rush to do the the
uh Expo
thing and then I died and then the next
day after the honey works I died in the
hotel room again and then on Monday
everybody was having
fun the Red Bull oh but we didn't share
uh like okay I opened up a new
can and then we took paper cups and
before I took a sip out of the
can I poured it into the cups we were
not uh exchanging
saliva no I was especially because I was
worried about that I said oh yeah I'll
take a
cup
hygi hygienic
CH no no no no no no no no no can Fury
debunked I did spat
not I didn't also because I said I I
want like two sips from the Red Bull
because I don't I cannot first of all
energy drink bad for fro that's why I
don't want to drink the whole can second
of all I already get enough energy from
two or three sips of Red Bull so I'm
enough uh I hav't that would be enough
for me so does somebody want to share
the Red Bull with me I asked and then BS
was like yeah yeah so I just like poured
out a little bit for myself because I
didn't want the whole can to begin
with yeah we know we know how little
energy drink can have a crazy effect on
me and I think it's good that I'm not
pushing my tolerance my my whole life
whenever I drink energy drinks may it be
Red Bull or Monster whatever espe
especially monster cuz the cans are way
too big it always bothers me that
they're so big cuz I only need free sips
really and I don't want to like
forcefully force myself to drink more
when I don't need to because I know it's
bad for my
body I don't need more energy no thank
you I'm not drinking them for the flavor
even though the monsters are pretty
nice but I'm not going
to yeah push my tolerance and and push
my body health
yeah it would challenge my
heart no I saw in Japan again I saw the
small baby monsters they have small
monsters oh the game music stopped it
died I'll turn on a different one this
one I wish we had those in Austria the
small
monsters in small cans like kind of in
shot cans more or
less yeah cuz we really I feel like
monsters are way too
big I mean I see I see like my friends
chugging down the big monster cans I'm
like damn I just need two
sips like everyone else seems to be fine
with the signs of a monster but no
they're they're quite a bit Yeah is it
500 MERS oh my
God that's a lot
that's so
much do you hear the
music why do they only make them this
big I don't know maybe they tried to
differentiate themselves from Red Bull
maybe they heard that people think Red
Bulls are too small and so they make
themselves bigger but like I guess like
if people for the people who drink a lot
of energy drinks then yeah they they
want you know for them the monster size
is probably good
size but not for me
yeah is okay can hear okay
okay appears like value ah yeah could be
like an trying to show value thing too
mhm we didn't really know what it was a
friend of mine downed a four pack in
like 2 hours and was having heart
palpitations what the
fruck holy
[\h__\h] your poor
friend oh my God that's
terrifying be careful guys don't drink
too much of the energy drinks okay don't
overdo it you
Gamers same thing happened to me oh my
God chill the [\h__\h]
out Tassimo thank you for the WR Super
Chat I'm amazed K this is my first time
watching a live Holo live concert and
I'm just blown away by you and everyone
else and it's not even done this is just
the first day your new song hit like a
truck and you're dancing was on fire I'm
truly glad I can witness this thank you
so much that sounds exciting for you I'm
glad you could experience it like that
first time is probably very much like
whoa this is
amazing thank you so much D get up
there and I really appreciate it hope
you enjoyed the rest of the Fest as well
if you watched the other ones too I hope
they were fun and enjoyable to
you fantastic
oo nice I'm I'm really
[Music]
glad hopefully you get to see a lot more
like
this yeah it's it's just you know our 3D
concerts on YouTube they're they're fun
and amazing too but it hits so different
with an audience doesn't it in an actual
venue It's So
Different yeah Flappy Boy Thanks for the
red super chat regarding ESC will never
be privy privy to what transpired behind
the scenes it probably doesn't matter
anymore but Germany missed out big time
ly M I'm glad you think so they might
have made it with this one the absolute
girl boss power paired with the central
corer would have killed it I think now
was March end of March I think they're
already done with the preliminaries no I
think the prelimin preliminaries were in
February so they have I think they have
a fixed song
now I did not listen to what their song
to go
is um it might not have been that they
rejected me because of the song it could
have also been just the logistics being
like weird to
them yeah I had some conversations with
them and explained how things could go I
I suggested several
options and yeah in the end they can't
tell me why it didn't work out so it's a
mystery but in the end it's uh
yeah with uh all
the problematic you know
things uh it's
fine
yeah you get backing from cover well I
had their support to do
it h when go
collab all right all
right
oh I am back from
Japan and I I think I re before I told
her that maybe in April we should do it
cuz then I have time again so it's
almost
April we can talk
about talk and plan talk
about and I have to write in proper
English cuz she uses deep L to translate
I think or not deep L probably publical
talk about and plan our
collab I am a bit more confident in
using Mak sense now too but I don't know
how to use it for live streaming
[Music]
yet April okay thanks well I mean we're
on like the last two days of of March so
it kind of has to be in
April not happening in March I can tell
you
that but hopefully soon yeah I'm I'm I'm
I'm up for it I was thinking about it
too don't worry I have it in the back of
my
mind let go go watch Kima dance I want
to know her reaction
ah
yeah I I want to teach her Cima
dance maybe she can help me with my
wobble my leg wobble wobble
wobble she might have a heart attack
when you Ser her face is always so funny
I have the go girl
reaction I can't make I can't make the
big
oh does she dance with she does she does
they all do like from her group they
they do a lot of dancing looks so fun I
want to join them
I want to do I want to do you know I
wanted to do K-pop you like uh dance
challenges for YouTube shorts but um
still like cover doesn't really
know like for archived Stuff how to
acquire song writes for Korean songs
like for Japanese stuff they're like
okay we can do it you can do it but as
long as it's like anything outside of
Japan is like difficult to them and so
like recently I asked again can I please
do it can I please do it like nobody
gets copyright stricken from the people
that I know so like I don't think it's
that kind of issue but they still have
to you know like get you know proper
rights and all that uh so like that's
not going to happen but I was thinking
go Idol
group I can do their songs probably I
can get permission from them directly
probably and then and then just you know
that's at least something
something out of my own songs that I can
do but I was also planning um even
though they they have some they um
distributed some motion for uh suici
Senai song I was thinking of just doing
it myself not using the motion I want to
do a quick YouTube short maybe I found
some time early next week to do a
YouTube short on so he says senpai's new
song a song and also when I replied to
mik on Twitter uh because of her new
song I told her it's so cute she was
like oh please Dance it and I'm like
okay
okay so I got two things two dance
challenges within H life on my to-do
list right
[Music]
now yeah I I just wish I could fix my my
leg problem but those two dances
probably I can I can handle it somehow
[Music]
yeah yeah so moving on uh where was
I oh yeah and probably doesn't matter
anymore but German yeah so so so so so
so I I do think like it would have been
I guess a good song cuz like cuz you
guys really like it left a great
impression on our big ass stage I would
love to show them my performance of Cima
and be like hey this could have been us
but you said
no they may they might have made it with
this one the absolute girl boss power
pair with the cenal Cory would have
killed it yeah thank you so much for the
sweet
[Music]
words yeah but I understand it might
really just be the logistics and I I get
it that's like intimidating and
difficult to
solve we'll see we'll see how how they
get placed how they get ranked
I got to listen to their song that
they're going with Unwritten than it all
Jim Tracy D you all for the red chat you
were absolutely incredible Ki Kima is so
awesome and the Coro was amazing and
your duet with chlo was insane as well
you two sounded perfect together so
proud to call you my oce than you I feel
like uh with wild card especially you
say we sounded perfect together I kind
of agree um I was uh
um I liked she was kind of singing in a
lower register for the chorus especially
while I was singing in a higher
[Music]
register how's the song going
again on my wild
card and then she was singing like oh
[Music]
no we a wild card
M
yeah cuz I like her low register a lot
too yeah register when she sings in a in
a lower tone she lets out the cool voice
in
her and cuz she sang in a lower tone it
made my my higher tone shine quite a lot
so that that harmonized quite
nicely yeah so thank you Jim Tracy I'm
have you proud to call me my I also to
call you my
[Music]
chicken y thank you for the rest of the
chat no need to read out loud oh so nice
but I'm fine actually shees girl the
level of spicy and new song is off the
roof you and Moy cooked well and the do
song with Chloe Senpai oh she's not
Senpai your hips are a lethal weapon
after OG song I was kneeling but the duo
knocked me off
completely thank you yeah Double K
bangers
banging your
knees
yeah thank you we did
cook that's why that's why I love my
angels that's why I love them my sweet
angels
than I hope your knees recovered since
then please take it easy chicken knees
are really really weak easy to break
careful I don't think you even have
kneecaps so be
careful SE thank it all marry PPP D get
all for the red super chat yeah you
don't don't
you kimra was mesmerizing and wild card
was so cool oh yeah right you guys are
tadpoles you don't have knees at all or
legs looking forward to Kim's official
release Big Ups to your team for making
these bangers and your coros it's always
a privilege every single time I get to
see you perform my one and only oi is so
amazing thank you D I know a lot of you
guys normally don't listen to K-pop so
having all of you really dig
Chima this is big
PR very very delighted and
honored seems like we hit the right
vein I dabble
Kima goes hard let's go let's
go glad you think so
really two more frog weeks and we'll
finally
hatch what is it four weeks for a
tadpole what
what what do you mean ah do you mean
then it would be a full month and that's
just like the YouTube rhythm of
memberships that's probably what you
mean
survive we don't hear in whole life so
it hits hard honestly I'm surprised not
more especially Ian members try to go
that direction but I'm glad cuz then I
have my
Niche so this n CA is a 10 out of 10
Banger let's
go I hope you guys will be banging your
head once the the real deal comes out on
YouTube and Spotify
Etc so thank
[Music]
you marus all HD all J thanks for the
pinky twice now twice you have made me
soop outside of a concert venue Wawa the
new song was incredible your dancing
with Chloe was Transcendent and sexy I
have the best oi ever and no one can
tell me otherwise we like wa now need I
need a handy you were at the venue right
cuz I saw
you I saw
you and then you were shown on camera
too and
uh the members around me they were like
oh I to kfp and I'm like oh yeah I know
I know I know like I know their name and
they're like really I'm like yeah very
very common
kfp and then feel like they showed
someone
else to and I also recognized them might
not have been a kfp maybe it was was
just like Jimmy or so they were they
they showed a lot of prominent
[Music]
people yeah so I can't imagine how much
of a great time you must have had cuz
you were at the venue as such a hardcore
kfp you must have had the time of your
life you
know so I'm really happy for you can can
na for the pinky K on my knees I can't
kneel any
harder you [\h__\h]
served [\h__\h] oh she swearing hi
smoothie welcome to the
room better release soon because I need
to hear it again those moves I feel
pregnant oh my
God that was sexy if you told me this
was Beyonce or Rihanna song I believe
you nah I don't get those vibes from
from the
song if anything maybe Rihanna but
nah you don't listen to enough Beyonce
or
Rihanna I think Rihanna Rihanna
Rana you need to listen more so you can
tell it
apart maybe the moves definitely not the
song the
moves yeah ah yeah I can actually
actually see some of that yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah actually yeah I think yeah
K-pop Coral are very much like western
style
Coral yeah can't say the same about Jpop
but K-pop definitely adapted that
mhm very cool very nice very hipop
yeah dropped
something this movie comes back cuz I
made the
noise noise hi baby I'm going to pick
you
up no don't
go why won't you just stay in my arms I
love
you she has been
caught she's
so oh my God
God I don't understand like she lets me
fall asleep with my head kind of almost
like low key on top of
her with my whole
arm like on her
belly my hand squeezing her
fur sometimes squeezing her her paws and
all that she lets me do that but and she
lets me carry her around a little bit
but but she doesn't want to sit on my
lap even for a
second what the
hell she does feel safe yeah I think so
like otherwise she wouldn't let me like
she wouldn't she wouldn't fall asleep
while I touch her her paws and don't
squeeze her paws I really squeezed them
and then she falls asleep after purring
endlessly she such a baby I love her
it's so so relaxing to fall
asleep with her purring right in my
[Music]
ear just a smothie thing no smoothie and
choners thing they both don't want to be
lap cats it makes me so
sad my cats it's about my
[Music]
cats
are there lap cats for other people no
of course not no no no no
no you shift around no well it's about
lap cat when I sit there's not about
there's nothing about shifting around
that's if anything a problem when I
sleep but they love to sleep right next
to
me and as I said like even while hugging
them so they don't mind a little
shifting cuz I I made them get used to
it but but when I sit really still even
they don't want to so it has nothing to
do with that they just don't want to be
like held back and restrained I
think Nightmare Before Christmas style
and evanesence
Chima if anything retrospective should
give you Evanescence
Vibes my album song
retrospective I don't know what you're
talking about I cannot hear
that so moving on
and again D thank
you Game 8910
than oh yeah K pop everywhere G thanks
for the red chat
d amazing amazing amazing my Kam oi is
so great man thank
you hearing Kam oian oi or even just
oi makes makes me so so so so so happy
thank you I'm so glad to have you guys
thank
you this means a lot to me
really so much I I
cherish my chi and my Tad
[Music]
poles
love Sai thank you for the
pinky to say that you said the stage on
fire would be an understatement I was
all struck the moment you sang Kimera
the dance and your vocals were just out
of this world and the wild card too sh
the Wild Card truly enjoy to see you
perform love you so much love you too
thank you thank
you I'm glad Kimera was so positively
received I'm glad I chose that song
then yeah I mean I I wish I could have
performed like my album songs too
there's you know some um people also
like especially Japan his Bros when I
was like ego searching I saw them like
fising oh I wonder if she's going to do
pineapple or I hope she's going to do
sleep talking and stuff like that yeah
those would have been candidates if it
wasn't for Kima but I hope even though
it was a new song and you're like uh
don't know how to Vibe I hope it
was uh the best experience and I think
Kima is relatively like it has a a lot
of repetitive wordss like
Chima you know so that's definitely one
thing where you can join in besides that
uh I don't even know it might be
difficult there's this part that goes
haha you can join in
there besides
[Music]
that that part twoo
there's a lot of
Chimas so the
repetitiveness
definitely is something we can work
on De Cima made the biggest splash thank
you yeah it's it's a great opportunity
to promote an upcoming song so yeah I
wish I could have released it right away
but I still hope the promotion takes
effect a little bit
please algorithm please going to try my
best to remind also Japanese Bros cuz I
mean most of the audience there was
Japanese Bros going to try my best to
remind them like hey the song is out now
you liked it a lot didn't you go
listen I super busy so this concert kind
of passed by me but I'm excited to watch
I you didn't watch it at all
yet oh
[\h__\h] oh my God God not ret retrospective
doesn't have a Coro yet but I would
probably just do like a holding a guitar
kind of thing no no real
Coro
so
I'm doing I'm doing once long of the
concert on
Sunday so yeah we didn't last time we
did do the movie because the VOD was not
up
yet okay unknown than for the
pinky D I don't have enough words to say
how awesome you did with everything you
seriously I'm so [\h__\h]
incredible you truly are the best I'm
extremely proud of you my o Kim was
still amaz I can't wait to listen to it
on Loop forever I'll leave that to you
then the looping you are the loop
Master you're in charge of the
loops thank you Kima I think it has good
looping
potential thank you so much unknown I am
so happy you like
it you Loop all my songs so it better be
something you're actually enjoying to
listen to I don't want to I don't want
to torture
[Music]
you for the red chat kiaha wait holy
[\h__\h] it's almost 1:00
a.m. what the [\h__\h] so much for being
efficient I'm going to read this and
then I'm going to
go I mean I cooked yesterday so I don't
have to really cook and maybe I I won't
eat at all I do have leftovers from
yesterday but I I don't know if I want
to eat
anything so I don't have to cook that's
a good
[Music]
thing froggy wa uh I cooked um glass
noodles with um just some veggies like
carrots and leak
Le and like a soy soy based sauce was a
really quick dish because
um the some of the things were like
yeah like the the veggies were pre-cut
in this case some dishes they have some
speed dishes and for those speed dishes
some things are precut or whatever in
this case the veggies were pre-cut
though so supposedly it goes a bit
faster how was it it was all right it
was all right all right all right
H yeah I like glass
noodles I like
[Music]
them yeah thanks for gifting the
membership I need to cook moreid glass M
with glass
noodles yeah I don't I haven't had them
in ages either that's yeah that's why I
want to cook more of them they're pretty
easy they're so easy to
make h I think they're also really great
for like cold noodle dishes cold like
noodle glass noodle salad kind of dishes
I think they are they're great very
versatile yeah so fried scho thanks for
the red chat than you all the
performance you gave on stage today was
out of this world the movement was just
so smooth and the hips oh my gosh the
hip movement was so
hypnotic
that I could swear my ocean was no
longer a chicken but a snake or rather a
Chima amazing song by the
way I can be three things at a time so
it can be a chicken and a snake and um
preferably a phoenix though you can
combine them I don't have to be just one
thing yeah I'm going to be Cima which is
maybe very fitting for the the one whole
life member who do does all the zoos the
M something
something I've done so many that I
became a
Chima M
Chima
oh should I do a video like that is
there is there a Kima on idya cuz I
always use their dorky little pictures I
feel like it's not the same if it's not
from idya which is the website where I
get all those amzo pictures
from Kima
[Music]
I think it's the same word in Japanese
they have but I can put my face three
times in
there their Chima doesn't look cool at
all it doesn't look cool or or badass or
or mythical look at
this
and why is the snake coming out of its
ass why are they aren't they supposed to
the the threee heads to be like next to
each
other Where Heads normally are why is
the snake in the back and why
is why is this
positioning I mean I guess the snake
replaces the
tail wait is this how Chimas usually are
put together
H is this correct oh it always has a
snake oh
really I don't know in this art style it
just looks so
dorky it looks so
silly what I thought Chimas I thought
they have the head like all lined up let
me let me check oh yeah I guess that's
true uh cuz I
think I think I also looked at different
different chimaras that are like you
know like a lion and a dragon and a
goat but the most Cannon Chima seems to
be yeah this
combination
[Music]
ooh yeah I see there's also a a lion and
a dragon and like a it looks like
um what's it called the thing that
[Music]
uh
um not Nota hypog gri yeah
yeah a hypog gri dragon lion combination
where they're also all lined up in one
line so yeah I thought I thought cuz I
looked at those too I thought that's how
it
is they all look
[\h__\h]
up they must be
suffering must be in
pain
[Music]
damn your tail is a [\h__\h]
snake chicken and snake is B basilisk
oh can we get snake V tuber in Hol so I
can make a basilisk unit with
them
[Music]
what a
crony she's not quite a snake she's th I
know people like to connect her with a
snake but she's not
really not really officially a
snake character right
right yeah have
mascot doesn't doesn't make
her really
I can I can team up with her
snake European beast beastar in Legends
basilisk is a legendary reptile reputed
to be a serpent King who causes death to
those who look into its eyes
y little bers small ity bitty
bers frog with no legs and no head
hands
cute oh yeah similar to Medusa mhm yeah
yeah yeah they have similar
skills must be must be coming from the
same B base class and then they spec
into different
classes from the class
tree Base Class same what do you think
is the base
class what is it could it be
not
animal
no you're just saying animal
names
lame I guess makes
sense
tangent tangent is bad
[Music]
and did I read all yeah I did than you
fried
screw D
Dy you will see my hips again I I I I
will show him I hope I hope my hips are
satisfying for you
[Music]
guys yeah these
hips mean they're not
bad I I got some
chunk I got some
gatan I don't know how to a there we
go look look at
that yeah there's something there to
work with
oh I am perfectly hugable and friend
shaped cute there little I mean I I it's
going to be difficult to dance in this
form because obviously
small
limbs but I'll make it work don't worry
I'm I got to take care of this I mean
the MV might be gaha but
um all future performances will be held
by
me what is this cimara doing here get
that out of
here all right guys I'll continue on
super chats uh soon we're at 36 wow
wow
productive tomorrow is Saturday is it
yeah it is already Saturday I think the
stream starts a bit earlier because it's
a longer game I'm hoping to finish it in
one
goal so I'll see you I think 5:00 p.m.
or something like
[Music]
that I hope this time I can sleep longer
cuz I keep on these days because of
smoothie I wake up early then I eat
breakfast
I make thumbnail I put up stream I chill
a little bit and then I go back to sleep
a little bit um I kept on doing that I
if the stream starts earlier tomorrow
then I won't be able to do that
so yeah I thought you just fixed your
sleep schedule no uh no it's basically
just me waking up because of smoothie
annoying
[Music]
me
cute time help
cute no
[Music]
no
cute okay that's it
Kido and and in froggy we
say Arab dirty see you tomorrow we're
playing uh a game that I don't think
they're whole life fan in particular but
they were also looking forward to it the
death of the game tomorrow I think Frog
song um they also tweeted uh about
looking forward to it so they might also
be in
chat yeah thank you so much for
[Music]
today
bye
I
[Music]
byebye frog sleep
frog
[Music]
Amy