[Music]
n
la
[Music]
ah
la
[Music]
h
KY Kitty
ke oh um H we were just talking about
really funny things you missed out we
were like we were like getting into a
discussion and then we were like wait we
should probably like start the stream
yeah so we are um two girls with big
heads you guys are calling us MTO I I
just told her that I'm calling us Luigi
and Daisy because I'm orange you're
green and you are a ghost well Luigi is
not a ghost but he sucks
ghost and I'm recently playing Manion we
that's weird if you say it like that no
there's nothing weird about it yeah when
you chose Luigi's Mansion I was like
that's a questionable Choice what what
oh H do you have a problem with Luigi's
Mansion does it hurt you to yeah he's
sucking my ghost
kind have you ever has
any has anybody ever has any wait what
did you try to ask me has every has
anybody ever tried to okay let's say in
a different way okay okay has anybody
ever tried to vacuum you uh I don't I
think people have tried but nobody has
has nobody has won they've all failed
how does it feel to gets
vacuumed how's it feel um it kind of
like tickles a little tingles yeah oh
nice yeah let's do a little
bgm okay so uh how about you introduce
yourself K
Kitty wrong wrong oh uh can you fix this
so yeah hold on the mic is like drifting
a little you know all of this equipment
I have here right now better than me you
know the mixer thing I know it was like
I have the M arm there it is oh nice all
right okay so introduce yourself my leg
is sleeping [\h__\h] move over you want to
put your leg on mine
it will be hard to reach you honestly
but introduce yourself
oh hello everybody I am M Phantom I'm a
ghost Ma and I'm haunting
Kara's um room
today being
haunted welcome um in my home yeah I was
so I was I was worried like maybe you
would have some salt by your front door
but you had nothing I was able to come
on in it's so funny you say that why
wait my leg is waking up oh when I move
you the pins and needles yeah oh no well
I won't tell you why that's funny for
now but it's funny uh you'll eventually
find out um I'm scared wait is this the
secret ending you were talking
about wait what's secret ending oh no
secret oh no no okay no no no um so yeah
uh this is an off collab y y we just
happened to both be in Japan right now y
y and
we our first collab and off collab and
um I know the first collab first off
Club you you're are you like are you a
fan of
me I I so I have heard that you like me
could that be true
[Music]
maybe a little a normal a normal amount
we actually we had dinner you know we
went YY Nik yeah and we had some nice
chitchat and like every once in a while
she would like like look at me with her
smile and and sparkly eyes and tell me
I'm cute and I'm like oh my God
like you you look boyfriend material I
need to like date you what the hell like
why are you so you she's you're so cute
but you tell me I'm cute no you're cute
it's criminal that you don't think
you're cuter it should be a criminal
that cute girls when the cute girls
don't think they're cute they should be
arrested for cute cries but no I I I um
I did tell you though like like when I
made myself really cute like a couple
days ago I did feel like I was like cute
yeah yeah yeah but yeah today I don't
know about that but um that's why I keep
calling her cute all day and she she
paid for dinner I paid for dinner she oh
and yeah so you know we went to Yakiniku
and like um we had to like choose a
course right so we look at all the
courses and like all these courses have
like things in them that we don't like
but we don't like the same
thing so happy but then it was like it
was like bad because it' be like oh do
you like do you like this no but it
worked out perfectly though who's going
to eat this yeah but actually we ended
up eating like pretty much much
everything so yeah it was good it was a
good amount too and it made me feel so
validated like hey I don't like this
what what you think Everyone likes this
and we didn't like it yeah like for
example you know Japanese people really
love tongue yeah cow tongue yeah same
thing right
yeah they love it but like we don't like
it much it's too chewy yeah we ate it
don't but we did we were adults it's
edible it's just not not our preference
right the other ones were soft and like
they melt in your mouth yeah we had so
much Wu w w w w so much but it was like
a small course so it was like not it was
like the least expensive we didn't
overeat oh yeah but you were asking
about dessert and and I was saying I do
have dessert in my freezer as you saw
and you never had a love potion 31
before is that a are you trying to make
me fall in love with you there's no need
CH it's true I if you're in the mood for
ice cream right now but if you want we
can have ice cream I don't know if I
have spoons uh if I have enough spoons
so do you want to um eat before we
sing actually I guess if anything we
should eat it after the stream I guess
yeah I don't know I don't know I don't
need it right now um it's okay but I
still have a lot of um ice cream in my
fridge yeah in my freezer a lot it wait
can I see it yeah where is the bottom
one yeah bottom a pretty good look I
thought I would eat it so much faster
but these past days I just didn't feel
it actually surprisingly maybe I'm sick
oh my God there's so much in here it's
all the same flavor why do you like this
one so much it's the best and they don't
have like first of all they don't have
bass and Robbins in Austria in the first
place but like even in America this is
my favorite flavor but they only have it
for Valentine's in America for example
so only Japan seems to have this flavor
throughout the whole year love potion
yeah so whenever I get here I eat I'm
going to fall in love with it and then
I'm going to be so sad that I won't be
able to eat it all the time oh but
except for Valentine's do you like mint
chocolate yeah yeah yeah yeah oh why
don't you have any of that in your
freezer I I don't know you know maybe
it's not my favorite I'm going to throw
all of this
away why would you that
no but okay so I have to be honest I
don't like mint
chocolate yeah it's
weird that's okay you like mint
chocolate huh yeah I love I mean is your
favorite ice cream no no then there you
go you're judging me and saying you're
throwing them all away huh but I don't
dislike it a I I like like I'll get mint
chocolate candies and stuff a is that
your favorite chocolate
no what's your favorite
chocolate like Oreo
oh like Oreo ice cream Oreo ice cream is
so good M I do like I I do like Oreos
but I'm never in the mood for them I had
like this one face in my life where I
ate a lot of Oreos and then then that's
it that I never wanted to eat them ever
again but I like you know the hug and
duts with cookies and cream yeah yeah
yeah yeah that one is amazing so good so
good I love having that one is that Oreo
it's not Oreos in there right not
officially was like something like that
yeah I mean cookies and cream is
basically Oreo right yeah yeah kind of
yeah that's what I'm thinking of when I
say or oh okay yeah that's my go-to hug
and duts hug and dut hug and duts no I
usually get the do one of the hug and D
oh the like
caramel yummy yummy do do come to Brazil
come to Brazil
today is
an with us too mhm by the way have you
guys noticed I'm I'm kind of I'm wearing
this to match her but the fact is her
face is so big that you know I I have to
like make myself big too I mean you're
already big you're
already well you know if I if I wanted
to show more of me matching your colors
I would have to like kind of like be
like this that's weird right that looks
so funny I'm too big I'm too big yeah
why can you explain to the people why
are you in this form uh it's not your
normal form it's because I'm traveling I
got to save
ectoplasm weird reasoning but okay we're
not going to question it hey right yeah
don't question
it so we're just going to sing something
maybe we should sing one song now oh
gosh what do you want to start with oh
thanks oh my God thanks for the super
chats by the way it's funny that you
know you paid for my dinner but I'm
getting all the super chats so that's
okay oh also hello iami s
[Music]
Mama yeah I didn't want to meet aami
Mama it didn't work out last time but
this time maybe this time yeah yeah yeah
sounds good yeah yeah yeah I said a
triple triple
fret okay okay let's okay let's you want
to like okay you choose should we just
choose something from this first page
already or maybe that's not a good
starting song is it too exciting for a
starting song Oh wait wait it's fun to
get excited I guess so yeah it's good
okay yeah yeah yeah then our first
song this song's fast sorry I need to
not to
nongo ro ro yeah I can't sing this one
fast so oh by the way guys normally for
like off cab kadas I like take time to
like wrap the lyrics in a way that like
there's split lyrics oh yeah it's just
nicer than singing the whole song
together you know it should be like you
know more organized but no time for that
this time so we're just going to like
tap each other's shoulders to be like
hey is you a part now like whenever we
feel like it it's very very chill what
if I never tap your shoulder I'll just
sit here I'll cheer for you I'll be
like perfect yeah just how you like it
yeah it's my free
concert nah I'm going to I'm going to
tap your shoulder okay several times you
can tap me anytime how how big are
you have to tell in this form huh I just
I don't know why I just you know I was
thinking about tapping your shoulder and
then I thought about tapping something
else
but tap that
ass should I is that how I should I'll
sing I'll sing down
here
no okay first song is out the raps of
yay uh oh
oh let's do this I have I
have let's go it why does it start like
that I we the lyrics it's a lead in it's
a lead there
okay me is this okay guys yeah tell us
the volume we you oh oh Sor I'm confused
Without You
multitasking
[Music]
okay foree
[Applause]
[Music]
we did the dance
together fore
[Music]
with
[Applause]
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
for oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
so chaotic I know it's so
okay I justed the volume a little bit
guys you like it CU I said it's too loud
okay sorry don't
[Music]
with fing bre
me
[Music]
without okay okay thank
you okay guys I see I see you you said B
toot so I made it quieter Melody volume
toot so made it quieter now he's saying
the echo also okay I'm I'm I'm turning
it down don't wor this is a sound test
everybody sound yeah yeah it was it was
pretty loud to reverb yeah yeah sound
like we were literally in Koke I know
like thex we are in karaoke
yeah okay but that was fun chaotic but
fun yeah we're getting it I like the
song really me too it's so fun I have
some memories with the song oh yeah
yeah anything um you could share you
know yeah I think I can share um oh let
me turn this off oh yeah and
turn this on
yeah
um so you know Anime conventions right
yeah I normally neither watch or like
participate in any like stage things m M
like I mean
before poloo uhhuh I I wouldn't even
like watch them I didn't really care
much about those
usually uh but there was one time where
uh like at a at a like small pretty
small localish convention
uhh me and my best friend oh uh decided
to participate in like a singing contest
oh yeah and then uh oh yeah wait I
didn't sing it she sang this song didn't
she she sang it but it feels like I sang
it because like I heard her practice it
like a million times she didn't dance it
no she's just sang it it's so fun to
dance it
though at least this
part the fingers going
out I was about to turn to the I sang it
but then I realized oh I didn't sing it
she sang it you're like gaslighting
yourself yeah I'm living viar sleep for
her pretty much yeah but Nea of us won
anything [\h__\h] sad even though we're
both good singers me and her huh rigged
rigged rigged what did I sing did you
sing you only remember your friend song
yeah why that's
weird or did I sing it I feel like the
song is so hard to sing too cuz there's
like a lot of parts and it's also very
high it has a lot of lyrics
yeah and it's fast yappa yappa yappa
yappa do you guys do you guys like in
the Indie sphere you're Indie right yeah
I'm Indie in the Indie sphere do you
guys say yappa yappa is that the whole
life thing right now what is yappa yappa
ah okay you don't like Skip skippa
skippa and ypp yappa yappa we have these
words now I think it's because of our
new Italian
[Laughter]
Edition yeah it's the Italian virus
Italian virus Mama but immediately like
everybody else is saying it like that
too so cute Sni sniff oh sniff sniff is
a thing thing yeah cuz there's like the
dog sniff it's like an emot on Twitch I
think sniffer sniffer but you stream on
YouTube right yeah oh nice good job we
have we need we need more like you know
streamers on YouTube YouTube yeah like
all these Indies they're on on Twitch
too far it feels like they're like un
yeah a twitch World scares me be now
right it's scary like I just I just I
keep on seeing like things being added
that people don't want like just now
they added this like webcam not webcam
thing but like the webcam apparently
turns on like what the [\h__\h] yeah feel
like it's like a collab feature and it's
just like if you accidentally hit it it
turns on your webcam it a bit Yeah I
they just baned k or something like that
what the [\h__\h] does that mean like what
we wouldn't even be able to do this in
trouble man thank God we're on YouTube I
mean YouTube has you know its issues too
but we like it here don't we guys y Chad
also likes it every every time I like
even mentioned about like dual streaming
or so on Twitch they're like like like
as if as if it's like Doom upon us like
no not twitch I don't I been saying that
for like like a year now and I haven't I
still haven't done it cuz I'm lazy [\h__\h]
I think yeah to set it up it's probably
not that difficult but I'm too lazy to
set it up I I'm do you know how to do it
no I don't God damn it I don't even know
anything about twitch I don't even know
how to I think but I have a Twitch
account and people thought I was fake
because it's so I don't even have a
profile picture and I would go into
people's chats and i' be like hi and
they'd be like that's a fake you need to
ban that person no don't ban her no
she's real oh yeah I think people have a
lot of issue with the ads on Twitch
because they're really long yeah I get
it we have ads here too but not in the
live stream you have you ever pressed
the button to add insert an ad no I've
done it once I don't think it worked why
did you insert ads because I was like
I'm going to torture you guys I'm going
to insert an ad a you're was like you
guys are being
naughty it's like a time out
I like that that's actually using it as
a way to like punish your
fans you yeah she hates you she hates
you guys hey hey you guys are acting up
insert
ad maybe I should do that too where's
that can you show me where's that
but oh no they're going to be like that
would be a good time to insert ad uh but
give it a try yeah where where here oh
my God no wait I didn't is it going to
is it BL I don't know I don't know did
it work I don't know did it work I don't
know oh oh I don't see an ad did you
guys get maybe I don't get it because
I'm premium I'm
premium jokes on you I have premium me
too know it works did some people get an
ad well they won't hear me how long is
the ad I got an
ad she gave me too much power the kfb
are going to be like never let mint on
your this channel ever again n damn
that's funny should I add another one
numbers no ads wait will I get more
money if I add more ads I don't know how
it works everybody's going to skip the
ad they won't even care this is this is
kind of tempting no was it just 5
seconds I guess cuz you can skip it
really fast guys don't cancel me for
teaching her how to insert I only know
about it because that little pop-up will
come up I mean you just want me to like
be successful in life and make money
right got to put in the ass I want my oi
to be rich thank you so that I can
actually pay for a I got a sixc ad oh
that's not bad oh Skipper Skipper
Skipper
Skipper okay let's sing another song
okay is there something here that you
know un like I at do the that one this
one yeah oh do you know it well yeah
that's why it's in my favorite I don't
think it's very good I'm not very good
at singing it though but okay
um okay we'll test the volume it just
let us know if it's anything's too loud
or too quiet you guys yeah I'm trying to
adjust on the goal yeah show
show only my world one oh
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah I see you gave up on your phone
lyrics and they reading from here yeah I
did this one's not bad okay
[Music]
is it okay okay probably
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
for
[Music]
fore for
[Applause]
[Music]
very difficult
right my mouth
just ya yaa
[Music]
wow
looking Loop this planet to away only my
[Applause]
[Music]
amazing
amazing yay you did good thank you you
did good thank you your voice died a
little bit there from being Gremlin
mode what what song is like a good song
for you to go
like um there one huh is there one like
a good
one let me see if there's hamutal uh is
it um I have to like write it exactly
the way it's oh yeah yeah just put in
hamut
talo hamu is like Katakana right hamu
yeah and then T is Kani yeah yeah the
Kani oh this one yes okay I can uh at
least I think sing the chorus I don't
know about the rest yeah mean it's the
same the whole
time and I'll do the calls and you sing
it all right I'm excited okay yeah yeah
yippe yippe okay she's going to fulfill
her Destiny this is the only thing I'm
good at have
no that's not true you can do more than
just Dan okay okay
[Music]
myself
fore
[Music]
foree
fore speee
[Music]
[Applause]
to God are you okay yeah I'm going to
get noise
complaints oh forgot I'm so sorry no
like that's okay cuz I made you do it
but like I realized after I made you do
it I know I'm sorry I got to I got to
into it I got to it's funny oh no
neighbor must be like what the [\h__\h] is
there a gremlin next door what the
actual
[\h__\h] my neighbor being weird again
yeah Noisy Neighbor
this so why does this cute song for
children have such an insane call
explain is there history to this
actually I don't know I think it's just
easy to do it too oh I yeah makes sense
you just want to like add it to
unexpected yeah yeah maybe it's fine is
there other children songs like is there
like Pokmon songs that have
that uh I think so can't I I know there
is some I can't remember the names of
them all there's some probably someone
in chat that will be like yeah this
one you can mix anything you guys yeah
that's true although I'm I'm really not
you know I maybe you don't know we need
to get to know each other so I need to
tell you so uh you know I like Hello
project yeah or I used to more than now
but um so they don't like do proper
mixes usually there yeah they just go
like hi hi hi
and somebody I like that one though I
that's the farthest that they'll go
probably in terms of like
mixes you some people did do that okay
she's motioning like can you explain
what is that it's like so you flip your
arms or your hands out yeah twist them
yeah you twist them out and then when
you twist them back in you make a heart
and then you just do it over and over
again yeah yeah you just reminded me I
saw
like otakus do that at the
concerts and like sometimes they would
do like some Oshi jumps but more and
more they got like um strict yeah and
said they banned it like in most venues
but but even then sometimes even I would
sometimes do Ori
jump and CU you know I got to oh she
jumping so fun be mindful of your
neighbor everybody but also oi jump oi
jump o JP yeah yeah what else do I do my
I'm I'm always trying to teach my people
to do ketcha and like like recognize the
moment when you have to do ketcha it's
basically always just the calm portion
of the song is when you do the ketcha
you guys remember do you remember what
ketcha is if you don't I'm really mad
I'm going to place an ad right now
everybody what is it remember what Ketch
is mate mint fans are not allowed to
answer because they probably know you
remember you remember
yeah yeah you but you you say you
remember but then say what it is a slow
Rising yeah yeah Kesha no
not Justice
[Music]
for they don't really seem
to disappointing I told them several
times always tell them kch kch it's
important you have to send your energy
to the idol you know oh my God YouTube
YouTube overloaded my memory on my
Chrome but now I place the I
the can't stop me my finger is going to
press it I'm going to do
it do but you are doing to to
me I want to do it I want to do it we
don't even see what the is three two one
oh she's gone mad with power you guys
she's mad
give me the money YouTube give me the
money wait okay come back guys come back
come back are you back someone said
dodged D I got a beer
ad we could do the ad what's the ad we
can advertise just yesterday I was
advertising um wa let me bring it over
the headphones right
yeah here let me bring it over uh here
uh okay here's the head here's the head
everybody
y let's let's get rid of that otherwise
I'm going to have to like Mark the
stream as sponsored oh oh oh what was I
going to say ah do you know okay I'm
going to ask you something
okay why are you
gay why are you gay what you don't know
wait you don't know
it the ghost but no oh
no I think I'll have to show you later
it's hard to explain in words um you
just asked me didn't even know I
understood I thought you were I thought
you like relatively well informed on the
internet culture I like this this is
like from many many years ago like
centuries is a century 10 years or 100 I
always 100 [\h__\h] what is the 10 decade
decade it's like two decades ago or so
what yeah but everybody knows it I
didn't know it I only found about it
recently now you can teach me it's like
there's this okay it's a news
program um in a let's say it's it's a
long time ago and it's but even then
like it's it's in a in a place where
it's not really accepted at this point
you know and then the newscaster like
they invite like somebody who is gay and
actually no I but you know the
newscaster just goes right away and asks
like why are you gay and and then yeah
like you know and then and then you know
I thought it was like why are you
running you know that one like why are
you
running that's similar I guess but
that's different right that's different
though yeah why are you gay and then and
then he's like who is gay and why so do
why you do so to
[Laughter]
me it's so funny uh there's like a video
of a Channel I used to watch I don't
remember even what it's called but they
had like howto videos but they were
never actually the how-to videos and it
was like how to summon a ghost and then
he has the little Ouija board and he
goes hey ghost does your mom know you're
gay wait wait wait a second wait a
second do you know that I
recently somewhat recently summoned you
on a Ouija board yeah yeah you know I
know I saw I saw you saw I was like busy
and then I was like
what the [\h__\h] ising me what's happening
oh yeah I I had to think of you even
before I maybe that's how I you know
found out about you I don't know
maybe Ouija board Luigi board Luigi
board is that why you call me Luigi no
but it could be another
connection another one con did you know
did you know guys and and
little mid Min yeah did you know Ouija
boards are like just totally controlled
by yourself wait what no no no no no no
no no I've always controlled the Ouija
board ah you the one you say you're the
one yeah as the ghost as the ghost well
you didn't have much control over mine
I'm going to have to tell you I was in
full control of M I was
[Music]
busy so like if you weren't busy you
would have taken over yeah ah so it only
didn't work because there was were no
available ghosts in the vicinity yeah
everybody you know ghosts have like very
busy lives
[\h__\h] y'all have probably way too
much free time what do you guys do all
the time up there like where are you
anyway I'm being a ghost made what what
I'm paying my taxes my ghost taxes why
are you not why are you not moving on by
the way like is there's surely ghosts
who are not actively ghosting and are
just like moving on to like I guess the
are you in the afterlife I died and I
have unfulfilled business ah so what is
the business cute girls here I am I know
so are you done
now what okay here I go I'm going
to wait she has to find there she goes
there she
go so have you have you had many ghost
friends who then just like are done with
the business and they leave yeah is that
a sad
thing yeah I mean you know is it is what
it is is there like a kind of like a
beef between um remaining ghosts like
you who just do like fun and cute things
versus the ghosts that like haunt
haunted mansions and like haunt people
like in an evil way do you guys have
like beef is this like two different
like fractions and stuff like that I'm
also an evil ghost so what people about
you yeah I'm a vengeful
ghost yeah is that your lore yeah really
what wait but didn't you say your
business is cute girls what so are you
vengeful
about well you know it's keeping me here
there's still more cute girls to see
where's the Vengeance though someone
said no wonder she's so mean and places
[\h__\h] ads
[Laughter]
everywhere I'm I'm I'm I'm done
questioning you for now okay even though
I feel like there's some plot holes what
no
M you don't seem evil I am very evil my
chat would say I'm evil I think my
chat says that with the cutest chibi
face smile ever
say ridiculous there's nothing evil or
scary about her at all she's barely a
ghost like I can literally touch her my
hand doesn't go through her guys I think
she's a
faker it's all just like a scam guys
she's not
no it's because you're a mythical
creature you're a
phoenix why have you manifested in front
of me H you summon me I summon you yeah
that's ages ago you're [\h__\h] late can
I get a refund I had to answer everyone
else summoning me first what priorities
I thought it was like you AI or
something it's like a miss you know God
do some
conflicted okay okay let's let's let's
uh here go so shy if my Oshi summons me
like I'm going to question it I'm going
to be like I can't go to my oshi's house
so scary you were probably also confused
because like when I summoned you I was
in Japan and then it took you a while to
arrive but then I was gone because I was
back in Austria ah it's like Santa Claus
I'm trying to find your chimney together
yeah yeah you were looking for me and
then you finally thought you found me in
Austria but then I was in Japan again
also what if someone anyone is like
using a Ouija board is like I'm Takashi
Kiara and I'm summoning like it could be
a come on you can't be like deceived by
something you would know a person's soul
wouldn't you I thought that sometimes
they're really convincing but if they
like use a
soundboard it's ridiculous like kitty
soundboard you're so bad at your
job it's not even my job I'm a
maid
wait stop thinking about I have to think
deeply about you fall apart okay but why
is a phoenix own why is a phoenix own a
a fast food joint well oh you want to
hear it you want to hear it well okay so
i' I I've revived many times I've done
many things and now I'm just doing that
because I'm I'm kind of like sick of
fighting and also there's not much to
like be fighting here in this world
anyway yeah and so you know well why
can't I be a ghost
made because okay so you're saying
you're normally I I wouldn't be able to
touch you normally then how are you able
to touch a
broom I don't I okay also wouldn't you
sometimes accidentally suck yourself
into the vacuum no I'm a I'm a I'm a
made Cafe maid
don't I'm not I'm not
cleaning as if you if you break dishes
you don't clean those
either dishes is there no dishes well
our patrons are ghosts
so oh so ghost ghost uh ghost Cafe yeah
they come for the ghost the maid
service wait is there nothing to eat
eat oh what's the point
then for Mo magic so ghosts have a need
for more magic but no need for food and
drinks and so oh I get my food and
drinks from um s like you know when
someone offers offerings oh yeah like at
a shrine or something you know and then
it's basically wasted because you can't
take it in in your body right so they're
wasting it's not
wasted I'm I'm questioning you so
much I like questioning you youve never
met a ghost
before have
I guys tell me if I
have a ghost a
ghost I I mean I've met you should ask
you Casper you should ask Kia she
probably knows all about it you know
yeah but I I I think her ghost Laura is
probably very different from
you you guys have like differing
accounts know maybe she reaped you
oh could that be do you remember who
reaped
you no no may have been how long is it
ago uh I don't really
remember long time ago probably a and
then she might have she might have done
it cuz like she hasn't been actively
doing it for a long time true true but
then you know she has been doing her job
apply for a long time could have been
her so you know maybe you know cie
longer than I do
maybe the Lord goes deep everybody
enough that now sorry I'm bringing us
deeper and deeper okay okay uh is there
anything else you want to sing here it's
okay okay what about here
M feel free to say next
next oh do we want to do sad
song Maybe at the end at the cry at the
end you guys going to
cry H you want to do the can I actually
did I sing that song before
in hello oh it should show up
[Music]
um maybe should show up
what no and like I'm like 100% sure it's
there somewhere it's just like like
weird I don't understand this program so
much wait you like um you like uh
the yeah maybe we sing a b song you're
not bringing up the one that somehow
weirdly uh fits us you me right which
one the the one that fits summer
summer ah oh okay okay
uh I have it of
course it's just a matter
of this app finding what I need to find
right one page bro it's 100% in
here it's just weird like you have to
enter things like in a way oh yeah yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah oh wait ni
what that's impossible ah you
know
um oh sometimes it's different like
that is it not in my favorite though I
didn't see it I don't think sorry
guys
memories oh wait how do they ride ah
wait if I if I ride it with capital yeah
I think cuz that's also
oh okay okay okay okay if I write it
like this search Tada oh it's very
specific it's so specific like when I
wrote Honey works just in lower letters
guys it doesn't show up if I write
honeyworks with a big h and a Big W then
show then it works then it shows up wow
it's so specific um we're looking
for why is there not in there oh don't
even is
it do you know any of the others not
very
well not even this one oh I know that
one a little I only know the chorus I
think though because of the anime you
only know a little bit okay wait
uh wait k me no
she it isn't it written like this yeah
it is maybe they don't have itd okay we
got to go for my list girl okay sorry
from your list okay sorry sorry
everybody it's not it's okay no it's my
fault it's the it's it's no one's fault
ghost rule do you know you're a ghost
you should be able to sing the song I no
I know it it's so good though I know it
but I don't like know how to sing
it learn it okay for the
future um I was thinking like cuz like
this Bak song is by the the sing the
like voice actor but the the other one
doesn't is not sung by a voice
actor
um
nothing I'm just looking at everything
how about
that one that one oh gosh okay I will
it's so nostalgic it's so nostalgic I
don't I remember the chorus mostly I
don't remember the verses very well so
I'll do my figure it out you you'll
remember it yeah yeah yeah I'll figure
it out you'll remember I'll I'll remind
you I'll bring it back into your this
was
nostalgic
yeah can't type yay can't do the uh star
no it's okay okay here
Go Happy materal yaho do you guys know
the song are you guys Boomers too I sang
it before in a k a while ago and they
were like oh my God oh my God yeah so
nostalgic it's from Neiman
[Music]
yoak happy ready go
something
[Music]
woo
okay
[Music]
for why do I give you the difficult
[Applause]
[Music]
oh go when you do it I want to join
in so five one you're my idol no thank
you cuz that move that we just did I
know I know it's I think it's in h 22
yeah
[Music]
happy hi
[Applause]
hi two SC two SC two
SC yay
fun cute yeah that song so fun to do
calls too so easy so wow we got nongo
joed by our wait we
did we so Nong I was about to
say you
two I'm so close to saying it but it
didn't want to be
Savage
[Music]
you you usually say that I sometimes
saying and it's usually like they they
find it funny but at the same time I
feel so Savage for I feel like they were
cool yeah it's just a joke yeah it's
joke it's joke it's
joke are you guys having fun CH are you
guys having fun cuz we're having like a
like a kind of like a egoistic amount of
fun it's funnier I think when you like
like you know are in the room
but it's probably
still right
yeah my my cheeks kind of hurt like from
like smiling smiling me
[Music]
too but why are you looking at me I'm
I'm I'm I'm I'm happy
to see you yeah get to know you me too
you're so cute know you I like you I
like I like that you like
me I don't just like you I love you oh
my
God I like people that like me like
those people are really nice for some
reason like specifically the people who
like me are really nice to me I don't
know why it makes no sense they like
that's so weird then why would they be
nice to you if they like you yeah people
who don't like me I feel like they hate
me so
rude I'm just like joking I'm just
making no sense I'm having her for you
guys your arms were uh you're you're
cold wait you warm you're a ghost why
why the [\h__\h] are you
love you guys you are a phoenix you
should be fiery
hot no you're just I'm absorbing I'm
absorbing your energy that's why you
just you just I'm eating your life force
you just don't know it what the [\h__\h] get
out of here you invited me in I get to
eat your life force why did I it's not
even October why did I all go somewhere
weird do you want to hang out again in
October yeah for sure I was like already
kind of like thinking about that but do
we like can we like I got to come to you
I really want to go to Austria please
like [\h__\h]
do I told you I would before a I have to
and you in a a certain cockroach oh yeah
she came to see you didn't she or no
yeah but like she said she wanted again
oh and like she said she would come with
you do you want to hang out with her
when she comes here where's here Japan
yeah Japan when is she coming uh in like
a week
yeah she's coming in a week I think so
yeah what let's [\h__\h] go yeah we can
all hang out I really don't have much
time to be honest you know my SCH I know
you don't she was showing me her
schedule you guys this we we got to have
dinner or something like that we can we
can arrange like a lunch or a
dinner that's fun
hey
how show me with your fingers
[Music]
uh yeah it's a very busy time for wa and
the whole of English I think until this
day huh yeah okay we can probably figure
out like a dinner date or something I
don't think we can do like a collab I
don't think so either sorry we can just
do like an online collab sometime in the
future as well we'll we'll talk to you
we'll tell you what we what we ate and
you girls are always welcome to visit me
I want to see your
cat you you know I I I came to this
realization that guys can you post the
the cat emotes for the ones who know
what I'm talking about because like yeah
that's us oh my God it is literally us
like I I am my own cats you you smoothie
I'm chunkers turns out oh my God didn't
realize I was my own cat I'm I'm I mean
your hair's got mint in it like me yeah
like we were I guess always kind of
supposed to yeah we look so good
together we do honestly I never called
it mint though I I used to just call it
turquoise I I'm not sure is that Mint or
turquoise I mean if it's mint in my hair
it's mint in yours it is kind of the
same tone right yeah it's not as
invisible in this hairstyle um on the on
the tips in this hairy it kind of
becomes more green at the very bottom
but in it depends on my hairy yeah but
if you look at the kis yeah I know they
have the same color to it's mint it's
mint where is turquoise more blue I I
think so I think turquoise is a little
more blue like my no not like my ribbons
like a light blue oh yeah that's light
blue is it some people saying turqu
darker it's more blue yeah yeah yeah now
I got to look it
up or
turquise wow you know how to spell that
oh no you don't
yeah no that's just that was an accident
I know how to spell it I don't know how
to spell it actually but that was like
more green and that was more blue like
at the T because I guess it's a stone
it's like a shade right or like it's
there's a shade range yeah there's so
many shades it's one of these colors
overlap you guys mint overlaps with
turquoise are you actually made of
turquoise turquoise turquoise made made
turqu and then like mint color
Ah that's that is that's not even your
color you are not you're not that I am I
am I am though that's green that is I'm
going to expose you first of all you're
not a ghost and you're not even [\h__\h]
mint that's green what the [\h__\h] is that
look at that Google is lying to you I
have this other one too
no you're not no they're going to call
me
turquoise me she see another one that's
not her now let me pull up
turquoise you're you're um what do you
say when someone's not a fake uh you're
um imposture no something like that um
here what's
the that's literally that's your color
no it's not that's too blue that's too
blue that's too blue that's more similar
than the greens no just so messed
up this is so funny
someone's someone's calling you out for
bullying they said this is bullying
you're
phony no you're fraud that's what I
wanted to say fraud I'm a big your frog
and the fraud wait this is the same no
wait that's the wrong one no that's no
that's not good no it's too blue that's
too blue that's too blue it's too blue
it's too blue but you're not even you're
not the green one either I'm if anything
you're closer to what I just pulled up
no I'm closer to the
m why you you said it's two blue right
or two green two blue you said that
one's yeah two blue this one yeah like
that like turquoise that's pretty you
happy with that one yeah yeah yeah yeah
you like that one yeah yeah
that's the
same lit she approves of it that's her
here they overlap it's that's that is
straight up mint color sufficiently
light
turquoise made turquoise has anybody
pointed this out to you before no
it's so over name Chang incoming oh my
God I have to
Rebrand I have to graduate and then come
back as mid turquoise oh no I'm sorry
what for what I have caused I think wait
um maybe that's a good timing for a sad
song oh yeah okay let's sad song it was
on the previous yeah but would you say
it's the last one or more you have more
time oh um
[Music]
been yeah we can have more time okay but
we're so sad about your upcoming image
change um so you could just recolor
yourself no slightly adjust the Hue no I
am
M okay your sad song wait can I do
something real quick yeah yeah hold
on got to do this here we go you doing
what are you doing can you change the
color here no I mean I can
hold on I want to do um wait I think
it's this one I don't even know there we
go
okay I have no empathy for this fra
froster
fraer you're a fraudster I'm a froger
you're
a I knew that you were in love with a
certain
frog you guys
you can't say can't or
can yeah you could say later say later
okay say
later let's go okay sad s time everybody
be sad more sad okay I'll be sad
try well I'm I'm actually
happy you you're supposed to be sad you
should
yeah it's so J for me guys it's K
[Music]
over our
cycle our someone was pretty
[Music]
great
for
[Music]
fore
for
[Music]
no go all
day
[Music]
for fore
I think if you don't know the anime the
lyrics can mean happy things though yeah
maybe right that's true it feels happy
to me stop crying you little [\h__\h] okay
I'll stop crying I'll stop
crying I'm normal now y y
a
yeah memories good memories summer and
but it's like I think it's like you're
not going to meet again like meet again
after 10 years and like you know yeah
we're going to meet again before before
then 10 years so it's okay okay oh to
God like tomorrow kid no not tomorrow
want to sleep over huh no I can't even
like I had a massage yesterday oh and
then I felt pretty decent after that
more or less it was an okay massage then
I don't know had better massages yeah
but sometimes like when I sleep in this
bed uh I sleep really bad and wake up
with lots of pain ah it's a hard Bend
it's not really but like the pillows
[\h__\h] too a can I feel your
bed not right now oh okay well yeah last
night I um slept really bad and then
even though I just got the massage yeah
I woke up and and had like huge pain in
my like shoulder blades and my no is the
pillow May or you said it's like the
pillow like okay I brought my own pillow
too but like the pillow that's here is
like really thin flat oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's like too low and my own I
don't know it's not not really meant to
be the main pillow mine is just like a
support emotional support pillow why
yeah how can you feel bad you you ghost
why are people like M I just wanted to
feel the like the soft it was I was just
going to go was my head no naughty
thoughts get your heads out of the
gutter everybody
oh
what she's leaving me what's happening
what's happening that's your
friend oh my
God she has a
boo my boo do you want to be my boo
yeah wow did where did you get this like
a crane game yeah Ena got me this at the
cuz like I've been you know I've been
playing Luigi's Mansion a game that you
hate so much um for whatever reason
can't understand because you're a fraud
anyway
um I've never seen you I've never seen
you burst into flames once can you show
me right
now not now because because of my belts
that hook Papa put on me mhm the belt my
chest Bel fashion accessory that's a
fashion accessory no it's real I I
cannot only my full power because of the
belt it's under my skirt I want to see
you turn into a bird a big bird right
now I want to see that too but like it's
the belt please complain to hook Papa
what did I just
say she's not even reacting to
it yeah but like yeah I I kind of like I
I I think I always like boo but
depending on the game I like Boo more or
less boo but boobs too I like boobs boob
single boob bo boo I like you like boo
yeah I have a boo plushy too and I I
actually have a quite a boo things I
have like a boo NightLight that I keep
under like in my room oh uh you know
there's another hole I remember that she
got me she's really really good at crank
games too and she also got me a booing
it's like not a night light but it does
light up when you like hit it why you
why are you abusing him why do you have
to hit
him why I don't are you bullying if I if
I hit you do you light up maybe well no
because you're a fraud I'm not a
fraud w't let me hit
you didn't light up I did it
telling you guys I'm telling you you
don't know
anything she's like she's trying to make
fun of me now it doesn't work it won't
work like that no it does work no I'm
calling you out is there a song that
where I can say I'm sorry to you for for
the
song Oh the bottom this is about
you I S this for you I don't no this one
I okay sing for you she you can this is
bullying this is such bullying but I
mean the lyrics don't fit so much it's
just a title that
fits oh my God but you're calling me a
cosplayer I'm not like Mar I'm not
like that's
[Music]
you this is so nice s though this is so
messed
up okay C with the bo plushy okay he's
going to absorb my tears yeah no absorb
the the ghostess maybe you become more
of a ghost
[Music]
I'm
sorry I'm
sorry don't no yeah you
[Music]
are I'm gonna hate this
song we're finding meaning in this
one fore
[Music]
love you even if you're not a
ghost I'm a
ghost okay don't say it's
[Music]
okay for
[Applause]
[Music]
the song is so sad no yeah yeah it's
your voice so Ela thank
[Music]
you goodbye give me
fore
[Music]
for I love you very much
you know what that means no
transparent no true no it's not true yes
it is I just I'm sucking your life
energy you guessed
it yeah good job
yes do you want to sing a Sola song okay
I want to sing that last one with you
too right there eventually okay we could
do that one okay then one son on now and
then we can s that I think probably by
the if you want
to yeah she sent this too do you want to
sing this alone I would feel so
self-conscious I want to hear
it oh I will we get it oh my god oh yeah
lyrics better looked up on the phone
yeah come up on the phone for we're
going to get a special solo from this
ghost oh my God she's going to um maybe
Sparkle do ghost Sparkle I thought it's
vampires right yeah vampire Sparkle but
now you're going to spk oh my God I'm
nervous don't just jump in if you need
if you okay if I need help jump in okay
let see does this
work oh yeah
over yeah
[Music]
yeah strange box and
Cima lying down on the floor late night
and you don't know don't know don't know
don't know what to do hard to tell
what's wrong what's right if yes or no
don't no don't know what to do oh the
storm it's hard and you're losing the
way just take a chance hand down in the
rain cuz you got the key never throw it
away don't forget don't
forget get out of my head life is only
what you make it you're going to be
okay so go ahead and do it do it if you
want let's just get do it everybody's
going to know your name the Sparks like
the flame turn the Dark of the night
into day don't stop don't stop just
going Your Own Way shut up I'm
frozen the head in the game keep up keep
up and never be afraid of make it hot
like a volcano strike a match and burn
it up kick your feet against the table
to the feet of your own job the Sparks
light the flame so don't wait start a
fire today don't stop don't stop just go
your own
way I'm looking back oh gosh wait this
part do this part the gas loud going so
fast that it shouldn't be loud that's
how we like it you heard what I said get
out of my head life is only what you
make it you're going to be
okay so take a step and move it move
itless you try you won't get through it
everybody's going to know your
name cuz I T of the night in today don't
stop don't stop just go your own way
Don't Be Afraid trust your heart keep
your head in the game keep up keep up
and never be
[Music]
afraid this part so
high oh my God it's so
high he hey
[Applause]
your so don't be afraid just your heart
keep your head in the
game never be afraid make itot like a
volcano take a m and burn it
up to the Beet of your
own so don't wait start a fire today
don't don't
[Music]
just yeah yeah oh my gosh that's so much
pressure singing an original song of
yours in front of you oh my God it's so
fun how like in the last uh chorus
normally I have to decide am I going to
sing the chorus normally or am I going
to f on the ad
lips we can share it I love saying that
part I love singing that too I thought
everyone you were going to sing the
normal part and I was going to sing that
sorry it's okay I like that part I do
whenever I listen to that part I'm
[Music]
like oh my god I've never sung that song
like I've never even tried singing it
before but you were the one who
suggested it I know cuz I like it but
then I got really
anxiety it's okay ghost of anxiety
interesting ghost anxiety do you know
what about like Chima we don't have to
sing it but like I like him I well I
pressed
full oh you did you know I I see you
like that ass
yeah oh my God God how the hell that
Happ wa ghost things see I am
transparent it fell through my head my
headphones fell off you guys and it like
went through my head why did it only
happen now why doesn't it constantly
Happ because my energy is running
low okay I think we can maybe do one or
two more songs what do you say time wise
yeah I think so too two two
or cuz like we could do like this one
too I don't know if you you don't have
to we can just like end it with this one
too I don't know we could do both if you
want to do this one and then end it with
another yeah okay okay good it'll be
good advertisement too for my thing oh
okay she's skiper Skipper Skipper skiper
Skipper Skipper Skipper oh do you want
to be Cher or um I don't remember if
they show it in this app uh if they
don't then I'm I won't be sure which one
is which do you know it by heart uh uh
wa let me check yeah let's see if it
shows shows let's see like a proper K
application will it show
us
oh interesting way of showing it but
okay that works that works
interesting which one do you want to be
uh no you suit Lanka more obviously it's
okay I'll beer no I'll be chery I'll be
Cher but which one is Cheryl uh the
first one right okay yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
let's
[Applause]
go for
[Music]
down
[Applause]
[Music]
but you have no
bones I'm not even
[Music]
you know like the melody the medley
version ble yeah they like in this part
they sing like
the oh
[Music]
it's so
cute kcha
[Music]
let's
go for
[Music]
you were like organize it so I was
like that so funny I was trying to like
communicate to you while we were focused
on singing like are you going to sing
the high one or or the low
[Music]
one it kind of worked out it worked out
no it worked out
[Applause]
y it worked out but because we were
looking at each other and trying to
communicate we messed up right yeah
sorry
everybody did you guys hear that that
was our headphones smashing together sad
I I was going to have like a good like
friendship moment putting my arm around
her like you know like but our our
headphones just Bonk Bonk
I'll give you a hug later yeah if I can
you yeah oh can I I'll possess someone
outside are you okay with hugging
strangers
actually I'll possess them and I'll be
like hey Kiara you want a
hug I don't know about that headphone
blocked
everybody oh man that was fun I really
I'm happy we can do this yeah I know
actually I think this is my first ever
off collab like karaoke ever it's not
like like you like I mean I guess you I
mean you've been I guess around for a
while but you just like weren't like
streaming for a long time you lazy ass I
you know please don't say you are
lazy crazy yeah I'm crazy not
lazy oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's accurate oh surely yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I stopped streaming for a
couple years it wasn't really my thing
oh now it is your finger gam yeah I'm
it's my whole personality I made it my
personality change of mind change of
heart change of spirit yes
yes so cute girl next to me we in whole
life Ian yeah are having
a [\h__\h] concert this weekend this
weekend oh my [\h__\h] god that's insane
it's coming closer with every day I know
oh my gosh I'm so excited for you I'm
getting anxious now nervous why I don't
know I don't you're born for the stage I
think it will be like pretty different
from our last one M like in a few ways
um so I hope people will enjoy it and
like it are you are you excited for New
York yeah I've never been to New York
yeah I was telling her how to be careful
was guys you didn't have to tell me I
already heard like a lot of like things
about New York I was like don't accept
the friendship bracelets they're not
real yeah but those are like everywhere
that's I think not just New York they're
like oh yeah that's true yeah the
Friendship isn't real you
guys ours is real
yeah so wait was I was going to ask oh
yeah do you have a ticket for like uh
streaming oh uh not oh is this being
streamed too yeah of course oh I can
send you free one really
mhm if you want yeah yeah oh my gosh I
send you one is it okay yeah
[Music]
sure but only if you help me advertise
to all your ghosts that are watching the
stream too the concert by singing Our
Song which I will just say she was the
one who suggested singing it anyway okay
song so much I actually sing this song
all the time to myself what really I
love this song it's so cute I got to I
got to get the lyrics I actually I'll
put them up on on this screen if you
want to read oh okay yeah that works
too uh will that bring the right song
well yeah but that's kind of like far
isn't it for you let me let me like and
like put it there if Windows 11 doesn't
like mess with me okay now we okay like
is this close enough for you to see yeah
that's good that's good that's good are
your ghostly eyes good enough to see
that yeah I I I have good eye vision are
you looking at my contacts yeah yeah
that's the only reason why you have good
eye vision right now I didn't know ghost
have to wear contacts okay a lot of a
lot of the ghost world is like the
regular world like the the you know the
human world it's it and it's not great
that's why when people are just like oh
you're ghost you must be able to do like
I still have to pay my ghost taxes so
awful huh so you need like lenses but
you don't need food no I do need food I
get it from the offerings remember oh
yeah but you don't eat it yes I do I'm
like I thought didn't you say something
else and I'll possess people I'll
possess my I'll possess the Wisps my
viewers my fans and then I eat that when
they're eating like them during dinner
and then eat and I'm like oh that was
delicious thank you and then you
possessed them yeah I thought they're
dead too oh no not always no not always
she's so inconsistent maybe dead
inside yeah me too yeah okay it's okay
though the next song will be the last
song The Last Song
everyone and I would gladly like to
invite everybody to watch Wawa in
concert this weekend y yeah there's uh
streaming tickets um they're I don't
think they're in my description right
now but if you go look up breaking
Dimensions the name of the concert or
whole life English concert whatever it
will come up on Google yeah um and you
can you don't have you don't have to
stream it on streaming plus you can also
stream it on spawn if you don't have
access to streaming Plus for whatever
reason wherever you uh live you know
wink won wink so you know wink
exactly that the name of the song yes
that's the name of the song that's the
name of the song baby all right I hope
you guys had fun I think we had lots of
fun let's collab
again okay here we go I think the song
starts right away oh right away you're
right you're right okay I'll try to do
the okay
alling the distance across the sea
endlessly
cheerfully meaning High to
[Music]
Heart waking from a dream Swift up into
a stream I make a wish and wait for my C
how will I connect
in this new frontier we're joining
through he thriving in a scene where no
one's ever been with vibrant colors
bursting like stars radiant and War
charged with energy that's carried us
this far do the
calls each new de brings a miracle to
life stop rning on top straight to the
top that's right
we're ready to change the game a
shimmering showcase creating a new place
where we can shine day by day sparkling
stories will
intertwine get ready to cross the waves
foring forward with courage to run
toward a brand new stage let's go live
Bridging the distance across the sea
endlessly follow
me and we'll turn to p
hi breaking oh breaking through the
doubt we know clearly toing toing trial
sharing all our hopes we can conquer any
challenge with a
smile
wo we'll link our hearts as we search
across the globe knowing no matter where
we are no matter how far we can be
let's
[Music]
go I want to chase a wish
unwaveringly playing out a grand story
share the future that we can see making
them
reality take my hand and reach for the
screen all we need our glittering dreams
our hearts and souls all fulfilled in
the world we
be we're ready to seize the day
traversing the pathways discovering
highways the everywhere step by steping
stories that we can share get ready to
lead the way with each generation a
shining sensation a dream UNF let's make
friends making a moment of History
joyfully follow me we'll connect the
world they'll hear our song ringing out
over Hills and O our Legend grows and
continues we'll carry on Starting Now
setting Hearts In Motion connecting all
of
[Music]
[Applause]
woo that part is so good I love the
ending I love that part too I mean I
love the reference to the uh Japanese
songs too but like the ending it hits so
much it always makes you so emo every
time yeah when I first like recorded
this for like the the release version I
man I felt like when I was standing in
the recording boo I felt like I was like
in the you the [\h__\h]
musical
overs that part oh my God I remember
when you guys released it I was like
repeating it I was
like so good is there anyone in the chat
who's going to our concert in
[Music]
person are you I know there's like you
know not much space in the venue
unfortunately so there's not many oh but
arm in
W me me me me thank you I wish me me me
just so you know when like you you just
if you don't know how to vibe to songs
you know just usually you can just go
like hi hi for anything that's like you
know in that kind of rithm just follow
the the crowd yeah and then when it's
like quiet then you do the catcher you
know not the Keta you do the KET the
yeah that's all you really need to know
oh yeah but I I I haven't seen whole
lifean fans do do that I think so far
really we need to have like aay teaching
stream I mean I I like I before and you
know here and there we try but it's hard
to get like everybody into it really but
it's okay I feel like they'll get it
they'll get it yeah yeah just follow the
dudes with the uo so true also the
problem is like um I feel like all of
these techniques if you know it well you
know how to apply to any song but i' I
don't know I still feel like you guys
like might need like guides to each song
so far the world doesn't have too much
ketchup has like barely any ketchup yeah
yeah but you guys uh I noticed like you
guys are not like feeling that confident
about like just like trying it out when
you're not sure if it really goes there
um sometimes I want to do like karaoke
streams but I want to like do karaoke
with w you know like like just like they
play the song and then I do theate to
help you know yeah yeah so like I wish I
could just like tell you the whole set
list and then teach you for each song
like what you got to do but I can't tell
you sorry guys what what song am I doing
oh you can whisper in my
ear it's confusing because you know I
got a lot of I got I got World Tour too
oh busy busy I don't know what it's want
anymore bu bird bird yeah but yeah just
like like guys just just um feel feel
feel the the Rhythm yeah right yeah feel
the rhythm and then just go hi hi hi you
can do also go oi oi doesn't matter or E
doesn't matter yeah feel the yakai in
your soul relase it maybe you heard it
when we were doing it but you can
actually you can if you feel really
intense you can
go yeah sometimes people like in the
crowd will one person will go and then
the rest of the crowd will go it's
really fun instead of just say hi hi
you'll have someone go and the rest of
the crowd will go yeah it's so awesome
it's like kind of like a like when you
do it yourself it's like kind of like
you're you're like winding the oi up
yeah o exactly yes everybody try it try
it at the cont
[Music]
name breaking Dimensions breaking
Dimensions so
um I'm I'm going to like be ending the
stream so like oh you going in German we
say Zen and all that but there's a thing
I have to do oh stay there oh okay where
where is she going why are you going
over
there get out here get out of here get
out of here a
[Applause]
[Music]