[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
Nikki
kitty kitty kitty
sorry for the wait everybody hi and
first of all my laptop is really loud
right now sorry about that if you hear
it but it's trying as bad yes he's
trying he's trying really hard on it
yeah we are apparently in the middle of
a tutorial because apparently you have
to do this tutorial hello we're going
right to the game I guess I just want to
get out of this stupid tutorial oh yeah
am I left-handed
oh wait how do you oh we can switch
those but I think you have to hold them
like this wait no you have only like a
gun is Quick Draw
um today we'll play one two switch Yeah
it's a one two switches but it's a game
we have really nasty candy in front of
us and the laser of each game has to eat
three yes and they have bad flavors and
cookies
[Music]
um
apple juice thank you enough she's
showing it as if it was a camera
I'm QVC hi guys this is my lovely apple
juice how do you say apple juice
this
this so I brought tissues now so we're
gonna buy one stream let's go try it try
pushing it which one this one which one
this one
yeah there you go I guess this is a
tutorial it's a gun at the very end good
I was gonna break open an apple
yeah in this game we have to look at
each other's eyes
what was so embarrassing
lower your guns with a muzzle facing the
ground blow your gun
lower your guns with a muzzle which
button are we even gonna like push up to
shoot oh God wait how did you know it
was bad looking in here okay wait it was
all facing the ground
Jason
is this because I love this okay
face each other
ready who's gonna die
[Music]
fire
okay okay
let's go
Austin why why am I a little better
right now I'm charging as far as I know
oh well
well we bonked each other's guns so did
you give me the faulty controller no is
that what this is
oh no what do you mean control it's a
real gun oh that's right
it but so this will not count yet
because I think this is a tutorial I
just started the game for the first time
and it immediately threw me into this I
don't understand wait what if they don't
do it oh do you have to like unlock them
and when you first get the cages
let's go for the game oh okay okay Anna
okay
I'm not my choice all right my big iron
isn't so big anymore is it guys there's
some some spicy ones that are really
difficult apparently spice Zen I like
that one how can you lose in them
should we play that one we have to be
active start by relaxing you didn't tell
me
well maybe we can just do it while
sitting like this
also like who can stay still that's not
fair I have a Tremor a trimmer that's
not fair I shake is it like who can stay
still oh it is we should try it let's do
it
now you want to do it okay okay how do
we start this
behind me
I'm saying hi to everybody
and we kind of jumped in weirdly
um hi hi
[Music]
we just came from dinner with Inya yeah
it was really good it was tasty yeah and
now we have a special off collapse
um I had so many ideas for aqua levels
oh and this is the one I came to
even though they were others I had a
longer uh like desire for like I wanted
to do karaoke with you for a long time
no I started thinking about that too
yeah but there's so many things I want
to do
but so we're doing this because we're
combining many things with another today
you improve your strength in apple
breaking oh I haven't
yes Apple I bought the smallest apple I
could find it's like normal size I would
say no that's
well what do you think
you think it's possible I keep
it
I'll give it my best
I almost like forgot about it but I I
was reminded also partial by my viewers
and now we can do it on Stream So at the
end we'll do that did you notice the
apples and the thumbnail
oh
yeah
and and yeah this game is fun because
you have to look at each other and
there's many little mini games and
there's so many mini games they're only
really short and after each game we'll
eat the we'll eat some beans
me and the bird at 3am looking for bees
3 A.M 3 A.M it's already so late that's
okay don't worry about it let's play
this one what's that mean
[Music]
take a pose
we're gonna do it while sitting
all right hey but sitting is kind of
like the easiest isn't it
I'm looking at you I'm trying to look at
you goodbye you're so beautiful stop it
you're gonna make me I'm sorry
what did you say I don't know I can't
hear a movie bendo's knees is abandoning
I'm bending bending knee to me no no no
no no no no
is roasting one of us which one is he
roasting probably you are you only
holding out one arm I'm holding on both
arms
holding up both arms okay
you're really going for it yeah this is
sitting eating can we stand up without
shaking too much this is a real
challenge I don't know you're not
looking at me at me I can't look at you
otherwise my face
try to stand up the problem is I'm
sitting on my feet
but it's not even fair why am I moving
so hard
as well
why I broke oh no wait there's somebody
reminds me did you have a Wii
fit no I don't have the fit one because
there was a game it was actually really
terrifying I wonder if anybody in your
chat you guys remember you had to sit on
the floor in a dark room it was a dark
black room with one candle in front of
you on a wooden floor and you had to sit
as still as you possibly could and you
watched the candle dance
um and then we have like footsteps all
around you in creeks and it was actually
pretty scary it's pretty good
[Music]
interesting hey
I'm overall we played that game very
wrong but okay
let me first uh beans
I think I never have done this before
like eating this kind of beans
but
this will be up first I shot
[Music]
um
we didn't open the beans beforehand
though
oh yeah
um
maybe we should have opened the beans
yes we should have hooked me I'll just
write this apart oh you guys do remember
the game Scary oh it looks so enticing
Many Colors oh but yeah we said that we
will not look at the Colors oh that's
right okay when uh taking them out so uh
I guess I'll try to open it somewhere
can you open it I guess you don't you
will not do something for me I will tell
you back while closing my eyes
thank you
you know me and gura I feel like we're
kind of like synced right now today we
open the door at the exact same time and
we tripped over the street at the exact
same time
there's a scissor in my makeup bag I was
gonna say you got any like eyebrows
there should be a big scissor in the
pink bag and the small scissor too oh in
here the pink one yeah yeah
come on if I look in here oh sure go
ahead I mean your personal bag
if a lady if a lady lets you look in her
personal bag that means you're closer
than you would expect yeah it's just a
makeup book
you don't hide stuff in your makeup bag
no what do you hide and you make a bug
let me tell you now they're watching
they're listening well you will have to
open up up of all these kind of things
eventually when you are my guest at the
girls talk
okay okay she's eating the beans
okay it's free what do you think about
these kudas
U
first Bean
rice Bean
don't listen
okay that was good there's something
sweet like like bubble gum or cotton
candy okay okay because that could have
been a really bad one
of them I heard about certain ones in
the Legends being number two Bean
um okay
oh
what is that
um
I don't know what that is but it's not
good is it feet nope
is it baby
well it tastes like come on description
I don't know how to describe that it
feels like I maybe have eaten something
taste like this before
but it shouldn't be eaten
what should it what could this be
I don't know that's Gordon Ramsay tell
us what is the flavor profile they miss
something like a dish soap or so I don't
know a dish so
I have eaten them before though okay it
was bad but like not like I would throw
up bad okay last one it was brown does
that help you it was brown it was brown
Brown
[Music]
I can leave
cannot tell what that is I guess it's
normally you should not be eating that
it was bad but I'm good I'm good
um I got lucky on the bad one
being number three
hmm oh
[Music]
it tastes refreshing
and Bryant
mouth-wise it also doesn't taste like
something you should eat though do you
have pink moon tastes kind of good Pika
Pico what color was it blue like Frosty
blue ish green blue also hi Callie okay
blue like fully blue
good which one which blue
oh that was a really yummy it's toilet
paper yes it was good
yeah I think it was yummy toothpaste
why you got lucky good okay please don't
give me barfo I never wanna have butter
obviously no no no no no no no I'm doing
undo game so light is that plus
the more red pepper that's not what I
mean I can't wait why are we looking at
the OBS screen anyway yeah
yeah oh do you want to look Adobe ice
cream I'll do this and they should be
DeLand this game is all about having no
delay if you want you can see yourself a
little bit like this
no I
don't like it go back
no no
I want to go back game so like plus
there we go
ah which one do you want Samurai hi okay
hey okay ready
no Story look how silly they look
silence
you will try to catch it when someone
froze it
[Applause]
[Music]
and then you have to go like boom catch
oh
okay okay
stop explaining is this called We're
Naturals okay is this actual Samurai
training we're like yeah put your
fingers up oh sorry wait yes
in one hand and bring your hands
together to catch this everybody clap
your hands oh
stronger
wow that's just gonna hurt
okay I catch take your stance start
when whenever you want no we're waiting
for him okay
no no
no no no
do you want to do it
yeah yeah just for this one
okay I just I didn't understand
okay I thought she was doing a fake
I thought it would say something and I
would hear it too but wait did you like
get a signal or something no I just do
whatever you want oh you do it whatever
you said
give it to me again game
together to catch the sword
[Music]
left swings first oh again okay okay
ready
[Music]
don't kill me
okay
[Music]
which beans will you pick today I have
to win once at least because I need
Kudos
what colors are these are they looking
good
um
Bottoms Up go go go
start
are these all bad
it tastes like cough syrup
what the [\h__\h] ew is it is there cough
syrup
no
I'm guys I don't know what else could
babe
but I mean I guess I've had a lot of
stuff like that recently for my clubs of
syrup
say
they want you to eat bars medicine yeah
maybe there's a medicine today oh Red
Bull tastes like cough syrup no no no no
no no no no okay okay next one next
oh for once oh a decent one
tastes like a dessert uh-huh
um is it coffee
no banana oh I think it's vanilla oh
banana vanilla banana
banana okay we don't care about the good
ones you don't care about the bad ones
huh last one
it was like Gray
oh no she's making her face she's making
a face
oh no oh no fine good
oh where did you speak to me what is it
well
which one wait I think it's like
dead fish or something like that
oh your favorite I love fish I'm a cat I
love fish
um
[Music]
I've been gonna have some ice tea here I
have to make I don't want to eat anymore
of these no more no more how do we
switch Anna
oh wait I'm looking at this
all right I'm sure the next okay fine
you're making me nervous now because
you've got this so really bad yeah what
is the ratio man
which one am I good at oh wait I think
you can still unlock games because
Corona assemble had way more okay
um
let's do table tennis
level three
huh okay
what if I'm left-handed by the way it
doesn't matter
isn't there an anime ping pong girl
something something ping-pong
is there I guess there's an anime for
everything
go ahead Zach are okay is like fast and
R is like normal what
um wait no where was the difference
because you can show just by like
yeah okay sure of course we're gonna use
the strapless Safety First
um mindful of your surroundings and
stand far enough apart so you don't bump
into anything
we're gonna stay seated for safety give
me the ball thank you
start left players serve serve me
[Applause]
oh
I don't know like how far should this
like there's a distance anyway they're
back send it
what how am I supposed to know
[Applause]
because I missed it
finally no no no no no come on
make her eat the jelly beans
oh
listen to the tutorial
[Applause]
s
they didn't say that we're coming
oh okay you actually told me thank you
yeah bye
wait is the best of five I think maybe I
think he's specifying
[Applause]
okay
yeah finally
oh
yeah good that's gonna eat
I can hold it for you yes close your
eyes
close them also while eating can you
pour it for me yes
okay just pressing the beans I'm not
looking I don't know if my face is
showing up one two three there you go
how does it look one looks very sassy oh
no but I I wonder if you know sometimes
the good looking ones also are very
disappointing
okay do you know what you like about the
puke and your body is preparing for the
worst oh one of them could be bar no
like my body I'm already preparing my
body's already like you're gonna barf
and I haven't even done it yet so it's
like
I don't know I don't know go ahead okay
that looks good that one looks good
don't worry
don't laugh
enjoy
good right probably good
strawberry
now okay
yeah it's sweet I don't know what it is
fruity something
okay
number two number those together go get
oh
that's the interesting one
[Music]
this is
vanilla
bag and one more
yeah yeah
[Music]
did you get only good ones
yeah
she's free she's free
all right I'm gonna make a loose again
don't worry
leave it to me okay we didn't play this
one yet this one's very spicy too
apparently yeah
oh yeah
wait is it awesome
and when it gives you a signal you have
to go up with your hand that has the
controller okay okay
nice
Pamela Anderson the lady that was like
the hot life guy yes wow no that was me
oh
I have pictures of you on my wall oh who
knows the pictures of family and this
one in
that way
um
[Music]
when you feel it vibrate
stop cheating
[Music]
let's hear it for our winner
beans in your mouth
beans beans no it's because
I think I was standing there I just
didn't take it
my ringtone
yes yes yes okay
excuse me
maybe we should always do one practice
run and then one real one
okay okay
I'm going to know these games I'm gonna
take you um
all right let's go
joy-con when you feel it vibrating okay
okay face each other on your marks
my name is ready
[Applause]
oh no
this is the real door race oh yeah do we
have any comments about why you've been
losing every single time for the
doorways we started making eye contact
now
um oftentimes because if we if we have
if we have dinner together the eye
contact usually starts at the dinner
table and then continues until we get
home
I
[Music]
think one swing your arms move your legs
raise your hand
what do you want from us no we're gonna
like eat these now okay
cute
did I I think she did I say I did too oh
okay okay
and I used to really self-conscious and
I was just thinking about like how I
would have been really nervous points
hey you you had one on your hand but yes
I
like got rid of Mine by putting a banana
peel on it huh
yeah like rubbing it on it was like a
natural home remedy all right here we go
we might have an interesting one here
I gave her free beans okay
number one okay good uh Clippy yeah it
could be
good yeah this one should be good this
one should be good
taste test
yeah it tastes like blueberry Dairy and
blueberry flavor things and it's like
smelly things this is definitely not
blueberry
but it's a fruit it's definitely a fruit
lemon is not blueberry it tastes like
smelly stinky blueberry that's Apple
you should know because you're drinking
apple juice what kind of apples are you
eating okay okay next to the second one
oh oh
[\h__\h] oh yeah oh oh oh I I know what she
got it
[Music]
oh my Lord
what is that would you like to explain
it tastes like it tastes like bad
tomatoes bad bad Tomatoes it tastes like
tomato that you're gonna be eating
a tomato you shouldn't be yeah what
color was it
it was
um
like a dark brown
that's rancid it tastes like a it tastes
like a like a cockroach
[Music]
I have one more should I just go next
yes okay oh god oh this one
don't say that I'm gonna
if I barf and then pass out of my own
Pew speaking of barf
oh no
no I won't
maybe this one's fine
oh thank God oh my God it looked bad
Oh I thought this one might be no no I
guess barf is like orange yeah
okay
oh save save oh yeah yeah is that
there's a smelly food for everyone
I've heard there is I don't know
interesting well if that's a bad one for
you or not we maybe we'll find out wait
I have a question so all these people
that make these funky tasting beans have
to taste test it and make sure that it
tastes accurate to the actual thing so
that's probably like all the crazy
flavors right like barf and smelly feet
and God knows what else is like skunk
spray they're gonna have to taste
like quality control they're gonna have
to taste every one of those things
because they just base It Off
I say they based off a smell like for
example like how else could you like
know what a stinky sock like you're just
trying to recreate the smell with this
with a taste you're gonna put it in your
mouth and like swish it around like that
this does a stinky sock taste the same
way in your mouth as it does when you
smell it has anyone ever tried I can I
can I can conceptualize The Taste
sometimes yeah
my own usually but cheese maybe cheesy
cheesy there's a cheese and salty I mean
like stinky feet aren't they kind of
cheesy with some salt like sweat um what
oh no I don't know what are we talking
about mine okay
what is this
oh
which one which one let's unlock all of
the games
shave what is that oh shaving is fun
they're all so good
oh
you can now play Team Battle
join the right or left team and
challenge your friends what
you can now do you like the Mario Ware
version
have fun playing
[Music]
oh okay you can choose which one do you
want the telephone ball crowd uh
Treasure Chest milk
milk I've seen the uh cool we'll play
this in the famous club video we'll
probably know it is Senpai and maybe
you guys would probably know yeah so
basically you pull it down and while you
pull it and press that r
that was so difficult because you have
to press the upper one first
so like you're caressing the utter have
you ever met this cat before I have a
milked a cow before when I was a child
because we were taken on like a
Countryside week
in class what do you feel like
milk it's too long to love but I don't
think we enjoyed it
[Music]
it was it wasn't no other senpai
wouldn't it be funny if after this one
again like spoiled milk no no no
ironic
it's honest works
what is Ellen is the buttons I'm not
coordinated enough can I spot pants
probably you should be able to do 100
Pro Gamer ready
let's go let's milk
oh my god
oh yeah
he's Broly we're feeling oh
look at that milk
I guess we're like he's got such a week
did you see that stream
oh how
yeah more
more
[Applause]
you did not expect that one coming I got
10 cups you got nine colors milkshakes
[Music]
more beans I'm gonna put them in all at
once
[Applause]
I feel like they all stay in the same
place
okay
I'm gonna eat all these beans at the
same time so we can go to the next game
enjoy no no
no no no
no no is it taking too long it will
confuse you oh okay one by one one what
I think you had that one before
um
my mouth is rejecting it
you're rushing it a bit too much thank
you for telling us we might come back
later to do this again spicy cinnamon oh
milk
wouldn't
what which one is that it doesn't even
look like the picture
oh no
it's hard because the cinnamon is
overpowering what color was it don't you
not to eat it together I don't know what
that is it's like it was a dark brown
flavor it tastes like a color they like
cow poopy oh God I look sorry
so apparently that was bad
I was just like lemon lemon yeah that
one no it's not what is it I don't know
because it was like dark oh yeah it's
lemon I'm just oh the last one lemon
yeah yeah yeah okay I saw we had some
bad ones some blue ones but still no
vomits so far
we should take out just the vomit ones
at the end and then do like just rapid
fire
well you would just suggest to Dad
if I have to break an apple on stream we
have to Rapid Fire the barf ones
give the people what they want you came
here to see us barf didn't you yeah
I don't even
in this one there's one yeah they're in
there they're in there all right all
right next game
um what do we got uh sneaky dies
signal plans
shaving is nice too Shake it's not
shaking like that Mario Party game
Mario Party eight yes
oh bad
okay let me play no no I want to play
let's slap the bones bomb exploding one
how to play
I thought it doesn't look like that it
should look like the Mario Party a one I
mean soda doesn't look like that of
course it looks like this that's like
bubbly water it's like bubbly water and
still water
yeah
fizzy fuzzing water
oh yeah yeah we can we get the gist
thank you hurry my brain's going in the
gutter please hurry
oh oh that's a big butt oh [\h__\h] oh oh
shake it
hi
oh the one controller this one just one
I'm watching it again
[Music]
why are you doing me yeah
how does it know if you doesn't mean you
should watch to join me well okay I have
it now I guess it just means it in
general
[Music]
[Applause]
she's always trying to give it to me
well well if it isn't the consequences
of your own actions
more beans stealing I feel like there's
always the same ones
oh neat nail no I pinched myself
oh [\h__\h]
hi there's um at least one new one in
there I think and why are they always
the same ones houses possible oh well
that's uh what was that one
that one should be good is it like
bananas
shut up
um oh
yeah that's um that's uh I think this
just soap or something like that oh I
didn't do so before
just normal that's like a dish soap I
would willingly eat there's some dish
soaps that you wouldn't want to eat but
this one I would willingly eat and take
the consequences yes yes I think I had
that one too so it's decent mm-hmm
how about the last that was fun
I don't know I think it was some one of
the ones you knew okay okay
do you think maybe they don't put that
many nasty ones in there because people
might feel like they can't eat them and
they'd waste their money
that would be very nice of them
I would appreciate that
but then it wouldn't be fun to be funny
because they're they're meant to
bamboozle someone only heard this anyway
right that's the whole point of it okay
how about shaving
it's funny because you don't know you
you guessed how much you've been shaving
I'm gonna shave as much as you can you
don't see until afterwards I was really
bad at this one last time
[Music]
oh interesting
he said God damn it come on
press the button to get ready okay I'm
gonna push it in until my time let's
practice a bit of your joy fun gently
along your face following the curves and
why doesn't mine move properly
damn that's some thick hair
move your joy-con gently along she's
gonna wax me guys
recalibrate the controller
it's not moving I moved all over my face
relaxing stream don't go no stops you
guys are gonna want to do it
wax wax
there's nothing to wax on me
unless maybe some of my I think we could
still watch my arms up
no I would prefer my arms I guess
because my eyebrows are pretty important
I really don't like the look of that
shape
no you would you know that would you let
me wax your eyebrows
no
exactly
okay can we get this one calibrated
nicely shaving wrong
shave off their entire beard wins press
a button and get ready
uh if you had a baby would you be clean
shaving what would you do
uh if I had a beard hmm if it looked
good on me
oh no it's not much better but oh well
it will look good on me then
I guess I wouldn't shave it but
like would you look yeah to your chin
sorry game hey why
what's better I guess I'm gonna be
eating the beans it's okay okay give me
the beans three
[Music]
if there was
oh it sounds like something's happening
if you have a beard like you had a beard
would you let it go down into like to
the neck and like whatever it would be
I would I would keep it like a decent
length but not like like so maybe some
makeup like um
I won 100
wow
look at that system tactics strategies
Oh No I gave myself
they're my they're my feelings
oh no it looks so bad in like the the
um
my hair
what is this one oh I don't like the
sound of that oh this one you've had
before I guess this one's gonna be good
and do it
oh yeah that's an interesting one oh
good
what does that taste like to you because
I know what it is
she was eating a goober booger oh
like what it is
to say it was pretty accurate really
it's like salty it's like salty but in
an unpleasant way you saw the ones I had
did I ever have that one it's like like
a greenish color I don't think so light
green no I'm looking forward to it now
you want any boogers no oh you should
take your mine I think I have it in my
nose at dinner
yeah I may have seen it
you didn't say anything
hey dude you got a booger
[Music]
do you love me Booger you let me walk
grandma in my house okay it was dark
so it didn't stand out that much it was
a cute booger
um
[Laughter]
it happens sometimes they're just fruity
yeah that were good ones I think you had
like a oh even blood through the tissue
yummy what a nice dessert to have after
dinner how long was it in my nose
no maybe the whole thing oh man
it's okay this is struggling with the
towards the end like I felt that I was
like no no I didn't notice that you see
vario okay with it did you watch me eat
it you ate it I'm just kidding
this is good
I wanna why does it not do anything
what I can't do anything oh wait I
didn't oh I just didn't update on
obviously
we're not playing that okay
go next
[Music]
round oh these are I don't even know
what these cookies
[Music]
oh yeah
wow
so much fashion
um
you'll nail this one
oh
we are mating dancing
their surroundings and far enough apart
so you don't bump into anything or each
other
turns
hands hold your joycon and match the
Rhythm with both hands
wow
sorry sorry I said a little bit more
like this okay
try making some gorilla noises
gonna be like what are they doing
come on
[Music]
sounds like an owl excuse me oh she's
successful my lovely my lovely baby
woman
come on
what what without hitting your chest
she was too excited
where are we
what we got oh
oh yes thank you ma'am
who's the king of the jungle are you
because I missed the whole thing yes
definitely you'll carry my Offspring yes
yeah yeah that's okay
it's time for me to rip you
I think there's like genuinely only like
one or two barfs in here someone go for
it well well
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
free
probably nothing interesting
what are you saying wait this is it free
okay yeah it's free yeah ah you can go
either way
that's again like something bubble gummy
lucky
I'm gonna push the bar first yeah oh
it's a watermelon I don't even know
um
we're sour but really good
Maybe
what color is this
uh um like dirty shower drinks
shower challenge
okay
you put down the drain that you
shouldn't
oh yeah
which one is
[Music]
boring
we wear good gorillas but let's who
should we should we pick up the phone
okay what do you say after mushroom
um
you start the conversation oh we place
it like this
who's the better secretary
how's your phone skills
oh good I've been training it before
what about you
lacking lacking yeah
wait when you say four skills like what
exactly do you mean
um like if you're expecting an important
column like any type of telephone
oh yeah okay not a Discord call not a
like a Google me but like a telephone
now I don't like calling like old
doctors are so appointment thing is yeah
I don't like that I don't know why it's
so easy was like yeah wait what do we do
I call someone where you get called
and place your hands on your knees okay
hand them
the phone as soon as
hello ants are nice and loud just like
that
start
see
ing
[Laughter]
you got me I got the sale you're not
gonna believe it but I won the yacht oh
because I said
I said
[Music]
maybe hello
okay
let me pour it for you
the more we use the less we'll be left
okay it still looks
did you just push the vomit ones I see
you watching The Vibes
give me your hands
you didn't know she mushy fast enough
give me your hand
give me your hands he wants to kill me I
know what these are
godspeed thank you well let's start with
the I guess because I know what this is
I can have my eyes I'm gonna start with
a good one
oh is it
[Music]
um
again cotton candy I've had that orange
so many times now
um
next one is
I think it is it looks like it could be
something fruity anyway what the [\h__\h]
what
wait I was just what I think there's no
way no way is it smelly no it can't thin
oh
um
[Music]
but I know the last
Moon it may not be though what is it
it's surely
oh wow they really didn't put many in
here there's like um there's maybe only
one more in there is there one more
there's only one more should we do at
the same time yes okay
get it over with wait okay try and get
it out there
I showed them
it has an inviting color though no it
doesn't
but this is not an inviting color guess
a tissue this is like uh like how a
human react when you see like a poison
frog or like something in nature you're
not supposed to eat but it's orange
aren't you not supposed to eat like
things in nature that are bright red I'm
thinking of like the Mario mushroom is
bright red the toad is still cool it's
also bright red
and strawberry okay
okay
here we go three two
[Music]
oh my
whoa oh my God
oh
foreign
[Music]
it created even more puke
did you properly bite into it yours
looks intact and okay my body rejected
it
let's seal it in a Pandora box forever
[Music]
oh my God [\h__\h] that
yeah I had foam uh coming out of my
mouth
am I
what he called a toy wood in German
rabbit I'm a rabbit
well at least that's nothing we have to
be scared about anymore is that why they
only put two in here because those were
the guaranteed this is so mean
that's
so mean
but we keep playing oh no
stopped again okay okay
we continue though because I want to
play more of this are you okay
you wanted to eat like if there were
more like 10 at once I am insane
[Music]
oh wait what is this I didn't say I want
this but I guess
you count how many number how many wins
are in my head okay okay
you get like
after nothing I'm pretty good now I'm
I'm uh yeah maybe get a different one
one that you know is good are you sure
that was neither lemon or piss and I'm
willing to take a giant
what
ball count it's lemon right okay there's
another one that's yellow that's also
really bad
it's roughne egg in there girl
I gave her a very concert look this
one's okay actually it's fine I don't
realize there's rotten egg in there what
the [\h__\h]
okay okay
let's count some balls
slowly tilt your joy-con left and right
to feel the balls rolling around inside
that's so difficult
[Music]
how many balls are inside the Box
use your control stick to guess how many
balls are inside the Box
I hear noises from your box too enjoy
calm down once you've made your guess
oh wait no wait don't look at my answer
are they different balls
we'll have different ones
how many balls are in your hand thank
goodness as fast as you can original
stick to guess how many balls are inside
the Box
set your joy-con down once you've made
your guess
mm-hmm
likely yes
like I guess oh where I got that from
tea bag one minute left
how many balls are inside the Box
use your control stick to guess how many
balls are inside the Box
so many I can't think of you
set your joy-con down once you've made
your guess
I don't know I'll go for this um it's
either this or that
hmm
30 seconds
it's either mine or yours okay okay
I was about to say something
[Music]
I should pick some for you what have we
not had yet
probably
um
you pick eggs I'm sneaking in and
putting it in your nose in your sleep
uh oh this one could be yummy
I think it will be yummy
[Music]
um
which one which one
what about this one what is that one
yeah
yeah oh
yeah interesting
oh
it smells so disgusting what is this one
it's not even on the list
okay there you go I'm so sorry oh boy
my name
well hopefully marshmallow but I'm
hoping it's something else because this
one looked darker
really I thought it would be sausage
sausage yeah
sausage one this looks like it'd be more
sausage
is pretty good I guess it looks nasty
but this one nasty yeah it looks nasty
okay it is nasty what is that I don't
know what it is
so perfect
oh no it tastes like um
no idea I just want to grab some pizza
Uncle oh
wait maybe that one sausage
no it tastes meaty more Brown it tastes
meaty all right
last one oh
my mom no way
the thing is there's like there's rotten
egg and there's
um
something else is disgusting something
yeah I think earwax or something like
that
no
never thought about it no
what
do you think
no I've smelled like you know what's in
you know belly button but it's so
disgusting why does the belly button
stuff get so disgusting because it's
dark and moist and bacteria loves warm
dark moist places like that's why your
feet smell but like earwax I think that
at least wouldn't smell as bad as like
belly button stuff because like belly
button and stuff you like oh it smells
it smells really strong
why are you asking me these ear wax
things because we're eating still the
tastes okay
it's on topic oh yes it's doing the
thing again okay
oh no no no no no no no your joy-con
no more balls get your balls in
his next Cuba which is
try
tweet sing I'm your treasure box
unravel the treasure chest
that's fun
it's pretty fun you have to turn it all
around a lot
easy listen let's go who's the best
pirate best pirate we have to make at
home
okay let's go imagine this is for you
we're gonna Marine's in the Box
sideways and press a button push that
button
what
who wants
what what you don't even have a sister
drives it looks like broccoli oh is it
even is her assistant even working
though
it may not have been working
that was fine like this after
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
that's your imagination okay
it's all in your mind all in your head
we know that one's good I haven't had it
before that was good
um no this should be good those should
be good yeah they're good they're good
that's me bro
hey
yeah the green one is just Apple
Apple
was it cinnamon that could be cinnamon
it feels like you crack the safe or so
it's just it's really strong I won't be
able to taste it you don't like cinnamon
it's too strong okay
this one I might yeah
I think this is the earwax we try to eat
it you can't get as bad as vomit
she made it really ew face
was it worse than vomit
nah Mama gives you gag reflex
this one's like you want it oh
that's right now
[Music]
I'm scared
that's foul oh
yeah there was some eggs I didn't hatch
give me them something
um
are you out of like dranky apple juice
not strong enough
that is vowel that is Battle to the
highest caliber wow it was the vomit
worse it is on the same level as vomit
worse than Ramen it's same level oh [\h__\h]
wow wow
wow okay I probably want to play it
again right yes please okay
oh [\h__\h] oh well then you'll probably win
because I'm bad and Furious
thank you foreign
[Music]
90.
I think I'm doing well I've been doing
well let's Go piano swim
oh where is it
what what kind of like brain uh Power do
you need for this
oh it was a mistake to ask to do it
again
you don't have to eat another one are
you sure yeah we just played this one
for fun again okay same okay
this one we have
10.
[Music]
oh yeah
try to crack the code oh
you hear like a click I see and then he
turn more
where is it where is it
cracking correct yo oh
you felt that one yeah oh they're having
such a fun time yeah oh I love this game
but you're aware that we're not playing
right now right
90 degrees to find where the vibration
feels a bit different
just a bit different
[Music]
but when I like hear something could
that be from you too
share headphones
disappear
hey what is it
huh
what does it disappear where I felt it
um
don't call the police boys
what
it's right here give me I haven't got an
either
is that yours okay it was mine
it's right here whatever
it's not gonna be our job after whole
life that's for sure oh I'm getting
no no no
it doesn't smell like whatever I've just
eating well the rotten egg for example
wait how do I it won't
yeah
it's maybe a faker
oh
okay do you hear the sound cutting off
it's a capture card being weird
I can't restart it afterwards oh yeah
yeah it cut out brother but in OBS they
still hear it
I don't understand
so guys I'll restart the Elgato you'll
see it was that good but we also won
who has has anyone keep been keeping
count who has been eating more beans
[Music]
but it was way too long for both of us
we're really bad at this one
do you want some beans
this one
is maybe one we didn't have yet another
little ninja
[Music]
I'm sorry that's what was at the top
I really don't know they're all so
similar
nothing else
we need more scary
yeah
it's darker than the last one this one's
jumping on the last one this one too
this could be lemon or
oh she wants me to enjoy it she's so
sweet to share it with me yes
[Music]
eat my rice
what if it's just lemon it might just be
lemon
what if I throw up again for real
absolutely I have to hold it in my mouth
please don't think of me as disgusting
if I throw up on my skirt absolutely not
there you go
foreign
[Music]
that's amazing how awful that is I I I I
think
um you got way more taste of that
I I was uh very quick to spit that out I
had it like it didn't touch much of my
mouth of my tongue it touched more like
the upper side of my mouth so no taste
buds there but I just had a little peek
and that was probably
um
I don't know it could have been no it
was probably eggs because from the color
it was probably dead yeah because I
don't think ear waxes that it wouldn't
make us react like that what does how
will we know it's Fearless which one is
it yeah like I thought I thought it was
this one because this one's brighter is
this one it was even brighter
remember I know it doesn't have any like
different colorings oh
yeah
so back to the other ones we've had okay
you know what the earwax you will get if
you cannot crack the Apple like you told
us you could
hahaha
okay wait we're not playing that I want
to play a different one we didn't play
before why does it always like
automatically start these things shut up
[Music]
is it dinosaurs and die shake your cup
see it you shouldn't be asking that to
me because I would always say dices and
I only learned in ttrpg that many dice
die and I still don't agree with it it
doesn't make sense right that should be
ready at the same time
wait a game
what was this the player with the
highest
what
shake shake shake shake
then we turn it around what the right
player rolled to 12. ah
as a game
but you can try enticing yourself tells
you how many you have and you have to
guess if you have more than the other
person
say something you know if you have like
a really high number and they might
really
should assume that the other person
cannot really have a higher numbers
normally
but the highest number it could be with
three dices
you have
well if you have a really no low number
you would want to convince the other
person
[Music]
to throw the dice Shake the Dice again
a lower number than you a game of Bluffs
yeah wait what there's rules I'm so bad
at this
oh
God okay it can only be doubles okay now
I get this way more than less than flip
it over
game
well why is it telling us this player
wins
what
shake your joy-con and flip it over to
roll your dice
excuse me
I'm thinking you like vibrations what
what ready I haven't the wrong I didn't
choose
on the wrong side use the vibrations to
check your opponent's dice
say something because I put them first
like this but you have to put it like
this and I think it's pressed
so I was like game deciding
yeah we're doing it wrong
[Music]
we will understand don't lift it but I
want to lift it when you see okay shake
your cup are you okay
we're having a nice girls party here
okay no your own total it's just just
what girls normally do when they're
upset sorry when they're together
late at night almost midnight shake your
cup
and flip it over to roll your skin
sneaky dice so you listen to like
again like with the safe like how many
are in there but when you turn it around
turn it around like this there's only
two days
yeah but for example if it's like I
guess if it tap's like one two three
four then you know you have uh two fours
and then you look at uh what what number
that would be like 16
and then you know I have 16 but the
other person could have 20 or 24 or 99
so let's make that person
Shake again
I was really bad at this
[Music]
this is a mind game you put it down you
figure out if you're right okay
holding on right now uh yeah
roll your dice and flip
yeah
what am I feeling for uh I think after
you turn it around
use the vibrations to check your
opponent's dice roll I have no idea what
that means
say something about your opponent's dice
roll
um you die full of [\h__\h] is it sending me
oh it's sending me what you have okay
roll your dice while you're coming I
want to tell you what I have because
you're supposed to I don't know how to
play mind games
we should roll it together come on WOW
concentrating shark oh you need a lot of
time to count that huh there must be
many numbers
shut up
one two three four five two seven eight
nine ten
I don't know what do we do no I actually
have no idea
the higher it is the more you should
make me shake it again oh just how much
if if you feel six tabs for example it
would be 24 and then that's pretty high
so
you would make me shake it again shake
it again well if you shake it again I
don't want to shake it again well you
should shake it again I want this to
have this Burning experience no well
then I won't Shake either that will be
the bonding experience that we're not
shaking fine flip it did oh okay I don't
think we have to flip it I think we um
press the button yeah no
oh
game okay
yeah you did shake your joy-con and flip
it over to roll your dice yeah you did
because I got nine so I do have yours
you're getting feel mine I thought I was
feeling mine no no you feel mine and
then you're like wait she has a high
number oh I wish it maker
again basically okay
now let me get it
use the vibrations to check your
opponent's dice roll
say something about your opponents
okay
if you want you can re-roll your dice
while your cup is facing down
mine when you're ready flip our cups
open at the same time
you should not
check
I just understood it okay I understand
the game I just don't understand how to
[\h__\h] someone
oh you're ready anyway I did it and well
I have the ultimate mind
I am Megamind
if you re-roll your opponent will be
able to feel your new Total
so wait now what do you think about my
new Total sweet the number that you just
wrote isn't mine
okay wait well then I just re-rolled is
my number so you feel a new number for
me
because you were ready and I thought
that means you're confident
in winning
would you like to re-roll yours perhaps
no
no your opponent will be able to feel
your new Total
what's this word by the way it's
bothering me Sherman yeah what does it
mean how do you like
audio input uh recording two
microphone
sorry for the threatening German
do you know what I mean
yes yeah because you know what that
means ambulance butterfly there's like a
butterfly puppy and then German's like
she doesn't know the meme I'll show you
later you will like it okay turn it
around
[Music]
let's go
I can't
if you re-roll your opponent will be
able to feel your new Total
here whatever that was okay
wait
what does it it the number that I feel
is it telling me for example if it's the
first one would it be like
would it be foreign
[Music]
I can't lie I'm like the worst liar ever
flip it well how do you feel about mine
are you both ready no we're not
wait hmm let's open them up at the same
time okay no it's not it does not two we
have no more rewounds anyway game
oh yeah
oh wage
[\h__\h] get any of this anyway
[Music]
so only if you have a double it's
it's use the vibrations
confused and what's something about your
opponent's dice roll
I think it's poo poo poo mine is when
you're ready wow that means it's good
that means it's good
[Music]
so last time when it was a dice I
counted
last time I encounted six
how many did you have
how many well no the thing is and showed
me in the end was what I was that what I
was feeling
but that it came from you I don't
understand this game so last time when I
got doubles you felt ten ten no I didn't
when you're ready
one two three four five I feel like I
felt more than five so
what what do I know
doubles kill the strategy roll a double
get double the points but how do I know
I have a double does it count to ten or
does it count to five this player wins
so yeah
yeah well I felt four yeah what did you
feel
eight
okay I did feel eight okay well we
didn't have doubles I wonder what you
feel when you have doubles do you feel
too like the whole thing or really one
no you probably just feel the
super music
[Applause]
[Music]
play something easy
yes baby
[Music]
I can't do Hannah Montana
excuse me eat the wings
oh God I'm so oh baseball
a little baseball very popular in Japan
[Music]
I already forgot what they said in the
beginning
so baseball baseball is a mind game in
and of itself oh yeah the picture and
the catcher they're always going like
this wait you know what you're talking
about surprisingly
it's between the pitcher and the catcher
on the same team oh and they're they're
they are descending each other
telepathically sort of and hand signals
of what they want to throw to throw the
guy who's hitting the ball they want to
throw him off yeah yeah yeah and then
he'll raise his glove and the hitter
goes oh that looks like a fastball but
his hand's doing this or you'll watch
the movement in the glove
and the gloves will sometimes move a
certain way because he's getting because
each each throw each pitch has a
different finger
oh and then they throw it and then it
turns out to be oh
well it's not a it's a curveball it's
not a fastball we'll see things with the
curb all the time is left because he was
just pretty invisible and then the
vampire blue goes it's very interesting
yeah okay it's my game let's play it
quick it's better shut up
I think by the way my Applause is
probably dying soon
but we will have to open the Apple soon
[Music]
do I decide if I wanna festival or
change
no
you'll do that wait what do I do oh you
are wait oh wait you throw an eye hit
that's not gonna go well
I can't tell you
wait
you're not supposed to live when
pitching hold the L or ZL button and
gently swing your arms oh but you do it
while you're full yeah cause you're
supposed to hide I'm just gonna hide in
my club
how do we start
how do we start how do we start
ah are we in it right now I don't know
what's going on
I can't do anything here should we
tested yeah
oh
yeah I I
swung it when she threw it
okay
[Applause]
I don't know what difference
here comes the pitch
perfect
[Applause]
but I don't know when I know what's
close to me when it's the loudest
and you want to crack
at the crack and you are the crack you
want to crack it okay okay so I wait
longer
did I wait too long which was a true
little when pitching hold the L or ZL
button I promise we did it too fast
that's two okay
how is the pitch
[Music]
should I be running with you
all the way let's go do that make up for
all this [\h__\h] before
it seems like it did make up for it one
uh next players
and then you would sit down and you
another person would come up so this is
this is okay MP team member number two
all right all right hold on
the L or ZL button oh and the kid on the
hill is trying to swallow the park
okay okay okay
can you sing the opening though oh
second
it's not what they're saying always
um
yeah give me like a Beyonce oh
we can't play a baseball game with no
like
emotional can't play the Atlanta's
National Anthem do we have one why did
it go to out now
because I set your ass down get on the
bench
pick up the sunflower seeds
smelly okay
[Music]
and gently swing your arms
[Applause]
thank you
damn it it felt like I hit something
maybe I hit his face or so
I'm gonna throw a submarine [\h__\h] she's
never gonna expect it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
Rick
I have one more okay fall down
It's All or Nothing
for Austria
strike
how did I get that home run
there's another one
how many is it like a full team it's so
like gentle so sweet
okay good
job
[Music]
I guess
right oh [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] you need glasses
oh my God
this is the fullest count of the Full
Count
[Music]
[Applause]
why
oh
it's rich
I guess
it sounds funny yeah
oh when pitching hold the arm straight
swing your arms
OMS oh I'm the Frog oh god oh
okay
[Music]
I'm pitching hold the r or ZR button and
gently swing oh
throwing up
this is my kids this is my chance
when pitching hold the arm or ZR button
and gently swing your arm to throw the
ball
gently
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and gently swing your arm to throw the
ball
favorite that was a tactic from me
phone you discharge a little bit sleepy
sleep sleep fun okay
[Music]
what pitching hold the r or ZR button
it's so hard to hear it
[Music]
is this connected to your stream uh oh
you can make it louder it's not gonna
get louder on stream
holy cheers
you should have that up from the
beginning
when pitching or ZR button oh is it
really loud for you yeah oh I can't hear
it for real I can hear it now but yeah
it was quieter or [\h__\h] Frozen
[Applause]
they're gonna take away my contract
it's rude
dude
now it's time to hit the fan girl I
don't know what that means but do it
[Music]
I'm swinging it like a lasso
coach is glaring at me this is better oh
it's the airplane
or no
[Applause]
wow I feel like we're we're son and Dad
so sweet who am I
and be signed because your first son um
so proud of you I know I never let my
feelings show but I'm so proud of you
Mom
and that's the only thing you suck at
hold the arm what you have to get back
hey how long does it go I'm almost at
you guys stop Full Count
Brown
[Applause]
hey
okay
it's okay you're very adopted by me
anyway
oh
I will try to get my face moving again
do you want some beans
okay
no beans but no beans but oh Apple time
yes okay
if you guys remember from the last uh
full myth of collab on my channel uh we
were telling each other lies and truths
nice balls uh and uh okay this is
distracting me
don't let go serious just yet but you
can like you know make your preparations
I guess actually just when we're rooting
for the home team
sorry
oh yeah so she claims in her three
stories the one true one was that she
can oh please tell me what was it I can
tear an apple in half with my bare hands
is that song well I I thought it is
false until it's proven true to be fair
um I don't typically eat apples a thing
like base
look like they don't eat apples like
bait not this big this big this big
you know how they sell like little
apples as you can use as like bird food
like they're like lunchbox size for kids
you can they're like super small they're
like
yeah
that's really small oh
yeah I feel like often like oh my when
my Grandma had uh I'm not pre-coping
shut up an apple tree those were like
really small okay she's like making
preparations which I think Bob Mortimer
did not do
the one in the show who did she said the
same thing
who played the same thing but it's okay
I I I can't do that I wanted to play
people do that trans she said nailing
them you do you gotta give yourself a
little bit of a start because you need
that you need that help are we ready are
we going all right she has an apple in
her hand and she's I don't think it's
coming I don't think so either good luck
though okay she's doing it
maybe hold it close to the microphone
maybe we can hear it crack my hands are
too greasy from playing this game
look Grace will help oh it won't try
harder
every strong strength
power pressure
when those physical questions
you know if you if this turns out to be
false
then we have to change the score
that's how I eat my apples without
cutting them at home
why don't you just bite straight into it
because it hurts my teeth
you know what though technically I
didn't say I do this with every Apple I
just say it can be I think it's
vegetables
making excuses now I'm sure the children
cope
the apples here like I think I mentioned
it
remember that
okay yeah maybe the stem maybe get rid
of stem
I'm into a physical Justin fashion
Justin
oh
no that was a little huge
the only food you have for the rest of
your life
alive
okay
it's not fair yes you're only half grown
son
um
I hear it I smell it yes smell the aroma
I just gotta work harder on it
because it's getting so much bigger
it's thousand as impressive as you know
it should be but she's getting there
come on
oh now there it goes there it is yeah
you can't do it it's too big I can't
wrap my hands around the right way oh
yeah there you see and then what you're
supposed to do is
oh
you've come so far come on
there it goes
wow I could just cut off the parts
I'm covered in apple juice
yeah
beautiful like a butterfly it looks like
a butterfly wow
an apple half for you for me
I'm gonna take a picture I could take a
picture of it yeah as Peru okay
I can't do it
let me put a bean
see you
Apple for scale
um
don't smell but
oh God I'm sorry I'm sorry
oh is it the Apple the Apple [\h__\h] like
happiest like refresh everything here oh
no I just laughed at this moment
okay I'm gonna take a picture for you
guys
she really did it she did the
unthinkable The Unbelievable I told you
I could do it it wasn't true
[Music]
gonna upload this possibly after
checking on for Reflections on the Apple
or the Jelly Bean
it's coloring the Apple
truly unbelievably believable
good job good job
whoa impressive so if I'm ever lacking a
knife or an apple I'll do it you'll do
it it might take me well
wow wow she believed her apple breaking
she wheeled her apple breaking into
existence
incredible so if you guys ever think you
can't do something just do it just
believe in yourself
I'm sweating now yeah me too and there's
an apple carcass pieces everywhere
that's okay
the rats will eat it
well we did everything we wanted to do
thank you
[Music]
they wanna
gout toe gout
I think I've heard it before you get in
your toes when you joined
and it's like it's actually you can get
it from eating gallon of cheese if you
can no they used to call it like the the
disease of the rich right way back when
when like the Kings and the Queens would
eat the really rich food and that's all
they would eat because they had the
money to and then it like it affects
your joints and they swell up and if
they're in their toes you can't walk and
stuff like that oh so disgusting that
I've like killed my camera again that's
fine that's fine it looks like you're so
good
well that was summer to leave for you
guys hope you enjoyed it
the fun and hope you enjoyed YouTube
I guess I'll um feed them to Alma Elena
have them pick one and say yeah this is
earwax
looks like you should do it and then
when it's not I'm like oh whoopsie
Ur I dropped that one and I was hoping
so so sorry you forgive me
and we never did something like this
I mean we tested for all of them
we tested them blindly so how could we
possibly know what they are
hello
because it's killed right because
all right thank you guys we're gonna go
to sleep it's already late bedtime enjoy
what we say
[Music]
oh