[Music]
h e
ah
[Music]
K
ah hello
[Music]
Kiki
K want some jazz you like some jazz
yes
hi oh my God don't look at my boobs so
much um yay it's fre D reveal of the
fever night outfit how exciting wooo
okay wait clapping is my hands go over
another but clap clap clap clap clap
clap don't look don't look
my boobs basically do the thing that
crony's boobs do don't they like when I
do like this that's what Crown's
boobs
yay
yay it's fut W wait let me move myself a
little bit where am
I okay who
whoa
oh yeah like this is so
okay so first and for foremost this is a
fan-made model by
Sean thank you for making it although I
did buy it I did I mean okay the money
is coming but Sean was so nice to sent
the model uh a little bit early so I
could use it for today's
stream thank
you um but it was originally fan-made
like I didn't commission it he just made
it and I was like
yo um and then we were like you know
talking if I could maybe use this so
here we are and today uh was going to be
3D anyway whether or not I was going to
do this with the femite model or
not but I am in femite model 3D woo uh
but it's a special occasion so I cannot
models like this I cannot use them all
the
time um so only on special occasions and
today is a special occasion like that
aren't we happy I tried hard to prepare
this and get this ready uh including the
game cuz somehow my C game capture
wasn't working anymore and also the game
that we're playing today is only in the
Japanese Nintendo store even though when
I researched online it said there's an
English version but I guess that just
means it's in the Japanese Nintendo
store and you have to then switch it to
English I don't know what the [\h__\h] uh
but that meant I had to make a Japanese
Nintendo account and I get the money
from a prepaid card through
JMA finally I got the game but that took
a while too yeah yeah yeah English
version but in Asia I guess oh
W I can squeeze them you can squeeze
them you can te
them
Wes
so oh my God that's fascinating that's
actually what I want for my to
like that they separately move oh I
think by the way the Creator the artist
of the 2D outfit is watching
to they they were tweeting it out uh
being happy about having it turned into
3D right away but yeah so you probably
curious about the f as well you already
got like this little treat
but do you want cuz I'm like kind of
squatting here do you want to see
more
yeah yeah unleash
unleash you want to unleash it are you
sure
[Music]
okay I can B way I can make him smaller
and I can make them even bigger I think
this is like the middle size and for the
fs as well I there was a setting to make
them a little bit bigger so I made them
bigger and this is um a good setting I
must
say
uh
wait let's go over
here
T wo
[Laughter]
oh my god let's
[Music]
go wow shiny
booties shiny shiny
booty want to do some Arabic hm
want to do some arobics with
[Laughter]
me by the way shout out to Amit who
helped me uh troubleshooting a little
bit before the
stream aerobics with waa we can finally
make that come true in 3D now yay y y
yay the physics are very physical Let's
get
physical and you know what's really cool
one thing I
noticed um unlike cuz you know this is a
fan-made model so I can't use it in the
Holo app and I noticed one
thing in the Holo app when I like jump
and so on I think when it's not like
when it's live the motion capture when
it's live it like does weird things but
so far I haven't noticed anything
weird in
this program so that's really cool let's
go
so we're going to play fit boxing today
in this high quality 3D but I didn't
show you full body yet let me show you
full body going to be fit boxing with
hotsun and
[Music]
Miku
T there it
is yay
look at those F I've been
squatting wow oh so the
FES there was a something there my
cat my microphone is a little bit far so
uh when I go further away it will not
sound perfect bear with
me we can do the fever night dance
baby I forgot baby what was it again H
meet me underneath the straw light I'm
also my headphones are uh they have a uh
you know they are attached with a string
so I can't do too crazy [\h__\h] yeah I'm
I'm too lazy to set up uh wireless
headphones or not too lazy but also too
stupid you want to should we should we
try a little bit
let's see uh is this a is this the final
version Oh what is
this that doesn't seem to be it what
about ah this
one
oops I'll try to remember the cor but I
don't really remember it uh even though
I I recently danced it
[Music]
something like
that huh
[Music]
I don't [\h__\h] remember wait the course
I remember
[Music]
I don't
remember oh yeah the tracking is good
right no oh
wait wait let me actually just pull up
my Coro
video
then where's my
cor night
videos you fing works a lot better
compared to what you you mean when I did
uh same accent suit tracking in my in
the Holo app possibly honestly yes you
might not be so wrong with that the hair
bounce is astonishing oh yeah wow I
didn't notice wait are you looking there
or there because look there
you're right oh my God I didn't know
this
w
Jesus both right oh my God yeah I'm so
happy with this it's like the first time
I'm actually like properly testing this
it's pretty amazing I have like a bunch
of expressions and stuff too but it's
kind of hard to like turn them on and
and like trigger them all when I'm doing
full body and not just sitting there at
the PC
okay wait
um
night I think I think it should be
here fite fite fite F fite I found
it okay that's my Cora video so the
audio
is
yeah is this already mirrored I don't
remember
oh
yeah right I need to try
[Music]
myself ah
o
oh oh
oh it's been a
while
[Music]
w C
cable and I'm supposed to turn but
there's a cable
[Music]
spe
that this skull ball makes me wild my
headphones
[Music]
da
[Applause]
[Music]
okay that was a little
attempt of remembering Fe night I'm so
exhausted
though I'm so exhausted I'm
twerking but wait well for real can you
see it there's physics there wait who
was that who was that ah herb what's up
herb twick with me come
on jiggle jigle
jiggle right there's some there's some
Physics there oh
yeah
yay yay for booty jiggles
those
FES very noise very noise a't it very
noise in
it noise jigle in
it so
now shall we uh slowly start doing the
thing that we came here for we don't
need me could just do this for an hour
like low key I was thinking so too but
uh no no no no no chuny wonky is
watching this by the way she's right
there okay actually she fell asleep
don't watch me chunky I'm doing Unholy
things it has J day yeah yeah yeah it's
a toggle though I think I can also take
off the the shirt but I think it looks
nice and wave because it looks more like
the
reference yeah
soorry I'm exhausted so I I need to get
in
my sorry I learned this from Kobo
actually Kobo taught me this like she
was just suddenly she would be
like and then she's
like I swear Kaa is the one who taught
me this I thought it was so
funny it was so funny of course it was
yeah
so okay let's play a game it should be
working I tested it
beforehand
oh wow
got the controllers although they're
hard to uh touch buttons with with my
gloves on but it should be
okay uh oh yeah
sound oh yeah now it would be double but
I
think
uh I'm I'm already sweaty
spaghetti let's go press a
[Music]
ah
crackling I'm to fix
it jump scare what do you mean you
should have been prepared for that I was
telling you I'm setting up things
so
there hi okay well that's
fine ha
[Music]
I'm getting
dizzy let's figure out what this game is
about
okay um buttons is it free ah wait I
think I did like the very very beginning
tutorial but I didn't do the first real
exercise yet I was vibing
yeah eh should I move out out of the way
for hatun
Miku I'll move a little
bit like over here I don't know I'm
watching for the OBS screen so I know if
I go off screen accidentally cuz that
seems to still be happening
okay as always but this is the first
time what do we have
you want me to
do water but uh a towel uh chunky wonky
is sleeping on the
towel
[Music]
okay stretchy and when I was practicing
this you will see now that when I'm
punching I'm actually punching but it
was like really not um registering it
but as long as you guys see that I'm
punching then I'm fine with that yeah I
need to press
longer just use strong I'm going to face
palm with my
sweat
hi white girl white girl twerk twerk
twerk white girl white girl go white
girl go
woohoo
wooho woohoo
what girl
go where's the music who turned it
off I'm drifting
[Music]
serious
serious all is serious okay
okay feel so stretched
[Music]
I'm
sweaty I already warmed up I already
warmed up
okay we already did
that we did that though
[Music]
but it's going to get my trackers like I
have a Tracker here a belt on the hip
it's going to like move around
and
what okay are we good are we are we good
what she doing still same stuff that's
all you're going to stretch I guess for
boxing only makes
sense what what she doing oh
better than
[Music]
sh my my $6,000 gloves are falling
apart are we
done we did it
[Music]
let's do a proper
one I feel like me moving the belt
around mess some things up but oh
well oh
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] for
[Music]
I
hit
FOC what do you mean
[Music]
[Applause]
for
for got
my okay
[Music]
I'm going to [\h__\h] you
[Applause]
[Music]
wony what do you think about that you're
running away now oh come on Tony wonky
she too scared of my power
[Music]
did I wake you
up
sorry my finds were too loud right
[Music]
this is the
result we can do better than that but I
swear I was like you saw me bouncing
around like
hardcore
yay cool down okay cool
[Music]
down let me try to fix my spine it's
kind of
so sideways now huh where is it where is
it oh oh my God maybe I should
recalibrate
oh what the
[\h__\h] maybe it's should I Rec no it's
generally [\h__\h] up
now don't
look don't look it's huki
let me
just reattach this maybe wait it's hard
with the gloves they're so
[Music]
chunky come
on
okay
reattaching what gloves are you using
monus $6,000 monus
gloves okay okay in theory that's secure
[Music]
now that's relatively straight [\h__\h]
it oh cool down stretch better be a
different stretch girl give me something
else
[Music]
wooo okay this okay
I know do we really skip skip I don't
have the energy for this right now I
want to dance there's bu songs that you
can punch to
right no dancing just
[Music]
punching she's making fun of
me she's making fun of me
I beg for shirt
toggle if I can find it
[Music]
again no don't look
no no no
no no
[Music]
no no no
no take it all
in enough punch punch
oh what did I do I punched I punched the
menu can I please do a a normal thing
now why is this is not working hello oh
I'm listening to her
I'm
[Music]
sweaty exercise
sze mze maybe is with cute
songs oh yeah
[Music]
cute is there any anyone oh I have to
like have
to have to uh unlock them
[Music]
what else is there anyone that I can
dance no not yet I want to do po
[Music]
I don't even have to unlock these songs
I can just listen to them
here uh but there's not many that I
know I love this
[Music]
song I don't know the
Cho I love you I whole life
[Music]
ID
B I'm just doing stupid things
and I need more is there can you get
more songs in this oh well let's let's
start
punching let's stop punching
baby hi punch
me punch me
in oh I have to press
longer
no no I don't want to
[Music]
H let's
go I hope there's nothing new that I
should have
[Music]
learned oh
dear out of r
[Music]
do I even need to do
that what is going on I'm
pting
[Music]
oh I'm just doing my
oh why it's not reacting
[Music]
though I'm trying this one's not
reacting my hands are exhausted noal
[Music]
arms I'm doing way more exercise than
they want me to do
though okay this okay easy easy
[Music]
hi let's sit down and drink water
what do you mean 44 my age isn't written
anywhere on
here no way no way don't believe these
lies don't believe
it shiny
[Music]
you too my
lady
mze mze what do we
have I want to do me
[Music]
[Applause]
we'll do that one when
[Music]
I it again
okay go away
chair go away
chair moving it with my hips cuz I
can so we have normal punches side
punches and upper
punches
okay new
[Music]
fore
Come n n n n n n
[Music]
hey me
no should just do it early
[Music]
wait my gloves open
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
God okay rib
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm it's by the way I'm I think
[Music]
no I can't it's so
exhausting hi hi what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
love these lyrics so
relatable [\h__\h] you
up what do you want huh huh you want to
[Music]
the fight welcome to the fight club baby
[Applause]
[Music]
spee
fore okay this
bam
shees that [\h__\h] is
[Music]
dangerous yeah really good
song really good
song shut up don't tell me I'm I suck
I'm amazing I am
now what what the [\h__\h] is that two two
two one two
what um excuse
me
no no
she wants to fight me is there other
Miku songs here or is it
just no
[Music]
okay let's
do let's
do should we do vampire wait where did
Vampire
go where did it go oh wait it was UN not
unlocked ws and St hole that one fun
that one's going to be
fun and then we can do Kam
Bo God
damn God
damn if only narissa was watching man
man brings all the boys to the yard and
they're like
[Music]
we should do stream let's do like a
little
bit closer
[Music]
I'm
pressing fore
[Music]
he
for my
arms oh God
[Music]
go
again stop
me my
I
fing please stop please stop please stop
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] just
happened my P
crashed am I
moving my my PC just froze
what happened my PC my whole PC
froze I thought I thought I was done for
I thought it was
over
oh
[Music]
Cy
wait oh oh you guys don't even
understand this song came out in a
million wait yeah we're back right well
since how long what was the last thing
you heard me say oh I think we just oh
you heard the Cali thing you just you
just having a little bit of a
lag do you guys know do you guys
know the
lore the Nik n Doga lore on the song you
just heard me scream C okay because my
PC froze but not as long as you guys
were gone I guess it took a moment to
reconnect
yeah that song uh back in the days it
had a
Coro but it wasn't really a Coro you
know the people were just turning in a
circle that was the whole dance to the
song now you're
enlightened yeah it's very deep
lure wow
eh we're getting some
stuff wait so are we like we only
unlocked one
song she almost she almost brought me
into a dance lesson again into a
punching lesson again no no no no I'm
doing this all
naturally hey I thought you unlocked it
[Music]
oh it's so
nostalgic I I have to use
looka a so maybe we actually have more
songs than I thought we have now we have
Luka wait just just be
friends just be friends
all we got to do is just be friends Time
to Say Goodbye just be friends I want I
want
GRE just be friends just be friends just
be
friends a song that me and Callie should
cover okay so when I'm sitting there's
some weirdness going on but besides that
I think this is really good isn't
it okay Luka Kelly let's do something
what do you have to offer h
oh but it's not there is it
[Music]
because is is it not
there I mean that's
fine we can do
Kam but I don't know how many more I can
do guys this is so exhausting
[Music]
let's
go break it down go white girl
go where are some other white girl moves
not
sure just whatever comes naturally to me
though I
[Music]
guess lasso girl lasso twirl
what's this by the
way the elain dance what's the Lan dance
wait I should know that one that sounds
[Music]
familiar oh my God
a stting weak
[Music]
is to
spe
do
know slow
[Music]
motion my body is too slow motion
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] let's
go what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I hate you I hate you
I hate
[Music]
you okay thise
sorry just trying to get up just just
trying to get up from the Dance Floor
[Music]
I'm so
dead
oh
oh ah okay my my hand
batteries are my finger
trackers are running a little bit low we
can do without them
but to break to break to the break could
the side
[Music]
woo my legs are more together by the way
just saying cuz I'm a lady this is not
how this is not how I
sit oh my
[Music]
I should put on my
jacket I should put on my jacket by the
way I have
freckles and this is really just a bug
in the
Matrix okay it's kind of cute
[Music]
why would anyone want
this forehead let's
go I'm so
dead Mama
Mia
oh oh yes this is fitting
[Music]
ha you don't want to play tic tac toe on
my
forehead trust
[Music]
me aha
W after
[Music]
exercise W and see
chicken
oh oh this one's dead oh
[Music]
k
k you say
[Music]
put my arms
up oh now
okay
enough
enough enough
enough V is Happy good I'm happy if I
can make sampai happy sniff
sniff oh my God this is so embarrassing
can I put my jacket back on
please mama
[Music]
M you know what we can
do you know what we can
do enough of the
[Music]
game we
can we can
I was going to say we can try to learn
C's dance but at the same time I'm
wondering if I turn on that
song I might get copyright strike not
really copyright stuck but
like n it might not be
good yeah I don't want to do I don't
want to risk that here I
guess um
better not to but I was going to uh
record fever night anyway so I start I
danced if you late to the stream I
danced Fever Night in the beginning of
the stream trying to remember my own
Coral uh although n now my hand is out
of battery so I shouldn't record it now
H can which one is it this one oh both
now both let me charge them
I can charge them
while I have them on although I mean 1
hour for this kind of stream I think is
enough
anyway but let me charge
these
thingies these thingies not the I was
going to say t h i n g i e s but
actually f i n g i s is even more
accurate
ah ah get in there what the
[\h__\h] get
in good that I have ice cream in the
fridge you know those um those uh
Kinder uh what are they called Kinder uh
surprise
eggs chocolate
thingies apparently they've been around
for a while but I found an ice cream for
it like the Kinder chocolate surprise
egg
ooh ew
ice cream and I bought it I only saw the
Kinder Bueno uh ice cream before it was
really good too and today I tried the
the one for the not not Kinder joint no
the ub's eye 's eye Surprise egg the one
that's banned in
America by the way I have the cat mouth
on isn't it
cute this
one it's kind of weird this one doesn't
work well need to work on that I think
there's still you know some things we
could
fix like um why is there like a black
line
there lipstick lipstick doesn't doesn't
look very
good
[Music]
lipstick lipstick
Jack O post oh is that the one in the
splits no I can't do a split
you like the freckles me
too I I wanted freckles for a new outfit
but they said no and now I have freckles
here and no one can stop
[Music]
me don't get used to the forehead it's
not supposed to be a normal thing
although I have to admit it doesn't look
so
bad looks quite all right
cute oh if only my hands wearing so
[\h__\h] broken right
[Music]
now
yeah
cute oh thank
you I appreciate it good mouth tracking
yeah I I would probably change some
things cuz it like defaults to a very
Square
mouth shape too
much but you know this is we can say
this is a prototype I paid for it so we
can adjust
it we can change some things but also
this makes me think the creator of this
actually made some other models um for
me a fan-made model so maybe I'm just
going to collect them all maybe I'm
going to catch them all there's a uh the
great Wanderer tgw
model and and I think some others
and there's a dark version of this
one where the the suit is
black with yellow highlights I think and
uh fishnet fishnet FES tights I
mean G oh I guess it's a g version Maybe
let's bring some some BTM back yeah so
but this is I think I think this is a
good good uh amount of exercise that I
have done and completed
damn it this is such a
Vibe ah my YouTube chat ran out of
memory that's
exciting I need a shower now I'm very
sweaty
spaghetti but yeah this was freie F
night wa I will only bring her out for
special occasions but I probably be
making uh some shorts with this with The
Good Old Fever Night song and dance
along to it and maybe I'll do some other
dance shorts with this too because I
mean it's calling for that isn't it and
I still I still actually need to do the
W robics I have I have a a wow robics um
how to say uh exercise thing that I made
previously for the outfit reveal and
then I didn't use it because my freede
motion tracking was
broken I can still make that into a
video like its own
video and we can use a
model a routine yeah that's what I was
looking for
routine W arobics aerobics routine by
Yours
Truly I'm glad you guys like the model
and I'm glad you enjoyed the stream we
should do more so I think like all kinds
of like exercising streams like ringfit
Adventure for example we can also do
again and use this model I just I just
shouldn't use it too much if I use it
too much I'm going to get in trouble
probably only special uh occasion so we
got to space it out a little bit Yeah
spacing it out as long as we space it
out it's all good a 3D off collab like
this well but I'm I'm I think so far I'm
still the only one who owns this kind of
suit the other ones have like different
kinds of uh home fre that's like a
little bit uh less quality I don't know
if we can put it together like
we could put them together but it it
wouldn't be like we wouldn't be able to
really interact with one another we
would just like be overlapping two
layers of motion capture from different
softwares basically there would be no
actual like uh interaction uh possible
and it wouldn't seem like we're in the
same room you know what I
mean cuz it's like how to say I don't
know how to explain these things in
terms in real words but but uh in the
cover Studio there's tracking with
cameras uh and like suits with little
bouncy balls not bouncy balls but
reflection balls reflecting balls on the
suits you know so that's I think Optical
Optical was the word Optical motion
capture and then what uh we have for
home freedy is not Optical what was the
other
one
oh I forgot but that's the other thing I
if if we were together in an optical
motion capture Studio I think that's the
word uh then you can like
interact but like this is like going
through Wi-Fi and all that and it's not
based on like location it doesn't know
where you
are I don't know those are not the right
terms but whatever
I can see my future in your forehead oh
is it our future
together smooth
[Music]
R thank you okay so oh I I think I need
to learn how to do how to end a short
stream with a nice cut off so um I'll
I'll end it there I I think I'll just
dance into the
[Music]
ending how long is how long is 20,000
milliseconds
is that 2
seconds or 20
seconds it's 20,000
milliseconds 20
seconds you like the square mouth yeah I
think it's pretty cute but uh I like it
too but it should be a little bit a
little bit more maybe
okay my my wait are they back let's see
can they come back or are they still too
low my
hands oh my
bad oh okay one's back that's
okay n they're weird all right thanks
for watching everybody tomorrow we're
playing witch spring R 4 p.m. wa time
CEST uh join me we're doing Super Chat
rating tomorrow too I hope hope see you
[Music]
there oh they're back
e
[Music]
I
Ed wait a
[Music]
a put in