[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
we're live
[Applause]
everybody's dressed up
hello everyone
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
how everybody feels that i think
everybody is feeling pretty
[Laughter]
i need to do this
[Music]
it's very nice delicious christmas
cocktail okay
[Music]
oh this one must be mine i made that
yeah
[Music]
oh yeah most definitely what's inside
this string
wow
[Music]
no it's mine now it's rain
it's mine and then wait ina
now i can now i can feed you like this
[Music]
i just took in a string
today
[Music]
yes
does that mean we have to kiss
i showed you my mistletoe please respond
oh my god
okay you want a kiss
do it
oh
[Music]
do you want to give me a kiss
oh
[Music]
i know
then i'm never going to come out of your
mouth no i don't no i don't know
[Laughter]
everybody can see
yeah i saw it from eno
let's get drunk i want to hold the
camera
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
it's a
[Laughter]
[Music]
magic
delicious she's doing more than good
health i'm i'm great
this this really helped with my throat
just now
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's wrapped up like a present
hello i am
[Music]
just kind of want to unwrap them
yeah before we were setting up i was
feeding i was feeding cranium
drinks
like a baby bottle i don't really
realized everybody was gone
[Music]
from bottom to door
oh my goodness
[Music]
you want to eat it you smell it you do
not throw it up there let me let me
balance the
[Music]
i want
sorry about it
[Music]
do it again i missed it do it again for
the camera
it's gone
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
oh
it's kind of sweet
don't
ready
[Music]
they're fizzy
wait i want to give you some candy i
don't think i can pick that off okay
never mind i can't give you anything if
you can't either i've been trying to
pick it up and i cannot
this is a lie you can pick this up
you can make chicken at least
oh
[Music]
she's
i can hear it i can hear her from miles
away
it's half black and half white just like
it's like half of half of your panties
are half demon and half of your panties
are half angel
[Music]
cronies eating too many cookies for real
good i see the void
oh she's alive oh look it's
disappointing is she alive
[Music]
nothing to hide
that is definitely a diaper
[Music]
maybe it's a diaper
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
so much is happening
i'm trying to do my best to capture
everything but everybody's
everybody's just so cheerful can you eat
it
[Music]
can i feed you let's try it
where's elevator elevator
sensei
i'm a sensei
uh i will leave i will give you a signal
and then you all need to count to ten
and then you can join the magical
wonderland
[Music]
[Applause]
don't press any buttons yet but you can
press the button for here winter world
not yet but okay now i want you guys to
count to ten starting
starting
okay
three
four five
five
six
seven
eight
nine
ten
oh
[Music]
is
the biggest one
[Music]
hey can you can you stand on the
snowball
like a like a houseball
stand on it stand on it now run
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
oh my goodness
that's
it's taller than me
mouth
oh my gosh it is
it's bigger than me dangerous
perfect
comparison
i think i could fit inside that yeah
wait
[Music]
uh
yeah you look really cool
is
[Music]
all you can think about is just throwing
money into that
[Music]
it looks like you got a new it's nobody
let's go to bales
i do i'm powerful now i'm unstoppable
but i thought but i thought you have to
kiss me under the mistletoe
but i thought nobody's coming
[Music]
little here
cute
[Music]
baby
[Laughter]
this is my my swamp oh gosh can you can
you can we like stack them on top of
each other so um you can have a real
body but you can have a real body
there's a candy
[Music]
do i need to be saved
thank you
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's exactly what you wanted for
christmas
[Music]
you have to
scroll
[Music]
no it's okay i feel
i mean it's been in several other
people's mouths i don't know how to feel
about
it only been on yours
and you guys are fine with it right
oh hello
okay stick it on my head
you can't tell the difference between me
and the candy cane
[Music]
you're not going into my mouth
um
[Music]
oh yeah it's the mistletoe now we have
to kiss
oh
[Music]
iris i just noticed you're wearing a
santa man
i think
did she
[Music]
out of here
no it's a big piece of coal for you it's
from santa down in hell oh he's really
angry thank you
oh
instead i think there's like there's a
lot of santa santa
replace him no nobody could replace sand
actually i think anyone can replace it
yeah you've seen them done at malls
countless times
yes
what if there's like a lot of santas a
lot of santas and you'll never be able
to um get rid of all of them because
they just respond
[Music]
oh santa's
santas i don't want to break in his
dreams
i'm sorry to
spit out the real truth the hard truth
santa
if you've been bad or good to be good
for goodness sake
but you can't be good at all i hear burn
all the time because
i do hear burning
i do hear bernie
sanders
[Music]
is this a sauna or something what is
this
oh
do the magic do the magic tricks
[Music]
it's okay
do you guys feel it
say is like the inside of makes no
difference when i say
oh really
you all need to be closer
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay that's a little too close
[Music]
what's going on in here
i'll try to take you out
[Music]
beautiful harmony
we're the ones who are gonna die
next time we go in here there's gonna be
a dead body and there's gonna be a case
and the
[Music]
stop
[Laughter]
i'm showing i am showing them to you
right now
[Music]
somebody
[Laughter]
don't say anything just close it
there goes the coal
[Music]
you should not get what you want for
christmas
hey
she's dead
oh no did we do this
so who's the suspect
someone says the light
you are my life
that's right
i'm joined she has the lantern and
everything enjoying let go
let's go don't go to the light don't go
to the lake rooney
so light at the end of the tunnel let's
go
let's
[Music]
skateboarder who says see you later
bowling
she wasn't good enough for him
now he's a superstar slamming on his
guitar
pretty much he triggered something
inside of me kiara
ooh can we all escape
[Music]
da da
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my goodness
[Music]
oh is this a sign here come here
[Laughter]
[Music]
do you need a kiss from connie
pretty granny
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
where's all this anger coming from
[Music]
oh man
oh
[Music]
my first
my first idea is to watch what mimi's
going to
produce
[Music]
okay okay okay um
i'll wait for
your masterpiece
i'll come back to see your masterpieces
[Music]
i didn't mean to draw this i don't know
how to erase
i don't think there is an eraser
is a mustache that's okay
i have no idea what it is it just
started dry
and you just can't stop i'm gonna make
it work i just can't stop
i'm trying to make it break a work
somehow
i disappeared
[Music]
oh this is adorable
bucket
bucket oh thank you i'm drawing pickles
[Music]
happiness
maybe maybe
[Music]
oh
it looks like i can give it a switch
this one
[Music]
can i can i pick this up
oh my gosh
you do just kind of
you're already stopped
i i wanted to make the snowman happy
either
now it looks like it's vomiting out some
yeah
it's inside
oh my god what is that oh this one oh
wow that's this is so neat how you like
this how is this how is this one so neat
compared to the one behind you beautiful
oh it's a good question i mean what can
i say i'm just a bit of an artist i
don't know
what can i say i think you got a knack
for this i especially like these
lumps
yeah yeah my size
yeah i like yourself thanks
i appreciate that thank you i'm working
real hard over here
working real hard
nice one
is yours disappearing
gradually yeah
is it disappearing here okay
well um beautiful things don't last
forever i guess
[Music]
oh
those are hands behind you those are
hands those are my hands
[Music]
we're missing something
hey what'd you just draw there
[Music]
yeah what can i say i have big yeah i'm
just worried that i'm just worried that
they'll get a little cold yeah all the
better to grab you with iris come here
oh better to punch you in the face with
[Music]
yeah what do you guys think you guys
like it i think it looks i think it
looks pretty christmassy
yeah now she's really stamped
she's like an evil santa she's like in
pretty i like the santa bender than the
old one
yeah you know she's she slighted me so i
started drawing on her i'm gonna give
her devil horns oh she already has them
[\h__\h] never mind
am i looking like
[Music]
save me it says
oh my gosh how long does the skirt fall
to treasure
[Music]
it looks just like fauna
i see the reindeer it looks like a cat
with uh
yes it looks like a cat um
with a steel bar in his head
[Music]
you gotta stay still though
we all knew this day would come
[Music]
is
i can't tell which is up and down and
left and right anymore i see it's just
come back
[Laughter]
oh
i'm making my circle to keep away from
alaskan bull worms
i thought you were just i thought you
were sure
you're just tying
[Applause]
by shout out to wait the worm is right
here
i don't know him oh no
oh no not the bull worm
i'm a candy cane i'm a nice candy cane i
don't know the candy cane is looking a
little bent up don't you think
they can't see it sorry it's not fine
you must be a very poisonous worm
because look at those colors
i mean you wanna do you want a piece of
me do you want a piece of me no house
for her i wish you could take my camera
do you want a piece of me nope i'm good
morning
no no no
in here
[Music]
i think you guys are like pledging
together
[Laughter]
you're the worker of this
this house it's here i always work i
always work it's always like this
it's always like there's a nicest
innocent relationship huh
no my
my presence here is all that matters
what presents have you no we're safe
what presents have you given us on top
of us right now
[Music]
isn't this nice and cozy
very warm yes
she left
wow that's a very green santa
yeah
it's actually really circular
thank you how did you do that perfectly
done
just keep going down in circles yes even
it's even more perfect than you
i know
wait what that can't be
yeah move over cranie we found something
even more perfect than you
[Music]
no no no we can't do that
you have to destroy it
[Laughter]
oh i was just about to let go of my pen
and you say impenetrable that's amazing
totally on purpose gag
fauna
yes
i think this this is probably the cutest
thing that i've ever seen you draw baby
you're such an artist
look at that
it's very lovely good job thank you i
feel like you're jiggly
[Music]
it looks like eyelashes
so precious so kelly's arms look so long
yeah i'm taking a little rest they're
very stretched outward right now huh
i'm taking a rest on my channel let me
give you some mittens
sure thank you yeah yeah
my fingers hurt from drawing so i'm
going to take a little rest here you
guys can have this
tomorrow i'm going to wake up and my
hands are going to hurt again because of
vr and all the gripping
horny
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
of course i'm the one whose head turns
like whoa can i get in this cage over
here
hold on i want to go chill in the cage
i'm a captive of your heart
and your heart's captive save me oh no
where's the sheriff now you're safe here
you're safe here it's a shelter yeah
no nobody can eat
where's the key in my heart
[Music]
is
so
[Music]
i want to help
what is this igloo floor is this is this
another shelter like the one that granny
made
oh yeah
yeah
what are you hiding from
why are you scared
[Laughter]
why are some of these only some of these
snowballs look like
long eggs chicken eggs
chicken eggs
what if they are chicken eggs
i guess we'll find that in strength
[Music]
can we like bring like a really really
big snowman snowman
baby
i can't believe i'm still playing
minecraft
what do you mean
you'd never circle craft
it's circlecraft
minecraft
minecraft is a lifestyle
i can't stop anymore
i i can't even i can't even stop to go
see what everybody else is talking about
this has to be done
[Music]
i think you can fit on the shelves
nice
hey we need we need an antenna for the
wi-fi
[Music]
it's an igly
christmas
[Music]
i want to turn in the igloo
ugly
[Music]
it just needs some flaps
yes
[Music]
today
can i draw something on you
small fries oh guys
mcdonald's
[Music]
i want to give you guys drink
and then and then i'll give you some
chicken with chicken i mean that's
pretty good you guys ready i'm gonna
show you guys a magic trick
yes
[Music]
one
so
[Music]
it's so beautiful
is
[Music]
this moment can be forever
i'm just thinking about how
[Music]
bail whatever what are you doing is
going what are you looking at
pest control
that's actually that's actually pretty
good actually it's a monobrow
it's meant to be a mouse
oh yeah
a mustache
why does everybody want to draw santa on
irish
[Music]
sure i already exhausted all my stories
but i'm happy to listen to you guys
and
christmas stories
inside you can't say anything
you good grown skirts
i'm good i'm just uh building a wall
around uh iris
to keep her safe he's been bullied so
many times
[Music]
imagine how she'll react when she wakes
up
you gotta do it fast you gotta work fast
[Music]
thank you
what are you building
i thought i thought it was a bunny
i thought it was a bunny tail but okay
that means you need three you need three
of them then you need a tail and then
like two of these for the butt
like one is gonna be one is going to be
the tail and then like
the other two is going to be the button
yes
there we go now it's a bunny no it's a
bunny
you guys are making progress
yeah i think so
don't you think it's missing a bit
something at the front
[Music]
i think it's missing a snout
that's what's missing
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
welcome to darkness
hope has ascended
and
[Music]
is
if you
i never really um
i never really
oh yes celebrated christmas
before this is the meditating yeah
meditation
[Music]
best christmas on earth
oh my god
i didn't know you couldn't draw even
more on top of this
exactly it never stops
getting darker and darker
oh kelly looks like she has like a bad
stomach ink
oh i'm good i'm just chilling
drinking tea
sipping tea in your hood what the [\h__\h]
is that
are you sure
yeah it's tea and not alcohol
i'm just holding it
you're holding it up very very clearly
why are you all i'm not eating
all judging me
what's with all the judgment all of a
sudden i'm just holding a pen really
close to my face all right look
judd judge give me that one too
judge kelly
thanks
i just want both just don't worry about
it
i think you can only grab one
it looks like you're grabbing both of
them
you guys want to check something out
watch this
[Laughter]
[Music]
give myself the key inside the cage but
i can't get out thanks mume
all right here we go oh boy my chair is
behind me so i can't really go that far
anyway this is my cage this is my secret
circle my safe my this is my safe space
right here and you guys can't enter you
can't come in it doesn't look very
exciting by safe space
it looks like your head is safe for me
because it keeps me away from
it keeps me away from you oh my god
cronie is trying to out here
it's hanging on my safe space
oh
[Music]
can anybody pick me up
i want to be picked off
[Laughter]
next time next time
[Music]
i want to sit next to taco i want to sit
next to taco
[Music]
no i want to sit next to taco sit next
to talker here we go
[Music]
all right
you don't have to run into the fire
roasted shark
shark fin stoop lady stoop soup shark
fin soup ladies
oh my gosh kiara you're wearing a
similar dress to me i didn't see that
you guys you guys are having kind of
revealing kind of revealing dresses
yeah yeah
yeah small chippy pooper
thank god anyway
finally scooby-dooby
[Music]
it's a chicken sandwich
i appreciate that
um
[Music]
oh
can we can you holidays marshmallows on
um fullness and fullness and iris's
horns and then use them as
uh
yeah yeah
you can use them to roast yeah that's
such a good idea in the campfire
[Music]
wow
merry christmas
merry christmas merry christmas
[Music]
yeah you guys want to hear it
that's it yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
great awesome do i like okay i look like
[\h__\h] up right now should i meet
somebody
thank you
yeah
all right here's my story
once upon a time
in a snowy village by the north pole
there was a very large man
named santa claus
he wore a red outfit and a red santa hat
and his only joy in this in this lonely
cold dark and despairing world was to
give presents to the little children
essentially he was the giver of all
things hope related
however
there was someone else
who wanted that throne
someone else someone else could
could not stand the fact that
this this bold gentleman was giving away
presence and hope to the children
so late in the night when he was on his
sleigh
hold on there's an ending
when he was on his sleigh
his reindeer taking him away into the
night
suddenly something very strange happened
it appeared that there was a sabotage to
his sleigh
and suddenly the reindeer were cut from
their reigns and santa was left to fall
to his death but who was it that came
flying out of the sky to ride on his
reindeer and take the remaining presents
to the children
who could it be but the one
the only who could it be
we need the council to decide
[Music]
we can arrest her
anyone else have any stories
we can like hook up
hook her away
[Music]
of those uh make a story as you go
around things we used to do them in
improv classes so everybody starts off
someone starts off making a story then
everybody adds like a sentence to the
story
[Music]
somebody start
and come up with an intro to the story
so like
just start up a story that you would
write and then
say next and then the next person will
continue the story so who wants to start
is there like a word do we say a
sentence
it's like a sentence
a sentence or two yeah sentence or two
[Music]
one day there was a snowy night and a
giant snowball fell down the mountain
and came to life
and upon its giant heads rotated
mistletoe and
large lifeless eyeballs
[Laughter]
assume the flesh of humans
and suddenly
[Music]
suddenly
it grew very muscular snowy arms
a fake thin legs
it started marching towards the city
next
it began its slow yet motivated march
toward the city however it need not walk
because after a while something akin to
a ceiling fan emerged from its head as
it slowly was pulled upward into the sky
and made its way towards the waiting
homes of many children
and families across the nation
next up son okay
the
helicopter realized that
it did not need its body anymore
because nobody is perfect
so
the body fell off
from the sky so as a helicopter as a
helicopter
flew into the sky the body plopped off
and landed
on top
oh
and yes
the body continued moving on its own
without the head suddenly gaining
sentiment in some of its own
and it wanted revenge upon the head who
had left it
excuse me
[Laughter]
i'm back
what there's a story maybe iris can't
continue at the end
oh um someone paraphrase the story for
me real quick
oh god um a lot happening in the
snowball that like came down the the
mountain and then it turned into a huge
monster that looks like crony and then
it has a helicopter head and then it
came off and it plopped down on the city
and then its body separated from its
head and now it's getting ready to
attack the city
oh that's a horror story okay
um
what did you say phonak oh i wanted to
get rid okay um
[Music]
without eyes
worry about the thing
just those are logistics
matched on chrome
[Music]
oh boy tell us your story
to the gym
to
not skip leg day but saw
saw itself in the mirror they thought
oh man
so beautiful
they opened
[Music]
yes open their mouths
appears
a little fairy
a little fairy dressed in santa claus
clothes
[Music]
fairy jumps out out of the mouth
and luke said uh not crowley did the
monster whatever looks at the monster
and says
you are beautiful no matter what they
say
and words cannot bring you down next
moon
the santa ferry also reminds the monster
of how it has lost its way
and so it abandons its lands for revenge
and
[Music]
[Applause]
delivering fast food and then it gets to
a familiar home and then
oh is it ending is it i think
you you end up getting this
give us like give us a stellar ending uh
and this wait wait who was going to the
house again
the big monster that like turned into
the liverpool now
the big monster that turned into a new
sleeve
and then turned a new leaf yeah and then
he saw
he saw a stack of cookies and milk
very delicious looking stack of cookies
and milk
he couldn't he couldn't
couldn't help but take a bite of the
cookie
the cookie was poisoned
[Laughter]
yeah forget your happy ending
he died
and
everything is all better again
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's so sweet and christmasy and wintry
and then as it went around the circle it
got darker and darker
what else can you do it reminds me of a
tree story
yeah it makes sense happened to a friend
of a friend of mine
[Music]
all right
[Laughter]
it looks like you can crush the
oh my tree
i'm sorry
i wonder who did that i don't want to be
up there babe you're not gonna see me
[Music]
it's a black box who comes to visit or
else yeah so the whole guy can drop the
body cares about santa all right here we
go
[Music]
now he watches over us beautiful never
forget
[Music]
i guess
i guess we'll start here we'll start
over here at this present whoever is
this first president
um this is give me a second
who's president
it's basis present
oh base present
[Music]
after you see
oh my gosh
anyway this is for me bae this is my
special ornament for you i made it
special for you oh just the perfect
preface
let me tell the chat really quick okay
uh we did a secret santa where's the
camera we did a secret santa where
everybody uh
everybody was assigned one person an ian
so there's 11 of us and uh everybody
made a design a sketch for an ornament
to be put on the tree and so this is
bay's ornament right here and everybody
uh made and designed one of these for
each one of us so callie made this one
yeah
[Music]
oh nice
it looks perfect perfect
yay we have a green box who's this for
oh this one is it might be fun is it for
your name
[Music]
huh
[Applause]
[Music]
who do you think made that one
it's kind of hard to guess huh
i have absolutely no idea
i did it
i made that one
[Music]
oh
how do i make it not like this all right
oh you can write it
um
[Music]
put it right next to the nightmare fuel
i didn't see any nightmare fuel
it spread out a little bit
[Music]
this i think it's santa's next oh isn't
mine isn't mine
[Music]
oh
what's this
[Music]
oh
inside space
[Music]
rotate it
yeah
did you make this did you make this
armor oh
no i didn't i wasn't me
okay the iris like this can other people
guess the phone i make this
how did i say it was it anything was it
was what did you make
of me
yeah
[Music]
hey
i'm gonna put it i'm gonna put it high
up
close to the place to the sky
yay up and stay
[Music]
inside
yeah hanging hanging out for me
i have some lights inside
[Music]
all right
oh
[Music]
she's so adorable
did
did mummy make this
no
it's so hard to tell
did kiara make this
no no i can't make something so cute
shush your art is adorable
thank you
cute
who made it
i'll think it's mad
did they make this
[Music]
yes
i love it
[Music]
oh
that's beautiful
so cute thank you iris
van parker
merry christmas
[Music]
let's see what's inside oh
what is it what is it what is it oh
[Music]
i'm already feeling bad about the one i
made yeah is this is this from is this
simple
no i didn't make it
uh
or sana no i didn't like this one
[Music]
it's from your kohlheim
um
[Music]
okay we got another box over here
looks like brownies
oh
[Music]
what time is it granny
it is
all the times
it's not rainbow
oh that's true it's not rainbow just
make it rainbow
stone
cute
[Music]
no it wasn't me
who could have made this beautiful
little thing
ami
no it wasn't me
[Music]
me
i was already worried about when i saw
everyone else's i thought mine was so
lame
[Music]
just a mini version put yourself up on
the tree yeah
yeah
oh it's like oh it's spinning
it's spinning
yeah
spinning
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's so fluffy
this is the fruitiest taco i've ever
seen a very old taco
[Music]
thousand years
i mean it's called
i'm gonna lick it is it fake
what flavor it could be uh cream i don't
know
their masterpiece
[Music]
yeah i could see that it was like a
cream
who made this one
[Music]
hmm
there's not many people left
yeah there's not that many people left
so we got we got
we got
[Music]
was a detective no it wasn't me wasn't
me
was it
wasn't you
no
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
right
i don't like santa but i like this
this should be santa instead what you
want to replace
with looking up into the beautiful night
sky suspicious do you want us you want
to replace them with this thing no no no
real suspicious
i i i would like to take a day off on
christmas thank you
[Music]
i don't think you can close it but uh
gonna just close your eyes you didn't
see it good at what's in it
oh wow
[Music]
can we sell that as merchandise
yeah
[Music]
yeah wow
i think no
oh i haven't really been paying
attention
[Laughter]
[Music]
i love it
it's perfect
[Laughter]
[Music]
is graphic design your passion perhaps
perfect design is
thank you for the interview thank you
very much
is this a watson box
[Music]
like i handled mostly everybody's um
like stuff oh then i just moved this i
handled everybody's like uh sketches and
stuff and i gave them to the modelers
but i haven't seen this one so it's a
really it really is a surprise
[Music]
thank is i know who made this i think
everybody knew either where is she where
is she i think i know
hey
that's the most thing i've ever seen
[Music]
it's
crunchy boiling water and you get some
fresh pasta with no essence your hair
gets super soft yeah maybe the center is
just a big bowl of cheese it's like
cherries oh that sounds good
yummy
i like the chip yeah it looks tasty
thank you
thank you awesome
[Music]
i guess here's like right here is a good
spot right there
that's delicious
[Music]
okay to cali here we go
open sesame
[Music]
[Applause]
hold on give me give me the one what is
it what is it hold on i can
oh honey
[Music]
it's a lucky dead feed that's marinating
in the glass
yes like all the dead beasts oh
mistletoe is so cute
that is very pretty
very well crafted is this from sana oh
no it doesn't mean oh
really watson you made this
i made aaron how did you know it looks
so good
not saying that i don't think you can
make like great words
[Music]
is
tree and now we're decorating a real
tree that's kind of weird
[Music]
wait who's left who didn't
i don't i'm not sure
[Music]
it's
[Laughter]
is this
is this no you know it's sana's right
yeah yeah
[Music]
right next right there
right there
yes it was me merry christmas
[Music]
chrysler
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh tearing up a little
merry christmas
i'm glad i could be here
merry merry merry
christmas i wasn't gonna be able to make
it so i'm glad that it ended up working
out
yeah i guess we can't use the mirror
because the mirror is kind of messed up
who could have oh who could have done
this
i don't know
[Music]
maybe there's a way to
move the marker stuff give me one second
i believe ebay i believe
where do i put the camera here
[Music]
let's see
i feel like i'm small enough to become
an ornament
yeah you could be an organization i'm
not the same size of another camera even
though it looks in the mirror
okay
[Music]
that's okay oh kelly i didn't even
notice i was going up your skin i'm
sorry
oh it's okay i forgive you thank you
i know you didn't mean it
i'm gonna destroy you in pokemon later
[Music]
sound is so small sonic you keep it in
the middle right here i could fit on the
tree i can put on a tree somewhere oh
i'm fine
um am i covering up anyone here
uh
[Music]
oh
what's the number again what's the
number you gotta call ghostbusters now i
want one
phone number
what
is so
thank you guys thank you for watching
vince and stuff cheers
[Music]
yeah christmas is not over yet
one gather over here
where is she look at they're on
here
yeah
and we actually i have a small
announcement before our big announcement
so we can gather in front of the tree
like just like we were um actually
this vr chat world will be available
publicly for everybody in the community
to use so it's like a gift for everybody
yeah
um on the 23rd on wednesday uh so you
guys can come explore the studio the
halloween map the winter wonderland and
of course uh you know the default map
and we'll push updates when when uh we
need to update you know maybe council
could get some rooms or something
someday huh
yeah
hang out with your buds yeah
and um we have another announcement is
it time yet actually let me see
i mean we're a little early we have four
minutes but um no problem should we no
problem it's good
let's do it
i think yeah kiara's good at announcing
stuff kara you want to announce it oh
god oh god no not me please i don't even
know
[Music]
okay guys
so
whole live english whole live english
has created
a special song cover of the classic
christmas song the 12 days of christmas
yes
[Music]
in 20 minutes i believe that the link
will be up so you guys can watch the
premiere of it has all uh 11 of us and
uh yeah look forward to it today
[Music]
check it out
any closing thoughts thank you for
making my christmas everyone
[Music]
okay
together on my channel on the 22nd uh
like it depends on your time zone but
for most time zones is the 22nd december
wednesday we're also doing a stream
about it so yeah please check it out the
reservation is
up about 24 hours before
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
exciting a lot of things a lot of
presents for everybody
yeah
big presents i actually have presents as
well
giving back to the audience
they're going to be uploaded to my
channel oh
so please check them out there are three
of them they're a series um and then
also during my christmas party
um which is happening uh about uh it's
happening tomorrow it's more than 24
hours though
during that party i'm going to uh give
you guys a small visual preview of an
original song i've been working on with
someone here
come be there to check out check it out
uh it's gonna be cool i hope that you're
excited for it
it's one image uh it's an it's an
animation
we're going to show you it
um it's uh it's cool it's a cool song
that's your hand
it's a cool song
it's cool
yay
[Music]
closing thoughts
there's my hand inside your head i have
one short one
yeah i just wanted to say um
i'm really glad to have met everyone
this year
we can have what no and i hope we can
have fun more fun next year
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is
[Music]
[Applause]
huge shout out to the developer and
seafoam and the vrt team who have been
working like day after day punching in
hours getting everything working and
looking really cool and working well so
thank you guys for giving this present
to us and also the community yeah thank
you team thank you
[Music]
yeah the year is closing out and you
know last year we closed out with only
the five of us and now there's 11 of us
so i'm really glad that we could do this
together and you know this whole week
there's a bunch of cool streams you guys
are doing uh so you know you guys in the
audience make sure to check them out
everybody's doing christmas streams and
stuff so make sure to check them out and
happy holidays happy new year thank you
everybody for watching
[Music]
happy happy
panties
[Music]
wow
you