[Music]
foreign
assistant
[Music]
thank you
that's junkers though she's also here
cat party
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
the moment
the moment I switched screens without
even saying anything
it's movie immediately left
[Laughter]
how does she know
but by the latest once I started talking
she would have loved like chunkers did
um
I mean
at least I got some cuddles in during
the loading screen
okay I am
why is Kiana's not so [\h__\h] tired
why is she why is she sounding okay
well
I woke up an hour ago
at 12 and already had breakfast
yeah
wow no no Red Bulls involved no no no no
yeah wow impressive right well thank you
so responsible oh I mean I was
contemplating moving the stream a little
bit but only because of some
over over
stepped deadlines
but I thought oh well
these couple hours they make no
difference anymore I'll just I'll just
do it after Minecraft before the karaoke
stream
uh surely that will be fine
yeah
yeah I didn't want you guys to be like
why did she move the stream Sasuke she
didn't wake up in time
I knew it
even though that's not the reason
well well I wouldn't have minded one or
two more hours of sleep why are you
doing
my n a people you guys love me too much
you guys just love me so much what the
what the hell
what time is it over there
oh my voice is a little bit raspy but
still
uh and I need to fix this
uh six seven four but four is what EST
no PST right PST is always earlier than
EST
the really [\h__\h] early ones
why is it so early for everybody where
are my sea viewers I'm doing this for
you
Korea 8pm nice see people like you today
I had not Australia 9pm nice there you
go there we go wait now
okay can I do a poll because this is
appalling appalling appalling
where
the [\h__\h] are you
uh n a
or dead area
uh
uh you're Europe or that area
or NCAA
uh to pan Korea
because if it turns out that it's mostly
an a
then even though it's like [\h__\h] 6am
for you and I will be laughing
or like more like questioning my
decisions
where are my SCA viewers
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
okay okay here we go
that is interesting
it's like 50 50 50 but not really
because it's free options so that is um
not 40 45 more like three point 33
points something
yeah yeah right
[Laughter]
I even knew there was a point there
okay I see I'm not that stupid as you
think I am
oh what the lava doing hello welcome
and hey bros but look there's wait 27
out of the currently voted 1700.
how much is that or it's rising though
it's still do be rising and the 27
States stays the same
how much is that what 270
wait we had 100 1 800 now though
voted
okay so like maybe 300 people
are here at at least 500
are here right now at four to six a.m oh
we're at 2 000 votes
like 500 people I hear and woke up for
me or are still up for me at four to six
A.M
why why do you love me so much
[Music]
love finds a way oh romantic well it's
good that you guys are here
because
well if lbs decides to show my Minecraft
screen now that I tapped back in would
you like to do that would you would you
would you like to do that
would you maybe
consider consider it would you maybe
want to do that
yeah
you you wanna you wanna show when I'm up
to OBS
you captured it just fine before the
Stream
uh Minecraft it's always like this with
Minecraft somehow
it doesn't wanna
oh wait ah okay here we go it has a
different window now there we go so it's
good at you guys are here because
I am alone
I am the only one oh nazica
[Music]
no one's yeah this is the classic MC
experience for me
for me personally
oh wait we need bgm we need everything I
don't hear [\h__\h] I was gonna fix that
uh
it is like 8 P.M in Japan now but I
guess today no one's playing Minecraft
[Laughter]
I missed you boss haven't you in a while
missed your voice and streams why
haven't you tuned in in a while because
you're like the third option in the poll
also but I am happy to see that it's
like pretty pretty even I mean obviously
there's more
um sea
Etc reviews right now because it's a
better time
glad they are here
uh
what was I gonna do oh yeah I'm mute the
desktop audio there we go
yeah yeah some obviously it's a weekday
uh it's 1 p.m in Austria right now so a
lot of Europeans are probably working
right now
how do we find the exit ah I remember
the beetle is somewhere over there
somewhere over there uh hi Panda wow
what a nice small home I was gonna say
nice because it's nicely decorated but
for panda this looks like animal abuse
um anyway
reporting from France oh hello welcome
rare stream time yeah it's it's only
because this week if you have looked at
my stream schedule
um I I am not around Friday Saturday
Sunday
I have a long weekend
um
and so I thought I need to make up for
the lack of streams at the end of the
week by squeezing in more during the
week
and uh uh
I have found it
and so I'll now we have other Sumo sound
in Minecraft I think
I'll fix it in a moment hopefully
and and yeah so today we have two
streams
um I'm literally like using every moment
to do work before I leave work for the
weekend behind BJ I'm kind of loud okay
really
yeah I feel like I got one guide
where am I where am I
he's over here
what are they called again
[Music]
ninja I don't know what they're called
out still really
oh my head hurts oh
okay I lowered it even more now it's
really [\h__\h] cool and quiet though
ah
foreign
I will not play in silence I mean I
generally I feel like you know if you
watch a streamer for hours and hours and
hours I feel like if you're that type of
viewer then
I totally understand if you would want
to play your own bgm and not
Bend to my wishes
um
okay
can you double I'm so sad I'm not a ball
what would you be what what else is
there are you are you in the Antarctica
or so
what what what else is there we're back
to the
um topic of continents
oh well Africa for me is Europe or that
area because you guys are like down
down there oh yeah
I can't I can't ride every country down
there
continents if I were to try to write
every continent down then it would uh be
known that I have troubles writing all
the continents down so I was
purposefully trying to not do that
is there a Bed somewhere here
just being honest with you guys
no no I mean I know I know them all yeah
but you know I mean I've even been to
Africa yeah
okay why is there no sound let me fix it
really quick
there's no Minecraft sound
oh the Onsen has a bed
no no
um Minecraft
every time I have my game capture
plugged in
I
this has been an issue I've had like
four or forever
so I think I fixed it now
um you know when you open your sound
settings and it opens this new window
and it's like output input Etc
and then an output you can choose the
The Source right and um it always
automatically goes back to Elgato sound
capture
which makes no sense and then I have to
switch it
in order for myself to even hear
something
I switch it for example to like Michael
XLR music output
and then it often fixes it but it will
still default back to
Elgato sound capture like in the drop
down menu
even though I just clicked something
else and then and then for Minecrafters
now I had to go to the extended sound
options to another separate window
scroll down to Minecraft and then select
music
output for that one specifically for it
to be heard
yeah it's been forever like this stupid
stupid stupid
sound capture freaking Elgato what the
hell why why don't you do this to me why
makes no sense
um we gotta sleep
they said that Onsen has
uh huh
Yum Yum Yum Yum yeah it's a pain to deal
with that
oopsie
where are we doing so I think I remember
it's like up there and then left I think
right that's the first time I see it
Tower
lit up at night
wow that's really cool especially
what was that sound
it's a monster especially
what was I gonna say oh yeah with my
with my beautiful filters
here's a band yay soup
I think I went to the top before
I remember something like that let's
take a little silk
um good morning soak
hey are you oh no never mind you don't
want to play with me either
um
wow what a view this isn't so bad if I
would just look at this this looks like
we could maybe be the Japan's River
Maybe
[Music]
this view looks actually decently
impressive 4 a.m good morning why are
you away
surprised at me streaming makes no sense
why are you awake I should be asking you
um
for me it's like 1pm 20.
yeah we were told you would stream
I asked you woke up just from me thank
you thank you thank you thank you I
don't even really know what we'll be
doing guys
[Laughter]
nobody's here
and that's okay you know I mean I'm used
to that I I it's basically a Gamble
for me to play Minecraft
and one cannot always have such Pleasant
experiences and last time because then
it would just take away from how special
that was right
and I do like
I don't know
playing along because I'm used to it
Minecraft is fun alone as well
apparently my mom who was sick of
Minecraft for a while
she started playing again too after
being inspired
I didn't see that last time what the
hell
I was probably
busy looking at something else that's
amazing
it's moving
or was it really not there last time I
was online that seems weird because it's
been 2023 for a while
build cave pin on Instagram
this is the thing I don't really like
building things
worst case yes we can try
we can try that the worst case
but I already built a kfp in the old
Japan server
and yeah I'm not really
Focus can I say hi to my frogs wanna say
hi to my wrongs remember when I built
this when I went out to get some frogs
and then I found them pretty quickly
but I built them this nice little
something showcase
and building this was relatively fun
because it was small and easy and I
could just be creative with the indoor
decoration I liked that
um
now first of all I'm just gonna go home
and to
you know
uh put down all my things
and then we're gonna think about what to
do
yeah Minecraft has frogs now
so happy
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I was saying anyway yeah
yeah she's playing again
uh I mean there's not much more to that
it's just a fact she's playing Minecraft
again it's nice Saturday I managed to
reignite her passion for it isn't it
isn't that nice
what has she been up to um I forgot she
told me but I forgot I'm sorry hi Mommy
she's probably watching
see something else she's been up to
though not not uh concerning Minecraft
though
my mommy you know she lives in the
middle of nowhere right now like
literally like it's it's literally in
the middle of nowhere
for a while you know
and
[Music]
um
yeah
she doesn't have always access to the
best uh or like even decent
food things
yeah
uh so she was apparently really really
craving noodles good decent noodles and
I I didn't know that she told that to my
sister
um but
because of that my sister
gifted her
um
a noodle making machine
and my mom really excitedly yesterday
posted a picture of her first noodles
and it looks incredible
I'm actually like
tempted to get a noodle machine for
myself but I already have so many
kitchen machines and many of them I
don't even use
[Laughter]
but yeah now my mommy because she she
wanted to eat noodles and she can't
really get good quality noodles where
she's at interestingly
she now can make herself noodles all the
time noodle stream yeah a little machine
for nothing hey
let's not bring that up again my
shortcomings
why must you always bring it up huh
where are I'm just trying to sort things
in right now just give me
give me a moment this will take a long
time
what am I doing I don't know man I
should I should really like organize
maybe we could make it into a really
boring organization stream
like actually you know like like some
other members do it impressively with
everything properly organized sorting
stream yeah
that would be the most boring [\h__\h] ever
for you guys I think wouldn't it
whoa
food fun for Mama doing no one deserves
lacks of lack of tasty food
oh well now she got the noodle machine
though
and yeah the noodles look really good
but I guess
could have just done the thing that I
saw in the YouTube shorts probably taken
from Tick Tock that I told you about
where you basically just take
okay I guess she doesn't even have
access to that but you basically you
take you take normal dried noodles yeah
that you cook in the hot water and then
you crush them up in a mixer until
they're like sand and then you throw in
two eggs and then you knead it until it
becomes something like a dough and then
and then you cook it and it looks
disgusting and it's really unnecessary
it's just a stupid YouTube short AKA
tick tock
really stupid
so stupid
I'm not serious when I'm saying you
should be doing that no no no no no
hmm
yeah
this place is a mess
I don't know where I'm putting things
makes no sense
makes absolutely no sense here's some
press Marine do I have no other
prismarine shards
anywhere
oh there's a crystals
well well well okay let me put
let me put this in here and oh this in
here and
this one is so full
oh I can like literally throw this away
let's throw let's throw this [\h__\h] away
like who needs this like uh what
everything I don't use
all these iron things why do I have all
these iron Things No One Cares I'll at
least get rid of the ones that are
not not and durable anymore
like what what when no when will I ever
use that makes no sense
um a silk touch golden hole okay I will
keep you
my beautiful pack more beautiful isn't
that didn't I put yeah I put never right
on this one
sexy
very sexy
no one needs iron chest plates
no one needs that
this one never
I never fish though
oh this one's decent
okay
[Music]
shovel I'm gonna put the
shovels shovel shovel shovel shovel
right
okay too many shovels
too many shovels
throw away Dead bow Dead bow
this one yeah that's what I was gonna do
uh ah this one you mean I didn't see
that one let's get rid of the crossbows
don't need to crossbones do I need this
I mean it's just cool to have it Fancy
Fancy Fancy
[Music]
weapons
I mean
if you could melt it back into gold that
would be nice but you can't
as far as I know unless eventually there
will be an update that makes you able to
do that
or at the moment it's not possible hmm
wow I'm sorting
amazing we should like put these two
together we should make an anvil because
I have no more anvil
see
no more Advil and will do cool
eh
[Music]
it becomes a nugget okay not even worth
it I don't care it is noticeable though
whoa
[Music]
throw it all the way into the ocean guys
don't do this in real life don't throw
your iron
swords and your crossbows and you all
definitely have into the ocean so
carelessly like me don't do it
don't do it don't do it
[Music]
okay sleepy time
kilo to toss away yeah but only if you
have it in your in your
uh oh wait
only if you have it in your shortcut bar
down there no
yay Pro car batteries and stuff no
yesterday I watched this
um video from terzo if hermit crabs are
op or something like that and yes they
they're not OP but they're like pretty
cool right so
then if at some point they brought up
that sometimes they because there's so
much trash in the ocean sometimes they
use like um bottle caps and stuff as
they're as their new homes which are
kind of superior to their shells
surprisingly I would have thought that
maybe a bottle cap is more sturdy than
like a tiny little shell
Discord what what
I mean if that was real Discord wouldn't
there be another sign next to the next
to it what why is somebody role-playing
as Discord
Discord why are you awake um
do I have more gunpowder somewhere we
should we should Farm gunpowder is there
uh any gunpowder Farm somewhere guys
because I want to make fireworks
thank you
let's clean this out
put it elsewhere
Discord forgot he's on Main
yeah oh Bae has one base I I remember
that one AFK Farm
that one wasn't really efficient was it
but but okay okay
I remember when I was using it it wasn't
the most efficient one
uh and this is good this girl's there
okay so we want gun powder
where do I put these books let me put
them
down here and let me bring oh
where was that mending book here
a fortune
I'm gonna bring it downstairs
maybe I should extend my downstairs this
by the way ah I didn't even build this
remember hookah Papa built this
secret downstairs
I've been using it since
okay Papa yeah this is really old like
people don't probably don't even know
like who built this because I often go
down here on stream but then you know
you don't know the backstory
y'all know the backstory
mmm no I need to sort it all out it
makes me angry
okay books go here how about that
oh my God oh my God
oh my God
[Music]
what a mess
I wish I could duplicate my body and
then go to the afq4 I have key AFK Farm
while also being here
should I should I throw this away
projectile error oh it even says what
you need huh
no wait there's Ed there's a aerosol
mounted on this one is that what it
means because this one doesn't have it
in the icon Discord what the [\h__\h] the
[\h__\h] Discord if it's really you you
gotta ride in the chat
because then you have the actual Mark
maybe maybe for super chats it gets rid
of that
let me get rid of these look why can't
we still not make like useful crossbows
yeah I mean does anyone I guess I would
give it like cool enchantments like we
give to the bows
maybe then
oh
let me add that fortune free hmm if I
combine these will this one get Fortune
free if I like repair this one with this
one
will it get Fortune free
yes oh really
but is it expensive Maybe
crossbow that shoots fireworks
destroying what you can do that no way
what you can
do what what that's cool
that is cool that is hype what oh shines
are here hmm
[Music]
just trying to sort this [\h__\h] out now
sorry guys this is now a really boring
stream I'm sorry I'm sorry but other
people other people do this in their
Minecraft streams right this is this is
just maybe it's just boring for me but
it's not really boring for other people
maybe this is just you know
normal
for some people is it okay
it's relaxing
okay I mean a lot of you guys are
probably very tired right
not me not me
okay Emma rounds I need another box for
my precious things
um
there's not enough space here but I also
should be sorting things out like I'm
doing now
[Music]
um
I haven't slept on you
you could sleep now but you choose to
watch me
um
I'm not feeling well so this is perfect
right now okay
there's a game called unpacking it's
literally about the awareness I know I
know I know I know that's why I I
haven't been playing it ever because
it's just not tickling my fancy
you know
um I was gonna throw this one into I had
like this box right yeah with some of
these bottles
[Music]
um
oh I saw this somewhere else
[Music]
nope
I saw this here
[Music]
oh I almost throw away
all the useless weapons again
yeah I I didn't I wasn't watching Cali
play it but I I heard of what happened
no
I heard of what happened
and that's why I think I dreamed about
cobbled the following night
oh
I keep checking check engine
let's let's not do that all the time
okay
[Music]
oh I can do this ah now I get it thank
you I don't even have to click on it
okay
[Music]
okay uh
okay
[Music]
she was yeah I know I know because I I
was reading the whole thing like I
offered her account because Cali's
wasn't like usable yet in the new server
or like in not even it's not really only
the new server but
on a solo trip this fall so this is an
appreciation post for your past gym and
101 streams I've got six months to and
become fluent at cursing When I visit
Germany and Austria it will be useful
right
um
didn't only teach cursing in my German
101 streams I especially
I especially tried to give you guys
useful knowledge so I do I do not
like how you were wrongly advertising my
German
streams no no no no no
me not like no
no no no no no no
no it's wrong wrong wrong
I'll just keep this one in here
food
for the food God or chest
that was the most useful part don't no
no that is not true no no do not do not
do not do not it's not true
that ain't true
I shared good phrases
for using them in uh when you're like a
tourist
especially For Tourists
um
it's really old though so
you get you you could you guys sorry my
my help my my my I still need to get
used to speaking today
um when you also call me that often
don't you so come on
[Music]
um
then it's in flashbang ah
she will be forgiven oh I saw this
somewhere else
I think
no maybe I didn't I know I brought it
over there ah but I don't I think I feel
like I don't want it there what what do
you use this for
what do you even use this for you sound
so natural like an Austrian do you have
tips on learning wait are you serious I
am Austrian
I am indeed Austrian
okay I had to make anvil
and will
iron iron block okay I have iron
somewhere where did I put the iron
where did I put the iron
I have iron I know it what's with all
the empty chocolate chests huh
Where'd I put the iron
uh I saw it somewhere
I thought it was Swedish I wish
being Swedish kind of seems cool to me
certain countries just I don't know give
me that vibe
how's Phoenix soon I don't know no idea
I haven't been there in ages maybe we
should check
iron block iron
block of iron why did you not come up
when I look for iron block eh was it
free I think it was free
and well there we go
wonderful we got an anvil again
I like the sound it makes
okay so we make this and we make this
all but I need what
what
why why not it doesn't tell me I need a
certain level wouldn't it tell me can I
just not combine this
and you should be hearing it
oh the success would be gone really
and compatible oh no
oh no
what if I do reverse
okay cost six but gets rid of the silk
touch
um
no we don't then you're not getting one
guy well how can I trust anyone anymore
huh
supposed to okay here we go how about
this
now I think I mean it's hard to make
sounds right now
um I don't know how to make sounds fixed
do you hear it okay
okay
um
can I hmm
oh
this one's pretty good and I didn't even
give it a name huh can I combine one of
uh yeah
can I combine this one or this one
or or this one with this one
crazy I'm gone
okay
wait
there you go I'm a genius
both mending can go together either way
wait what's this these and have not
bending
okay maybe this this
[Music]
um
oh wow
17 for that one but it becomes wow yeah
it becomes better
70 okay okay okay okay
how about we go get infinite levels at
phono's place
eventually
today but not right away
[Music]
let's put away the things I don't need
oh
I don't care both both good swords
[Music]
okay but these
and put away my
ball one of my balls oh these ones I
should
oh wait
can I combine ooh protection two and
Protection One boots that are almost
dying can I combine these
hey let's go and then becomes Protection
free wow
this one needs another three okay but
then it would be fixed
sounds good sounds like a good deal for
me
[Music]
um
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
and my my iron let's make here you are
now the iron chest congratulations I'm
so happy for you
sleepy time what a deal what a steal
um
I saw somebody mentioned in a chat a
couple
minutes ago
um but yes I have an announcement to
make uh additionally to my already
stressful week schedule that maybe
doesn't look stressful to you but it is
for me
um
is this direction right based uh Farm
so this one isn't like where you know
the Onsen is more or less
that way
yes
oh wait a second
we're so high in the morning exactly oh
[Laughter]
near bunkeroni I don't remember where
bunker run is see out of respect I'm
blocking out all information on
bunkeroni
is it not like near the ah
oh thank God there's water here
it was somewhere I think where it was
kind of cold
basically okay good
um
all right I will walk
certain amount
what was I saying oh yeah so uh this is
it wasn't on my schedule because I
literally this came in like what are you
doing
has something in its mouth two days ago
two days ago guys
I was asked to do this so
um
I was like okay uh
maybe in in this one time slots okay
uh
squeezing it in because apparently it's
either
this weekend or never
so on my first day night but Friday
morning jst 6 A.M
[Music]
we'll be streaming on crony Channel
is that isn't that why wouldn't you like
question why why is it on chrono's
Channel
yeah
it's on her schedule right yeah
yeah so yeah have some ideas right yeah
so it's like you know like pecula did
the stream with Marine Senpai on Modern
Senpai Channel
to announce that Malin Senpai is on
Valkyrie connect to upcoming
and uh uh yeah I saw the illustration
for that yum
I didn't
feel two days ago when I was asked to do
this I didn't even know that crony was
gonna you know you know you know I don't
want to say it I don't want to say it
because I'm scared but you know I mean
you know I mean that's you just yeah one
plus one
um
I didn't even know
even though but yeah
um very cool
somewhere here
and I will be there to I guess just
comment so I don't know why I am there
but
I will just uh this is it right
I will just oh God
um do my thing you know that I do at
sponsor streams
uh somebody already asked that lumus I
think I did
I was like I guess not since it got like
finished cancel finished it on their own
right
anyway uh how does this work again
there's a chest here right oh okay but I
will AFK here now because last time I
said I would I don't think I did it for
long
I mean I'm not gonna be really Advocate
um I don't really want to escape
what two Fork I one don't enter not
inside
fog what
oh that's okay Frog who the [\h__\h] wrote
this Gouda
oh snowy
and cute they're green
it sounds like good out right now to me
judging by how she talked yesterday or
generally does okay okay not surprised
yeah okay so let's wait a little bit
only a little bit not forever
um
should I go all over but then up there
it probably doesn't consider me to be
down here anymore does it
is this really working though
oh I mean up on the Santa Tower this one
this one
[Music]
this one at that up there is the FK spot
oh oh okay okay
[Music]
up there okay
yeah so uh thankfully it will only be a
short stream but 11 p.m my time first
day I will there's no bed up here I will
be
uh on crony's channel for I guess a
little recap and looking at crony's uh
Valkyrie connect design I suppose
judging by what marine and pecora did
now that is a really short stream that
is shorter than short in my terms
will you be awake for it stop I feel so
bad about that one but I wanna tell
crony do not worry because this is for
me 11 p.m after another stream of mine
so I have no chance but no choice but to
be awake
um
I have no choice I will be awake and
afterwards I will I will be gone for the
weekend
but this way
this way you now have
five streams of me
in this very empty week which is just a
normal week now
it's just a normal week now
like it's just like squeezed all into
like four days
or free
Tuesday free days five streams Street
squeezed into uh three days
um have a great weekend Canada thank you
oh man it's so empty
uh almost like fighting extra tomato on
your burger exactly
um
you give us so much streams even when
you're busy I try because otherwise you
chickens crying
I want you to I want you to I want you
to cry for me
maybe I should practice my Korean skills
up here while I'm here I mean what else
useful can I do I hate this I hate this
cry I was a joke
short week yeah no empty week
um
[Music]
oh I could do my deadlines but then
because then otherwise I say I will do
it and then I don't do it
and then I don't know
I'm scared don't kill me
that probably didn't even spawn a single
gunpowder didn't it
oh it brought me two well
okay I will I will
are you also like considered to be
afking like is it working when you were
like in this screen
[Music]
because then I would I could do it
before my you know until my karaoke
stream
for real for real
for real food it does okay okay okay
because it's awkward I don't know we're
already not doing any anything
significant in this stream we shouldn't
make it any worse should we
am I the only en member streaming right
now probably right oh my God such a
European
you'll welcome Europeans
you're welcome
oh wait no wait some some like uh Bales
or Iris could in theory be streaming
because it's their Prime Time right they
could be streaming
but I am
nonetheless the only one
okay I'm gonna go to
um fanas uh fancy fish farm
that wasn't the name Shaggy face on the
membership
sounds very German
here from latam just watching with the
breakfast good morning thank you
why is the weather so shitty and I
always think it's night time when the
weather is like this but apparently it's
not
why do I always walk this path
because I'm too lazy to find the
Minecarts
shade it looks so good yeah it does I
mean in water and then in the never it's
kind of nah
need to turn it off often
this is so cool cool
that's like legit
cool
I love that
oh now now this gotta be night time
right you can't tell me this is not
night time
[Music]
oh
am I running right now
yeah okay
Muna looks scary
yeah
this is scary this zombie is scary
no Wally today to stand by my side and
show me things I mean I've already been
shown everything but
holy
[Music]
that was so sweet of her
I see now it's night
yeah yeah
[Music]
could he cry
where are the ID members where's Kyla
um
it's okay guys I'm used to it I'm not
sad or anything I'm used to being alone
foreign
[Music]
let's go to fauna's fancy fish farm
Kyla just trained for almost 10 hours eh
is she done with her with her doctor's
thingy
sadly Molin
Owen
wow so many rails
what about cards oh there's a card
I'm impressed
nature
was the other way shorter
is this way shorter by any chance
is that when they made this other
one
no okay
[Music]
ever since maybe you've always been my
number one OC thank you Kelly
I'm happy to hear that thank you
Kayla Farms 200 ancient debris
uh wait ow 200.
did she use the same way of farming that
I did
because I didn't get 200 out of that I
mean but if she did that for 10 hours
okay okay
same way TNT
damn
Alex
I do not know what you're talking about
why are you
hey
wait which direction ah
this way right
let's go
Kyla was alone for nine hours so you can
too believe
we'll see
oh
it's just lonely oh [\h__\h]
ass it's just a lonely day for Minecraft
I guess
if you play Then You're Gonna Be Alone
it seems all these [\h__\h] Minecarts
from recently
uh this way but I want to put it here
let's go
um
wait wait wait wait wait no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no that
let's not make this worse than it
already is okay I stand here
then it can't go through me right okay
there we go
it didn't even have enough power to go
up the stairs eh even though I started
like quite far away
I don't understand
normal day in EN server yeah yeah
wait last time I ran after one but I'm
not the only one who
you know had this happen to them
being left behind by their Minecart
is the stairs they block the cards
come with me yeah this one at least okay
that's where it stops
but the other one went ahead man what if
I just walk
why don't we just walk there it there it
is oh it stopped again
ah the rails need some maintenance
yeah who do they call
Ghostbusters
probably not
what do I call them
hasn't played Minecraft in a long time
huh I felt like she doesn't like it
though
we played in so long
what do we do to get Ahmed to play
Minecraft again
I'm missing C is not working
I meant playing don't lie to me I know
it wasn't her it was Cali
[Applause]
I know
oh no I'm like generally asking what do
we do to get armor to play
if we've come so far that even Cali
plays Minecraft again
then it's it's not too far off I will
keep these Minecarts now and then put
them on the other side
it's not too far off to think that the
Army would play again make her a must
don't we already have moms
they're already Moss
I think there is
also I still have no fireworks I need to
find a boat is there any boats here why
is there no boats in the boat PL
a oh sure are you any boats in here oh
what is that
I thought I could open it oh
nope no boat
that's a fishing course but I mean it
has this thing it looks like there would
be
maybe a boat
but
food is where are they docked I mean
somebody has to bring them back right
when they go out there I guess did we
fly
no we we came back
wait
the boat and Something In The Water ah
fish
I found the boat let's go
ah I just want to get some levels so
that I I won't be held back by
what I want to do because I don't have
the levels
there it is
really some impressive things in
Minecraft I feel like when she finally
follows the type when she gets into
something she like gets really
passionate about it huh
is that not so
am I wrong
about singing and that's just because of
the filter
you do be like that
okay okay there we go
I'm right I'm correct
not wrong
kiwan was never wrong
she did sweet ones I saw like uh well
she hasn't done that in a while though
right she attempted speed once before
um
the only game that ever made me want to
attempt the speed run honestly is Tunic
I will never forget tunic like a long
lost lover
ah the passion that we
exuded
the many romantic nights we spent
together
ah
I will never forget
I love I love tunic so much
[Laughter]
the nights the days the hours we spent I
will never forget
never never never
all right here we go I just want the
levels I don't want to mend anything in
particular hi
let's sweep
ow ow
very hurtful what the [\h__\h]
their dead bodies come towards me
aren't you supposed to get healed
I thought this there's some kind of like
function that heals you here too
oh well
no need I'll just eat my chicken kfp for
the win can't see the best
very very many nutrients
many vitamins in my chicken you ask me
which one well obviously vitamin C
change armor my armor rubber no it's
fine it's fine don't scare me they all
have mending oh they actually really all
have bending
that's okay don't scare me
oh why last time I feel like they didn't
do this much damage to me
oh my God I'm Legit gonna die she Coco
let's play it okay
[Music]
oh
they're gone where the fishes
[Music]
I'm killing them too fast I guess oh but
they do respawn really fast it's really
impressive
it's really impressive
Minecraft stream idea suggestions
tutorials walks along yeah why would I
do a tutorial is popular private World
Redstone study what never roof hub for
answer what
what are these ideas are you trolling me
yeah and the father asked many times we
are not allowed on the roof nothing I
was interested but I saw the
conversations
we're not supposed we're not allowed to
go up there
mulfana is the only one asking though I
think
I don't know what did Paula want to do
like some Farms or so
I wonder what what it is that's so
fascinating up there
Kyla asked to they allowed it now are
you sure
I'm [\h__\h] scary
there we go
ah scary
a gold Farm oh is that what you can do
up there
can you not make a gold Farm like in a
normal environment
[Music]
it's hard to see
wow level 14. let's go
only allowed to go not build now ah okay
okay
maybe she could do like uh I have an
idea for a gold farm for her without
making a gold Farm there she could ask
for like 10 Gold Blocks or so or one or
five I don't know in exchange for as a
payment in exchange for a tour up there
because like I'm Legit curious like as
if I'm a tourist I want to be I want to
be toured
I've never seen this magical mystical
place I am curious
that way she can make gold
up there and over the never ceiling
can I get a croissant for my birthday
hello
yo I
I wrote We I chatted with gura again
yesterday
I'm having like I think the more more
communication was gooder than anyone
else right now definitely more than
Denmark
[Music]
and blessed by the cat shark shark cat
she have a stroke
she's fine I think I think
what
how high do I want to get guys
what are these weird funky reflections
how about 50.
oh do you guys know when chocolate
what was that level what was the highest
level she got
it was choco Sensei right she was like
endlessly leveling
and we got much higher
hi
700 plus
this is farming levels but for what what
was the purpose
I'm over 50 now hmm let me clean this
really quickly up from all the fishies
no
that's nice okay
today what do they bring where does it
go
ah is this what they dropped
all that praise Marine oh
that's really it like some fishes and
some prismarines
that's it
lamb why don't they have out
[\h__\h] was that
how did they hurt me
how
did you
guys
[Music]
did you curse me your thing they shoot
lasers I was up too high oh what is it
open up there probably has to be what
the [\h__\h]
Skittle okay okay
all right all right enough levels let's
go
oh the weapon let's bring the weapon
back
eye
I hate I hate this
I hate going up this these thingies yeah
don't worry I don't worry don't worry
I'll bring it back
I'm not trying to steal it
so many beautiful stars wow
Dana look look at the stars
you can press space and you won't have
to look straight up I think oh oh
yeah I'm pressing space Oh I don't have
to look up but then at least I know when
I'm there
it's kind of weird to look elsewhere
flop flop flop funny fishy flaps
well oh
oh
there we go
where did where do you put it look here
funny fish Falcon has been returned
now where to go oh
that's so hard to see
and home is
oh somewhere there wait no no no no no
no no no
this way
I think
home is where Chihuahua is right
ah there we go
[Music]
should check out ee too what's EE
h
what's ee now
don't use ee that's rafana gets all the
emeralds her raid Farm
it's hard to choose
weather operated by fauna only
okay
it's okay
too dangerous really okay I don't really
it's okay I don't really need emeralds
right now
plenty Amber roses at home too and if I
want emeralds I just give them iron or
something
or bread or whatever
because I got Phoenix then okay I have
my own Emerald Farm AKA phoenixson
it's not natural
I want to live life naturally
she's got like 1K oh
one cave yeah okay good to know but
right now I don't really need
emeralds I think
go go
here we go here we go here we go
while I'm spawning and dying shortly
after in lava is not natural you're
asking that as if you're
thinking it's
I mean you you're asking that ironically
aren't you I know that I can say frail
you the little chicken mine
can't be Buzz doesn't like farming
nature built factories how ironic
[Laughter]
hmm is it
yeah yeah yeah I mean the whole nature
building
Automatic Farms
to exploit everything yeah that is
ironic
you won't die from falling into lava the
heat will roast you before you reach it
reach what
are you talking real life we're talking
real life right why are you even telling
me that
that's just the nature
things wow
I'm not so impressed by that one instant
very hot well I would assume so
that reminds me for something yesterday
I tweeted something did you guys get my
joke
I think uh Nina Nina wrote to me I think
something like you're a machine like in
a positive way because I guess I I I did
something
yeah and I replied with a near automata
give
from
the like leader of machines or whatever
and I don't think you guys really
understood what I was getting at
because no one really replied like oh
damn koala smart it's my choice of gifts
it's pronounced give
oh really
I knew it was from there but I didn't
get it
ah see that's why I'm explaining it to
you guys now chicken Minds once again
failing us
I've been avoiding spoilers sorry oh
I mean I was just looking for generally
like machine gifts
and I don't know I felt like that one
also looked
looked pretty
fitting to the
purpose Jazz what's up thank you
damn Jeff you're always sending those
stickers why why why don't you don't you
have anything to say
to me
prob I guess not
I guess not
all right I'm back with 54 levels of
only leveling was this easy and MMORPGs
man
which brings me to another point
hmm
tends to finish so many games
it has come to my attention that kfp
uh has made a list
about the games that I finished and the
games I didn't finish
um which is cool and all to see you know
but I do not think that World of
Warcraft
a game that I have played on stream you
know for a little bit of fun
uh belongs to the unfinished games
section I don't agree with that because
uh and everyone G
the way you consider it finished
eventually that is just your personal
opinion
World of Warcraft isn't really like you
know you can't finish it there's always
something to do in an MMORPG in theory
you can always like raid and stuff yeah
your animal refugees are finished when
you think they're finished so I call
openly publicly for a removal of World
of Warcraft from my unfinished game
section because it is ruining my
beautiful
ratio
I want it changed
otherwise I'm throwing you into the
usual room
do not
Justice
there's already so many other games in
the unfinished section that made me
really wonder am I really the game
finisher but all these games like I
never I play those games not planning to
finish them and you guys know that too
oh
[Music]
no I give you permission to consider
thank you here a world of Walker player
says I have permission to finish to say
it's finished I mean there's a chance
I'll play it again but but
what was I gonna do
but
for you know I just feel generally like
it shouldn't be in that section it makes
no sense
mending
no wait which ones was I gonna put
together
which ones
man let's let's mend these ones as well
if I have some diamonds
I just need diamonds right I need more
diamonds is there a diamond farm
somewhere
is that something
it doesn't exists
whoa
[Music]
no
um
it's emotion you don't even know what
you're talking about that's why you're
asking now
Evie thank you
I take my thank you back
Kyla no no you cannot Farm
uh yeah it's called Kaila
you mean just requesting her that is the
farm uh hey we could uh go mine for some
diamonds I wouldn't mind that um
fortunately so can I which one can I
combine these already have three so I
can't huh
this one's better
oh
um
this is
a decent ax
not the best one it's a decent one
now I'm out of diamonds do I really have
no more diamonds
[Music]
let me check
you can get diamond tools for emeralds
which are formal formable though yeah
true
put some more diamonds down here
yeah those might be
all of my diamonds okay oh
[Music]
make a list for Kyla no I feel bad like
no no no no no no no no no
you can't do that
[Music]
wait all my levels damn they go away
quickly huh
this one should we name this one too
this one's pretty decent too isn't it
oh
pretty
decent too
two two
I have caps lock on that seems
above average shovel that's a good name
too
this one's
not worth it
but I'm doing it anyway because I got
those diamonds
okay here we go
oh can I this one I can
wait this one has bending why would I
repair it with
why did I repair any of my mending
things with diamonds
yeah why
I don't understand I don't I don't
understand either I don't understand but
I mean
now I don't
know well excuse me okay I I get it now
I
I noticed
eventually
but hey look at this looks nice doesn't
it like all these repaired things
doesn't look nice to you
I think it looks very nice
I'll keep um
which one is this one oh thank you
coming
okay
[Music]
I keep
um
ah the pickle ax oh this one has silk
touch me yeah no need no need
this one could use another enchantment
should we enchant it
with what what do I have this one has
efficiency too and mending right now
let's enchant it make it special
what should we give it I have I've got
some books
these all have silk touch so we could
give it silk touch I guess or
so then I have a second
or even a third one these are all like
attack ones I guess oh I'm breaking
you know silk touch I guess
efficiency five and
silk touch all right
what how do you do this again I need
like one of those book thingies right
what can you do can you I forgot can you
do it
hahaha
like this
oh yeah you can ah
okay
and silk touch
hey now it's more useful
hi recipes diamonds bro you still on bed
yeah okay
that's totally fine I will go get us
some diamonds now I will go digging
why not don't have anything else to do
I'm breaking free hmm
what but now it already has free
enchantments I can't add anything
I think
let me
can we can I put the prismarine shards
together into like blocks or so
it should work where's Marine
yeah oh
all right
that's it wow you don't get it no
I still have some more don't get much on
this do you
and what about these 50 45 ones
and what do you do with these ones
the crystals
lanterns oh what
oh God damn it
that's what you you use them for only
that
um
let me put press Marine stuff in here
okay
and I was going to throw away
and yeah
okay
okay okay here we go here we go I wanna
go dig I want to go dig
sorry I just threw that puffer fish
not even into the water I am I am
ruthless
should we just dig like sex like
somewhere here or somewhere specific I
wonder
[Music]
I'll just dig oh
ah wait no no wait before we do that I
want to make some uh fireworks
need some paper from my paper Farm
yeah
I make some useful things too that
people don't know about
who don't even know
I think a lot of people don't know about
this Farm but like we don't have enough
paper Farm on the Ian server Dooley
name the farm it's a paper Farm
mama told him
yeah I made it with my mom don't
discredit me what the hell
okay this is the this this should be the
paper one okay but no I guess not I'll
make I'll make
um this one into the paper box
okay I'll wait a couple
fireworks
now I know there's like different levels
right but people usually always just
made the basic one right the basic one's
fine right
thank you invisible loner I agree yeah
yeah yeah yeah
the second one you made doesn't work
that's okay that's okay poor Iris then
lost off stream how do you know that
even though it's uh off stream
is it going better for flying ah so the
others uh because you can use the use
them for the
not for the bow for the other weapon
thingy
are they more useful for that
interesting
she tweeted it
but she wasn't when did when that
happens it wasn't even online
what did she just tweet that now
if not then that wasn't relevant and
then you it was really
really not relevant to put that into my
chat but okay
um
um okay I'm I will put my thingy my hot
wings here
[Music]
and I don't need this many fireworks
to go digging let's go digging
where do we go dig not right here I
would say
oh greetings from work thank you hello
how's work going
let's go digging most exciting thing to
do in Minecraft
mining literally maybe I should bring
my elytra
I won't bring my Elantra I have a backup
anyway
yay
hold on I'll bring some more food too oh
no I have plenty okay
I will fly somewhere
um choose a Direction guys tell me North
north south East West which one
and chest hmm
right behind the chest I place it I
place it on the
the other server actually I should bring
um should bring this one
hello
East
and well why are you guys not giving the
same answer
yeah
yeah no north south
sweet
[Music]
is West Western East
wait that doesn't work that with this
self right
okay let's go south
kind of a boring Direction guys not
gonna lie okay
oh God
what what how
there you go
I think I'm self now
take off shield no it's okay
I mean I guess you know I would see more
oh whoa why am I upside down
I don't wanna dig in a snow region
I don't know why but I don't like it
[Music]
karaoke stream in
seven and a half hours right
I I guess we'll dig and um
I guess
maybe after that it's just over
my my least it's okay guys you can say
it honestly my least exciting Minecraft
stream to date
it's okay sometimes you know some days
are just like this you know you can't
can't help it and it'll be like that
it will be like that
I'm all right with that okay but we'll
read super chats a little bit I think
I can afford to do that I think
time wise
I think we're good
[Music]
you guys get the coordinates
of home
I will land right here because I see
something interesting wow
not you not you not you
which one was the second one okay
well
doesn't have to be exciting every time
thank you very reassuring
I appreciate that hmm
otherwise the here it is one
ah two three four five six seven
eight
nine hmm
[Music]
let's get some more
than oh like why why is it visitable
why such a thing visitable anyway how
did she chain her Warden
in a way that it can be visited
so weird
obsidian
beautiful obsidian
obsidian I forgot it's the only way wait
no obsidian was when you when you pour
water over lava right then you can make
obsidian
just trying to remind myself how you
make it I don't remember well
is that more obsidian yeah
but the crying one cannot be recreated
right only
spawns naturally or can you make crying
obsidian yourself
again from training with Pikmin
oh ah
piglets right now okay well I wouldn't
count that but
foreign
get that one too
and the gold plug did I get it gold
uh another one here gosh I should put
the pies please don't tell me to bring a
bed another
an amateur
guys
[\h__\h] it's so dark now you did did you
really
yeah look at these disgusting tools like
what who gives a [\h__\h]
[Music]
should we fly north again
huh
oh man I forgot like all these important
things
um we came from South so we would fly
north right
oh man
I can't believe it I got bamboozled
so stay in fire no but for real I need
torches though at least
at least torches
what's the next big Minecraft update
next interesting thing
[Music]
what's that
is that EEE
how did I accidentally find it
let me sleep here
and look at them emeralds
foreign
what new bamboo wood bamboo blocks oh
cool okay that's some cool stuff
and when is that coming
let's say something
no
no where is the number one oh
there's some Gunpowder too
oh oh is that what I dropped wow
oh there's not a thousand emeralds
I'm impressed Kiana again
hole
was it pillagers
did you clean it out oh wait a boat wait
not my boat where's home
North
[Music]
yeah yeah I can imagine she must have
needed some for with a fight did you
bring movie home not yet I kind of was
like thinking of doing it though this
stream that's why I put mummy in the
thumbnail
from the really
doesn't have anything to do with the
stream right now
sorry about that
I didn't know what to put in the
Frontline because I didn't know what to
do but I can bring mommy home any
anytime one question though that I was
curious about
um
that Tower is not
villager made is it
uh well I wanted to ask uh so they pick
up blocks that like the block that you
give them they will try to find more of
that right but uh does it it doesn't
have to be like mined right so if it's
like a stone block will they just take
it from a mountain or so
and bring it to you or does it have to
be mine and you know like like dropped
on the
on the ground
I feel like I feel like I'm lost
only if it's loose on the world it
really so
that's weird though like how does that
help
I only pick uh I guess it
but also only what I give them right
Southwest
okay thank you
oh thank you thank you for the
coordinates
two eight two
eight two
how
didn't I fly in Just One Direction
it's a bit of a gimmick
okay bring your things to a designated
spot
um
well now I'm home
yay
[Music]
well but then I thought
then they're not as useful as I thought
they would be
because
well
then you actually have to like you know
I guess mine something but then when if
you're there to mine it then you're
there to pick it up as well
um yeah they're just cute
yeah I was wondering why would they
bring something so like relatively
helpful overpowered helpful but I guess
it wasn't that helpful after all okay
and then they're really just cute okay
yeah
[Music]
I know nakama
is
useless
just cute
where are the Torches
there's some there's not many
if I want a lot of uh
here's some more
if I want a lot of diamonds and that's
not much but okay
can we make more what do you need again
not cold was it it wasn't cold was it
and sticks
no it is coal Coal and sticks
I'll try to make a couple more uh uh
didn't I put sticks in here did I not
ah there I did
and cold cold I just raised the part in
Charmed where coal shows up and oh man
when I was younger watching Charmed as a
young teenager more like a child oh I
had a crush on coal but honestly who
didn't have a crush on coal
he's very crushable
first crush I I wasn't saying My First
Crush also didn't he have like a demon
form that's really creepy but yeah I
think that maybe changed my mind a
little bit but
yeah he's
before he you know shows his true form
and I don't care what spoilers right now
because this show is from a million
years ago and you guys are not going to
watch it anyway are you
if you haven't watched it yet it's so
tacky it's such a tacky show but the
second and third season are already less
tacky than the first season
so it gets it's got it gets better
don't worry
but yeah
coal
he's he's so he's pretty handsome he is
pretty handsome
something about you know guys in suits
that's just
it's just it just works I don't know why
it works so well
or should I put the coal
why should I put you coal hmm yeah I'll
put you there
okay
chicken's trying to spit themselves into
a suit this instance
since they're fancy they are
suits
suits very good
the last thing we want now is about
where is where did this bed go I think
it's never been
I'll take
okay now we can go Johnny
maybe not the same place but
I'll see what I can do
YouTube dropped before you said it eh
YouTube you're good
you ever wants to show Lucifer I think
you like the main character there uh no
I don't think I did
I think I've like
heard of it before
thank you
being a suit no David Tennant in the
suit yes why why why do you think you
don't look good in suit I think
everybody looks good in a suit
women too like damn business baby
why am I running out of fireworks
already okay I'll go somewhere like here
close by
it might be icy but oh well
mmm
yeah okay okay okay I'll take that I'll
take that
okay this is approximately where I will
be digging I think
oh
let me make
oh here screenshot coordinates
I will dig
should we dig down because there where
are diamonds again
like
six seven something like that was the
magical number
let me start down here then we are at
uh
uh 30 no
60 free okay we have to go down quite a
bit
we might meet water I hope
not should we do just one path
two is nicer but we should just do one
path otherwise man I'm gonna get spammed
with stones
foreign
[Music]
it changed that much wasn't it actually
like six before
something like that
is that water
no interesting
I'm bad at this I guess I forgot how to
do this
here okay okay good
uh I should put in my second hand the
Torches eh
I remember the strategy
it depends if this is a new chunk or not
oh
oh it probably isn't it's pretty close
to our headquarters I feel like somebody
must have flown by here before right
is that a little Kev Kev
spooky spooky spooky spooky spooky
spooky spooky spooky I don't like it
hmm did I bring two shulkers
what why is this shocker still of me eh
I'm confused
no I don't like no no scare me
scary scary
I'm not as efficient as I used to be I
think but oh well
I get diamonds probably barely we should
uh wasn't there a thing a term called
strip mining
is that where you make one long path and
then make the path to the side
well here my knowledge It's All Coming
Back
I'm not as bird-brained as you thought I
was
I am I remember why is this here that's
bad right it wasn't that bad
it's usually a sign of
water
[Music]
no it's okay
okay
if you say so
so what should we talk about guys
is there something you want to talk
about I already mentioned the crony
thing
I I wonder what her first thought was
when when she was told hey crony we want
you to do this sponsored stream um with
Kiana
ever since that happened I feel um very
awkward towards crony I'm scared
wait what's that
the sponsored thingy that we did before
was that
that was that was before
uh we went to Osaka to the Universal
Studios right that was before right
what you fed her turkey exactly yeah
yeah
everything was normal then
she treated me fine normally
so you would think I don't have to be so
concerned but I
I got uh flashbacks you know when I read
that and I wonder she probably doesn't
feel so happy about
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you you
you
otherwise they're selfish you're like
f-tier you're literally ft here why are
you here
they spawn here why hello are we 20.
does that mean there's an End Portal
nearby
she probably doesn't think about it at
all
maybe not generally but when we're
reminded of a sponsorship stream
maybe then
she
she thought about it I feel like she may
have thought about it
I don't know I thought about it
that is my possibly my most shameful
moment in my almost three years of home
alive
[Music]
but don't worry I will be there I will
be awake because it's 11 pm for me I'm
always awake at 11 PM
don't worry
[Music]
macaroni call me chronini
recently I feel like I get along with
everyone pretty well
uh hey we're at five now
so should I go further there was this
this one what was it what's it called
Deep slate
what does that mean doesn't that mean
it's a new chunk actually
if there's deep slate
optimal
[Music]
laughs
oh I have
a happy day out tomorrow and one year
anniversary it hit
Diablo four stream oh yeah I wonder what
she thinks about the new Diablo she
probably didn't try it
loud
[\h__\h]
she might remind you five times on that
ah no worries no worries crony I'm I'm
around I'm around so minus 50 minus 60
might be good okay okay so since it has
deep slate that means it's a new chunk
that means that now diamonds are at -15
okay okay
foreign
s would also have also have the diamond
layers around level eight oh okay
hey Ultimo you're still following up
okay let me read that another time but
for now happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday oh you know what I
thought of um to talk about Ina's new
outfit I haven't mentioned it yet Ina's
new outfit you know
when I first thought I think Ina showed
me like personally
a long time ago
I think it was still at the
non-movable stage just just the artwork
I think
and I thought it was very cute but is it
just me like her ears immediately made
me think she looks like Shrek now
I was like you know those are Shrek ears
and she's like no no no no
no what are you talking about what is
that
what's up
no I'm in a cave I don't want to be in a
cave no I hate this
it's so dark
oh no
can't unsee it now you mean the flaps
yeah
I can't unsee why did you not see it yet
eh
how did I mention it did you not did you
not
how is it not obvious to you now until
now yeah
well then
you cursed us Kiana
don't blame me
how do I do this
[Music]
well that's good but I don't think I can
do that forever
uh it's really low
maybe I should just change direction but
this looks pretty big
um
right
how about I go
now I'll go I'll go straight for a while
thank you
I guess and then down again
[Music]
yeah yeah but anyway really cute pretty
simple but like obviously very very
usable on streams her new outfit
and then she has like a controller and
stuff
I was thinking you know you know asking
for something like that it just takes up
a lot of like resources if I ask for a
controller and then I would probably
have to give up on for example and a new
hairstyle like an extra hairstyle and
then I'd always prefer to have a second
hairstyle over a controller which I can
just put a PNG on top of myself I I
think so for me the priorities are
elsewhere
hmm
even though it's nice it would be nice
to have it as an asset like an actual
properly attached but now that we can
attach pngs to ourselves anyway it
doesn't look so bad I think I mean this
one I can't attach because it's a gif
honestly need to ask them to
um make it possible to attach gifts GIFs
that would be very desirable
ideal
the hair better choice Ryan I think so
too
don't need the controller hand a
different hairstyle gives so much more
variety and cute
right
Mr chicken pad give
oh which one
this one like some of my assets I just
haven't been using because I don't I
can't find them anymore you guys are
welcome to remind me of certain assets
if you want me to use them again like
like the cat pad thing one that there
was an animated one like anime cat
patting one that I don't know where that
one went
I need to put them into my resources
folder but back then I didn't have a
resources folder yet now I do
there's one from JT and one from Jolly
yeah yeah I think so too
anyway I'm glad you guys agree with my
values
nothing though against uh you know like
for her
why not if she's happy with just one
hairstyle
good for her I I wouldn't be but her she
[Music]
can we get much shorter
then she would be bald probably
we are at -17 and there's some gold here
finally something
come here
hey yo
give me the there we go
ball is okay too
I guess
yeah yeah
I mean yeah in real life yeah but that's
a YouTuber
I know I don't know
but I feel like if I said Okay I want my
hairstyle to be bald at least that
wouldn't take up resources because they
surely a bald head under my head
somewhere
so what would they have to do nothing
nothing
dangerous dangerous
so I could get a free bald wait
wait free
so even if I don't want it just as a
joke couldn't I say hey
can you give me a bold option fun I
should be asking us she uses her her
bald asset a lot but that makes it more
funnier I think the fact that it's just
a scuffed PNG on top of her makes it
funnier right
what no not again
it doesn't look so low though
ah
matakayo
um
both girls are unironically cute
in real life you mean yeah yeah
actually I've seen some extremely cute
bald girls
the one from dances and Dragons was
really cute bold as well
[Music]
should I go down
I'm scared I gotta bring back fighter
Wawa here we go
I'll go down
I'm going down
um
maybe I could place my bed before I go
down
there we go okay
okay
I'm going down but I have no water so I
will have to survive the jump which I
think it doesn't look too tall so we're
probably okay better with Elijah so you
fall slow
but I want to be protected immediately
against whatever is down there
[Music]
um okay
how do you like quickly
uh switch something out
[Music]
how does that work again if you put it
like in your hot
barfingy
shift click
use your blocks of bread I can't live I
don't know how to do it it's like
there's nothing to build it onto
highlight and right click
what
um whatever
I [\h__\h] said [\h__\h] scared I'm gonna
die I'm gonna die
how to fight how to fight I know how to
fight I know how to fight I know how to
fight
thank you
[Laughter]
uh uh
they're not coming for me that was the
only one at the moment
where was the snow falling
I did it wrong I think I did it wrong
uh where's my sword what the [\h__\h]
okay okay
chill everybody
see a lot of enemies what's that looks
shiny what is that
it must be Lava there because it's also
shiny
[Music]
what doing wait okay why am I incapable
of running why am I incapable of running
I am too stupid I always panic in these
situations
wonderful good shot Chihuahua
so proud of myself
all right
this is
a big looking cave probably connected to
uh oh God panic panic probably connected
to the the other entrance that I saw
and then I was trying to avoid it I
guess I can't
you little [\h__\h]
let's try to get this one too from a
distance
ah
oh my God see if he's not moving I can
like really
uh
guess correctly why is he going away I'm
here so
where to shoot
okay more
more
oh he's got an enchanted book
[Music]
I see a diamond
I feel like these these torches lights
this place up like barely only barely
nice nice nice nice oh yeah apparently
according to Kyle carrots compilation I
barely hits the
um wither
I I think that is
not true
I I am I'm saying don't believe this
slanderous accusation but
um well
[Music]
um
I think
maybe you didn't see much like physical
damage but I definitely did a lot of
mental damage to the Wither by
especially after he was dead by telling
him how how weak he was
and and you know I mean
I mean he was just I would have had 100
more hits in if he didn't die so quickly
emotional damage yeah
I I don't know how to shoot with zoom oh
hi
we don't want to shoot at the Enderman
how high to shoot with zoom there we go
I
there we go beautiful
snipe
all right all right all right here is
one Diamond our first diamond and
whatever that is what is that
glow Legion
lichen
that's it wow impressive where are we
now and minus ah minus 45. oh this is
where we wanted to go
oh so basically they just
help they're just helping me do some
strip mining here huh
no I have places on the other side
I was just thinking is that where I
was before and I was like nope nope nope
nope nope minus 41. if I go lower than
minus 50 are the chances for diamonds
much lower
is it really good to stay around -50
30 day free trial so is that is that
what I'm using right now
don't strip while mining
who's on what are you talking about
what's with your imagination that really
concerns me I don't know what you're
seeing but I think I am fully clothed
below below -50 is better
-58 is best
below
wait
oh you're right oh wait
I got confused um
I need to go lower than this not higher
I thought it was too low because logic I
guess
confused
did I just shoot the that was on purpose
I totally shot that bat on purpose
okay I will go a little bit deeper then
oh I hear lava though
[Music]
no oh
a little lava pool
um
very cozy oh yeah we're at -53 let's
just go this way
away from the lava don't
just
close that off I guess
am I running out of torches
this level is fine
okay
okay then I'm just gonna go straight now
I think
53 or maybe one more
careful maybe we'll just stay here
that's just let's just stay here and be
very careful there seems to be a lot of
lava around
I don't know
can you build stairs to where your bed
is oh oh I probably should but it's okay
I lit it up really well
so I feel confident enough
where are the diamonds
where are they
did they make them even rarer than
before
it be a pain in the ass
that song is
that all cap
where's that okay up
huh
here's a little a little taste for
everybody who can't come to uh
uh the karaoke stream tonight
let me try let's try
while I'm digging
princesses
ah there it is
I'll just work lyrics here oh
and then on it
needs to load every song though it's
pretty slow 45 48 49 40. it takes a long
time I wonder if I loaded one spill it
afterwards not have to load it again
hopefully
52 53 54 55 67
60 percent
why are you looking for diamonds again
that's because I thought I had no
diamonds so why not get some diamonds
there's nothing else to do
[Laughter]
okay
we'll tell you
oh it's supposedly starting but I don't
hear it
uh
[Music]
I should hear
no it loads again oh but it looks much
faster
[Music]
here but whatever it doesn't matter
how the lyrics coming in this makes no
sense
[Music]
I don't I
don't know
[Music]
foreign
I forgot their name they're so shitty I
forgot their name
[Music]
in a wrong order
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
Canada
[Music]
some money
a festival
where the lyrics
[Music]
up and down down
I haven't found a single one but you are
here with me so I won it doesn't matter
as long kfb is here with me yeah
didn't find the single one
um
[Music]
I tried to summon them with a song where
are the diamonds
hello
what a joke
this should have been the moment the
very moment to bring me all the diamonds
I want to go lower there's so much lava
okay
probably I've I've made so many
directions I probably won't even know
which one's the right one to go home
okay I hear
I hear it I think
but
I also sensed the diamonds
56.50 you guys said 58 is the best okay
I'm trying I'm trying but we gotta be
like extremely careful
do we have another Diamond song
yeah
was there like an AKB song
something like that they probably don't
have that in here though
yet
it's a pretty
good good song actually I actually like
that one a lot I don't like many nkb
songs but that one I like and I don't
have it right now
ah the micro song
Diamond City Lights
that's that's a Diamond song I guess
yeah
Diamonds by Rihanna I can't sing that
one now I could sing it
in the I mean I can sing it because I
don't give a [\h__\h] but
um where are we oh 50 oh that's too high
here
58 okay
okay here we go I guess let's just go
straight for now until we meet the
Fateful lava
uh
what was it
shine bright like a diamond
[Music]
you will die you will die we're like
diamonds in the skies
I don't know
[Music]
the lyrics at all the diamonds in the
sky
right away
foreign
[Music]
diamonds in the sky how do I
oh so alive
we're beautiful like diamonds in the sky
wow wow
[Music]
beautiful like diamonds in the sky
beautiful
diamonds in the sky
no the vibe will be fine trust me it
didn't even sound like song anyways
Diamond City Lights
lyrics
ah beautiful
down there I opened up memories
I found something that I could live for
curtain shove as you opened my eyes
and life came rushing inside
behind my heart's encrypt and keep it so
low listen and you might hear a Melody
your fire sparked the passion keep that
keeps burning
magic that helps me to believe
all the colors of the nine and the way
they help you hide
I'm learning what it's like to love and
be alive oh there will always be a
tomorrow
never have to be alone Diamond City
Lights
[Laughter]
what's inside another love I feel by
your side the coding these emotions
you're the ocean I wanna dive into
tonight
don't cry look in my eyes and you might
find a shimmering light
we'll guide you to the where but what
where was I
oh now let me guide you that was a bit
different
let's go to the place no no no I skipped
I was right it was fine
when Rey Skies they take the colors away
far away I'll paint the rainbow
days and days
[Music]
where
just just like the uh Magic uh that you
always said with me left
right right
maybe now you need to believe that there
will be diamonds as the hands of time
progress it's so easy to forget the
miracle that helped you bring me to life
oh there will always be a tomorrow
will never have to be alone
gold
City Lights
illuminate what's inside and all the
love I feel by your side the coding
these emotions you're on the ocean I
wanna dive until tonight rainbow colored
Skies invite us to the garage and no
Time Won't Wait cause it only leaves
behind don't cry look in my eyes and you
might find a shimmering light now let me
guide you for your time
[Music]
in that very moment you know what the
[\h__\h] popped up on my screen
right in front of me
in front of my Minecraft screen
windsip reminder to maybe
buy a subscription
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] you and there's the [\h__\h]
diamonds I'm going back now I don't care
anymore give me my torches you don't
deserve torches
you don't deserve them
I am so cheap I will take my torches
back no that's right
let's go to the place let's go to the
place let's go to the place where
our happiness won't fade away
if you could only see
[Music]
everything we could be
a diamond City Lights
emotions you're the ocean I wanna dive
into tonight rainbow colored Skies
take a ride I know time won't wake up it
only leaves behind don't cry look at my
eyes on you might find a shimmering
light
which way
foreign
check first
oh oh this way yeah
yeah
Diamond lights Rainbow Skies in the
night there's no need to hide the joy in
your eyes fills me with life so let it
shine
yeah I sang the whole thing
oh I'm already back though oh
at this place at least
you got any more diamonds here hmm
very disappointing
I I got one diamond on all of that
baby
I should just ask Kyla but no imagine
Kyla going for all the suffering just
got me diamonds man
no that's not fair that's not fair in
what world is that fair
um
so where's my here
all right it's time to go back I can
stream endlessly today
I have some things to do
yeah
Tony eyes
imagine lava being on over there
imagine imagine
I have a scent by card on her yeah but
let's be real I don't even need diamonds
that uh like originally or so
[Music]
um
thank you for the diamond cut out the
preview I do want to sing the AKB song
at some point so
it's really pretty and it's a famous
sound so there's probably an
instrumental that I can use just not in
the application that we have now
not yet
surely joy sound has it in theory I just
need to get it
I'm taking all of these back are they
going into my inventory
I had to go into my right hand left hand
bed
huh
I mean at least I would spawn somewhere
if I die on the way back I'm okay with
the bed being there is any downside to
the bed being here
are you feeling lonely these days I mean
I was like you know joking a little bit
about that a couple moments ago but no
I think you know there were sometimes
um like especially I think last year
where it felt very lonely
like well IRL and and in I'm gonna be
honest and Holo too
but
it really only takes like
you know like that that much dream where
somebody joins me for a little bit
that's all it takes
down
it's going down
no it what where where am I right how do
I go back
I don't understand anymore
be going up
yeah yeah and then like
and then recently good at writing so
much to me
you know it just feels it feels nice
to to know that I exist
yeah
so recently you know I've been feeling
really oopsie really good
I'm good I'm good
yeah
[Music]
I'll let you know it exists thank you
and you guys always do
you guys are what keeps me going even in
the darker days
anytime soon
be patient there's there's really so
many whole life members uh I can't like
constantly collab with everyone all the
time I think I prefer just um doing uh
an off collab of Coronado and did I tell
you I have plans to go to Japan
uh and honestly time passes by so fast
that
it will be
sooner than later
probably
no
yeah I told you guys
in June
I'll be going to Japan
and I hope I can
like make it so that
I have uh like a place where I can
stream well again
like last time because I don't want it
to be any different for you guys besides
the streaming times of course
uh North
[Music]
720 Pizza
true true
what's that tough what the [\h__\h] is tough
guess I'll keep it because I don't think
I have much of tough
will you be there for your birthday
when's my birthday uh
for my birthday
maybe not
um I'm still like I still don't know
they still haven't given me a date on
when I can do my birthday thingy
um I was hoping
to combine it
but
[Music]
um
questionable
[Music]
God shitty weather to be flying
I think for now I'm going into the right
direction
yeah yeah so I doubt I doubt that it
will be on time my birthday
sadly so what else will I be doing on my
birthday I I probably will just do like
a call in Collins are really fun too
anyway
um
Colin and
you know
merch announcements stuff like that
I'm already home
I'm already on Mozart
yeah I wouldn't I didn't go so far
because I just wanted
to not use too many fireworks
well then I shall take the train
yeah the usual b-day stuff
the usual birthday stuff that you do
when you don't have 3D yet in the whole
life a 2d stream weird to tell because I
do have Freddy I wonder I wonder
going on there
how come
I feel like I'm back in 2021 or 2022 for
that matter
no wait no no 2022 but I did I did get
myself with my own power and
determination of early birthday I did I
did
I did
that it's a 2021 flashback yeah
3D Collins
at least you'll get it later on just not
on birthday
um I I really want a date though that
would be nice
so I can plan you know I want to plan I
have the thing is like I wanted you know
that I want to do an album right so I've
been planning to if things would be on
time to on my birthday uh concert not
release the album but like tease
one or two songs on it but if the
birthday like with the choreo that's why
I'm actually already getting choreo made
right now what if um my birthday is like
two months after the album release or so
well I guess then I can
use the plants but then I feel like I I
would have to do more of my album songs
oh man it is just you know difficult to
plan anything at all
now
Chihuahua album let's go
but yeah I'm working on that behind the
scenes
and
another thing that's been constantly
worked on
behind the scenes is my new OP oh wasn't
that the Phoenix Sun accent that wasn't
right
new outfit
I'm extended
I it's it's in the late stage of being
finished now no no animation yet just
the artwork
um
late stage now
so
maybe if we're lucky end of May
we could have it done
um
I have brought back an incredible
impressive amount of
one diamond
and I have practically achieved
nothing in the Stream
one time
Diamond maybe the real diamonds
was the well let me see the conversation
we made along the way
um
not really
oh
you know where we'll go now
while I read some super chats
I will
go
to base AFK form yeah
yeah cause I'm
I follow my word yeah
I'm a I'm a phoenix of my word if not
anything
no no it's not your conversation skills
it's mine I mean today I mean my
conversation skills never lack never
yeah I mean
nothing special today thanks for the EU
friendly stream uh you're welcome I'm
just sorry that I can't give you guys
anything really exciting today
but no you probably fine you're fine
because
uh 10 P.M
Austrian time
you're getting a karaoke yeah so
what
and that's not too late
the real sad Bros are the sea and Asia
Bros
who for them it will be like four five
six A.M
sorry
foreign
[Music]
when will you rebroadcast
sometime next week uh at like
8 9 10 pm GST or so
you played Minecraft you mind you you
you you you what does it say
you crafted I think it's a success yeah
yeah I guess so which means I finished
Minecraft didn't I I did the things I
think I you should put Minecraft in my
finished games list now
I mined and I crafted
I did the thing that is in the title
I mean yeah wait is Minecraft in the
finished game list anyway because I did
see the credits before
is it is it is it better be
it better be
it is okay okay otherwise I would have
been mad
all right let me put girl Minecraft
aside yeah
I'll just be waiting here
for as long as I can but this is not
there's no roof here right if I stay
here forever
wouldn't I like be attacked by those
flying
thingies
that's kind of dangerous I gotta keep an
eye out
the Phantom so shouldn't there be a bed
up here really
should have brought a bed
I should can I add a roof
because I don't mind like staying here
for hours even when I'm like literally
AFK
[Music]
thank you
okay I'll add a roof
um can I hmm
I'm going to add it on the top line but
I guess we'll add here it doesn't affect
the farm right so
I can remove it afterwards if need be
don't fall into that hole
there we go now I'm protected
hey
remember to torch the roof
top
I might do okay okay can do candle can
do
oh
scary
perfect
[Music]
how many
there you go that's enough right
okay
I'm floating I'm floating I'm falling
yay
Free Falling isn't there a song like
that
[Music]
let's see how many there are now
nine wow nine nine nine nine
very good
all right here we go
now I'm free
all right
if you guys are not sure yet if you want
to go to my karaoke later
telling you you should
I want to sing that song
but
the lyrics worry me but uh I do want to
sing it
[Music]
that one song
oh yeah
uh once again what's it again
I forgot
Best Buy in Ian is the Phoenix obviously
hey
not chicken attack yeah cut my lap into
pieces this is my last resort the
vacation with what was the word
don't give a [\h__\h] if I cut my own what
if I cut myself what what was that
suffocation
is defecation a word
[Laughter]
what wasn't that uh
[Music]
right yeah
excuse me English not my first language
okay here we go no no
we have a streak of sending chickens
away
these days huh
[Music]
okay chat where are you
why are you not here chat owner
I refreshed you
let me
do this
what
Sean are you good over here boss
here here
we're standing right here eh sit down
are you standing why is it not showing
so weird
don't change this
there we go just change to size and
suddenly it works but 10 pixel I just
changed it by 10 pixels
okay
so the other day we finished super chats
from the Fire Emblem last Fire Emblem
stream
[Music]
and today
let's see where we have to continue
thank you guys for watching though if
you guys are leaving and I'm staying for
the Super Chat reading thank you very
much for being here today I'll see you
again soon hopefully
maybe later in the karaoke stream or
maybe tomorrow when we play whatever
well no one
no no no no
[Music]
staying for the tune
what's the bad background music tune
what
um
[Music]
why are thumbnails called thumbnail
to do with the nail on my thumb
oh
I like Angel's boy so I stay thank you
thank you
sometimes
sometimes I wonder if anyone likes my
voice at all but it's nice to hear
there's some
[Music]
I do really
really
you do really thank you
oh thank you
thank you
[Music]
I like your chicken voices too guys
oh thank you just a red string
you
simpleton thank you I agree
[Music]
wow that hurts me
common Bridal
um
okay I will move on ignore that because
pain is nothing to gain from pain
nope
ah Lulu hi Lolo thank you
for the rest of the hotel wow I love you
too
thank you
one guys no no not necessarily
oh well
stop stop it guys
stop
exhale thank you
love you as a person thank you I mean
you know I appreciate when at least
someone doesn't let something like that
stop themselves from watching me that's
nice
okay here we go
Jacob 47
gym choice
driving to Mexico whoa
hello
foreign
have to notify me of username changes
you remember that but your change isn't
even that like misleading I I recognize
you
guys I sent super yeah you did
yeah yeah yeah
uh a blue one
you don't remember
oh you guys don't remember when you do
this
wait I like this one I'm a pamelo which
I guess by the context means your Kyla's
fan you can request a lot of things to
Kyla it just means more Minecraft
streams we love Minecraft don't worry
help us uh
oh
are you guys suffering
too many Minecraft streams
oh
they'll start again
and yet you're watching another another
Minecraft stream from someone else
[Music]
not enough Minecraft it's not a
complaint probably
no I love them
are the little penguins is that the like
Indonesian word for penguin
thank you
Corral Gall no one asked
no
what does it mean then what does that
mean why are you laughing
translate to hammer guy or just try
oh
Indonesian word for penguin is Kyla
[Music]
the mirror out now this is a real album
back to horror I mean family friendly
games today's game is darkest dungeon
do I even need to look this one up it
feels like
it feels like
it's just gonna be
a horror game
oh yeah that is pretty dark it's pretty
dark it's not it's not a horror game it
seems It's a challenging Gothic
roguelike turned based turn-based RPG
about the psychological stresses of
adventuring
no thank you
I must reject
surely this was Mira L as well right
face tangible no
no
it's too dark
it's great but very difficult
you guys should play it not me Mr
casberg
Hotline Miami I'm open to that one
fancy thank you
uh did I say hello
as Sadie versus
I wanna play
um Dark Cloud
play Dark Cloud
but
where how
that's not random it comes from The Dark
One
yeah ah thank you at least there's some
people who know it
it is on PS4 was it always on PS4
because I yeah I played it when it was
on the PS2 probably oh
on PS4
oh oh
is it a remaster
or just a port
[Music]
I had that one
yeah yeah I like remember nothing barely
anything from it but you know it's never
one of those nostalgic things to me
hmm I see I see I see I see it
time to learn the new film system
[Music]
pink bacon United
by the way guys you know what I made
yesterday I was lucky one of my recipes
was indeed a short one
I made a burrito and I made plenty so I
can eat uh after this stream and then
after the karaoke stream as well
yeah burrito this time this time
definitely better burrito than last time
last time uh the burrito that I made
with hello was a chorizo burrito
and it was good but like I made it so
that it was constantly falling apart I
didn't know how to fold it this time I
folded it correctly and this time was
not no chorizo it was um just minced
meat
and the beans
and onions it was supposed to be a quick
recipe so there's like not much more
except salad salad with like a lemon uh
what was that milk buttermilk lemon
dressing or something like that
[Music]
and yeah and and so I put that in and
the the rest yeah was just that
um
no cheese actually interesting
just realized there was no cheese
oh because it wasn't part of the recipe
it was fine the way it was though it was
really yummy surprised that you don't
think chorizer is too spicy for you I
probably had like a not so spicy one
surely there's more spicy ones mine
didn't really seem very spicy
you put so many food tweets on Twitter
maybe you should consider making a
cookbook of all the foods you make as
birthday merch yeah but no I see
sometimes people suggesting that but
all my recipes are from hello
so they're not my own recipes I can't
just take the recipes and put them in my
birthday merch
I can't do that
yeah I would sue me
now I have to try every kind of tacos
yeah I never had actual tacos before I
think
still
but yeah burrito was really good I was
really happy I had that yesterday
gonna eat the rest today
probably gonna finish
and then yeah tomorrow I gotta cook
again
no I mean surely you can't have
copyright on food recipes but if I put
like 50 hello fresh recipes in in one
book
salad as my own merch I mean I think add
one oh add one ingredient recipe in line
nah come on that would be so shitty
nah I can't do that no no no I already
know what I'm doing for for um birthday
merchandise
actually
about Anniversary merchandise though
and I think I also know at least one
item
and I I would love to spoil but maybe I
shouldn't spoil everything so yeah
you're allowed solo anniversary
emergency yeah I asked for it I I said
last year I already said hey can we have
link solo merchandise maybe next year or
least
um
maybe maybe that will be like at least
one group item as well who knows but
we're also having uh solos um
they're gonna be a little bit close
together though because birthday is on
July
and anniversary is September but I'm
gonna make it stuff that's worth it to
get oh and on the other side I actually
uh turned down the opportunity
to make merchandise for my new outfit
seemingly it has become a trend recently
with Cali and Ina doing it and some
others too probably
and I thought about it and I thought no
I I could but I said no I don't wanna
because first of all I can't really
think of anything that has to do with
the outfits that would work as
merchandise besides an acryl stand it
was a little bit considering it because
it would be cool with this kind of
outfit I think but I thought like why
I I don't want to like
you know I know there's some fans who
like just will buy anything and I I
appreciate the support but I don't want
to make you guys feel like you need to
buy it let's save the money I said
instead
um they tell me how you don't have to
make merchandise for your new outfit uh
there's like if I don't do this then I
can have something else instead like for
example I could do another whole talk
Anniversary merchandise or I could do
Thanksgiving or something like that you
know
I can do something else instead and I
feel like then if it's for something
else I'll probably feel more inspired
and motivated to do something than
forcefully making something for my
um
for my new outfit yeah
yeah
whole talk Max would feel fitting I did
that last year
yeah
maybe I can do a resale of my last year
who'll talk merchandise for the next
anniversary hmm
oh yeah I just felt like it's not
necessary and I don't I don't need to
Overkill with
merchandise right yeah I'd love a new
backpack oh
really you guys want backpacks
a Carefree backpack
maybe for anniversary then
but you'd probably wanted to not look
like too obvious
like with my face all over it right I
could I could make it
a little bit more decent looking
yeah subtle looking
backpack not sure if it would be good
quality though I can't promise like
insane
quality like a like a Gucci bag
it's just a logo and an inside like a
cute Kotori pattern lining
yeah
should we have a bright orange though
probably not
there's already so much bright orange
maybe maybe it's just the logo and then
the main color could be black
yeah and then with some orange accents
like the zippers could be orange
and yeah
the inside would be just a turquoise
Kotori lining
[Music]
or maybe I wonder if there could be two
options
color options I wonder if they would do
that
[Music]
I'm actually down with that
a black is just a easy
easy
okay I finished reading these I think
did I I finished with I am a chi right
ayamati I am
okay next
is
passport
this one
did you finish every last time yes I did
yeah now you make me doubt myself but I
think I'm pretty sure I did
wait wait wait wait I I was actually
asked
they were like Chihuahua answer us
please please tell us what you want for
Anniversary merchandise tell us
I should write it down really quickly
anniversary merch there we go
okay okay
uh number one
um
I want I won't say what that one was the
second one is
um
uh
rucksack hook sack
in did you know in Japanese the word for
backpack they use the German word as a
base they say they don't say ryukusaku
but they say which is from ruksak
it's interesting sometimes they go for
German words rather than English words
to to borrow them not understand is
different is like a specific type of you
know for the
elementary elementary school students
it's a very specific one specific shape
like yeah too
um
we say it looks like in the UK really we
use the word really
why
really
uh kfp design a simple design backpack
and I can do one more
Ayah I should I should have one thing
that has like an illustration as a key
visual
so you know like the like the blankets
that had the key visual all over it
what should the BAM
[Music]
no thank you
a tower
I'm doing that for my birthday
um
you're doing a towel for my birthday
uh oh battery power bank oh interesting
well normally I like to have like an
overall theme you know so like you know
previously it was like cozy at home and
kitchen stuff and all that but this
doesn't really seem to have a theme
we could have something that makes sense
with the backpack
um
something that makes sense with the
backpack and has a big illustration on
it
um
I mean it doesn't have to be a big item
though
wallet
a water bottle I have a bottle for my
pretty
phone cover but phone cover are not
Universal umbrella is probably not
allowed
laptop sleeve I like the idea but not
everyone would like be able to use it
[Music]
pencil box pencil box cute
kfb notebook
oh I like that too but just the cover is
the is the illustration and the inside
is like
just normal Pages maybe with a little
Kotori on the edges or so
a planner yeah even a note uh book or
like a
one of those planner thingies
with like a little calendar inside as
well or so
just a small one
I guess it could be good
for illustration
one maybe
a notebook planner
okay
Maybe
and maybe we can make it a set with a
pen I feel like they would allow me to
do that with a pen as a set because I
want to make a pen because I've been
looking at this this susama pen that I
have and and it has like you know a
floaty thing is inside the pen
it's like a chair you know the chair
inside and it moves if you tilt the the
pen
yeah
and there's like some sparkly stuff
inside as well that moves around too
finally we can take actual notes when we
need to remind you of something
[Music]
the chair
and the cat the cat also like it's like
the the in the pan it's like on the left
side is the cat on the right side is the
the chair and if you move it around it
looks like the chair is chasing the cat
hmm smart so we could have little kfb
chickens in the pan Maybe
um moving around wouldn't that be cute
and some eggs
eggs and chickens that'll be cute
I watched suzuma yeah yeah I did in like
January with uh coyote and Canada senpai
we went to see the movie there because I
wasn't sure when I would ever be able to
watch it and I was really curious
hmm
the idea of a set of notebook with a pen
all right super chats Turkish monkey
shouldn't take a 47
metric sauce
Ben Ben madly thank you oh thanks and
welcome with me to my first review I had
to answer the call for more European kfp
love from the UK again yo
wait are you answering you know are you
from are you from neuro
are you here now Ben
if that was your first student you could
have come from neuro
I wonder you're probably not here now
you better come again that better not
have been your first and last stream
I need more European viewers please yeah
you know they're always welcome
but you said UK
yeah so what
so what
[Music]
oh
a bit too early for him I had to
probably yeah yeah
well if you're watching the VOD thank
you very much for joining kfp hmm
are you at work though oh thank you
hello how's work doing
how's work
you can't represent hello you're
reporting in hello
girls yeah I saw I saw the poll already
in the beginning of the stream that you
guys were very present even though it's
a weekday
thank you for being here
work is good because while I is here
love love love love
uh love you thank you soon
Apex
up X anina for the red super chat hi
this is my first time watching Kiana's
live streaming not a clip video I feel
great to finally be able to send Super
Chat thank you for always telling me
interesting shows
[Music]
yeah
thank you so much I'm glad you were able
to watch the stream for once probably
not here now I assume but thank you
nonetheless
I appreciate it very much
what's your first language German
I hope to see you again
[Music]
kfp I have been absent in recent times
however last week I've been thrown into
the usual room for the first time in a
long time I noticed kfp is not as
rebellious as they used to be what they
tend to do to you guys in my absence is
Carefree brainwashed
well you're asking them
what they did in your absence the real
question is what did you do in your
absence
that's the first question you will need
to answer before asking any questions
here at all
what did you do
where are you
bellstar
um
I don't see you here to answer my
question
sauce
[Music]
oh
hold a talk with downstar
not quite whole talk yet
don't move her vision is based on
movement no it's not
cool
rights of free donation
oh
[Music]
not interesting yeah looking for the top
thank you soon
um
if we're telling them would you like to
swap outfits like you wear hers and she
wears yours
hard mode besides Cali
only swapping outfits that means that it
would have to like fit my hair color and
all that
and
Why didn't
Senpai probably would work with my hair
color
any of her outfits really but I would
probably go for
the hey
the one with the zipper
oh yeah and I do love like mummy's
casual
and
I would like to see myself in crony's
casual as well and and all of Amy's
outfits I want to try her kimono I think
color wise it would fit really well
because she has like this yellow with
some orange in it
and I love Amy's fancy outfit and casual
outfit I love them all
just have to make them fit to my body if
you just put my head on top of her
proportion wise it's not gonna look so
good I think but
[Music]
the fish on my head
uh I love that gimmick so much
yeah I'm so short
I want a cool or Korean pop star Kia
outfit a cool or Korean pop star hmm
foreign
outfits are usually always so intricate
like this one's the new one's pretty
simple in theory
did you see the cool illustration on her
t-shirt I'm on it too
hey Mama Told
me selling the T-shirt as merchandise
for her new outfit merchandise
or is she selling her
slippers oh so
[Music]
she didn't say
she will she hinted at it oh why is it
not
right when she shows the that's weird
okay
she heavily implied okay
cool
that's a nice t-shirt I would want that
if it was the T-shirt
it could be the the slippers too though
because she has cute slippers too and
then it would be Cali slippers me
slipper uh you know slippers I did not I
did slippers before then there's almost
all miff slippers
just need Amber to sell some slippers
I'm gouda to sell some slippers
[Music]
okay let's go uh where was I
um Brandon thanks for the pinky ethical
dilemma both cats are meowing for you to
come play with them but ah I think I
read this one but they're in separate
rooms when they're watching so they will
know if you choose the other cat what do
you do and I think I said John Chris
because chunkers gets jealous I think a
little bit or mine she doesn't really
show it but I feel like she she's sad
yeah
Jacob 47 Alexander
thank you
and darling dream of Duncan looking for
the top donation
big wait darling dreamer asks for big
twin turkey Wawa please I already did
twin tails for my kimono I really like
the kimono hair maybe I could like ask
to have it implemented in another outfit
in the future
but when I when you ask something like
that it always takes so much time and
blah blah if I were to put the twin
Tails onto another outfit which one
would you guys like to see it with which
one would you think it would fit
because I only have so much extra stuff
for this casual one so maybe it
shouldn't be this one
but
um
I would say they're not necessarily fits
any nah maybe maybe the dandel I guess
default I can't add it to default
not really allowed
[Music]
twin Tails let's go yeah maybe deandel
but I feel like style wise it doesn't
quite fit with the dandel
these braids that I have
would work with the dandel actually
and all the Twin Towers I love them but
like style wise
they don't match with the fancy dress I
would say
and with my new one that you don't know
yet
Maybe
I'm not sure
I'm not sure about that I would have to
see it to judge it
too bad I need oh
I need to whatever I do for my next
outfit I need to do something that fits
with the twin tails
and I think if I do the favorite night
thing I think the twin Tails would fit
with it
everything that could work
yeah hey
hey
right yeah yeah
a great great
yes yes yes
[Music]
public comment on that nice oh
ah because you want to talk about it but
it was Members Only
I guess out
I'll do that for my next next outfit
but don't worry it will take forever I
want to do a fever night inspired outfit
spoiler alert
spoilering is really hard just because I
needed your guys's opinion to decide
we have so many outfits at this point
that
I feel like I have to really think it
through when I decide another one
[Music]
Mama Looney winning
I would yeah I would probably just send
all the mamaloni art as a reference to
hookah Papa and ask him to draw
something like that
FIFA night almost at 1 million views it
has been like that for a while
thank you guys for trying
listen to favorite night after this will
you
and we get to 1 million
uh where was I
um
uh I think oh yeah looking for the top
thanks
Mr Ken's big stand kitchen and Ben Matt
madeley medley thank you thank you again
oh he says he's now a loyal kid of being
employed really oh then why are you not
here just kidding just kidding
simply thanks for the pinky your art is
so much better than you give it credit
for your Cali painting looks absolutely
amazing you might think that your style
is too old but retro is so in right now
thank you for the stream it looks great
yeah but that's like different you know
me also wanting to do fever and I like
what is it 70s 80s workout attire
um for an outfit yeah okay that's
because it's [\h__\h] cute but that old
is different from my art style old I
think in my opinion
oh well
it is is that 80s
your artist is cute okay chill too
I don't want to be 90s dojo
whatever whatever whatever don't even
let's not even get into it
uh by the way the other day I after we
did the fifth simulator I couldn't hold
myself back I I had so much fun with it
that I continued to play a little bit
afterwards
I just went back to those houses and I
did a couple of
requests of destroying things
I didn't want to like do too much but I
played a little bit without you yeah I
just had so much fun with fifth
simulator you just do it why because I
had just ended the Stream
and I don't know
just wanted to play a bit more
a little bit more
promise the story with Vinnie uh no I
don't think so
not really
um
playing it tomorrow yeah probably I
think I'm feeling Thief Simulator more
for tomorrow than passport two probably
still on deciding it though
oh anyway
from appreciate your your sweet words
very much I still want to improve my art
style don't change it
but I'm glad you like it Flappy boy
thank you for the red super chat and
your art no wait not that I knew
anything about drawing but I'm
fascinated by your process this has
probably been explained already in the
past before I joined care of people did
you receive formal training well I am
more of an auto Didact deduct what why
didn't you pursue drawing further okay
okay here we go again uh story time
now I was
always very much into art since I was a
child because my mom was also into art
and she gave me like supplies and stuff
and I got like a cheap tiny drawing
tablet very early on as well
um
and yeah so I did digital art and and
non-digital art traditional art from
very early days and my mom always like
was very supportive of it and
um so in when it came to school
I actually like
in
June or hi first I was also hoping to
focus on languages so I tried to get
into
no wait first no I went into I went to a
language school for like one or two
years or so but then Latin was [\h__\h]
me over so I left that school
and changed to a normal one but then
eventually so I demoted Myself by going
to a shitty school after that but then I
promoted myself again with my hard work
and my skills and abilities because I
signed up for art school for high school
and
um yeah I had to do like a like a test
like a uh basically audition
for the school and not yo like back then
when you get into that school
it's like a huge thing like getting into
that school is like only the cool and
and skilled people get into that school
that was the reputation it was like
in my city this school had like the best
reputation especially like the specific
um
branch that I got into and wanted to get
into
um
because it also had like different
branches like technical branches
which weren't that
I feel like the artistic one was more
pretty more you know impressive but they
were all very cool the school in general
was really cool because it was also
really modern you know it was a cool
school you don't just get in there in
Austria generally there's no school fees
um there's I think I have never heard of
a private school here before but they
probably exist but they nobody goes
there I guess because you don't need
that we don't need it we have cool
schools where you don't have to pay for
it but this one at least you don't have
to pay to get into it but you have to be
you know skilled to get into it which if
you think about it is better anyway
it's not paid to win it's just
be good to win
so
yeah
um I got in and I remember my excitement
because for junior high school before
going to the language school I first
attempted to get into
what kind of school was that it was
another special school where you had to
audition
and they would look if you are valuable
enough good enough to join the school
um
it was a gymnasium that goes through
Junior High to high school both of it
um because we have both like some only
go to end of junior high and some are
until the end for eight years but this
one was I think kind of music focused I
think it was a music school
and I really wanted to go there because
even though I never had the
chance to play anything besides the
basic flute that you learn in elementary
um because we just didn't have the money
in my family to get me any other
instruments or lessons for it for that
matter yeah recorder gang which really
is nothing to flex about
so basically I think they only took
people who already
had some instrument
skill
that's not recorder
at least [\h__\h] Guitar Man
but I didn't even have that
that was probably my downfall
I felt very
um very
what's the word I just
looking at what the other
um contestants had to offer I felt very
outskilled
uh yeah but I was hoping that I could
learn an instrument at this music school
but no I was inferior so I was rejected
by that and I remember like I was so
devastated when I got my rejection my
mom was with me and I I was crying
I felt not good enough yeah
into a different pretty good school that
that language school was also very very
what Prestige had a good good reputation
to
but then I failed with Latin [\h__\h]
Latin
after
one and a half years or so so in the
middle of the year I changed school and
when you do it like in the middle of the
Year there were just not many options
so I had to go to a pretty shitty School
where I was like like even more of an
outsider than ever
oh I hated it but
at least I had like two friends or so I
think even though I was like the weird
one
and the nerdy one
I think they had like
the the other students had even though
they didn't really like me because I
wasn't one of the cool ones in their
opinion
I think maybe I was like respected
nonetheless a little bit
in a weird way
um
and then and then
because they you know always treated me
so like an outsider I felt even prouder
when
you know at the end where everybody was
like uh like trying to find a job and
most of them most of them instead of
going to high school went on to get a
job like
you know one of those like training
thingies
it's pretty common in Austria you then
you don't go to high school and just do
that instead because you will also end
up getting like some kind of certificate
at the end
apprenticeship yeah
and then you know at the end of the year
you know they're like all right let's
see where you guys are all going and I
eventually I get my acceptance letter
from this super cool art school and I
flexed it and I felt like
they were all like yo damn damn this
girl she's going to this like super cool
awesome school that everybody knows
hey
yeah I may have been
like d demoted once from good school to
bad school but then I promoted myself to
go to a really cool school again
now it's amazing for a while but
unfortunately
uh I would say the art school didn't
really help me much with my personal art
goals
because I was hoping to draw like anime
style stuff I was always just doodling
that in between the things that we were
actually supposed to do
but then unfortunately in art school art
isn't all that matters and
after like two years or so math
it was always [\h__\h] me over but it
really [\h__\h] me over at that point and
I couldn't
I couldn't go to that school anymore
but at the same time I had this offer to
go to Japan so I went to Japan instead
and that was like such a risky thing
and my mom also
wasn't sure what to make of it and what
would come out of it but I was like well
what do I have to lose
what do I have to lose at this point
like man I I can't continue going to my
dream School
[\h__\h] sucks I feel like a failure
so let's go to Japan I went to Japan I
did my thing there for a while
and then that all fell apart eventually
after two or three years or so
I'm telling my life story now that fell
apart unfortunately not really my fault
though and so I had to go back to
Austria I was [\h__\h] depressed
and I had nothing I had no home I had no
friends I had no job I had no school I
had nothing I had no money I had no
furniture nothing
and I had to build everything up from
zero
got myself a shitty apartment really
quickly got myself an apprenticeship
really fast
in in the hotel
they accepted me immediately because of
my
language skills at least
that was the lowest point yeah
one of the lowest points in my life
but I worked myself back up and I did
this shitty apprenticeship where you
earned basically nothing
for three years
lived in my own apartment
and yeah worked really hard to
make a living
without much support you know or from no
support no financial support from
anything only the things that I did gave
me financial support yeah and then and
then
I was still I was still under 20 I'm
still under 20 now but but yeah I was
under 20.
hmm
and other dad and I finished the
apprenticeship and then then I said [\h__\h]
this city I'm out of here then I moved I
continued to work a little bit long in
between that was actually after I
finished the apprenticeship that's when
I I think that's when I
um that's when I auditioned for uh
Lufthansa got accepted by Lufthansa
thought that this was finally me
promoting myself again in life starting
this cool new chapter moving to Germany
already found an apartment I think and
was gonna start working in Germany for
Lufthansa as a flight attendant
and then shortly before my training
would start
I got the result from my health
uh check and
told I failed
yeah and then I was like well [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay I guess whatever [\h__\h] it
sad I really liked the idea of doing
that but okay
who knows maybe I dodged a bullet
because
um I know that flight attendants the
turnover rate is really high because
it's
um it's very challenging very hard on
your body not even saying I dodged a
bullet because of the sea thing just
because that still was a couple years
before that
but
you know
just generally like health-wise it's not
a good job and and it's really [\h__\h]
toxic the work environment is super
toxic from what I hear
from many other flight attendants
terrible it's horrible
but it would have still been cool to
have the experience at least for a while
you know it would have been cool because
I saw it as a chance to go back to Japan
every once in a while uh
oh also I said okay I guess I'll
continue working in a hotel and then I I
you know I moved City and I started from
scratch again I had to live with a
roommate for many years because first of
a really shitty roommate then with a
nice roommate
because I had to save money didn't earn
much didn't want to go full time because
I still wanted to do other things so I
did only part-time while while still
doing other things
did that for a while was quite fun
and then I was like I saw and then I saw
oh oh
Japan now has working holiday not
anymore for six months for austrians but
no finally they also have a contract for
one year and I was like this is my
chance working holiday you cannot do
forever you only until a certain age
you're allowed to do a working holiday
once in a lifetime so I was like you
know what I'll do it now I'll do it now
because I'm sick of this boring life
anyway
and now I'll take this chance to go to
Japan for for 12 months
because there's so many things I still
wanted to do in Japan last time I lived
there
that I couldn't accomplish and I felt
like it always I always left this book
open in the middle of a chapter and I
finished I didn't finish writing it and
I wanted to finish writing it even if I
changed Direction a little bit still
doesn't matter I need to finish this
book of my life
so I said [\h__\h] it I'm going I left
everything behind again
including my cats
went to Japan
and the moment I arrived in Japan the
sea thing hit Japan
thus
ruining my once in a lifetime chance
of finishing this chapter and
hindering all of my opportunities and
things that I wanted to do in Japan
during that time
this was another really low point I got
really
depressed again spent all day in bed in
in the dark in my tiny ass one room
apartment
in Japan watching pekora senpai and then
whole life came by and I audition for
all alive
and and I made it and I mean that is
totally also not the direction I wanted
to take originally that I was hoping for
but definitely changed my life for the
better
um
and now we're here
back in Austria but very happy about
being in Austria content
yeah
so that's my life story I don't know why
we did this whole life story somebody
just asked about my background of Art
um
orange and starry
in a compact form there you go
[Music]
big Lord dump
yeah because context exactly
can you repeat it at all you better
watch the bot if you just came in and
want to hear the whole story you better
watch the [\h__\h] VOD
oh
yeah this made me cry so moving really
well I didn't try to make it sound
emotional but yeah I I've been through
many ups and downs in my life many times
where I felt like you know I wasn't
worth [\h__\h] and I would never accomplish
anything
because again and again no matter how
hard I tried
I always put the most into it but no
matter what
things just wouldn't go the way I wanted
it to I was hoping it would
but everyone's in a while life would
throw me like a little piece of Hope
again like a cool school that I could go
to but then I would fail it again you
know
and okay well next thing let's start
working at Lufthansa okay okay okay
heads up I'm like excited for that oh no
can't do it after all okay okay let's
let's go to live whatever let's just not
think about let's go to a different city
and start life from the scratch again
okay okay here comes Japan my once in a
lifetime chance of a wrecking holiday
let's go let's go let's go
I'm Gonna Leave live the life that I
wanted to live
and then let's see thing
uh so many and then the first time I
lived in Japan also like I worked so
[\h__\h] hard but uh it was destroyed by
things that are out of my power
so
man I wouldn't know what to do if I were
you to be honest boss
yeah I like to say that I'm really good
at like standing up again once something
got me down but I I'm not gonna lie like
at that point in my working holiday stay
in Japan
I I lost hope
and I lost confidence in me being able
to get up again
I thought it was over like there was no
light at the end of the tunnel
it was just everything was negative
everything was depressing everything was
[\h__\h]
uh
I'm so glad I tried to audition for
whole life
I could have just been pessimistic and
say nah I'm not gonna make it anyway and
not even try and I did because one thing
I know is when I auditioned for
something I usually make it even if it
seems pretty unlikely I mean the music
school was just because I didn't play an
instrument and okay I mean you know but
I managed to get into art school I
managed to get into Lufthansa I managed
to get into many other things that
seemed highly unlikely
yeah
um
never had trouble finding a job you know
quickly got my apprenticeship faster
than anything
Eurovision next ah
Eurovision
is the one thing that ruins my
my success rate
yeah but gotta keep keep on moving
forward exactly
so I hope you guys can now that I've
repeated my life story
even if you knew it already I hope that
can motivate you guys
um
foreign
[Music]
I just failed my life chance test so
it's very inspiring oh
there might be a difference
life chance test equal to it that you
maybe don't consider
like me I didn't when I was just
watching pekoras Empire I didn't
consider really that you know I would
make this my main job
but but now this is what I've been doing
for two and a half years and it's been
it's been life-changing
thank you long time no see thank you
hey
yeah
man
maybe maybe
all the ups and downs you know they're
they were all necessary to eventually
lead to this moment you know
to Japan for the first time I already
spoke pretty good Japanese so I I
couldn't necessarily say that I wouldn't
have picked up that skill
if it wasn't for me failing Art School
or leaving art school but if I wouldn't
have left art school and finished it
properly
yeah yeah things would have been very
different I think
um
still had an interest in Japan and so on
and so eventually maybe I would have
tried to do the working holiday
nonetheless
[Music]
but with different a different drive to
it I think
um
don't make that stupid joke
do you think you'd be an art hipster no
I feel like if I would have finished
that art school to be honest
I might as well just finished any kind
of normal high school because
I feel like it wouldn't have really
helped me much in life
it's being specifically art related
I was like what can you even do with
that
what can you do like digital art and all
of that like the thing that I wanted to
be you can do that completely unrelated
to going to an art school you don't need
that you just need to be good at your
craft
you know
like get as good as Ina or so and then
it should work out because and and all
of that really is just practice you
don't need to go to the art school
you just need to
try really hard for a long time
to to get a certain
um to make a name for yourself as an
artist which is difficult yes but the
art school won't help you with that
how yeah right how what no there's no
how to it no if you want to get good at
Art you just draw every day that's it
um
anyway now
just do it no art art is the one thing
where one of the few things in life
where you really don't need a talent you
can create your talent a talent would
maybe help if you have a natural talent
for it but honestly it's really just a
bad practice so
practice and then you have the skill and
then you what you really need then maybe
is a little bit of luck to get a name
for yourself to get out there and then
to get the good jobs
that you want
um
so that's what I wanted to do and could
have done
but yeah
kind of like that with music yeah
I suppose so
more or less yeah
a lot more more luck necessary with
music than
with art I think
[Music]
I think there's like a million musicians
and bands out there that make really
good music and will never make as much
money from it as like I know Beyonce or
so
or Paramore or whoever
never just because they don't get the
chance for it
um
feeling okay after that walk from Emily
Lane yeah yeah I'm fine I'm you know as
I said just during the Minecraft stream
too I'm feeling pretty content content
right now
[Music]
I'm okay I'm okay I mean there's there's
constantly also some
negative things in my life
negative influences
but
um
this this time we spent together makes
up for it mm-hmm
and so generally it's overpowering it
and I feel
I feel good right now
[Music]
stop being sappy and all that but God's
sake
uh
we we dig so deep
deep deep talk we would dig it so deep
that we almost fell into lava guys
but still no diamonds
maybe the diamonds is the tears that we
cried along the way they're just as
sparkly
ah
whereas minus five thousands
yeah I am
frog on toast
um
plans no ideas yes
[Music]
we hit bedrock
let's stop digging now
where was I anyway
I have Flappy boys
thank you for the red super chat mwah
let's leave it at that shall we miss
visit
[Music]
Super Snake Mario dance
Flappy boy here
laughs
oopsie I tangented too much
waiting for that kiss forever he fell
asleep
by the end of my story
[Music]
asks for art background gets life story
instead well I mean
I mean the context
since I'm getting a lot of complaints
about a lot of chickens pooping
everywhere and our entire need of
diapers help there you go
there you go see here's someone with
with older sanity to themselves
[Music]
I don't know what to do they don't
really agree with me
they don't they're really really
rebellious about the diaper I'm sorry
Poncho we'll have to teach them just how
to go to the toilet normally
[Music]
yeah let's teach him in the usual room
I think that will help
you need excuse me lunch box why do I
laughs
if you really think it's the solution
I'll wear one but are you actually okay
with changing all of our diapers all the
time
[Music]
for some chickens their job will be
diaper Changers you know
surely someone will do it
[Music]
that this one's over took longer than it
needed to be because I am tangent Queen
[Music]
here's my marvelous thumbnail
for the Widow fight
a hit
let's go Joe
Jacob Duncan
Stratus fighting for the pinky intention
is my birthday tomorrow and this is my
second year sending a birthday superchat
oh
oh thank you just want to thank you for
always being amazing I'm happy to call
you one of my Aussies
one of them huh okay
I wish for uh all I wish was hopefully
you can maybe sing me Happy Birthday
I will
[Music]
hey happy birthday to you
happy birthday to your shoes
[Music]
it's your second birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday in your shoes
[Music]
[Applause]
cause I'm a phoenix
[Music]
so what we learn from that
is that there is one another one
or see that you should have and that is
yeah happy birthday
Strat is fun
are you here stratisfy while you're
watching someone else's dream huh
I mean I think the best argument really
is that I am a phoenix I'll be I can I
can be there forever for you
so your other oceans are they
Eternal like me hmm if they are okay
I'll think of another argument but at
the moment I'm feeling pretty confident
about that one
so you know you don't seem to be here
but I help you pick this one up in the
VOD
thank you so much
[Music]
literally half of myth is Immortal yeah
but who knows who knows who your ooshies
are satisfy who knows I don't know
you're not telling me
you're welcome to tell me though
they might just be gone this is two or
three days later just kidding uh Sammy
but or same budget
a hole anole
[Music]
what I understood they might just be
going on a vacation or something I don't
know
Bob Duncan them
you know I was almost worried because I
was late but then I remember who these
girls are I got here almost like 40
minutes late still haven't started
yeah still preparing but
you should be thankful because if we
were already completely prepared by the
start of the stream then the stream
would have been five minutes long
because then we would have slayed the
river immediately
and then that's it
so it was good that there was a lot of
preparation
hmm
[Music]
yeah
on time if that is true we even started
on time
Jacob 47.00
and Jacob thanks for the pinky
I like how before Jacob's Super Chat is
cyrex saying River you will whoever
whoever you already or not here it comes
that's before the fight at 1 hour 20 and
at one hour 23
Jacob sends a Super Chat saying
congratulations
[Music]
so anti-climatic man
thanks Jacob
maybe another cold thanks for the pinky
too good job now find the Bedrock
version of the Wither if you want a
challenge oh
is it very different
Bedrock version
how is it well how is it different
[Music]
Java is much different than the weather
in Bedrock more harder why
does he just have more HP or
it spawns Weber skeletons to help it and
why does it why why is Java often so
different
why did I do that just make it the same
it's weird
thank you
more experience summons and that would
have been way more interesting
I would have been fine for me
fine in my book
[Music]
Java was the OG version
oh Bedrock is the one that is really
different oh so they saw the Java with
her and they were like well that's [\h__\h]
let's make it more difficult okay I
appreciate that but
I will not play Bedrock just for that
um
we should have different stages to the
fight yeah it would be cool if the
weather changes up and gets like bigger
and more heads or whatever
[Music]
more scary
maybe easier for children for Java
I feel like more children would play
Bedrock for some reason
of this image that they do
[Music]
oh it doesn't work with mods
or privateers oh really
um sorry thank you for the pinky most
epic battle I've ever seen especially a
fight with the whole truly glorious
yeah I was like panicking for a moment
when I fell into somewhere because I
thought it was important no I was more
panicking because at that point I saw oh
he's going down fast and I wanted to do
some more damage before he dies while
I'm stuck in the hole
yeah
um
I was really I don't know if you can say
it was 10 out of 10 cyric you you are
very ironic in that one aren't you
thank God Ena pulled Acro yeah I'm
surprised she survived so long did he
never like hit her properly
how did she survive so long it was
constantly aggroating on a
huh
[Music]
she kept eating the carrots damn but
like when you eat you get slower and all
that so she still managed to run away so
well good job
oh without that
if somebody else would have accidentally
aggroaded like me
I don't know if it would have gone so
well
because I was panicking about eating the
carrots when I tried thank God it wasn't
necessary most of the time
uh
yeah
[Music]
Dodge buff
Excel region the whole time
anyway anyway anyway uh the Diamond
Double Jones
and
amancy
that's it
[Music]
so now it's five hours I think I'll take
a break now eat something
and then
um practice some songs I also gotta do
my a couple of
deadline recordings
I'll do that before I eat I think no I
guess
it's already past midnight in Japan I
think so I should do it now
[Music]
okay thank you guys for watching I'll
see you later in the car okay
uh you're welcome to send me suggestions
I guess on Twitter I'm already doing my
best to learn songs
uh the Korean ones so I don't promise I
can like learn a lot of new songs
English ones but no
feel free to send me recommendations for
songs that you think I know maybe
okay
there is no karaoke waiting room yet
that's another thing I have to do
it's in five hours
so see you then in the German Wednesday
I'll feed us then thank you for watching
[Music]
um
oh
thank you for 20 memberships
alrighty are there even 29 members in
here huh
you guys are getting access to the
wonderful upcoming members only
wallpaper it's gonna be
hmm so good
keep an eye open for that first of May
bye bye
[Music]
see you later
thank you
foreign
[Music]