Take it and
fry it instead and you'll get it when you're done carving it.
Use a lot of khasi cloth. It's
more than a [ __ ].
Wherever I see my face, I feel sorry for using Mor Tot's color.
Even if I get a Lotus, I'll be able to pass on the next one.
I'm sorry,
why don't you scold me?
We had a good time and we were far away, and we loved each other so much.   I
only understand.
[Song]
Ah it
has rules. Even if you look at Maejo, Maejo, Mae, I do
n't want to. [Song] You can look at sports uniforms. If you're already here, give me this. [Song] I'm a person who plays with my heart, I shouldn't.  Remember that apart from you, my
heart is still there or not.   The
eyes can only
see that
[the song] has
n't reached home yet.
What will be the development? Let's know.
Your heart came, so I really got it.
[Song]
Note