[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Sorry to have kept you
waiting, you can hear me. Kaoisho,
wait a minute. Let me
show you a glimpse of BGMBGM in action. I'm out over there
today.  It's a collaboration.
Today, we're going to study German,
so a
first-time
German teacher will be on Channel 7. He's
cute. He's so cute even when he doesn't make noises. He's
moving in a cute way, but it's a little weird.  Let me have you
come right away. Please wait a moment. Please
wait a moment. Change the background music to this.
Okay, then please come out.
Please introduce yourself. Takanashi, I'm
Kiyohara-sensei. Lie. I'm your teacher today. Hololive
English 1.  This
is an unnecessary Takanashi character from the new generation, but he
is English, but his native language is actually German, and he
lives in Austria.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you.  I'd
like to learn German from my teacher.
Even though it's my mother tongue, I'm not very good at Japanese. I
'm always told, "Thank you."
But the truth is, I'm having fewer and fewer opportunities to speak Japanese, and I've
been living in other parts of Japan,
but I'm
going back to Austria.  I haven't
really had a chance to talk since then,
so if I don't talk for a while, it's worth it.Also, I
tend to forget words, but
thank you very much.
But that Chiara seems to have a really loud volume.
There are some comments in English.
Thank you.
What do you think about overseas diary th?
[Music]
When I'm streaming, there are usually
quite a few overseas diaries.
Overseas, the number of overseas diaries is increasing, and
sometimes they say English.  I spoke a little bit of
Spanish, and I was learning Spanish,
so if I spoke a little bit of Spanish, people
would come to visit me and go to Spain.  I'd
like to hear you speak Please introduce yourself If you
come suddenly I can
understand your bad English,
so Hello Konkagura Good day Yes, firstMyselfto
English
I'M7
IcametoasFROMTHE
PLANETChiliPepper
youwalk
I's illustrator artist
for
dese naki ni Ayame Hololive
say
Nakigamizuki from Prism  Project When I
listen to other Japanese people introduce themselves in English, they
only say 3 lines.  I
feel like I've memorized it, but the teacher
seems to be able to get away with it,
and I can understand a little bit of what I'm saying,
so I don't know
why, but my university was in the English department, the
English department, the
foreign language department,
so yeah, German.  I've never done it before,
so I'm really excited today.
[Laughs] I'm
not as good as the English members,
but I'm a lot better than the Japanese members of Hololive. That's amazing. That
's seriously something.  When
people overseas say a little Japanese to a Japanese person, people
always say, ``
You're so good at Japanese,'' it's become a meme.  She
says she's
good at English, but she's really good at English, Chiara
-chan, and she's also good at Japanese.It's not like she's good at it,
but she's really good at it.I'm
really
happy.She's also good at German.  I'll
study a little today so I can talk.  I'd
like to go there
for just an hour, but it's
difficult, but if I take a screenshot of what I'm going to teach today and look at it
a few
times, I'll see if I
can remember it.I'll
keep an archive of what I'm trying to do, so let's look back and
study and do our
best.Thank you in advance.  Please, why are you
studying German today
? That's right. Well, that's not this.
Thank you. Can you explain it in Japanese first?
I'll see you next week, etc., somewhere in 2023.
Okay, it's a 3-day event, and we'll
be out for about 2 and a half days.
Wait, wait, wait, 3 days. That's probably it. It's been
3 days since this year. It's
been 2 days already. 6 people
are
FREEDtoday
ISS.
Where are they?  It's a
huge and popular event.It's
really popular, but I didn't really start it.I
always
said I wanted it to be at least 3 days,
but I always thought 2 days was too
short, but this year.
Intertwined-
chan's wish has come true, but it won't be this year.Next
time,
the information I didn't know
is actually coming out here.The
name of the circle is Stellatia.Comic
Market 101 It was
released at Comiket last winter.  I'm thinking of bringing a full-
color 60-page illustrated book and new
Kagura merchandise.To
be honest, Kaigan Nikki
is in the chat, but probably most of the people.  I
can't speak German.
Can you tell me this in English? I can do it in English, too.
Please.
Heisactorygoingto
japany
andto
your
andre.Actually,
Tiara has been appearing for two years in a row.  All of our
fans were
thinking, ``Maybe it's going to be there,'' and thanks to that, we said, ``Of course,
we'll go this year as well.''
There are quite a few people like that, so even though I'm not there,
there's a good chance that some of my fans will come as well.However,
I haven't had the chance to meet them overseas either,
so I
'd be happy if I could meet them this time.
Well, I'm going to take the trouble to meet the
person who I want to meet as an illustrator, because I'm still a mother of that Hololive machine.
Let's meet in Japan someday when we come to Japan.
[Music]
Please, OK, well, I changed this to German,
but I thought it would be
okay if I changed the German word in the tweet before saying "Where is that Germany?"
Ok, I'll send you the pack later.Okay
, I
made a mistake.I can't say it anymore.Well, first of all,
instead of saying words, I
think it would be better to give you a little bit of information.As I
knew, Dusseldorf
is the most Japanese city in Europe.  It's a city with many
That's
right, this is really
interesting, and that digital tofu is, well, the
biggest one in Germany, and
among them there are 5,000 Japanese people.According
to information from Wikipedia, I don't know
if the number is increasing now, but there are
about 5,000 Japanese people.  It's
amazing, but this one
has a lot of history, and it
's like a history lesson, um,
and it's probably right, but there
's a company from Japan.  A company had already
set up a company in Germany, so they
sent Japanese people to work in Germany.For
a while, they
seemed to like the German dresses so much
that the company was already starting something.
What do you mean by going abroad for work?
Even after the business trip was over, there
were a lot of people who wanted to stay,
so I decided to stay and start a family there.
As a result, there are now about 5,000 people. It's
cute.
[Laughs] I'm
happy because I'm wearing a uniform. I'm a student.
So it's a really nice city that makes me want to leave Japan and live there. Seriously,
if I had
even the slightest desire to live in Germany or Europe, I would have said that.  It's
better to have a taste of other countries, but I want to eat Japanese food.I
want to talk to Japanese people.When I
feel a little lonely, I
go to a tofu restaurant or a Japanese restaurant.I
can meet Japanese people and eat Japanese food.
Yeah, I
think there's something like Eo Sushi. I think there's also sushi, but somehow this is
connected to the next thing, but it's set right now,
and
it's a place where everyone gathers after this poisonous event.
But the reason is that there are a ton of
Japanese restaurants lined up on a single road.
[Music]
Ramen, tonkatsu,
sushi,
yakiniku, everything.
Izakaya There's an Izakaya in Japan too. I wonder
if they have alcohol.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's amazing.
Even when I'm not at that place, it's a little crowded.
But when I go to Dokomi, it's really crowded, and
everyone's there.  There are a lot of
Japanese people working there, so I really
want to go there, but the people who go are
people who have been to events, cosplayers,
and ordinary people.
It's a Japan-themed event, so
when it's over,
everyone goes there
thinking, ``Let's eat Japanese food.'' I see, I heard good things about it.
But,
it's my first time abroad,
so I think it's better not to go there.
Okay, I
want to eat something like German Shock. I want to eat it. It's
seriously crowded
and I have to wait in line for such a long time. I don't like lining up at any store, so
I'll stop.  One
commenter said, ``Maybe I should take a look.'' I think it would be amazing to just walk around, so it's nice to see it, but when it comes to where to eat, I think a normal restaurant in Germany would be better.
[Music]
But I
heard that European sushi is different from Japanese sushi, so I don't eat it, but
Japanese sushi is fresher.
[Music]
Fresher is better.
Well, uh,
sightseeing is best if you have time to go sightseeing.
There is a little
Well
then, I'll ask the
teacher if the garbage staff could accompany me.Maybe they
can show me around here.The
media's
Half Nixley is said to
be famous.The place I've decided to go to at the moment is
Cologne
or something like that.  We're talking about going to see it. I'm going
to go shopping. Well, it's because of the dress. Yeah,
well, it's
close by train, but I'm
also going to see Dusseldorf and Cologne, and something else is prettier.  I'm
sure I'll go there a lot. It's
certainly close.
[Music] I've
never been there, but
everyone knows how beautiful it is. I
heard that climbing the cathedral is very difficult. I heard it's very expensive.
High, high, big, big, big,
look forward to it.If you've
already decided on a museum, you
probably won't go, but
there's a museum about that ship.I
think you'll probably have a little free time.
If it's nearby, I'd like to go there.I see, OK, OK, here's a little
information, uh, Sensei, I'm not a teacher today, but my
teacher, Nana-chan, Nara-chan, I have a question that you
asked me earlier.Before the
broadcast, umm,
you
have to be careful with your bags and stuff.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, my
experience is that you
should be very careful in Berlin, the capital of Germany, but
in Sluf, I have never experienced anything like that.  I didn't have one so I
didn't pay much attention to it, but
Seldorfer says it's pretty
safe.I think it's pretty safe, but
tourists can
tell Nana-chan is a tourist just by looking at her, so they might treat her a little differently.  No. Is
there anyone who approaches this person thinking that they can easily steal it?
Hey, it's
better to hold your bag tight. Well,
if you're careful, I
don't think anything bad will happen to you.  It
's my first time in Germany, but it
's my first time going abroad, so I
was a little scared.
Well, I guess I'll be
flying alone on a plane. Yeah, I'm
not on a plane by myself. I
have a friend who is an illustrator.  It's
a bit of a relief
[Music]
By the way,
premium economy or something
like that, economy, poor economy
[Music]
Well, if you cry once, I
guess it's still good.Actually, I'm thinking of going with Premium Economy.  I
thought about it, but it turns out that I probably won't be able to get a seat
next to three of my illustrator friends, and they'll
be separated, so I feel
like I'm going to be in economy.
I've been back and forth to Japan probably about
40 times, but I've
flown the same distance so many times
that I'm seriously dying.  It's
really hard on my butt and legs, which makes me want to push
my butt. It's been about 12 hours, hmm, and it's
like that when I get that chocolate. I
was expecting that, right? Now,
take the cushion. I'll
check it with my hands, but I have no choice but to sleep. I have no choice but to
sleep.  I'm the one who sleeps, too. I wonder if I'm the only one who
sleeps because my body hurts and it's so tight and the space is so small
that I can't put my feet anywhere.
I'm not good at sleeping while sitting, though.
Japanese people are good at it.It's true that Japanese people are good at small places.They're
sleeping.I see.I
received some marshmallows.However, there was
something related to this, so I thought
Japanese people should be careful when they go to Germany.
Please let me know if there are
any customs that you don't want to do.What are some of the things you should not do?I think it depends
on the country, such as poses, words, and actions.I'm sure it depends on the country,
but I'm wondering
if there are any customs that Japanese people would do that you
shouldn't do.  I do
n't
think so. I think there are so many things that Germans shouldn't do if they come to Japan because they're too polite.
But I don't think there's that many things that we shouldn't do if Japanese people come to Japan.
I
went to Germany in the past.  When I talked to a friend about this, I was
told that I shouldn't hold up my index finger.I
often point my finger gently at people,
but on the other hand, even in Japan, I was told that I shouldn't do it.
Because I heard it
[Music] Do I
really need to worry about that?
But yeah, I don't think there's anything we should do.
Germany also tips, although not as much as America does. Yeah,
Japan doesn't have tips, so I didn't think about it at all. They tip,
but they don't tip that much.  I don't think I need to think too much about it.For
example,
if I were to eat at a restaurant, it would cost
me 18 euros, which would be about 2,000 yen.So, if it
were me, I would have to
pay the closest one.  I
think I'll add that amount to a certain amount of 0 and pay 20 euros.If it's 24 colors out of 18, then it's
close to that amount.If you
think that's fine, then go somewhere else and
give it to the cashier when you make a purchase.  You do
n't have to tip the cashier when you go shopping at a supermarket or something. Well, you do
n't need to tip the cashier at that supermarket or a clothing store, but
at a restaurant, it's better to tip.  It would be
better to raise the tip a little bit, but honestly
there are a lot of people who don't open it,
so I do
n't think they really care about tourists.They
don't give it.If they
don't give it, they can't decide.It's
not like America, so people don't rely
on tips that much.
If you don't get one, you're probably lucky.If you
're going to a fancy restaurant, it's
better to tip at a fancy restaurant compared to a slightly cheaper restaurant.But it's a
cheap illustration, so don't worry about it.  Ah,
comment section If you use a towel at a hotel, they
won't replace it unless you leave it on the ground.That
's right, there are quite a few hotels like that, and
for some reason I still use it,
but it's a bit of
a waste to have that towel taken away.
Because it costs a lot of money, and because it
's not as kind to that world as it is to other people,
that kind of thing happens quite a lot at hotels.I didn't
know that, but there's
usually a card in the room with an explanation like that.  It
's on display, but it's not German.
No, it's English. It's mostly English. Both German and English should have been
changed. Let's read it properly. I'm
alone in the room. I
once worked at a hotel,
and there were
Japanese customers.  Whenever I came here, I was
quite
surprisedand
sad.The
Japanese people were
surprised.They said there were no bathtubs in the rooms, only
showers.There are
many rooms with showers, but there
are very few rooms with bathtubs.
7-chan's room will probably have a bath in a little while. There's a
chance that there won't be one. It's okay. I see.
Baths are part of Japanese culture. If you
think about it, I guess it's okay. It would be
better if there was a bust section. You're
relying on it too much. Yeah, I'll definitely be there.  Because of the bathtub, it's so-so.When you
check in, if you
ask if there is a room with a bathtub in the bathroom, they
might be able to adjust it for you, but there
's a chance that it won't be, so I'm prepared for that.  I
haven't taught her any words yet because she's talking too much,
but I think I should start teaching her now.For now,
I've added a little more to this one.This is the
first time we're together.It's better to teach her this first.It's about
pronunciation, but, well, it's the
same as English.  We use the Roman alphabet,
but German
has some special extra characters. They're kind of
cute, like emoticons, but even if you add the phonetic characters, they
don't really convey the meaning, so you should listen to them and memorize them.
Yes,
remember it with your ears.The dots in the first ah are
not eh, they are nice
nice nice nice nice nice.
Well, I guess it's
a little closer to the picture of the English word.
[Music]
What are you laughing at, teacher? You're
cute.
By the way,  Sometimes it's
written like this.
Because of the keyboard, I can't write this character,
so if I can't write it, I
write it. That's how I get the message across.  The
next one is uh uh uh
uh not uh
This is difficult It's difficult
but this is important The reason why it's important is that
Austria, the country where I live next door, always starts with these letters
Then
[music]
Nice nice nice and then the next one is ja
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
still close to the sea. My
mouth is so narrow. It's
in the shape of a woo. It's
making this sound.
I hold it in the shape of my mouth and whistle.  It's difficult, is
n't it? This is used
in German to say goodbye and good-bye,
so the
next one looks like a B, but the letter
vision
is pronounced with a strong S, which is a bit harsh.
It's normally SS.  So, for example,
what kind of word does it appear in? It
goes something like this. This
is nonsense. Now, it's the swastika. It
often appears in the names of cities. It's like I
said earlier, though.
When I don't use the keyboard, I can communicate with WS.
[Music]
Well, I
think this is pretty easy to use, but
in German, when I talk to that person,
I
use ``
How are you?'' and ``C.''
You seem to be extremely polite. Like you.
That's how you say it.
But, uh, I generally use C to people I don't know,
like people who are younger than me or who look younger than me.
Well, it depends on the atmosphere, but for example,
if someone comes to Nana's booth at an event, I
think it's okay to be honest with those people.Hmm,
I see.Yeah, but I don't really
remember either.
And if it's too hard to separate them, you
can just use C for all of them, or
you're CE.In
Japanese, you
can add san or chan after your name.In
German, you would say
room.  It's
like that Female and Mr.
But there's this, and
it's in front of the name.I
only use it for the first name.Takanashi:
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm
talking about hair, I'm
talking about hair, it's
okay, it's okay, I'm not talking about mold at all
[laughter] I'm
sensitive,
for example.  Changa
There is a possibility that people will say "Maybe Maybe Ka Gura" Hmmm
OK.
This is basic information, but here's where it gets
serious.
Can I use it? I'm sure
there are some words you've seen before. I
'll start from the top. Well, I've heard them before.  I
know it's that simple, but hello
[Music]
Guten tag Guten dark
Good morning Hagen
Punctuation Morgen
No, nice Good
evening Guten ament
Perfection
Good night Hagen  It's
not Gutenaftonat, Naft.
Like a cat. Cat.
Please get angry. [Laughs] I can't hear it. Discord is on Discord. I'm listening to the sound, but I can't hear it. I can't hear it. I wonder if it's working. [Music] [Applause] Thank you
very much.  Dance
That letter appears here as well.
[Music]
If you want to say just a short thank you, you can say danke.
That's okay. It
's better if it's shorter.
[Music]
I'm sorry.
This is also difficult, so my suggestion is that
it makes sense, so just say Sorry
Siri.Anyone can
understand it
in English, but it's already German.If you
have any trouble, you can use English at all.Do you understand?
Please tell me if it's okay.
[Music]
Ok, but I'm having trouble.
In English, anyone can do it without worrying, so it's
a little different from Japan.
[Music] Well,
if you say no, then
hey,
finally 99.
[Music] How
is J pronounced in German?
Like Wine
[Music]
That's right,
if you read this 9 in Japanese, how many places will it be when it's gone? In
reality, it's gone, but if
I pretend to read it, it probably does
n't exist, so I want to read it.
But when you
say "Ii to Ai" in German, it
becomes "Yes, yes, yes, love."
If I hadn't been told that, I would definitely have called you "Main".
Plus, this is an English pronunciation, but when you put 2 and A
together, it's normal, it's
good, it's good, that's right, that's what it is, that's
good, that's what it's called in German.  I
don't understand the words taught by Kanauchi, but just in case you see this one,
and then I see the one above, and then I understand. It
definitely appears in beer.
Beer is
not BEER.
No, no,
BL in English is
also German beer in We.  teeth
Even in ie, pronunciation will last a lifetime.
[Music]
German is BR. That's right.
Juice Juice
There are some that are more difficult, but this is also Chiara
's
greeting at the end of the broadcast, but I
thought this might be difficult, so I turned
to chess.  By the
way, what did you
say?
That's right. Well, that juice has the nuance of "see you later," but afiracene feels more like goodbye. It's amazing. If I'm being polite, it's better to say amphirasen.  It's
like a white powai, and it sounds a bit lame,
but yeah, I think you can feel free to tell anyone.So, when you say
bye-bye to someone who came to an event in anticipation, it
seems like you're using juice.
[Music]
If you want to make it cute, I
recommend
lighting it on fire.
[Music]
Teacher
[Music] Don't
cry. I'm so
happy that there are so many cute words that can be used.
Oh, and that's right. It was written in the chat just now.
But this is me, uh, the words I'm writing here
are the words that Nana-chan asked me to say,
but the one thing that's certainly not here is the
word ``please''
in German.  It's
out,
please. We're
living in a separate residence or together.
For example,
[Music]
Please pay the bill.
Well, I don't think I'll be able to remember this.
[Music]
Please pay the bill. That's right.
What do you say when buying something? At a restaurant, in
Japan, you often go to the counter and pay in front of the front desk.
In Germany,
there are a lot of press conferences at the table, so it's
hard for Mr. Wait to come over.
When I thought the clerk wasn't coming, I
waited for Mr. Hotta and his eyes to turn green, and then I
raised my hand a little
and said, ``Hold on,'' and 3 people came.Yeah,
but I'm
a little worried about the employees.
If you're too embarrassed to say it, just look me in the eye and
raise your hand, and I'll say OK.
Look at me, OK.
Or
raise your hand. The words I taught you earlier are after cooking. I'm
sorry, but we're already in the same cooking group.  I
think I'll draw this too.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, um, Japanese. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
[Music]
Even though I can't move, I have to pass.
When I say, "I'm
serious, look where you are, come on, let's go to Japan.
There are so many people that I admire so much, and
everyone really admires me, so
Naa-chan is like a god to those people.He
really is a god. He'll
do anything for me, and
anything will be forgiven.  If you
speak only Japanese, you'll
be treated like that.I want you to bring me
something spicy.I'm
not sure if you'll suddenly bring me rice, but it's
fun.It
's Kagura-gami, it's God.
Yeah, I'm a god painter, so I
think people will relate to it more. What do I
say, God? In German, I say God
as it is. Well, it's similar to English,
but it's stronger in WT, so
I say God good.  I
'm here. There
's also a pot here, so let's move on.
This is my name that can be used for anything. It's a
negative to
say "whatever".
Marshmallow has arrived
[Music] They said it
can be used in the same way as in English It
just came.
What do you
think? This marshmallow knows about the future. It's amazing. I just happened to find it and thought it was amazing. It's like, ``Well, um, um, um.''  MyNavi SMyname
is
similar, is
n't it? Either one is fine.If you want to
introduce your name, you can use either name.But
for example, say ``I am God''.
Then
[Music] If you
want to memorize it, use it.
Hey or nana.
Erase the English and I
'll teach you some simple words.
Delicious is like ``
wrecker.'
' It has the opposite meaning, so it's often
used in German.
As in the case above, when there is an ER at the end of a word, I
think people who pronounce it very clearly will pronounce it correctly, but
when they are speaking normally, it
tends to deteriorate.
There's a difference between "bite" and "wrecker,"
but people who speak normally end up saying "ah" when they do that.Also,
everyone's pronunciation is a little different depending on where they're from in Germany, etc.I
guess that's also marshmallow.  I was asked, "
Does Germany have dialects?" Yes, that
's especially true. My
impression is that
people like Berliners
have strong dialects.
Dsseldorf is
pretty standard. Dsseldorf is
pretty normal. I don't know how to
say soccer. It's not the most correct German,
but I don't feel like anyone speaks the correct German. I don't
know which word is correct anywhere.  No,
if that's the case, then it's strong.There seems to be a dialect.Eh,
strong, strong, strong, even if it's too strong, it's different.I can
hear it.Do you
understand?I also heard that
people from Dsseldorf and Cologne are a little different, you know
?
There are some people whose dialects are too strong, but
there are also people who are kind and talk a little more normally, so I
guess I'm just lucky.
[Music] You're
not alone, so it's okay. I'm sure you'll
find someone who can speak German.  I do
n't know.
But I don't know when there are events.
Maybe when I'm getting married, it's probably like that. On the other hand,
when it's an event, I
'm there a little bit, but I'm always there.  It
doesn't seem like it's possible, but it's like,
maybe,
please give me a ride to the venue of the event, etc. I was like that too, so there are many times when I'm not there during the event, but, but, but, when something goes wrong and I need help, it's like that.  I
think it's a little hard to say, "Well, I like this, I don't like this," and I
feel like it's a bit stiff to say it in German or Japanese,
but I think I like it anyway.
marks
For example, if you
want to say, ``I like Germany instead of this,'' then you can
put the word ``Germany'' here.  It's
a bit strange to say that one cat is active, so I
guess I should just say I like cats.
[Music]
So do I. I
like dogs, but I like cats a lot more
.  I'll
just put it out for now.If you
put in your favorite words instead of that one, you'll be able to say whatever you want.It seems like
it could be used when introducing yourself, so you can
say something like, ``I like this,'' and ``I don't like that.''
There's a way to do that, but yeah, it's like the
stone mark dance from earlier,
so it's like, ``I don't like this.'' It's probably the easiest way to tell Makitas because they
use the same words. Or, ``
This is a little
scary.''  It's a
harsh way of saying it, but I'm from the 8th generation.It
's a chopstick.This is
also a very emotional way of saying it.It's
like I hate it, that's right.It's
used when you hate it.I wonder
which one is better and cheaper, but
Magbas is more
common.  However, since there are many words, it
might be easier to remember OKOKOKAlso, just now, you
said it in a very Japanese way, but
let's not put any luck on this word.  Is
it a voiceless sound that ends with an S instead of a ``out''? That's right, that's
right, that's right. I
see. When Japanese people
speak English, German, and other languages, no one
can understand them. This is the reason why only Japanese people can understand.
Yes,
that's right. I'm
saying it in furigana, so maybe everyone is like that.
I understand why it's like this,
but that's why I can speak Japanese.
That's why I can understand Japanese people's English.
But people who can't speak Japanese can't understand Japanese people's English.
Japanese that you can't understand
has a set of vowels, so oh, yeah, yeah, that's
true. For example, McDonald's,
Disneyland, yeah, that
[music]
Japan is a little hard to understand.  It's
not the same for people who can't speak well.
[Music] If you
want to improve your English a little bit, try erasing the "uh"s. I
heard a good thing.
Everyone, I see.
Ok, let's
move on.
Please help me. [Music] You can just use that helper, teacher. It's easy, right? [Music] [Music] If you want to make it look pretty, add the bitte you memorized earlier, and eat well. Please, please, help me.  It's like, "
Please, please." Hilfie is cute. I
remember.
Um, to be honest, this line is long, so I don't
think it's okay to say it in English, but I'll teach you just in case. Can you
speak Japanese?
Not everyone.
In German, J is in English.  It
sounds like Y. I'm
sure it's H in Spanish
as well. Spanish is different again.
If J in English is J, then
this is English
German. It's
pronounced like Why in
German, and it's confusing like
J1 H in Spanish.  It's
getting confusing. Can you
speak English?
Englishsplay
English It's
long, I'm sure. If you're
having trouble,
EnglishEnglish
please
Japanese.
Put a mark after the word.
Japanese, etc.  You
can say it in English, remember this too, that's great, that's
great, that's great, so
enjoy it.Now, for example, if
someone comes to your booth and
buys goods, this is Nana-chan's greeting.
'' You can say, ``
BTS''
or  At the end, you can call it an anniversary tag.
That's an
easy-to-remember anniversary tag.
[Music] I've
kept it short.
To make it easy to remember, I basically
do this on a daily basis. When I greet people, when I say bye-bye, I
say...
leaving  I
think I can use this.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Here, let's
move on. I'm
happy,
wa. Well, you can say "I'm happy" in short in Japanese,
but I've been
having trouble with
how to say "I'm happy" in German.  For example,
when I receive a present or
receive a compliment, I have the
nuance of being happy.
I can't think of many things in one word.  I
feel like the lines I wrote are a little stiff, but there's some FR in them, but [Music] It's hard when they're connected Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, this is difficult.
Either one is fine, but
this one
makes me happy.
This one makes me
happy. It's a different color. Which one is better? Hmm,
which one? For example, where do you look at it?  When a
fan comes to visit me,
or when I receive something,
which one do I use to tell them how happy I am?
[Music]
Natural
[Music] If I had to choose, I'd
say the second one.Dance
White Mesh
Even so.  After all,
in such cases, I usually only say thank you. I
see, I'm already happy
with the emotions I've put into it,
but I should just say it in a way that makes me feel happy.  I
say happily, OK, I'm nervous.
Well, that's
right, it's similar to English. Let's
put more effort into the second half of the sentence. It's like in
English. I
feel like I'm putting more effort into my head. I'm wearing
accessories.
Wow, that's
amazing.
Pay in cash.  Masu
[Music]
Haraba
or
[Music]
Shorten it and add the word you already know.
This
R is pronounced.
If you say it firmly, you'll pronounce it, but
if you say it this way, you won't pronounce it much.
[Music]
OK, it's
cute. Once
Swiss
Even so,
this
is an event where you can get a taste of that Japanese culture, so
everyone knows it.
[Music]
Even if you don't know Japanese,
there are some words that you'll definitely know,
such as "goodbye." It's
one of those cute, cute things. So
cute.  It's such a worldwide word, it's
cute everywhere.
[Laughs]
Pronunciation is important here.
[Music]
I see, here those strange letters have appeared again. Hey, they've
appeared. Same thing next time. It's
beautiful, isn't it? It's
difficult to pronounce it, isn't it? It's beautiful.
This can be used for both people and scenery.Dou
is for you.Dance
this and that.If you can
buy it, put it out.It's a little different.Dance
[Music]
However, I don't think you can remember the difference on the
spot.  I
don't think it's necessary to say it without a subject, I don't think it's necessary to say it all the time.Instead, it's okay to
use the word Amazing.If
that's the case, I can remember it.Yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes.It's
fun.I
really
don't say it like this either.This is also
hard,
hard.
This means I'm having fun.The
other thing is, this
is fun.There's a difference here.There
will be a WS that looks like Smash SSS B.That's
true, but I
don't really say it like this.It's
fun.  How should I
say this? Don't you think it's fun? [Music] [Music] Don't say it in words, for example, when you
tweet something like, ``I went here today and it was fun.''
Yes, if you say it like that.  That one properly  I
don't know what happened, it's going downhill, so if you're going to say it like that, I think it's okay to write this, but if you just say, ``It's already fun,'' I don't say it much, but on the other hand, it's
not fun, it
's me, a pest.  I
don't mean it's just fun, but I
'd like you to tell me some words that have various meanings.
[Music] I think
this word is actually
used a little differently depending on the region.
[Music]
Yes, there are words like ``Yay!''
I want to ask you, yay, or yay is that
UFO
Yahoo
Yahoo It seems like it
can be used when playing games,
when you buy something, etc. But when I feel like that again, that's what I
think when I force myself to say
simple,
short words.  Rather than memorizing English, I
think it's better to use understandable English. What is fun in English?
Wonderful Fan Fan
Fan Fan That's right. You're
right. I don't know what it is. How to
make German natural?
After all, it's a different word than a proper selfie like this.
[Music] The words that
convey fun
[Music]
If it were me, I would
say it.
[Music]
Well, it
also means wonderful in German,
but
it
also has a meaning.
A little naughty
[Music]
Yes, I've always
used it to mean gentle. Yeah, what kind of
book will it be
? That's what happened. Let's go home. I'll
remember where this is, where that is.  I
feel like it's mainly used in Austria.That
's what it means.Heh, the
meaning of this word may be different in Germany and the north.Maybe it's
different, or maybe it's
used in its original meaning.  No
[Music]
There is something like English in English or that kind of thing.  To
be honest, I
think something like that happened to my older brother, but
people who love games sometimes say things like this.I
thought they were supposed to pronounce them.There
's a German word for laughing out loud.  I'm
going to write LOL in the same sentence again.
But if I were to put it into words,
ah,Rocky.
[Music] That's
interesting. I guess I'll add this as well.
[Music]
[Music] That's
interesting.  "
Please don't take pictures" is what I
mean when someone takes out a camera and tries to take a photo of all the reports from another world.  I wonder
if you can understand
that battery, but it's OK to say
something like this on the top of the head that a Japanese person does, right?I
think it's OK for Japanese people to say something like this, but I'm sure it won't get across to you.Why,
when it's OK, do you
make it like this with one hand?  teeth  I heard that it
can be conveyed, but I don't think it can be conveyed when it's on the head.Eh, maybe they
could have done it with both hands.  They
use marks, but
when playing overseas,
punishments may or may not be OK, and when
playing overseas games, the maltobutt may be the
opposite.
Well, for example, let
's say there's a quiz game.
So, what is that? There's a check box
next to the answer.
When choosing whether the answer is correct,
there are both people who put a check mark on it and people who mark it with a cross.
This is just a mood, so it doesn't matter which one.  It doesn't matter, and it's
not correct. Some
people cross out all the answers and checkmark only the correct answer. There
are also shades, but if only one of the answers is crossed out, then it's wrong.
Well then, there is a meaning to it that is correct.Japan is
completely different from Japan, so a check
mark means a cross, so it's
interesting.Well, it's
confusing.A
check mark
means the same thing as a ``wa'' in Japan.``Don't
worry, please'' is from another world.
Photos or no no no no no no
no no
That's right, where is the toilet?
[Music]
Nedabonyu is pronounced W in English,
but in German it's
pronounced [music]
Where is the toilet
? There are other words as well.  Let's
go.
But it's easier to pronounce.
Um, the word ``Bettei''
seems to be prettier. What, I think Crow is a bit dirty. It's like the difference between a toilet and a toilet. I see.
Or in English, that's the word for toilet.
This
might be easy to remember as well. You can learn the German word for "toilet" and
say "toilet" in a voice. That's
right, the difficult part here is German. I
know there's a "Deadidas". I don't know. It's
difficult. Before the words, uh...
There's "Dare Dee Dusty", but
that word...
[Music]
There's a gender thing. It's like the words
``ra'' and ``nashi'' in Spanish,
but they're complicated and confusing.This
seems to be the most difficult part when learning German.
Okay, let's keep it simple.Boyster, it just so
happens that the hardships are the same, but I
understand.Sometimes it turns into a cat war.Are
you a D?
Why, why, why, it's different, etc. It
's not really decided, but it's
pretty much decided yes, yes. Voice:
That's right, monster specs. Yeah,
no, no, what's the
point? All the words you asked me to say
are yes.  Well, since you taught me this, I guess I'll put this out again at
the end of the challenge. Challenge Nana-chan at the end
[Music]
Stellarcia Incircle Highish Stellarcia It'll
stay for a long time
[Laughter] [
Laughter]
[Music]
4th year 8th year
Equipment
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Do
n't overdo it,
but I feel like I'm a friend of Germany, and
going overseas is
something
like Hololive, a
word coined by a Japanese VTuber
who doesn't watch VTubers.  I
don't understand this, so I
think it would be better to say it in the park instead of because it's popular overseas.Yes, I have a
lot of friends who came from Germany at the same time.That's
all for me, Professor.It
was very easy to understand.
Hey, I want to say GOODLUCK. Good luck
Nana-chan. It
may be scary, but it's not scary at all.
Please enjoy it. Please
try some German food. I'm
thinking of posting lots of photos and Vlogs, so I brought my camera.  I'll
also get some videos from you.
If you need any recommendations for German cuisine,
please tell me how to fix it, but I'm sure
if the staff came with me for that meal,
they would probably be able to give me some.  I'd
like to hear your recommendations, I'd like you to eat this,
etc. I'll
tell you later on Discord.
Thank you. It
took a long time, 1 hour and 40 minutes, but I
wanted to teach you properly. Thank you. I'll
look back on it so I
can use greetings and other things properly.  I'll
repeat it
properly and memorize it. Please do your best. Thank you. Dance
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Separate Thank
you for your hard work The last
part of today's stream was also in German What's that?
Bye bye
Well then, thank you for watching today, Chara.
Thank you, teacher, for your long
lesson today. Okay, if you have any other questions outside of class.  Let's
play, I definitely saw it. I
was able to flirt with Hololive's mom again. Yay, I'm going to start flirting with her. If
you're Japanese, let's play by
all means. Alright then, everyone.
Juicy
[Music]
Bye-bye
Now that
microphone.
Wait a minute.
The mouse is lying.  Oh
yeah, there it was. There
was a charging cord. Wait a minute. Come
back up. Turn it around.
Prime Minister:
Okay, okay, okay, you can move.
[Music]
When I wake up, you're there and it's new again.The
actions you gave me were so
kind, but I was so sad that I almost
cried, and I was screaming.I wanted to meet someone again.I
don't know their name, but I
can hear your voice.  But instead, I
started running, thank you
[Music] It
may be a nuisance, but no one
closes my eyes
to myself. I'll
just pick up the feelings that
fell here and
deliver them to
you.
[Music] It'll burn
like this
[Music]  music]