foreign
call with Canada Senpai checking if
she's okay with it too but I'm very
disappointed to announce that um it
might be the first time in history that
I have to move Holo talk
and I'm so disappointed because
ah I got a cold on Monday to Tuesday and
then
uh I thought it was getting better each
day
Maybe
I feel like today it got worse
and it might be bronchitis now
so I'm [\h__\h] uh
sorry flag
anyway
um
new date
23rd of
December because I have to do it before
Christmas like I'm not gonna do a whole
talk for a while after that because I'll
be in Japan
um
I'm very sorry I'm I'm so mad at myself
I'm so bad
but yeah
um funny voice Chihuahua out and I'll uh
see you
soon but for now I will focus on
recovering
and button touch
to Amelia Watson who's back
starting from today or tomorrow
you know I'm addicted to Twitter so I'll
be around
oh my [\h__\h] god I'm so sorry