e
down
m
[Music]
oh
n
[Music]
o
and here we go oh wait you sitting we're
cuddling already we're sitting
together what is I am look you're so
cute K KY
hello
[Music]
yay uh uh wait wait controls confusing
um welcome everybody to Eden Eternal
with wa and
g
h um we both have experienced is playing
this game and we both love
anime and I finally up perss for this
game I was trying so hard we finally got
it and so we will try to relive and and
satisfy our anime freet topl anime mmpg
urges by making this perhaps into a
little Series E an eternal in
2024 you will not believe it for real
like I think we will repop at this
server with all the viewers as well um
we're I'm currently kind of we're not on
the what are you looking at we're not on
the uh first uh server there's like
several servers we're like on a secret
unpopulated one you guys will end up
following and finding us for sure but
that's okay that's okay this person
right next to us already yeah no way
you're like a viewer but you're so like
holy [\h__\h] like damn the cash send me a
dual request a do it do
okay okay what for real yeah are they
going to kill me girl you're so suicidal
what the heck take care I don't even
know oh miss zero miss miss good luck
good luck help you're not going to win
this why do I do no damage cuz we're
weak we're level
one wa gy I'm I'm surprised you kind of
look like
high level already like you don't look
like you just started out why do you
have those sick guns and that outfit I
don't know they is in my default damn
girl uh oh yep oh people people there's
a c Guild oh my God so cute what the
[\h__\h] little Froggies did you get
yourself cash upop [\h__\h] what the heck so
when I installed the game I was like
okay first thing I'm going to do is go
to um the cash shop but I I held back
because they didn't take my payment
anyway
so I didn't buy anything what the hell
why you guys kill me wait how do I go to
the cash shop should we buy stuff right
now no no we shouldn't we shouldn't we
shouldn't for now let's oh my God why
are they flexing so hard why they got
Phoenix
feathers bro oh my God we shouldn't buy
stuff right now no we shouldn't keep
your money people will give us things
for
free yes yes maybe maybe wait you you're
so dead glamour did he end your misery
that player killed me I'm ready to
explore now it's so orangey oh because
we're all orange we're all orange it's
orange they're welcoming us all these
pumpkins wait they got little cats what
the heck what are those cats
cute baby wa this is so distracting um
focus so one thing I know noed we were
spawned here but I don't remember when I
first played this game I don't think we
got spawned here I think there was like
wasn't there like a different area I
think so wait so where are we supposed
to go now I just warped to this person
clicking on the quest wait I got a
marriage
proposal you can get you get no you
can't get married this early you're only
level one if anything I'm going to marry
you but it's funny I I think when I quit
eating the journal that was around the
time when they rolled out the marriage
system so I never got married in Eden
aernal before but no of course I'm not
sorry I can't marry you guys I have gigy
yes back off who oh yeah it just said
99% off sale for $1 get a total $100
value items what should I do that you
get
75% and a 25 it just popped up it was a
popup get out of there wait okay first
first of all everybody stop sending me
marriage proposals it's very Charming
flattering but
don't second of all where do we go to
level I keep on wanting to press shift
to dash but there's I guess there's no
dash if you click on the right side
there should be the quest where it says
talk to Marie and you can warp there oh
ah right we were supposed to take a
quest I got uh wait to the right wait
where where do they how do they Mark
quest uh people
in the the um the quest
box that popped up on your
screen still right here this is still
overwhelming and More PT um screens are
overwhelming can is there like a right
click to like make me walk there
automatically or it should warp you
there it just brought me there oh
teleporting to ah will cost your zero
portal Stone okay goodbye kfp
where am I goodbye is this still in it's
still in the city
right just kind of oh oh yeah it's in
the city she bring somewhere else oh my
God now we're in Limestone M yay this is
what I
remember my hair looks so funny I have
these like hair flaps but when I jump it
looks like wings or something look look
from
behind oh yeah the way that they move
they're
so rectangular
yeah okay this is the like beginnner
area I remember uh it was that way wait
do we have the quest already do we have
any quests are we taking quests we
should have a quest I am currently what
is this we have a 3-day Mount cool
heyo Quest
local did you take a quest here is it
like kill some
monsters um it's talk to
people mine says talk to I don't have I
talk to this lady you
know wait where are you does someone
have a no one I have orientation
problems let me walk in front of you the
I talked to this lady and she had
something oh aha I'll go to the force
and help you look I found your husband
wait what did you
click oh don't know she had a
oh a question mark on
her she didn't have one for me that's so
weird was your question mark I think she
gave me a quest uh no not really wait is
this bugged
out where's your
quest
uh right I don't see anybody with a
particular like hey this is your main
quest kind of Icon am I blind try
passing q i I canceled it q i n at the
same
time what the hell uh no that just
opened up a lot of different
things just gave us so much
stuff yeah shift left click to track a
quest
no bottom right check quests yeah do
mean this window but why am I already
lost can you give me your quest
yeah where's the quest fish around for
the quest Journal well the quest Journal
is just this Quest log
right I'm currently looking for do I
have to like go back and like get the uh
talk to that first lady again maybe
maybe how are you going to get back
there I have I I bound I bounded my soul
to the ah okay wait no wait I'm I'm just
in the Limestone Mountain no the soul
binding was a lie I'm just
here yeah when I Arrow bluish
Arrow bluish Arrow that's so weird oh
wait here available Quest
nothing what where are your quest I I
was able to open like a little window
that says available quests oh wait if I
undo the level choice
okay I got something
yippe I have to talk to Madam cynia and
now there we go there we go waa what is
this big cash up window I love it I know
that's why should we buy it it's only a
dollar off see okay I want to buy it but
my payment option didn't work last time
I have to like look into it I have to
pay I have to buy pay safe cards can you
buy me a pay safe card PFE card let me
look at these options send me some
money purchase Oh my God the
popup select payment method I used to
always save up my pocket money and then
buy all the cash up stuff all the cute
outfits but back then all your allowance
yeah but back then I didn't have that
much money so everything was so valuable
to me and I was always like struggling
to get you know money to buy the cutest
outfits that's name
Miku
streik say stream Mirage that's that's
just the name literally is stream Mirage
of that
person that's not hu that's just stream
Mirage that's just
stream okay wait what do we do not talk
to the talk to Andrew oh I like how
they're always teleporting them talk to
L okay oh yeah they do they just let you
teleport everywhere I don't think they
did that back in the day that's probably
just quality of life improvements now
huh yeah they're like we have to make
this game as easy as possible so people
say and they
play okay and now I have a level to
Awakening free main quest from last you
have that too yeah I have it okay okay
then we got to go oh got
alpacas I love we need to get an
alpaca let's go which we can get if we
spend $1 did you already kill two um
mushrooms no
yes yes you're so fast okay wait I want
to here Bam Bam Bam ow bam ow I am
aiming to be a a double sword wheel
person what are you aiming to be now I'm
not sure I'll probably just level a
bunch of them until I pick one that I
like okay yeah that's the cool thing for
people who don't know in Eden Eternal
you can uh level several classes right
and you can switch around right that was
eat and eternal not a different game
right was this game I'm mixing it's just
like Final
Fantasy I guess yeah but then yeah also
for certain classes you have to have
level certain other class classes and so
on yeah I think we finished the
quest I wonder I want to see statistics
of how
many players this game had in the
previous days compared to
today I want to know how many people
play this game normally like what's the
usual player base like
yeah when I found out that this game
came back because like originally it um
it it died it was like ended it service
mhm and then it came back I don't know
when but when I found out that I was
like oh my God I have to play right away
but no no no no no let's let's keep that
like first impression of coming back for
a stream so it's holding back you're so
fast gigy don't die am I dying I'm fine
but
still get away from me normally I these
muss away play A Healer so feels weird
that I'm not a Healer this time I was
thinking that too I was like I could
play A Healer but because um healers are
always good for parties but because we
have all the viewers we don't have to
play the Healer I guess so we can force
them to heal us yeah so we can be
selfish DPS for once and then people can
heal us I guess oh let me try some
attacks here there you go wow
flashy I'm killing the boss right now
die
yay nice you did one hit and you left y
your job here is done my job here is
done I
helped I'm speed running I got got
places to
be normally I would always play the
Healer just because I felt like I don't
know I I like I don't normal combat it
was always too scary to me and it felt
like too much responsibility but then
healing is also huge responsibility
right I like the responsibility of
healing yeah especially if you do
raiding what ah I killed the boss
without having to get the thing from the
boss Quest I have to kill him again no
what the heck resp quickly at least yeah
he's already back oh y you left me no no
girl you left me we're we're playing an
em together why did you leave
me I'm I'm right here I'm right here I'm
waiting for you right here H where where
outside yeah I'm outside the cave I'm
outside the cave I'm right
here you're you're
dooming this is not the proper MPG
Behavior we have many um skills I have
I'm level three
now yeah I think I'm also level
three am
I wait what am I level three or level
two what
confused okay I
left prerequisites on the other classes
kfp do did you guys like play this game
before like you shiny ones or did you
just uh in short amount of
time uh accomplish this this coolness
the
swag yes a
bit okay what about the rest of you the
moment I it was scheduled I
started wow what about these like red
people red orange
people cuz you look like you invested
like what the heck why do you have
Phoenix fers and you got like this crazy
pet started an hour
ago all the count wa sasuga yeah I
thought so you're like what what level
wait what level are you 11 oh that's not
wait no
that's I don't know is that that's a
really cool Mount is the top left the
level character level three oh yeah that
person wasn't even that high
level we're they getting the stuff that
means we're going to get those stuff too
yay all right I'm uh at the I'm I'm
collecting gem appraisal tools from
sharp horn Yaks what up
you I'm killing
Yak let's see if we can get to the max
level one day together or easy we're
going to get max level here on this
stream do we have any like exp buff
items if we spend $1 we can't but I
don't want to like immediately level up
I I just want like maybe an exp buff
that's all I really want yeah I think
the it they put it behind the $100
discount where you get
75% buff w
wow nice and then if you go into your
inventory there's a cash shop code that
is like redeem this code and you get
stuff and if you click on the gift box
next to your face you get a login bonus
oh yeah I didn't I didn't get that last
time when I made my character what the
heck uh the what to next that one a
finally what is this level class XP
charm are you using the XP charm right
now not yet okay I could be we
could ah magic a that's where the cat is
from those pick up the items or what was
it or do they just
attack those pets you know what I mean
do they attack or do they pick up I
think they just pick up I don't remember
them attacking yeah I thought they
picked up items and maybe gave you buff
oh don't
know okay uh damn this is all happening
so fast with like teleportation and it
wasn't always so fast I was walking
everywhere so many items by teleporting
around like this all the time you know
at least uh kfp takes a long time to
catch up to find me again I'm like
teleporting the whole
time they have to wait where are you
currently looking at all this I'm okay I
found the 7 Day exp boost I you the cash
up no no no they give you a code okay
okay they give you a code to um get
items beginner pack wait I got a lot of
items
here wait wait he they gave us like five
I thought we only get one they gave us
like they gave us everything I thought
you'd choose I I s back in the day you
didn't get all of this was like the
reward from one Quest and you get only
one pair of shoes that you choose now
you get is so good now they give you
everything
yeah clo armor here these ones wow this
part contains the the Wooly bull alpaka
looks rather
plain oh oh it's attack oh I attack it I
I thought it was attacking for me
so many people here alpaka I thought it
was spawning an alpaka and it was just
misspelled I'm I I have been
deceived oh well okay guys goodbye again
I'm
teleporting I see you're with me gy for
once I'm
[Applause]
here
okay defeat Rocky High mushro let's go g
let's go I'm on my way I remember these
places it's so nice to come
back you should use the code too so you
can get the
EXP go code wait okay tell me again what
code where do I find it if you go into
the cash shop and then in the cash shop
where is it how do I get into the cash I
don't know the L yeah how do I get in
the cash shop if you press I right yeah
huh and then you say it press reward
code on the bottom of the
page oh how do how do you have a and
then type in Eden 500k why the hell did
you find that code it's in your
inventory oh is it uh caps yeah all caps
you're so crazy
G why so CL this in my inventory what
did we
get lots of stuff they give you like
item sets and then they give you a pet
and um also gives you the the EXP
there's so much
happening wa uh did they where did they
send it to should be in your inventory I
think it was just in my inventory
automatically uh is it the Justin's
small pack no that's probably something
else that's something else but I got
some stuff and Candy trick
pack ah what is ah ah don't
[Music]
I'm getting healed thank you not enough
space in the backpack okay maybe later
for now I can
use uh this exp
charm sure
okay ah wait I need
to collect F fitted spore from Fe Sprout
did you get that
already no not yet I'm going I remember
this exact one in this exact
location
nostalgic oh my God I the Sprout I see
it what is this Hunter's
Box nearby Hunter's dropped baggage open
and take a look inside there are traps
for hunting it seems to be us let's put
them nearby and see do I have to I don't
want to yeah we don't have to this not
our not our job ah wait did someone have
to choose
and not enough space in they're they're
they need to give me another extra
backpack they they're spamming me with
items right now what am I supposed to do
they give you it in the box that you
just got from the cash shop you get like
20 extra spots damn no but do I have any
extra bag that I can't see right now in
here that I'm not using what's with all
these pets why do I have like five
pets you will need to you equip all of
them right
now uh uh I don't know wait
was Battle prey okay is this is it out
now oh I aha
it'suh yipp join the pet aha
ahuh have you already bound all the pets
to you no I only bound one but I can B
all of them apparently yeah then they're
out of the
way okay
and then I could probably just throw
away this
right and then throw throw away all the
armor parts that I can't wear or or
should I
not that totally I bet you could get rid
of all the noob items yeah if I need
something better then your school
kfp
character okay now maybe I can open it
oh yeah I can open
it
uhuh ah there it is a how
nostalgic the
bag everything's so nostalgic to me but
if I put this down here is that still in
the inventory yeah okay eh I don't I
don't know if I want this but okay uh
okay where are we talk to Aina oh yeah
give me the
items nice my inventory is so full of
garbage same girls same where's the it's
not really garbage we're Suffering From
Success they're giving us a lot of nice
stuff it never used to be like this you
back in my day you had to really work
for your for your gear for real for the
gear and for all these like Buffs and
stuff and the Animals we didn't have so
many animals back in my
yeah now they just give you everything
like a hand
out thanks I guess oh already done okay
this is so
fast maybe we should walk to places to
make it less fast I
know you are son of Eternity what is she
saying being able to come here and
complete my test you really are the one
I've been waiting for with innate
mysterious available ID she said
suddenly the mission is to build a
perfect Paradise in this world you are
son of
Eternity I'm son of
Eternity son of Eternity oh finally a
merchant for me to sell my
stuff but what why are they giving me
all these
items I guess they want me to try out
all the
classes
ooh bless you thank you M what is summon
the monster why would I why would I want
that okay I'll do it got to
summon I do it so you get out of my
inventory wa I never use my skills
everything's happening so fast that I
don't even think about using my
skills yeah this what are these skills
anyway I didn't even look at them we're
just zooming
through this these are the new ones that
I don't really need
he's
strong
okay
yppe okay I got some clothes too and
another backpack
yippee
yippe okay I just got rid of everything
okay let me click
this ah yum there's so much
stuff oh okay can I throw this away huh
yes what is this another
demon
okay make sure to summon your inner
demons gy I'm summoning
them woohoo also are there skill points
I'm pretty sure there's skill points in
this game right I haven't used them yet
yeah I haven't used them either are you
ready to go into this
dungeon in here dungeon dungeon quest uh
oh is there no Quest do they just make
you go in oh no never mind oh yeah
Kev Kev has level eight dungeon quest
with rings as rewards
okay I think I'm ready I'm looking
what's in here I couldn't I guess you
just go in I walked in and I clicked on
multiplayer and now I'm in here oh it
might be solo I think I remember this
might have been in a solo dungeon oh no
there is multiplayer to what do you mean
you didn't get to
choose all right solo it
is solo good time you don't want to be
with me I do but you went in anyway
didn't you I went to multiplayer ah what
okay wait I'm coming out I'm not sure if
we can I'm wondering if we can be in
here together I'm
coming okay
of course we can be together we must you
need to be solo for the quest
oh is only solo that's what it was okay
mhm makes sense my memory it's like they
hate people being friends it's like it's
not an
MPD why is I clicked on the solo one and
we're in here
together that makes no sense I swear I
click Sol right better c yeah this this
better count is a
solo it's like the the devs are watching
and they suddenly change the rules for
us cuz we're
complaining like they want to be
together thanks devs maybe it's a bug a
welcome
bug oh my God why are you so op why is
your stuff so much
flashier I am a
gunslinger I got the most powerful AOE
actually I don't know I don't know
nothing about this class we got some
crazy AOE going on
too come here buddies let's
go it's a new class you have a new
class yours is a fancy new class I hear
oh why you so
fast we got to go we got to go you have
a little a little thing running after
you what's that do I have that too prob
my friend yeah you have have it
too where
do I don't see it I'm blind what this uh
items will be bound upon picking up roll
the dice roll why are we rolling for it
I need the shields you you can have
it yeah you can't use a shield and a gun
that' be
crazy I just can't believe that it told
us to do it solo and we're in a party
yeah hopefully they won't make us do it
again but it counted defeat herck yeah
it did Count oh my
God you're you're you're so strong off
we go whoa am I going the right way
you're going the wrong way I think where
am I going now I shall run in front of
you let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go ah okay well at least your HP
isn't doing so well because you're
rushing through it doing everything I'm
going to die but it will be beautiful
are you doing this thing where is is
there a word for it in English when AOE
people gather all of their victims
around them first um pulling or I don't
know yeah yeah I'm
pulling
damn she's doing the typical thing myy
myy Callie
Cod this
do I don't I don't know do I need what
no teleports out of
here okay I'll take
it did we do it all yeah we did it
yipp talk to
Easy think my soul
uh talk to Kev talk to Soul Garden
ah but you that guy right there right my
progress oh okay talk to him too talk to
bomman I have two quests running right
now yeah me
too oh you can get more Quest here I see
a lot of exclamation points in this town
mhm Dodge training bash training I'm
I'll take them all
oh what is that I'm on a beach right
now pleas open store it's a beautiful
beach so
sparkly these are taco does kind of
because they got that onion ring and I
know it's jellyfish but with the onion
ring it just looks like taco
does
cute look yummy
why' you make gigy so small I didn't
make her small she was born like
this yeah I Was Born This Way yeah I am
of this size leave me alone you're of
this size what what is your centimet
[Music]
again
153 15 you're so
tiny that's a normal hide did you not
eat your broccoli and stuff when you
grow up no I I like you bro I maybe
maybe when I was growing up I like it
too late you know it's when you get
older and then you enjoy food you don't
like anymore FAA FAA has a freaking
itasha sheesh I love that alaka I want
that
awesome I
[Music]
wanton okay I'm teleporting again how do
people even how are you guys still a
people to follow me when I'm constantly
teleporting how do you do it people know
exactly where to find you
how it's
terrifying okay I got so much stuff in
my inventory again what is
this an enchants
uhhuh I shall wear a ring don't I have
space for two rings yes
and cluff armor can
go I know I could sell it guys but I'm
just thinking I want to get rid of it
now and if I need money
[Music]
then I'll just ask you guys for some
offerings yeah give her all of your
possessions oh yeah Mor's horror r ah
right level you already level
10 I think from the quest I picked up
you're so fast
[Music]
wow what
happened what happened where is the
eagle a oh I I became level 10 why why
yipp I didn't do
anything wait
um which ring is better for me I'm
wearing maybe it's fine although yeah
maybe it's fine cuz oning ring is I
think more for like Mages and stuff
will be right back real quick I must
okay we are be all right what is
these H accessory can I wear it oh I'm
wearing it I don't remember these things
being a thing back in the day maybe I'm
wrong like trophies
amulets right she really
disappeared oh and a shield
oh I'm wearing the shield I didn't take
off a sword did I oh I
did oh then let's switch these two
eventually I want a dual wield but for
now I I would say it's
okay okay it's amazing how you guys are
controlling yourselves by not sending me
a million like trade requests and stuff
or maybe you guys are just not able
to I'll give you the benefit of the D
what what are those
what are
[Music]
those that's a interesting bird looks
like several birds in one why am I
teleporting to everything it's now I'm
getting used to it I'm just doing it the
simple
way back M there we have to move
everywhere with our
feet and then when we had an alpaka that
was the greatest relief ever because
finally with the alpaka
wait I'm sure these are around here
too where are the eggs I found
egg when you had an alpaka that was like
so much faster
suddenly now I I'm just brain empty
which is nice too to at least get
through the start of the game
fast okay I don't need all these dye it
unless can you use those D items also on
cash shop I
items cuz I looked for the cash up and I
think the cashup items had their own
dying Dy D
products diable class clubes yeah class
clubes that doesn't sound like I can use
it on cash up items which is what I will
be covering my whole body with
eventually hopefully so I'm welcome back
so I'm going to get rid of that
okay uh I am currently doing a quest
at the beach again we the same one
yippe let's kill
them I I want fashion so bad me
too but like the the ones they currently
have in the cash shop I don't know if
there's some cute ones but I want some
that are not in the cash shop right now
do you think we can ask the the
Publishers to put something into the
cash shop we will buy we will use our
money yeah please but since we are like
Reviving their game with some people can
you make can you let us have the cash
off items we want although let me
rephrase it of course the game is
already alive on its own you don't need
us to function but we're certainly
bringing some people in right so please
can we choose the next like rotation of
cash off items is that how the cash off
works it used to always like rotate yeah
like they bring in some fresh stuff and
then other stuff uh is like removed and
so
on I want I want different clothes too
which is what also makes some so
exclusive and like sought after because
like for example something hasn't been
in the cash shop since like eight months
or so and you really want it mhm yeah
just like in apparently in an r o b l o
x game
where just yesterday I I learned
about I don't want to advertise on the
games you know but I heard about this
like headless headless skin that you
only get during October Halloween or
so I did see that when I was looking at
the cash shop of the r
o game you play everything that you can
play online are you just like addicted
to everything that's online
yeah
unfortunately what online game have you
not
played um that you would may be
considering
playing I haven't really played many
shooters so like Halo I've never played
oh what am I here oh just TR
okay what's the point in like traveling
I can just teleport there ah funny
hi
Julian I'm looking at the cash shop
fashion right now and I don't want them
you right like I I I they're cute too
what they have now is cute too but
there's better stuff like in the
character creation you could preview
like all of the cash up
items and some of them are
just so nice yeah where are they bring
them back please you think you have the
gacha for them in this lucky
bag I don't I'm not sure does it say
what's possible to be in the lucky bag I
think there's probably like a there is
pumpkin Knight Terror and then at 3% it
says mythical weapon free choice what
does that mean huh what does it look
like ah you can preview
items but uh it was like either like
shift or alt or CDL and then click on it
but if it's just like some mythical item
then I don't know if you can preview it
oh yeah they're all in a box so you
can't preview it damn take the me they
do look like they're
um wait a second fashion though I have
to think for one moment because this
Quest isn't as automated as everything
else able can find out who wrote the
villain secret plan by analyzing the
handr to C you must get a free piece of
fresh pork from Bo from a boar ahuh like
this uh but did I already
did I already get threee pieces of the
bors maybe
not did
I have to think for one
moment oh thanks for the
heal okay I got fresh pork which I don't
think I had before yeah okay so I get
three of those you guys are following my
instructions of not stealing my mobs
thank you there's enough mobs for all of
us it seems yeah they respawn so quickly
good good good a thanks for the constant
heal what a service all I should attack
with
skills okay now I have free
pieces uh take the meat to iron who's
iron this guy is Julian and the game is
not teleporting me to iron
now what how did they expect me after
babying me for so long how do they
expect me to know where to go yeah why
are they suddenly making us walk it's
not
fair kfp can you lead me I know where
wait where did you go I don't I don't
there's too many
names there you
are isn't this so
nice that we can play together with all
of you guys I love that
yeah this is what MMOs are all all about
Community yeah and normally you know
back in the day I was always like going
for like the newest anime M RPG on the
market because being there from the
beginning means you're part of the
community easily and you know it's just
like it feels better when you're there
from the beginning but like sometimes
like for example um Final
Fantasy uh 16 was it or 14 14 14 I
joined like sorry controls confusing I
joined too late
and
then I I I just I just quit after like a
month or so in that one month I became
max level but I didn't have any friends
I didn't know anybody
no
yeah okay did I do it I'm sure if you
start it now there'll be so many
people with me yeah I guess so yeah but
it's not quite quite the same like
having so many people around me because
you know I'm a streamer versus just
playing normally it's a bit different
but it's still
fun I don't know why I was going with
this the next best time to start Final
Fantasy and have that feeling is when an
expansion pack drops n but still I don't
think so for me it's too late also I I I
paid I purchased Final Fantasy 14 like
four times I swear if not even five
because I had to it's so weird I had to
buy it so many times
I can't even explain I don't even
understand anymore what happened cuz the
shop was being funky or something or
like your account wasn't bound to it um
I think like one time I bought it in
Japan and then one time I bought it in
Austria and oh I think like okay one of
those times I probably lost the CD or so
I don't know I don't know yeah something
weird about the region lock and the
accounts there was definitely a region
lock that was my problem I moved back in
the day from Japan to Austria and had to
restart you stuff like that wait so why
that's
evil what do you mean item what do you
mean what do you mean where's my did
that last mob just not dro the
meat no I have to go back but is it was
this in the area no that was not an area
no no where am
I can't Fe pick me up I'm scared and
lead me to the Bor meat
again yeah where's the bore meat I am
also at the bore meat Quest okay the
meat you just kill the boes and
then well I don't really know I got led
by the people I'm about to die can
someone help me can someone help me I'm
about to die I'll send my healers to you
I don't go heal
K thank you okay it was right here
that's
oh I just I think I just got bore by
bore meat pork by doing nothing because
you are killing
bores I'm getting all the pork are you
getting pork no oh I'm picking up all
I'm I have six now yeah you you got to
you got to uh KY can you lead her to the
the guy yeah there's a cook a
chef and I I can give you my free slices
if you don't have anymore because I got
six
now I okay I'm still getting more thanks
to
you I'm not even in your area and I'm
getting your quest items take all of my
meat okay you you're probably fine right
do you have enough yeah I have three
okay where do I cook this this so fun I
I tell you take the meat to
iron yeah iron that's literally how I
say iron
IR no wait that's not how I say iron I
say
iron and his name is iron which is how I
did say iron
right I think therefore I am okay more
talking this
Quest iron I found on
eggshells nice Quest thanks girl is this
these are not even main quests sorry d i
these are just side quests do I need
these no I didn't have to take that
Quest at
all why did I do
that okay let's quickly do that side
quest because I just don't want it to be
there uh cron Eagle cron Eagle
cron cron
Eagle she's here in the game too crony
glob where are
you uh
I remember that was some special
Eagle wait that I have to spawn it or
what break break the eggs on the floor
to lure out the
chronicle okay fing to these people when
in doubt read the uh Quest
description uh egg egg egg how about
this
one crony
glue no
crony GL crony GL crony
GL
hey my
way I'm I'm doing some weird side quest
right
now I was also doing a side quest are
you doing the walking on Dancing on Exel
one no it was called visiting
aen uhuh and he just made me run around
so many places
okay visiting even I'm at the main quest
that's level 13 right
now am I too far in front of you great
robber I'm on eil great robber okay yeah
hey how how are we like at the same
Quest when you were gone for like 1
minute or two
minutes and those one or two minutes do
a lot in this game I got to I got to
keep up I got to meat up where is Sher
oh have you found
Sher I have not seen Sher all right
let's read uh violent robber
Sher just spawn randomly I found him H
he's like a little boss
here
[Music]
die there we
go okay talk to Brock
speed try not to fall behind the
levels I'm trying my best
here robbing
Hood wait what why is this why why is
this why was it
so oh what happened with the color what
were they trying to tell me it felt
familiar okay kill everybody let's
go are you with
me I should be here yes yeah in here
what was that oh class level up maybe
okay uh
[Music]
swordsman get know last night I Dreamed
A lot of weird stuff as per usual mhm
and uh can somebody heal
G she's taking too much trouble for
herself
again where are the heers at
anyway I was like uh in a car for some
reason I was driving a car please don't
let me ever drive a
car um and I was I was like trying to
park it so this road that was I was
driving it on it was really like a slow
Road and uh people were in front of me
right and and probably the traffic light
or so was like on red further in the
front that's why no car was moving but
because the cars weren't mov moving I
thought that everybody was parked and so
I just parked my car there in the middle
of the road and moved out and then all
the cars drove away and I was like oh
[\h__\h] I need to park my car I thought I
was parked and so I genius and I feel
like I would do this IRL that's why I'm
telling it quickly in the stressful
situation since I already left my car
and stood next to it I um just moved the
car okay pretty strong though I moved it
with my bare
hands like 2 m to the left to park it
there and then for some reason instead
of spilling spaghetti I like lost like
three tooth and I fell on the ground you
lost three three have your teeth the
teeth however like I I sometimes have
like weird teeth dreams but I think in
this case it the teeth had the same kind
of like vibe to them as in that game
inscription
oh the way they were dropping it and the
sounds they were making when they were
dropping it just felt like inscription
teeth so it it wasn't the same kind of
like anxiety
inducing teth tooth loss but still
anyway I um I know how to park a car for
sure totally we're not killing the right
people have you finally found the right
people that we have to kill cuz we need
robber and assassin I'm oh yeah you just
have to click on them and then and War
there oh well thanks for doing it for me
no
problem teeth dreams are so stressful
like you dream about losing all of your
teeth and then you wake up and you're
like what just happened yeah I've I I I
do get those dreams every once in a
while when I'm I guess like when I'm
like nervous or anxious or so it's
always like at those
times oh bosswell someone else killing
him right now now we have to wait for
the
respawn lunchbox you ruined everything
you ruined everything I can't believe
you are playing this game as you should
be no you're not supposed to take our
mobs okay I'm waiting for the wolf's
pocket watch from bosswell Spawn maybe
you can go find the boss wait no wait
same thing
I'm just waiting for
boss he should spawn right here there is
mine here he
is
awesome okay Brock we're coming back are
happening so fast for real I don't have
space in my backpack oh God that's
because they give me every freaking item
I had to choose back in the day I had to
commit to one like cloth cloth armor or
heavy armor or leather armor and I have
everything I have
everything it's
ridiculous thanks but I don't need all
of this give me more bags please I have
this here too does it give me a bag no
then I will not open it what's this
eternal ah Eternal coins is that for the
cash
shop Eternal coins is I don't know if
it's the premium though I need to spend
it
is this stronger
no
oh so many
[Music]
items get rid of this
ah then this 99 okay this can
go talking to this person talking to
this person the teleporting to talk to
this person just go so fast maybe we got
to find our like um bank account
somewhere in the city there's like
storage H to get rid of all this garbage
yeah at least like all the like enchant
Scrolls and everything they're taking up
so much space right what did you do you
changed your
size you're so small now oh I did not
mean to do do that it's probably
CU oops troll yourself I didn't mean to
it just why did it become so TI It Happ
even tapped I guess it happens should I
throw this I'm throwing it away I'm
focusing on swords right
now okay cleaned up a little
bit what was that
ooh World unknown kfp obtained the proof
of power they write that in the has
achieved the feat of besting Mars spare
poppy n they announce it in the world
chat
sick congratulations congrats you're
famous in this game now yipp just like
how I always wanted to
be once they gave me stuff that I can't
even use oh my God yeah I always want to
be famous in an MMO me too
and I think I think I kind of like was
like sble times like one time I was
really like so fast when um a new game
came out I was like the top of my class
of in that
server okay like I was number one in my
I was grinding so
hard you were busting your ass for real
and then you rewarded for it everyone
knew
you I I I need to go into the dungeon
are you with me multiplayer one second
I'm waiting inside oh I remember
this oh my god let's
go okay while I'm waiting for you I'm
going to look at stuff oh okay okay do I
not add anything here on my own
actually going to sell a bunch of don't
remember how it was in my
inventory real quick rid of this this I
miss this type of games me too that's
why you can also now from today onwards
join Eden Eternal and play with us not
sponsored not sponsored
though but o you want to play with us so
bad of course they
do
understandable I am in Here solo are you
in here oh do we have to be solo you can
yeah it's a single player dungeon again
at least we'll be togetherit
we know maybe we can be together
yeah I'm joining solo please please
please please please please please
please
please yeah you're here
what I don't
understand this is
nice die so this dungeon is apparently a
little bit more difficult than the first
one we did so be careful
uh what is this oh I don't need that me
neither I roll a
oo nice this feels very really
nostalgic they're hurting me I'm like 10
years younger again
YY this is like a
youthful playing this game
small
W gigy by the way speaking of you
fo I don't know how that's a segue but
recently I've been using something that
I learned from you without really
knowing its origin um a painting is it
for like what have you been using uh a
word crazy I was crazy
once blah blah blah where is it actually
from
it's like I don't what is this meme or
what is this or crazy I was crazy once
they locked me in a room a room with
rats yeah yeah why when I look it up I
see um a Roblox
video what it's from freaking I've been
quoting Roblox
think please don't original origal
Rox okay I pulled a lot of enemies
please help has been posted since at
least 2002 and it was a copy pasta on a
journal
site help I'm helping I'm
helping why can I not drink these
drinks there we go
okay oh level up oh I I got a main quest
just from leveling up okay you ignored
the boss that we have to kill here in
the middle of the room I did not even
look at it did not even see it girl so
wait pre inter pre
internet it came out
2002 I'm helping I'm helping I'm helping
I'm helping okay
okay get away from
her oh that's a good heal Health tonic
thanks okay let's go let's go woohoo
okay oh I I pressed need on that I don't
need it what are you are you wearing
light armor or what I yeah I'm wearing
leather armor oh
okay yeah but I'm using the the set that
they gave us in the pack so I don't
really need any armor
oh what am I wearing I
wonder they put the they're like gift
boxes and then you can put them all
on need to take a closer look later
maybe you're
dying it's
fine it's not fine I'm okay be careful
if you die then you die it's not good if
I die I die in real life yeah it'll be f
f but real the embarrassment will kill
you why did you go into the bus with so
little
HP it's fine it's okay I don't know
about that what are I going to do kill
me help what is
this what he's de easy okay yeah I guess
I was fine but rol where oh Rolf is
outside well nice sick we're done it's
easy I love it you're you left with 450
HP I'm out of here I'm Turing this quest
in I got things I got to keep going I
got to keep going further and further
and further where's wolf here
Spence go to
Spence don't give me all the items I
feel bad for wasting
them
okay where's the auto sort wait what but
crazy I was crazy when was not something
created in uh uh not originally created
in response to the September Song right
no it's a copy pasta
from so long ago apparently did I have
to activate these I don't
remember I have to huh I didn't so far
have you been activating those
teleportation way
points no the big crystals you have to
yeah I I think so
cuz I clicked on it and it did like a
plum Plum Plum
sound oh well no time for that I love
these enemies they're so
cute a they they're like aren't they
like one of the mascots of the
game and gigy also has one running after
her I think oh yeah they are so cute M I
love how every every anime mmpg has like
one one in the game that is like kind of
their mascot so
cute where are the guides for this game
where do I put my
skills wait where wa I I I I thought
there's skill points and so on but in my
character thing I don't know where would
I be putting it where where do you where
do you give out skill
points yeah you found click on it it's K
button the K button ah there it
is okay yeah probably about time to
spend
some of these points I don't know either
uh I'm currently a Thief what is this
act why activate oh okay I am already
dead uh I don't know I don't I can't I
can't look at this now G is stressing me
out
wait rer from Lum and Vine Lum and
Vine I
he
okay here we go I You've Got Mail I've
got
mail I have money I have set Money G
this is my dream like just getting free
stuff in my favorite anime of
RPGs who's sending you male my fans girl
my fans oh my God so many
males was that a lot I'm not sure I
think that was maybe considered a
lot okay nice PE give her more no no
chill chill I I I don't have give her
cash up item now too I don't have use
for the money right now but yeah maybe
for
no but we have to make a sh
eventually so for the Guild creation we
need money I think I just got
glasses uh yeah wow so intelligent many
things I need to sell so much this get
out of here my eyebrows are so angry
angry
angry this can leave this can leave
[Music]
too copper mace by Sentinel dual pistol
wow
by
item
oh if I'm okay carrying where did she
not put that in here okay wait I can can
I also have a long range weapon in here
too h no okay not at the same time
okay is this
new ah that is maybe better than my
black Iron
[Music]
Ring this one
mhm go away go
away I wonder what if you like start a
different class what the best way the
level
is from level one without a
quest where's the leveling guys I think
no but cuz you have a character level
and then you have the class level so you
would just level where you would usually
level in your current like character
level
class and yeah then your level transing
your character level will go uh your
class level will go up pretty
fast okay um you're transforming what
I'm now a magician
what
suddenly becomes Mage with no
explanation let me
see yeah yeah yeah I used to be I used
to be cleric I think was I oh yeah
warlocks were so [\h__\h]
strong warlocks and what else I'm I'm
trying to be a blade down answer guys I
need Bard level 35 as well maybe I
should start on that now
too N I don't know then I got to become
a in order to be a Bart oh no I don't
have to be a cleric I just have to be
level 20 okay
cool what's
this what
this so many little Windows itty bitty
windows 8,7 151 remaining class
points there's so many I can't I don't
know what to do did we get class points
from one of the packs
or will I use these skills forever or
will I replace them with better
ones I'll probably I I won't use them
anymore when I become a blade Downer
right Max it all I guess what wait what
oh wait that's not is that
using ah
ah is this using my gold and this is
using my class
points am I using this h on the for
makes
invisible yeah
okay is this set now
s set okay it's got a flower thank you
person who sent me a flower someone sent
you a flower via
DM yeah in my little mailbox I already
forgot their name I'm sorry I want
this send another mail and I will send
back a thumbs up I also I got more
money 100 gold thank you crazy I was
crazy once and I got all cash items and
stuff mhm no not not yet we're not there
yet but this is like a dream fever
dream where am I with quests right now I
don't have a quest is it because I
reached level 15 why are you
16 I don't know I'm AFK trying to find
out what to use the skills
where's my next quest game tell
me where's the next main quest or is
there no more main quests there's a
quest here but that's not main
quest guys I hope youve been keeping
uh account of everything I'm I've been
rushing
through teleporting
through you must be aware of what's next
for me
uh unacquired
quests but these are not main quests are
[Music]
they
go
[Music]
H can you reset your skills does it
matter what what does he
want do I have to buy
something oh God I accidentally no
no I pressed Max on my
skill that's fine I did that too on
everything almost
everything what's with him what do I
don't I can't take a
whoa whoa I remember
this isn't there oh isn't there
something over
there oh beautiful oh hello Birds what
level are
you
one me no not you the enemies oh I am
level one oh yeah my magician is level
one no now you're already level three
oh you're zooming through oh look at
that
map where do I go I'm lost click
explation below your map for Quest and
my ah this one yeah aha oh we're going
back to
Aben sorry uh unknown you just came here
but we're already traveling
again okay I'm ready to travel I'm
collecting water in my water bucket what
your current Quest that you
have um I just finished a side quest I
think my main quest is I don't even know
I just finished the level 12 visiting
Aven
2 went back to the first city main quest
is level 15 I think I'm done with
visiting aen okay wait let me talk to
all these
NPCs wow I I feel so delighted talking
to these in insightful NPCs and not
listening to them at all yeah I'm not
reading I got places to be quest to
finish visiting aen
4 why is she
running why are you not
teleporting
girl
that okay thanks cool cool cool cool
cool all
right visiting aen
five sker
sker sker
sker I mean does anybody really reads
the quests in these kind of MMR pges
maybe there's some MMR pges where you
maybe get a little bit invested in the
in the quest dialogues and stuff like
maybe in Final Fantasy 14 but yeah I'm
not reading
most
MMOs it took me 3 years to read the
Final Fantasy 14 story wow that one I
mean I did listen to it too because it
had like these cut scenes and everything
that was definitely interesting but I
don't think even the creat creators of
the game probably don't even expect
anybody to read the class
today for the most part I feel like if
you're playing anime MMOs they don't
really expect you to read yeah it's nice
that they provide something to read in
case you want more than just a Mindless
grind yeah but I think we want a
Mindless
grind don't we I want a Mindless grind I
want a Mindless grind yeah she gets
it I'm I'm uh killing parrots right now
but it doesn't seem to be a main quest
why did I get into this what's my
problem with parrots what my unresolved
issue maybe I'm mad that we don't have a
parrot to to
yet
yeah damn these
parrots I'm so lost what am I doing this
this yeah I don't have this thing
anymore down here why
not where is my main quest
now have I activated
this there we
go and
uh I always read them but I know plenty
who
don't yeah yeah yeah FF I do think
reading is
recommended but I don't think anybody
judges anyone or expects anyone to read
the the quest iog with
these like games quests yeah and don't
ask me about this game I know
nothing why are we here what what are
their names I don't know
K you don't read anyways shut up I just
said that in Final Fantasy 14 I did
listen to the
story I did she'll read where she needs
to why do need to read and eat an
eternal sorry sorry I love your game by
the way Sor sorry sorry sorry game if if
I don't know if they're listening but
obviously I was very insistent on
getting the perms
yeah we're having a great time many
times we love it we're just not reading
we're illiterate yeah and now I really
don't
know I really don't know where where how
did you get that
quest which
one uh the next
one oh I don't know I've just been
picking things up as they popped up in
front of my face wait you've acquired a
new knowledge Point skill level has
reached maximum what are you saying move
that my skill level has reached
maximum oh wait Thief level 15 is maxed
or
something was that oh do you have to
level up other things too was fief Capp
at 15
really oh but I I mean Bard is only
starting from
20 oh it's your character level Max oh
yeah that's
wait how are you already 17
chill just do my character level not my
class level is Max
15 how do
I I guess you have to level more for
your character level and then your class
level goes up with
it but I guess what they're saying is
your class level can't be high or than
your character level maybe yeah yeah
yeah okay so my class level is currently
maxed uh
anyway I don't know where to
go does it show what quest are you want
nothing I don't have a quest does is
there like a thing that says pick up the
quest here or or available Quest above
the
Box um
no it used to have that little blue
exclamation mark on the map but now it
doesn't maybe if you go into your quest
log again like what you did in the
beginning and then it says um or you
untick it and then show all available
quests
a uh wait that's loog what was the
button for
it um
um that's not
it Alpha Quest yeah but
uh that's not the window I'm really
looking for also it says like it shows
me all the unacquired quests but it
doesn't are
the are the green ones main quests no
right cuz then why didn't I
[Music]
this green are daily blue okay where
where main quest though and where's the
main quest where you your screen too I'm
just hitting
crabs okay just smacking them I just go
back to aen maybe
[Music]
uh where is your quest that's strange
the rainbow fall Forest ones are the
main ones rainbow fall
uhhuh
ah
uh oh
oh okay
really
really didn't it always say
main all right there we go I got the
level 14 yay uh main quest to you're at
the level 15 one right mhm I like this
guy he looks
interesting
okay ah thank
you sometimes they don't give me the
next one and then it's like what what
where do I go now how where we
headed didn't I kill these already what
the heck
sorry I came back to bully you again
what is wrong with me why do I hate you
so much leave the wildlife alone it
didn't deserve this they really
didn't we're just
bullies wait oh lumy ly oh are you guys
oh wait what does this enemy remind me
again of um that rout
uh
ah shat will tell
me die MRA yeah
now okay now I'm at the level 15 the
relationship between yming and
colorful
waterfall uh I am
at oh same place at the waterfall I have
to
defeat Forest Giants have have you done
this stuff yeah I did that one I'll wait
for you I am at the level 17 Quest how
are you so ahead of me you also took
time to sort your inventory and
stuff I don't what happened
clicking I my I'm so my brain is so
wired to just keep doing the task if
they're in front of me so I was like
clicking on them and and you call
sasuga Forest Elders okay I'm going to
smack all these Turtles for
now
wa oh there we go that one's actually
called mandra GAA a huge
one kind of looks like fliff no fliff is
like one of like the first anime mm RPG
that I ever
played fliff yeah life of fun I loved
that one so
much yeah it's a really cute
game I
remember grinding that game and then
working so hard to get to level 20 just
so you could fly
yeah that was
incredible flying around
everywhere I think the models were
really cute yeah at the cash up items
and the cash up
items they need to give us more cash up
items and eat an eternal I want to spend
money but I want I want clothes I
want I feel like back in my day was this
was the snowboard outfit and Fly for Fun
or and eat an
eternal there was like this like certain
items were like the most popular ones
and I think the snowboard item was one
of them but that might have been Fly for
Fun
oh yeah five or five remember that yeah
the
Snowman the all the Halloween or not the
the Christmas outfits are so cool I'm
D all the cool kids had the snowboard
outfit
man let's go okay I am now atat SYM
level 16 guardian of the Rainbow Lake 2
Maine is this where you
are um
um I am one after I
think literally every player I run
across is in the kfp
[Laughter]
guild they like we have to band together
yeah what is that name I
impressive his name is IA Thea what do
you
mean he's going to cook you don't
rude no
respect I think the kfp guild should
become one of the top guilds in the
server and then you oppress wa so much
that she'll join your guild if you were
the number one Guild in the server
imagine if they still have the um like
there used to be some kind of like guild
war where
four of four was it like four of the
leading guilds or so they fight against
each other in this like uh
like they poured into this
field and the four Guild fight and then
there's one Guild winner like one wi
winning Guild which is like reported to
everybody like oh this is the the guild
that won and now they're like cool I
don't know yeahp
battle I wonder if that's still a thing
if we could get kfp to win that that
would be I'd be so honored but you guys
need to actually know how to play the
game if you want to win that trust me
you have to be pretty
op I mean you can be you can't get there
I'll start spending
money I believe in
you why' she refuse to um not enough
space in my
backpack okay and I so much
garbage the heck do I do with all
this Con one million views on Mirage
thank you we reached 1 million views
yesterday yay let's go let's go that's
so
epic stream
[Music]
Mirage she gets it so good I watch your
dance videos that you upload all the
time and I just
they're so cute how does this work do I
like oh I don't have to fight
them oh more brain empty stuff
nice ah but I still need crap meat have
you done the crab meat
already yeah girl I'm on the quest
after stop doing
things I'm currently inventory sorting
okay take your time with
it so much stuff in here stop stealing
my enemies okay why do I have such a
such a cute
umbrella how dare you outfashion
me are you getting my crap meat for some
reason I hope
not no I'm not I just got boots though
purple M
purple you got boots yeah you just gave
me boots boots I didn't okay now I got
crap
meat what it suddenly turned into a
mushroom did you do that Unown Unown is
my private personal
healer my heal [\h__\h] let's
go at least I have one I'm surprised
you're the only one who chose to be my
healer people don't want to play healers
in
MMOs you don't want to play healer I
want to play healer I used to want to
play healer but I like healer most
people like DPS though no I'm also
healer person disappointed in every
single kfp who has not chosen the role
of the Healer not chosen the world to
protect your
tental yeah imagine you join the same
MMO as kiaha and not picking a Healer so
you could follow her around like that's
so cringe yeah yeah
you have an
obligation you started up this game you
downloaded it you installed it you made
it an account you have an obligation to
protect me yeah now now you have
to how dare you follow your own selfish
goals of becoming a strong fighter in
this game you must be my
healer no just kidding I'm with the
turtles
now Turtle oh they're so big
looks like
dinosaur got to sell these
items you're no longer in an enur oh
wait my exp thing were off
not
no wait no no no no no go
away
no the
huh what was I
doing oh when I was going to activate
maybe
another exp
time y cuz I got to catch up you're
always two steps ahead of
me I think I'm looking at your your
Buffs I don't think you're using the 50%
one which one what 50% it looks like a
sun and it says 7 Day
you see it in your
inventory oh you might not have redeemed
it I I didn't open everything yet
because it's filling up my
inventory I think you need to find the
one that gives it and then in that box
it comes with a 10 20 slot backpack
too not sure
where I don't I
okay I got another backpack yeah that
might have been it it's something that
looks like a 20 slot one there's another
one here oh my god oh
another bag okay I have like several
seven slot
expansions but no 20 yet it came with
the one oh never mind what about this no
when you put the code in it should have
given you something I don't know if you
had toed it somewhere else but giv a lot
of stuff when you redeem the
code I redeemed the code and what did I
do then I don't remember
anymore did I get the thing where is
it that's strange Chad did I get the
thing after I redeemed the code I mean
Redeeming the code you guys didn't see
me do that but because a different
window opened
but did I get something after that I
already don't remember cuz the game is
giving me so many
things did you actually claim it from
the item Mall item Mall item
Mall item Mall don't attack me no leave
me
alone I oh yeah it might be the item
Mall how do you open the item mall again
should be I ah
uh oh yes there I see
it there it
is
[Music]
ah must wear Eternal growth armor
set
ooh
clo
o oh that was the wrong one
oopsie uh oh God my inventory is so full
here 20 slots
nice o why did I
open that one what are these things
Eternal Legacy weapon
pack B loot staff
axe dagger sword here this
one sword oh okay nice and a shield
Shield there we go oh yeah can't see it
but I have a cute let's go shade yeah
cute and then anything else and you use
the armor sets you can equip all of them
right now and they give a set bonus oh
and then there's the oric jewel I think
that's what you meant that looks like a
sun yeah
yeah uh set set sorry what set bonus set
bonus to S should be the armor set oh
yeah I was looking for the right one but
I I opened up the wrong
one forg Legacy armor said that's not
the right one it should be it says
Legacy no that's
heavy oh they have you can equip all
those right now so it goes in the the
slots and then stop taking up
space uh what the
heck what oh I I do I can't wear all of
them oh yeah but they're not like used
in that classy
mhm
damn cloth clo clo clo
see by the time I'm done with all of
this you're going to be like level
20 I'm just hitting crabs near
me what about weapons weapons I can only
have one
like okay
lever L Lev Lev
Lev
um
oh light armor light armor ah
night
armor uhhuh current equipment okay this
one's outdated this one's
[Music]
outdated this one's better although the
jungle coat looks cute but goodbye
goodbye
goodbye okay um should there also
be uh a head piece ah this one that's
that
[Music]
one
o sorry guys sorry chat this is taking a
while I'm confused there's so much stuff
what is this by the way is this a quest
item
okay am I missing so ah here it is oh
cute it's a little ah I have a bandana
now cute but here it looks like a little
tiger hat
thingy okay I
think I got everything settled leg
Legacy Legacy Legacy Legacy Legacy
Legacy Legacy Legacy leg
okay your are you around
me I no clue I have no clue
okay I'm I I killed the turtle
egg and I'm giving back the
quest and I I got rings I think or I'm
getting rings I want to sa Quest as you
now okay let's go defeat
Clooney all right I'm there I feel like
I used to have that AL
C yeah those those cooler alpacas they
have like this whole like uh
seat like looks like a frone it's
amazing when do we get it well I have a
normal alpaka for one day now but one
day is not enough one day isn't enough I
did a quest that gave me a permanent
alpaca but I accidentally archived it
and I don't know how to get it back what
it's gone now alpaca is gone now
H collect uh what how does this work a
there we go
wow look at this beautiful scenery chat
we need to appreciate when we're not
teleporting around we need to appreciate
the scenery for one
moment yeah back when you had to walk
everywhere and had to look at everything
didn't used to be like this yeah I did
appreciate the
scenery okay against the black toad free
main
quest I fear we will not really be doing
things together until we're going into a
dungeon again
mhm I remember this
a good old
times I am also killing frogs right now
oh okay so hopefully I I think I'm
getting your kill participation count oh
oh uh wait actually yeah I should be
killing a
wizard oh what
W
surprise it is
I okay reporting my
quest are you done too yeah yeah yeah
okay defeat water
pump I got to travel to all these
places uh let's defeat water pump where
is water
pump I'll just go here hello
is
this LOL I you
guys my poor healer constantly has to
figure out where I
teleported uh here I'll help you healer
since you're so
helpless or oh did you find the the
water pump and stuff I found one did you
get that oh yes I
did I I I see the other one I'll take
the other water pump okay and then the D
Bar
where's ah maybe he wasn't there when I
teleported there because yeah yeah he he
was not spawned yet but now he's spawned
I'm killing
him thata is a real MVP
yeah Kudos and
props wow we did it did something
together it's been a while teleports
away immediately
no so
depressing okay next let just make it so
easy to go places in this
game we're leveling up so fast we could
be max level in the near future what is
the current ma level actually do we know
is it 60 and probably not like let me
let me I 100 some now let me ask in the
world chat hello what is the max
level no I need a world call how will I
ask the people my
question I want to be the I want to be
the lowlevel noob asking questions in
the world chat and being ignored by all
the high level
players is it
90 90 we can get that easily
easily hey why do you have a world chat
thingy and wasting it to say something
you could have said in my stream
chat thank you 90 it wasn't 90 back in
my days I don't think back in my
day was much lower than that I remember
I wonder if this still exists I feel
like around the time when I quit eating
the tal is when they like on my server
implemented this like Sakura cherry
blossom tree island that you could
teleport to pretty sure that was cute
yeah it was so pretty and it was so
fresh and new and fancy
wow don't even remember what we did
there I feel like we just played
um oh it's a dungeon we just played hide
and
seek are you in a dungeon right now
nope I finished wait why did it leave me
here is he inside the dungeon the Del it
might be you can only I got distracted
by doing a quest by choosing a single
player dungeon oh okay so for real for
real ah he's in the
dungeon let me see are you coming to the
dungeon I'm trying why can't I finish
this Quest it says I'm stuck on the one
that says deliver Crystal pillar Shard
and then talk to him to
finish talk to who does s I feel like I
probably already did that why is it
broken why can't I turn this question
maybe it's not broken maybe it's just a
skill issue not enough space in backpack
it happens it happens
no get out of my
backpack so much
garbage was that the right one yeah got
to keep Mor's ring you know got to keep
engaged to
Mor or at some at some point I will
maybe replace it this has crit rate plus
six crit attack
speed HP MP is this better than my moing
ring kind of
not completely it doesn't have the
accuracy what about this
one okay this is this is like a healing
[Music]
ring M crit this is not what I
want why did I open that that's just
jamming up can I I guess I could just
archive these maybe I'll need them I
don't think I'll really need them will I
really need them probably not I'll go ah
this one though when I want to level
Bard probably the guitar guitar is for
The Bard I
think rid of
this okay okay
okay F Paka could carry some of the
sword no as far as I know the the mounts
cannot carry but eventually you'll
replace all of these seven slot
expansions with 20 slot backpacks and
then it's not big issue
anymore and at some point I don't think
you'll be spammed with items this
much when will I use all of this how do
I use all of this fast singing violence
attack oh
hello
welcome I'm going to die wait one one
don't run so fast wait let's do this
together I will die that is a promise
why you here some
die I'm no longer the class where I have
self-healing oh you had selfhealing and
you're still like kind of dying at that
point concerning W
wo I don't I don't need yeah we don't
need it looks nice
still look at us with our pretty
umbrellas so cute hard to see us from
behind the enemies will think that we're
just a like a clover flying around in
the Wind we're blending
in it hurts it's hurting girl girl it's
hurting me I think I'm like between us I
think I'm the tank now so always hand in
but don't overdo it s it hurts it hurts
you're like the lero Jenkins of this
group and
I find it amusing I'm pulling the ball
going
to my [\h__\h] stupid DD is pulling
the even though I'm the tank she's
ruining
everything tank tank they're damage
stealer doesn't understand who the tank
is tank what are you are you what are
you now Mage I'm a yeah I'm a mage
now okay and then you're really not
supposed to be like tanking what is this
something just popped up e activation
50% off I can spend money to get um what
is this oh enhan
Scrolls more enhancement Scrolls yay
yay well back in my days when I used to
play like Fly for Fun um do you know the
classes from Fly for
Fun I know them vaguely you know there
were two Mage classes um one was like I
think like Sai Sai something and they
were like it was like a oneon-one Mage
and then there was the AOE Mage which I
thought was super cool but most people
hated the class it was like
Elemental something and people hated it
it was kind of weak um but I liked like
healing for AOE people because it was
stressful cuz they were conly being
attacked by 50 mobs at once and
especially those like Elemental AOE
major whatever the class was they were
pulling like I swear like 60 of the
strongest mobs in one go it was just the
time of my life running after them were
always on the on the move like running
from the mobs while healing and this so
good I like moming classes a lot oh yeah
I just like seeing all of the monsters
on top of you and they just die oh what
is this oh
pistols wouldn't those be for you for
your other CL from my other class yeah
die one but in that case I guess the the
Mage was kind of tanking they had I
right those were like the
only Mages that were not completely
squishy because they did have quite a
bit of HP oh man good times I need
hunting the bow I don't really need at
all I'll GRE
that let's see who gets
it do you how much money do you you have
by the way I
have 30 gold okay I have 140
gold you need to be richer people need
to give you more money nah why are
people slacking on giving you money I
don't desire such a trivial unimportant
thing why are people not get give her
money now the in-game money what I
really desire something way less shallow
and that is Cash Up item
can you trade cash off items again I'm
guessing yes yeah if you I'm pretty sure
you can people are sell it on the
marketplace also like in the in aen wait
I have to reach level 19 BR why am I not
level 19 for yet let me kill these
mobs oh Prett close a less
shallow there's so much more depth and
meaning to cash up costumes that only
change your visuals okay
okay it it it there's a lot behind that
you
know I just can't explain it I don't
know you deserve cash shop item thank
you you too you too do you think you
want to like dress cutely or do you want
to be like
cool cute yeah
cute I want
cute me what are these astral
costumes no idea astral costumes what is
what is this ogre doing
here he's not even red he's
yellow hey this guy's not in the kfp
guild is he just a random leveling
[Music]
person I wonder then we're kind of
disturbing his piece maybe I'll go over
here
okay ever play Ragnarok online did I
play I feel like I did but some games
are kind of like Blurry to me some
memories
are I played five for fun uh trickstar
online e Eternal Aura
Kingdom um twin Saga o twin Saga was
cute uh and a bunch more I can't think
of right now I also played World of
Warcraft that was my first MMO RPG my
mom basically got me into the whole
family
play uh f for the whole family
yeah I was such a noob
though my chat are you dead hello Chad
what wake up
chat are you suffering
chat are you being silenced by
someone why am I not silencing you oh
I'm almost I'm almost level
up come
on oh yeah my chat is broken right now
no what's with this old girl YouTube
bring it
back oh chat is back
hello why did you why did you froze on
my favorite topic aka me telling you all
the games I played back in the
day you were going to you were supposed
to throw back and RPG names at me for me
to remember if I played them or
not blame YouTube okay why YouTube
why wasn't there Dragon Saga I I tried
that yeah I played it not very long
because I I wasn't like I don't know I
felt like I didn't have a community if
there you played nost tail nost tail I
know it but I don't think I played it it
wasn't very popular in like the
German M refug Community I think at Le
that was my
impression Dragon play and soul yeah I
think I played that two and then there
was this one game uh what was it again
where like you would wait to get into
the server like a whole day a whole week
and it was really like you have to be so
lucky to get
in and then when you were in it was like
the laggiest piece of [\h__\h] ever uh I
guess that could apply to a couple of
games
I many a lineage yeah all of those kid
SRO yeah I think for what I'm
remembering was maybe particularly Silk
Road or
so I love Silk Road oh I was yeah all of
those games had problems with their
servers Z is so awesome I always imagine
it when I close my eyes and think onl
yeah did you get it to the server you
hacker I don't know why am I barely
getting exp are these what are what
level are these oh they're on my level
though there we go
oopsie oh yeah Final Fantasy 14 I play
too of course yeah yeah yeah and
um just gave me a backpack
Seven slots or
what no like like a cosmetic backpack oh
oh who gave
you f I think I got no from this Quest
oh nice good job quest thank you for
your
kindness Fantasy Star online a yeah
that's yeah PSO uhhuh uhhuh PSO 2 I
played as sponsorship
right good times good
times I like PSO but it's so I feel like
it's kind of dangerous to um stream
because of people's custom messages you
know like people can draw whatever art
they want and then put it in your chat
yeah and then they can make a naked
woman if they wanted to if they really
wanted
to oh AB noi I played like for like one
or two days but I don't think I knew
anybody else playing it and I just felt
like kind of
lost oh finally level up to 19 was I
supposed to be 19 yeah
okay all right oh I'm selecting a quest
reward you finally cheaping out and not
giving me every single weapon oh these
are we did it we grew up they don't have
to give us handouts anymore they don't
even have the weapon that I need
they just have a dagger I need a sword
who do you think I am I'll take it I'll
take
it okay wonderful Ultima Online oh that
sounds familiar
[Music]
too
oh vindictus vindictus I don't know
that's one that I I don't
know okay what are you doing KY staring
at this thing that just popped up on my
screen okay it looks like what popped up
this time what is this oh this I see the
wings that we saw like the red Phoenix
wings it says day two I think we have to
top up to get
it pop up with some real money yeah
we're going to have to use some real
money so we can get this proceed to top
up I think I'm really going to like
inquire
about cash up item
rotation oh no actually that would be
insane if they like changed their plans
for
me that would be improper
maybe it just told me I am ineligible
for purchase please contact customer
service for assistance yeah I had that
too like I had submission like that too
I couldn't
pay why why want our money why you don't
want our
money why are these not counting a did I
kill long man Puma oh there we
go I
remember something weird in my Eden
Eternal times once upon a
time I I was like just chilling and I
met a player that was somehow like quite
the underdog like
very like I don't know had all of the
cash up items you could imagine and was
selling cash up items for gold in World
chat all the time eventually like I I
think I only got to know that person
because I bought some cash up items off
of them with my gold and but they had
like everything and then I think we kind
of became like in-game friends
and
because I was so well liked I think
eventually I think I found out that they
were able
to H what was that this is so blurry in
my mind but I think they were like
either secretly a GM or connected to a
GM and could
spawn cash up items all they wanted what
am I remember what is this I don't know
anymore well maybe that's really
um I I no the GM Island story is a
different story that's a Fly for Fun
story
God you guys think that was a hacker cuz
honestly at the time I I really did not
understand I really thought they had
some special ties I think they also told
me to like keep it secret or
so I was just like oh oh my God I made
some great connections like I'm give
a don't let anyone know I'm doing this
wiing your face I I think they were
saying like don't tell anyone that this
is my secret like private account cuz
I'm a GM and
I want to have some private play time
where people aren't disturbing me but
that might have very well been [\h__\h]
that could have been a
lie oh
no oh no what have I
done no I believe in them they were
actually a
GM could be you know you never know with
the DMS cuz they felt cool with their
status some of them they were like GMS
and then there were like some kind of
helper GMS I think who weren't as
powerful as the others but they were
like definitely trying to flex with
their stat with their status okay I'm
back to the Pumas why we're out of
portal Stones they took it away from me
Nan portal Stones you once you get level
20 you can't free teleport
anymore I don't know how I get anywhere
by
myself do I even have any where are
they where my now you need a nice
[Music]
Mount do I do I
move it says it has used auto route for
your destination but it's not even Auto
routing me why am I not
walking these boots I made for walking
[Music]
that's this is not as
good I feel so
betrayed
[Music]
1,217 not stronger is
it
no I got some guns are these the ones
that were supposed to come to you but
we'll always find better ones I
guess a
[Music]
guitar 92
no bunk
[Music]
Hammer security col
less
axe
staff what do I do with all these things
chat what do I do with all these
enchants do I even need them Can I stack
them are these are any of these
stackable why don't they
stack level one level two
great
ah fast singing
no they they won't
stack um wow
okay
wow
goodbye
100,000 goodbye trash them sell or trash
are they all trash are they really
useless for me I don't know
maybe they are maybe some of them are
nice I don't remember the whole like
upgrading system that well
anymore so I'm not sure anyway let's
continue Quest I am so lost now that I
have to
walk why will it not Auto well now we
cannot be so spoiled anymore we have to
enjoy our time riding on our beautiful
alpacas whatsoever can't believe this ah
you want to file a
complaint if you file a complaint maybe
I lose my perms that I worked so hard
for I will be filing a complaint no
you're going to lose me everything how
do I work wa Stone Elder are you st
you're Stone Elder
okay no but you're not the one you are
the one I'd like to speak to your
manager I'm so surprised that this game
was like
revived anyway I'm so happy I'm so glad
people understand that there's a demand
for these nostalgic games to come
back there's still people who want to
play it just like me and gy
yeah okay
I I guess this is why you have to use
the portals yeah so you can I've also
ignored some of them and forgotten some
of but yeah have you not activated a
single one I haven't activated a single
one oh yeah it's also telling me to buy
something remaining 16 minutes 50% off
hot well I would buy maybe if I were
able to put money into this I got I'm
getting the backpack
too did I activate the stone in
here surely there is a stone in here a
teleportation Stone
oh yeah I see it on the map where is it
it's like up
there can I is there invisible wall or
[\h__\h] I'm walking I'm on my way
back I I'm about to finish the
selfimprovement free quest which is
reach level 20 and then talk to
someone okay base Crystal activate come
on is this not a teleportation
Crystal I believe my current Quest is
level 19 knowing one of the mountains
and that's the main
quest okay level
19 yeah you're behind me on a quest for
once I'm on my way slowly walking as
fast as I
can okay well I'm level 20 now too so I
guess I'll you know have that issue as
well backpack
um what am I
[Music]
doing what I I wanted to open this one
Goa not really gotcha but oh I got the
world call messages now I can write
something in the world chat like stream
Mirage or something stream Mirage
um did I get anything interesting
I have to go attuned to this
Crystal are attacking Sana mayor Pier is
asking everyone for help oh my God
what's happening oh oh there's so many
Zone attacks going on but I don't
care CU I don't know where they even
really
are are these all main quest
this are they all main quests ah I think
I know now where you got the alpaka the
the forever alpaka from I haven't done
that Quest yet it shows up for me now
let me do that really
quickly collect ancient alpaka food
recipe eh from what talking to
you the treasured seed
formula ah they need food they need to
be fed
unbelievable I know they're so greedy
how dare they they should just eat the
grass that we're walking
on where did that even go oh
nowhere
uhhuh
okay people come here to relax nice but
uh where is my
alpaka where is it I already received
it I already received it now I throw
away this one day
alpaka goodbye one day old alpaca I feel
bad you're just throwing it on the
ground I just threw it out of my
inventory even though I used it once and
it's already attached to me mentally she
just a I I just destroyed its existence
didn't abandon it it just doesn't exist
anymore how
CA okay now I have I have two level 20
quests how to assign work and heroic
traes
[Music]
resel
H I will do whatever the quests are
telling me to
do what is this wherever it is sending
[Music]
us I finally made it back to where
supposed to be I think well I still
don't have to pay for my
portals so zero P
Stones what is going on
here what are we doing
here
uh what's like uh what was
uh oh I'm making him work do I have to
come back here four 5 minutes did you do
this like weird farming Quest yeah I did
the weird farming
Quest did you finish
it yeah you just walk around and talk to
the people in that town and then you set
the things a I think I'm doing
it right the quest
I am now on understanding the mountains
part two it happens when I'm level 21
okay oh oh something spawned and is
attacking
me oh okay but that gave me what I
[Music]
needed now I have to wait so
long will they give it to me
automatically when they're done
gy um yeah you see the the orange scroll
the bottom right yeah yeah that's where
you can redeem it
okay so it's okay to leave the
area my alpaca is so
cute friendly
Alpa proceed to talk po up I wish I wish
I I
wish wow this cooking you see the wing
WIS that's where the people are getting
the wings not
[Music]
fair wow no but I just I don't want
these item oh what is that cute paperino
okay
cute but what I really want is an
outfit you cute did you see the pop
arino it is really cute
[Music]
a okay stop selling me
things um I think I did all the quests
I'm just waiting for
the crafts to
finish how how do you get more of these
portal Stones I thought it was just like
um
you need to buy them where cash shop
cash shop oh no no I'm fine generally
I'm fine with traveling everywhere from
now on this is how it shall
be no it doesn't have to be like this
you spoiled should be like this you
spoiled little
brat ouch something is hurting me in my
fum what what is it Splinter yeah it
feels like a splinter but I I mean as
per usual with splinters I can't see
it but why I just wow how evil
indeed you ever get the splinters where
you have to dig underneath your skin to
get it
out I think probably one time time I did
but it's been so long I don't really
normally get splinters it's been a
while but every time it happens I know
that I want to
die you
know doesn't it so painful though it's
underneath your skin and you're just
like you're digging downwards you're
like oh my God it's the worst
ever what is this a small
course to safe for oh without any
penalty oh nice have to run
[Music]
everywhere
whoa he's got a pumpkin thingy
nice
cute that's not even a kfp right oh what
the heck what is there I don't see
anything in my
Thum h
let's check out the cash shop while
we're chilling let me show you guys the
few uh fashion items they have right now
um it's not much but see uh okay I'm
mounted right now oh my God you can see
my panties when I'm mounted like this oh
my God stop cover up uh your leg
help okay so this is what it looks like
this is like the yukatas they call them
kimonos but this is really not a kimono
it's more like a Yukata but okay then
there's these cute uh head Wings this is
so cute it's like a mouth it's a head
item you have it in your mouth it's a
chocolate ala popsicle right and these
crosses they yeah okay my hair is
messing it up but I remember these These
are pretty cool um oh lazy Corgi oh my
God that is so cute a big po arino on
top of your head do you see this so cute
his butt oh I didn't see his butt hole
oh my God I like the head Wings a lot
too I think they're really cute n I'm
not a big fan but this dress is all
right like they don't Dr many choices
with for dresses but this is nice if we
combine this with maybe the bunny
backpack and maybe a different hairstyle
if I had
one um wow wow that is aesthetic the
bow overlay for your weapon even if you
don't use a bow you can use
this okay there's more yukatas and stuff
there's a
car that looks okay I'm not a big fan
that is a
car and that's it they don't well how do
they want to make money they need to put
more stuff in
here I need more stuff
where do I okay so the other way to
getting other items would be buying all
like on the market place I suppose like
uh from real people playing this game
who are selling some of their cash up
items but they're going to how much do
they want make it really expensive yeah
they're like oh she wants this we're
going to how's the expensive with 143
gold can I you know what the kfb G Guild
should pay me um like a weekly amount of
money everybody needs to like taxes you
know they need to be collected and they
need to be paid out to me so that I can
buy these
items I don't know how the economy is in
this game right now like how much do I
need is this a lot is this too little
can I buy things with that yes if you
want to be in the guild you must pay 10
gold a
day every single person no wait I I
think I'm not thinking of taxes I'm
thinking of um well it t
TI what's the word
t I think that's the word is is it
correct t
t is that the same thing as
taxes collection you're in some way you
know so I shall be collecting
that I shall make use of my
[Music]
[Laughter]
following guys you guys do some research
about the economy okay the the game has
a a Discord e the channel they have a
Discord can you go and like find out how
the economy is doing and let us know
please thank you and yeah see if
anybody's selling some cute outfits I
might like have you guys on the lookout
I wish I could join the Discord wish I
could
join yeah you how good you have it why
did you become so big is there why why
does this keep happening why oh wait I
also have the reason with not enough
portal Stones now where am I going now
oh you're right here I cannot teleport
anymore maybe I can buy some portal
Stones I thought you said you're okay
was walking no I was that a lie no no
no do I have to read to receive this
Alchemy tool oh you're
here it's walking time is this another
one of these crafting things yeah how
does this work how do I collect Aly to I
think we could give him a crafting
assignment here we go uh what do I put
in though ah wait ah there it is it
should be in green yeah yeah I dare I
didn't see it I'm blind
request why are they making us do so
many of these quests now I want to kill
things gur
gur oh nice that was at least created
immediately
[Music]
okay
um ah I have no Quest oh is it because
you
couldn't what happened H is this a main
quest that's not main
quest am attempting to do these Quest
where is this you cannot find path to
gos mountains well God damn it you have
to use the teleportation Rock to get
back to the main continent before it
auto pass uh okay where where was it
again over
here right is that it yeah oh there's no
stone who stole the stone yeah I forgot
where the stone is too where is it I
mean this one's
broken there should be a stone thanks
for the memb 50 memberships wow wow wow
wow wow is are we in oven right now
where is the
stone a a so pretty
[Music]
here a good
times i s i I hit a gigantic pumpkin on
accident now he's going to kill me help
help me I'm Sorry by the way I'm so
sorry
here um what was it again it was like
um was it
here where was it again here here here
wow 600
gold 600
gold egg that's small how do
I I teleport out of here golden
alpacas he cute a pck a
banner where are the um where are the
wow where are the
outfits is a tele pation Rock in this
town I'm so
lost where out of your
[Music]
WS I can't see them are they in a
different shop was it you do you have
different
things no chicken tie ped nuggets and
Phoenix
burgers thank
you and normally here when you go to the
server number one there's people sitting
around right right here and they all
have like shops open and some of them
are selling cash shop items too I bet
they have fashion people can buy yeah
what have you checked your mail has
anyone sent you anything in game oh yes
oh my god oh let's [\h__\h] go oh I got a
flower
bouquet I got HP potions cuz they're
apologizing that they're not a
Healer uh oh 25 slot backpack expansion
yay 25
gold and wings golden
wings I got Wings let's
go oh let's go wow wow wow wow
wow your wings nice and this is in
instead of my umbrella I guess yeah
nice yeah give me give me wa so much
bigger in my inventory is so
big okay wonderful now I thank you for
your
ties um going to
check where to go
next ah does it at least show where the
quest is closest to it doesn't really
does
it I'm trying to find the warp portal I
think I finally found the warp
portal yeah yes
I found it the warp portal is this where
I'm going to here we
go gos
mountains what quest are you
on um my main quest is understanding the
mountains part
three is my current
Quest
h Huh
I'll try to get there too
eventually gos
mountains I don't have portal Stones
anymore got a got a how far is the one
I'm currently following I wish I wish it
would show me where I'm
going where am I
going do should I perhaps stop here to
activate the tele
portation why is uh this
not where is teleportation
point off this
Mount is the
balloon is it the balloon icon I thought
it was these
crystals there's no balloon
here okay I'm ready to kill
you're ready
to I am ready to kill go
somewhere where I am
not yes so many
kfp what are you killing I dare some
rocks does that not show on the map but
obviously every little village has one
of
these
okay
now that is activated oh this guy is
here
here I thought he would be further away
nice so let's follow your quest you said
understanding the
mountains go go
go if I were to know one of the
portals that there there's the guy I
wonder if the alpaka would lead me
through the portal or if it would just
walk the whole way over continents it
walks the entire way instead of the
portal oh so it would be good to know
the name of the regions and stuff that
we are traversing through and I can't
believe to find out the stuff now ah
well I am also now doing the thing you
are doing wonderful
[Music]
yay except you are done it seems I I am
done I will wait I'll I'm somewhere it's
my inventory close okay
on my
quest go gy what's going on in your mind
oh stream Mirage stream
Mirage my head now I just going to ask
like generally what's up with you how
are you doing are you stressed are you
okay I think I'm really head empty right
now head empty in general in general wow
that's a a good somewhat good State
there could be worse state of Minds to
be in there could be much worse states
to be but right now I'm just head empty
okay
nice are your are your head thought full
head full thoughts
um I don't know I'm feeling like my neck
is killing me for a while and I googled
um at what point uh it should be
concerning if
a if a pinch is still there after
several days or weeks like at what point
it should be concerning and it seems
like maybe it's already
concerning oh that sounds that does
sound concerning right um so that's
concerning and
annoying and but besides that I just
realized it's November and that's
stressing me out because that's that
means it's almost the end of the year
which it really shouldn't be very
stressful like why are we already there
at the end of the year I know October
went by so
fast not just soon before you know it
it's going to be 2025 yeah don't please
stop I hate
it you have what are your New Year's
resolutions I don't really have I
haven't thought about it yet because I I
haven't had time to think about it yet
I'm still like with my mind I'm still
around like my birthday or so in
July like my
anniversary it really does feel like the
year just
started but the year so it's
gone It's So Gone Girl what are we
supposed to do 2025 will be better we'll
have so much time in 2025 you're lying
you're lying every freaking year since I
joined became busier and busier and this
year's summer was like the worst for
me so
no no you'll be less busy and you'll
have so much time for yourself and to
play Eden Eternal in
2025 really yeah sounds promising I mean
I like last year I thought that this
year I would be less busy because at
some point I realized oh they're not
doing Holo life summer so like last year
we had a a whole life summer concert
that added to all the other stress this
year we didn't have that but then I had
World Tour now I'm saying this year I'm
saying well next year surely I won't
have World Tour what else could there be
but then in my mind I'm thinking what if
there's a Revival of Hol of Summer again
next year there might
be I can totally see that no don't think
about the future think about the
now but weren't you telling me I should
look forward to
2025 look forward to 2025 but only
January 1st right but you know and then
I need to welcome uh the possibility of
a Revival of whole life summer because
you know that means Justice in
swimsuits
oo that does mean Justice and swimsuits
oh my
God no don't think about it think about
the right now it's eating Eternal time
no no no I want to think about Justice
and
swimsuits M that's too far away it it's
no 2025 is so far in the world chat
Justice and
swimsuit shut up shut up girls and guys
we are in the in a game and we need to
behave and not write random stuff in the
world chat these people don't what about
the everyday people that play Eden
Eternal they have no idea what's going
on like who are these people why do we
see so many people running around on
server
4 what is this new guilt that is like
going up in the
ranks what's going
on now they probably don't even notice
that there's people running around on
server 4 because we're all in the noob
regions and they're not in the noob
regions well well well cactus fruit from
Cactus okay I remember this portal I
remember these dinosaurs I remember the
scenery I barely hear this kind of
nostalgic feeling from you today even
though you said you played to max level
back in the day I I think when I play
games like this my brain goes so
empty understandable I feel so smooth R
right
now why don't you appreciate this I
appreciate I'm having a a good
time and being smooth brain it make me
happy you
know
understand I love the feeling that we
are progressing very we're getting there
someone just gifted me a spooky
Halloween Mount and this is awesome wow
really I also got one and I got taxes 50
gold and the Spooky it's so is it is it
is it a purple
alpaka it is it's so cute but I'm
ditching my alpaka again but this one
it
flies it flies and it has it has 10%
more movement speed than the basic
alpaka get out of here so cute I dropped
don't drop it don't Dr I I dropped it
without checking for sure if this is not
like time limited but no it's not oh my
God amazing you gy do you know that I
actually collect like alpaka like
plushies and figurines and stuff oh my
guys even have alpaka wool blanket and
stuff alpaca s plushies all kinds of
what call yeah there's like these
typical wellknown plushies I think but I
just collect any kind of alpaka things
they're so cute this is amazing oh look
at it
go do you have a photo of your alpaca
collection I can take one but um the
truth is I also like lost and and threw
away a couple of the big like the really
big ones first of all because some of
them I had in Japan and I had to leave
Japan and I couldn't like bring
everything um and also just like when
I'm uh when I moved from like my like I
had like a roommate thing before I um
joined
Holo so when I I would so okay I lived
in Japan right uh for like a year during
the time when I joined Holo and um why
why am I using this all pck oh it's
bound to
me okay never mind um so that's was like
one year and before I went to Japan I
lived with the roommate and when I was
going to come back I was going to just
go back to living with the roommate
because I was still not going to have
like lots of money to live alone
probably but when I came back I had this
new job AKA H life and so I lived like
maybe one more month at the place with
the roommate and then I was like okay
I'm out uh I'm getting my own place Yoo
and then I
yeah and I just left them my roomate my
besy my girl who took care of my cats
for one year that crazy girl forever I
shall be grateful to
her so yeah so kind where was I getting
with this gy they they kept the alpacas
I'm guessing no no they didn't keep it
but like when I moved then I also had to
like just downsize a little bit I
thought okay I'm going to get rid of
some of my biggest craziest plushies
because
this is just too much but I've had so
many alpacas over my
lifetime they are so friendly looking I
like their long neck they're so friendly
looking looking and one SP spat me in
the face before a baby
alpaca it was very friendly
indeed well at least it was cute it was
so [\h__\h] stinky you have no idea that
stank was so hard to get out of my
body incredible stank it was disgusting
I feel like I can imagine it like you go
into a barn and you're like oh my God so
many cute animals but they smell
terrible yeah and the stupidest thing is
I got kind of scammed because this baby
alpaka there was a staff I was on the
alpaka farm and there was baby alpacas
and when you go to the staff they like
let you hold the baby alpaka so oh my so
cute that's why I was interacting with
the baby alpaka in the first place but I
think when he was like trying to give it
to me that's when it spat me in the face
and I like kind of dodged it but it
still landed on me on the side of my
head yeah and now it's a core memory it
is it
is it sure is no I hate ELP just kidding
I love them
so defeat did you still get to play with
it after it spat on you I hated it and I
did not want to get close to it anymore
because I thought okay you hate me I
should you know I should stay
away oh you're you took it as a message
yeah I mean you know it was probably
scared so that's what if he meant it in
a good way there there's no good way no
no you don't think you don't think he
meant it in a positive way no has an
animal ever like done something like
this to you like attacked
you no I don't think I've ever gotten
close to something that could spit at me
would you take it in the good good way
you
think I I would
try I would do my best would you take it
in a good way if I spat at
you
yes I would take that in a good way how
I thought you would say that I'm like gu
yeah
okay but I don't want to SP that you
don't worry I would you do it to me in a
positive way if you were to do it if you
ask me for it and if it really makes you
happy I could consider it but I would
also question your
sanity are you okay okay I'll keep that
in
mind not saying I will ask for it but I
I will keep this in
mind you're so interesting and I like
it thank you I'm just running around
with this huge flower bouquet
now but how where can I switch out like
I want to use this from now on where can
I switch that out trying to figure out
how to get this Cactus oh I found it is
it here where do I switch out my alpaka
I already threw the one into the void no
why is it here um there's like I forgot
where was never mind never mind I think
I'm good oh I had another I don't know
where it came from but I had another
alpaka
goodbye why did I
walk ah
um this is better still not better but
I'll choose it anyway wait a second
where I let me put this here he's so
cute it makes me so
happy c m and games make me so
happy thank you for the beautiful gift
than
you oh I have more mail I got more gold
they have to pay their their TI yeah how
do you how do you guys get so much
money have you what what are you
doing are you stealing money they're
offering their soul to you I accept
it my thought I had you guys' souls for
a long time already cupus beats you're
standing in the NPC
[Laughter]
okay defeat gun RX7 9 defeat Robo
vt80 these sound like PC parts and like
microphones and stuff yeah these aren't
real things H what is this what's just
doorbell noise oh my commission oh I
heard it
too is your commission finished I had a
commission a commission I don't know
maybe it was just a notification maybe
it's just telling me about the cash up
things ding dong no is the Discovery
messages on in the middle of the screen
no no it sounded different than
Discovery message I no clue what it
was oh here we go do you have good good
drama stories from playing MOS back in
the oh trust me I was um always
surrounded by drama but uh I mean that's
so long ago I really don't remember it
but I I I a guil
drama not just in like no not just in
the guild there was drama everywhere I'm
in the
dungeon why am I in part of the main
story quest uh
yeah are you in a dungeon I'm dying
no I I must ask for your
assistance oh I will try what is that oh
maybe why is she not attacking wait why
don't I have that Quest
is it a main quest yep uh one of the
Shale Cavern level 21 okay I'm going to
wait here for you okay I want a level 22
M what did I just do my my main quest is
level 22 you told us a couple years ago
you got bullied out of maple story um I
didn't get bullied out of maple story I
didn't play maple story really I think
maybe I just tried it out but I got I
think I got bullied out of e
Turnal
actually yeah which is the sad thing cuz
I really LED eat an
[Music]
eternal I was just um too
cute how would they do that to you I
don't know I don't even
remember it's just
drama everybody the drama yeah those
people they just loved drama was weird
drama yeah I remember playing
um 14 a couple years ago and joining a
random Guild and then I I like remember
stories of like the guild leader
cheating on her husband oh oh that so
being passed around I was like what is
going on oh
no that is dramatic yeah when you play
like MMORPGs with like your
significant other that is very dramatic
I
guess yeah I think it was like you find
your partner then cuz I I would assume a
lot of these people are finding
themelves in the game and that just like
is asking for drama
mhm I think it's cuz she was like a
military wife and then she was playing
XIV A lot and so her husband isn't like
home
14 yeah who says that is that what they
say that's I I say it
oh hey we're on the same level actually
for once are you coming into the dungeon
or what I have no idea where this Quest
is like I don't have oh wait no I see it
I have it I have it now I'm on my way
yippe what is this by the way have you
seen the path of
Destiny I looked at it briefly and then
how do I
please roll the
dice you can't control ah cuz I'm in the
dungeon but I think generally moving
around and doing quests and stuff makes
you able to roll the dice so we'll try
it
outside okay talking to this
thing you ever played yes I did I've
already told you I'm here many
okay let's go life for fun was the best
thing
ever
this let's go I already cleaned up the
first couple of
enemies what is this way do I have to
inspect us I did not mean to warp on top
of them help help
uhhuh I'm coming it's fine I killed them
huh
yay we're strong you gave me the
illusion of needing help I thought I
did okay okay floof because in German we
called it floof because the Y is like in
if it's in a position like that it's
pronounced like an O floof floof floof
floof it's cute pronouncing it like that
is
cute you're now qualified to start a
guild oh yeah with level 20 I can start
a GU
I don't know if we should make our own
Guild or if we should just like become
the leaders of the kfp guild we take it
bro we just take it they raised it we
take it they prepared it they held it
warm and then we take over obviously
like what and then we demand to them
they give us not my fault yeah not my
fault that I we go into this game and
they already have a guild I was thinking
we were going to make a guild and invite
everybody not my fault that they were
like ahead of us a few steps it's really
you your guys's fault they they prepared
it which I really appreciate you know
good job for preparing
it okay away from me security
giant he's strong is he no not really I
guess and then whoop I don't remember
this dungeon at all weird I don't really
remember this
either maybe actually ah this Parts
feels a little bit familiar but this
part also remains me reminds me of uh
Wind
Waker like this room reminds me of wind
wer the alignment what the hell why does
it sound like that it's really
loud okay it's stop so greet
that yeah me
I don't know which part hostile takeover
it's not a hostile takeover it's an to
be expected
takeover meant to be Destiny takeover
yes you should have known that it would
be taken from
you don't have enough
MP oh oh now I'm running into MP
problems do you need pots no I can use
mine okay used them before what's going
on
[Music]
here how do we do we just run through oh
we
do robo VTO a zero is here chaos Fury
what a name oh I remember this
part let's go I didn't know it was a
level 20 dungeon though
Oo we shall wait where did my pots go
did I just throw all my pots
away but by
accident no there they
are yay I don't need this no
goodbye okay we made it while we did a
dungeon together another one we did it
we're so
good get me out of this
dungeon
I is it because inventory full no what
do you want select the quest I'm I'm
choosing Quest
I need to talk
to a
guy is he at the beginning of the
dungeon
[Laughter]
no these mobs just ignore me ignore
me a
no never knew Eden etern was still alive
it died but it was revived at some
point where are my family
kfps what is the pier chat who who's
able to see the pier
chat trying to my inventory is full
again what can I get rid
[Music]
of but then I have to walk all the way
to the front again too
right wa where is he he's in what he's
outside no why was he outside oh
no
no have to go back inside the dungeon
will the will the will the enemies be
there no he's right at the beginning if
it's the first guy you have to talk to I
talked to him okay I'm fine the enemies
didn't
respawn
okay they're running around though
looking for me the remaining ones
oh G mhm you said three
hours right yeah is it leaving
time we can play a little longer really
we are we are playing again next week so
no worries but will you be playing off
stream will you be grinding at all will
you
be
maybe okay we have to set each other
like a Max though
like go don't go further than
this so that we can play together again
okay don't go further than level 40 okay
okay
okay but gigy next time do you want to
open a POV or so like I don't know why
you didn't do one yet this time but oh
lazy you are running around a lot on
your own so maybe people want to see
your POV they want to see my POV I'm
sure they want to see your
PO okay maybe next time what is
this what where am I running did you do
the I don't know if I want to join right
now cuz like are you guys going to be
like really noisy in the in the guil
chat I was asked to join the quiet
down I'm going to be so noisy and
spammy take the lead of
but that's not but I won't be the only
one doing invites right I I don't want
to do any invites you guys have to take
care of the invites like inviting more
care of
people that's your guys's
job oh I walked all the way to the back
to enter the exit the dungeon again was
that so
necessary go go go on your Mount
girl well uh invite me again at the end
maybe I'll think I mean I think it will
end up like that anyway but somehow I'm
hesitating right now I'm not ready to
commit
yet not quite ready yeah she needs to
see what you have to offer I want to
feel free a little bit longer you know
yeah you can't tie her down yeah you
can't even though I said it's my guild
she's a free
spirit I'm I'm glad you like the game so
much that you're thinking of grinding on
your own gigy I just feel like it's a
waste of our our sun thing you know it's
7 days and it'll probably keep going
while we're offline oh true will it yeah
I think it will I think I think it will
go when we're Offline that I'm like we
should play maximum value true true
[Music]
true you summon
machine why why would I summon this
thing in the middle of the city oh is
this protecting the city
now interesting
M who of y'all actually play this I am
making them actually playing this and
I'm making them become really invested
into it this and the story and the and
the and the more than everything they're
becoming hopefully invested into the
economy everyone is playing it and
they're enjoying it I can tell why does
she not go on the freaking alpaka on her
own there's a story no I she's not
independent enough I didn't really mean
that but I'm I'm looking forward to
seeing um my kfp chickens getting
married in the game can you imagine that
always in hold weddings we should hold
really Grand
weddings and I shall be the
officiator H see them get married but
everybody who wants to get married has
to pay 100 gold you can like uh the
couple together can pay it so one can be
50 the other one can be 50 so you have
to pay for it and I must officiate it
and it can't just all happen like
whenever you want it we have to you know
plan it and we can do a mass wedding if
there's many
applicants But first you have to of
course collect the
money sounds like a scam no no no no no
out there in the real world these
wedding appriciate this they don't do it
for free do they
yeah you have to pay kiaa if you want
her to be at your wedding yeah this is
not a cult by the way not at all mass
wedding is a cult what do you mean I
don't know what you mean at
all this is not a thing a cult will
do if I were a cult uh leader
um then I would be I don't know what
would I be
doing I would be forcing you guys to
give
[Music]
me I don't even know maybe maybe I would
make you guys pay me money for weddings
give her more
items no it's okay I have
plenty what's in your
mailbox good stuff wait I got something
I got a cluing box
cute I literally can't equip these this
item where did you get it from oh I
think they're showing you the that you
can do did I just get 500 gold what the
hell why did you get 500 gold and what
is
this what is this
huh how do I take
this is it gone maybe I is this just the
remaining thing what is
that H what is this is this just what is
is this just empty don't
understand uh what did I get from you
guys I said
Dr
[Applause]
cute oh and it's because it's purple
it's matching with my
alpaka and I have some crazy panties so
cute
oh is that the
gacha the gacha you opened the box and
got a gacha I think it was a gacha item
I'm looking more and more like a cult
lter as I should
be was look kind of cute with the
backpack but my hair is covering it up
um if anybody finds a um
hairstyle
uh thing I can pay for it I have have
873 gold I don't know where it came from
it's weird but some of course I can pay
for
it let me know I think they used to have
hairstyle uh thingies as well hairsty at
well not right now in the cash up right
now they don't have
any
sad I have a bunch of quests that I
can't figure out how to finish
it side quest
or yeah I have some side quests when I
click on it it doesn't route me towards
where I want to go
a
mysterious
a didn't that M have F no I already took
it oh what this one oh my God
what I have girl I have
1,300 is that a lot is that is that a
lot in this game maybe
maybe it
is but uh maybe not
like if they can already be like level
90 I feel like back in my days maybe it
would have been a lot of money but now
it maybe maybe it's I don't know how
messed up is this
economy how messed up is it where is
this I have to go to
3021 97 they want me to go to
coordinates okay
[Music]
okay I'm just doing main quests I don't
know what you're
doing I'm doing all the side quests too
a all of
them
yeah how do you find the
time they just appear in front of me and
I can't not do them you
[Music]
know 30219
seven here Alan why are you not in the
kfp
guild there we go somebody invite
Ilan I don't know how to join somebody
invite
Ilan then I
go here
[Music]
what's this oh wa I wanted to try out
the
thing can we roll the dice playing
Monopoly
oh c to number can exceed six but how's
this
work dice to I move okay there it is do
I use get out of this oh could I have
used like multiplied by two so what the
heck what happened I got a treasure
piece okay let's roll
again a free let's try this multiply by
two six oh maybe I should like aim for
something particular cuz now I have six
one 2 3 4 5 six exp unexpected gains
okay let's go so you just get Buffs from
this um get all kinds of cool stuff I
yes how
fun oh yeah but was it a buff I guess
not an item is this what I got I don't
know oh let roll the dice
again
[Music]
two where shall we
go should I take this I shall take
it oh did it did it change my buff oh no
no no did it maybe not I now have drop
treasure rate increases by
5% cool R ooh is it permanent or is it
just a little bit uh 1
hour money accidentally Discovery is
this how you guys have been getting
money how much money did I
get is this the one four Eternal
coins free crystal cross
Metals Fire Gem
ooh
1% huh wait where did
my okay it's still there okay enough of
that I'm moving
kfp always
chilling around
me how to
let me finish this
Quest can I also get invite to KP please
KP invite me I like an invite
too all right let see where
is ah the inventory is so large I
have how many members do you guys have
this 50 no 33 members out of 50 for Now
26 and see now they're already spamming
the
[Laughter]
chat
scatter did I already get my status
where where am I rank leader I'm the
leader uh let's go you're the leader now
you took it from them we have our
highest level people are 65 50 40 and
40 I got to work a little
harder true
true can you guys still invite because
everybody else is just uh registered
member do I have to how do oh no
somebody got an invite okay good good
good cuz I don't want to I don't have
time to invite
people yeah everybody has per
Guild what else can guilds do are they
going to have to maintain it somehow you
want to
join
okay I come join
yay we are here together
yay
nice
wow one of us is there only me like
registered member or leader and no
other uh status I want to give you
something cool too
promote action failed you cannot what I
can't weird is there do I have to like
create ranks maybe oh
yeah
oh oh oh no but can I make new
ones I don't know how this works gu not
huh well we all know that you're
special you don't need to prove it with
a rank I know you're special yeah I
don't need a rank to be special you're
literally giggy
morning yeah and everyone knows
it we know it's may also be inv area
okay here recruited I have personally
invited you
[Music]
you're going to the next area the no
desert
area is it what yeah I'm in Beluga
Bay Bela
Bay what I'm still I think staying in
this
region
probably okay I'm killing some more
jellyfish
is they look like tacis to me because of
the onion
ring their little onion ring but now
these ones are spiked they're Dangerous
Ones the play has joined another guild
unable to invite why are you asking to
be
invited if you already have some
Guild
betrayal why are they lying to you
is this are am I hearing B sounds I
should level my b class at some point
but should I do it
now I'm not in the mood right now maybe
off
screen I got to love our other classes
too people can just like add me to their
friends list is there
something like what can people do when
they're
friends I wonder I don't remember I
don't even know how to get to my friends
list I I haven't even added you as a
friend I think oh I saw you added the
beginning oh yeah it says you're on my
friend
list oh maybe it's we have to add each
other and then people can add you but
it's only one way okay I added you now
now we're actual besties
oh interesting way to do
friends Golden Claw
assassin do
ah these little
rats
[Music]
okay
breasties besties ities we can be
besties G why
why
why I want you to tell me
why why can we not be
besties look me in the eye and tell me
why
um I don't see the issue here I don't
see the problem I mean just because
you're small doesn't mean you don't have
a breast you should have a breast yes
yes yes it's it's just like not that
like poking out like mine but you still
have a breast but we're we're still
breasties sure sure sure sure mhm it's
totally possible and imagine if I had
larger breast then if we were hugging
they would get in the way and I wouldn't
be as close to you you know no not
necessarily because your breast would be
situated lower than mine
so it would be like a puzzle piece that
is true but if we were like sitting down
and hugging they would keep us from each
other but who really does that our
problem is that when you're hugging me
now your face it will be in my
breast I know what you're going to say
that's not a
problem it's not an issue for me of
course
notm being short is Good
[Laughter]
Guys where is this other guy he needs to
respawn come
on come
on why are you so why did you learn how
to raise people up so well oh that
there's there I don't know I I would
even consider what I say r i just maybe
is it the Des
Iration no yeah I think it's not
necessarily the things you say it's just
like your natural
Aura just oh I guess it's because I am
unassuming and unthreatening
that like if you really wanted to you
could kill me but because I'm so
non-threatening it's fine well you know
I mean no I think it's stuff like to be
honest to be very honest you're very
funny and you talk well you have always
something to say and sometimes it's like
very smart comebacks and sometimes it's
good jokes and
stuff and um gigling and blushing you
you you love every you show interest to
everything for example that I like and I
think you you always you you're capable
of showing interest towards everything
that any of the other H life girls like
like you're like so versatile I guess
and with that interest that
everyone I think people that have
interest and passions are beautiful and
I want to hear about them my interest
and passion is you haha no um no um
that's no your MMOs tell me about your
MMOs my M I just love listening it's my
favorite thing to do
a yeah no I really think you just
compliment everybody you have you have a
a natural talent for complimenting
people thank you that's why everybody
happy to hang out with everyone but like
genuinely I think some people genuinely
want to know how you do it because like
you're just so good at being loved
I I don't I don't know I guess I don't
think about that stuff and then in my
head I'm just like I want to hang out
with everyone that's how you do it you
just don't think about it just
chill yeah I guess like if we're talking
about it I I feel like if you have
ulterior motives it's really easy for
people to pick up on like you're doing
this because you want to gain something
out of it then I I I feel like everyone
knows that but that's why you just have
to genuinely just be an
empty makes sense yeah it feels like
less forced and less um more natural you
know I just want to hang out I'm having
fun in Eternal
fun I want to get to I want to get to
end game with you and we should get
married we should stream our marriage no
that's why I'm like like constantly
rejecting everybody's marriage proposals
because I'm I I it's not like you know
like I'm I'm not trying to like ship us
anything but in the game like with you
have to get married to your friends we
have to we're meant it's literally an
MMO
yeah we could we could be so pretty on
the altar it's part of the game play you
do know that since I'm obviously not
paying the fees you will have to pay for
both of us so you pay 50 *
2 I'm not giving
youed Will you will I will pay for our
wedding I need you officiate it too yes
well I will pay for you to be there you
can probably shortcut it by having kfp
send you the 100 gold guys I need you to
send me 100 gold so I can get married to
the person you want to marry Ty y thank
you they will support it I'm
sure you can't so live vicariously
through
me that's exactly what you should
do oh you're in the same area as me now
yeah I am yipp I feel like I've been
here before cuz I fought those enemies
before maybe
they were like sending us around in the
hopes that while we still had free
teleportation we would activate all
those crystals but we didn't God why
didn't they tell me
that maybe they didn't we wouldn't we
didn't read it who
knows I missed the teleportation but
this is fine it's still Auto walks yeah
it's chill it's
jaill I I think I almost like this more
than instantly teleporting because I I
didn't even know what the hell was going
on when I was teleporting from one point
to another immediately yeah there's more
downtime and then you can sort through
your inventory while you're walking or
look at other stuff yeah look at the
scenery the environment figure out where
the hell I am on my own be more
aware aware of our
surroundings yeah we need to live in the
now and then otherwise otherwise we're
just like Zoomers
yeah we're not Zoomers we are um slow
Walkers slow Flyers right now oh I
remember this oh this is so like wow
unlocking core
memories oh my
God I'm still hoping for f for fun perms
at some point I I do want to get like
this feeling of oh my God I'm so
back again I want to revisit all the
places there as well oh
man what is Fly for Fun on now anyways I
remember looking it up and seeing it on
like brows also DED and yeah it's like
there's um like a revived version I
think it's an official version I'm
pretty sure mhm um but it does seem to
be on a browser I don't know if it's the
only option though because this game
also you could play through Steam
apparently but also just through oh uh
downloading the client from the website
maybe there's several options for Fly
for Fun 2o but yeah harassed
tourist
oh are these CRA have you ever played
Latt tail Latt tail
no again I don't think it really had a
big present oh I mostly played uh MMOs
that got German service for some reason
there were just so many German anime M
morpg players out there here in the
German speaking countries that it was
like lucrative for them to make German
servers um but some games I don't think
lot did lot I mean that might be wrong I
didn't I didn't really sense a
presence I know what's get rid of that
from what you said it feels like most of
the games we played are the 3D anime
MMOs yeah except for like tricks online
for example but I wish I could play like
trickster online now because back in the
day I I didn't understand what I was
doing at
all maybe myish wasn't so good yet I
don't know I really didn't understand if
I was doing anything right at
all I wish they would bring back
trickster yeah I wish so too they're R
Reviving games like these why not revive
all of them bring them all back can we
sign a
petition please bring the old MMOs
back where is the oh do I just get any
of these birds iron axe
okay iron claw and iron ax are you
killing birds or are you already pass
that oh I'm on that Quest too oh where
are you I don't see you I don't know I'm
running in circles in the town because
I'm lost
I just oh I found the online to there
was a two did it look the same no it
didn't look the same you know I really
used to love what the characters look
like they're like the Sheep oh my God
yeah they're so
[Music]
[Applause]
cute and all the loading screens were so
cute oh man
why why couldn't I have played it at a
time where I had better understanding as
a gamer like I I really have to say like
my my gaming
skill from back then compared to now is
very
different yeah more knowledge through
the other MMOs too I wish that I played
them more with better knowledge also I
feel like I was a big noob
I want to play Oh wait I should be
unidentify my f God damn
it ah go
away well okay I definitely already have
the feather didn't
[Music]
realize I know elord is still pretty
active every time I see it I want to
play it cuz the characters are so pretty
a with all the
fashion is is it it's like still kind of
like chibi style or yeah it's chibi
style nice there's so much fashion in
that game it's
crazy fashion sword It's Fashion sword
not L sword it's all about the fashion
everyone plays for the fashion
[Music]
until you hit end game so the grind is
genuinely awful yeah grind and end game
is rough in a lot of games I remember
grinding so hard in Fly for Fun I was
just like the the most painful [\h__\h] ever
with like zero I I'm not joking
0.001% exp or so when you're like right
before max
level per mom
0.0 1 or 0.001 something like that
something like absolutely insanee like
that it was such a pain in the
ass yeah for some reason all MMOs I
really feel like back then all the
grinding was less than 1% and everyone
was like yeah that's normal and then
even like in one day like even if you
grind really hard the realistic amount
of XP you could get is like maybe 5% of
your exp bar and that was fine that's
just how it was 5% of your exp bar per
day if you're max level
is this is how it is yeah it's normal a
yeah and then if you died you lose 4%
exp not the death penalty oh
yeah you could spend all day working or
grinding and then you die and lose it
all
great that's how I like it all these
quests no it's a good thing they took
out exp
penalties oh is that not a thing anymore
nowadays I feel like it's no longer
really a thing I know maple story took
it out I think po has exp penalties if
you die but that's a much different game
[Music]
okay I'm level 25 now
chill ow things here
hurt this area hurts me what the hell
where are you things don't hurt me where
I am o actually I don't have a quest
anymore why give me what quest are you
on I am
on the daughter and the Pirates man part
two
uhhuh interesting it's level 26 Quest
but you're level 25 you can still take
it I'll go that
way he but is that a main quest yeah
it's a main quest how many main quests
are there is this a these main quest how
do I know doesn't say it here are they
all main
quests defeat ah thank you I joined the
main quest just in time for you to
defeat all three things in one goal for
me I've done it but now I have to walk
somewhere I'm also coming oh I see
you hello let's
go feeling this mob real quick I have a
feeling I might have accidentally given
kfb a addiction for this game for some
of them some actually might be playing
this actively now maybe also to impress
me next time I go online with like level
60 o yeah you guys better be max level
the next time we l
again isn't it nice to have some MMO to
play with
[Music]
everybody we have to walk to
43566 or is that but also all the all
the what was it Gremlins is it just
Gremlins yeah they're GRS you guys are
also welcome to join kfp Guild of course
if you are interested this yeah guys you
want to play MMOs yeah we might play it
more often gy will have a PO hopefully
next time
so
potentially am I okay if gig is okay
with of
course please come and mingle if you
need to scratch that MMO
itch all right yeah collect great full
Essence from ancient
ear what oh
here
[Music]
Uno lead me towards the next ancient n
game how am I to
know
here
doors
do do you know the Mexican
cat wa cat
um how does the melody go
again does does it come until
CH the one with the Maracas and the
hat I don't think I know what cat you're
talking about you want 100% know it but
I'm just not not sure how
to explain it
if I saw it with my eyes maybe I would
know somebody made a waa version of it
orange cat version
cute I want to see it someone like is
that what it was a cat because it sounds
like
G maybe that's
why
yeah is it the Super Mario Bros free
music one oh maybe that's Super Mario
Bros free music oh could
me I am here my inventory is so
full H too bad you don't have a 25 slot
backpack expansion huh someone actually
sent me one well I got a I got a I got
some cool stuff again oh
ypp
oh now I fought with the 50 gold you're
trying to marry someone but no okay
composed alpaka Mallet this hammer I
don't p a hammer oh
cute oh my
garbage rid of this how to see my hammer
how do I um how do i p out my weapons is
there uh how do you change the stance oh
there it is oh wait what the
hell what oh there there's the
face a cute it's so cute I'm going to be
hitting people with
now nice I need to find um the like
place to store my stuff maybe we should
end it now wish yeah I am down to stop
yeah right you need to go prepare for
your next collab yeah I'll go to
aan I should go to aan too let's find
the
storage and store all those weird papers
did I have yes get out of my
inventory surely it's somewhere in the
middle
right book
Merchant not that
one I think it's more on the left side
over there isn't it here yeah GG Bank g
g
bank I remember that yeah it was a bank
okay you take a take this and this and
this and these and these and these and
these it's going to look so clean
afterwards and the bank can have bags
too take all of these what do I want to
do with these
nothing get out of my
inventory
nice
um more bags are always welcome if you
don't need them kid
FP wish there was a sort option I got a
pencil too as a weapon that's
cute going to have so many things that I
have to
rotate a sword option would be good yeah
don't think there is such a
thing put these away and this one what's
the pet food for find the Pet's
durability pet as in not the alpacas
that I'm riding but like the for example
the the green thing that's following you
yeah that one okay now I needs to be
fed I haven't been feeding mine
[Music]
either who's making these noises ah
they're doing the caramel dancing n
that's right I remember now the dancing
this game is the caramel D
[Music]
Dance they're so cute you is so cute oh
by the way I didn't wow I'm actually I
made such a genius promotion here by
wear making us wear the lesto cloaks
today uh I think yeah people have seen
it right
the things that are on sale yeah we have
basically this cloak but uh as a blanket
that you can throw over your body it may
show uh sold out right now but I think
there they should like I thought it was
pre-order so for sure they'll restock it
if it's sold out but uh yeah it's a
thing now isn't it so so cute it's such
a cute
idea yeah it is so cute you want to wear
it so bad
you're so good at promoting
again imagine wearing it when you watch
and Reco you know yeah yeah at home but
also I feel like maybe some people might
bring it to conventions and stuff too
and then you see who the the real Ian
Recco enjoyer CHS are oh you watched Ian
Recco season one huh me too me too what
was your favorite dungeon oh mine was
totally the Phoenix dungeon oh hell yeah
so cool that was the best
D it
was oh and then maybe maybe people H cuz
right couldn't you do was there a test
that people could take that fans could
take uh that said whichi right there was
that so you can be like oh I think it
was like what character are
you Talent are you yeah but then maybe
maybe we can have a test and then people
will tell each other oh yeah I I'm in
this Guild I'm in that Guild I'm suran
Guild oh cool I'm scol
wand yeah really sweet I just made us
wear this cloak cuz I kind of thought it
was fitting and it makes us match even
more we're already matching because
orange but now we're matching even more
I is so
cute makes us feel like adventurers yay
no ah do you guys want to take a
screenshot everybody who's still like
hanging out here come to uh this person
has a rainbow Paca what o cute o I don't
see it they just went off their Mount
why why would they do that show me all
yeah get back on your Rainbow
alpaca oh right here uh hoken okay uh
let's go over here guys follow Wawa
towards the church thing or whatever
that is don't worry we won't get married
[Laughter]
yet not yet but let's everybody can you
guys like make some r goes on the uh
stairs and me and gigy will be in the
front at the very bottom in the middle
and you guys like go up yeah yeah yeah
the big ones who want to flex their big
mounts further in the back don't cover
up people too
much yeah yeah yeah yeah eh good can I
move this can I move my oh the back of
your dress is so cool oh thank you it
lights up it's kind of glowy yeah didn't
realize it's so glowy is there a way to
move the chat window sure
ah no I can make it bigger and smaller
but I for sure there's a way has did
everybody anybody figure out how to move
the chat window stop GTA around stop
drifting oh my God has a little alpaka
in the
front oh well okay then the chat will be
partially on the screenshot maybe unless
I zoom out really well
um should I for the screenshot turn off
everybody's names
maybe oh no I think the names are a part
of it yeah okay yeah looks very like see
yeah very MMO with the names on okay but
uh do you want to stay on that because
alpaca covers up your whole
body come down you have to show it you
want to show the alpaca
sideways okay but close come come a
little bit closer to me okay yeah
okay um yeah newcomers you stand behind
us okay oops I mean to click there and
then I will open I don't know if there's
an in-game screenshot tool but I'm just
going to use Snipping Tool yeah when I
tap out the game lags don't worry guys H
cheese wait how do I wait how do I get
rid of this selection
here why have I why do I have people
selected there we go okay cheese
cheese
okay
um wow day one of
kfp in and and Gremlins and gy and
Wawa in E Eternal Yi they won look at us
wow we got to 25 and then next time
we're going to get to 50 oh hell yeah we
will we'll be so
op I'm excited one day KY will win the
guild
[Laughter]
war I'm excited thank you guys for
joining this nostalgic adventure of
ours it was nice to have all these
people around us following us giving us
free money yeah I love the feeling of
community yes so true thanks foring y
everyone yeah I hope you had fun too
gigy grinding I had fun such a hard
grind the G stands for grinding yeah and
the second
G good grinding good
grinding good grind yeah
um I hope I I know gy didn't have a POV
but I hope uh Gremlins who were late or
so can you guys forgive me if I read
super chats for like an hour or so I'm
like so behind I I kfp will kill me if I
don't read Super Chat at some point and
I I had collabs and stuff so tomorrow is
members only is it okay if I just for an
hour the grabs don't care shakes The
Shoe Box shaking
it you don't
[Laughter]
care well thank you for having me thank
you I I I'll see you soon next week we
already have a time and a day set so
we'll be there hope you guys will be
there too it's so noisy here
C we'll see you for the next Eden
Eternal yeah thank you goodbye goodbye
everyone
bye I will see my way out oh no I'll
miss
you
goodbye goodbye
a and then I was
alone yeah we started
something something that could be
amazing something that could be so
special something that could be a part
of our
lives for a long
time nah I don't think uh I don't know I
don't know how long we intend to play
how long and how often but it's nice to
relive everything for now and see how
far we can get one could say
Eternal we'll see we'll see are you an e
streamer now are there any e streamers
at
all back in my day they weren't back in
my day they were like maybe some people
who uploaded their um fights on YouTube
some special
fights uh I remember in Fly for Fun
there was this like an me in this like
mechanical technical looking City in the
in the cave with the lava and all that
and and the boss fight there was like
clock I think it was called Clockwork
and people were uploading their best
fights against Clockwork yeah Clockworks
yeah yeah yeah yeah on YouTube I
remember
like uh fighting Clockworks many many
times as a Healer
[Music]
right before we go into some Super Chat
reading let me upload that screenshot
right now cuz um I don't want to forget
about
it
yeah our eeden
Eternal Adventure has begun and the
grind is
real so many of you guys joined us
yippee
by the way if there's still any
Groundlings here in the chat I do want
to say like um I kept on saying kfb
because the guild is called kfp and it's
like automatically making me say kfp but
um I'm I'm sure there's like me some
Gremlins out there who um you know were
watching and maybe also playing thank
you so much I I really appreciate it I
hope you guys can enjoy this
[Music]
too it's just like the The Guild being
called that of makes my brain constantly
say
kfp as if you guys weren't there but
you're you're very much there and I'm
very aware thank you so
much yes wow so many people maybe we're
going to become even
more we've absorbed you a little bit a
little bit
Gams
GS the cute
grams okay um I won't take too much of
your time because I want to make sure
the V is available for people who want
to watch it
ASAP but I really do need to read some
super chats I'm so
behind it's really a
by uh what music are you going to put
on actually ingame bgm was so
good I wish I could still play
it how are these ooh ah this one's
cute okay and where shall we
[Music]
go
maybe rpt office with the cloak
[Music]
or or I take off the cloak and we go to
the
office the office I guess doesn't need
the Halloween thing anymore we could go
to the normal office but this normal
office currently has cherry blossoms I
don't know why
[Music]
wow refreshing need to find the next
version again I guess now it should be
already winter version I haven't used
the winter office in a
while I need to find it but for day
there will be cherry blossoms I guess
we're in Australia or
[Music]
something you think I should what you
want Halloween to stick around in
general or or my Halloween office
what do you
[Music]
want I had
Ramen like I only had like an hour
between the
streams I realized like I I thought I
had a little bit more time and I um
after the previous collab the bux shot
rouette um me and out I wanted to talk
with her about one specific thing but
then we just kept on talking about all
kinds of things and it went on and it
went on on and then I was like [\h__\h] I I
am actually I probably should eat
something and and go to idle meeting and
stuff so we finally separated and at
that point I only had like 1 hour
left to well eat and rest a little bit
and I really felt like I needed some
rest and then I just like rested for
like 10 minutes while I was like
ordering food and in those 10 minutes I
I was like petting my cats and I already
felt like falling asleep but no time for
a nap and I rushed down my food was good
though it good I had
[Music]
Ramen normally I don't have like such a
like big dinner kind of food before a
stream but I really felt like eating
something bigger at that point normally
what I do I I have like a little little
sandwich or something for so to say
lunch like whatever my second food
is for breakfast I have usually one quo
or something else and then for lunch I
just have like a little sandwich
usually and then for dinner is when I
eat the winner winner chicken dinner but
now I switched it around and I'm going
to have something
lighter for the dinner I
guess quel
quel I've been getting a lot of quas
again but now I'm kind of sick of it
again and want to switch it up
again every time every freaking time
that I go and get my quo around noon
they're like
ah just woke up huh and I'm
like
well
what but they're nice they're nice and
they always try to give me the freshest
one the fresh
quo remember the story from that I told
you where this one employee was
like yeah like weird about how I was
getting along with the lady employee
that guy he quit a while ago I guess so
he's
gone but even after a while like when I
told him to shut up uh about it you know
it got awkward for a while but then I
just didn't go there for a while also
cuz I was in Japan and so on
and then after a while the awkwardness
just was gone and we were just like
greeting each other like normal people
again but then he's like oh yeah I I'm
I'm today's my last day I'm like
[Music]
okay yeah but I'm like so G my face is
so
known everybody knows my face I'm the
quo lady who always always comes to get
a quo
yeah I'm going to read super chats just
give me like a moment to catch up with
you guys why are you guys you want to
catch catch up with me too don't
you yesterday I took the day off sorry
about that I did get some work
done uh not just work but like H work I
I cleaned out my whole
fridge there was so much like stuff in
there I threw out all the stuff that I
didn't need and I I took out all the
like shelves and cleaned them at the big
basket shelf I cleaned it in the
bathtub and
stuff I haven't cleaned my fridge a
single time since I moved
in and maybe that sounds disgusting to
some people but I feel like a lot of
people just never do
it it was actually not that bad at all
it didn't really have any stains it had
like one small stain in one spot from
like some something sticky but it wasn't
really that bad at all actually
surprisingly in a good
State wasn't stinky either or anything
it was I mean it's still like that
fridge uh when I got it in February that
was a fresh fridge so it has been like
not even a
year I've I've been just treating it
well
H so yeah it wasn't wasn't stinky or
anything but I still felt like suddenly
I felt like I need to clean out my
fridge
now and while I'm cleaning it out I
might as well clean the inside of the
fridge
[Music]
too yeah and then I did some more Mo cap
yesterday cuz um I was trying to film
the aella video cuz I'm making a video
for it to go with it cuz you guys in
theory already could listen to the
capella if you just listen to the bot
from when I let you guys listen to it
but um that's why I thought oh maybe I
should add a video to it to make it a
little bit more
special so yeah uh a little simple video
and then the coolest thing I realized
yesterday I mean actually I didn't
realize uh both chy and and Sian pointed
out to me that the um software that I'm
using
recently has a function now get this
normally so when I record in the xense
software uh I just like uh record like
the bones and stuff you know the bones
movement and in the software I'm not
myself I'm just like a bone skeleton
moving around can you imagine
and all that is being recorded is the
motion and then uh chagy gets that
motion and puts it onto my model because
I legitimately don't know how to do it
that's why I always need che's help and
chy puts it on the model and then
there's some jankiness here and there so
he like cleans up the jankiness That's
What chy
does um chy does not do Moab because chy
does not have any
Moab equipment whatsoever but maybe it
would be cool maybe for chy to one
day you know get some would be surely
interesting I don't know if chy wants
to um but
yeah uh that's what I do and then the
thing is though that in uh maybe there
is a I don't know is there a way I I
think so I could probably somehow figure
out how to record my facial
map through my iPhone through the
softwares in there but it would be
separately it wouldn't be linked to the
what I what I'm recording in
xense and then you have to like link it
up and I don't even know how to do that
anyway I have to record it my my face
only um so chy has been adding the cute
Expressions as well that's a big thing
by hand you know for those YouTube
shorts
M yeah
and
so whatever that has been fine because
Chey seemed to be you know happy doing
that
and uh but now I've been made aware that
the software that I've been using
recently for live streaming those
models uh has a function where you can
record the motion in
combination with the face and when I say
record motion I'm not saying like record
like something that I showed you
yesterday like just a video of my model
doing it no no no there's like this
motion format called
[Music]
fbx um and so it's like if I were to
just like like in my streams right in my
3D streams obviously my face is moving
obviously my body is moving it's already
combined there and so you would think
maybe oh why don't you just record that
it's different that's that's just like
if I record that how are we going to
like use that for like videos and stuff
where we want to put a background in and
change the Angles and so on no but what
we found is that it's possible to record
the motion data and then edit it
afterwards I put it on the video and put
the put it on a model and put it and
change the change some motion and fix it
fix it and change the Angles and
everything make a music video
whatsoever yeah now I can do it now I
can do it at the same time like capture
both the face and the body which is
really
cool the future is now yeah and I'm
learning
yeah it's hard to explain but so far I
couldn't do
that yeah yeah yeah yeah I didn't know
how to do that so far and now it's like
in one one software already combined one
click get both things
combined pretty
sick yeah now
chy has been looking at it I don't know
if it's chy said something's wrong with
it but it's also okay I'm not sure chy
has been writing a lot today and I have
not had time to look at it
hopefully it works hopefully it's usable
because chy said the quality is a little
bit lower than what like I normally
record in the
xense
software chy is feeling a little bit
under the weather so get well soon no
rush we can
wait we can wait on the Milestones
people have been blessed by many
Milestones
already
yeah
okay I feel kind of like out of breath
and my throat hurts but just going to
read super chat a little bit
but this is already kind of my seventh
hour of streaming
going into my seventh hour of streaming
[Music]
today black lung from working in the
mine so
long huffing the the Mind dust or
what uh do we know is GD around do we
have a super chat points to pick up
on I thank you Mirage official M oh nice
okay oh yeah just as a reminder U my
mom's coming over so I won't be
streaming on
Monday yeah yeah and then next week um
I'm still going to probably like stream
plenty next week uh comparable to this
week um but uh next week is uh
Jakarta and does
I cannot stream obviously during a
specific time frame that is quite long
uh it's like
a almost a
like yeah it's a it's a pretty long time
frame so Friday no
stream but then I think on Saturday like
a few hours after the concert I can
stream so right now it's looking like 2
days off which isn't too bad
it's
fine Monday and
[Music]
Friday and oh my God so next week
there'll be something
[Music]
big next week
is a thing I've been waiting
for wallets are in danger
your wallets are shaking right
now unless you know if you if you're not
into buying merch of course you're safe
don't
[Music]
worry mhm it's very exciting um it's
going to
be known
soon yeah and that's not the only thing
in that month though there some cool
stuff happening this month
[Music]
M
be let's
go wait so where was it um the music
video
right scroll scroll scroll scroll scroll
scroll scroll music video music video
what are you sure huh no the the recap
no sorry G can you say it
[Music]
again oh thank you thank thank you for
the
membership haven't recovered from the
super groupies super groupies was a
little bit um
expensive yeah recap I think pretty sure
it doesn't look like great out to me so
I'm going to read the recap super
[Music]
chats got the wobble watch yeah people
have been receiving their super groupies
merch just around this time the watch
looks really fancy it better be looking
really fancy it was expensive
right
yeah cool stuff hope you guys enjoy your
fancy stuff you got yours too
oo I love my watch and jacket
thing still waiting on my acrylic
oh oh got the jack up but mine came in
while oh
speed MB was first I know wores uh yeah
I'm pretty sure I read that already so
recap is next let me find the
thumbnail
here what a cool thumbnail it's like
woba from Two Worlds the shadow world
and the the mirror world or whatever I
don't know it looks cool
or a different
timeline I
I sorry I need to tangent about one more
thing
I
watched someone play through the new
life of strange game until the end now
um
and while I don't
like completely agree with
everything that this person is is
confused
about in the story cuz some parts I
think I'm not going to judge anybody any
streamer for not picking up on things
while they're streaming a game because I
I think you guys also don't sometimes
don't realize like you make fun of me
for not noticing things but I think as a
streamer when you're like trying to
entertain your chat and everything um
it's easy to miss some things that might
seem really obvious to
you yeah it's a debuff and I think he
had that too a lot uh cuz there's so
many things that me while watching was
so obvious to me and he just missed it
and didn't didn't understand a lot of
things but overall I still must
say did do you guys have you I'm okay
I'm guessing not so many of you guys
played the new life of strange game or
even played any of
them is there anybody who played it or
saw someone playing it
I hear it's really bad it
was it's what threw me off is like the
over dramatization of SE certain
things uh I'm not going to say a name
but there's this one character who has
an absolute meltdown in the last
chapter and I don't think it is um
Justified at all like why would you have
such a meltdown why would you
I don't
understand Zoomer emotions yeah but
there there's really like plot-wise not
a big explanation of why not just this
character but other characters in other
situations as well are reacting so
dramatically in my opinion like
especially in the last chapter of the
game
it's it's that was really weird that
felt so weird like why is you so [\h__\h]
dramatic I don't want to spoil anything
but just a
man it's more like drama for the sake of
drama I guess like and yeah seems like
there's a lot of CR CR critique to
[Music]
it it's like
they had a hard time finding reason for
the drama that they wanted to create so
now it feels like there's just no good
reason for the characters to freak out
like
that yeah it it was overall just weird
but visually pleasing I
[Music]
guess is that a fan server no it's an
official
server you can join too if you look up
Eed on the tal it's on Steam and it's
also like they they have a client on
their official website that you can
download uh I think it's it comes out
the same you can either get it from
Steam right I got it from the official
website cuz I wasn't sure if the steam
thing was the same thing but it seems
like it
is and then there's like free servers
there's a like there's the English main
server that you could join and then in
within that English main server there's
like several servers too that are all
connected it's just like you choose
where to spawn just to like spread out
if the B the servers are busy but you're
still all in the same server so to
say
yeah as long as you are as you make your
character in thean server yeah okay here
we
go oh smoothie you're still here this
whole time she's she found a box that
she likes to lay in sometimes in this
room
why is she she looking so
confused what
happened she's so cute she's
so she loves me so
much yeah she does like to stick around
these days it's really noticeable
like I think I noticed um was it was it
after today's
stream at some point I found her in my
bedroom on uh a cupboard on a blanket
like I I put like a nice fluffy blanket
on the cupboard just like folded up and
she was like lying there like the
baguette that she is and and I made
myself a place on my bed just for 10
minutes right and she looks at me I look
at her and I see it in her eyes that she
wants to come over and she comes over
and she goes like and she sits on the
pillow next to me so again I had my
[\h__\h] next to me my my smoothie on my
left and my chunky wony on my right and
I'm spreading out my arms to pet both of
them happiness but was so cute because
chunky monkey was already there she's
like she defaults to going to that box
but smoothie wasn't there yet but she
sees me she sees me getting uh onto my
bed and she she comes over it's so cute
even though she's already in the room
she Cho is to come over you don't even
understand all these feelings that I
have it's the small things you
know yeah it's blessed okay okay Jack 47
D James Jackson D yuk Mike D Flappy Boy
Thanks for two red super chats congrats
on your fourth anniversary show nothing
but spectacular acts however magia and
Mirage totally stole the show besides
those my favorite song must have been
whatever whatever whatever with Taki
good choices Peak comedy you two
goofballs must have had such fun
recording
it I don't know how much fun Ena had she
was so
tired also thanks for releasing my new
favorite Viet song I leave the due
praise for the vocals and Coro to as
someone more capable in said I'd like to
ask about the lyrics M hinted that they
may be intentionally relevant to content
creator what's your take on them uh
Mirage lyrics
[Music]
I don't really have a take on
them I'm
sorry
um I don't really have a
take yeah she did a lyric explanation
Stream So bet best to just follow
that I'm probably more clueless than
usual this
time yeah
so listen to
Mo thank you Flappy boy M M M thank
you you Dan The Gamer cre Dan unknown
thanks for the red super chat you did
such an awesome job with the fredd live
every single thing about it was
seriously so incredible I watched it
four times already and still need more
wa Mirage is just perfection it might be
my new favorite song of all time now
unless you can't stop listening to it
thank you I do really think Mirage came
out really nicely and I'm I'm very
positively surprised by how it has
caught so many of
you
m I thought it would be a little bit
more uh like you know nice to listen to
but not my kind of song
reaction I think the me me me me me me
ru part is just so catchy
right thank you unknown oh you said
another Read Super Chat to I can say for
sure that I will never ever stop
streaming it no matter what you're way
too amazing wa I don't think I can ever
praise you enough you truly are the best
ever and I'm always extremely proud of
you I love you so much thank you you're
so nice thank you thank you thank you
for always supporting
me I'll do my best
to be worthy of your support going
forward thank you so much for the
love I hope I can give it
back MW mwah
mwah thank you so much sorry my throat
hurts I can't talk so well hul thanks
for the pinky press for thank you good
night thank you and good night you sound
like a talk show
host thank you
Honolulu and mous fam thanks for the r
to chat congrat on the release of Mirage
absolutely amazing kind of reminded me
of Huna
really I will say I had some
inspiration which I asked the team to be
inspired by in terms of like style of
music but it was not
Huna yeah I'm not feeling the Huna Vibe
at all from that but thank you I'm sure
it's supposed to be a
compliment reminds me more of I uh I was
not really the inspiration but I know
what you mean and what I chose was an
inspiration kind of is similar probably
yeah thank you
Mouse the flying toe
D Skye thank you for two pinkies because
I want to wait for today so I haven't
sent Super Chat in Fredy life now is
ready so first I love your freey life
besides Banger Mirage I have heard nice
type and sticks helic quite a lot of
times really nice type too so that is
really surprised to hear you sing that
thank you nice type is such a fun song
it's like a little bit too
short right had made me also want to
repeat it many times before when it came
out I'm such a
[Music]
banger second thing is I got the Alpa
world tour ticket
W see you in there last is I start
watching Gil girls it wouldn't be fast
only watch three episodes for now but
for now I like the vibe I'm keep
watching oh
Sky you're getting extra points from me
for watching Gil more
girls oh speaking
of who was it was it hokan who was
supposed to watch uh rings of power
now have you beun
[Music]
still watching that okay but what you're
starting with season 1
and I I don't know um I will understand
if you don't like season one but you
have to watch the season two as
well which is
better
okay why would you make H do that he's
making that him do he's making himself
do that actually he put himself that
like
ultimatum he's put it on to himself I
never even suggested that I watched res
of power now since I promised you I
would oh did you watch it all already
mdv I caught up Umbrella Academy too
oh I already forgot what I thought about
the last Umbrella Academy Season I think
it was okay
it's probably good that they ended
it yeah anyway anyway anyway thank you
Sky MW mwah mwah enjoy g
girls it's been a while since I last
watched
[Music]
it only had 20
elves it is kind of weird how yeah how
like they show they're trying to make
you think like for example for the like
the war
scenes like you don't you I don't know
the whole thing with how
many Orcs or elves or whatever there are
on each side is
always really weird and unclear and then
you think they completely obliterated
one side but then there's still some
left over but it really doesn't look
like many but then suddenly it's so many
again and that's
weird the logic behind it is weird but I
don't really
care loot poison thanks for the red
super chat hello Miss takanashi could
you please send a greeting to zasu
draconus I'm his mod and you are a huge
inspiration for him I love to give him a
greeting and a kiss from you
[Music]
okay
is thank you what do you mean I was a
huge inspiration for him I'm not
anymore what the
hell better better be your inspiration
again fell off shut the [\h__\h]
up that's not what that means ah well
yeah depends on how you interpret it
I fell off little
[\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] woman of the Phoenix D happy
belated birthday and four years
membership wow thank you so much without
you I wouldn't have gone to Japan and
met so many wonderful people hey see
sore
exciting congratulations
I wish you all the best and enjoy your
time at sore which
one as
well G py yeah this was literally the
best fre life I've seen ooh that is some
High Praise thank you oh I'm honored
than I'm proud of it too glad you liked
it it's hard to like there's so many
great uh performers and so many great 3D
lives being blasted out all every month
by whole life so it's hard to really
stand out I guess um I was going to make
this life stand out even more because
originally as you know I was planning to
have a um IRL person show up
M stuff like that to make it more
special but things really didn't work
out a lot of things didn't work out for
this one a lot of things are also not
working out for the next one um
yeah but I got my dates for the next one
now and
uh yeah sadly sadly I guess
unfortunately it will be like external
studio now because in-house studio is to
busy and too
occupied around the time when my new
dates are um
but uh
yeah I mean it will be fine though
because they showed me like other Frey
lives that have been produced in that
studio with those staff his like
external staff as well and it looked
really good like the quality is fine and
everything and I don't have to pay for
it of course um but still like I don't
know I wish it was in the house chy won
[\h__\h] spooked me suddenly jumping up
to the table and fluffing my arm holy
[\h__\h] gust of wind and
fluffiness hello I'm going to touch your
belly what are you doing here what are
you doing
here when you sit here you like that
spot don't
you
yeah you know you like that spot
a baby
yeah she's squeezing herself between the
the Monitor and the
keyboard yeah and like she rests her
head on my audio
mixer so
cute y she's purring really
loud we can always seem to tell when
it's not in her eh I don't know if I
wouldn't have told you I don't think you
would end up
noticing but no I told you so you will
know but it will be fine I still get to
um like it's external staff but my usual
director is still going to be like
directing it together with external
director
apparently um but I'm sure the quality
and everything will be fine it's just
like it's more comfy being in a
environment that uh I'm familiar with in
the in-house one would be more
comfy but I'm sure I'll be
fine the other results of uh that studio
look really good why are you walking on
my on my mixer yeah I know there's a fly
there you don't have to you can ignore
the fly I don't know why that fly is
bothering me today in this room maybe
because there's no lights in the other
rooms
attack and she's really not even
thinking about attacking she's just like
slowly W walking around over my mixer
again thank you and now she's sitting in
front of my
[Music]
camera yeah you you're going to sit
right there you're taking up 60% of my
table She's So
[Music]
Soft oh
you're so cute you're so
[Music]
cute yeah go to your corner
here okay no where you going stay just
stay
here find yourself a spot that you
like she wants your stream 100% of your
heart that is true
a little motorcycle yeah so
cute um J D thank you
Y for the pinky mag is one of my
favorite anime songs so when the music
started playing I just yelled out loud
it really surprised me and you all sang
it so well thank
you yeah it kind of gave
me a little bit of Goosebumps as
well thank you so much
that was good I
know thank you thank you
m r
d d for the pinky hi W I couldn't watch
Mirage stream live but I still want to
congratulate you for the successful
performances thank you for your hard
work thank you I hope you caught up with
the V you got to you have to you're
obligated
to it's free
it's free but thank you so much
than kiun thank you for Pinky as well I
love your version of night typ and found
it really funny seeing people first time
reaction to the lyrics and wasn't to
hear the fact that it was a money song
what wasn't to hear the fact is that I
don't understand what you're trying to
say but did you not know you knew it
[Music]
right had to make clear in the m see
that it's a k song but not my original
song even though it sounds like it could
be because of k
sound got to make it clear people will
otherwise
misunderstand
oh are they weren't surprised to hear it
was a Moy song It's a mo K
song the combination of them is what
hits so hard
[Music]
thank you artifact D thank you oh oh
thank you
wow I I don't know
[Music]
uh I don't know if
I would necessarily agree that but it's
nice of you to say so thank you 100
gnomes D
[Music]
ego Jones thanks for the pinky love your
BS and everything you do thank you
thank you everything I do it's it's that
easy huh oh smothie what are you doing
my cats are getting up te it
seems very up
te they're like why is Mom streaming
twice today what the
hell and game 8910 d n TJ d 7 to7
[Music]
D yum yum d
d PX Latin d freeze strap
Dan cak cat D pudding Channel Dan Stark
Mandalore Dan
cool than space waterful thanks for the
pinky K I'm okay with anything you watch
and I'm happy you enjoy it I'm not ever
complaining over your likes don't worry
oh we're in the rings of power topic
here and giving rings of power a chance
just for you I believe that I believe
you that the second season is better I
will share my honest opinion once I come
around it oh okay I wonder if you
already did I'm looking forward to it
thank you for giving it a
chance Shiki
and J D FR SC D PGW 135 thanks for the
red super chat what an amazing new song
and amazing life anything with you on
stage is a guaranteed
Banger thank you that's that's too nice
of you I've been following you since a
few days after your debut I'm so proud
of what you have accomplished so far and
I promise to follow you on till the very
end oh it's a
promise oh I like your commitment I like
someone who is not scared of commitment
let's [\h__\h]
go to the end
together space wonderful sent another
pinky a while later after the other one
love you so much M I couldn't be proud
to be a kfp to be your fan and
supporting you no one makes me as happy
as Yuki waa you'll forever be my T oi as
there will never be anyone like you and
you're the best to me I'd hope that
there never will be anyone like me we're
all unique I hope we all have our Naes
and our special Specialties yeah thank
you so much for the nice words I'll give
you a kissy for the two
pinkies thank you thetive fire F fishon
[\h__\h] because you changeed detective fire
to defective fire
I changed dun to
funun you're confusing me defective fire
dun oh maybe it's not supposed to be
detective fire at all maybe defective
defective that is a word I
guess
F thanks for the pinky you did in fact
say that you're internal in your Deb
you're not
Timeless uh what is this in regards to
Eternal I might have said that yeah
because I just couldn't find good words
for
it was it was it about my age not really
Eternal though but today we play eeden
Eternal I am Eternal today for
sure D for the pinky even though I
recently started watching recently let's
go I'm appreciating all the time spent
with you you helped me to recover after
am I leaving and I'm ready very thankful
for that you're my best commos ever I'll
support you till the end thank you so
much yeah I did notice that you were you
know kind of new I was like oh this
person is like showing up a lot these
days must be new I'm glad that you're
around and glad you found your way to
kfp welcome welcome welcome hope you're
having a good
time really appreciate that you here
Jason Henry D tar
[Music]
are the egg cups wide enough to hold a
eggs uh oh yeah a good segue I don't
think they are saich eggs are big um but
thanks for reminding me I could show the
pictures on
stream wait I think I only downloaded
them on my phone did
[Music]
I I think I
did um
merch too bad like the picture the
picture are so nice but I think the
picture from the plate is blurry like
the illustration is blurry the stand
isn't blurry but the illustration is
blurry
unfortunate CU such a beautiful
illustration um
but there's finally sample pictures we
only have how many days you guys know
only a couple days left so if you are
waiting for the sample pictures to
motivate
you here it is in case you haven't seen
it I uploaded it on Twitter yesterday I
do want to still I think upload it on
the community board or did I I think I
did did I did I upload it on the
community board did
I 8 days we have eight days left okay
for the merch to be ordered here this
glass is so
you know I normally only get like one of
each for from my own merch for
free so I'm like lowkey considering
getting several of the glasses because
I'm worried that if I use one a
lot like I don't know how how durable
some of these like printed on things
are I've had some experience with some
like mugs that I got from Holo where the
color wear is off I probably washed it
too hot I guess or washed it too often
um I don't know if the these can really
wash off the gold I'm a bit worried
about the gold like I generally don't
know I really don't
know I don't I'm not going to hand wash
I just got to be careful I got to wash
it on low don't put in the I put
everything into the
dishwasher well then I'll just try to
not use it too often but I I think it
would be a nice Flex to have like like
maybe F four or six of them so when I
have friends come over for like I don't
know New Year's or so or Christmas
family and so on I want to be able to
present the takanashi kiata glasses it's
like the Fine
[Music]
China I want a couple of these
glasses but I wonder like if I want
more how do it work do I like if I
purchase through the store wouldn't that
be like stupid in terms of like
like they should just let me buy it with
like with like the
cuts being you know I don't know how do
I I don't know I don't know how to wrap
my brain around it but they should let
me like buy it internally and then
deduct it from my
[Music]
salary is go to the warehouse I don't
even know where the warehouse
is
uh let me let me
ask by the way if I want more than one
of for
example the
glass is it
possible buy more and have it deducted
from my salary
[Music]
I really want a couple of these they're
so pretty I really like them and I like
this shape of glass
[Music]
too cuz they fit really nicely in the
dishwasher cuz they're not Tall
Glasses but now you now you're telling
me don't put them into the dishwasher
but they're the perfect size to be put
in the top like the middle rack of my
dishwasher
man what am I supposed to do you have to
hand wash these you'll ruin them
really I'll
try I don't
know I've I've graduated from
handwashing I'm
sorry I only hand wash if my dishwash
was broken and I had was my
[Music]
knives but yeah wait let me show you
um the complete set it looks so nice
together right I was a bit worried you
know um if it would look nice together
but it looks nice together and it's like
it it became a legit like breakfast uh
set kind
of you know we have the egg cup which is
so cute like we already figured out that
you guys when you get the egg cups you
should should put uh like a cooked egg
in with the shell on still and then draw
face and stuff onto the cooked egg
shell and then take a picture because
it's like only the uniform right you got
to give it the face and the head and
then you get rid of it of the shell and
you eat your cooked boiled egg and you
put the salt and the pepper usually I
only put salt but whatever on top see
it's all
combined it's all combined it's
amazing and again I don't think anybody
has ever done in Holo uh salt and pepper
shakers and egg cup so that's a first
once again maybe I'll be a transcender
again I don't think so
actually these ones might not become a
trend but that's
[Music]
fine I like to have my things be
unique yeah but it's a really cute set
so please consider it um even the people
who don't really eat bolded eggs
normally maybe the reason why and for me
this is personally one of the reasons I
would eat boiled eggs more often if I
had an egg cup that's why I decided to
make an egg cup for
myself and yeah you guys really like the
angry expression apparently from the
Shakers here they look so
perfectly originally I was hoping that
they'd have some more like sculpted
options that are like sculpted like a
like more original
but they didn't have many options to go
off of like they had square or they had
this shape and I was like okay never
mind well this shape is perfect anyway
it's egg at least it's egg
shaped you're my salt shake or Shake are
you referencing
twice Shake
[Music]
sh we need more wa Friend R you plushies
e more
shaped like us yeah it's shaped like you
especially like the current eggs in the
chat there's not many but there's a
couple
so link is in the description if you're
interested
[Music]
my throat hurts use an egg holder when I
do soft P egg or pickle P an egg holder
you mean something like what I have an
egg cup you should get this egg cup it's
better it's
better this egg cup needs a body put a
body in
it now I'm almost done with this uh that
stream Super Chat so let me finish them
up but yeah I'm really happy with the
merch uh pictures they look so nice like
the orange everything's so
[Music]
orange okay let's finish
these
um probably was here was it was it Jason
Henry D tanak
shakar Indo 5 Alpha thanks for the pinky
good evening K just wanted to say how
much I AB adore your new song they keep
getting better each time oh really wow
I'm sorry but with your dancing in those
shorts I couldn't help but remember that
time you ripped your pad
why why just because I'm shaking my ass
shake that ass for me shake that ass for
me come on now shake that ass for why
though why why
why
[Music]
man that will forever fall follow me
just because that's one of those things
that is embarrassing to me but I like
use it as
content just like my Thro picture and
my non-n knowledge of reading
clocks until recently and my ripped
pants these are just some of the things
I do for Content or like that I share
for
content and then it follows me forever
ever should have known should have
known but thank you so much stop
thinking about my repent o I'm no notes
D HEC D thank you
d d Nathan cotton thanks for the pinky
five years ago me would probably think
I'm weird question why I give money to
an online anime girl sit down and watch
with me and after five or so minutes
would be asking to send super
to well but what 5 years ago you
question you giving money to any kind of
streamer like any like a normal IRL
flash twitch streamer or so would that
be questionable too if not then 5 years
ago you has no
logic uh to apply there because it's the
same
thing yeah personally yeah yeah oh okay
well but yeah I think it's
like easy to and hard to understand easy
to critique and hard to understand for
someone who just doesn't have any like
creator that they're really into
but well of course I will say this
because I'm the one receiving it but I
think it's perfectly valid to want to
support a creator that you really like
and that gives you free content all the
time um if you want to support them and
if you believe in what they're doing
it's like not different from going to
your favorite bands concert and spending
money on their concert or on their
merchandise and so on it's not different
at all it's like different um different
forms of um entertainment one is music
one is stream others other things are
like podcasts people pay for like
listening to podcasts too right like
some are free some are
not yeah anything like that um nowadays
you know with the internet being such a
big thing and all of our lives a lot of
jobs and a a lot of like opportunities
have been created on the internet and
then there's like just so many ways of
making money on internet and making
content on the internet and like
thankfully thank God there's people who
are out there supporting and
appreciating people's works that um they
put out there and you
know like
I for me it's not just streaming it's
also like the big picture like making
music being an idol stuff like
that it's more than just like
streaming
and it's my life and it's definitely
like a very privileged place to be
in and I 100% understand if people don't
want to or can't
support via using their money that's
100% fine there's this balance you know
with these kind
of uh content creator and viewer
supporter relationships there's this
balance some people are just normal
viewers but they're just as necessary as
the ones who are also like giving
something and all in all to have reached
this like perfect cycle
[Music]
yeah I mean the internet can be really
cancer and dangerous and weird and can
produce a lot of things that are not
good for the
world um but it's good that it also
produces some good things and I think
it's very valid to support the good
things that come out of the internet if
you have extra cash to spare and if you
can't but like I just said that's like
part of the cycle and very necessary as
well for um how to
say can't find the word not natural
growth but like the overall just growth
of the content creator just needs more
you know of everything we need every
everybody everybody has a role to play
even if you're just watching a
video and even if you're not even
subscribed it's yeah it's like an
ecosyst organic yeah that's what I was
looking
for it's an organic
ecosystem that's what we are oh Smo is
over there hi she's sleeping being
cute with her face towards me so she can
always notice if I'm done
[Music]
streaming wear an organ we microorganism
no a big
[Music]
organism
yeah yeah yeah I'm really I'm really
lucky and privileged and I thank you
guys so much for always supporting me
and making this possible for me
very on topic as we are reading super
chats that's why I always since the very
beginning want to make sure I read the
super chats um obviously you guys know I
can't like read the message of every
single one of them that would take too
long but I want to make sure you guys
know that I am
grateful and appreciative and that I
take note of your guys' contributions
thank you so much even if it gets tiring
I will never stop doing it
because for me it's the right thing to
do yeah thank you so
much uh where were
we not saying that anybody who doesn't
read super chats is in the wrong but for
me for my
personal peace of
mind I want to make sure that I do
it before anybody takes my words out of
[Music]
context
right where was I I wait Nathan your
Super Chat wasn't even finished oh what
oh wait hey this is Nathan from 5 years
ago and I just want to say this guy's
got some good taste but he keeps using
the term Kam oi and rolling his eyes at
me for not getting Idol ult
culture yeah it must be really
interesting to think back um to yourself
from before Hol life because I know so
many of you we talked about this before
but so many of your guys' lives were
very different before H live right your
interests and the groups you would
surround yourself with if you would go
to conventions at all for example some
people some of you guys wouldn't even go
to conventions before H now you do and
yeah it's
crazy very different very different kind
of
life which is cool very interesting how
things can change so
quickly through something like that
thank you
Nathan and nice little insight and
tangent
7 d f to the pinky yeah flying money oh
my God it's flying it's growing it's
evolving it's growing wings the money is
flying these days
damn oh we going to get our money if we
can fly how we going to grab it we got
to go instead of fly fishing we got to
go money
fishing lunch box D looking for the top
than for the pinky which is the last one
1.55 million Subs do right after
releasing a banger coincidence I think
not my fifth birthday in kfp was a few
days ago so it feels the like the Fredy
life was my birthday present too pretty
life special for me so sweet of
you yeah the 1.5 five caught me off
guard somehow like I didn't realize that
we were hitting that yeah noways I'm
just happy about um any small movement
in growth you know because it's slow for
a long time now but there's sometimes
there's some phases where it's a bit
more some streams that are a bit more
you know yipp 1.56 soon soon I don't
know maybe maybe maybe maybe we're
growing we're growing definitely I'm
working hard to grow
kfp and give us more employees so that
you guys don't have to be
overworked if I could subscribe a
thousand times I would thank you I
appreciate that yeah it's the fault that
counts well happy belated birthday
looking for the top your fifth
already like I really don't understand
the logic behind Okay I mean I
understand if I think about it but I
find it very
mysterious that I had four birthdays in
Holo and you had
five magic are you living in a different
timeline or are you in two time
and I haven't even been here for 5 days
how can you have five years how have how
can you have five birthdays when I've
only been here for four
years just makes no
[Music]
sense good it's breaking my mind so I'm
going to end the stream you know it's
good timing um I need to think about
this a little bit behind the
scenes there's no logic behind this it's
it's probably got to do something with
the Illuminati I'm gonna come back to
you guys with a conspiracy theory okay
um
so thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you for watching today those two
streams tomorrow is members only we're
going to finish monari yay we're
reaching the end finally of that
Marathon can you believe it I'm now
going to go so that the VOD can be
watched The W on theand waa and gigy On
Demand
today
yeah feel free to play the game more if
you want in your free time
guys the E Eternal Community will be
surely happy to have some you know more
people running
around yeah maybe maybe that way will
get the economy flowing more too can we
still send m oh I think you probably can
oh my God I'm going to
be I'm going to be hit in the face like
a stone like a boulder is going to be
thrown at me with all the mail I'll be
looking at when I come back is that how
it's going to
be hopefully don't don't expire I don't
think so but I'll check in maybe every
other
[Music]
day Okay in German we stay a vas in Al
oh I see some bad ratings
o Al good
night I don't know anything you are the
one who knows
everything H throat is tired head is two
cat is
two m he
[Music]
oh a