[Music]
do
so
[Music]
one
cake mommy
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
everybody
it's us the saviors of tonight of today
and we are here to entertain you
yeah yeah yeah yeah let's start off
thank you for inviting us
no
it was an open invitation you guys all
said yes let me join and i'm happy that
you guys wanted to join uh to make this
evening not so empty to fill up european
uh primetime alice yes
europe is very lonely without you girls
happy to be
yeah it seemed fun and then i wake up
and
everyone was here yeah i'm excited to
play with you
i love your motivation sana because it's
like super early in the morning over
there and you still wanted to join thank
you
i mean like
who wouldn't want to wake up for all of
you me
i want to get up at 5 30. i mean i did
it before too i think but i'm not not
really my first choice but anyway let's
have each beautiful girl introduce
themselves let's start with uh the top
right on my screen fana
hello uncle fonna i'm fonda from
ho ian council i'm the hero nature and
i'm excited to draw today
yay
drawing is also your hobby isn't it
it isn't i think a lot of us yeah
like a lot of counsel you know
actually no not only counsel everyone in
the leanne likes to draw everyone
thank you
give it up for fun
thank you thank you
recently had her birthday and her
birthday is now a birthday merch is now
on sale so go get your birthday bird
you guys gotta remember that stuff is
only available for one month so get it
while it's hot otherwise you'll miss out
on it and you'll regret it for the rest
of your life yeah
that's right
okay
[Music]
all right
it is a speaker space from holley in
council
good morning good morning
good morning
what do you eat for breakfast besides
bread i know you're a lover of bread
ah i haven't eaten breakfast yet i just
woke up and um
yes brush my teeth but what do you like
to eat for breakfast
yeah
oh okay well that's not an option
[Laughter]
yeah austria's uh very far
very far i don't
i don't i don't like to say i live in
australia anymore so now i can proudly
say i'm far away although i would love
to visit australia one day never been
but you guys make it kind of difficult
to enter your country just like japan
[Music]
didn't i make a rocket ship for alma
before can i not borrow that one
uh it's in the workshop
what happened with it did you break it
yeah one of the
jets exploded oh
[Music]
i'm sucker for that
yeah
yeah hi
it just looks so good hi ina this is
your usual streaming time slot and i i
took it away from you it's mine now
oh i got this i could have slept in
kiara i'm kidding
no sleep it's time to draw enough no
sleep
actually there's no war behind the
scenes uh when
i heard ttrpg was cancelled i
i actually
dm'd dmt9 was like do you want to do the
minecraft collab
and then we ended up saying you know
what maybe a big collab or something
else is better but yeah we haven't been
playing minecraft what's up with that
what's up with that i was thinking
so we can like work on
connecting them sometimes you're saying
your mind goes down so it didn't get
eaten
okay good anyone who didn't do it we
were reminded by management several
times
oh everyone did it yes i think so
wow
cali do it i haven't checked if it
worked or not but i did it
now i am
doubting myself and doubting my memory
well uh maybe after the stream you can
go check it out if it worked
minecraft time
okay next up who just uh
had a stream in her new office
hey amit yeah
i call me too i said hello english
number one detective amelia what's up
what's up
how's the house how's it feeling in the
new office streaming from the new office
comfy
it's comfy yeah i like it i'm excited to
get back to streaming catching this i
missed your streams on
oh
um come back to us come back to us
i'm here we missed you
okay glad to have you back on it and
last but not least
oh god that mess in the chat is made by
none other than uh gouda
do you guys know what she was trying
[Music]
all the little boxes square on square
boxes looks like what it's almost moving
boxes
you just push them over to gooda's place
huh you're like you deal with those i
don't wanna i don't wanna flatten them
you're gonna land
up and you cannot stop me
no she's gonna mix it all up it's my
favorite board atlantis let's
go
give me a sharpie let's go
oh but but i think uh
good as you have a kitten now right she
will be happy with uh boxes
[Music]
my cat don't care about boxes now he
cares about me climbs me like a tree i'm
the boss
i take it as a wind that's nice
i remember when my babies were still
really really small they also were
constantly like sitting on me but when
they get older they kind of stopped
doing that guru
you can you are mine you can hear my cat
climb the back of my chair on screen
sometimes cat zoomies i love it when
they're so needy like that it's so cute
i mean mine are still needy but they
they take like a certain amount of
distance yeah they don't want to sleep
on me they just want to sleep right next
to me
it's cute with you but not with you
yeah exactly let's catch you
okay so today we're playing draw and
guess
there are two game modes there's one
where basically one person draws we all
look at it and we guess at the same time
in the chat what it is
until we get it right i guess i know
there i think there might be a time
limit and then there is another time uh
game mode that we're also gonna try but
it's a bit hard to explain uh
it's like
let's say i get a word a lot of people
get a word at the same time we draw
and then
another person
sees what i drew and
tries to guess it uh
no i don't know i don't know whatever
we're just seriously afraid
of as well
[Applause]
uh something i think no that's not it i
changed one thing that we only have 30
seconds to draw it says very dirty
seconds we can only draw with one color
one pen and normal mode wait what was
that are you donald duck
ah i'm sorry
but later we can also switch this mode
where your drawings turn invisible yeah
okay but for now uh wait rounds
i don't know four it's always it says it
will only take nine minutes wow
okay let's do five then
okay and
okay let's get the first round started
there's like slight changes we can make
but for now this is what we're gonna do
let's go
[Music]
okay oh i try it's a long word okay uh
wait
this is the right mode are you seeing
what i'm drawing
yeah i think it's blue
oh [\h__\h]
oh
so much pressure
oh we need more than 30 seconds okay
okay i thought 30 seconds was a good
amount but apparently it wasn't
circle circle
circle
oh
[Music]
that
gave you all the easy word the warm-up
just the warm-up for understanding yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
wait what was it
detective
four letters you know oh i got a random
word and it sucks
there's a button at the bottom that says
get around the word yeah oh
[Music]
oh wait cheese
is that supposed to be a country oh no
you're minus one
the chat confuses me it says someone
guessed it but i don't see it in the
chat then it was just
counting
um i think it hides the correct answer
yeah it has the correct answer i'm not
smart
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah want to get turtles my plan is to
get turtles
a towel
i want frogs and turtles
all right what do we have here table
what's a table that is
a table
that is a
dog
one
dog one what ah dog under table
show us what you got
what
no
oh gosh i wish that was me
what
i don't
okay
me
it's an easy one
i did a random word nice
wait what
oh it shows the order and how
how fast who it was first there uh-huh
yeah oh come on
she's standing on the shelf who's that
that's right it's a face
in german we like being
the drawing time being the same as the
the uh
thinking of a word time is just
not enough interesting yeah yeah it's a
little bit fast
i'll add some more time next time you
can't stare at your word too long yeah
or you're in trouble
what is that
a photo word
um
[Music]
oh no how does this work
um
hmm
this is such a good drawing
[Laughter]
oh god
um
i can't think of good things
no random word yeah random way okay next
time
oh cute
[Music]
okay
drinking so much tea lately
oh my god this is hard it's around the
world green tea black tea all of it
yes
wine
that's a book oh it's not it's a hat is
it you don't have much time man
this is hard i'm sorry i'm sorry
yeah okay
and where's this similar word
um
oh
interesting
wow some people haven't abstracted
groups
[Music]
oh that was like triplets
oh my goodness that's a long word
i thought it was a mutant
original
is
come on
come on come on
where are we going come on
all right chicken
happy
turkey
mutton
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
ukraine
ah
[Music]
there's so many things that can go wrong
with an elevator if you just start
thinking about it just jump in and jump
out
i i like elevators suck
be sure to jump in if i win one with you
what is this
[Music]
[Applause]
nice
ah close there's only four letters
oh oh there's a number of letters up
there oh i didn't look at that i thought
it was a generation
okay this is a random word i'm sorry
this is really hard
oh dear um beans
how do you draw this
random words it's just so difficult yeah
random words are hard
i just actually think a word
[Music]
come on
it's like this and then it's like this
it's like
ah
what is the name
[Music]
wow
that's too difficult
how would you couldn't even remember how
an improv
two-point perspective
uh
legs
rise no
what fun how what's that oh what
don't don't ask me how i guessed it
[Music]
ten seconds
oh
[\h__\h]
how was that
[Music]
wait what's the
i know it's perspective
what
[Music]
oh i gotta hide the code next after the
video just suddenly closes over there
it's always wrong
[Music]
i
nice
well i feel like a winner too
wow
let's go oh
god damn it god suddenly showing the
code like that
to me
it's still just us really it's still
just us yeah i shouldn't leave
oh you're gonna leave that
okay
does someone else wanna make it i feel
like it always gives me the same code if
i make a new room
oh wait let me i can make it i can test
it
yeah i still get the same code
oh i can make one okay okay finally
okay
we kind of do
bless us with your grace
i mean
i'm into so many colors
um let's do
the same mode but with more seconds
there was like 30 seconds and something
around 80 seconds and something that's
even longer i think that 80 seconds or
so is enough
okay oh man
you think 81 seconds because
it's a long time huh
i think so
oh yummy
how do you change your color click on
the link below
oh wait wait
click on where
the little black dot
oh yeah there's a dot on above like
just saying the little dot doesn't mean
anything
it's like i said so many thoughts no
problem
okay i'm i'm ready
okay i hope i picked the right set ready
we will find out yeah we'll find out
and game is back in a moment after
everyone
yeah apparently nice is much longer
a skull
let's go
there we go oh
okay
if you want to make up your own word
one two three
this is rough okay um you can do it yeah
you're a good artist believe in yourself
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i didn't say anything
okay i can't improve from this what
peak drawing hint what is america all
about
oh yeah
that is a loaded question you can't ask
that
breaker just kidding
it was how in the hell was that freedom
what the hell
wearing skirts is better
oh yeah loves no underwear
oh right
there
huge
that's the pink man i didn't like the
choice of words okay um
um
[Music]
ah okay hey what's oh uh someone guessed
it okay i don't need to give a hint
what's this
what's in your what's on your
what's on your
ah
[Laughter]
hey yo watching what's on your tongue
today
who is on your
that's a good one
[Music]
yeah we can only choose words after all
not make them ourselves i still can't ah
that's okay okay bring it
bring it on baby
like good drawing
yeah
[Music]
like i can tell right away
one two three four five
what is
oh god
what are those
was that easy oh
what oh oh no i was just overthinking
get out of the room chicken driving get
that chicken get out of the car
that's it okay
he's a guy let's say i was
or decision
oh
that's true
that's a macaroni
let's say
that's a nice box because it's called
he's drawing in yellow it doesn't mean
it's cheese
yeah okay the brain says cheese
what do you think it is it's not cheese
it's cheese
what is this
a goblin
oh
no no one got it yet
who says
[Music]
a mouse
i feel like there's some plot unraveling
here i know what it is i just don't know
what the word is
it looks like a takatashi
with a hat
yeah
what is the word
what are you trying to say oh
maybe like a shift crew
yeah
our film crew
wig
what
[Music]
oh what oh why are there some really
difficult ones and some really easy ones
what i don't get it
you're just making it more complicated
no it makes perfect sense
think simple that is the difficulty
thinking is simple it's just too
difficult
oh now you're giving yourself all one of
those holy
holiness he's vibrating
oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
no you can do it
that sounds very cranky clover
he's a grumpy old man i love dad
ah
wait
one two three four five six
six letters
it's a
what what does uh
say she doesn't like this
ah okay okay it is
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
i think we might be
uh
i'll let the environment
oh
hi
you gotta think outside the box not in
sun
but it's warm in the books oh
comfy
books one two three four five six seven
[Applause]
[Music]
uh speed
how did you get that
because brain why is it a crocodile oh
yeah oh yeah
oh that's is that me marrying pat pat
from see you later alligator cause i
freaking love him so much
i love him
a man that game was so good i found it
because of you
later alligator it's such a cute game
yeah that one's really cute yeah
it warmed my heart that's one of my
favorite games of all time now oh really
yes yes right yeah that's cute
it's a good endorsement
is that
the teammates are coming not sponsored
oh god everybody get down
[Music]
not my branch mine's horn
is
[Music]
ah the farthest yellow chicken has horns
two wonderful versions
i'm not sure how to do this one um
okay how about this
just guessing german words oh
and then like um how about this
and then how about oh how about
but like one is a bow and an arrow and a
sword and then there's a wrench
and stuff like that
oh
[Music]
differently though
i would have just drawn like
maybe minecraft interfaces
it is kind of hard though
very well done yeah yeah very well done
smart i guess that is called equipment
oh dear
go go go go go terrible i hate these all
okay fire us with your
oh my god i don't know how to draw this
okay nine letters
i love them we draw excess words or not
please please
[Music]
what is that
oh
they're mad
no
this stands for confrontation and
differing opinions because it's quick
[Music]
without drawing excess words i don't
know
oh
um
there are several ways to draw it
uh
three letters ah
oh come on
[Laughter]
just type in w
nice that was easy
five letters
by inna
ah
uh
stokes
i know i almost typed
stone oh that's a perfect time
[Music]
that's just stunks
why is that not graph g or a p h another
word for the graph maybe i don't know ah
oh geez ah
[Music]
learning english words
yeah trying to help what is it standing
you're close girl you're close just
think about music too gura
yeah oh yeah cali currently that's her
album in the music
[Music]
i was also missing out okay
[Laughter]
is this participation point
yes yes yes
oh
that's an eye that's another eye one two
five oh
um
oh
yeah
let's go
let's go i saw you're still high
holy life think
who's your tinker
you shape a noodle
clothes i think almost all of you
already guessed it but in a different
way
yeah oh my gosh
it's a good drawing though
who's so angry at us what did we do
don't be so mad guys
we're trying
oh damn he's so angry
he's so happy
anger
okay we just don't know what anger is
you know
yeah you're better off that way
understandable ina never angry never
i've never seen you know angering before
i just changed the wrong word probably
oh look at that look at that profile
look at that until 7.
[Music]
how do i help our friends here i don't
know
it's not a house it's a
ah they're not gonna know though
you can eat
egg
of a pie okay
have you guys watched scrubs before i
love that part where the janitor is like
how much how many nickels or something
like that is a quarter or something like
that
and you know that it's in it you've seen
it what
where where the janitor is like giving
in the first episode so it's giving uh
uh jd a riddle about about uh what was
that what is that riddle
something a stupid riddle
ah there's something like five i have
five nickels one of them is not a nickel
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
oh no
aha
nice it's not mad no no
arithmetic
[Music]
i can count
[Laughter]
i thought it was in england too
oh
[Music]
oh that's cute
that's uh teammates holding a picture of
ame
look at this photograph before they eat
it
that's so cute
[Music]
i don't get it it's cute
could be a lot of things
it could be anything
could be
a picture of
uh
of your favorite
comedian
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i can't believe
why did no one write that yet why didn't
no one guess that yet i was about to
guess
pictures of me
[Music]
oh it looks like a
oh
looks like a
yeah
ah
easy
looks like a what
looks like a looks like a
looks like looks like
i can't help you
i can't make it any easier than this
come on
guess what i'll eat left
i think one of these i feel like this
one exactly was featured in your omo cat
fashion review
probably
it wasn't quite rhymes with
one of these
perhaps
crying for them
[Music]
[Laughter]
it was out
i got an indian i got
oh
[Laughter]
immediately
what's another word for corpse
i thought there was a portal in the body
of my body
no no
oh dear
oh
okay
um
dissect no no no
[Laughter]
don't don't break his heart
why are you smiling like that though
he's getting sick today
he's doing his job he likes his job
that's his passion
and he earns a lot of money from it so
they're both easy let's go with the one
that's maybe not that easy
[Music]
oh it's not
um
okay that's the important part
[Laughter]
what did i do dammit i don't know what
they wear um
don't get distracted
on them
[Laughter]
i thought this would be easier
how in the world
she has a chart i tried to look at stuff
oh yeah this one's gonna be easy okay
why is the first thing you think of when
you think of nurses
i was thinking about
thinking about glasses
sexy halloween outfit for the
film
but that's my last track and i didn't
know
what to try
oh
[Laughter]
completely remembered how that looked
like originally
oh is that
is that anger again no one two three
four five six seven eight nine
that's not even i can't spell
oh
that's not it anyway
what what
ah what
okay
what nice face that's shin
you draw really good oh my goodness
wow
oh okay damn um
surprised that you you figured that out
nice
okay
ah one two three what what what is this
that's so really lettuce no i mean where
are you are you leaving me again
why is she crying
she's eating bread she has to be
it's bread no internet connection no tv
connection oh it's a gift uh
game sold out
look
um
uh
whole life is question mark
um
plus gaming
equals
um
who i plus gaming is
me tuber i don't but there's so many
letters let's
something you need to play
[Music]
that's why you're crying
we hate that
we hated
it uh should have just sent a link to
the channel the
channel
anyway
salt
this is one two three is that inna
[Music]
in her new year's outfit maybe
or maybe not
i don't remember how you drew it i was
trying to draw it like how you drew it
anyway um
arms
oh geez you know what
it's not going to work
i'll make it easy for everybody
what what but why is it
i guess because there's an option i had
everybody get it
no what is this
oh this is hard
[Music]
oh my
yeah all the choices are really hard
[Music]
oh that's kind of bad
um
[Music]
no it's not
what is it
it's one word though right
no it's yeah it's one word but like it's
like a this thing describes a
story
from
the
oh
[Music]
nice okay you tried man you tried
little guy
submarine [\h__\h] hold on
redo again
how do i do all this
40 seconds
what is this you pick the teflon
jeez i really didn't think it was gonna
be tough what is this
ah this is so good
what is this
baby cage
oh my god
[Music]
shrimp i know there's yourself cause in
my stream it's always we always stream
in the bedroom scene i guess
why what are you thinking aha okay
uh
yeah yeah
medium difficulty
what is that watson
popcorn the giant broccoli
when small almond becomes
big
growing
older
can you tell him you're close yeah
also chat thank you for also trying to
guess things i see you there nice to see
you
active and alive
four
cheese
yellows
uh
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
because i know you're sweaty
i listen to your stream
i have thermal paste like all over my
hands and face
easy
what that's what thermal power why did
you put thermal paste over your hand
offer the pc and just thermal paste oh
yeah
i was changing out my cpus uh to test
them don't worry the worst thing you can
get off your hands you just need a tiny
amount of it though
[Laughter]
sometimes it gets on you and you don't
know that it's on your hand you just
like rub it off
yeah
maybe this is the easiest
oh god
[Music]
looks like they're holding a lip
uh i give a hint it's for school
ah
where's school what
yeah look at the amount of letters
though
nice nice size okay okay
yeah what
[Laughter]
oh
wow we're pretty close this time not
lost anymore
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm hiding the screen because colors
really fun
really really close oh it's good
yeah
so fast shall we try the for the last
time since we don't have that much time
anymore uh should we try the other one
do one more game
how long it could yeah
that's too much 47 is a little bit maybe
half i don't know sound or anything 47
is good yeah
it doesn't even take that long yeah
let's let's let's do it if i
[Music]
okay
different game mode let's go
let's go
do you guys see something i only see a
white screen
i just say we have waiting here
waiting for them
oh
oh oh
good do you see something
oh i only have a wide screen i think my
game crashed
oh no
it says waiting for other players oh
yeah maybe you have to wait actually oh
yeah yeah maybe wait yeah but i'll wait
let me guess everybody um my mouse moves
how does it turn
oh i see
it's just one yeah everybody has it i
don't think that many people will know
this i know who wrote this kiara
no i literally just have a complete wide
screen in the game
oh music i need to
yeah yeah the game is going so maybe we
should rely on yeah we should be alone
okay ah how do i end this sorry okay
let's pause the game i'll rio
return to lobby okay oh yeah you didn't
crash
all right nice to rejoin
okay
my pc my gamer pc couldn't handle this
super hd game
yeah
can i say what my word was
yes
it was godric
how am i supposed to jump i figured that
you're a good artist you could do a good
rendition okay right i know but they
don't know what it is
like give enough a challenge word
easy on everyone else it's not a problem
of me drawing it's a problem with
someone guessing
it's not a challenge okay so the problem
with you drawing
oh
[Music]
sorry that was a tough one that i gave
you
please mercy
i don't know how you're going to draw
that
i only have a mouse and a dream to my
name
what
i don't want to draw no
no what i don't
[Music]
oh we have like no segments oh god you
have to draw really fast
wait what are we all right just drawing
this oh
[Music]
else chad um this is this is really
clear
but we'll see it later guys
we'll see the other
matches and all that oh
it's so stressful
so stressful
[Applause]
okay wait the game is way louder than
before what the heck
am i allowed to draw okay i know it's
like way more intense all of a sudden
oh my god
[Music]
help
fish
oh god i don't know if that's gonna uh
what is this
um
it could be so many things
uh
i do not know what this is
maybe it's just
yes it is really fast but yeah drawing
is
do we all guess at the same
time okay everyone's guessing right now
he's looking at different things
no
love
yummy yummy okay this is rough i love
tropical milk
oh we get to see everyone's drawings and
guesses of the word sunflower oh well i
thought it were some flowers
yeah and then someone else looks at it
[Music]
like yes
oh
yeah i gave you that word and oh
[Music]
i thought i saw pigtails
okay i saw pigtails somewhere else
oh
okay
all right
okay i don't know what i thought it was
somebody misspelled it okay guys the
drawing is
[Laughter]
[Music]
i tried to hide
yeah oh my god
that's close
that's a good one
does it only give you guys one choice
yeah it only gives one choice it's kind
of funny
like what's your favorite drawing but
i'm gonna give you one
wave oh
i drew
that there we go this is easy it's an
easy one
right
[Applause]
[Laughter]
i went above and beyond i shouldn't have
dropped myself
without the fish it would have been
better maybe
[Laughter]
what is that give that to someone
totally out of context would they know
what it is
oh
wait
wait even the drawing is basically the
same as mine
wow oh come on
come on
that is so cold
it does look like somebody carrying like
a bag of money
[Music]
ah
i'm sorry
i got it
right it was like it's either santa or
you know
or not
i'm sorry
i could have i could have gotten it
close close oh yes
does have twin tails yeah
hmm i love santa's twin tails does
anybody win i like all of them
we had no win
we all won because we all had fun
another round yeah yeah because
it wouldn't be like 47 minutes
[Music]
i don't know why i'll get something
pretty easy
i gave something hard that was the only
thing in my mind at this moment
[Laughter]
yeah who wrote butthole by the way
what
guess who
who put butthole ah
we tried this word in the practice i
think okay my who put butthole
unanswered question
if you put butthole where you raise your
hand
all right it was me but i just i didn't
know what to put
easy
[Music]
oh gosh
easy i'm so sorry
um
what
we're going for easy awards
i don't know if this is easy
i apologize my painting's bad
i like that the game gave me the option
to turn down the butthole though
very nice as if it's not no i don't know
what this looks like
oh no
[Music]
oh i don't know what this creature looks
like
so time to hook up a reference there's
no mommy
oh no i know what this is is this
is this what i think it is it has to be
right
[Music]
okay
this one won't go wrong right easy
this is the only winner that we're going
to get probably
okay oh my god don't mess it up
[Music]
so close to greatness but we'll give it
we'll give it a win
oh that's difficult art
oh art
squidward
dammit
[Music]
banana boat my idea seriously yes um oh
easy
oh my god surely banana boat's not the
word that would be stupid
hey but it's both a boat it's
[Music]
on the banana boat it's close it's close
somewhere in the same universe at least
[Music]
it could have been worse
thank you you really want to go river
rafting huh
let's do it together
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
oh my god
but at least well you were you were
actually trying to draw m m's right in
that moment so
that's something
someone gave for the word ticket
so i have to remove myself
[Laughter]
oh
no pizza
where
[Music]
wait
the eyes
[Laughter]
[Music]
i couldn't remember the name i should
have drawn one dying at the bottom
[Laughter]
just the fire i thought it had a chance
a good chance
it's a cute baby i like your cinnamon
food it's a warm on fire
i feel like cynical husband
has a nose or something
oh
i'm gonna troll
okay i've got a troll but specifically
for one person in this room
oh
good luck
i'm nervous
uh
okay please have mercy
we can do this we can we can figure
something out something simple oh no
what's that pretty easy
[Music]
oh that's hard
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay should we go back to the ones in
tears
can we give the same words we can just
do one round um or two rounds however
many were missing and we can start the
first round by giving the same words
maybe okay i want to go again
quick oh enter quickly
sorry i didn't see that coming but maybe
we can yes
maybe we can try it
you can
oh man i have tears in my eyes
i'm sorry
what are you right what's so funny no i
won't tell you that i hope i hope we can
repeat that whole thing
[Laughter]
oh whoever wrote that word please write
it again and make me suffer even more
yeah it ends up being the same i think
so
maybe someone else can do it
but with um
i don't know i guess the
the game mode that we just did with the
same amount of seconds and
less
rounds i guess
i don't know how to set it up but i made
a room okay over the settings
uh fun on my different right do you
remember the settings
um
no
it was 15 seconds
okay
15 seconds
rounds were there supposed to be
no
we can do like two rounds right
yeah let's do like two rounds if you
have the choice gouda
also we need to close
oh
wait two rounds you said um
sorry can we do one oh okay one round
i'm sorry no problem
let's make it feel like it's so loud
with you guys
yeah
yeah i don't even rest up after this yes
oh my god
it was so funny though
i can't get pizza man out of the out of
my head
pizza man fun
the settings are confusing kind of yeah
i hope i did that right where is
okay okay okay nice
but uh i hope i did this right
wait i'm not ready
oh okay fast mode for sana maybe does
fast mode matter i mean 14 minutes seems
okay what do you think sana yeah i can
do i can do that much okay
[Music]
let's try it
i hope this is right oh god
is it right
yeah yeah
wait what did i write last time uh
oh god
oh hmm i remember
[Music]
so unstable we do we do real quick let's
try one more time quickly
get out
you can escape and then return to life
yeah yeah
nobody sees it i'm ready just waiting
for
all right
okay i'm ready let's go
i'll take it off okay
don't crash on us now game
come on do your best
oh okay i'll change my word down because
it's for someone else
[Music]
i don't know any funny words
um
[Music]
i don't know that's not funny
but maybe something funny will come out
of it
just right now you're not laughing again
okay
[Music]
i have the waiting for players stuck on
my thing but it never goes away oh
but chris should we try one more time
one more time to reverse one last time
one more time
i'm surrounded with you guys
that gives me another chance to change
my word chad give me a good word
quick chat
uh
oh god quick chat
oh dear
yeah i was thinking that too
i was thinking that too but maybe
because as you said it so many people
think about it too oh no
mind blinking
i hope it doesn't overlap with anyone is
someone crashing in the game right now i
hope not
nope um
waiting for other players
oh
oh my god are wrong
that magical word has reached me again
[Music]
it's fate
how do i
how do i even draw this like
correctly
[Music]
oh there's so much time
oh yeah there's a lot of time but not
enough to draw everything
all right
like i can enjoy your cute features
yeah
draw us cutely please
i don't know how to improve this how do
i improve this
it's too cute
[Music]
and then i'll give i'll give you a
little thing
this is hard
[Music]
i don't know it says oh
probably that what the chat said
oh
oh i like that um
what's inside me
in my mind right now
wait what the its eyes look like
something like this
cute i like it it's so cute
this thing is so cute
ah cute that's way too much time
cute
let's try harder then
how's everyone doing
i think with so much time we won't have
any issues matching our guesses anymore
um
[Music]
maybe it gives us more time to add
unnecessary details to confusion
yeah
why are you
that's how i'm feeling right now i've
seen you before
i put this word in the last round too
but not this round everyone gets the
same word i still have different words
um
he's the the person who brought us
happiness
oh happiness
fear
and tears wait who has braids
what
grapes there's braids i can't think who
has braids
it's happening oh goodness
pizza
it's a big man
[Music]
it works
[Applause]
welcome back pizza man we missed you
you're a nice triangular shape
animal
[Applause]
what is a fursona is that not a frisbee
exactly
thank you
that was adorable
i'm so sorry i spoke that wrong
what was that supposed to be
barbie
okay
i was gonna go kirby but then i went to
college
[Music]
yay
i'll give this one i'll give this yes
oh no oh please hey kirby it's just so
much happiness
[Music]
very popular right now though
yeah
[Music]
okay
the opposite
oh
the chat casted right though they
guessed dakimakura when they saw that
first drawing yeah
you're like oh i know this
but not a phone
ring
[Music]
that is
yeah
you know you did something right of the
game agrees with you damn
perfection is this the last round oh yes
let's do another one i want to do
another one this one
oh boy
um
[Music]
oh i don't love that i just need to see
more of it
okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
oh
oh okay um
i don't know how to draw them but i hope
this is somehow correct
i hope i do them justice
what do i look like
are you all
concentrating yes yes
making masterpieces
for the next person
[Music]
uh
oh what's that i don't know about this
one
i ah rely too much on chat i have to
stay true to myself uh-oh
yeah no i i wrote my own thing
even though the chat was right
this one is easy i don't even need that
much time take it away from me take it
away from me
[Music]
okay
yeah translated that to japanese and we
have
[Music]
it was it was funnier when it was faster
yeah
i feel like i'm adding too many details
and making it more confusing give
yourself limits
end it faster don't give yourself too
much channel
make a masterpiece no i'm not so easy
come on you can do it last person
okay
[Music]
where
going on vacation
[Laughter]
always sleeping people looked very loved
[Music]
they want to be lovely
i love i love alligators
[Music]
he became
in both situations god is getting it
over it yeah it is
it's the same thing
it's basically that getting over it is
basically just about fauna growing into
a big big beautiful plant
what's that
running plant
golden plant
a
i mean it is candy asleep yes
we are generous today
we've had way worse attempts before so
yeah
did you did you see the new girls debut
she doesn't like sweet things at all at
all
yeah possible oh
[Music]
think of the staff as her mommy
maybe she'll give this one
it's a
new it's a family a story of a beautiful
family creation no wonder um it was
acting
weird no no no no no
oh so
[Laughter]
run
pancakes okay
that one we didn't mess up
yummy
yeah pancake
oh nice and i guess pancake breakfast
you can breakfast
pancake for dinner yeah i just wanted to
give him um more ways to win in case it
was just breakfast not pancake oh
big brain you know
yeah
yum yum yum i want some pancakes i wish
i wasn't too lazy to make breakfast for
wait there's ranking
oh yeah we never got this far
what oh
wow
okay
well thank you everybody okay fun round
uh maybe we can play it again that was
fun yeah especially when we have no time
yeah
and that was fun
for organizing the craft no problem
easy peasy just like the one with
confidence
it was worth waking up for ah
it's good to hear
wow maybe you'll become a morning person
if i just ask you for a lot of
collaborations in the morning and push
it
[Laughter]
i'll make you pancakes
there she is there she is
yeah yeah this is
kind of uh as a replacement to
uh ttrpg because unfortunately that was
canceled but we'll do that surely
sometime soon so please wait for that
everybody if you
if you're eager to uh see how teacher
rpg continues or ends
yeah um thank you everybody for coming
here for gathering here today girls it
was fun really had a good good laugh
today
one of my best
yeah let's play more games more games
more games yeah we know what
a while ago a while ago someone some
girls of you here they were like yo
let's play raft and it never happened
what's happening with the raft cooler oh
my god i just wanted to play a raft yeah
there's too many of us so we have to
have multiple rafts yeah but then
nobody continued talking about it
it was we were all busy with the fest i
think yeah yeah yeah okay let's try it
again and also as we said we need to
revive the minecraft server i think yeah
yeah we need to do it like something
else to build mentality the new ceiling
oh
yeah oh my god you make it even you're
gonna make it even bigger
yeah yeah i gotta reach the top and then
um i'm planning big things i just don't
have any other resources
please that power is really important
for you
all right
all right so many plans for the future
and thank you everybody for watching
today uh please subscribe to the girls
channels they're all in the description
if you haven't subscribed yet do it and
with that um i say goodbye to you all
and the girls say goodbye too
and in german we stay
happy
[Music]
have a good night bye bye
do
[Music]
you