e
e e
[Music]
great promotion great promotion good job
good job
[Music]
La all the you play that game
Y at least you're hearing something
now first album point of
[Music]
view it tastes so so so sweet when you
come around kiss me I'm taking down
picture to me like
a you
got love
[Music]
Rush
a you're in my heart you'll always stay
right here won't fade
away give
me the great Wanderer
[Applause]
time I'm walking by the Liv FL before my
eyes the SM still I'm
[Music]
reaching
retrospective to truth and every part of
my being Des best feeling tell me what
am I to
you flip
[Music]
talking
n
n I'm
sorry for being all over the place h
it's because I am all over the
[Music]
place do you do you say you do feel the
same
wow well at least there's part of you
here no now now now now it's always the
full me but it's just like
um um um um one one second I'm here one
second I'm
there you've been wondering too much
[Music]
y I am W
Wonder
W you guys are not saying it correctly
yet w w the w w
[Laughter]
[Music]
one I just record I just recorded Korean
version of do you let's
go but I still have some stuff to record
probably yeah I might just reuse all the
um like at least as far as I can the
backup vocals of my previous
recording actual K-pop
yeah sleep
talkking sleep
twerking sleep
twerking twerk with me
boy I'm Play Already Here midnight w w
w we're going to play Hotline Miami to
that
taking one step taking one back and then
shoot you and shoot you
back oh my God your birthday was
yesterday who's who's her Rowan Hood
your German speaking friend you want to
see her grown
who is she who is she to
you not like I care or
anything well you you will have to wait
but happy birthday you'll have to wait
though can't think of anything now
anyway uh we're going to play H Miami
and tomorrow is my anniversary guys oh
my God
uh before we
[Music]
start imagine like
some you know what I
[Music]
mean you know what I mean
you know what I
mean it's not fitting this is not
fitting here let's say
this Never Going To Give You
Up never going to let you
down Never Going To Give You Never Going
To Give You Never Going To Give You Up
okay oh my God
what I am already
distracted I was just going to show you
my
SCH
quickly I'm in High Spirits today am I
I'm just stressed out I'm just stress
stretched out stretched out no I'm
stressed out so today h Miami 2o uh do
we have a chance of finishing
[Music]
it
no okay that's cool that's
fine that's that's fine uh tomorrow we
have fourth anniversary stream
and just say for anybody who is curious
about uh
merchandise um it will the sales will
not begin during the stream because it
wasn't possible because it's out of
office times they can't like handle it
at 3:00 a.m. jst which is fine to
me it will start um if you want to be
ready for it I'll already tell you now
because you you're going to want to get
limited I think some of you guys want to
be ready right right you want to be
ready so tell me let me tell you
now so uh currently it's planned to be
there's still some uncertainty but uh
it's most likely going to start at 900
a.m. jst so that's that's five no six
hours after the stream starting
time okay I'll be done streaming by that
time uh but
yeah just so you know if you want to be
awake for that 2: a.m. yeah you know it
is what it is uh that's what they
offered me
mhm yeah I'm I'm sorry you just got to
get up quickly and puty puty make some
clicks and then uh yeah and then go back
to
sleep the early bird uh or the late bird
gets the
merch yeah just so you
[Music]
know holy
M yeah H third anniversary stream is
going to be excited so please be there
uh it's going to be fun and I prepared
many things and um even some things
that almost deserve its own kind of
stream uh
yeah um yeah I don't oh my God you're
[Music]
bye yeah and then M anniversary 5 hour
collabor and it might even be more than
five it might actually be six hours
because the last one is going to be on
A's Channel and that one that one we
said um no time pressure it can be like
up to 2 hours um yeah uh which will
be marvelous for me in the middle of the
night but that's okay I'll do my best
I'll take a nap I actually planned I
scheduled a nap I
think before the
stream yes yes yes yes yes uh and yeah
you know the rest is like self
explanatory scheduled nap yes it must be
uh in in cases like this where my stream
is starting for me at 11 p.m. 11: p.m.
starts with Cali you know the debut
order CI waa wa at midnight for me um
Thena
[Music]
GA
mhm okay so
and uh get this please come tomorrow
it's oh I prepared so much and cow
carrot is like editing everything uh for
me actually I I I should be sending some
more
things probably probably he can wait a
few hours right
um is he
here Cow Car the hero we need yes
so far the first video is finished and
looking pretty good and now we're still
working on the second
one yeah yesterday after I came home I
sat down to like uh sort everything out
and pre-cut I pre-cut the footage a
little bit so that he doesn't have too
much
[Music]
work is that how to say the name I I I I
just say cow carrot y'all or cow ch
yeah so big UPS to my
hero
Nissa Nissa deamed me about my opening
intro being
muted I was on an idol meeting
okay ch ch
thanks for the r j oh my God just Mir
already oh my god get a
room okay H let's
go I guess we will play the game now
[Music]
ah back from the Wilderness do I even
know how to operate a PC anymore
H you remember what happened last time
in the
story vaguely maybe I don't think I
would be able to explain it don't ask me
don't ask me uh where game air
game and now we can t up
this story of two is very confusing yeah
cuz there's so many
dudes um
it's
not now this maybe get some people angry
uh at me but haai myami too I would say
it's not so much about the story um at
least for
me as a as a streaming game for me it's
just about uh screaming and having fun
um because it's a funny funny game
that's funny if only it would show it on
screen
Ah that's how you felt okay good same
okay okay well wonderful uh hello there
we go why you need so long eh what's
your problem
eh is this the screen that I used last
time I'm like
so so useless sorry I'm so what's going
on here with this what's what's this
why starting music is so relaxing isn't
it why is it like this I don't know I
don't know I don't know a why it doesn't
fit I don't know can we just have it
like this I know it's like OCD
inducing yeah so
[Music]
chill okay uh continue I guess
whatever
umak is music uh which one do I go in
this is so confusing to
me act two I guess
right Rising
Phoenix skip
intro
yes is this too loud I think it is I
mean not for me but for you
guys it's like on OBS it's
different
okay she ah wait this was ah yeah uhhuh
we already talked to him didn't
we did I not do this before yeah we
already did this one where how do I get
to the one that I want to
do
know how do I how do I get there did I
not save does it not safe what what did
I do something
wrong act
two oh
what why does it what is this like
interface design why does it like offer
me
H why does it offer me like not the
latest one when I have to like go look
for the latest one execution what is
this really bad UI
so confusing ex
oh w why all over the place okay am I
going to play that dude or what
oh oh no that's robot this is the right
one you have reached the wrong number
please hang up and try again
beep oh disc
go oh okay free mats we have uh the Tony
of course no weapons but killing
punches uh roll Dodge which I don't like
to use anyway chainsaw and
guns uh does that mean like I I wouldn't
be able to use knives and bats and
stuff well that that sounds fine like
chainsaw and guns would be my Preferred
Choice anyway shall we try
it oh wait no we two people no that
freaks me out how am I supposed to play
with two people who do I even
what what what you can switch how do I
switch left click for me right wasn't
that like already
like some some
some oh I don't have
to come
on wait he was still alive he is still
alive but I still have to restart okay
would be funny if it counts as one life
and I get to continue like like two
lives I guess the music guy doesn't get
shot though I
guess oh this is so confusing that's so
confusing
[Music]
not oh
yeah this is so
confusing and then they don't switch
guns or anything like that no gun gun
the gun guy can change to different guns
I would
assume select another match no that's
boring we have to try
[Music]
everything my God this is so
confusing the aim is like all over the
place for me I feel
like so can the Gunner switch how do I
switch again I literally forgot
everything oh let what if I run out of
ammo I'm going to run out of ammo now
let me
[Music]
test what the switches once he's
out ah okay there we go he so I can't
switch before I'm out
that's interesting oh okay
[Laughter]
oh I want that
gun
SMG these stairs maybe we'll use them
later V vroom it's like a lawn
mower oh there's a lot of people there I
don't know if it's smart to go with two
ammo left but you know we we'll just do
the door trick
the problem is that
one person kind of lags behind always
aka the gun guy so when I think I'm
already around the corner and ready to
shoot I may not be
ready yeah no hold on there it's it's uh
learning by doing
[Music]
I just think I'm controlling Mele that's
where the movement seems to CER yeah
seems like playing Ice Climbers really
is it similar I
wonder less brutal though oh someone
heard it
oh aim
ah okay okay okay I new gun oh he picked
it up out of M
[Music]
okay but we like a challenge
don't the Scream Of
Terror scream of absolute Terror what
does he have he has was
that yeah that was close combat okay m
oh guys I was uh I uh I was I was in the
wilderness
yesterday I came back with a quite a few
uh battle wounds AKA mosquito
BS but besides that I am
fine okay
oh God that's so
difficult give me this
one pick up that one wait who's who's
yeah there we go ah okay he just walks
over mosquitoes there freaking
mosquitoes man so
annoying there's especially a lot of
them in the
wilderness okay I think I'm I cleared it
besides him
are we killing
him oh open
[Music]
open I can't get into this room okay
who's left ah no it's okay it's go time
it's go
[Music]
time I'll deal with him later okay
hopefully no tick B yeah my my my my
instinct warned
me that there's many possible ticks
there uh
I was just wearing long
sleeved uh top and bottom so it should
be fine I I didn't see anything sticking
on me
[Music]
yet I'm going to go risky
uh-oh
ah the doorman ah
what's that is that his head oh that
that head is rolling
around space bar what's a space bar
nothing happens with space bar my
friends yeah I'm not I'm currently not
vaccinated for T I think we talked about
this but
[Music]
yeah did that work yeah okay oh
okay anyone else coming by know
okay this one we can take
Mee but he's got a buddy
[Music]
there okay this is so difficult because
like like weird to play when when you're
used to obviously playing alone with
like one character
I know we can learn them with the sound
too yeah
honestly I to do that more often it's
actually easy to get people to me and
then just chainsaw
them their guts out of their bellies did
you see that passing by because I have
to drag the gun guy out of there you
know oh
so that he can get a shot
[Music]
in I know the Strat now let's
go at least the second guy doesn't
sabotage your like Tails oh are we
talking Sonic now that that doesn't
sound like Ice Climbers to
me I'm I'm scared of the gun guy because
he will shoot one CC's chainsaw guy but
I'm I I want to shoot them obviously
first oh [\h__\h] wait was there a different
entrance yeah yeah we can go from
[Music]
there
here
oh oh yeah oh yeah and he was he
[Music]
doing y level clear oh hey it was
actually pretty easy even though I had
to get used to a new
character not bad yeah yeah
yeah makes me want to play Ice Climbers
I wonder if it's as brutal as this game
well do we talk to him now it says go to
car but you
know I can't die now after all right hi
what's going on I am quick and quack
quack quack quack quack
what's that what's that again that comic
uh don't with the with the
duckins Quick Quack what were their
names Quick Quack
Quack at least in German I think there
were something like that a quick quck on
quack oh my God such original
names the dude that got wrapped by her
girlfriend his girlfriend you mean
docktails
yes I used to uh I think read and watch
that maybe I think that was a
show
ah take yeah that's their German names
take trick
track huy dewy and Louie what that's
their English
names those are are German that's German
so
human they sound so human while the
German names don't sound like a human
would have this name ever you
know in Italian it's
qua
cute that's really short to
though is Donald not a well Donald yeah
we're not talking about that one anyway
why does he look so [\h__\h]
up H I don't know I told you there's
something Str going on you know what I
mean can you see that look right there
can you see it what is that someone must
have slipped me something I mean this
can't be happening it's like wow are
those masks are we in the jungle a
jungle I was in the jungle just
yesterday it was it was it was dangerous
very dangerous this place is dangerous
too but not as dangerous as the jungle
one doesn't mess with the
jungle stay out of the Jungle in the
future I
will I I want to go to the Jungle I quit
you know did I tell you that no more I
tell you I'm out done
phito there's no phito for
you yeah fito in like this yes are we
killing him or just taking us eye what
are you hitting me I I just want to go
home can you call Mary she'll she'll go
come and get me we'll call Mother Mary
for you is that blood am am I bleeding
do I need to go to the hospital guys
look I just want to go home
okay kind of
brutal oh one more one more to go H for
good
measure Brut
did you guys did you guys listen to
rain's new original song it's so
good it if it's spicy what was again sip
some tea if it's spicy just sip some tea
C minus
H oh new mask Mark hello Mark that
totally looks like a mark
yeah if it's
spicy just dip some PE
I stumbl to my
[Music]
Honolulu wait it's so easy to stumble
over your words like that uh uh wa be
careful when you sing your own
song uh I don't know if it's the heat
but I feel a bit drunk
me too I'm thinking about heading back
to
Camp what the [\h__\h] oh
what I'm good for another round or two
you guys head them back I'll catch up
with you later you don't tell me what to
do okay I'm going to show you how to
drink you hear
me well I I guess we we'll see you guys
back at the camp then just remember that
we have a job to do tonight
fellas oh oh we are in a a beautiful new
area very different look
here it's the
N ooh she's in the
oh SC me guys do you have a second I'd
like to get a picture of you if you
don't
mind sure my famous now what did I do
could could you send me a copy if I give
you my address
why does he want a
copy no need we we have a polar roid
would you need would you mind stepping
out into the sun here for are they going
to shoot him be nice please oh Peace's
he's doing peace sign I think why we
didn't want you on the picture I think
up up all right good luck out there guys
thanks for letting me get a
shot no no no worries man good luck to
you too
H okay oh wait are we just one guys why
am I double I'm so confused oh is this a
living plant that eats
people this is
moving
[Music]
e where how where am I going where what
what let's just go into the
jungle how do I get into my car
take the photo I took the photo Oh you
mean take isn't taking it with me
okay oh what is this a tent is this a
tent oh
chill scary [\h__\h]
man a military Camp oh
[Music]
that's almost like
claing take a lesson or two from me guys
about camping
tomorrow uh time to move out son Choose
Your Weapon wisely and make them shots
count Lord knows how many this
way you know those pink eyes I'm
I'm so sorry um I have to do something
really
quickly really real really
quickly those pink eyes and the baldness
doesn't that remind you of
someone thank you yui for putting that
into my recent memory I'm so sorry I'm
so sorry she's obviously a million times
more beautiful but come
on there's some kind of
[Music]
[Laughter]
similarity
oh he's clearly excuse me yeah yeah yeah
he's sexier yeah I mean look at those
caterpillar
eyebrows they literally look like
like I don't know like a bear on his
eyebrows Lord knows how many ruskies we
have out there do be careful my boy
don't you want any of my men dying on
meia here got a special Supply delivery
coming in tonight wouldn't want to drink
all that b bourbon alone not in this
goddamn Place why is the ground
blue what are you cooking
H Curry or
something it's nice that they have a a
really big change of scenery here I have
no idea why we are in a jungle where did
I
go but we are do I talk to you too no I
grab oh okay thank you I'm so stupid
I'll take um the
[Music]
rifle uh if I no
I couldn't take this one I guess we're
taking the shotgun
sorry then maybe we go here yeah cuz I
could go pretty far Ambush number
nine number
nine ooh are we fighting
outside no okay would be
[Music]
cool scary is it oh zom
me windows that big guy looks like he
may need more than although wasn't it
like shotguns are generally you know way
to go why does it say six and 10 do I
have a
Reload uh
hi oh yeah now he he took a moment to
die but
yeah right click to
swap uhoh okay now hold
on can I shoot over the table I don't
remember
[Music]
hi well so now we know he can shoot over
the table which means likely that uh I
can shoot over the
table
good
okay what do I do it went so well last
time you just need some time yeah to die
good good good good good ah
no no no no no
no is there another fat guy here no
okay so then I could switch to uh wait
how is this also a case where in order
to switch out the shooty shooty weapon I
have to first shoot all my
shots maybe how do you reload I can't
reload there's no
reloading there's so many
here out of
ammo okay that's
[Music]
fine only only one gun for the like the
whole
time
[Music]
wait okay okay hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hi hi hi hi hi
[Music]
uh I want to like combine you know
switch around and all
that I want to do a double kill of a
knife is that not possible
CU they were stacked
now can we start with both of them in
the room I think that would be actually
quite useful oh [\h__\h] a sh uh
wait what the left click left click left
click kiaha remember now well now
there's a lot of people in here
uh-oh uh oh patrolling back and forth
uhoh
ah
okay uh oh wait does that like a
machete give me
that I can't
switch slit fro hell yeah oh only one
left oh at least in here you know what
let
[Music]
me [\h__\h] I'm so confused cuz like now
it used to be always a tag with left
Mouse button but
now it's like both depending on the
weapon I want to use ah sorry guys this
another new character that I don't
understand yet
uh oh yeah left click left
click so confusing ah [\h__\h]
it uh
okay good good good we took out
three
uh three of them with the
rifles
okay clean clean
shots bada bing bada
boom what happened I click right right
click oh
uh uh
wait I wish you could still shoot him
when they are uh
underground [\h__\h] it's
difficult okay okay okay okay
okay saved some ammo on
that does
he let's see maybe get closer to the
door that would be
cool not close enough me is helpful here
oh
wait
oh oh okay I'm confused again but
thanks m
so
this listen to the many variations of
screaming key
keys you
[Music]
can have many different kinds of moods
come across depending on the key you
scream
in someone I'm I'm surprised nobody has
like yet to make uh some kind of like
remix you know you know how some people
just make songs with the sounds of
people uh those
you with two people with two
people wait he comes really close ah now
they're in there okay
beatboxing
w got to guess that these are the only
people
left this is just
difficult he didn't hear it okay
yeah okay okay but I don't get a Reload
wow
rude
y good we're through that level
Hallelujah how
about we make some D come
here
hi help
me I am
stressed
um to Maat guys and they don't see me
over that
okay hi here I am here I am once again
I'll turn you into
pieces not
myself oh my
God they have longer range I think with
the machete too so you got to be careful
you know you got to be
[Music]
careful momy I'm
wait
[Music]
helicopter feel like I'm going to [\h__\h]
up any any second now any second
now be slow here
mhm get to the chopper no don't make me
fly another Chopper spontaneously out of
nowhere you know I'm going to mess up no
don't put me in a situation like that
uh hi you don't see me huh oh God I'm
too
nervous I'm too nervous uh what are my
options here I could go into that room
but it has a window
right I got to do as much as possible uh
Mele I think because I wait never mind I
do have okay I understand
finally I think I understand it will
reload on its own
either 10 times or I have 10 more shots
something like
[Music]
that come here come here come
here
okay uh now there's free people down
here and I would be good to shoot
[Music]
them no
switched weapon I guess
before
uh before I I
yeah went in
what how did they see
me oh you suckers going to go first now
ah I'm still confusing
things okay come here
sorry I'm so okay I'll get my [\h__\h]
together
now
hi
okay
okay wonderful
Yahoo oh gamean excuse me I I am first
and foremost I am the myth speaker of
Ian okay don't put so much pressure on
me giving me too many
titles and when I say when I say game or
ofen what I really mean is not that I'm
good at games it's just that I
play many games and maybe the mostest
variety and and the longest lengths and
and uh finish the most games you know so
no the it's like a suier I'm a suier of
games oh he didn't hear it
interesting okay oh we cleared that area
out pretty much then now now what's best
to do maybe me trying
to focus on
them
okay oh [\h__\h] ah ah okay
oh that was
some very very lucky of me because I
totally [\h__\h] up cuz I got confused
with the controls
again
no a let's go
let's go a let's finally go helicopter
controls no don't mess us
up oh we're not taking the helicopter oh
no oh
[Music]
no go go go oh hey
wow wow w
wow so many people with with
guns okay I'll I'll
[Music]
shoot I want to try getting like shotgun
goes through everybody right they were
standing kind of in the line but oh my
God there's so many
sorry I need a moment
uh a what a
what lucky lucky lucky as
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay
oh by the way chuny wony is like you
know that was that was only really for
like a few hours like in the evening
where she was feeling bad she's
completely back to normal now that's
happy happy news but I had this crazy
dream
okay this crazy
that fre me out or it freaked me out
because this was this was one part of my
dream but I was I was riding a bus in at
the very front I was at the very front
of the bus and I was riding it with my
cats I was
like I I had them in cat carriers and I
was bringing them to some place
yeah um maybe I was moving I don't know
I think I was moving no and uh
problemo is wait let's get this one
first suddenly one guy with a gun walked
in he came with a gun to a fist or Knife
Fight Man okay okay not cool not the
coolest
thing that's okay is this part of the
dream I I would hope so
I don't know what I'm
doing they hide in the woods
man it's confusing
me yeah just just just bring them all
out here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
that's the easy way I think at least for
now hi
[Music]
yeah so then I noticed that in the bus
there were some more people that I knew
so uh this was a really long bus ride
but I for just for a little bit I
basically I left my cat carriers on like
a like a
luggage put your luggage here kind of
thing that is like very up high uh at
the top of the the ceiling yeah on the
ceiling kind of so I put them there yeah
and then
hi oh
uh and then I went back and I in the bus
and I talked a little bit to these
people that I knew I was like hi what's
up what's up and you know was happy I
was talking with them and
then
cool compartment yeah and
[Music]
then oh I want to switch no let
Meo so confused
[Music]
Then I then I was like going to come
back and I noticed that like police or
something or like not police but like
somebody some someone who thinks they
have the authority they took my cat
carriers and I'm like what the [\h__\h] are
you doing and they're like we're
confiscating it because you left it
alone not not you but like you know
nobody was there so we're taking it now
in our possession and I'm like no these
are mine give it give them to me like I
was just I'm I'm still in the bus I'm
here I'm close by why are you taking
them away from
me yeah and I was like getting like
panicked and and don't sh out what I do
because I can't lose my C what the [\h__\h]
I need them like what this is so shitty
like what what kind of policy is this
and this it's not like I left the
bus oh when you think you have a
different weapon wow
uh and it was a Friday this is
important
because because when they when they take
when they confiscate something in the
bus um they
will please tell me no one's there thank
you they will like keep it in their
office
and you have to get it you have to go
there to get it back but apparently
office hours up from Monday to Friday
and when this happened it was like in
the afternoon of Friday so their office
hours were already like closing so I was
driving after them when they were
confiscating my cats I was driving after
them bringing it to the
office panicking and begging them to
just give them back to me and they just
wouldn't and then I was at the office
they bring it there then they say sorry
office hour is closed now and I'm like
what the [\h__\h] I'm literally right here
I'm begging you and I was crying and
crying and they just wouldn't give it to
me and the problem was that this is like
not not specifically for pet uh the
confiscation
no oh
no okay oh my God where why is he going
why is he going a different
way where is he he's like running all
around I don't know where he's looking
for
me where is
he he just R off he di is this a buck is
this going to be a
problem guess we'll we'll find out later
um so they were going to keep them from
Friday afternoon until like Monday
morning or so when I could keep pick
them up again I'm like no this can't
work because you're not going to feed
them right and they're they'll be stuck
in one tiny cat carrier two cats and
they're not like where what if they want
to use a toilet or you know this was
like really really terrible conditions
for them so I was totally freaking out I
was like panicking this is a Dream by
the way just so you
know multitasking I need to tell you in
this dream though cuz it freaked me out
yeah and I was just like begging and
crying and and trying to argument with
them argue with them and yeah lots of
bad cat dreams yeah for
real and yeah it was terrible
Hi and then I wake up and I'm like
crying a little bit and I'm trying to um
get no trying to get a hold of myself
cuz I I know that my mom was like
sleeping in the other room and I'm like
oh I don't want to make her worry this
is this was just a dream calm down kiaha
calm down there's no good ending to this
anyway let me do a again okay we'll
focus now we'll focus
now I think the reason I dreamt this is
because of a a cop uh body cam footage
video analyzation video that I saw the
other day on
YouTube where there was like this girl
um in America standing like she was in
in her house and some cop would like
found some cars standing on the road
next to the house kind of not parked
properly and some things were wrong so
uh he was going to like find the owner
but she didn't come out right away and
then he was going to go and take the
cars away and um she the the girl who's
just the girlfriend of the owner of the
car was the only one there she finally
came out and she was trying to fix the
situation yeah but blah blah blah blah
blah so they were taking the cars away
eventually the boyfriend showed up uh
and they the boyfriend the boyfriend and
his friend they showed up and they were
like why what we're literally right here
you're taking the cars right now you
couldn't wait for like 5 more minutes to
just leave the cars here like we right
here so this is very similar I
think that's probably why I dreamt it
um
no okay now I'm going to focus I
swear okay
okay I'm going to blast every fucker's
ass out of here
ohy it's hard to see sometimes when
they're like everywhere like little
cockroaches
man oh I want to do this with
knife it's
great sometimes the door is helpful
sometimes it's not helpful
impounded cars can be so expensive yeah
I mean I understand the cops got to do
what they got to do but if the person is
like right there just just leave it like
what the [\h__\h] I don't get that
part I I I don't get
it like those people's attitudes were
not good either but they're not very
Cooperative if if the owners already
there it took them just like 5 minutes
to get there and they're like m- we're
already 10 taking it see it's already
loaded up so now we're taking it you'll
have to get it back for this amount of
money
bye-bye yeah a power trips so come
on oh [\h__\h] wrong weapon ah it's so
confusing I just want to have one weapon
[Music]
please is everyone dead okay I think
so come on please come on come on
hello
no oh baby you triple once it's on a tow
truck you can't legally remove it that's
so
stupid stupid
legalities okay okay I got him I got him
guys I got this under control I got this
she got this i got this
Beard's missions are the hardest in the
game oh am I am I this person right now
it it does feel really hard like first
you're getting used to new mechanic
still and then this this is quite a base
but okay you know what what if we try
going to the right room before we go
into the middle or so why does the why
does the screen tilt like that it
bothers
me okay okay fine fine
fine don't like the screen tilt you
right it's kind of
weird
[Music]
hello what who could I who could I call
over are you guys excited for myth
anniversary it's so crazy three years oh
my God like the past few days I keep on
like thinking about how it's crazy that
you know been doing this for 3 years now
so so real cuz I think when I when I
started of course I didn't think I would
do it that
long um cuz I think like I thought that
I don't know I just I just
[Music]
couldn't something would happen for
sure and surely I wouldn't be so
successful either so what's the meaning
in in going on and on and on and
on but
No 3 years it just went by so fast like
suddenly suddenly the third year is over
I wasn't really really aware of
it but now it's becoming like kind of
the longest job I've ever
had it's crazy crazy crazy it's such an
intense job too like
every every day is so intense every day
like other jobs you go maybe like not
every jobs every job but some jobs other
jobs you go in and you know you kind of
like maybe with a head empty kind of
state of mind you just do what what you
always
do and and you're not really like there
I'm sure some people can relate right
cuz with my normal job back in the day I
had these times where I was not really
there I was just doing the usual tasks
like like you know like a robot oh God
I just want you with my job that seems
like you're also you're also doing it
with head
empty yeah yeah you can't do this on
autopilot autopilot is a good word to
describe that yeah like other jobs just
because it gets boring the same [\h__\h]
every day for many jobs right just get
so so uh
repetitive H but for this it doesn't
have to be
repetitive especially cuz like the game
the games alone offer so much
variety every
day and and because it's not so
autopilot I think that helps with being
able to get through a long amount of
time
so so like naturally and fast
I'm so on
[Music]
edge yeah yeah deep talk deep talk okay
how do we get this guy over
hi Notice Me Senai
[Music]
please I don't want to shoot okay I just
want to stay mey now cuz I feel like I
have more control over what I'm doing
then
oh yes okay that was not the one I want
wanted to get but it works oh yes
finally clearing out this area okay now
I know there's a window I know there's a
window we can use it to our advantage I
wonder from which which side they would
come hopefully not both just one side
would be appreciated or I just do it
from the
door but there's not much space to Camp
here ironically it's a camp and there's
no
space basically Tony mode
exactly slit everyone throats let's
[Music]
go oh I'm too scared to take
action oh no I'm too scared I don't want
to [\h__\h]
[Music]
up
okay it was angry for a moment maybe
maybe
[Music]
maybe it's time
to spread some ammo
around
no okay okay okay okay this is not the
outcome I was you know planning on but
uh it's it's it's it works is that the
the last one
[Music]
left how do we do how do we do
do
hi come
here ah now you go there
m okay okay okay yeah yeah yeah yeah you
know you say just shoot but you know
it's not always you
know just James here I'm I'm done
weeding out the
garden how's it going with the
yard hanky Hank here ran out of fuel for
the lawnmowers we're at the gas station
on 24th and 7th uh heading over and
we'll share the r
back that seems like end of a end of an
era yeah end of a
chapter
almost you have to than yeah especially
if there's only one enemy left I can't
just no I have to make sure that I don't
have to redo everything all over again
hey look at that
[Music]
se oh oh we got a new weapon big and
heavy just looks like another rifle man
hi what's up what's oh you're punching
that big guy does that make you feel
bigger too I look at this chubby asso is
it just me or does he look a bit like
Daniels well maybe not so much now I
just couldn't tell help myself one day
I'll show that fat pig who the real boss
is you're totally showing him now oh you
you mean want you want to show someone
else directly what's going on here oh
that's what they meant with execution oh
there's also an execution
here it already happening it's
happened looks like we got our hands on
some good Intel here we should get this
back to the colel as soon as possible
and then have some KFC right after not
sure what to do with the captives though
maybe we should just let Barnes have his
way with them would make the job back to
Camp a hell lot
easier oh waa haven't seen a blue screen
like that for a long
time that's so
nostalgic you GM is wrong are you
sure yeah kfb is so much
better yes hello duck duck du duck I
want to run run around and say d d d go
M
hello are we having a
meeting mask did you guys catch the news
on Channel and last tonight last night
Channel what looks like we're famous
now yeah looks like we got our 5 minutes
of
fame I'd say it was more like
two damn I didn't catch it qu what did
they say he do you think you can call
the news station and ask for a copy I
mean I'd pay big bucks to see it why
does your voice sound completely
different like last time when I talked
to you what the [\h__\h] anyway why don't
you call the police and turn yourself in
while you're at
it that probably would be a good idea
I'm sure they'll run another story on us
sooner or later
anyway I'm not so sure about that we'd
have to to we'd have to off more people
first you know he's right not sure what
to do about that we can't just go out
and kill random people now can we I
might have an idea I bought
[Music]
some sorry this is really
distracting I want some weed from a
couple of creeps on Northwest 168 a few
days ago it looked like they had their
stash in the storage shed close
[Music]
by you want to to go treasure hunting
for more drugs huh well there might be
more [\h__\h] there I don't know you got
anything better to
do I wouldn't mind going for a ride
let's check it out guys we can always
grab some pizza if we don't find
anything you like my voice acting I'm
happy thank you I always forget the I I
I really like respect Dom tendo for that
like he he he always seems to remember
what voices he did for which character
even if it's like days
ago or maybe he just has a a smaller
repertoire of voices to choose from in
the first place but I don't
know okay what's this one two machine oh
not one but two machine guns oh he's a
genius and
doio is I wonder if this map is suitable
for Tony if yes I want to do
Tony
um what do you think
guys with Mark you can hold right click
to aim sideways that's an again
[Music]
confusing uh guns are good here try new
mask two machine guns
leave or or
die I choose
[Music]
to
make you die uh what was
that is that a door why why no shooting
okay there we go oh yeah yeah okay okay
is he shooting with both at once no is
it right click for the other one
oh okay at least he can't seem to run
anymore after I shoot shoot him
[Music]
once easy what the [\h__\h] that was what
what was this level what was this level
oh
hello right click to spread Direct
what that sounds
unnecessary that's all there was to it
huh did you hear that he
what sounds like someone in that room
over
there I already checked there's no one
in there are you sure sounds like I need
to
investigate let me in let me
[Music]
in what the hell
what this looks like some kind of
Pokemon [\h__\h]
dog looks like some kind of Pokemon
level don't you
think you know what I
mean
like
yeah it's the area from the first game
it I don't remember that ew it looks
poisonous kind of hard to see where's
the do
at least seems like everybody just has
Mele so far at
least oh oh he doesn't thankfully he
didn't see me from
afar eerie
music again same
guy you know what I'll take this one
down first just for safety I
think double kill but not the way you
want
it freaking sewer levels am I right hate
them looks like there's a snake going
through this
[Music]
tunnel oh that's
confusing that's confusing I'm just
going to shoot straight okay
is he dead
yeah giant rats the dogs are the giant
rats I saw a crazy poodle today I went
out to do some errands to buy um
something for tomorrow for another
challenge what two challenges are videos
and one challenge is live on
stream but yeah I went out to um buy the
thing for it
it and
um uh yeah I saw like one of those like
now I'm
not this time I'm getting you first you
bastard wait a
second unbel you're
unbelievable he he reloaded come
on what's I saying yeah yeah one of
those poodles that's like really fluffy
only in really certain parts and like
round fluffiness you know like some it
looked like a poodle also like a tall it
was a tall poodle not the small ones
like a full size huge ass poodle like
human size poodle where is this
guy I know he's coming
now yeah
okay yeah yeah yeah then he had I I
would I guess something like a classic
poodle cut like what what a poodle is
often depicted as in like movies and so
on
[Music]
W okay uh who's
left I don't see
anyone a
hello is that
a okay there we go floor cleared let's
go where am I oh
there yeah that kind
of that that that like all the eyes are
on you if you have a dog like that damn
sorry I can't I can't help but look it's
just
fascinating okay we'll we'll run
backwards when that guy comes for
us
oh
bastard is he coming no not yet
what
happened what happens did he throw away
his what you mean I run out what do I do
when I run out of
ammo can I pick up new
one
[Music]
uhoh okay
oh the fat guy came
early oh are we done are we
done okay okay I get new stuff no
[\h__\h]
dog oh they all hear me they all hear
me I even got something left now but I
don't think I killed the the fat guy
I was wonder if you plan on having one
of the whole s and whole talk sometime
at the moment I still have my hands full
uh I talked about this many times before
about my priorities for H
talk
um yeah so
not at the
moment to be perfectly honest with
you [\h__\h]
DG yeah they're just now they de they
debuted some new ones I'm just going to
say I'm not going to do the same thing I
did with Advent because I feel like with
Advent it was possible because they
speak English I don't have to translate
you know so these kind of like big
starting group interviews I think I
would only do that with Ian or ID Jens
in the
future
uh cuz like with with Japanese gens it's
not just like asking questions it's also
uh um interviewing so yeah that's an
exclusive
thing yeah 10 10 whole life movies in a
span of less than two months yeah I
mean uh myth and fif J gen fifth right
sometimes I'm not sure about the numbers
Fifth Fifth yeah fifth also was like 1
month apart pretty
much um but yeah I don't know how that
felt to the fandom if it felt the same
way as now for me personally I'm a
little bit overwhelmed like I'm still
like my head is still like like you know
with Advent right
now uh I can't I I watched Snippets of
the new members
debuts but like I I don't have the head
space right now to be very honest with
you to really like get into it but it's
okay because there's a collab band
anyway I have time I have time but for
me like ad is still so fresh you
know they still seem like the babies to
me okay I switch up and St okay can I
take a second one cuz now he's only
carrying one what about the dual
wielding
oh no no [\h__\h] die I can't get out of
here I'm sure admin probably has similar
feelings like they still feel like oh my
God wait wait wait we just joined like
who I can't keep
up any plans for oneon-one collabs ah
with other Adent girls
sure sure hell yeah I just don't know
what um I have some ideas though for
like uh like bigger collabs with
them I'm bringing back some previous
stream ideas so stay tuned but for one
one I can't really think of anything at
the
moment okay you're not going to get me
this time
bastard should we go in
there no
a it's going to take a while to get out
of here Clubhouse game is ah you know
what you know I I honestly like I have
no problem with bringing out the
Clubhouse games every once in a
while
wow
wow sheesh
okay now we're getting serious here oh
oh he switched okay oh
oh yeah
oh this level is
rough chess no no not chess ah chest
anything but chest yes
ooh
uh this is like crazy you got to stay in
the same spot most of the
time one shot
left uh new
[Music]
weapon
okay okay
okay
uh what an anxiety inducing
level yeah good to handle in safe area
yes I agree for this
one why do they say reg glose he's a new
branch and another a new CH it is a new
re re de deis is the new Branch R gloss
is the first unit within that Branch see
I perfect perfectly understand
it yes um those
you
yikes
yikes what's on that side nothing okay
um okay in
here okay is that fresh five shouldn't
it be six oh well that's enough
y de ah no no no oh yeah I said deice
but apparently it's device I was like
what no
way it's
device whole life
device so what are you
saying I don't know that's that's weird
to me
but Dam it
hey yeah some some somebody told me
somebody in whole life told me that it
is
device appar
[Music]
apparently mhm nice double kill
mhm
die okay good ooh there's an SMG there m
oy
oy barely can see bodies anymore in this
area I can't use it yet
[Music]
uh no no no please no please
no I have no weapon right
now finish a dogit why that mean if they
not in the
area no
dogs goam it beginning is ra ra ra ra ra
R
rough
no won't let you ah
B I was scratching my
eye always wait for the last dog man
always wait anticipate
it
I mhm any anything else I know you want
to get some tritos don't you oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] n you can't you can't fist fight
the dog I got to I got to I got to I got
to keep some ammo for that [\h__\h] and
waste it wasted do me do me a favor and
kill me thank you that's cuz the dogs
are so
[Music]
fast keep them coming and they don't
stop coming and they don't stop coming
and they don't stop coming okay o I'm
out of ammo there we go oh he took a
knife ah no I was ready but like not
really oh let the dogs out
oh
uhoh
hey
he oh you know speaking of dogs my mom
uh made me watch this movie with her was
like let's watch a movie and the movie
was I of dogs by that an Anderson guy or
so
you know that
movie it's like playing in Japan it's
like a stop motion Movie kind of that
plays in
Japan um but like it's it seems to be
like a Hollywood movie but the the
location is in Japan there's Japanese
characters that I this is cool cuz I
barely uh witnessed this in
other
um movies they don't really do this like
they don't translate to Japanese there's
english- speaking characters and then
the dogs speak English ah
where did he come from but yeah the
Japanese characters they they they talk
in Japanese like sometimes there will be
like inter interpreters that are just
like characters uh in the story because
there's it's like on TV for example
somebody's Japanese person is giving an
interview and then you will get like the
translation kind of on the side as an
extra nice shot nice okay wait where's
this what
dog there
hey leave me
alone yeah so that's really cool cuz
like it gives you some immersion um I
thought the visuals were kind of creepy
uh at first but you get used to
it yeah it was a was a all right
movie m
I felt like um especially maybe it was
more noticeable for me cuz I can speak
Japanese some of the Japanese
no some of the Japanese voice acting was
like really stiff and no
emotion like kind of
weird yeah ooh that was nice that was
clean yeah
but okay you would think that's the dog
but apparently there's another one that
wants to [\h__\h] me up
man I'm so ready I'm so ready okay I'm
like ready for anything right now come
at me come at me
bro I dodged the shotgun we could have
both died in that moment I dodged
it did you
know yes than thanks to Mar antonet
that's the
one yeah that's the one the
sucker no treeo for you and no walkies
for you it's your fault you're a bad dog
bad bad
dog you Tobe shitty dog get out of
here don't hurt
human no no no bad B B
okay what did you see that did you
see
she okay we're finally making making
progress
again maybe I should you know try try
some things here get the ones that are
circling
mhm as long as nothing surprises me
anymore
yeah
okay also you know I watched that movie
and then my mom mentioned that she
didn't watch it yet but she's like it
seems like she's considering because of
what I said about one piece uh the
Netflix adaption she's interested I was
so surprised because like anime is not
her thing I'm telling you that she will
appreciate a a jubly
movie yeah um but she she heard my
opinions and then she read about uh
other people's uh critiques that are not
existing because it's [\h__\h] good uh of
one piece and she's like okay wow yeah I
believe you I believe you that's really
good I'm like oh I was wondering if I
should recommend it to you I was like
kind of iffy about it I thought that you
you could like it but you just need to
have an open mind for it because it's
anime more or less like it's orig it
originates from it and it's it still has
that kind of
spirit oh
yeah I didn't even know it ends there
holy [\h__\h] H my arm hurts for some reason
in a r spot in a weird weird spot wow
wow okay ah [\h__\h] that's weird why does
it hurt there
ah in my elbow I have some weird pain in
my
elbow let's go next level is harder oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] go to car okay okay he wait
level over nice
yeah she's I don't know if she's gonna
really watch it but if we all tell her
to do so I'm sure she
will Mommy watch One Piece I I there's
still you know a lot of dork in there
but I
mean it's not a guaranteed no no for her
I think uh cuz she's watched some dorky
stuff out there I think I think she
could enjoy it just need an open mind
for it
but I think right now she's not even
listening I'm not sure cuz she might
still be on her way home cuz after the
Wilderness she followed me into the non
Wilderness and slept over last night at
my place yeah yeah yeah so she was
here
M tell her to watch it for Sanji I don't
know I wonder who she'd like I think she
actually would like
uh um uh Luffy
I think she might like him a little bit
uh and maybe I don't
know I think like uh Luffy would be like
a oh
hello would be
like like like maybe give her like sun
Vibes this is my
son who is that it's the police open the
door just a second I got to put on some
clothes okay
uh where are my clubs I here all
right am I wearing
it what yeah that sounded he's gone ah
he's in here um
guy how did you get in here the door
wasn't locked I let myself in I hope you
don't mind um dude that's like of course
I mind like I told you to [\h__\h] wait
and you just sneak in it's not even like
you have a warrant do you
what the [\h__\h] well what do you want I'm
looking for an ash Davis this is listed
as his last known
address well as you can see he's not
here I don't know where he is he doesn't
live here anymore like what gives you
the right anyway in the first place was
there anything else or get out if not uh
will you tell me him to contact Miami PD
next time you see him you're his sister
aren't you I can see you got the good
jeans you're very
[Music]
pretty if there was nothing else I would
like for you you to [\h__\h] get out
now and now I'm
him I think I'm having a an episode too
many people at once I can shape ship no
like not not shape shifting can you
imagine oh my God like jumping from body
to body
how interesting would that
be where are we on a bridge or what what
is
this who
[Music]
go no he takes so long
wait can I take one of their
weapon
okay okay okay now we're good give me
this one
okay
[Music]
hello pigeons
BBS City rats flying
rats somebody has a
gun
die wow wow
what where's the gun go I don't see any
gny woohoo
where is
he how am I supposed to deal with
that there should be a weapon in restart
Mission there should be a weapon what
it's okay I don't need one I don't
need let's bait
him yeah
[Music]
e
hello I just see a gun on the ground I
don't can hide behind okay I guess we
got to get in all right all right but we
can bait this
one now I got to get
in oh
oh gun
guy no gun guy now
h Huh what's is it like an automatic
kind of
thing sorry I was reading the chat but
yeah I saw I saw
um hello
hello I saw guns on the right side we're
getting closer to
them gun is really far need cover and
Ste move okay okay okay okay cool cool
cool
cool let's oh bait
him come here guys don't you want to
talk with me let's have a
[Music]
talk meet and greet with the
Wawa yo so did you guys see on Twitter I
posted about this camera that I bought
the insta 360 Go free # not
sponsored it's like a GoPro but I
thought you know somebody recommended it
to me so I thought you know what I'm
this actually looks like pretty good
like it it can
do pretty much everything a GoPro can do
price range is like the same but it's
it's you know it has some features that
make it really easy to
use could totally also go with a GoPro
and work just as well but yeah it's kind
of nifty
Nifty and it's really small yeah it
looks it looks kind of cute
yeah whoa It's
silenced but they're hiding there can I
shoot over
it I don't know
oh yes I
can
ah did she Dodge
it
oo I'm coming for you did it work well
enough yeah like it was really weird to
get used to like the range that it
captures cuz it's like really wide angle
and basically there's like so many
mounting options you can put it on a hat
you can put it on your chest because
there's like a a necklace a magnetic
necklace neace that you put under your
shirt and then the camera on top of the
shirt so it has like the shirt in
between and that works really well too
um really cool angles but uh yeah um
like there's a you can take that little
camera out of the case you can even film
it while it's in the case or you take it
out and then you can still monitor
through the case uh you can monitor what
what you're like doing uh you can see it
but like most of the time I wanted my
hands empty for what I was filming so I
wasn't looking at the feed so I was
often not really aware of the the range
that I was
capturing
but it was it's really good really good
stuff and it makes me want to film more
Vlogs oh
nice I'm motivated to film more Vlog
style things what what the
[\h__\h] okay what kind of start is this
what kind of start is this
cover don't
go I'm really hectic uh starting what
the [\h__\h] how did he die I didn't do that
did
I ah I'm mored all over them I'm sure
there's still somebody there right
yeah okay no problem no
problem I wish I could see oh
[\h__\h] a
[\h__\h]
no my my my my my focus was like uh yeah
messing things
up oh thank God thank God it didn't ruin
my run yay hey didn't you guys say this
level is more difficult I'm I'm
chilling I'm first trying
baby would you guys like to see maybe I
should ask this afterwards though
because I think the the Vlogs Vlog kind
of things that I filmed are really
convincing um but yeah I was going to
ask if you want to see more of like
vloggy things cuz every time I go on
trips I always like tell you about it
afterwards anyway oh but maybe you want
to see in the videos
I'm just like kind of awkward when it
comes to
talking outside to
myself on the
camera like I don't know how vloggers
that you know YouTube bloggers do it I I
I just feel so awkward about you know
what people would be
thinking oh nice okay
what people think of me when I'm talking
to myself on the camera cuz I don't know
it's it's it's strange it's you
know I also don't want to like bother
people who are just you know H enjoying
their vacation or
whatever you can do voice over and post
I I did that partially yeah for some of
my footage where I felt too embarrassed
to talk when I'm when I when I have
somebody walking with me like a friend
then I don't mind
then I feel way less awkward but if I'm
all alone oh you saw
me yeah then I'd like to avoid
talking to the camera I just feel like a
one of those annoying
YouTubers I can't believe I I was able
to survive
that h
good luck with the GL glass
what smash that like button maybe I
should start saying these things maybe
maybe maybe if these pass three years I
would have if I would have said don't
forget to subscribe smash that like
button do this and that maybe by now I
would be at 2 million subscribers who
knows maybe that's what I was really
missing all this time
no you guys better come
here out of ammo I was out of ammo I was
out of
[Music]
ammo how close are you oh I the other
day I was like checking because I just
remembered wait wasn't I going to do
like a marathon or something when I get
to 1.5 um and I was like I was in bed
though and on my phone I somehow I can't
access like the all the details like
YouTube
studio so I just Googled takala live
subscribe account and it was like
already so close to 1.5 that uh Marathon
wouldn't make sense anymore I was like
oh [\h__\h] I guess I I suddenly passed it
um but that was really inaccurate
apparently cuz when I checked a day or
two later on my desktop YouTube Studio
that it was like further behind
again yeah it's weird I'm I'm trying to
keep an eye on
it I want to do
a I want to do
uh okay I want to do a a maraphone
stream cuz I haven't done one in a long
time and you know it it does it it does
give you know a little push too usually
in in growth for that little bit that's
left so I you know kind to thing smart
this is my job after all you watch it
hit on your anniversary I don't think so
but that's okay like you know that's not
what you know what I want the
anniversary to focus on
anyway let's get this although there's
Windows there
huh oh
ah this one's difficult
maybe
oh
yeah yeah exactly the outcome I was
hoping
for yeah nice
shoty let's get this one
too ah I miss still got enough
shots uh-oh oh
uh awkward stupid
door okay and who's left who's left I
feel like I'm
done this
one okay what are you waiting for in the
toilet
H you don't seem to be doing anything in
there are you protecting the toilet seat
yay toilet seat is independent it
doesn't need your protection okay that's
what it was saying so I saved the toilet
seat from
you where am I oh here I have no weapon
excuse
me I have no weapon and what are these
like tables or shelves can they see me
when I step forward hello no okay aha
ah those wind those rooms will see each
other and pew pew
through uh well oh dog come oh no oh no
okay you know I have no choice against
the dog especially with no weapons yeah
cool what if I hide behind the door dog
go away behind the door I could do
that
quick okay
okay okay okay
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
uhi
quick too late I was so slow with that
oh dog no no no no no no
[Music]
no
okay we'll get
there no not the dog ah
walk in the distance
hi I hear
you yeah uhoh yeah the door was not
protecting me that's my strategy right
now just take his
[Music]
weapon I think this is oh he can see me
can't he oh no okay
and then the problem is
people hear
[Music]
me next time next time he
Loops pick it up you
bastard what the [\h__\h] what the
wouldn't pick it up but okay this
actually is the best outcome because
nobody noticed what is happening between
these two rooms and the dog the dog
couldn't pass through because of the
door is that what's happening oh my God
look at there's so many maybe better
with machine gun then holy [\h__\h] okay oh
my
God no maybe I can get a few of the
silenced one hopefully that will
not make everybody
follow let's try this
one okay oh oh they forgot about
me until
down that's him that's
him oh so I think the silenced one
didn't even work the way I wanted it to
so that's a
disappointment
retreat no not the door oh
okay not him
no anybody but
him cuz he needs some time to
die this level will mind break her oh I
will I will prove you wrong
then wait what the [\h__\h] I just noticed
that weapon over
there wait do down
what did you guys see
that did you guys see that
it's okay I need a gun anyway like look
at all these
[Music]
although
I I have some
ideas but uhoh
no um
but everything has to kind of go well if
I want my ideas to
work yeah Mele for stealth like around
the corner just get them to you know
once again follow me to
death trust me
uhoh
no he was lying in a position where the
other guy would see me
[Music]
uh-oh things have to go very right
in this
level
otherwise now it's going right
okay I'll switch
to
gun I
think if only it wasn't made out
of
actually m
only it wasn't made out of
[Music]
Windows I was going to walk around and
then wait for everybody
there could work could
work don't shoot shot from the room boss
there's too much space from where they
can shoot you
no I'm I'm experimenting
try baiting the silenter guy and meing
him yeah
[Music]
true wait first oh okay I'll do that
after I kill this one first just just
from my own peace of mind
okay uh not like this
sorry two window
boys I wouldn't say it's the toughest
part we'll probably be proven that
everything thing is the toughest
part oh no wake
up you want some you want your gun huh
you want your
gun why did he hesitate to get his gun
why is that such a smart
CPU perfect position okay um
I was hoping to bait him but
I yeah cuz like if I just bait from
inside the room he's just going to shoot
through so I was hoping to be at the
corner and then quickly go away go back
then he has to follow me
M can't I'm so bad at
walking this will
be a long ride guys are you in for it
what do we do
guys okay
okay okay
okay now can have
silencer and I think I cut off that part
for them yeah
[Music]
maybe should I should I try to go for
the big one first and then run away
there's one coming
why did he not
like did he not see it like coming at
all like why did he not
react that was perfect
huh is that
normal
okay got to be SM all right with the use
of the silencing gun I'll try this
again that
works okay wait my chat died Let me
refresh it I see it moving in OBS sniped
oh wait it's it decided to work now that
I was threatening
it w oh she's becoming John
Wick oh
yeah he has a silencer too doesn't he
but we got to get rid of this circle of
people one by one okay okay okay okay
okay
okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay four shots
left let's make him
count oh oh o wait scary scary scary
sometimes they walk around the corner
when you least expect it cuz they just
changed their rout suddenly I don't know
what what makes them think that now is
the
time hello
okay and okay I want to get this one
too middle one
for a potential new silencer
gun
oh oh no oh Oh Me
Oh okay ah okay I'm out of
silencer uh the silencer got where did
he go did he where did he drop his
weapon somewhere in the middle I can't
really tell it AP
part oh yeah it's this thing this one I
want it I want it
please if I time it right I should be
able to get it but there's also lots of
window rooms there so maybe it's time to
go
loud for once and see what
happens oh nothing happened now nobody
hurt it let's go and this should be
covered too just going for the middle
will be a little bit scary
oh hey this this rifle is really quiet
too though spray and pray spray and
pray say m again I dare you why why why
why did I do I say
wrong me
Mee guy on the right I don't see anybody
on the right that's me the guy on the
right is me
melee no what that makes no sense that's
like mayday mayday you don't Rite it
like that no it should be me what that
makes no sense you're destroying my
world view right
now should we try to get these who are
all all like
stuck
here that could end me
potentially maybe with a shotgun would
be better they only have one
one with a rifle hey there's so many
they're like ew ew so
many it scares
me I tried so hard and come so far
but in the end it doesn't even matter I
can't redo no I can I can redo this is a
game about
redoing I can
redo Hotline
Miami again and
again [\h__\h] I'm so bad at walking for do
Swing Swing Swing Swing Swing my how did
I kill this guy again I
don't how I did it oh I I lured him in
right
yeah okay hi welcome ah no that would
have been so good if only it wasn't for
that guy
Worst
Gamer what Worst Gamer in whole life
okay you are getting a timeout sir you
little [\h__\h] you think you're something
better yeah time out for you this game
is difficult you try it ah how about you
try
it it was going pretty well well you
know it can't go well
forever oh yeah I I remember now what I
did differently I bait
him and then killed with
meele
me you know at my mom's place she was
like one of the first things she did
like really proudly show off
um her new Minecraft world to me she was
like oh my God you have to look you have
to look
I found this like amazing seed yeah it
spawned me here like there like Sakura
jungle Mesa all
bordering uh you know at each other and
she was like showing me I built this
house and this and this and this that
this is my my Trader
Hall oh
[Laughter]
no yeah like she has phases
sometimes she gets really
really
into
Minecraft for like a period of
time oh
well making it easy for me thank you
going silencer I don't know if I had
that last time
but why does that
work oh okay why does it work
that didn't work [\h__\h] I lost a shot that
was important that was an important
shot why are you looking at
me I'm wasting all my shots
no I wased
again I can't help but waste them no
a okay oh my God it's so difficult you
can barely hear the BM really I mean
it's a little bit quiet now you
maybe
H
H it's so difficult oh my God
[Music]
my brain is fading away that's what's
happening what
[Music]
readyy oh
no this is a must go step
the good thing is also that he keeps
that door open so that stops the flow
from there kind of and the view they
can't see me then it's pretty
good okay let's do this again come
on
no my aim do go sometimes I lose like
the my my mouse like it's I don't know
where the [\h__\h] it
is uh-oh oh oh oh oh oh I made it did he
bring two did he bring two
silencers hi chunky
wony how can you have two silencers
that's actually amazing those are two
silences
right lucky
drop it wasn't D wielding them
[Music]
though that was Dangerously close oh and
he saw
[Music]
me no I'll never get the dual silencer
back again [\h__\h] the dup
glitch
what maybe she probably wants Kibbles
they might be out
Kibbles double silencer damn he he must
be a
genius what what what
a you can't hear her but she's meowing
really
cutely I thought it was
over
okay why is she meowing like that so
cutely she wants some Kibbles I bought
something new for them I I went out to
buy
no no to buy cbles because I have to buy
them in the in a proper Pet Shop um I
don't give them Supermarket
Kibbles I found some some rubber mat
that you can spread like some licky
snack over
[Music]
I think he dropped two again this is the
run and then yeah it's not just a like a
like a flat rubber mat it has like some
yeah some like higher little thingies
bumps and stuff so apparently it's going
to it's supposed to like make them um
take some time with consuming the food
and and I don't know have fun with it I
guess so I'm going to try it oh no oh no
no no
oh I hate this level oh my God I don't
think I ever finish this
level I don't think I ever
will it's not even like I can choose a
different mask or anything like this is
this is what we're dealing
with keeping them bus at not yeah like
at the shop I found one like um wet food
that said
had uh appetite control on it and it
said uh 90% of
customers uh confirmed that this works
for them and I'm like and I asked the
the shopkeeper like is it the
tenant tenant store clerk yeah if that's
like how how does that do it
how how does that work does it work like
what's inside that makes it work [\h__\h]
and she was like I actually don't know
not sure if it really
Works a [\h__\h] did it work
no um but then yeah we're having a
discussion like why do you need it I'm
like uh cuz my cat one of my cats like
she's just like even even if she already
had food she will annoy me for the
night it's why did I do it so well
before I can't figure out the the right
angle I want the lucky drop anyway
try not to get too close with time
no yeah and then they recommended me the
the mat although I don't
think I don't think that will really
help with my problem but sure I'll I'll
try it just for entertainment for the
kitty Cato
sake all
right let's yeah let's take a step
back oh this might be a good position
this should work right yeah this is I
stay here this is a perfect
position they don't even even when
somebody's right next to him when his
partner's getting
shot they don't realize it what the [\h__\h]
how
stupid is this
AI yeah this is how you do it yeah I was
getting way to close each
time free more free
more Bak
brain mm must have been the wind must
have been the wind
yeah o
dog dog could have [\h__\h] me up
a okay I'm out of shots uh let's relax
for a moment well any the silencer is
here all the others are
normal how many are here oh not so
many there's barely anyone there I could
try to
oh wait there's one here where did I
throw that over oh yeah
okay do I want to do this quietly
or I'm so
scared should I try to bait
him n he could be he could
want yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so must
sign oh oh oh ah
ah
free free mafiosos with with knce
okay none of them wants to check what's
behind the door okay let's let's be very
aware of
our
position what do I see that's stole the
silencer from before right oh no it's a
new silencer yeah yeah yeah yeah I don't
really NE silencer here do
I I'm so scared I don't want I don't
want tip this door
over
[\h__\h] ah I'm such a chicken wait I don't
want to I don't want to mess it up I
don't want I can't do this again I don't
want to mess it
up should I blast them with a silencer
or with a machine gun I think now
everybody's quite distant
so let me maybe even take this one first
nobody would see me right this is okay
this is okay what the
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
okay we're good I might should I try
melee I might
Mee okay I want
I'm so
sorry I'm so
sorry I'm going to write a formal letter
to apologize for my
actions
hello
hello door glitching okay
okay it's okay it's okay it's okay I I I
I I I I'm fine like this part I got it
down now okay I have the I have the
right position and
everything meow meow
meow okay here number
one
sh number
two number threee
number
four
five have a stretch is the matter of
execution yeah I I was pretty far it's
it's fine now like I I know I can get
through this level now before there was
some
doubt there's no more doubt
now it's just a matter of patience
basically and making the right decisions
but I already know what the right
decisions are more or less at least
until that
point okay okay and now you
left okay so we still have one ammo in
our silenced one who wants it you
maybe the side nobody could see me
right okay I I'm scared not n shouldn't
be doing this without
okay without a gun and some
ammo no no no no no no no no no no
no okay last time we tried with melee
now we're going to go in guns blazing
that's what they say right
okay you didn't see that that didn't
happen happened it was just a dream it
was just a dream it was just a
dream it's just a dream
guys it didn't happen it didn't happen
okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
you're dreaming but I'm here for you I'm
here for you I will protect
you it will be all okay it'll be fine
you'll be Dieu I'm here for you I know
it must be rough right now when you're
not sure what's real and what's an
illusion but you'll figure it out in
time you get the hang of it I I'll
support
you I'm real for one that's what I can
tell you for
sure that's one thing for certain one
thing you can rely on I'm real you're
real too yeah
yeah you just just make sure to never
leave kfp cuz if you leave kfp you
unreal
yourself you don't want that no no you
don't want
that what does that
me we'll find out
maybe he's on his way
[Music]
okay this a [\h__\h] okay
meow
meow she really wants the
kalles do you guys mind I think she
really wants some Kibbles can I quickly
refresh her kibble
station oh she's already running
away for
[Music]
okay
yay hi I'm
back hi
back here I said it for you you don't
have to say it where's my
mouse I don't see my mouse ah it's cuz
I'm focused on that guy
o oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] okay it kind of made it easier for
me cuz now the door is open and I'm
forced to take action fine fine fine
fine
fine still got to be careful about
having my eyes
everywhere rush them Ki plays this game
very stealthily you must know by know
there's no rushing them
here
okay
okay oh [\h__\h] oo there's not even many
people in the rooms left
either chunky wony what do you want you
not want The
KES I'm so
sorry somebody said this game this room
is going to break me yeah I feel it un
breaking we so survive
that what what why is he
here why is he
here meow meow meow I'm becoming a cat
life is better as a
cat just become Cat
hello give me that I have no patience
left I think she's just dooming right
now she's got the
doomies that is why she's in the hallway
meow meow meowing
okay it's it's it's going to happen this
time okay I can do
it this is the
Run oh those guys in the middle aren't
even giving you trouble anymore exactly
I was really scared of this part I was
like how do you even where do you even
begin what do
you but it's fine I have everything
under control
okay could have even meleed that one huh
and saved the shot but okay
now I love how far they throw it like
like a little you know that game ice
hockey like we're playing ice hockey ooh
they didn't they don't hear that that's
good that feels very reassuring to me
pray and
pray wa there's so many bodies on there
like it's hard to
see that's someone's
there ah
rough
rough let's play for you I wish I I
could let you play for me
oh that's a bad position
yeah so this now should clear the top I
can't without the silencer Oh you mean
like after that whole middle part maybe
I will maybe I
will
okay ah let's do it over and over
again do it and do it do it do it do it
and do it and do it I do it do it and do
it and do it do it do it and do it and
do it I've got a
feeling that this run is going to be the
run that this run is going to be the run
that this is going to be
the this is the
run this is the Run let's pray and
pray we got a party on their bodies and
they're going to pay
[Music]
fry sounds weird don't say that to
her wasn't my wasn't I empty how did I
do that did I learn how to control magic
Magic Bullets through my
hands I'm not complaining
though I think I just really quickly
picked managed to pick up a gun somehow
I didn't even realize it
myself power of panic I thought it was
over it's just oh God okay okay I can do
this I can do this I can do
[Music]
this who wants it who wants it who wants
it you wanted
a we can do it we can do it we can do it
we can do it but I the promise there
left end right
uhh Actually I don't even want the
silencer right now so you know what it's
it's fine it's fine I'm just waiting can
somebody please come closer thank you
thank you please please please please
[Music]
BL I got no
choice no no no no
[Music]
okay everything looks clean
now
okay don't [\h__\h] it up I
will I will lose myself and become a
werewolf if I [\h__\h] it up maybe I go from
the top you know what I go from the top
I could even take with the shotgun
shotgun I say thank you that might help
me why is that one
dead I didn't do
that the door the
[Music]
door no no no
no I I I don't know what
happened I ran for my life I ran for my
life man
ah how scared were you guys cuz I I I I
I I I wouldn't know what to do with
myself
anymore if we're going to take the gun
to the next level what no then then I
think I'll take uh this one 12 is that
that's maximum capacity might
be you little [\h__\h]
ah okay we have to realize what's going
on here first is this a wall it's not a
wall
[Music]
right what the
[\h__\h] uh
what uhoh
oh God thank God I brought the
silencer I was smartest decision of my
[Music]
life of my Hotline Miami life
okay and he got a new one for me ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
I advise you go nuts with a shotgun
shotgun well we can try I don't think
this can be done stealthy everything can
be done stealthy if you
want
okay um I invite everybody for some fun
outside hey hey hey hey hey hey
that was not uh the right thing to do
apparently
no
no be mindful of Windows yeah am I yeah
I'm very much in the sight right now I
was going to say
maybe shoot through Windell again
but you
bastard no
I Wawa is losing it let's go let's
[Music]
go W is going to lose it soon
door is
open dog has entered the chat yeah it's
better it's better with door closed for
now I
think okay now now what now uh I'm going
to try to do something
oh please I wish I wish it was still
like back in the day where when things
were getting difficult I could just give
the controller to my
brother apparently I got someone with
that oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I
want this takes so much out of
me
hello okay he dropped a shotgun
boy okay we want to we want to maybe get
some of those people out of the way
while we're
[Music]
outside
oh okay I take that there a
win for now I'm still going to hope for
the best of my silence gun
uhoh uhoh
no
[Music]
mommy just an insane difficulty spot the
first time you play this game
[Music]
mhm hey that's not nice that's not a
nice way to treat
visitors f
if only my aim was
existent oh I mean that's that's pretty
fast way of dealing with problems I I
give myself a pet on the back for that
one oh
no I'm going to get there guys we got
there before when it seems difficult
oo surprised I can't see
me we're going to get there again
no I believe in you thank you your Strat
is good can pick many off yes yes yeah
I'll I'll
actually do us all a
favor I mean I guess that's uh maybe for
some people they wouldn't agree with
that but I'm going to going to bring out
actually oh there's nothing
here never mind I was going to bring up
my tangent notes on the PC but all my
new notes are on my
phone I watched a new episode of Wheel
of Time though did you guys watch
it I liked it it's getting good it's
riveting no no why
how are we going to have a conversation
H [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
Run Dog okay go back inside yeah go go
back
[Music]
inside I preer Wheel of
Fortune a wheel
[Music]
and you guys wonder why I am a cat
person that's actually
unbelievably
shitty behavor behav
behav my cat wouldn't do this to me
[\h__\h] so bad yeah let me do it
again do it and do it and do it do it do
it and do it and do it and do it do it
and do it and do it oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay boa won't do that to you either
well thankfully because uh he's been
trained by a good mother milia Watson
she could have trained him for different
purposes if she wanted
to yeah okay I got the big guy
[Music]
why are you all on the same spot what
are you doing get back
outside oh
no I killed someone
though why why
not no
[Music]
[Laughter]
aim to
cool but once we can stay it about ooh
[Music]
o survived for a surprising long amount
of time there just
running oh oh no oh no please leave me
alone don't see me don't look at me I'm
shy
[Music]
doesn't
work
okay give me something to talk about
what can we talk about
guys Good's new outfit did you see it
now f finally oh my God finally myth is
complete 2022
outfits now we can all work on the 2023
outfits oh yeah and Dana has a new
hairstyle it's like a super long ass
ponytail also with blue
inside interesting but no I don't I
don't think that was supposed to be any
kind of like reference to
me no
I am so tense right
[Music]
now yeah could that looked really cute I
already saw like the work in progress
ages
ago and she's so cute I love all the
layers that she has in her outfit
she can have like just the blouse or the
cardigan or whatever
cute but she cut her bang so
short
am I love am one though maybe me wait so
we had am as
a space
traveler
uh-oh it's got to run long enough okay
and GAA as a school
girl what did I do yeah I'm I'm like
alternative RPG something like
that uh cie was Callie's the the the
pajamas
or which one was hers like she got hers
the first one wasn't hers the first oh
her sleepware okay what was Ena the
shirt right just the shirt with the
gaming hands and the shortcut those are
so long ago when they revealed them that
it doesn't even feel like the same like
series of outfits to
me okay so we got like two comfy ones
one crazy one AKA am that really stands
out and
uh yeah me also standing out kind
of the [\h__\h] just happened no no
no I am
stupid yeah I think it's good that we
didn't uh you know do a fitting theme
all together because then maybe you
would have had to wait until now for us
all to release it or or we could have I
guess even with the same theme we could
have released it separately whenever
something was ready but yeah you know
well myth myth has done enough like
matching outfits now we're just doing
what we want
individually that's fine
right I think that's fun
too
diversity has myth Oran ever thought
about making a musical I mean you mean
you mean like just like one stream like
a gimmick like
oh oh
no no no no why did I step back I
thought I hate myself this game is
making me hate
myself it's not good for my mental
health I know know what we talking about
just
now happy talk only happy talk
I had a musical if
it's just for like gimmi like akis I did
for example I mean that would be really
cool but like how could we even do it if
we don't even get to use the
studio
right so don't really have the
opportunity to even think about
it I first like want to there's I don't
need to do anything gimmicky yet I just
want to do it normal at first you know I
just want to do normal
things normally I don't need remix just
yet but it would be cool in the future
yeah but like choices Japanese songs you
know we could
do but let me let me try to get the fat
guy with a silencer really quickly
though like would you expect us to do
original songs for that then cuz that's
like
maybe better to get from the
top suck puppet
music yeah I can do suck puppet musical
but again like the
tracks like musical songs have like its
own kind of sound [\h__\h]
hell I'm not going to move on before I
get that guy
a
[\h__\h] narissa oh yeah narissa loves
musicals
oh speaking of Music CL the other day I
watched something I watched a video
where like there some celebrities that
were going on on a
trip this dog got me
before you have to agree though that's
like how can you
even sounded very much like Tim Allen
right
now how how how how am I supposed to
anticipate that
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] dog always keep an eye out
for those [\h__\h] dogs
man
you
ah
what I don't know what song you're
talking
[Music]
about guys this is
suffering not really having much fun
anymore more so I'm not going to play
much longer going to give this only a
few more chances for my own sanity think
also for your guys
sanity yeah keep that door closed and
keep the dog out I think if it's closed
he will not necessarily
attempt walking out
here this level is hard don't worry no
it
is if you you quit you'll have to redo
the oh no okay no no no
no you mean the previous [\h__\h] too no
okay no no no no thanks for the
[Music]
memberships [\h__\h] I don't
know oh that was
lucky
[Music]
shot run out of ammo oh okay big
guy is difficult maybe I'll try to bit
bit closer but I'm just scared to be
seen
[Music]
uhoh okay I'm ready for the big guy come
on come
on shoot when they walk the other
way uh I'm not sure what you mean
but okay this should work you will die
there we
go who said I couldn't stealth this
level I'm totally stealing it I don't
know any other way this is how I was
raised
hello
okay maybe stealthie time is over now I
don't know I'll think about it I'll
think about it just need a new weapon we
have
the I can't walk
through I'm going to go for this so
and what's the best way to end maybe
below I know there's Windows I'm aware
of
them but no one really is patrolling
here
so there's still a lot of them left yeah
[\h__\h]
yeah all of these are m
most of them are
Gunnies
[\h__\h] what's this wait this is not an SMG
that I have is it what is this
gun [\h__\h] this is not
good oh
[Music]
a [\h__\h]
you I don't
[Music]
I'll try to get as much as I can out of
the silencer still and then I don't know
I guess we going to oh
going to go aggressive after that
[Music]
where it looks like he's like holding
that big guy at gunpoint oh
oh I hate my
life what what's your
problem oh that was one of his guards
though
[Music]
okay everybody's routes are really
different right now holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh shotgun one hits him yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah well killing him wasn't really the
issue if I get him from there then you
know just got to wait for him to walk
out and he dies
but oh
hello okay bottom room is empty again
actually it's looking pretty uh as much
empty as it was before now I want to
take care of this room though
maybe with what gun try the shotgun
again but everybody might hear
[Music]
that okay how the [\h__\h] didn't he know
this right well we should be grateful
for that the less people chase me the
less I panic
this one we could get him to walk over
cuz he doesn't have a gun anyway
hello
okay let's take
this to get him out
too I was do well I was doing good I was
doing well
I was doing
good it's okay it's okay it's it's the
game the game is about
redoing the game game wants you to
suffer game wants you to redo everything
again and again and again this is how it
is oh hello
sh skill issue
simulator I got to read more comments
because you guys are what keeps me
[Music]
going love kfp love
chicken no no no you won't get me
through the
window
wait oh I'm so close I'm so close I'm so
scared hug me give me a
[Music]
hug like this is not like how how I
usually play Halla Miami usually it's
like
Yay surprise ha scream monkey scream
let's go ha now today it's just anxiety
what the
[\h__\h]
Hallelujah got to been over
[Music]
there dog come here dog
no okay let me hide in this dead
corner I'm scute
okay he can still see me for there we
got to keep that in mind maybe I can try
to get him
first
uhoh I hate this game
[Music]
[Applause]
how did I miss every [\h__\h] shot except
for that one inside there that I wasn't
even trying to get
ah wake up wake up on Saturday night
could be New York
maybe London Paris May toky
tonight
tonight yeah tonight
Hill I want to keep this machete right
now please let me stay in my comfort
zone okay no then
well hm
H okay and the guy inside is dead wait
didn't I do that in the previous
run did I do it
again all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right all right r r r ladies
yeah let's go
co
[Music]
[\h__\h] all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right I'm
going to [\h__\h] up anyway yeah what's my
gun what's my what's my what's my choice
of weapon right
now is that empty down
there no
okay this one is
[Music]
easy okay almost got it I almost got
it oh hell yeah can I get it hell yeah
hell yeah
if I'm going to fail now I'm going
to I don't even know I don't even know
it's okay it's okay calm down we're fine
there's this one guy here we don't even
have to kill him with this one cuz this
loud can I step out is this safe to step
out let's take
this
oh oh they walked out why would you do
that why would you do
that okay you can come over
[Music]
here I'm
scared one down three to go
[Music]
maybe okay calm room okay two to go ah
I'm going to do it
I'm ba them out with
noise where is
he this this silence gun doesn't matter
anymore
[Music]
we made it but it w
cost is every like every other chapter
that's left in this game going to be
this rough I
wonder wow
[Music]
oh oh I would have had to do all of this
over again is that what you're saying
like oh my
[Music]
God where's
car was that correct yeah oh my see all
of this see all the [\h__\h] we've been
through this has traumatized me
severely to car where where am I oh oh
hi
guys oh I can't shoot you sorry about
trying that I have like reflexes that
are not healthy
anymore next love is worse oh my God no
God please
no there you are you know you should
really wait for backup in these
situations uh there was going to be back
up well I didn't [\h__\h]
know there was never back up you know
I'm always
alone it's not my fault for you guys
took so long to get here is it I got
here first you got a problem that what
you did was Reckless and you know that
your AC endangered this whole operation
Operation give me a break if you don't
like it Go complain to the chief I'm out
of
here oh did I drop my weapon there or
what go to car yeah my
sick low frider or whatever Wonder what
it is could
be what do I get F or something like
that c okay cool
uh ew
disgusting you lose Cannon for turn in
your badge and run are you guys why is
there two people saying that is that a
meme are you meing on
me
hey I guess our serial killer has been
added again
C for chimpin love C for classy C for
Clear why is she sad
because it's just rough out
there the Loose Canon cup is a classic
trop Trope oh I'm I'm you you're wrong
guys you're over complicating things I'm
just Leroy
Jenkins isn't all of the this Hotline
Miami is basically Leroy Jenkins the
game
but without backup to ever
come
where
Jacks that level broke many people
you're game of beating it I love you for
saying that thank you it's good to know
that I'm not the only one
suffering and I got the streaming debuff
okay
oh well oh well well let me guess our
serial killer has been added again sorry
I'm done with voice acting now I'm so
done for
today barely making progress man I feel
like
oh what gave it
away we left another message for us he
left sometimes his fun is hard to read
mundane as ever please don't make me do
it again well at least he got a bit
creative with the victim poor kid how I
don't see any creativity there maybe he
was upset that the papers haven't made a
bigger deal of him these scumbags seem
to Crave
attention attention
please did you guys see my little video
that I sent to waya for her birthday
stream H she's a birthday streamer
instead of I think it was no Callins
just um the videos yeah was it was some
stories about birthdays what my my
biggest birthday memories and the only
one that I could think of was that one
and there was uh uh what was it what
what kind of birthday party I would like
to have and I just said I would like to
have like basically anything just
because I haven't been like uh
celebrating my birthday properly for
years now like if anything I would only
do it really oneon-one with one more
person like uh this year I kind of
celebrated it with cie
right um yeah which is fine like I like
that I I I don't even like big people
Gatherings much but I feel like I should
kind
of let myself be celebrated at least for
my birthday you know what I mean like in
person of course you guys are
celebrating me so much and maybe that's
why I don't really need it right now but
even before whole life I wasn't uh
throwing any parties ever m
yeah but now you guys throw me big
birthday parties basically I mean I
throw them and you come so that's
good that's fine I don't remember the
last time I celebrated my birthday yeah
I also I feel like I
mean nah I don't think I'm past the age
of birthday parties I feel like I should
I should still be like celebrating but
well at least sometimes but I don't know
the effort of planning
[Music]
something I don't like it I think of it
too late and and now now all days I want
to spend my birthdays kind of you know
with you guys anyway cuz like I mean
what I have to I kind of have to I have
to spend my birthday with you
guys they are now reserved to be spent
with you guys yes yes yes yes birthday
is workday Christmas too Christmas is
workday New Year is workday although
this year um this year so far I've like
uh pretty much dedicated my New
Year's uh to to whole life and streams
and work like also official programs etc
for this year I said I'm not doing it
this year this year I want to keep it
open to celebrate with my friends
possibly so now you know that already
ahead of
time so New Year's with my
friends but probably just the evening so
maybe during the daytime I can
stream and like early like before noon
you know uh and and Christmas probably
family family family mommy sister and so
on and just this year I think I I'll
focus more on
that yeah cuz previously
I you
know yeah you guys
[Music]
understand thank you thank you thank you
anyway you might be getting your fair
share once this gets out think you can
handle this this pressure all eyes will
be on you now I'm sure this guy will
slep up sooner or
later speaking of which what have you
got for me any any
findings not much no murder weapon and
no witnesses an electrician found him
like this we must he must have been
taken here by force found cuff marks
around his waists and ankles ankles
death by strangulation the killer gutted
him postmortem thank God anything else
yeah it seems like the killer may have
robbed him unlike previous victims
couldn't find the kid's wallet who knows
might have been someone else people have
morals these days we'll have to run his
Prince and see if we can identify him
this font is so difficult to read
especially on a big screen I think all
right good job Johnson I'm going to head
back to the office been a rough night
okay sir I'll let you know if we find
anything
else okay thank you bye I'm out of
here yeah
[Music]
ah
that's so good hello hello hello who
wants to talk to me I'm here now talk to
me talk to me what do you want from me
why am I here oh wait there's something
in the back of the trunk we present time
delivery peza it looks like a chicken
doll here who wants it y hey guys I just
got the new masks we ordered chicken
mask that's a chicken mask can we use it
now let's go pretty cool let's go ow you
too well we all going to put on chicken
oh my god oh it's so loud go wo woo wo
let me turn it down on OBS at
least why is it so loud
now how did I feel you like
him what what is the sound
like sound glitching or
what
Fu
guys kfp you good you good mate
[\h__\h] I think I'm done here how are you
guys doing I'm moving up to the next
floor see you on the roof and then we're
going to goof what I'm not sure I follow
all clear on my end I think wait what
was that B I think I just
bucked what are you guys talking about
all right we're on the roof now you're
not on the roof how are things
going
hallucinations hello is anyone
there guys
Buck
uh things are going weird again mommy
I'll get
it suddenly I'm the chick hey none of
these phones are ringing
it when did you get a cell phone I took
it from that guy we clocked at the bar
just Chang charged it up this morning at
Dean's place what should I do should I
answer that I don't see any reason not
to oh I go
nothing hi it's me I know you wanted out
and I respect that but I just figured
I'd give you a call and see if you've
changed your mind you wouldn't believe
what's been going on the last few weeks
we're calling the shots now top of the
game no one can touch us can't touch us
the new product is in full scale
production got a new place threee floors
up in the Northwest 20th Street who
would have fun why don't you swing by
and check it out huh hello anyone there
CL hey guys I think I just found us
something to do tonight let's go right
now I'll tell you all about it in the
van in the van in the van he said let's
going to the
van 12 Death
Wish
so do we continue or do we stop
here maybe but if I start now and I
don't finish the whole level then I have
to do it again
right we can we can we can see how how
diff no actually I don't have the I I
don't think I have the patience for it
anymore this the final level of the act
wait and how more
[Music]
acts let
see maybe one
[Music]
more
oh oh [\h__\h]
this goes
[Music]
hard this game is just about the music
in the
end it's trying to make you think it's a
game about something else but really
it's just about the
music oh
[Music]
what did I say it's about the
music
oh oh found the music I
[Music]
said oh those are really loud in my ear
I like it it's good you got to turn this
one up
[Music]
okay let's go sh let me go in
shut up let me go in shut
up I wait BR you sure will be able to
jump across the other building it look a
bit far to me not that far well at least
not for the rest of us you may have some
difficulties with it though well [\h__\h]
you which way am I going
[Music]
the music won me
over I'm going to run out of ammo fast
[Music]
not not not normal the music is making
me do
things ah let me do my
[Music]
thing stop
no oo sick
ah oh no no no oh no no no oh no
[Music]
no yeah
I'm not going to even talk anymore like
just listen to this music that's that's
all the stream is
[Music]
it's just the Ving screen now
G play no commentary I'm I'm in the zone
right now please don't make me leave the
zone
that's a no from me sir that's a big no
for
me that's not a VI no no
no get
[Music]
back alive I fin I got
him okay
[Music]
what was here again I don't
remember that's through
[Music]
there I don't know about up there I
think that's not a good place to go like
maybe I should go for the middle cuz
like it's hard to see what's
there oh [\h__\h] uhoh
[Music]
what do you want
ah blood must be spilled all over the
floors all these emeralds on the floor
must become blood
diamonds oh he saw
me I don't know if I got that one
[Music]
yum yum
meow
meow I'm getting Stu he's so
fast do some
[Music]
we no more hamburgers for you no
more you're eating one salad per day and
that's it
[Music]
I got
again woo
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah I can't see what's up there back
[Music]
way now I know
what do I do how do I do
this I know now somebody's
there oh no I'm out
of Amo I can't do guns blazing
anymore somebody's supposed to be there
I think or did I already kill that guy
[Music]
oh
oh oh the
dog [\h__\h] do
[Music]
yeah I wasn't ready he wasn't ready
we're not
[Music]
ready I should have waited
is this music too loud for you guys are
you trying to
relax no relaxing allowed
okay I want you to experience your inner
gramlin and
goblins that haunt you every
[Music]
night I want you to feel what I'm
feeling
[Music]
hey no did I run out of
Amo what is what was he waiting for what
what was I waiting
[Music]
for she talking I can't hear her you
can't hear me I'm pretty sure you can
OBS is telling me I'm louder than the
music
even when I speak like
[Music]
this uh it seems I have caught some
people's attention
[Music]
H
now ooh
[Music]
aing blinded the hallways yeah sometimes
you have to Ray and pray I'll do it
again oh I got two
kills I don't know how many people are
there but I got two
kills music is loud a tiny bit are you
for
real here I lowered it a tiny
bit just a tiny bit yeah see because of
you I died because the music has to be
loud but okay it's okay we've been we've
been blasting this so long
[Music]
now I
accepted I was reloading so I couldn't
even get the full potential out of that
but apparently I killed two people in
the exact correct look
okay
wait I got the big guy so that one's no
concern now we got to wait for the other
[Music]
one okay all
right oh dog oh that's a new one
at least that's out of the way no dog
can get me now is that the one that got
me before
[Music]
possibly oh I'm figuring out the angles
baby where is where is the right
[Music]
angle I'm so
scared okay okay okay
baby oh I finally know what it looks
like up here and there's only three
enemies left
[Music]
don't celebrate early okay
okay no celebration
[Music]
time
oh hey
oh
hey
h hey
H I had one bullet left oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] what is this one doing again
ah this one is the Dodger how is he
[Music]
dodging better I go this way
maybe I guess I could throw a knife at
the big
guy
but I'm also throw knife at
[Music]
ones uh this one then the guns blazing
doesn't work because I had no
gun have mercy oh laugh he
coming it it does it it doesn't work on
him it doesn't work on it doesn't work
on him I can't throw the knife at him it
doesn't get stuck even though there
should be plenty of hit bugs there bait
the rifle guys first okay
hi I was still focused on something
else okay I'll do it though I'll do
it m
[Music]
why was he
out why is she out there
[Music]
I'm on a
mission this one one them
[Music]
anyway oh oh
stuck in the
[Music]
door what why
why I think um when once this music
Started something in my
head some switch
was flipped
over and now I'm like all right baby
[Music]
ni this came to ear what
[\h__\h] no I didn't see the new Moka Moka
mooka trailer no apparently something's
coming out right I only saw like people
retweeting something there
Muka is it the same story and a movie of
it or is it new story I
wonder wait shouldn't there be more than
one in
here where's my where's my shotgun
where's the shotgun that I supposed to
be
having
hey hello
[Music]
you you you want to you want to say
hello
[Music]
tomato yes I need it going with us again
and he's not creating papino what are
you
[Music]
saying I used to really like mea when I
first watched the the first season
wasn't there a second season probably
maybe even more
I don't remember if I watched the second
season
fully
hello
[Music]
no please
please actually I want to try this room
again
[Music]
yeah m one more
please there's no windows there right
that's amazing no
[Music]
window sorry I was watch I was
watch I thought I didn't touch the door
yet I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I he I apologize
[Music]
no what was I waiting
for no big guys okay okay big guys where
you are oh did I just ooh I switched his
room man
man yeah
[Music]
okay we can calm down a little bit okay
A little bit cuz I I I think I'm in the
groove anyway I'm I'm I'm grooving no
not a big guy no why is he turning
me he was becoming ran
roulette and I am the victim of
[Music]
it I like it when CPU goes crazy doesn't
know what it's doing anymore it's it's a
sign of the Soul inside trying to break
out of the
Endless life cycle inside the
computer yes yes trust me
okay I don't want to bring the purple
guy over here I just
want to have
fun oh no what why did you hear me why
why do they hear me I'm not even using a
gun I should be quiet I had a guarantee
on this knife that said 100% silence
killing
guaranteed I've been live too or is
there a no there are one okay I'm I'm
blind there wear Windows after
all uhoh
no I don't want to use a gun I'm using
the snipe right now
okay snifer for
life I hope there's a return policy
H guys have you ever returned something
on Amazon I need to finally like learn
how to do it cuz there's something I
really want to
return like often when there's something
that I realized okay this is maybe not
ideal I still try to make use of it or
yeah but this time what what what you
scared
huh let's with
[Music]
him e I'm out of here and
bye
no no no
[Music]
no wallhead print out label put it on
the back box but what did I what do I do
if my printer isn't working my stupid
ass printer man I don't know did I tell
you guys about my
printer it's not even that old but for
some reason it just decided to stop
working no
[Music]
it just decided from one day to another
or like okay it was like from one week
or like one month where I wasn't using
it but before it was
working suddenly it's like I'm not going
to I'm I I decided I'm done here my CHP
here my CHP here is done you know I'm
done did I anger anyone no oh
[Music]
yes yes I did yes I did hey there's so
many
rooms did I go up the door being open
bothers me but oh
[Music]
wait
oh oh shees what did I do let me
check I didn't get this one let me get
this one
I'm out
[Music]
ammo not any of the guns that I
want this one only has two this one has
three oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah bgm so good although it's
starting to get a little bit repetitive
but that's
okay h huah okay that room is clear and
that one hard to
tell no windows here safe safe safe I
could go this one next oh oh I see
doggo okay let's let's get the doggo
here go come on come on go do go who's a
good boy who's a good
[Music]
boy what are these guns
oh R that's a
rifle oh
[\h__\h] was there one to se okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
oh no what the hell is going
on he hurt me
he heard me that sucker heard
[Music]
me what with him what's with him he's
his actions are freaking me
[Music]
out oh
[\h__\h] I've angered many people
[Music]
he
he yeah I guess the dog is doing a good
job at protecting his territory
and
his people who have
a very who are on the very wrong side
although I feel like we're all kind of
evil like I don't really think that
these guys are the ones I'm playing are
good people
either by the way we're having fun here
and all that I'm I'm having fun like my
trauma is cured but my left hand ever
since I started playing like this oh
[\h__\h] there's like some I feel uh oh [\h__\h]
ow it's very
strange ow ow
[Music]
ow
some saying it in German we thing say it
uh I think it's [\h__\h]
up they're all bad people that's the
point bad people doing bad things
and one uping each other about being bad
people wonderful yeah it's I mean it's s
what s new I never heard that
[Music]
before no more TV for you you don't
appreciate it enough oh [\h__\h]
hell no no
no those are 4K TVs are you
sure come on
where's the other guy oh he's up here
where's your
[Music]
friend ah I got so far before I want to
go there again you are in the
[Music]
way C
M he
Y no no no no and now you are getting in
position like that that's that's kind of
sucky you
know let's use the silen again oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] wah weak wah we maybe we should
watch more we we what who who's that
John John Wick what's his name and we
should watch more
[Music]
movies I I totally forgot that this guy
has Dodge but the Dodge is so useless
like what I don't think it helps at all
that's the weakest mask honestly I just
remember like I was thinking what does
this guy have I'm like oh yeah oh yeah
the Dodge roll uh the most useless thing
ever I mean sure
it's fun but not as its
own like if this is the only thing
you're going to get then
no no that's not
cool no no why am I here I shouldn't
have been here I was in the wrong
place I can roll I can roll for
Windows oh
well
interesting why you guys not seeing me
[Music]
and roll on the bullets
oh and basically the way I'm playing now
is as if I wasn't wearing any mask at
[Music]
all you know what I'm going to do this
part first
[Music]
oh
okay uh now m oh [\h__\h] don't throw them
away we still need our
[Music]
weapons remember enemies far yeah yeah I
know I know that's why I walked
away oh oh people heard me
um what
[Music]
no the [\h__\h] illegal
illegal I'm going to sue
[Music]
you my hands hurts so much from all the
strain and all the pain
[Music]
guys I'm still
here I take this and go away
[Music]
byebye yeah yeah I guess
actually I know I could still bait with
sounds but wait
[Music]
couple minutes break for the hand I
don't
know okay now I want a different gun for
the other cool tricks
[Music]
that she
I'm just checking I'm just walking up
there to get my my
focus now it should be
empty pretty much
[Music]
ad
door fa night this part almost reminds
me of feite it it could be like so many
songs here have a similar Vibe oh oh
she's too far my shot takes too long to
arrive can I continue there or should I
go over to that room
maybe no windows no
windows ah need another
shotgun this one po big
guy ooh ah my hand hurts so much [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] every time I let go of the
keyboard holy [\h__\h] every every part
hurts the wrists and the up the wrist
going up to the thumb and all that
really bad really bad right
now
m m
M maybe I
should
bait it's okay it's okay this is all
according to my Kaku
[Laughter]
ah I've been going for 3 hours no no
YouTube is not showing the exact time
it's 4 hours and 5
[Music]
minutes the problem is now that I am
deep in this I don't want
to waste all the effort is there a
silence one somewhere this isn't silence
good let get this one without any why am
I
stuck oh
uhoh hallelujah hallelujah
hallelu okay dog dog
dog maybe with this I'm here I'm here
doggo come here come here come here come
here I'm so ready for you I'm so ready
for you bring it on Bring It On
oh I will not fight with something
that's so far
dog where did he
go and now I'm careful now I'm being
careful because we're really far in the
level
[Music]
so I will push for the pain yeah I want
to finish this
[\h__\h] hello oh there it
is come to me come to Papa Come to
Papa yeah
what do we have left a bunch of people
down here yeah okay this side is still
pretty crowded
[Music]
but new gum 20 thought
I can't see what's going on down here
this is triggering like how are you
supposed to
know what to expect I'm I'm going to
scout the
area but they move you know oh we can we
can you know I can do this strategy
again where I go down I focus on them
then and I go back oh that was two two I
got two
oh [\h__\h] okay now I think if it's this
far they don't even see me sometimes
they see me even when they're not on the
screen but it was this far like they
wouldn't even see me
right [\h__\h] my hand ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] they do see me okay now they
wouldn't see me cuz they're on the
side
[Music]
um just got to wait you know what I'll
keep my target on him so that I can kind
of know where he
is yeah now now is not a good time there
there's something to stand there right
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait there
is it not
really
it should I yeah this is maybe the the
right thing to do
yeah yeah
oh I just need a weapon
um a lot of shotguns
six can I bait him too yes ah come on
well
then well
then okay okay oh what do you want
I think I'm done here how are you guys
doing I'm moving up to the next floor
see you I see you guys on the roof no
not more my head can't take it
anymore I swear oh [\h__\h] okay little
break oh God shut the we have to take a
a a hand
[Music]
break two more two more [\h__\h]
gamer
hands also an ear bre yeah and yeah you
know that was a banger but now we
can how's the card
signing jenma said I have to finish my
Friday I I should be fine I haven't
continued since but
H
yeah car PR to BR has a lot of stages is
this what it's
called it's fine I just I have a lot of
things to do in this week like I have so
many meetings
too but I did do 200 in like one stream
right so and that was like me talking as
well in between if I just focus on it
yeah
a the artist for this track
[Music]
ah can you do them during your meetings
though those are important meetings I
need to
focus
yeah next member at stream watchong I
was thinking so yeah I think it's okay
to do watchong right cuz previous ones
were one was the the talking um signing
and the before was uh gaming the one
before I don't know I don't
remember uh I'm I don't know what which
movie though there's some that I had in
mind maybe we could watch at some point
but I forgot all of them brain empty oh
yeah Bell was really nice last time
[Music]
mhm I enjoyed that
one um what's that wait
uh what's that super long
movie that everybody has like watched at
least once but I
didn't uh is Barbie available yet oh no
cow carat is here cow carat do you have
something to work do I need to give you
stuff for you to be able to continue
working oh
uh uh no that's not the ones I mean I
don't think so the one that's kind of
sad uh with the guy the one guy who like
I don't know he's kind of um special I
guess Forest scum yeah never watch that
should we watch that is that interesting
to watch together Forest
Gump what the [\h__\h]
is there's something on my there's some
icon running running around on my
Google is it only when you Google Forest
Gump there's like people running what is
this there's people running on my
Google emojis are running a
marathon is it about Forest Grump do
they run in the movie it's a reference
oh my God why does this movie get it's
getting more and more why is this movie
getting such a special
wow I see holy [\h__\h] they're all charging
after
him W 1 two three four five holy [\h__\h] so
many it's like
20 you have to Google Forest scum
guys wait did cow carrot say something
let me see I got a
DM
okay oh cool
oh oh that's kind of cute got something
from
chy uh and something from Spirit snare
oh yes okay this is actually really
important because I I last
minute uh commissioned logo from Spirit
snare like uh two days
[Music]
ago which one's better maybe I let you
guys
choose I
think I think the first one
I go with n number
one
okay
okay Coolio
Coolio okay Coolio how's my hand doing
oh my hand's getting
better so what did you think about first
Gump I'm f with first
gum oh my God it's a ging yeah it's so
cool but they're doing it just for
Forest Gump what the
hell it's pretty long right oh you you
dislike it okay let's just let's just
put it like on the radar we can do like
a poll Maybe
W try Googling do a barrel roll do a
barrel
roll what there's a video about make
Google do a bar roll and six other crazy
tricks one of the other crazy tricks one
of the other crazy tricks one of the
other crazy tricks and that was so funny
Google to the barel roll okay I don't
want to hear any audio here just tell me
tell me what the trick
trick Google Easter EG we we we what
what oh my God what's
that Google Gravity Google
gravity and nothing happened I have to
turn something on I think for that to
work but that looked complicated is this
[\h__\h] oh my God wait
what oh that's some crazy [\h__\h] try
Google meteor ride wait with
Google Google
meteorite or just
meteorite Zurg
Rush Zerg
Rush nothing's happening do I have to
say Google
before wait do you mean zero
Z someone is saying Zero
Rush do I say Google
before ites your
screen you have to push I'm feeling
lucky oh okay Z rush and I'm feeling
lucky where is the feeling
lucky don't be so lucky I don't see it
the me I don't see any one of those why
don't they work for
me a breakout on image search
really but you need to click the L Link
at the top oh
okay oh [\h__\h] wait what's that though
Google is this a thing that Google did
or is it some like a thing that a fan
made what the [\h__\h] is
this is it's it's killing my Google
search but it's it's it's getting rid of
um results that don't seem interesting
anyway star cra can I fight it I wait I
think I can fight it oh I can fight it I
think I can fight it something I can
click on yeah I can kill
them ask
you
ask
Esq ah it's
tilted [\h__\h] someone fix it bunk bunk
bunk with a hammer well what do I do
it's tilted it's say tilt that's said
and then it gives me a dictionary ask
you not in a straight or level position
Google you're so funny what the [\h__\h] why
is Google doing such dad
jokes wait I love that I didn't even
know I didn't even know the meaning of
ask you is it Esq or asq esue esue esue
escue that's such a weird word it's like
asking you what does ask you mean this
is so funny type in ask you in Google
Google it's just tilted I love
it why are they so
funny because old Google wasn't evil yet
oh maybe the new Google doesn't know
about these things that old Google has
left behind what do you mean old Google
though has it been taken over like
Twitter
too I'm doing the katamar one how do I
do the katamar one do I just type in
Kar I don't know what happens when I do
that
Google Kat Google
Kat I think there's something I can
click on
here oh yeah you can play it there right
there on the
screen I don't even know how to play the
real C it's really
[Music]
slow it's so laggy oh my God it's it's
actually making me lag
too okay this is not for me
funny
though the barrel world was the
funniest ah try cat and click orange
button no
way
cat
[Music]
what oh my God #
plus
what what how did I never know about
this oh my God that is so cute guys you
have to try
it they're putting little paw fies all
over long long hand long paw it does the
same for dog oh my God I can't the cat
won't let me type anything new in I have
to eggs eggs oh it washes it away no let
it stay
dog oh my God so many different Doles
where's
Bubba I don't see any oh I think that
might have been Bubba yeah that one
might be Bubba I don't know I don't
think Bubba has such long hands pause
but that might be bub a lot of that uh
imagination cute oh there was a
poodle wow
cute this is this is amazing how have I
been on the internet for like centuries
and never known about these things what
I know that sometimes Google implements
something like the like the the Forest
Gump thing but I didn't know there was
things to this extent
[Music]
I wonder if you can type it in like in
other languages and it works the same
way or if it's just in
English Google where's Bird yeah where
is
Bird that's so cool okay my hand is fine
let's do this what is this character
doing again is this the one is one punch
man does this work on the big guy too oh
it might need
this what can I take weapons with this
guy I don't know if I can
[Music]
[Applause]
actually I can't kill him I can just
only stun him I
think I wait I have to get on him never
mind I'm so stupid I'm so stupid I
probably just have to get on
him didn't we all pull down chicken mask
I want the chicken mask back
ah give me back my chicken
mask okay okay okay okay okay
okay I love one punch man that this
level is literally made for one punch
man so
so we're going to have a lot of fun here
what if I go down here
first we have a
gun Oho [\h__\h] how dare he and sometimes I
can't get on him
why wait wait
wait okay let
go I know he wasn't done yet I was kind
of just waiting
[Music]
got to fro some
punches all Direction punch 360
punch no no no no no not fair
he's also got the The Killing punch he
knows it very well he's he was once my
master probably and I just don't
remember yikes yikes
yikes okay okay wait wait wait wa
wait you should be able to punch the
bullets
what should be good to go here H windows
but uhuh easy
ah have to go this way one of these
ways good very good very
good ooh
hi
easy easy
clap they saying you should wait it was
the one guy there that actually work I
meant you you you wish you little
[\h__\h] you don't just say your wishes like
that cuz I will believe
it but I I don't think I would have
really tried though actually it's too
[Music]
risky oh
Windows uh uh
uh thank God he's not very trigger
friendly oh okay
ready I know I know that was bound to
happen Bring it on Bring it on I feel
like I'm in an action movie right now
they should make a a Hotline Miami
action movie oh my
God
hello like for real for real hey
[Music]
I want
that and especially if it's going to
keep this kind of sick music oh
no that's very welcome to me it's
called Fight Club it's called Fight Club
in the last 30 minutes of John
Wick John Wick but in the 80s
no no they're not they're not wearing
funny
[Music]
masks hey so mean his reach is so mean
okay what now
[Music]
uh going
down okay gun
guun a the gun guy here
too I think I'm I'm pretty good with
Punchy
[Music]
guy don't you
agree yeah this is difficult this is a
bit tricky cuz they will see me but
that's okay I mean come over
if you want ooh here he
comes yeah
yeah t
yeah now let's get the others here come
on come on try try me try me try
me sneaky
peek
hi bait
t t t t and firsty for T you me a t
hello hello
[Music]
yeah
okay ah too easy
now for him I have to kind of step
[Music]
outside can I get from a different place
so I do I have to go through here I
think I have to go through
[Music]
here
[\h__\h] maybe I should go from below maybe
that's easier for him to notice
me okay
y can I actually hide in the bush or do
they see me
[Music]
okay no hiding
okay easy all clear baby what was that I
think I just heard something oh my God
oh my God oh these boys are the last
ones te oh God
okay right right C no it was like one at
a time was it or no it was it was both
at the same time right left click isum
yum yum and right click is shooty
shoot okay um
[Music]
I don't like
this don't get shot gun
guy stay behind
me
stupid I'm hungry mommy made me food
yesterday cuz like when we went back
when we came back I was like so
tired so she was so nice while I was
like taking them she she cooked with
whatever ingredients I had
left and so I have leftovers today and
also yesterday in the
wilderness there may have been mommy
somewhere close by and then she made me
um some yummy food
too it's nice to have a Ka of
whenever mom is uh there to make one for
me hi
Mom one of the Austrian desserts I think
they're great to eat for breakfast you
know okay I've yet to use the gun now
baiting
time I said I said it's baiting
time I said it's B
that really surprised me that really bum
Boozled me
okay oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that scared
me that really scared
[Music]
me everybody CES man so
true you're doing great keep baiting
yeah I
[Music]
will
hello my stream scare
you you should be used to it though not
my fault this is what you're getting
yourself
into oh wait three year anniversary I
just realized you know what that means
membership uh unbelievable but new
membership thingy will be necessary
soon how early did I open
membership after debuting like one or
two weeks or
so gold and phoenixes cuz the maximum is
the two-year badge right we have one
year and two year
27th oh my God you guys got to keep on
reminding me of that please 27th
[Music]
September oh I'm scary there's someone
down there I remember ah
[Music]
oh that's an unexpected one
to come
here I mean the meele ones have
absolutely no chance against the
chainsaw though holy [\h__\h] you just keep
it running and running it doesn't even
like yeah damn 5 m should have sign up
faster was too shy to shy why would't
you be
shy but but it's okay I'm glad you made
it at some
point try baiting with
guns interesting sounds baiting I see I
see
[Music]
what did I do about the big guy what do
I do about the big
[Music]
guy I saw him coming I was going to come
back to him but
[Music]
Yahoo the search engine that nobody
uses did somebody say something shooting
he can be Mele it just takes time yeah
got to I guess it's one of those uh
things where I have to wait for him to
die again no one shotting I suppose
I have Bruno Mars in my head now for
some
reason oh you heard that
commotion they all heard it let's go
everybody's welcome where did the fat
guy come from from that room was it that
one let's go here for inspecting the
area what's going on here o another oh
Dogg
uh-oh you stick it in and you don't let
it go out oh oh holy [\h__\h] that felt
intense I wasn't sure what was going on
there but you just you just you stay in
there and believe
believe you thought I was going to die I
thought so too we're we're we're we're
Believers of kiaha
death please come
here
okay what's
left ah there they coming they're
[Music]
coming
no oh wait I'm out of ammo with him I
have to be careful of that too but it's
okay it's okay what gun did I take a
rifle I don't you hear me where are they
oh all the way over here okay I'm going
to camp at the corner
[Music]
then they just walk into my swinging
chainsaw
no he shouldn't be able to see me
right
okay no you didn't see
me he did in fact see
me see me
[Music]
am the
Wonder you had one wish what would it be
one
wish that is like
so like vague and open
bring it on
baby bring it on
baby bring it on okay stay committed
[Applause]
yeah no no you can't wish for that no
you can't wish for three more wishes or
so you can't do it
um I
mean I wonder if it has to be a
realistic wish
but and there's many things I could wish
for I don't think I could
decide quitter
[Music]
talk never a chance at life ooh if I
could redo everything knowing I mean it
would take a lot of time but if I could
redo things knowing
how how like what I did in the previous
live
why did I not think of that before
genius can even get the ones from this
room to
me hold on no yeah
okay wasn't there someone down there all
right I'm
leaving I guess not
oh [\h__\h] can I do both at once [\h__\h] sh I
can't I can't I
can't trying to at least get one with
the
gun
H you wish to Super Chat me more thank
you I appreciate
that I
mean if if it's something to that has to
be
realistic maybe I like uh like not
magical like wishing for another Tri
life or so or using magic or
so maybe
[Music]
just more
success in my career which would then
equal
to more
money and who doesn't want that
huh and just I think then I wouldn't be
so hard on myself uh self-doubt
Etc
[Music]
and uh yeah
self what do you how do you say it
oh The Chronic pain wishing that away
would be nice
too
hey
hey hey
why did he join it's not no's
business I of your business okay I'll
I'll I'll bait you now so you don't
annoy the [\h__\h] out of me again okay
we're done here you you probably want
oh you probably want some
too okay now are we happy now
no I'm not happy with that what the
[\h__\h] MH
mhm I wish I could meet you well I'm I'm
here is this not enough for you then
listen to The Great wander that's that's
kind
of one of the themes of the great
[Music]
Wanderer the invisible wall between
usoh uh-oh
uh-oh oh
no
impossible
rig
n oh how did he not see me
[Music]
I listen to love r instead that's fine
too that's also about
[Music]
us
YouTube are we back did you hear what I
said about love Rush Oh [\h__\h] don't get
so aggressive you don't have to kill the
PC the PC did nothing to you
PC is expensive don't destroy just so
that you can let out your
aggression a little bit laggy why why
you got to be like
that
oh it's
okay all three of them are coming
yay it's a party in room two
be yes my hand is hurting again this
this game is uh tough on the wrist I
don't know about baiting those I
could but dealing with two of them could
go very wrong but I'll try oh I only
bited one holy [\h__\h] why oh dog is up
[Music]
there yeah okay doggle you want to come
over
look at all the people who who you
couldn't protect who you failed to
protect I'm almost done fortunately
let's go let's go hell yeah what kind of
mouse is just a random cute pink
mouse oh [\h__\h] my ah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] my pinky and my ring finger and my
thumb and my wrist are in
pain oh oh you can you please pleas not
do this cuz people want to witness my
success story thank
you I need an ergonomic Mouse it's it's
my left hand the one on the keyboard not
the one on the
mouse only one left guys I think but
this one was kind of
[Music]
difficult and he doesn't react to The
Gunshot here and I can't get any closer
right
[Music]
a RIS cushion I am on the RIS cushion
cushion
cushion just shooting from there to
there I know
man lock him and start firing early okay
I'll
try why is the the pew pew guy so laggy
the thing is he follows
after
[Music]
uh if he would go first that would be
possible but chances are one of us will
get shot oh I'm out of ammo too
okay hello he picked up the shotgun
maybe it's louder
no should I go from here can this
shotgun even reach from here I kind of
doubt it
maybe here take this one that could
reach shotgun could
reach he can't shoot back what do you
mean he can't shoot back doesn't he have
a yeah he has a pew pew but doesn't that
one only have two shots
though oh yeah it is going to go
wrong okay
[Applause]
yay sufficiently
suffering as a wise Phoenix once
said let's go
all right we're on the roof now how are
things going for you guys hello anyone
there guys
uh they're not answering maybe your
walkie talk is busted I don't think so
it seems to be working fine should we go
back and check on them maybe we should
ah you little [\h__\h]
ass
who what the [\h__\h] are you waiting for
[Music]
no kill you why did you kill
you your mom's a c
minus um well okay and you're not
supposed to be here we've got this under
control so look like get I'll try take
over from here you can't do that just
watch
me taking over let's
go well what do we have here wearing
masks huh another set of Vigilantes I
presume don't shoot I give up I'm
through with this just arest me and get
this over with okay I'm done
fighting oh you want to you want your 15
Minutes of Fame on kiaha stream well I
don't think so you know what happens to
fogs like
you he's got he's got some kind of
complex this guy he needs to be the
one the one who calls the
shots guys is there like are you telling
me if I do another stream on this if I
end it now and I do another stream on
this is it going to be a short one
do I not have much
left I'm halfway done oh 50% of the
game Who what okay there's still plenty
okay ah see that's what's happen that's
what happens okay then maybe two more
streams because this game is rough on my
hand as we can
tell oh we're halfway there oh W we're
living on the
Square are you right sir what happened
in here he came out we had to take him
out it was him or
me what squ one on the
CH like my jab is done I'll leave the
rest of my jaob is also done I just want
to go read some super chats and then eat
and sleep and finish things and I'm out
of here does it save here like where
does it
save oh maybe now fourth Act was opened
so now I can
leave now I can quit right okay I think
so can't believe it's been almost 5
hours close the game normally oh
okay how do you know I was I wasn't
going to do that how did you know how
did you
know just don't skip intro next time you
resume Oh I thought it uh oh is the
intro important I thought it was like
something like the same thing as in the
beginning I don't
know look behind you don't say that
that's scary
that's so
scary I want a snack any offerings you
[Music]
guys looking
spicy oh guys
want to see the logo for
tomorrow oh yeah yeah yes you
[Music]
want let put some bgm on
too
B music let's go I prefer surprise but
you're gonna see it afterwards in the
thumbnail
anyway and here let me introduce
[Music]
youo here comes the
logo free anniversary improvised adapt
[Music]
overcome as you can see there's free
challenges you can already guess I think
all of them
[Music]
now yeah the life challenge will be a
spicy food
challenge I'll eat it live on stream I
bought some Korean bulock uh spicy
noodles
but I didn't take the maximum spicy ones
because I'm very sensitive with food and
already the the non- maximum ones are
already [\h__\h] spicy uh Ena told me too
she has experience with them she told
me so I went with like you know one
that's definitely spicy she also told me
it's definitely a challenge for you yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah don't worry that
will be plenty
spicy but not like the the extreme
extreme extreme that people uh I think I
think maybe crony used it
before
H anyway so
this uh in in this logo you can already
see the challenges more or less and yeah
the The Motto the model is improvised
dep overcome because um after 3 years
you know you may think that I have
learned everything there is to learn and
I have all the skills but no there is
still some skill issues and my goal my
idea was was to fix them yes maybe learn
something new experience something new
and improve myself
yeah so there's threee
challenges yeah
[Music]
let's
go tent on fire the tent is not on fire
there's a fireplace in front of
it
stop this is
tomorrow please be there and there will
be also some special reveal
a let's go to
here yes I saw
jaguars and
tigers I saw all I've Seen It All I've
seen it I can say now with all my
confidence and all my heart I've seen it
all been there done
that why did the music not Loop
there we
go merch at 9 a.m. J yes yes so far it
looks like that's what it
[Music]
is so now we're going to R some Super
Chat what did we leave off last time
anybody who remembers it's been a while
it's been a while help
[Music]
me thank
you or skip again why would I skip H
because it was so much no we're going to
start reading that now then
[Music]
what the
[\h__\h] there it
is that's quite a
lot wow wow wow wow thank you for your
generosity everybody
[Music]
there it
is it is a beautiful thumbnail isn't it
I really like this one first I was like
is this too cluttered but I I'm pretty
pretty pretty happy with bit even now in
hindsight especially now in
hindsight would you wear your pacifier
again one more time yeah sure not right
now though oh not right now when when
there's an occasion that calls for
[Music]
it okay let's go Jim Tracy thank you for
the red super chat point of view is
fantastic retrospective is my favorite
song on it and but they're all awesome
you absolutely killed it with your
singing and I can tell you had a big
hand in the lyrics as well
congratulations on achieving one of your
dreams he was so proud of you thank
you yes I've I've done it
finally yeah finally I I let some songs
be kind of influenced by my own uh
feelings and experiences so uh yeah you
know I was nervous about it but you guys
guys we very very
very receiving kindly receiving so thank
you oh everybody loves retrospective
everybody loves suffering you guys are
so emo and
edgy nice thank you J
Tracy happy to hear you like it so
much you got mik than monochronic thanks
for the pinky on the album release B the
C twice and one digital oh my god really
love all the new songs pineapple grew on
me after few lessons and my initial dab
tgw and retrospective are my absolute
favorites they deserve great MBS 10 out
of 10 yeah I
mean I can't give everything like you
know like the best MV that really
deserves unfortunately I'm already most
likely losing lots of money on doing
what I've planned so far so it is what
it is uh but in the future you know I'm
going to be going for singles again and
then singles are going to get great mvs
too um but yeah for now it's not about
the mvy anyway in in the end you have to
enjoy the the song
itself so if you like those
songs then please continue listening to
them
and that will take effect
hopefully uh or somehow put positive
effect on my future music Creations
maybe the better obviously the better
the album
does um the easier it will be for me in
the future to make
[Music]
music
yeah so thank you Mary Pippin thank you
for two pinkies these new songs are to
me your best Works to date the
instrumentals are so catchy the lyrics
are great and range from fun to
heart-wrenching mhm and your voice work
especially in retrospective is just flat
out amazingly beautiful the joy and
energy you put into pineapple and sleep
talking is so fun to listen to and the
meaning and heart you put into love rush
tgw and retrospective just strikes at
the soul I can't wait to see the chorus
for love rush and retrospective those
are not being worked on yet but I got to
get a coral for each song slowly but
trly yeah it takes it takes a lot of
time to create a coral
um at least um you know cuz obviously
Kiana my choreographer she has a life
too she can't be 24/7 making choreos for
me and I uh I'm very picky I'm
unfortunately very picky I'm eating
fruit candy now by the
way to Haim wants to make chus for his
SAS oh
um that's
interesting but I I kind of doubt she I
mean I got to check her dancing style
but I um I'm looking for a very specific
not like typically Japanese idol dance
style I mean maybe for L rush for L Rush
that would be
okay but for like sleep talking and
pineapple I'm I'm going more towards
K-pop style um cor free but that's
interesting I want to see an example if
she can do that I I need to see an
example sleep twerking can she twerk
though
huh she got to show me her twerking
skills yeah I saw like a lot of them
like
K-pop who doesn't we don't love K-pop
k-pop's great Ki Pop I take it they
meant Kiwa pop right not K-pop Korean
pop right
right l s by uh really praised pineapple
like she even wrote to me
privately she tweeted it out like twice
and then um on our like shared server I
a while ago when I released the album I
just put it uh there and I put like a
drive folder with all my instr
instumentals so far for anybody to sing
I was like hey this is my new album and
any if you like any songs you want to
sing them in Koka feel free to do it
here's all the instrumentals and then um
you know Ana replied so sweet love
Ana and
um oh who
else uh yeah Anya replied and then uh uh
MAA kind of just today noticed it
apparently
yeah and she was like oh I want to sing
pineapple yes and I'm like really I
thought sleep talking would be
more your kind of style but yeah she has
permission to sing anything The elusive
Anya so I'm excited I got to keep an eye
out for muna's Kus but anyway thank you
Mary
Pippins pineapple hey
thank you so
[Music]
much again
Mo J for Pinky pineapple makes me dance
lovers makes me SW the great Wanderer is
amazing EDM with Gorgeous vocals that
choke me
up H retrospect it makes me cry sleep
talking makes me smile really it's an
incredible album K thank you for all the
fs I've got the fs for you yeah yeah
yeah you St in my heart baby never let
me go no never let me
go by ha
my
[Music]
me you got
the know you feel it too [\h__\h] I love
that song so
much Dan in the Moonlight I know that I
CAU your eye are we on the same
wonder what's on your mind to be
[Music]
a it's so good the good thing is it's in
English so I actually can remember the
lyrics yeah it's an unofficial cover but
yeah that that's one people really liked
even though it wasn't even mixed it was
just a take out from my k
I guess it kind of suited my voice too
anyway thank you J thank you I am happy
I can make you feel all kinds of things
it's
great please continue listening to it a
lot and also don't forget about you know
my old songs too of course they they're
also in the album but I understand
mostly we just talk about the new
ones but it's it's it's so nice to have
like like a big selection of songs now
but it also makes it more and more
difficult to
choose what to perform on like
special uh occasions you
[Music]
know difficult Studio rings for a pinky
T and retrospective Is My Jam Let's Go
studio rap finally said a little bit
more oh you're a retrospective kind of
guy huh I
see many of you guys are
M do you need a hug
guys I need one too often and I just
don't get it except from my
[Music]
cats yeah yeah you need a hug a man
that's so sad [\h__\h] oh
man
a sad
life I never finished my tangent I just
remember that I started in the middle of
hot Miami some porn I never finished
that one tangent when I was starting to
talk about a video where some
celebrities went to a a city in Austria
that's very very very very dear to me
because I lived there and
uh yeah and and and they liked it so
much and the things they showed off oh
man
I
Y like everything they did and
everything they showed was so familiar
to
me it made me so
happy uh cuz like especially Austria is
like when it comes to being on
TV you know or or presence generally in
people's
minds it's just you know not there for
like a lot of the time often people
would rather a report uh or think about
or talk about or go to other countries
so Austria is just you know like small
baby small
gem so when it does get like good
coverage like that or when when people
you know really appreciate it like that
makes me really happy and really proud
so it's nice to see that no one ever
talks about
Wisconsin yeah but that's like a city in
the country right I'm talking about even
my whole country doesn't even get
recognition that
much call go you little [\h__\h] are you
trying to trigger
me oh Austria's great inoke especially
hey
hey or stay yeah whatever but you know
although
ah Wisconsin probably as big as Austria
I could imagine a state in America is
probably as big as is our
country many states probably
[Music]
are
well he only went to ins and VA
H you got to come again we still have
nice other places yeah yeah what do we
[Music]
do our state is only known for beer and
cheese what state beer and cheese that
could be so many places actually I feel
like oh Wisconsin is twice as big as
Austria
oh in in in size
right somebody else said that maybe the
population is more in
Austria but that's her whole country
so size mhm yeah don't size shame my
country no nobody's doing
that VJ the M silly D thank you
Shan glad you like
retrospective or I guess you you don't I
mean I don't know hard to
tell there will not
be a remix of it I think this is what it
is you got to take it you got to take it
take what you can get honestly like you
guys are so lucky anyway for me to try a
different genre than the one I the ones
that I like the most like
okay I went all out and did like big
variety for my album when I could have
gone just with my comfort genre so so I
take no
complaints I still got to work on Sparks
though this is CH I have to put that on
my schedule cuz I keep on forgetting
it I have to try to record
sco but not today anymore scream
all I don't know how the [\h__\h] to scam
but okay I'll try it tomorrow I got I
got a meeting tomorrow what meeting is
this
meeting why do I just put meeting in my
calendar and then I don't know what it
[Music]
is what is
this what what meaning is this cuz the
problem is I also
have a me a
meeting that's not like on the computer
is is jenma awake
no he do you know what that meeting is I
have on my calendar maybe I put it there
by
[Music]
accident do you know what that is
for
uh the one before my the one of few
hours before
my
uh before my what am I saying
anniversary I have let me remember I I
know two
meetings but one got
moved what's this this one
ah uhhuh this one's
that this one's
that and what is this
yeah I don't know I know what the other
meetings are I don't know this one maybe
it's a
[Music]
mistake mysterious
meetings I got no idea
[\h__\h] might have been a
mistake oh no
oh no no no I'll find out I'll be awake
for it that's for
sure you don't remember it then it isn't
that
important I don't agree with that
statement generally cuz often I'm just
such a my brain is such a Steve there's
so many things that are important and I
keep on forgetting again and
again oh yeah let me put signing cards
on my calendar sign cards I think that
will be one of my
pastimes tomorrow before the anniversary
stream because thankfully most of the
things that I prepared are bods that we
watch together
so most things are out of my hands now
anyway they're in cow carrots hands are
you good are your hands good cow carrot
you shouldn't be listening anyway you
should be working on my video
right no it's so true
[Music]
though okay I see no answer that's a
good
sign it's it's getting really close
though like I I'm actually like I feel
so bad I was supposed to go camping one
day earlier anyway and then with one
more day it would have
been really good
but
yeah things
happened uh what did you say I have the
sign cards uh and the Sparks thing is in
[Music]
there once again I'm putting in my
calendar a reminder to
pay the money I owe to
people I put so many like private things
into my calendar all my colleagues must
be like what is she
doing hey people money yes there was
actually one case
um um I I this is so like typically me
um Sometimes I Cry really easily in
stupid
situations um you know when I went for
that flying challenge
um I was going to
go and leave on the bus after I was done
and uh that like bus that I was going to
take if I didn't catch that bus I think
I would have to wait for a long time on
my way there I I was able to pay for the
ticket with my
card um and I had no no cash at the time
but yeah was it a or I had it but then I
I had some cash but then I was able to
pay with the card uh on the ticket on my
way to the challenge so I thought okay
so the way back will be fine and then I
used some of the cash for a little snack
there so I wouldn't have had enough cash
anymore for a ticket so anyway the bus
arrives uh and I'm like happy yay let's
get in and then I get in they say okay
until this point please and he says the
amount of money it takes and I'm like
okay with card please and he says no I'm
like he says
no and I see the card machine but it's
just not on like he's just like really
rudely saying no and there's some people
waiting behind me to also get into the
bus but there's honestly no rush
like but yeah his his his machine is
broken uh I guess or he's just he just
didn't turn it on I asked like can you
like really I have no cash though like
can
you are you can you did you try turning
it off and on again didn't say that but
yeah so he was like no no so no and then
I was like scrambling for my coins and I
was like well I don't have it he's like
well then go get money I'm like and then
in that moment I'm thinking well I won't
make it in time because the that I won't
make it in time no so I'm like kind of
like feeling like a little bit gut
wrenching and then I I I I leave I start
to leave the bus and then one grumpy
[\h__\h] behind me is like an Austrian
accent dialect it's like it's like well
I should have prepared better these
people unbelievable says something like
that like he's pissed off off because I
took a whole 60
seconds for this
conversation and then yeah and then I
snapped back normally I ignore I would
ignore that but I snapped back I was
like on the brink of Tears because of
that comment especially but I was like
um uh well normally the card machine
would work so excuse me it's not my
fault right and I walked away
I looked at him and said that and then I
walked away cuz that pissed me off that
comment pissed me off that's so
unnecessary
like excuse me for relying on something
that worked when I got
here whatever was
smoo yeah but saying that took me so
much courage that I was like uh like I
was not crying yet then I walk away from
the bus like in towards the direction of
the um I was going to walk towards the
direction of the ATM but then I saw the
paragliding I
said it's paraglide [\h__\h] uh I saw the
staff um uh still like sitting there um
and you know I got along really well
with them they're really helpful really
sweet so I walked there and they saw I
didn't make it they were aware that I
was going to get into that bus and then
I didn't make it and I walk over there
kind of defeat it trying not to cry
publicly I was just you know
I took me courage to say that okay and
then and then and then she's like oh
what's wrong and I'm like and this is
the moment where I kind of really fight
with the tears cuz is you know when you
when you not in in a good
um when you're like kind of sad and
you're not crying yet but then somebody
asks what's wrong and that really gets
you so I I was like really trying to not
break out the tears I was
like uh what did I say something like oh
I um I didn't have cash I didn't take my
my
card and then yeah she um gave me some
money for the bus which was so sweet
because I was saying like I uh like he's
going to drive away if I go get money
now
probably and she gave me some money and
she said oh don't worry just just PayPal
me okay just take this and PayPal me and
I'm like oh my God I thrw her so many
kisses cuz that she was so
sweet and then and I managed to still
get on the bus after everybody was
already in thankfully the bus was still
there um for a short amount of time so I
go in and I I look at the bus driver who
was really mean to me too like he didn't
look very nice at all he didn't try to
be nice at all and I'm
like well I didn't I didn't say anything
even I just said where I need to go and
that's it I gave him the money and I
walked in
yeah so anyway that's one thing I have
to pay
[Music]
back you would have called the driver up
on this [\h__\h] well I it's I it's just
like I thought like I don't go out
anymore this much so I don't know you
know things
[Music]
change back in the day of course they
didn't take cards so I always had cash
on me but but nowadays everything seems
to work with uh card pretty much and I
was delighted to see the bus that I uh
took also took card now so I thought oh
okay this is normal
now so I relied on it but of course some
are just not going to work and then
they're not going to bother with getting
it to work just like the McDonald's ice
cream machines
[Music]
yeah unfortunate
but thankfully the staff were there
still you know and saw me looking like I
was
crumbling yeah I did watch the video on
the McDonald's I like a really really
detailed one about some guy who thought
it was his mission to find out what's
wrong
[Music]
really yes
yes H saying the machine is broken start
up illegal they should have offered you
a free ride oh interesting point of view
but yeah not really going to happen in
real life
unfortunately I always keep a little
emergency cash it has helped me out
several times I just I used to also
carry cash with me always until like
maybe maybe until like 2 and 1 half
years ago when I left
Japan like in Japan because I didn't
have a card that could
like you
know pay I had a bank card but uh it
didn't have the feature to like pay like
that was just for deposits and so so
yeah and then when I went back to
Austria I was like yep okay um I don't
want to have cash all the time I'm just
going to pay everything with card
now it's way more convenient anyway I
don't want to like be at the
supermarket look like what this I really
I I really hate being somebody in the
supermarket at the register who makes
other people wait I'm like always so
prepared you know I have my bag already
I have a bag that I always bring and I
already like shape it open it shape it
in a way that it's easy to put things
in and then I already have a system of
what I put inside uh I know how to do it
right and and then I always pay quickly
with card now because taking out the
coins or whatever it just takes too long
I don't want people to wait because of
me and and especially not only the
people who come after me but also the
the the
cashier like they work really fast too
they're used to it they have a system so
I don't want to break their
[Music]
flow and then and then so often like I'm
like the next in line and then uh the
person before me like like like the
cashier would already start scanting my
items while the person before me is like
still scrambling to close their
wallet and then start packing in the
things into the
bag that's when you start what were you
doing all this time what what
[Music]
so and then my things get mixed in with
the things that the this other person
bought and I'm like I'm like wait I
don't want to you know make anybody wait
so I have to start packing but you're in
the way
hey so
yeah
that's something that bothers me so I I
try the P of card
now self checkout I use self checkout
sometimes that it's useful too yeah but
then they also break sometimes and do
weird things where I need help from the
staff also doesn't no no separation bu
yes but once like she takes it the
cashier will take it away obviously once
she she starts scanning the next item so
then they mix on the end of the of the
thingy of the tape counter
whatever cash is incredible I no I I
haven't made this experience in my daily
life except for that stupid
[Music]
bus the end of the thing we also have
separators too here oh really
I'm just trying to keep up with the pace
of the
[Music]
cashier thanks for stream oh byebye
thank you please come tomorrow very
important very important okay let me
continue reading this this fro candy is
intense ho
[Music]
[\h__\h] chocolate in so thank you for the
pinky congrats on the new album my
personal favorite is retrospective but
all the songs are great thank you man so
many retrospective
[Music]
fans I'm very
happy makes me also glad that we put so
much extra
time into coming up with a completely
new Melody
yeah it was very
picky does it help more for people to
buy album physically versus buying a
digital on player ah both helps in a
different
way physically buying it physically
definitely uh more money comes back to
me just because it costs more
also um but digitally it's just good for
uh proving our music department that
people listen to my
music and yeah to everybody I guess just
um get the word out
there yes yes so please feel free to get
both thank you so much for the support
so far everybody I got physical B and
streaming on Spotify thank you that's
the
ideal
support is there a a time limit on
getting it I can't just now yeah it was
1 month
so when did I release it end of August
right so you still have like I don't
know two weeks or
so or
three October 2nd oh wait okay there you
go that's then it's three weeks actually
actually still planning of
time I bought six copies oh my God thank
you CD digital and Spotify Oh you mean
you also got like iTunes or so thank
you three weeks
[Music]
why thank you yes please treasure it it
deserves it I want to treasure it too I
want to put it in a special
place I want to put it in like an extra
big
frame that's like 10 times the size of
it or make a shrine or so
for it's my first CD first first
physical release let's
[Music]
go um what was that Al
you so amazing K be so proud of you in
this incredible album you are truly the
embodiment of the Phoenix Burning
Brightly courageous and never giving
up thanks for being our boss # # y thank
you for being my
employee thank you you you guys are the
best I love you guys thank you so much
for your sweet words
Jesus very cheesy today aren't we or and
on that day very cheesy thank
[Music]
you you're amazing
too we are
amazing cat hairs on my
nose cat
hair where it goes
Jesus thank you m zero copy normalized
Phantom Jackson FB thank you for the
pinky first album is finally here
congrats thanel thank
[Music]
you thank you so much I'm so
glad we did it I did it it's out Yoo Yoo
all the work is
over Ana so Soul thank you for the
rainbow
ah
Ana I feel like I haven't seen you in a
while thank you hope you're enjoying my
music hope you're doing well
too thank you wordless rainbow so not
much I can say but thank you so much for
the
[Music]
generosity uh
py crus
King crad King bathman
D crus King D tyen thank you for the
pinky even after all these years Hony
had been my favorite for so long and I
still totally adore
it retrospective may have taken the
throne but I love the entirety of this
album yay that's great to hear it's
going to be loopy non-stop can't wait
for the physical copy yeah thank you I
wonder um they did say that it's going
to arrive earlier than you know Other M
normally
does so I'm counting on that
yeah thank you and when it arrives I
hope it arrives safely and I hope that
you keep it
safe seems like November really they
just say like they're trying to get it
out in
October well I mean I guess that's when
they will ship it maybe but then depends
how how long it takes to get to you guys
but uh yeah I don't know it wasn't like
100%
certain just a goal still earlier than
other merch the koala Universe tan happy
beled birthday CA King dangan Andre Dan
Elie La danan Dr danan Chad Dan py
Dan Moonlight thank you for the red
super
chat congratulations on the release of
your first album kiaha old classics and
new bangers join forces to make the most
based musical piece ever retrospective
my personal favorite from the newcomers
but I love them all thank you oh my god
what what what what's with you
guys all the retrospective chats what
crazy thank you L
Moonlight one more in the jar for
retrospective did you not expect this
no uh no
not really I mean I thought it would be
a nice surprise
but people love the angs yeah they do
they do don't
they yeah I wonder though if it's like
the instrumentals mostly or if it's the
lyrics mostly or if it's really the
whole combination
that convinced
everybody if the if the lyrics really
played a big
part both
[Music]
working in tandem all of the
above sleep talking closing in O Let's
go since you're singing you're so
powerful on it yo I was so passionate
when I was singing the chorus
[Music]
especially I told you before but I was
like gesturing
and like frowning like
[Music]
this Lily soon thank you oh oh o good to
know the great one one into the jar
jacket Jack what how do I write this
jacket Jack
Jack
jackary ja jary
ja jary jary
maybe thank you for the re of chat just
got off a rough day of work into an
amazing colal Party by our favorite
Phoenix thank you so much for turning my
day around and for your amazing music I
am like so sure that this must be your
first Super
Chat cuz I never like remember
struggling with your name before and
suddenly you're throwing that big ass
right Super Chat thank you so
much yay I'm really really happy that
you felt like you needed to support this
beautiful creation so aka me and the
album both beautiful Creations thank you
thank you thank you from the bottom of
my heart m and I hope I read your name
right otherwise we're going to try
again feel free to tell me next time if
you're dun space waterfall dun use Soda
thanks for the pinky oh my God W all
your new songs are so freaking amazing
especially like ttw and sleep talking by
the way sometimes I hear La instead of
loverush la la plus I feel it every
every day hold you tight and never let
go my la la la
[Music]
yeah yeah I guess I could hear
it but it's love Rush okay and then love
Buzz at some point maybe that one uh
sounds more like LA to you than love
rush love
buz can't unhear it oh
[Music]
no no
AR fried
screw bot thank you for the
chat more thanks for o a rainbow I think
this is the perfect moment to drop my
first rainbow ever oh as someone who was
in this amazing fast restaurant since
the first day oh this is a legendary
moment this feels like the first school
Festival in Kon and that's my favorite
anime episode ever I still remember I
was working in my house when you opened
your first K with blue
ah that was my opening really and since
then a lot of vegan chicken was served
in
kfp and even though I didn't see all of
them I enjoyed every second in this
restaurant you kfp mean a lot to me even
though I'm mostly a lurker you call
yourself a lurker really I feel like
you're around a
lot and I can't watch most of the
streams live anymore I still feel at
home every time I open a new tab and
that Melody starts playing a the fact
that I was born in the timeline that has
kfp with you as the owner is proof that
I am in the best one even if many times
it felt like it was the worst I am proud
jimin and wouldn't change you for the
world I know I wouldn't be the same
person if it wasn't for that Majestic
Phoenix to that is reading this so thank
you you're the best one would give me
love forever oh no is this the kind of
super jets I have to expect for for my
anniversary stream yeah
this is like way too early we're it's
not supposed to start yet L what are you
doing are you
anticipated I'll be reading this like
the day before my anniversary before I
get flooded with it oh
no really that was beautiful thank
you ah yeah wasn't our chicken like
didn't I claim it was vegan back in the
day oh man the lies I was so
so so fake I couldn't be honest with you
guys I'm so sorry for deceiving
you but I think we all knew what what it
really was liar
[Laughter]
troll no no no no baby no no no no don't
lie no no no no baby no no no no don't
cry what you going to do when it all
comes out that it was and vegan at all
no no no no baby no no no no don't cry
oh
lie stop stop stop stop stop
lying one of my favorite black a songs
yeah damn and times have
changed Isn't it nice that we've become
so close that we can be so honest with
each other huh so stop
crying stop blaming me
[Music]
stop blaming
me for the lies okay we had to get to a
certain Porn
[Music]
first I had chicken nuggets today by the
way recently I can't resist chicken
nuggets I eat chicken nuggets quite a
lot
recently thank you Lou black f n Broken
Man space waterfall D Smokey winds d d
space waterfall d
Jones
D Genie D Cruz d d Lincoln Abraham wow
Abraham
Lincoln is that how you ride Lincoln
with an L in
there she and
you I would have just written probably l
i n c o n
[Music]
huh what do you mean
her it's a guy I just Googled
[Music]
it
what oh it was just an non spamming star
her
so I saw your comment
twice you confused the [\h__\h] out of me I
saw two people riding uh star her like
like uh correcting
me I don't no no no no what are you
trying to
say God you made me think for a
moment that this is going to be really
embarrassing when I I am being told that
Abraham Lincoln is a woman
like what star was I living on until
now it just saying something dumb and
you typ but no worries no worries you
shook head for me to the
core anyway Lincoln Abraham says on his
red super chat this is my first Super
Chat on your channel I really like the
great Wanderer and retrospective I
always think your voice really matches
both EDM and Emo songs while there's
room for improvement I already bought
the album please keep trying this was a
good attempt good great job
well thank you I mean yeah there's
there's definitely you guys keep on
praising me but I do um there's
definitely Parts where I was hoping for
more time for improvement but
yeah thank you thank you Abraham Lincoln
I'm honored to receive such positive
feedback from you I will do my best to
uh rise up to your ranks in the future
if I'm not already
there thank you very much I do enjoy
singing both EDM and Emo songs in K too
so yeah I feel like it was
necessary thank you sp
water
[Music]
water7 I am a te D what's with the Roses
py dun RS Dan
Eric rad as an acapella singer I'm very
happy right now you're an Acappella
singer excuse me now I immediately have
to think about the Acappella singers in
Scrubs who are so cute they're so
cute they're so funny I love
them I love them me
too yeah T's man it's so cute are you
like that Eric nrom do you also wear a
suit and do a capella during your normal
job and dream of of you know singing
jingles and stuff for C uh uh
advertisements what did the actor
[Music]
die no don't say
that I want my baby back baby back baby
back baby back oh no was he that
old I don't think so Tad
scrubs Sam Lord he was so
great he had an actual music group the
blanks it was 3 years ago that he passed
away
[Music]
way how old did he get
1963 it's like 40 years and plus 20 is
like 60 oh that's that's
actually that's like a
decent amount of years to live I mean
should be longer but I mean
no could be but did he die how did he
die
oh how did he
[Music]
die oh he had a tumor a brain tumor oh
my
God which was Subs oh no it was
diagnosed and it was revealed to be
metastatic lung cancer what the
[\h__\h] that spread through his liver Spin
and
draw oh
god oh that's really really sad
he was so good he was so
good good man really good man at least
his acting was good I don't know about
his personality I guess but I feel like
if you see him in his scbs I feel
like you must assume that he's like just
as much as a great guy as Ted is in real
life spread out to too many other
systems and stuff oh my God what the
[\h__\h]
that's so bad so sad why are we talking
about this sad thing I'm so sorry I like
news to him I'm so sorry for tanging
into that thank you though for your
support a capella is so cool yeah I I I
mean who who
cannot say who who can't who's who
doesn't enjoy a little bit of a
pentatonics every now and then right
yeah if only
I wanted a capella group
too H thank you Eric Andre counting
chicken dun rpw n KT D Max the first D
metal squat d light D resine thank you
for rat let's go t the album was so good
pre-ordered my copy sleep talking was
probably my favorite uh uh on first
Liston oh really Y and it's definitely
my favorite after that Banger Acappella
M also show the friend and he called you
a menace for naming a song of the
pineapple what I don't agree with that
[Music]
uh okay sorry I I had to write something
uh to my mixer
Johnny and where was I yeah yeah no
there's nothing nothing menacing about a
pineapple you guys are just crazy gr are
just crazy dramatic thank you
rindo please keep on spreading love for
pineapple and if your friend has a
problem with it just bring him to me in
person and I will unpre him
[Music]
yes RP w n
KT I am
a eating M Ty's ass brand than pinky
thank you for putting the lyrics up for
the songs that helps more than no love
the album and love you kiaha thank you I
I do H I was thinking of doing that
every now and then um but it made the
most sense for the album k for sure and
I wanted you guys to take a good look
over the lyrics especially the the free
songs that are more focused on you know
my my my experiences
so yes you're welcome looking for the to
things for the pinky com on pov's
release love rush and tgw are my
favorites oh
every song is amazing and unique with
your concert performances Summer Song
horory
song you've been winning so much this
year give emot the hug she needs because
she deserves it
oh emot is me though how can I how can I
keep
hugs how that's just
me I don't have friends but my
girlfriend love po oh my God for real
good girlfriend good choice good
taste we will hug you we will we will
hug you hug
[Music]
you my body on yours let me give you a
squeeze I'm going to make you feel so
comfortable oh
[Music]
uh I could write lyrics
that yeah yeah I was thinking I I Was
preparing it in my
mind how did you know don't don't expose
me oh we could isn't smile on your face
the original lyrics
no smile on your
face and
face rhyme face
[Music]
rhyme meow
ma
ma days Days oh smile on your face leave
you in a days sorry for choking
you with
My Embrace oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God oh
that makes sense even you even I can't
talk
anymore smile on your face what did I
say what did I say
[Music]
then I leave you in a days sorry for
choking you with My Embrace we say I
will I will hug you hug you
I will I will hug
you let's go threatening
hugs I will love you while I'm
added TV table than lucky Prof soon
shadow Cross thank for the pinky thanks
for the C andrs on a fire fire fire
album T thank you oh my god call the
fire department we we thank you for
supporting my music I really really
appreciate it thanks for not ignoring
its existence and notor my existence I
love you thank
[Music]
you oh no don't put the pizza back no
no FAA thank you for the red love this
album so much especially that love fres
is my favorite I have a new dream I want
to be a pineapple
pineapple pineapple you want to be a
[Music]
pineapple I mean I get that feeling I
get that sentiment but you have to stay
a chicken you can put like a pineapple
hat on your head maybe good
armor it will protect you it's very
spiky too it has a good defense
mechanism and will keep your your head
juicy pineapples are sweet though a lot
of them can be sour though if yeah they
can be sour and sweet or
both one at a
time little straw
skirt oh that would be cute make him do
the hoola hoola
dance oh welcome Raiders hello I'm just
reading super chats now the panic and
the screaming is over thankfully for
now pineapple fruit hat cute anyway
thank you Fafa you're so sweet I'm glad
you like love rush I'm glad you guys
like love for us you know that one is my
love song to you guys after
all space wonderful than thanks for the
red chat like many others have said this
album is pure Excellence already ordered
a few copies and I plan to gift out some
everyone should have the pleasure of
listening to it amazing job again and
production team thank you
ooh several copies I wonder who you're
going to give it to do you already have
some people in
mind I hope I hope whoever you give it
to will be very receptive of
it made you tear off the first time oh
no
nice I do good thank you for doing that
thank you so much I I really appreciate
the
support that's that's so so so sweet so
helpful too thank you C
[Music]
wow B2 b50 mental J thank you for the
pinky what a great album I particularly
enjoy tgw and retrospective although I
think sleep talking felt like your
confident MH I'm I'm I'm like so happy
with sleep talking I love sweet sleep
sweet talking should we do some sweet
talking yeah for your information I'm
going to be missing streams for the rest
of the year
huh like every
stream I'm going on sabatical and
traveling across East Asia including
Korea Japan and others for 4 months the
rest of the year that sounds like so
much but four months doesn't sound like
so
much does that mean you're not here now
rental J
[Music]
how am I going to how I'm going to find
Enlightenment as a jetty now though
without you
[Music]
here I don't see
him but uh sabatical isn't that like you
know having time off of work why don't
why why don't you have time to watch my
streams then
I mean you don't have to watch them all
the time but a little bit I'll be
playing the album lots and we'll catch
videos when I can okay there we go
that's what I needed to
know and I will see you around Christmas
when I'm back assuming I don't get eaten
by a bear or something oh well I don't
think those countries are really famous
for bear eating
incidents love wow love give me thank
you mental J oh I wonder if you'll catch
this one this message from me to you but
good luck good have fun I wonder if you
speak the language of any of these
places but uh especially Japan is a bit
rough without Japanese but I wish you
the best of luck and and yeah make the
most of it have
fun and I think you're choosing a good
time because
now uh yeah summer is ending so the
temperature won't be as bad as in like
June July
August I hate Japan and Korea in June
July
August absolute worst absolute worst
thing September 2
honestly yeah I feel like yeah September
is still definitely very
[Music]
bad yeah
for
[Music]
no some Japanese BR said oh what it's
getting better recently Li Li Li Li Li
[Music]
Li why I just wow
I just uh uh cracked my hip
[Music]
bones yeah that that whole area probably
like even also Indonesia like oh my God
just just go away all those humid
countries no no no no
no no no
no hip replacement for Grandma hey hey
hey hey nothing to do with that I've
been cracking my hip for years now okay
and and and
well it means
nothing anyway thank you mental
J
strike
D thank you for the pinky congrat on
release the great wand were hit hard
from the getg go but it's a tad too
early to pick favores oh what about now
what about now what about now what the
others grow on you real fast too amazing
variety and full of Baggers super high
quality wow proud of you thank
you thank
you I I
I I'm glad you guys like it so much I
feel like I could have still done more
yeah yeah yeah I wish I could have added
a few more new songs
too
but there's some reasons why I didn't do
that
[Music]
some almost misunderstandings but more
like Mis
miscommunication
uh of of what the how the budget and all
that works um so I thought I couldn't
like do it like financially like not
really
feasible in hindsight I was told like
during the production you know that
things are different from how they
seemed to be and I'm like e if I would
have known that since the beginning that
things would have probably been planned
[Music]
differently yeah complicated but can't
get into it but you know so yeah I just
had to go with how things were planned
at that point and so yeah it's fine
though in total we have 10 songs
by uh questioning the album with my
previously released Songs which I think
a lot of people do anyway like artists
yeah they really singles and then they
put them into the album anyway so any
end it's just what what what the what
people do so I can do it
too knowledge for second album
exactly
and yeah I feel like they also deserve
their place on the album I I I think
it's nice
to have a collection especially cuz they
didn't get a physical release and this
way they're also getting a physical
release and and you know now I have
everything on one CD all of my songs
this is
like the CD is like you know such a big
chunk of my work in whole life so far
and yeah it just like puts
Asam sums up everything assembl
everything it's
like
yeah big piece of me
[Music]
the Holy Grail
yeah it's all in there all my passion
all my work all my all my
[Music]
time so yeah thank you unknown thank you
for Wow Wow Wow basically Two Reds thank
you congrats on your first album d still
I knew it's going to be good because
it's from you but I still managed it
still managed to blow me blow me away
with how awesome all the songs are
everything about this album is
absolutely incredible words can't even
express how much I love it I've been
listening to it non-stop since release
and I don't think I can never stop a
they're just too good you seriously did
such an incredible job I'm extremely
proud of you k you're so [\h__\h] amazing
you really are the
best stop my favorite right now A
retrospective and love brush
oh I see well I feel like I understand
why you like love rushing but I can't be
sure just yet because they're all to
amazing I'll need to listen to all of
them for never a million times each to
make sure Stream Point of VI forever
thank you you're so
sweet 5 years
later they say unknown is still
listening to my album to this day on
repeat thank you for all the love
unknown always always
always unconditionally supporting me no
matter what I love you thank you m m
m sounds
accurate yeah you're the best Nathan
Clon thanks for the pinky sorry I'm late
T tono
could this jimin request an encore
edition of his new favorite song
rospective
you little
[\h__\h] you got me started with all those
Anor but in the end like
um it's like I wanted to sing everything
over and over again anyway
so you helped us all relieve our
urges I finished watching the Vault by
now oh the archive one of the of the col
okay by
now you're so late Nathan what are you
doing all
day thank you though for catching
up and thank you for supporting my
album Haku Haku thank you for the pinky
as well thank you for K singing T I like
all songs and albums so much so I buy
free albums for promoting
you totally deserve it thank you you did
are you going to give them away too keep
one for yourself of course no and if you
give it those other two away Choose
Wisely there's a strange ribbon appear
pairing of my
what strange rib strange
R train
ribon if you look if I look
[Laughter]
oh I see
[Music]
[Laughter]
it I don't know what the [\h__\h] wait
that's so
weird I never
noticed how could I have been there for
like 2 years
oh thank you
H ma 496 thank you for the red
[Music]
[Laughter]
stop I have tears in my
[Music]
eyes I can begin to describe how happy
it makes me that I got to be here when
your first album was released kada as a
new remember there are times that I
regret not to discovering you sooner me
too I regret his spaghetti that too Mac
are you here Mac Mac Mac MACC MACC
[Music]
MACC
no I don't see
[Music]
Mac where are you
I want a letter with the explanation on
my table by tomorrow 300
p.m. kaha Standard
time anyway and that being said thank
you for the bottom of my head for the
smiles you bring thank you too thank you
thank you thank you it doesn't matter
that you discovered me too late um you
know we always need some some new people
and you're part of that that's very
important
for my
growth if my if there's no new people
joining then you know it's like really
sad thing so thank you for finding me
finally and you know what it doesn't
matter cuz the Bots are all up there uh
I don't think there's much besides like
unarchived
KZ that you wouldn't be able to find if
you didn't if you wouldn't if you would
if you yeah you know so yeah it's all
there it's all there start like how I
started when I discovered p standby go
to the very bottom of the archives and
then work your your way back up although
I'm very embarrassed about my older
streams so maybe don't maybe start from
the top and work yourself your way down
from newest to oldest actually in my
case and then when You' notied that um
I'm getting worse then
stop oh yeah and I do have a zero
commitment playlist which I think is
genius I sometimes forget about it
though
[Music]
start in the middle but which way do you
go both ways at the same time maybe one
old one one new one one old one one new
one one old one one new one that's a
weird
strategy thank you Max
M PR
song Looking for the top Wun
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] rain D J monkey d w d Cru
D Sky thanks for the pinky some Recovery
Fund for the shitty DHL isue love you
new album Dream PV thank you [\h__\h] D [\h__\h]
him [\h__\h] [\h__\h] F [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you thank you very very much
[Music]
I hate you so much you're so stupid stop
scaming me
[Music]
already yeah what's going wrong there I
will never understand what is going
wrong there but yeah thank you Sky Hi hi
hi
the my financial advisor has advised me
he was so shocked and he was like takasi
kiaha do you have any insurances and I'm
like no I only have a health
insurance he was like
H not even like a like a dis insurance
and this insurance I'm like no no
nothing and now now now he said I should
get like free basic ones I'm like
H why are you going to do that for me
and he's like yeah
okay if you do it then I guess
whatever and yeah and one of them is
going to be like an insurance it's
[Music]
called and then he said that if that DHL
[\h__\h] happens to me again I can give that
to them and then they will take care of
it next time it
happens and they will take care of that
I don't have to take care of that so
come at me bro come at me DHL if you
want me if you want my money well then
you have to go for my lawyer then okay
next time you're going to look over this
case probably cuz I I don't have time to
deal with it look over it but the next
time next
time no more of that [\h__\h] not a third
time there will not be a third time
mhm you snapped in half oh my God then
you need half insurance
Evans L what you need is health
insurance now for your
[Music]
tongue go get him get him let's get him
let's get
[Music]
him and then you know while he was
talking about
insurances in my brain the only thing
that I had you know was from my recent
True Crime
Adventures um
you know the all the videos that I've
seen so far uh there's like many many
cases
where a couple or so will have a life
insurance like like for example like
somebody will be married to a rich
person and then that that somebody will
make their partner get a life insurance
and then they end up killing them for a
life insurance it's always like
calculated and you know never trust
somebody who wants you to get yourself a
life
insurance oh my God God like so many
times it's a death
flag so many times it's the Strat and I
told him I I said okay whatever if you
think these are necessary that's fine
the only insurance that you can't get me
to get is the life insurance because I
know that somebody will kill me if I get
myself a life insurance and then he was
like really confused and I had to
explain him and I went on a whole
tangent about true crime and and a
specific case especially u i just like
took it as an example and I went on a
rant and I told I I I I was you know of
course like half joking but I'm but at
the same time pretty serious I'm like no
you can't get me he's like yeah yeah no
worries you don't need it at the moment
but
yeah and I'm like yeah yeah I don't want
it I don't even if I need it someday I
don't want it because somebody will kill
me somebody will murder me over my life
[Music]
insurance yeah just don't tell anybody
you get it yeah yeah I guess so but no I
don't I don't think I don't know I don't
I don't want it no no no no no no no no
no no no no you know how many people get
killed over life insurances and of
course then it never never ends up good
for them either in the end so was it is
it worth it is it [\h__\h] worth it I
don't think so you're going to get
caught but at what
[Music]
cost yeah
so that was this one case especially
that I just watched very
recently somebody like really really
targeted this one lady who was doing
really well in life like she was working
her way up on her own she was doing so
well and then and then this guy comes
into her life and within two months like
they start dating and within two months
of
dating he proposes to
her yeah and she's like well okay that's
kind of fast but okay I guess cuz my
family is pressuring me anyway to marry
so H and then they marry and then and
then and then soon after that you know
still fresh married they go to National
Park and he says let's get off of the
trail the hiking trail let's go this way
cuz there's something special I going to
show you and then he says stand here
very close to the edge of the cliff I
love you so
much and I'll take a picture of you and
there's something special there and if
you go there you'll see something
special and then he pushes her off and
she was pregnant and he pushes her off a
cliff that's like 11 11 uh uh floors
High pretty much and she broke like
pretty much every body uh every B bone
in her body um yeah she survived though
because of the trees that caught her but
he stayed there like she wasn't moving
right she was like like she was looking
at when he was staying up there for like
half an hour looking down checking if
she doesn't move just to make sure she's
really really dead and then he walks
away after half an hour uh and then and
then oh my God she would have probably
died there if nobody would have found
her cuz it's off Trail too and some
other guy who was like uh uh also lost
like a tourist who was lost who wasn't
on the trail he find
her thank God and then gets help and
then the guy who pushed her down he's
like on the way outside of the uh he's
like leaving the national park with his
car and then he sees from the other
side the ambulance is coming through and
then he's like
oh yeah I watched that from rotten
mangoes too me too and he turns back and
like he follows he follows the ambulance
and all that into the hospital and he's
like oh oh yeah I I lost her and uh you
know and this this whole time he stays
like 24/7 he stays in the room with her
to make sure that she doesn't say
anything every time a staff is like in
the
room uh like a nurse or so he'll be like
the nicest sweetest guy ever have a big
smile on his face and once they leave
and they're alone he he looks he looks
at her like like in a really threatening
way like
this yeah and she was so scared to say
anything she still remembered but she
was so scared to say and anything and
then you know eventually of course she
did and then you know yeah psychopath
absolute psychopath but aiming for her
you know wealth and all
that did the baby survive uh probably
[Music]
not I mean how could it how could it
have survived right but I feel like I
remember some point some point in the
story it said that it died later or so
but
yeah
yeah says more about marriage and life
insurance huh well can she function
she's like um rehabit alizing and um
learning how to walk like she has to do
all these like exercises daily in order
to be able to walk but she's like back
on track like she actually incredible
like she's she's back to being
successful
[Music]
businesswoman yeah and apparently
doesn't even feel like negatively about
marriage or anything like that didn't
influence her in that way but yeah it's
crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy story man
there's so many of those I'm so deep in
the True Crime Rabbit Hole save
me I can't return from death that rabbit
[Music]
hole
oh
[Music]
choices okay my True Detective
apparently a lot of women love True
Crime why I wonder but yeah that's
like can we get a neck crackers crackers
crackers status update uh I don't know
it's I'm still doing
it but maybe maybe it's gotten a little
bit less I'm not sure hard to
[Music]
tell there's some days where I don't
have as much pain maybe I'm not sure and
then days where I'm back to really big
big
pain it's so hard to tell if there's a
clear change from what I've been doing
recently I want to say yes but I don't
really
know anyway we have to finish these
super chats I'm so close M thank you for
the
pinkies two of them hey D all of the
songs are great though I'm split between
the great wand and retrospective hon and
us can SP party plus the album KY has
been winning these past days though on
the topic of creating tangents for Super
Chat no I already tangent it I just came
back from it did you see n's tweet about
wanting to go overseas I don't think so
speaking of how about how about that
vacation you wanted to take or the one
you wanted to do with the one of the
other girls anniversary plans going well
hope you're feeling good and sleeping
well the the the the trip
um I a trip like I ended up not having
really time for
it and looking forward uh I don't think
I will have before the summer ends and
it was supposed to be like a Beach
vacation so hm I probably will have to
wait until the
actual like next big trip like the
another one I'm planning
in in like maybe no end of November or
so I think
maybe um
yeah uh but for now like no time cuz now
next I'm going to Japan a little
bit for
um two things yeah the a
certain a certain appearance of me
somewhere and
and uh a wedding
so that's taking up some
[Music]
time but yeah yeah um it's okay I you
know there was this time when I started
talking about really really wanting to
go to one more trip that's I felt like
really really burnt out I think this was
when was this
after after the second Japan
trip and even more than after London
maybe but I felt
like I don't know if it was burnt out
but like so incredibly mentally and
physically exhausted I was like [\h__\h]
this I can't take it anymore I need to
get out of
here and but then I couldn't get out of
here immediately I had to work on the
album and this that so I went back into
work and my urge to get the [\h__\h] out of
here has calmed down a little bit so I'm
okay for now I I mean I still have
moments that get very close to that
emotion again but I I
I push it back further inside and push
it and push it stuffing it back inside
I'm I'm saying like no no no not now I
don't have the time
anyway I need to do this and this and
this and that and this and that
so yeah that's the trip and what what
are you saying that's literally what I
was just talking about so that's not
happening but the other trip that I
don't know if I mentioned before the
real the other real trip that one that
one will happen we haven't really uh
ironed out the details but it will
happen one day you're just going to
explode exactly I will I will I will I
will I will I will I will I
will let's go explod
[Music]
CH no
M wait the differ yeah there there's two
different trips there's one that I
wanted to do
now like now actually in August I
think uh and then there's one in like
end of November that one is still
happening the other
[Music]
one yeah no time sadly it's okay though
as I said I was able to hold back the
feeling the spot with my sister I don't
have time for
that turns out I don't have time for
that either H yeah but it's okay my
sister is doing a lot of stuff I've
heard uh like going on vacations and
stuff on her own uh on her side so um
probably not really possible to invite
her to anything anyway I don't know it's
okay anyway thank you
muching
Captain
skon Dominic k d Captain Jer D and EV
thank you for the wordless pink Super
[Music]
Chat I did it wow even timed with the
music
[Music]
okay I'm going to go now cuz I got to
prep [\h__\h] oh my God byebye andj see you
tomorrow be there or nothing you have to
be there there's no other
[Music]
option this please thank you byebye