[Music]
N
Eh
[Music]
nice
def
N
el N
[Music]
Masu
b 4
[Music]
Good, good, good, good
th
tue
N
[Music]
Masu
panacea
ere
room episode 3 is 6 minutes
dancer before popo 2 wifi espn cointy
chime icu jic yoahawaa
Guuuu demeure Aqua Nuu Karmin today
please US Space Spain ran A big boo Patty
These birds called virus on the fingers On joy and martial spa monk-like
plate armor only
[Music]
robbem sports pie t Advice
Eye Mei Choosing even the weakest fish  dakata packer
yogatte
soraad
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
to the the charles arukitai toilet liquid beijing michouekipona round rice to
Io-poi is standing up
we love a san
Modulo Sweets Day is a book about Mrs. Fake Girl I
knitted the office type Inare
ender ender ender Huawei besar ah
Tomizawa Utsuke-san beauty club is Europe
and America a Ibira 4th edition  No, it's
amazing to see Minami Oi Tokuryuu for the first time.The
current production 1000 yen series has many coins and is as good as event participants
.  4 Mother-in-law has a rap voice that sounds like Pins Swada Dion is in it
Gyaaaa scary Ernie This is called Star
This is Chal's
nitr fb Half's main caster
Tiller Quiz when choosing power Kazushi Hospital 4 Pinphone meets day loop
position in the boy Nope
meme  Hey, ah,
badge, aruzuni, arb legend, bride bus, this in future,
hamaha
andere stream, ah,
support our hospital, ah, kyuring deren  1 d render Harukaze
Tour Way Sound It's so good that you did it earlier f 4
In the afternoon, it's annoying right in front of me The
end stopper and the like by After the defeat, s Haneeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
1 daddy
Iker
1st away and Marine Cup round stamping piggyback interview
Ore ni Soccer Poyo
[Music]
noar barbora nebu sro osterman irex moose
Sumter
Ibo Speedy espana
What's your convenience line
nu do the roastery Department
Surfer nearer n with baby pain 5 en do do This is the
Vienna bag owner bye way
[Music] Do
n't cry because it's so hard Winston Pin, yo,
yayo.  worth Weiser Mini Bar Champ Blythe 3 base nonde
nof Pressure Peking ga-eh
Umm-san 4 Oxygen almost sulfur  I
had to meet Lapis in the space ---
Soya Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Perfei-san Booty Boo Interview Don't
look at the avatar, it's amazing web Keio Good luck
[Music]
aname
me
[Music]
kakeroma  is a non-bar 2-top tarp a can only see
ad spanish win veil special episode 4 part tea is also
good
zainfra ward nibara zakan do s admission
opusar car voodoo in f chan feeding
main duwives south raiders tips book s well that's it  Eunsu
over sea view Let's have a party with Espers by Ahana Shikyu
Aa
Micro Tokuwane Interview talk show for English-speaking countries  The
purpose of this is basically to
let people overseas know more about Japanese talent, although I usually don't have much time to spare.I'll
be using Takanashi Hosono's character to send this to you.But
today, as you can see,  That's different a building 1 day i herb ace place
aev in to surf + meer please user generated nas
ah
turf owner infant it's winter wing
about this program boobie prize winner ws esrb
sweets book spy woo sas  oms day
diffuser yarn and store
4 rice option berth with pone king kind good gen
gaff example ai it's a guy
tr 2 what's the lighting Misawa-san
ana redtop insider in sin 4
arm adjon and system ads carrying the last work in okoji
9 good child case  Fire sea water sleep skin room old corner
Booncam selection day dyed 9 shoulder de posh berry berry happy line
pipe voodoo  Vista Rosono Chance Turn Signal with Day Chin
Di Ke Earth Kao Gessner
Tone Brass 2 Sensor Mr. Tomizawa
I would like you to introduce yourself. Thank you. I
Thank you very much.
Then I will introduce myself. Web version Money Miss  Yusuke Tomizawa
Hon Bandai Namco Aru Saab
Terror the lies brand new title of truth ops
franchise
resin stand english use
wear for please stream
tte2
go  japanese I
didn't say anything, thank you very much. It's so nice to meet you. It was an island tour that didn't speak English. I was surprised. It
's not like that at all. Back in the day, we used to
go to America and stuff like that.  I
talked about it at anime expos like E3 and I study English hard,
but
since I don't go there anymore, it's been a while since I've spoken English.  I don't
know how far it will go, I think it's amazing, but it looks like I'll be able to go, but it's sunny in Japan today. Are you
sure? By the way, 8 is 6 for everyone. I
think it would be better to have someone explain that to me, but the visa is fine.
Which producer did the color based on that work?
Yes, that's right.
3 was Tail Dowat 5 years ago 6 years ago
anon Beth's previous work 8 Berseria
After this was released, the team here This is produced by myself  title  This
will be my first time with Tales, so in fact, this time's Tale Aleph is quite complete.As a
new work, I'm pro
Deuce for the first time, so I guess you could say it's the same as that
one.  It
's completely unrelated, but what is Misawa-san and I's favorite Terufuwa
series? Is it the Hard Registry series? Well,
when it comes to works that I'm passionate about, Vesperia is the one I'm most fond of.
Well, I liked it so much that I even released a remaster of Tales
of Hearts, but the ED version of Tales of Hearts
is expensive, so I'm playing that now.  My mom and I used to work at Bandai Namco,
so my senior was producing
this new work and the way he did his hair
[Music]
Booby, it's funny.
In that city, that killer talks about the town, but well,
maybe his head is too big, but his favorite works of that Piara are
Thees Onbu Xillia City and Unicolor.  It
's amazing because it's the first one that I did, and it's amazing because it's a work that I have a lot of feelings for.Introduction to Tomishunho I think I have to mention the name.Also,
Bersemi Ako, I
loved Berse Reasona,
thank you very much, yes,
yes.  shinhwa After all, I
think it's a title that many users have played for the first time, especially in World, so I'm sure a lot of people will
raise it as the top of their My First mountain.
Not only that, but it's my first JR
Pitty,
and it's over.Hmm, I see, what kind of voice is that, what kind of game?It's such a
power.  I
couldn't figure it out, but I fell in love with his charm so much that I
became a big fan of Teru-kami. Thank you very much. I
can truly ask such a character to be the star of Sono Anpa in the West.  When I heard that, I thought it was very reassuring for us.
[Music]
I'm watching all of those secret streams.
Feel 2's tease-related stuff. Well,
that's not right. Kiara finished selling Nekouya.  It's a lot of pressure, isn't it?  I
think we'll be able to hear some really interesting stories around summer, so I'm
leaving.I'd
like to get into the 6 question section.I'm a
user who is watching this program right now.  I don't know.
I'm sure there are some people who don't know much about it yet, so could you please explain the basics of refrigerated soybeans and
let me know a little bit? Okay, I
'm Arthur. That's
right.
From September 9th of this year, 2021.  Well, I guess so  This is the
latest installment in the Felzorb Booth series, which is an action RPG series that will be
released worldwide at the same time.The Tales of
That Girl series actually started in 1995, and it's
already celebrated its 25th anniversary in Japan.  I
'm grateful to Series 2, which has a long history,
but in the past few years, there have been a lot of opportunities for people outside of Japan to play Neoku, especially in the past few years.
In fact, we are aware of the fact that there are many passionate fans overseas as well, and
Tales Bar Rise is the first title in the series to be
released at the same time all over the world.  The
third thing is that the translation is in 12 languages, so I'm going to
follow up with the subtitle, and I'm aiming for a March Patty that will really get more people from all over the world to join me and get excited.A Currently in
development and production.  a It's a
work of art.
Well, the basic part of the worldview has already been released in the PV, and it
's a fantasy world with two stars, Ten and Reina, and Kono is
set in a world where the two stars are what they want.  It
's a fantasy RPG where the drama unfolds in a magnificent world.
Thank you very much. I'm really looking forward to it.  I've been
waiting so long for the new work, Nobateru, so it's really new.Even though it's called the 5th anniversary,
I actually had cancer one time ago.It's been
5 years since I've had a baby called Luceria, so it's been 5 years since I've had a baby.
Before Brunei-kun's Ligand, I also did Celia who dives, and it was so much fun that I can't wait to see if
Nakama will be even more talented than usual in the next work.  I'd
like to talk a lot about the influence of that. I'd
like to move on to the next question. Let's start
with the first question.
What was the reason?
This time, in Arise, we evolved the art style a little bit.As you
said, we are developing a new shader called Atmos shader this time.  Not
only does the warmth in that picture make it look a bit more realistic, but the characters in the foreground
also have a slightly more realistic feel.Ah, that's
true.In
addition, Mura-
chi, the effect of the light scales is a little more pronounced.  It
also incorporates that photorealistic style, so we're taking on the challenge of creating a very hybrid expression
this time.It's
called Sociedad,
after all.
Tales of is a good thing, and that's why I'm uploading the loops that I put on Superior, and I'm
getting a lot of totals from people who have this kind of hobby, but
this Araisu is, of course, that.  I sometimes think about it as an extension, but I
think it makes sense that it's a title that commemorates the 25th anniversary of a well-known brand, and that it's a game that aims to become a high-end flagship in a sense.
Even if we were just going to push the legs to the limit, we didn't want to
project a level of difference from other works, and we
had a very strong desire to once again update the Rails of character.  As I was having a little discussion with the development art team and the art directors, I
thought about whether or not I could create a new expression using various types of incense,
and I regretted it a little.  I'm
expressing a new way of living.A
warm and immediate answer.  I
've tried various things to come up with such a realization, and the result is something like
this one, which I named "The Kyogen Mart is also to blame".
Well, by the time it was completed, I had been developing it for about four years,
getting to know each booth sushi well, and
taking every photo I could to get it to triple its current size.
Of course, it didn't take that long, but even during that long development period, we
continued to evolve, and even the claws
were able to be seen in this way by the station, which is what I'm expressing this time, isn't it?  I'm wondering
what your impressions were.Although I've
seen everyone react positively to the new expressions, some people
seem to like the shades.
We are also very curious about your opinions on our new challenge. I
see. Thank you very much. I
think it's very refreshing and good. I was surprised,
but in the end I didn't feel any discomfort.  I thought it was very beautiful. I
think it's the shape.
8 Then Teru Saba Rise, how does it sound different compared to other incremental games?
Also, was there anything new that was added?
uwpa  Well, in terms of differences, there are many, but
this time,
there is a theme that we have set for the Arise Development Department.
Those are the two keywords of Gaha's inheritance and evolution.
[Music]
This is not to say that we are trying to return to everything from the so-called series up until now, but
rather to reconsider the uniqueness of Tales that should be inherited.
Well, don't say that I said in the polite column that things that change and things that evolve, because we
take that kind of development approach, there are special differences in the details, and I
think it's easy to understand.  For some reason I feel that feeling, and
what I've done is definitely the same as what the Tales of series
has offered to everyone up until now.
That's the change in appearance, and the
tuning after the top frame day of the 8th specification game design, well,
this time's Araizu has been hit with several radical modifications,
so
one of the things is that it's difficult to do this.
Well, I wanted to evolve the battle system in a very positive way,
so I
tried things like strengthening the human village system.  I'm here  The other thing that has
just been announced is the skit system.
This was also the day when we evolved the visual expression
to a 3D base, so this is
also a challenge in a sense, but well, it's still different from what we've seen up
until now.  I believe that the new expressions and ways of feeling that were not possible in the series will be able to
bring happiness to all of you, so I
hope that I will write about it again.
As far as I can see, it's still that great.  I'm
relieved that the original character is still there.The
theme is ``Fantas'', but if you say that it doesn't really have a unique character, you'll
be betraying the fans you care about most,
so...  We need to be very careful about this, not only
in the production of the game itself, but also in communication with everyone.If we do
n't avoid mistakes, we may
end up conveying things in a way that doesn't seem like it's really cold.  I
think that's possible, and I'd like to be very thorough about that since it's not even released yet.Thank
you Adol Narou8.For the next question, let's talk a little bit
about that character.  I have something I want to do, but I think Blythe is the
same as the other members of the Increased Group, and I
think it's a great story to say about the number one in the group.  Could you please
explain how it will work?
Okay, so when you think of Zorb on the day, it's the character of the party. I
think everyone is right about this, so if you take it personally, the
dynamics are
beyond me.  I think there are two parts to this, and one is
how to express the relationships between the characters
in an attractive way within the rustic story, or worldview, and setting.
Characteristics of a 36-person party as a Parry PG
For example, when it comes to battles, I think these two are the most important parts:
how fun it is to have a party of 6 people, and how fun it is to have a party of 6 people, and the fact that
Maru offers a lot of variety in
gameplay.  The position of this party in terms of the worldview is
very high, and the worldview is a little bit strange this time.The
two big stars of the shop trainer
are the shops.
Since a certain point, it's like being enslaved and being dominated.It's
made up of that station.Currently,
Patty has two races of dumb trainers, so
it's a party with a mixed voice, so it's not necessarily the first time.  The second point is that we're not a friendly group,
and it looks like we're going to have
that gold car or something,
but I don't know if there will be any fights.  In
this world, it's true that there's no way for a shopkeeper and Rena to get along,
so when you come to a place like this and have to check the convenience level, it's
hard to get to know each other right away.  Satoka: I
guess that's the way it is in a sense, in the early days, because you have experience with the private sector, and by the end of the journey, you'll be able to form a deeper bond with them.  express the world in the first place  I
think the players will be able to follow the party while playing the 6, which expresses the state of the world, so it's easy to understand Izumi I
would definitely like to see party growth with that dynamism.  I hope you'll look forward to it,
and I'm sure
you'll be looking forward to another aspect of the battle, and I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy the party as well.I'm
really looking forward to it.This time around, we've really
strengthened the characteristics of that action game, so I hope that this blue
character will be able to make a splash.  -Not just for promotion  I
hope all 6 of you can actually play the game and enjoy the feel of it.I
want to tell you a word about this, but I wonder if
that group is doing it.  I
think it can be said that the relationship is fixed.I understand that it
means "home".This
is Japanese, but it is
often used in Orekiru live performances, but I don't
think it can be understood without understanding.Hmm.  That's right. The
court is closed.  I don't know
what to call it, but the
ideas I've come up with are
j. Looking at all these people, I feel like it's a
good idea.I saved them from eggs.Ah, I saved them from being good friends.The
rest are from the top.  It would be nice to finish it. I see. It's
far away, but it's good with rice.
Now that I've taught you that live slang for digging, I
thought it should be thin. pt.
Take the cat with you.
The relationship between the character Blue Sea and the character Blue Sea may be a little sleepy at times.Nichiei
Abarise also looks like an open world game.I'm
also interested in the story structure.  However, there are a
lot of military flags, and I'm really
curious as to which direction the management will go in, since it's a one-way road that ties itself back to itself.If you
don't mind, please let me know.This
looks like a world now.  So from now on, I'm going to do it this time.That's
right.  The
visual look of the world has evolved quite a bit, so I get a lot of feedback that it looks that way.  It
's a type of game.
However, it's
not a game that has no detours at all, as people would say, and
there are sub-quests in Duck Village scattered all over the world.  There
are a lot of discoveries that can be made by taking a detour to such an unexpected place, and although it's not as surprising as the previous Tales of series, there
is a wide range of characters and their adventures.  I
think that's what's being created.I
think it's because the characters are able to jump or swim across the field, and there are
quite a lot of actions that make it look a bit like an open world.  become  That's
why this time, I really feel like I'm immersing myself
in this world by having the player control the character, and it's a
very different feeling from the previous versions of Shape, and I feel like I'm the
real person.  As for the experience, I
think people will enjoy it, so I think we'd like to push that a little bit further.That's why it's not
important to have a co-op mode, but to let the player control the character
freely and do things like that.  It seems that the
characters can feel as if they are really alive,
so I believe that it has been strengthened and sold as a school.I
see, the amplifier is not an open world startup Okihara.  I especially
felt that way when there was that dog star player, and the
world just felt so vast.
Well, that's true, but the reality of the test play is that it's not that big, but of
course it's not the same as the world.  Meal Report
Prefectural Road One day, strangely interspersed,
there are no fields, so of
course you can feel that sense of openness that you felt there, and there
are many fields like that.  In reality, we are connecting and fishing the world,
and once you enter the field, you will only be able to go to it once.In
fact, there is no such thing, there is a sub-quest about Joker and something like that here
till  The
field that you have once dropped into is still worth visiting, and there
may be something like that charm inside, so I think that the sense of traveling in that wide world has
been strengthened again.  I think
so. I'll wait.
Thank you. By the way, Tsunami and
Chiara, as well as the viewers, are
really interested in the character called Pet wo Hibisa Dasa. Well, they have similar names.
But regardless of that, I'm going to wear it again.It's
cool and I'm seriously in love with it.Please
tell me more about your personality and battle side.I'm
also proud of you.  Well, there's no doubt that she's a cool woman,
but
what part in particular caught my attention? Is
that the equipment? She has proper equipment that makes her look really strong.  It
's a big shield, isn't it? It's expensive for those times.  I do
n't think you'll see many characters using it as a weapon in other games, so
using a shield as a weapon is really good in
each case.
[Laughs] It's a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of.  mosquito  I have an
image of a strong woman, including the ability to be inclusive.I
want to praise Itaro's character, and I
work in design and engineering,
but the tops are the same.  As you can see from my first impression,
it's that woman, but she's not only fully equipped,
but she's also wearing armor.  I
mentioned that there is one.  There
are seven people in other states, but they are members of Lena's
pedal regular army, or rather, this AK, uh,
squad from the beginning, so they
meet the main characters in a somewhat unique position.  Well, that's true. Is it because
Buber
has taken the equipment and was given to him by the Southern God? Or
maybe he's learning using magic technology. That's how it
's set up, so that
big guy is actually that one.  I don't know
what it is, it's not a spell, but it can disappear and appear with a single stone.
Something that big
can also happen, so after all, she herself is Danajin.
Although she doesn't change May, she
indirectly uses that equipment.
As a result, he is now able to use not only physical techniques, but
also special techniques and skills.  I
think she's a pretty cool character, but what
do you like and dislike about Anu from Okiza-san?
Monocare 8 I mean she's herself, but I
'm sure Bano. Someone just announced this, but I
love Kisara.  As a book, it's a good idea.I
watched some videos of people fishing and
air fishing.That's right,
that SNS said it was a snack.I
included it, but I
love fishing so much
There's a looping motion called a standby motion when the player doesn't touch the controller, but of
course each character has something unique about them.  It
reminded me of the time when I was making golf bread, and I
wondered if Mr. Mixer would be okay.I do
n't think there are many people who cast an entire school in a fantasy world.But,
let's talk about what happens next.  Or rather
For her, she says that she
went on a lot of fishing trips during her childhood as an immigrant, and
there is a scene in the movie where she talks about how good she was at fishing.
For a little while, the boob is in a hurry for 4 shots, but Polarize's fuel is called a serve quest,
or rather, as one of the activities, I'm going to play it.It's
not just a hot sound, but it's also possible to get a real distance.  It's the sound  I'll tell you about it later.I
have a video of that for a year, so
let's have a look at it first.Maybe
it would be more interesting if you watched the story above and then watched it again.  You
might be able to tell a little bit from the video whether it's a good position or a high mother position at a party,
so let's take a moment and watch the latest video together.It's great.I'll be
here forever.  is c  I
would like you to watch the outside day with Tetsu together.
I Last month's Chime Idol was like that
[Music]
Extract and there are a lot of things before
face 4 ad It's good, it's bad
Herbal tea to do with Burna Peewee Groove  use
existing is asked Yes, get rid of it, this is Lady Ampeg's advice. I
was told a Felgra Beige name.
Play Pooh-style Media Perorating Cure. new
ok web 2 do Do
?
Seitsu
Process Caster 0
[Music]
rename
go I'm going to clean the inside - yes, ah I'll
buy Arai-cho, I'm going to sleep - it's time to test my eyes
[Music]
Now I'd like to go back to the scene
Eh, what's amazing?  I felt that way, but it was still interesting.This
video has a bit of a story line about Arise's up until now,
compared to Magiya, so there were a lot of dark aspects such as that card, but
also the promotion venue.
Since we're in the video club, we've seen quite a few aspects of this kind of friendly party,
and this time, after that, we've
cooked food based on the marsh concept of outdoor camping, and we've had the same Kisara
fishing trip we did earlier, and
fielder activities like that.
This is a specially edited video to let you know that there really is such a thing.
Thank you very much. Then I saw that little sister, so I thought it might be strange.  I
think, uh,
this is a skit story, but the way and appearance was a little different with this one, but it
skids in places other than 8A.  Is it
possible to enjoy it in the version
? I
understand, it has happened many times already, not only at that time, but
also at various times during the journey, even while playing.  It's
similar to the Teruzo series.
Sometimes it happens at a special moment, and sometimes it pops up at such times and
if you're interested, you
can just read it.  So, you
can think of it as a moment where you can take a short break from your
journey, but I'm sure that the 3D model that Arise has greatly evolved from has
changed.I see.
It's not just that, but the other skits are also in 3D, so it looks
like you can play around with them.As you saw earlier, I think all of those skids
had a little bit of a big style frame, but it looks like that.  It
has a cherry blossom edge that is scattered in the sky,
so what I like about it is that it has the same
feeling that I felt when I played the game, and it
feels like the characters are really there.  I
created this skit on the Gintown Line to give you the feeling that the six of you are on a proper trip.That natural reality that you can enjoy
is what I wanted to aim for this time.  I
think it feels natural.In fact, I want people to enjoy doing this skit so naturally that they don't notice it.That's the
concept of this time.a I see, this is a
skit that is evolving.  I'm
really looking forward to the remaining characters, Shisai Suki and Phil.Well,
I guess that's what happened with that girl's skit, and
in the main scenario, it was quite similar to what I said earlier, and the
relationship between Reina and Reina was very intense.  I also made some dishes where I felt like I might not be able to get along with the instep of the characters,
but when I went a step further with the skid expressions, I was able to
see a warmer side of the character.
Well, the relationship between the parties seems to be a little more relaxed, and the
details are layered on top of each other in detail.It's a Tales of style, or
rather, it
has a petit part, so in that respect, it's a character that closely follows the elements that have been used up until now.  I
think it's interesting to see the attraction between two people in such a close-up way.I think it's interesting to see the attraction between them.  I
want to see it.I was wearing something that looked like a cafe book,
but that can also be obtained in the game under the condition that it ends, but
when I want to enjoy something like a chicken cooking skit, I naturally want it to be different from that
on the skid.  It's the same with clothing attachments, but
since everything is reflected, it becomes a focus that wasn't there in the previous Ano Teruzo Skip, so I
hope you enjoy this Neyoru play.
Then, the skit is no longer about that suicide note waiting for you, but if you
put your character in that costume, they will appear in the same costume in the
skit.  Of
course, all of the floating sound movie scenes are in 3D, so the
so-called suicide note will also be reflected, so it will be the same,
so the only thing that will not be reflected is the animation 2D animation scene.  I'm really
excited because I'm really looking forward to it
more and more.a I also saw this video, and I thought about the competition as well,
especially when I was playing at home.  But the roast chicken and my mother looked really delicious,
and the
poses after the ghosts were really cool
.
Me a I want to know what kind of effects the food in this game has, and
there are character events related to food.  mosquito
Well, this time's cooking is often done at exactly the timing of Yae
,
and of course you can do it at an inn,
but the only way to do it is when you do it outdoors, there will be more noise, so enjoy cooking in those places.  I
'd like to have it, but I think
it's a bit of a roast chicken delusion to think that each character has a specialty dish, but I
feel like this is the character, and I'm asking for the specialty dish to be that unique character.
There are also good things about the game, such as the so-called Unlucky Mother, where you can
get even better additional effects,
and the occasional
exclusive skit with a penguin connection.  This
may occur, so be sure to steal those various dishes.
First, search for recipes, collect the direct ingredients, and then look for the special dishes as well, and then
pick the ones that have better effects and are more like the character.  That's why I
think Lori-nee is one of the characteristics of Tales, so I
have a recipe plan, so I'd like to try and complete it.First of
all, I'll start by collecting recipes.I
see.I see.I'm
really
looking forward to cooking.Two  In the first picture, there was a
story about that kind of cooking, but it was actually Mr. A who was the
first to play the so-called trial ROM.  It
's really scary. Thank you for letting Tsukiari do it.
Re Berry
is amazing. The
parent's curtain
was 9, but that's right. Here's my impression of it.
First, let's start with the
one that's really big, Houichi Oki.
For example,
when playing baccarat, the transition between the brain and the feed when you're on the field is
fast and smooth, and you don't
have to wait for Anoro.
Gackt-kun  It's
not fun at all,
right? Thank you very much.This time, I
chose the so-called encounter method, which is a legacy method for battles.
Well,
there are a lot of different opinions about what happens after a
battle ends, but up until now, after a battle,
everyone would see the public characters stand up and have a conversation based on the battle result.  There
was a sequence, but I'm going to
go back to the field right away,
and at the same time, use 8 voices to express that kind of expression.Hearing
that, I thought it was interesting to hear how I felt after that battle,
but somehow I
went back to the field from the paddle to the field.  I thought it was a good thing because it didn't feel out of place and everything
went smoothly, but that's exactly what
we want to aim for this time, going into the headquarters to battle, leaving again, and then fighting again.  I
put my finger on that pace a little bit, and I
want everyone in the store to have fun.This
time too, we created a comfortable form with the battle system
vocca pro and the field member system.
So, I really hope everyone can play the game and
experience it as soon as possible and feel positive about it.
Of course,
there are many people who say things like, ``It's good,'' and I think that's normal.Of course, I'd
like to think that if there were a lot of people who would say, ``It's just the way things have been up until now.''
But,
well, this
is our brand of Telezorb, but we also have one big goal: to have a lot of people play this game without feeling weird about it, so
we're
trying to find a balance.
There was also a part where I was really worried about how to put it into form, and I wanted to go with the scene,
so that's the
right thing to do.In a sense, the
reaction was positive.Well,
even those who have been to the series so far have said that.  If that's the case, I
don't know if that's the best answer, but one of the things that Laserrise wants to aim for is that it
doesn't necessarily mean it's wrong, so I'd like to share my thoughts with you.
Even though I'm worried about this, I'm still trying various things.It
's true, so I'm sure you'll get a lot of
different opinions, but I'm sure you'll get a lot of different opinions.  I
want to make future series even better.Well, I
remember seeing those kinds of memories, so I
was talking about trying to improve the details and putting a lot of soul into the college.Yes.
I think the balance was really good, but when I found out about it, it was very personal,
but I really liked this one, so feel free to ask.Oh, I
have another impression, but it's
probably a test.  Well, I
think I exceeded that amount by a lot, but
even so, I didn't aim for something that high, and
when I was just walking around a little bit, I ended up swimming a little bit.
There was that waterfall, and I went there to visit it, and Atsuto
found a treasure there, but I wasn't aiming for that, the scenery was amazing and
beautiful, and I
had so much fun taking that walk, I was so absorbed in it.
Thank you very much. It was really fun to take that walk.
Well, for example, when someone told me that they had fun shampooing their hair even when there was no public, Kuroko: I
think people would be really happy if they created field art.
Normally, you go first because there seems to be a treasure chest at the end of the roof or something that will give you something to gain in terms of the game.Basically, I
told you to do it,
but it wasn't just that.  The power that makes you want to go ahead is
really something like this.If you
don't make an effort, you'll have a tomorrow in the game.We're also making it, and you can just
feel how beautiful it is.After preparing the checkout, you can think of it as you buy it.  It wasn't just that.
This time, I'll be going back to the day I swam, to be
able to make a big jump and jump from such a high place with such a difference in height.The fact that I
can do something like that makes me want to try it.It's this exquisite balance that makes me want to try it.  It was
n't
until I had this game that I felt like I wanted to go on an adventure and that's one thing I wanted to do, like being a doctor.  A
nest with characters
Above all, Arai's brand remains a ministerial brand, but even
so, I still find myself taking a little detour,
thinking about how I can approach the beautiful end of the year, how I can welcome it there, and so on, creating a
spell for the world in front of me.  Fit
is another thing I want to cherish as an RPG, so I guess you
could really call it the rate, right? The
various high-new features that match what you can do with that rake are...
In the end, it doesn't change what you have to feel the character. That's why we're forced to
open up, and we don't dare.
So the world that expands the path is a tool to draw the character more attractively.
From now on, I'm
going to become an echo. After all the hard work, the characters have come this far. I want us to have conversations with each other,
and if that's how we can express the appeal of API.  I
think we need a home more than that, and
in a sense, that's what we need.  I
remember that we kept a lot of secret discussions about how much of this world we could expand horizontally and in terms of perspective, and I think that in order to achieve that goal, people
noticed.  However, this time, I'm calling it short chat outside of the skip and movie scenes,
but it's a voice-only conversation,
which means that when you're constantly adventuring in the field, it's worth having that
automatic flow, which is better.  I've
increased the size of my breasts so much. That's amazing.
Hmm, I don't know
what it is, but it feels
natural. That's what I think is important. In order for it to feel natural, you need a lot of
variation.
There were some things like that, so in the end, it
took about a year to do the human recording.
That's just my impression.
Chiara is the main character of that past work of Transferred, and she
was basically the main character at the center of gravity.For
example, in Slow Symphonia, it would have been Lloyd-kun, but that gyatama
wine character has generally been
one of the main characters over the years.  There are a lot of characters that use two of them, but that's
basically the one that I felt was the easiest to fight.Until
now, that's why I've been using them as the main character, but I feel like this is the main character.  teeth
During that test play,
since I was doing a personality test play, I switched to another character and tried that fight,
and even I was
surprised.
Everyone was easy to fight and fun, so this time it's a
reverse of that certain arc.  I thought I'd use a variety of characters instead. Is there
something special about that? That's a
very exciting story.
That's exactly what I thought when I was in charge of the video.  I feel
like it's a waste of time to respond.In the series up until now, the number of characters has increased from 6 to 8.The
characteristics of the children who are structured in the party, and even if they are
fired up by battle, are still very much like this.The
game designer has kept it a secret, but it is difficult to do so.  After all,
it's an exaggeration to say "mostly, most of all," but even if you
take a survey, you'll find that quite a few people do
n't make that character change, so it's not just us.Well, I
think that's the 100 majority.However, it's
true that 6  The character has to work 8 times as hard as the character.  It's
such a waste that people don't enjoy the Neko bottle design, but it also means that the real appeal of the work is
n't being experienced by the Neko, so I
think I'd like to clear that up somehow.  It's easy to understand when you say it's a surgery.The
first thing I did was to use those
two airy instants, Booster Pack and Boost Strike, and the
serve character will do that support action.
But this was also that murderous spirit. Now, you know, the
feeling that we're fighting together is, first of all, what we're trying to do is to make people
feel that way at that concert,
and this is really what Mr. Here is also playing.  Maybe, but the
boots made it possible to swap characters quite quickly even during battle.Yeah,
so I thought, ``Let's use this strategic power recovery catty a little bit.''
When I thought, ``Oh,
it's like that.''  You
can change your mood and you can change your strategy, so I
tried to make the character change very smooth, so I hope everyone will enjoy it and
give it a try.
Sometimes, I
really felt that she was replaced with Ishi-yeon-Jang,
and I think she's suited for a tunnel.  The
first attack really shoots down all the flying enemies and knocks them down, so of
course when you use it with some planning, you can do it yourself and
expand your chances.That's
really the point of the person here.  There are options for
how to manage characters other than yourself or characters other than those investigating in line with your play style,
so I definitely
think you'll be able to do that and everyone will be masters of sound.  So please enjoy it  I
think so, and to be honest, the action nature of the game has been
strengthened this time around through the use of pads, so I think the individuality that you feel when controlling the six characters is
also quite strong.
Hmm, in that sense, I've received feedback from people who say that after trying it out, they wanted to touch each and every one of them.In that sense, too, I'm happy.By the
way, for those who are playing for the first time, I would of course recommend the main characters.  I think it's fenda.  Have a
good night's sleep.Is there a character that is easy to control that is easy to do
?
Well, in the morning, as you said, it is easy to
understand and can be placed in a wide range of places such as school plays.  It
has its charm, but
for example, there's a character who maintains those aspects while
also being able to use spirit magic at the same time, and who sticks to the town as an under-arm.  The
existence of mutual feelings Wayne File File or java Right-hand man Joy
Run The day of the person who uses one festival n I'm going to put in the soil of Hai Hori, but
this time Sanza Let's go
to that series with this character
First of all, that person is right, so
in that sense, too.  It's
a bit ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
now first over to that Hori
Hanjage is fire wire The application is stingy le
By the way, I opened it at the end of the first ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh's story.
Well then, he's almighty.He
has an attack-centered charm, but
for example, there's a
character who's strong enough to be an all-rounder who can use spirit magic while still maintaining that aspect,
but he's
too tough to get into after that.  First of all, Aora Ora is a
character with a long beach that can be enjoyed not only by focusing on attacks but also by playing gacha.  If you
have a bit of a Patol Tsuki, you can try the first one, and I
think it's also interesting to play with luck and the difference in clothes.As expected, there is a character that I think is true, but I
use it like that when I'm standing.  I like a lot of attacks like that.Also,
in this game, Anonichi doesn't just attack the so-called target, but this time he
focuses on evasion of that branch action that has been mainly focused on so-called outrageous behavior.  Right?
Hmm, how do you avoid attacks from enemies?
And
then there
was just the fact that you can dodge at the right time and
counterattack by closing the distance, which is also a really good action game
feature.
Since the performance of each character
is different, I would like you to try it out and see it.In a
work that focuses on avoidance, Kisara is the only one who stands up, so you can receive it properly outside the workshop and
return it.Well, it's
raining here.  That charm that is different from that of
Amah
There are some aspects of him that make him stand out, so I
'd like to focus on attack for Kisara, but I'd like to focus on defense a little more.There
's a gay boobie in the foreground, but hmmm...
Even the really aggressive characters
have their own charms.  Yes, but there's also a character called Law who really can't do this. To be
honest, Mr. Ron 9 Minutes didn't try that much.
Other than Fen, I think the characters that were easier to play in the game
were Enchan and Gizarah. Knee has a bit of movement,
but she has so much equipment and a shield.  It's
a bit heavy to move from the ground, so I feel like I'm floating, but it's heavy and a bit
slow, so
there's a lot of introverted strategies that just go towards the target.  As for the
specs, it's like those 10 characters, so they have to keep their distance well and recover
while doing so, so it's a bit like a
public character for an RPG,
but it's also nice to be able to attack in a broken active way.
Hmm,
Toa's Boost Atago Boost Attack was incredibly easy to occur,
and I keep getting used to it over and over again with Bun Ibis, but somehow...
If you fight with them together, the battle will become very open on the team,
and the paralyzed devil party will be checked by all 4 schools.  I
think that's a big part of why it felt so natural to be able to do things in such a flashy way. Hmm.
By the way, I apologize for my English, but
a future in chess d.  2
re re re re anders Booth is good Anfin
Oh no pastel bride fashion with feet distry
r Moon's bikini is space Ie & pet a little still watch
Hermes turbo it's nice but pickers we are ion a little 60%
martin d t 4 lard club  Dio Fresh That kind of vision of the near sea Sonomachi
More Watch your
finger image Love is a good-looking dart
Yeah, well, I'd like to ask you the next question.
Ah, no. I'm going to change the topic a bit, but
a. It's about the voice actors who don't pay points. I think there are a lot of fans of Kokusai, so a. I wonder
if there's an episode about the casting of the voice actors. I wonder if it's about the Japanese voice actors.
Mainly, for me, I was able to work with that team on things like original Japanese casting, but
after all
, I do it every time at the audition.
It's open
After all, the amount of time it takes to play a single public character is
quite expensive.You
have to perform with
a lot of passion.  I
often hear people go into auditions with such determination, so
in Arise this time, especially the six
main
party characters, each of them took over a year to
record.  especially
So, well, it's
7 characters long, and I hadn't finished the game at all at that time.Well, I
started filming from that time, and the game gradually became complete.Well, I
wanted to ask questions like this, and I created scenes like this, so I added them.  I
'm cooing [music] that I want to take a picture.It's a problem for me as a creator as well.If it
were true, I would be able to finish shooting this and that all at once.
In normal games, that's normal, but
in Teruzobu, it's
really the skits and short chats that I mentioned earlier, and
once the scene is complete, there are voices that become necessary, and the
characters' emotions.  The
fact that things are always born later
is e 3.
No, that's true, but you can make games as quickly as possible.
That's why I always think that we need to start early, but it's never going to end. Well, this time too, the
recording of all the women was actually completed about two years ago.
So I
started doing a lot of promotion, and I've been appearing on a lot of shows, so I'm going to
start off by apologizing for keeping you waiting, and I'm going to start off by apologizing for oversleeping.
But which one was it after all?  When you
play this game, you can enjoy seeing how our acting has come to fruition into the character of Seiko, and
there is a character with real meaning, so we really
put a lot of effort into the production.5
Promotions  Recently, I've
been playing a lot of things like this, and I've been doing it with great emotion, but that's how
passionate acting is.First
of all, if you're a director in Japanese, it
's in your voice, so I'll show you that.  Correct
This time, there are also 4 English Boo Swords below.
Therefore, I would like to convey to the voice actors Manabu Hanno what true fashion is, and I
would like them to aim for acting that is close to it, or even surpasses it, even in No. 5.  We are doing it again this time around the world, and
as I said at the beginning, this is the first new work from Zo-bu that has been released simultaneously all over the world.The reason is that it was
written in a short period of time and was written in a short period of time.  It's different. It's been
almost a year.  I'm a
little wet. Vesperia Remaster was done at the same time, but it's a star right now,
so I was
working on the original work, so my dad and I were working on it at the same time,
but due to safety policies, I think that's all it takes.  I took the
audio recording and translated it into English and recorded it,
and then I did a more detailed project.It's a long time for Ross, so I have to match this as well.Japanese
and English are completely different.
After all, in order to make Pound Buber appear, I have to
change the glory that was translated twice in as much time as the thickness.The time doesn't match, so it feels like it's already reflected, and the
derby level is also seen in the voice recording of Voice 4A 5 size.
There are a lot of really, really delicate steps, and you
're saying you're doing this in preparation for the release of Oji.Actually, it must have been extremely difficult, right?
But from what I've heard so far, the voice actors for the English version and the Japanese version really
fit the character very well.  I think there are a lot of people who do
n't want to play that nice girl when they do something safe and
want to see the original 2nd version, but the English
characters are really good this time as well.  Is it true?
Truly, the English localization team is working very seriously on Arise,
so
for example, a certain character has a Japanese
voice actor who has also been active in various anime and other works.
However, in the American version, this voice actor seems to be on set a
lot, but he has been given a lot of voice acting, and after that, he is the voice actor who speaks English like that and disappears after that.  I
believe in a woman who can convince all the JRPG fans and animation fans that she is a woman who has a stomach-like appearance, such as having someone she recognizes come to her in the morning.  That's what I'm
doing, so that's exactly what I'm
thinking.If that's the case, then
I'm wondering if I can even talk about it with confidence.  That's
what I thought.I'm having trouble deciding whether to do it in Eero or in Japanese.For
those of you in Handa who know, are you in a troubled area?
If this is the first round, then the Japanese version
is the 5th edition.  Of
course you
can change the pitch as well,
but you can change it all the time and check it out.New, that's
good.If you
don't mind doing this, you can ask me the next question.  Is
it okay? I
think it's a little related to Acom right now.
Questions. Is
it okay to ask questions that I haven't decided yet? It's okay.
Ah, I
watched Nishi 9, but that's what I
thought. Is
n't that right?  The video of the horse Rise is blooming and there are various things going on at the
end of Kido's
arm, Mr. Iida, and he appears in beautiful clothes, but Sarah goes there.  What do you call that thing
that's so big? It looks so
big and heavy, but I'm wearing it.
Strandy says that and says something. Do you want to
talk about it? Um, how many
times have you seen that long arm?  I wonder if it'll turn out to be the case? It's the first of its kind in Japan, and thanks to you, a
lot of people come here because they get to relive the charm of lesbianism in a way they haven't seen before.  After all, that
There was a lot of discussion within the company as to whether we would be able to maintain a high level of performance due to mental factors, but we were able to implement something like that last year, and
this year as well, we have a plan in place,
so the truth is that
[music]  I
'd like to meet you overseas or something like that, but the
team isn't good enough. I
apologized for not being able to come up with that sudden plan, but I
want them to do it in a way that makes it clear that they're going to win.  I think
that's true. Besides that, we also hold events like Tales of Festival that focus on voice actors, but it's difficult to take everyone overseas, but if it's an orchestra, we'll use the local orchestra.  Everyone, I'm sure
you'll actually be able to do something like that. Well,
I wonder if we can try something from Boo Boo. The idea has been popping up in America, Europe, etc., so don't worry, we've started broadcasting it.  look  It's an
event that we would like to expand even if we just set up an environment where people can enjoy it at Zoid.Is it going to be streamed?It's
delicious.We've been doing it since last year.What's it like overseas?  I
really want to see Chiara, because I can't
seem to get excited, but I also want to see her play that can be said, and that kind of spoon, but I
really want to feel it at the live performance.
I think, and last year's theme song for past titles,
everyone cherishes the theme song for Kenkeruzo, so last year we did a full orchestral
arrangement of it, and it
was all in a medley, or rather in order of flow, and it was very well received.  That was really good,
right?
So this year, it's actually going to be an encore of that, so it looks like we're
going to have a set list centered on that theme song, including of course the great Arise song.
Well, for everyone in Japan, please go and tell Miyara what you think after both hands,
but I
really want to create an environment where the boss can watch it on stream or something, year by year,
so I appreciate your support.Kira has
1 loss.  When I was in Japan once, I went to the Multiplication Festival, and
I said, "Thank you very much." I was
really surprised. I was so surprised that something had just happened, and I went there without really knowing what was going to happen.  It's
become quite a big cultural festival to be playing a secondhand movie in a cheerful place. It's like a big cultural festival. It
's only for a short time, but it's amazing.
Everyone who loves the characters.  It
was a truly irreplaceable experience, and I felt a tremendous amount of love.I
understand that the important thing is to create a space where fans come together.
However, I would like to continue to develop events that have a high appeal, not just in our games, but in many different ways.
[Music]
That's right.  a
Well, this is the bottom part ok Slur Well, I'm sure everyone is looking forward to it, but
let's talk about Ateru Zone for a moment, but back to Rise
no I have one question.  It's a story of two inner worlds.  I
think there are a lot of udon stories.How is the story of the two worlds different from past works?That's right.As you
said, it seems like there are two conflicting worlds, so it's
important to depict them.  Even if there are a lot of series, it's still
asap,
and for those who think that everything is just on one side, Kaneda's way of thinking is safe, and
ur is
quite common in Anoko's series.
It's a way of thinking, but one of the reasons why I decided to use the structure of these two conflicts in such an easy-to-understand way for Rise this time is,
of course, to
appeal to fans of the series who have always been fans of the series, but because of this ice cream.  It's been a long time since I've
gotten a little interested in the Tales of series.For
example, I tried Shinji, but I haven't been to it since.But
this time I'm looking for a work that would be an easy-to-understand entry into the series.
That's what I want to be, that's what I want to be.I dared to
choose something
primitive and simple,
with the two being in a controlling relationship of only opposing stars, and
with an easy-to-understand stage setting that you might imagine.
There is one aspect to it,
and there is also
that binary opposition, which is very powerful, or rather, a relationship that
is easy to understand, so let's look at that.  That's why
I also wanted to see more complex human hearts and things like that.This
time, the characters will be expressed in 3D, so
investment trusts will increase as well.  I think people get more of the realism of the public characters, and
then the perceptual effects of the characters' worries and statements, or the
relationships between the characters are
a bit higher, or rather the reality is
higher.
of
There's a lot of interaction, and
there's a part of me that I wanted to express a little bit, and
in that sense, I wanted to express the actual, real-life worries of the characters in a world that changes in an easy-to-understand
way.  Since I am
trying to apply something with this intentionally simple structure, it
is a bit difficult to explain in terms of the difference from other works,
but
Buber took this idea into account and decided to create this series.  is the road
Well, that's how we're facing the conflict structure again this time.
Thank you very much for your hard work. Well, Building A. I
have a question that I'd like to ask you, but I think it's the last one.
Now that we're getting really close,
how do you feel now?Are you
sure you've achieved it?Do you have a new master?Are you nervous?Well, it's
been a long time.I started planning around the end of 2016 and it started to sink in.
So,
thanks to you, the gamer is almost complete, so I'm
half looking forward to seeing everyone's reactions, and
half nervous as I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of reactions they'll get, as there are various challenges ahead.  However, the
one thing that I think is really cool about this time in my career is
that, as I said earlier, I can promote it with people from all over the world and have them enjoy it together.
This was one of the goals I wanted to aim for this time, so I
think it's good to know even if there are various reactions,
but I think it's good to know that everyone can enjoy it at the same time.  It's
okay to have a reaction like, ``The characters here were good,'' or ``I
think the game design was good,'' or ``It didn't suit me,''
but I think that's the kind of thing that everyone all over the world thinks is good at the same time.  first  I
think it's important,
so the fact that we can do something about it is really great.  I'm
really looking forward to it, but on the other hand, I'm also really nervous about it, but the dub is coming up right now, so I'm going to go to bed, and I'm going to be wrapped up
in my futon, and I'm going to be like this all the time.There are parts
where I'm looking at it, but it's really like
Pork's pattern.  Ninaou  I
tried to make it so that it can be conveyed in a way that people can touch it, and with all of
your cooperation,
September is already an index, but I really
want to face it straight.
By the way, Chiara's love for that one year.  Shin: I've been spending a
lot of time celebrating the one year anniversary since my debut, so it's like I'm lucky and I'm getting a present right here, so I'm
really, really happy. You
mentioned last time that it was close to the nabe anniversary,
so this time too,
Hiroyuki.  That's
what I was thinking as I was playing, and last time, the first broadcast was for you on your birthday.Well,
this time,
when the AAA game comes out, Breathe and I will be playing it on the channel at home, of course, while watching that defeat.
I'd like to go there, so I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
a
Lastly, if you have any comments, Mr. Tomizawa, please let me know.
Yes, that's right. I don't like that.
In this way,
through Norma talk with Chara, I would like to talk to people outside of Japan about what is really Western.  With everyone in  Being
able to have a session was something that had never been done before,
so I'm looking forward to seeing everyone's reactions.I'm
curious about this, so I'm recording it, so the day it was streamed,
everyone was making a lot of comments.  I'm sure you're reading this, but I'm really happy to be able to
move towards the release of this book even though you're such an idiot.As I
said earlier, through this Arise, I'm really happy for the first time.  I'm going to touch your thighs
Even if there are people who say that, I don't think that's true or that it will increase,
so I
think there are quite a few people who are fans of Nemo Chiara, but didn't know about her, and found out about it through this program.  I'm thinking about it, and I
hope that those people will feel free to try
it out, and that we can play the game in a program-like format while having fun together.  I
think it's suitable for a work that can be enjoyed enough to be enjoyed, so please take this opportunity to check out Pyudo
Bar Rise
and the Martel family series as
well.
She has been talking about her love for the series ever since her debut, but
if you haven't played the series, I really want you to give it a try, and
if you can't get into Morgan yet, you can play the previous game.  But when it was released...
Thank you very much for your continued support.From now on, I will be working on some of those things before the release of the A wing.The official ambassador will be working as Basara, so please keep an eye on me.Thank you for today.
ronin
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. I will continue to do
my best. Thank you for coming to this studio today. I'll
be waiting for you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
[Music]
4th
mar
ah
2 me up ring matching zumyure
n
4 nanas 2nd part ame to spin I love it, plan do spinner
this feedback pue tax
nyan ii ii
floor goods sales tayaman warkiri kids day
win's foot mail 4 turn hey  If it's a cutter knead
oi garoge anabe
moe ah
down to do you guys
dub proud interview coffee I guess there's plenty y hope  It's a
threat to you guys
Ah
me
anders The cup noodle pattern goes well with the horse. Is the horse good?
Vienna Vegas Scan Page cato
Caldis Scan Day Kazarata thing work and pictures.
Yay to the carp turbo camp v Let's take a look
re re re re re re  re sr deren ode undo
weber ender n
seg's burn
iamy's plan swing easy to do mn game wii
chongz no way
beadstone
water apartment peche's jeans
re so me an goods 4 f 4 n 2 flyer rme
loss eust fur wool up the baby special okino 4
ten big star non 4 f na bully store boon
blue teeth bing this pinder  4 txt g o in this
for men and half with b 52
ran wing rtm fence
special omsb double dow play
interview afb  orange about choice ace tezu
maple sooo 6 cars dain d 9 wine
ah ah rare beast
[music]
awakening
pau sui fan meeting some ampeg scene slice good good good
yutsuru suke one
ramm Fanning family home of 6 people eat rice  It's like a shark that pulls out.
This kids buson rend tear the game the
voodoo regex wave new world bound temperature.  poooo
new Sorting pin for genitals and invar inside Story with showroom
Opening in autumn soon Children's Pock and
style
speed pro 6 a f sports re down to do World
manebi Coupo cheese normal dk Pace ah
's pottery 100 Inguk-san Cub players
[Music]
voodoo re zu barrel ex par 4
watch'n fun 2 n berwick no ano star motion
2 wesker goods prune ender ender ender  spencer
bagel follow roof 4 s arm by pink
des des myspade f brides anti-curve goods next web
n h 2
fence tooth is sjo main body charming ikepod
mending suke san aan higher day
comparison pen one after another naming row  Haeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee days windows
up out there out there
render swing way 5
nid smooth party in truth the queen is up and it’s normal law
As soon as you get a record, dance on the fence and be careful not to let it pass at home
nu do do do so ntr 4 f b 2 f 4 o
Um Affinase Ah Walker e a pen Pickdame 22 News Passion-san
Persoboy is so caring
iene Enchandu  for air
Well, the inferior products have fought five battles and are going to sing 4 s rapid w There are many pipes and
such parakeets a Jenny
Come on, let's make a picture of a star player with a thin Landers Stars, shave it off, and add Yoojung's buddy to it.
star hair
re the voodoo downshion part 4 s a mother
window worth to spain kai cab e part aya blue dua  I've got
over 3 bottles of Arai Arm flavor and Senryu ice cream back. I've already selected the phone. I'm
43 years old. I'm
leaving Kubo with a tarp. Let's chase the mystery together and get there.
Geo-gei with the Pospain model.
A Wear Blanche ok. Ah,
use to do.  n adeno restio meara son ben
darter star web contribution icas kuzo da poop me
ammy sanso hubrac free size down so md star
zuru miss size backup
space ns 4n force queen
barbie background
maybe four 4 swim good pants penny lane car ok
ees 2 minutes free
apyon master in campus ap 1000 cab e n
wing installer starfighter
i finally crop mag as grandismesh b su
mabao kai
this space e-mail archive -
Wig Teens all ages Carnation Spice Chon Artwork
and Lerner
Ion
Spying
[Music]
i  The pink house also smoked a lot of bras and
had a long celebration together.Smart Pretty SD Navi B Menche
PC Prom Spice Sisters Blue Do
Good Mend Geishu do n 4 al 4 wii your
Umm
Homua off the damn iggs
[Music]
tb r star black scale meister no. 6 head od spice wee raf
batting evo pu5
d spice ns  Benz sofa me to do n
y Heidi asame 2 r er 4 n
to it 5 The reason for harm is the upper side
Dog party
drinking aspect Wow wit tarp then mouse 4
display leaf pattern blueway see wife map
recorder
work sa  -Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaally
dare you do bread boo boo
seata rearea face odense ah djno
nook that guy's patty ap copy paste is
ideal short ripe airweave yevs pass scapefighter hmmm now
Eg's South Lapine
interview with withardine up and down dropper figure weather
me
share opti nds pass  I like the
Airbag Rubber Figure Club, you do this, let's go there,
ran.  Minute spin [ __ ] [ __ ] hey bar 1 shirley dx 4 se
kisaran
rice new zarah mousse ube also air barb pe god
pan sqp pla day ba ba ib ren
ispe scene
in this om
8 items squeaky sweet pim ah get it  It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been
in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
Changer Bound color pipi
yeah
Ogo Wade ime Hanpen mother and brother Wow Wow,
it's three soy sauce Ah, I'm improving my English and Medi
Okay, Okay, I'm
moving Eh Mema
Brainberry
Jack of all kinds Ah, there's a jack of all trades
Abbey  Add some salt, then it's good Kisana Bawa
[Applause]
is Sea Day Shizu Etsuyuki Pyu is good
Years Day Euro 4 Mize Nagatomi Rose Queen
Haa
Tyra fan car with k sosa snipeer ru
desu as wings ode to boo boo line girl
wow order p 4 beers artis api messer
amebaa through pure blue do the face powder futon speaking wedge
exe to wind low hospital  Fanee
[Music] Noir who
is aiming for the Japan office is a player who is twice as creative. Morio
Denki is pure and nice.
A lot of Dua tpe
inoa Dealer Whitmarsh love It's
fast without a point after withdrawal Yt Shigeeda's habit is catch so merry
Maybe so Display heating b Silent zoom fack plate
Produce Oubai's pure uuu eat for Ting Surf 33
[Music]
Etsu male bath  anb savior
esprit fury 2 walker
ur bath tu
[music]
voodoo catch general affairs fish
My squirrel work please 2
[Music] The
combination has changed
rt Home s over minutes res Kids aaaaa
Killer
rebn Old s pilot sk Tsutomoe
Saud day Sophie Zuchan Keen
Hime sauce misses Scooby the bone Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
vs dance skater Gueskar beforehand game for  a
wedding
raspini buehler abuf urano face wear rpg
uin
uz grater men's ar pt fishing
reiran no jeans
Pospeseeger good and attached a day etty teen layer fall nc derby's page
parosososone
fax web Fingers to Spain Inchan view aid at the temple
void also for apai nome boon
-4 masen let's meet dada biddy
Darwin rain  Jah we are
v and missing rod race wipestalk
ns At times like this Nabe circular 4 ip song
n snack chicken daddy
Yeah yeah yeah Shaan's mocking game
Thin Yuge re 4 Minhwa me up tour
Nooooo c mature dapaster so
maybe a certain outerwear for many long scenes to do for Suzuki
up your Dull surfing reception Potter lens type e
Aaaaaa
Dui wear world  Life is collecting dogs 2
Yes, the American and
British bonbon media with hydraulic pressure and strength are like that.
Salt and preparation are also
waiting for me.  de wicker
enjadodwien waiver inzer
mainty
nme spincast pastraz lee perry tape composition
aaron yade powersoftel wings to spring spa 4 ae min
klaus papiswee it justice first words
moriaki
web service cache apua ks bate andy  ncanty
so live and computing casting aizu skyloose good
van dam
win not you do stone
iphone  charlie news english case 1 sale loss radio machine
dinghy asino 6 mr r wentz pass when will you say 1
cannabis raw rescue songebooks
with me casting power 4 a such theory ek news tung
voodoo turn signal pass days 2
dart tour main is tim  aje cruiser 6
fashion dependent dulcet e 9 de microcomputer saa mir
we are free come across me to do a power
boomsound
No, let's go to the power that gives us pleasure lonely
Hmm, painter style p Ah v Chip Quo Apply for x3 books cap course ke
committee member Sabu
Yay figure cellosophy absurd world ABCs
Arm rain ramen oooh it's a flight Skip as It's a volunteer large
Innove new  Gyaaa b 2
voodoo
ko disc petteen spoon peruunzu baa baan boon
pattern pumps a lot
learn soap eb  the oc's wii bar
voodoo r polare who do loop owner's face katy
yukkyuanzen
arauza-like liar male hole champion 51 ownership a
eh vector blue commercial
[music]
voodoo
off blowgun dio  fear yo
anderen the veil ender ender ender
asaras per month spax ender sticker love door love
alba me now it's over a
yeah  Along
with the five great sentences, web swing is also 1 power, nao-san,
no chonchong smooth 2 c God really wife coaster
[Music]
Saa arenas beach ah papageno dere
Saa star web pay is warner good
Song learn a
De-sui video will love cross walk
Othello  It's good to have a dojoke, a
swimmer clip with a thing, once Ashtar 4 day, I'm
going to go out and get 4 less, boo
boo senso  Dale Ins Boo Boo good
as old as a doodle
star brewer pets
a
doso flight web adventure on the surface sen has
been black pen mea frets say body pot also better than
ummm and roll up your arms and express it with point vibes  yo etic bookend
star world wing
abe tuna noose no pushy fiber boo boo boo block
muta sperigin staff
second breath two companies straight where one day turns hmm
Double party up 3 nof Ping
p My mother is almost 5 times
today
Entity confirm 4
Ogudu
Vinny Ridge Satying Griffin Computing
Micron Gray Calm pv Wind call ab 8
Bool
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Check out
the number of accesses now Begin No, it's no use year
Handshake ansion andere It's a
cute place
Re an Sam
teacher burl pipe race add to do casplay rally car g
dickey's egg str black mud a yes it's
yushi romwine
can cultivation old inkyu sting in christine
oooh
web playbar
leno n
diff let's with keinkyu nice ummm then
This guy come
home web tsuweepchan
shock spanky don't do it nice
re down the rope please
re down the rope  Down Supreme & Supreme Outlets
web No. 8 In Space Ones
Jajaan Fein
Swing Aboi
play Farm is Ugi Samurai Good
Defense
Hmm
Off also stinks Pen Squad Sannu with caster bent
to an end r 4 me web base ore
4 s  Power theory rice me medieval r 4 terano lick burner rank e
already has a pre-cooler form opponent's chaa-bye-bye now es  Pose
Yasunaga Yasunaga Show Andis Sono Izumi Inage Ah PR
B 2 Pose -in is a pose -in Game
Ah Shima City Sumo Curly -up Store Sumo Paris Sumo 2
Choice Ah Ah
Ah Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Everyone
receives chura Sanaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Vision Starwear
General Amoy Day
Unser is also Tim but ni
reverse 252
Dondon Hon Chaiso Bandai What Queens 06 Iidanppa
4 Schools
Whistle
Arthur Firing Pau jj
span Such a pie
Inpopi server Weiss Weiss tu
#Hazugamijo od Sainara  Cure Tier Icernnnn
Pa's Wii Be A Turn Swap File Hyponnun
fc Toguu Mexie It's A
Difficulty  Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
ner Pingminn
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
im
[Music]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
Falci game 18th boi Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaiko
image  I don't see natural wood, so I have this.
After visiting Ise Shrine, I'm exhausted.
Pac e re as for each unfair. That's right.
Mizunaga Wow, it looks like you're
on a good Mac account. That's how you
sweat.  Masu
Epu Tsuda knot and red
ern before ikea minnow powder ruins and stupid cold symbol motor car
poly advice network spar in s burn
hmmm
a  I
chose the Move Glue
Ayahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahed R
Hanyu Blue RCC Sound Family Book, the father's grandfather is thin or Vegelap,
while the sweets dagger
ana is
also poured rice.  A member of parliament for a bellman,
when mother Bahia makes it,
Ran Way Bosnia C Fine Jasper Inn is
nearby.
[Music]
Navy road copper pot leash ah
ici Turbon pro vowel is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaallytherawlyawaaaaaaaaaaaatowantoaatowantotogotoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  The
pernspla sound t 4 a
blue minute game mas turfy is heroquirk a lot wood to prigeny no
bays to lease a man to do
Hmm
baby version her as for face pace structure
web ah ah ah big
big liquor corner alta rd Nesron Boost stance is gosho che
check round boy check the naughty woman
used f
[music]
ah falfa inches number  Da pampa
Kim Chai Jeter,
arrogantly barring the tag that was in the chest puapueppu position, ovenware drums bar
love seal,
swept caster right brain unexpectedly high
voodoo
archi The
reason why I'm
there I'm going to fuse feed how you do see iim 4 iphone Dog Grand Fally aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
ok oh
open
aaa Senkiyama ski mitsuka moven
amp 1 show  It's good for sharpening as well
Pocket 0 is really hot What the
hell?
Toamo Map Aho Ah Ah Ah Mello -like Days Bayes N Non -non is low -tempered, and it is strongly strong in Spain Po
Ah, a
mother Cadubi Ju
fine, Prius and D Former.
Hiking up a tan
Akiwofuu Baros breaking
news joint a
re resides comfort chef pants nude bbs  Kaneko p
[music]
voodoo star pass mo a o
fundis can i car fufu
jaby guard and distribution 525i zu birthday tree wallet 9 polly's morning
ah
entry column ah
[laugh]
Ike's benefit kiss
sq somuwa
waaaaaaaaan
Eh, don't worry, why don't you go
home?
Open the store Ferry season turbo Poisae Navigation sound Poe
ni poster a 5 af
Farah Shop or Yankee Fufufubububububububuu
Kyuu defeat on the Shion attachment in cur 99 qg Tomorrow Fight Tsun
chan Koi is
steaming
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
nio n one of mouth pleaser face pain fetish  so Wow, you
cut shop way, this Messer disease course is good,
you seem bossy,
let's be thin!
map with special good
Straw game and deep blind peg day Santo Moon
Boulf Naru Martin Panther se
[Music]
voodoo
India Boy Mae and the house where you live are also amateurs but a
Cassa is making it now 4 now mother variation armor  Guard Bucks Wow
Wow
7 Saving Bauhaus Fighter Brown Carry KX Loan
Anmaido
[Music]
and Farm [ __ ] Get Drug Dumper and Maybe
Daddy
Yeah
Line  Chesting Yani Hiinyan Bun Keio
Recommended Game Kuruma Jin-
kun, Everyone's Tide Age Color Ana Martin Monomachi
Pyontekomi Frespo Inc Define C Coser Zaboon Ya Blonde
Haired Long Figure
Noooo Dai Hmm
Beyond the dice, there's a pet service that sells whisky. That's Chester's defeated dog. I
rented him for sports at Oscar
[music]
why waste key
accu lion other chai2steller  starting soon
hi to self Surf yeah
meg
Nh shaky bread Samira Don't make it into a tight shape and collect it
Reac Total number of pins started
Operation Star Pink Purple Save a o 4
Rice and access surfing software bubububububufu  It's not what's going on.
why jackie penner worth pattern office wear bobby-chan beta
day employee edy jump
b chanpe oops
seat swollen dog lay down
favor weather barking
n original define cloth poster 3 steps inner car audio sound  Ha y-
san evanescence I don't know what to do, but I'm at a loss. I'm going to challenge you.
Hmm, Audi ice cone
speeder. I'm
already a tuber.
I'm so proud. Speeder
ana.  But aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, being
in the open and outside point pair star makeup living in a young country where I live in a really quadrilateral circle
wide My car rabbi's
school together and the
dim rice life
voodoo feet care  rd 1000 yen bestreben active
Bathtown doaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
today catcher
[ __ ]
web nabeso winter ni urine iso  I'm in love with my rubber.
Orisaka's spoon is also in the spoon. Hey, yeah, I'm going to cheer when I burp on the toilet seat.
1 year ago
Ngaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
body
omega shopyan hishi
dart follow pen
takao
ender truth burns suo office if carrying microcomputer 3 your
read me
poster well party skating skating ah dondon  none aps
nice fin to do fab pass many enthusiastic 2ska s power double breeze men and
women yukio
sweet type pe
oh sheaan shean weblog unhaired ponytails cube yaitain hissho
puro book
hoc fantasy too voodoo 3 sy 5 on face smooth
Wow,
Kisa
Komori is a
spa Pyer Gerugeru
Ndover Heath is good
Oh you're a place and a spoon
Ani
please
Fes or Fuse Milli Goods 3 Garth Under Wow
Whispaudi
piece
This guy's city was Usuda option osx Ninchu N
Ponte daaa minute pull lean angels It's hard to come Ahhh
Beijing Abu Aipu Dalshin-san's ice cream is small I
swam and it's amazing
staro
Road Wimbledon ase Sevigny asamana
proposed burn plan
bape's fit Sanhijri time-space big dishon push fupeing keep 4th place
Hyundo country Kim point campaign for new i
pink ano min
rs and do prune
chain efriend ea polare aspd ese noo  220
ana curl e 0 a day Higausa 6 ways Npinkusu Denbo  I
always think so at dawn
Aurora AI Pong
[Music]
rennos
Nachu Away Sonar bag for a hair
button type konde up-gei ran finally-gei
inform suit wa
wood as masuuntsuki salah hey
boku wo yappappa now sauce
nastran oas masu
dared no big zaler co2 taxi house s 1 o type
noah web xno obscene whos 4 f watch
[music]
web color me shop ahapin p game pinkish stripes
staff po
I see, it's a drawing turn! I
chose my father, Nezunee, Poni Emperor, Nabe
Suun
1, aha,
fire,
pocky salar, deres 4, c, rubber strap peropero wii
Opal Palm
with some terrific
foma GyaaaaaaaaaaamenwokeiDizon re 人GreenGreenfenty
man who do as miscellaneous expenses my pain feat a
melfo fc 4 re bird black wonder degree premium wonder swan
asn ios wii world green states 1
hmm
no no no no I'm going to beat
it and choose a spar but if I draw a guard it was my mother
hahahaha
Baseball Day
Aoya Nove love  Paying course walk The cause of the family in the family in is the cause of
Isara Costume Large Dobone Boin Stage Piles and the Mitsume
Mitsume Mercun's Color
s Naremasu Mitsuko
Ryumi Cleaner Darker's Sky Quartz Today Supreme Dowser Work Proposal Ping Game Speed
Interview Volley Cheeks Mother Sister 13 R 4 will be used nuh also Bauter
peep Friend will play with play attached 4 Play with garden peep with clip teaser included 4  air
fighter with a
word useful down prevention insight
in to do 4 points Yusuke Tomizawa
voodoo 4 soe s ah
Hey ridere bank ru delivery see a st ste remeber
pair's safety
post with ayu scan 4 b way peshin tantan koiteppa meeting
ana lenses for san
ah
nao show first dane
branches wo pe no r end
[music  ]
VOODOO Puta Pu -Ster
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
This painting on nerf gate not to do the
boss of Bo Pressure Awards,
then the breathing sound of the pyonboner is good, but the game eason 9 minutes,
10 furspember dice charger,
use the format evenly, ice-
cha-san in the show  pain scum form ice love guy and pain
to do good
voodoo
3 compatible yes
office web author play to compensate the legislator eh one point
maybe even know me under wear with  Me,
Katane
baby, it's amazing to practice every day.Muririn's Buddhist media level is good scope
channel.Sky's division is
good.Come on, fear.I'm an orphan cover comedian.
Even your stereo
Zoo Artpolis outside rice and now you're talking about one day and talking about
buying a phone
voodoo as par enos girly
up view spa pointer for  pc you do
nai
usp speech check p 100 a seat to do
rearrange rearea 4 te & scarf denver to do
nya
pop enjoy rate 4 always good chair see us to manneran
areas 1 to 6 after game position ape apes  wedge
spoon
rear edcb prefecture funny car minute
dx pink janjan only upon saa queen queen ppc
boops par afip 4 xp xxx  Pack session
Ochai and pet bloomers are terrible
2 dark promise spa sports up promotion characteristics
Sent EX pack line
Yeah
get the plan Ha
ha ha
Ebetsu palm good day bemoi
ana
Soba Mochama 5th place game
Fashion 5  s to do anman dohu dua
[music]
pe k
or 2
[music]
n
eme
[music]
n n
boo boo n
n
[music]
Hmm
[Music]
Whoop
Hmm
[Music]
Minutes
Hmm
Boof