[Music]
do
hello
[Music]
wow
wow welcome everyone for the first ever
full whole live english collaboration
wonderful i hear a lot of motivated met
crewmates only crewmates of course
oh let's not talk about it
we're going to talk about it especially
about you finally it doesn't matter if
you hide behind that little
glossy
potted plant
[Music]
i see a green root
are you good
i just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little uh
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then uh after a little while we had no
reports which was kind of says so father
did an emergency meeting um just to you
know because she was obviously scared
and which i was too
um
she reported okay she did an emergency
meeting and then what what do we see
free deaths
of course she's not sucks because she
made the meeting but turns out she was
the imposter how reckless is that
not to mention she kills
people so easily
was my imposter and she got voted out in
the first round immediately immediately
stand up live as an imposter was so
short
yeah
your stream hasn't started yet
oh no are you swinging
oh my god i'm surprised you even noticed
[Music]
um
people
[Music]
all right then um so i would like to get
some introductions from everyone and any
stream up yet
[Music]
oh
introduction can you all go girls give
me a reason why you are not suss today
starting from emilia go
oh why i'm not obsessed today um
okay
um hello everybody i'm amelia watson
hello live english miss number one
detective and um i'm not wearing pants
is
okay not it's us so next up bae your
introduction please and why you know
what we're gonna get
is about across our council representing
chaos everybody how you doing can you
stop
[Laughter]
[Music]
look at my pet oh yeah
you were just a little hamster
i mean you bought it with real money
for real human dollars
i saw the hamster thing and i was like i
gotta i got it
i used isn't that one of your kind of
your hamster
cause like
[Music]
wow that's kind of kind of weird what
what interesting
all right um so yeah um death is real
sus but guess what everyone i'm not
death i'm the sheriff around these parts
and because i'm the sheriff the sheriff
is never suss the sheriff obviously
didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
uh i don't know what that means it just
has something to do with the sheriff and
uh
[Laughter]
there wasn't enough room for for me to
spell it correctly
[Laughter]
who's next
no my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
you
oh
no no no plant has never killed anyone
little chocolate horrors does it ever
never i remember that musical
oh i remember
all right
yes um my name is grant almost
here what's up everybody oh i'm not such
because
um
[Music]
likely
it's iris live english project hub video
slash free singer
uh
i am very excited i
am a hundred percent say so i would
never lie which is why i would never be
suss
sorry
explains everything i would never i
would
[Music]
that's not what happened to my fox
yesterday
um
a very very um
good self-introduction while other
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
is
okay
again cronie please give us your
introduction
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro
from
the council
and
i am blue
[Music]
um it seems like your senpai has stolen
your color
but i'm a more royal color royal blue
[Music]
okay don't look at the color objectively
look at the color that's inside all of
us oh
[Music]
um
wait did cronie say why she's nuts us oh
right i'm not sus because look at this
i'm wearing a mask i'm doing my uh part
in this situation don't get close to
me well i tried to social distance but
i'm not suns because i'm doing my part
in the society
and
honey
i'm an upholding
i knew it i knew we were gonna get
kicked out again
hi chad how are you doing
that's a fun fun day for
uh setting up a lobby three times before
we actually get started
oh boy
all right you guys don't get to see the
code
i think hold on
all right
uh copy
paste
are we good oh could not find the game
you're looking for that's great
this whole
whole situation is a little sus
e and law they say
welcome back it's too late
yeah there we go
there we go
bye we're back my mic
what's up okay
[Music]
time is almost on time
please
i am the guardian of civilization and i
am an apex predator of the sky and i
could kill you if i wanted to
that's right
that's not how you defend yourself that
is that that is the most nonsense
introduction ever yeah
but i don't want to so i won't
okay
i believe that because you are so
peaceful
like
[Music]
um
the
priestess of the ancient ones
i
think and uh
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh i am not sucked because i'm already
dead look at the the halo above my head
i'm already dead inside
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you ina
next up sanna is not streaming but she's
here so please let us know who you are
[Music]
um hi hi i'm sana sugama from honey life
english council it's been a while hello
guys
[Music]
i have a big limiter on my head
let me turn yes
if anybody thinks i'm a sauce i'm going
to take it off and take all of you down
with me
that's really reassuring back into back
into the space where you belong right or
you're a part of it
you should be fine you should be fine if
you get kicked out i have no i have no
reason to
oh um well
i'm very happy to have you here shana
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you
and of course
we'll be
back soon so we can all look forward to
her streams
[Music]
and
i am the one organizing this and i'm
really happy that we could all get
together 11 people is a lot but we're
gonna have a lot of fun today so let's
get right into it are you girls ready to
be
thank you kiara thanks for organizing
here
three
two
one
[Music]
hmm
um
hello
i'm in the void
[Music]
i feel like something is wrong with my
own longest
oh
yeah
under hold on
i think everyone else is fine right
i think so
let me try uh
um
okay
one second
oh my
absolutely ballsy coming out the first
stream with the lights on with multiple
people around what was that about wow
who came out
[Music]
it looked like either iris or bay area
wait hold on i am black screened again
we just got started should we do a new
vlog i don't know if it's gonna be any
better though
i'll try fixing it but
maybe i don't know maybe reinstall among
us or something like that because you
had that before
we can't we can restart
we can restart we can restart
where did you spawn where were i
sorry about that chat i'm gonna
start uh
let's try to fix this
it worked completely fine before but i
don't know it's wrong
i'm gonna cut the stream for now until i
fix it sorry you guys can go check out
uh
everyone else's
stream for now
we're back
you guys can still sign the chat if i
fix it i'll come back
okay
hello i thought just wait here with you
guys
it's fine
[Music]
how are you
just in the void with me
oh well
thanks missed you guys
i don't know when their game is gonna
end so
money
how am i doing uh
i don't know
it's not been a great day i'll just
leave it like that
ah we have our good days and bad days
[Music]
um
it's just not my day
need to
go
are all good i don't know are we ever
fine
well now i can even connect to the
servers lovely
huh
sorry i'm damn still trying to get in
the room but
oh it just doesn't like me i don't like
either
i know they're done they're typing in
the
just gotta make sure i hide the screen i
just got in
wait
hello hello
hello
okay good good good
[Music]
yeah there's a code
sorry about the
sorry about the mess guys
oh
i'll be honest i just wanna go back to
bed
this is really frustrating
did
two
let's talk in here until uh
ina gets finds her way in
talents
uh new code
mm-hmm no i really hope it works in this
chord until you know it's here
okay
otherwise she's being she's gonna be in
silence the whole time that's true
hello hello hello maybe we should make
uh let ina make the room maybe ah
yeah yeah nope this one doesn't work
this one doesn't work it works for me
mummy got in wait let me try
but
[Music]
yeah can you try making a lobby
oh yeah okay yeah yeah let's you might
get the same error
because i got the same error uh when i
tried to creating the lobby before the
stream many times
just try again again again
i mean angels do get nerfed in this game
the more evil you are
the better connection you have
oh wait my ping is fifth oh
that's why that's why my ping is not
that not that good
it's cause i'm half angel guys don't
worry the angel side of me is nerfing me
in this game
yes
oh on the screen when typing code that's
right
looks like where
ina
i'm still having trouble making the room
too so it's just my connection to the
server
yeah
maybe maybe we can try i i don't really
think it's closer but let's try maybe an
asian server
we can we can try
do you want to try you know or should uh
maybe you guys can try someone else can
try making it
okay i'll make one i ate in asia
everyone change them okay
oh yeah
okay
code is
oh wait are should we not is playing
this on stream
i'm not saying it okay coda's code
the code
the code is code okay
oh d
e and at the end is an f
[Applause]
[Music]
um though if if i end up block screen
again just just go on without me it's
fine i don't want to hold everyone else
uh
[Music]
what
this is a full ian collab and it would
not be full without you around
[Music]
missing gaza oh yeah
come on come on cheers
[Applause]
[Music]
where are we dropping boys
hello oh what's this
oh
[Music]
oh god why are you so scared of me i'm
not dead
hello
i don't know
look check this check this you can see
where people are right
she can vouch i didn't do that yeah
i don't know where anything is i've
never played this map
it is not bad
hello
oh hello
hey don't don't kill me okay okay
gonna say can i do
[Music]
the only thing i can say about that is
that i heard kelly's voice close by for
a moment but
that was like i i didn't even see her
close by i only found the body like a a
few moments later wait where did you
find the body uh the very bottom
[Music]
the bottom area but i wasn't i wasn't
doing anything i was like looking for a
task to do well why were you not doing
tasks i don't think you're done with
tasks we just got started there's a lot
of tasks i doubt it it's a bit i don't
know how to play the game
[Music]
i saw him coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom
left side cali passed by me
that's very funny hahaha time to kill
hahaha
together but kelly went off pretty
yeah i was pretty lost
i was pretty lucky
stick around with anybody around but
callie just went zoo
well
she went
like doing my tasks if you oh really you
just said that you did you weren't doing
any tests now you said you weren't doing
the tasks
[Laughter]
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab to open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks
very easy tap tap
okay i was like i was like looking back
and forth between the map
i don't know though i'm not
voting tab
yeah i'm not sure
i'm okay i'm skipping i'm skipping
really we're skipping okay okay
um
did you vote
yeah i voted
that's enough to throw me out
is it
[Music]
okay so
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh well okay
girl i'm scared
i'm i'm scared i don't know where
anything is
cockpit
ah
[Music]
crash course
[Applause]
[Music]
oh someone got it someone got it okay
yeah
oh it's not here
i'm so lost i'm so lost
this whole game and i haven't seen any
dead bodies
i
did you finish your tasks no no i have
one here i think yeah this is a very
huge map i'm really interesting
yeah
i'm not used to this either oh
oh you can go into the bathroom stuff
oh
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
what what toilet door
i was in the
the cockpit
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom
um
we used a toilet
please
but it was locked for me
um because when i found iris's body
right as i hit report the door the
bathroom door closed what someone
someone hid in the bathroom stop you can
do that
i can't vouch for santa at least
i don't know i'm just lost everywhere
kitchen i was trying to put the egg on
the uh the frying pan
egg in the frying pan
okay
i was tracking her and she was muttering
to herself
walking to
[Music]
talking to them so they didn't have to
listen to nothing
are you guys just walking around
completely silent sounds kind of like
this
though i was trying to talk to you no
i'm just trying to chat because i'm
what i was talking to
where were you i was also in i was in
the area below in the bathroom i was
doing the test where you pick everything
up off the floor and guru i did see me
there but i didn't go up i came from the
other side someone's in the bathroom
someone's walking in the bathroom put
out a statement
[Music]
i don't know where it was i was just
lost
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom wait
when we spawn back in while i see you
come out no
all right in the yeah beginning i
spawned with uh ina and fawful i can
vouch for
[Music]
i just remembered
yeah just because you spawn with them
you can't vouch for them i mean i was
running around with sana at one point
lost okay okay
i don't know well found us us for now
okay
but are you guys really just not talking
oh we're talking i think
i'm just crying because i'm lost
silence
i'm still lost
[Music]
oh
milan in the bridge oh
what is this place
it's the vault
such a big big map
can you go on this
oh you can
oh
hello i am just hello
i'm just a
lonely lonely soul
lost
lying to records
hi
i'm so long
wait i am also lost
to the records
[Music]
where's kelly
wait
where's this place
wait that's super sucks that is so sus
what is it
i'm going to call an emergency meeting
what happened
do we look at this thing hey what
happened finish my task
um i was uh in the top right area that's
like uh before the wreck
right yeah around the records area
and um when i was about to enter the
rankings area i saw cali so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her and
next moment she completely disappeared i
went i went into all other like like
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared so what no she walked out of
the room
man you can vouch for me i went down to
the bottom and tried to go through the
vent and i couldn't hi partner
[Laughter]
what i mean is there was a vent down
there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's what i meant
[Music]
went down at the bottom i was trying to
go to the crying
i was trying to go right now
that's the second time that she says the
second time that i'm just saying that's
the second time wow for me she just
wants to she just wants me to get thrown
out
has a bandana i don't know
takamori being tested right now
what else would you call this [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting kiara
could be a next level imposter tactic is
true
[Music]
so i'm gonna vote
[Laughter]
[Music]
last time it wasn't me either i'm just
saying you were stressing me last time
but it wasn't wait why does oh actually
it's fine
oh no
i'm scared
[Music]
i am
can go to the kitchen with me
after
okay
here
how do i get
wait
oh this is the engine she's really
called for me now
funny no don't kill hello
let me go to the uh meetings
yes
what yes
having so much fun here
three because i finally found a way up
here
oh yeah i didn't know you could use the
ladder beginning of the game
is this a fire pole
like what emergency meaning
if you're ever looking for it here it is
oh that's where it is that's really far
yeah is okay
okay
okay oh there's so many of you
[Music]
which i normally
[Laughter]
i was just wearing my crowns and i found
it in the kitchen
[Music]
this whole time so like we i think we
can vouch for each other um we saw at
the end right before the body was
reported we saw ina and gura together uh
yeah carol's with us too actually
yeah yeah
they're fine they're all fine
[Music]
which kind of leaves them
[Laughter]
sheriff you kidding me
well
trying to save her reputation
by reporting the body she killed trying
to look like
[Music]
someone and then report them immediately
yeah you can now why would you ever do
that
um but we also gotta remember we haven't
killed off an imposter yet because all
of these are the bodies that we found oh
[\h__\h]
in here
okay
hello all right well i don't like you
pointing the finger at me i think that's
suspicious so i'm gonna point it right
back at you
i'm sorry here shove it off on your boy
i'm just trying to be a good [\h__\h]
sheriff
i'm sorry sheriff i'm interested sorry
are you kidding me kelly it's it's
nothing personal it's just i'm loving
this
this is beautiful
[Applause]
i don't know
last time
it isn't now
son is awfully quiet and so is moon mae
what do you guys do yeah
[Music]
why would i could have killed you if you
guys were alone i did [\h__\h] nothing
anyone who would vouch for callie is
there anyone listen
i haven't seen kelly either he's the one
who's leading me
why are you pointing the finger at me i
don't think i can vote you haven't seen
me
[Laughter]
yeah i don't think it's kelly
i really don't i did at this point
everyone had something about someone
vouching for them except cat
oh
excuse me hello
[Music]
wait
i'm scared
hello scared
um
[Music]
i don't know
okay i'll try walking this way i don't
know
[Music]
don't leave me
wait no we gotta go fix that this way
[Music]
oh it's right here okay
is this on it
oh yeah yeah okay okay we got it we got
it
we've been here awfully long
no i was right i got the button wrong
you know i did the wrong thing
hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
no spacebar
i knew it i'm a little stuck
oh my path's done by the way i'm going
to save a few girls
okay i have holly i think we know who it
is
[Music]
oh wait oh no lights
hi
oh wait
ah
wait got it oh wait wait got it
okay i'm going to
electrical
okay engine engine engine
no
i'm lost
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no i was with everyone for a long
time
no no
no you weren't with us
i understand that i've been on my own
but and i understand i will be voted out
but it was kiara and it was ina why why
was it me and why why yeah what was it
me and kyra
she says
why why it was a theory
do i dare say
what do you mean
you know what to say well ina kept
saying that she was lost and i thought
that it was
suspicious
i mean this is my first time in the
i don't know where anything is please
describe please describe with your own
words the uh past tasks that you have
been done doing
what was the last house that you did the
last one i did was the one where i had
to dress up a mannequin
and then i had to use the card
and i kept having to do the card i don't
know i'm going with my gut
and going with my gut feeling i'm gonna
grow my guts too even though it has been
awfully quiet it's a good analogy
it has been really quiet hasn't she
i think it's even worse
okay i think i don't know
[Laughter]
no no no
[Music]
no no it's not over
wait oh my god no you guys are so sad
no that's that's that must be
[Music]
okay
okay we got it we got it we got it
carol i'm scared
no don't come here reba
are you sure are you sure yeah how do
you prove that that's not you it's
either you or kiara it's either
[Music]
that was not that was not your boy's
victory that was definitely
using that i don't know how to play the
game card so i'm kind of glad i got
killed but ina deserved you know
oh god i don't think i can use that i
don't know how to play the game card
anymore
[Music]
okay yeah so i have a question so when
you're imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
uh
you know what but
like if you're doing certain like if
you're acting to do tasks that should be
probably longer because there's really
long time
um
[Music]
that was so kitty
well we did it chat we did it
that's the one
i can't use that card anymore if you
want to press tab okay
let me see what i can do i don't know
this game i haven't played
can you
give us a statement of how you were able
to hide your imposter-ness for so long
um
i blended in with the crowd you know
even if i could make the kill i i waited
for my chance i was
patiently believable
i still don't know where anything is but
yeah i got watched the performance was
so genuine you actually
[Music]
i asked you not to kill me and you said
okay that was okay those were my last
words
last week
is everyone's here in could you hear me
after i feel like the game was said
[Laughter]
okay
oh i wish i was an imposter
i'm going to go to the kitchen
okay
hey tall
oh my goodness the showers
right
this is my innocence
[Music]
i have the mega yes self report cause
you panicked uh excuse me i have a
question
was the shark near the washroom no no it
was at this time okay i saw i was with
and i saw kiara go left and then i saw
guru was also in the room that kiara
went that was right
i don't know that doesn't mean it wasn't
inna i wanted a movie can watch for me
movie can watch for me she was right
behind me
it was right behind me you were by
yourself in electrical because i was no
no no
i was humming the berries in cream tune
and i was like i know we're electrical
that's where you killed me last time
uh-huh
[Music]
did i stop by the washroom i spawned and
i spawned in the place with the folder
on the table and i went right down to
electrical i don't remember how what's
happening never stopped by the washroom
that's pretty much my fault how was that
i just thought
every time you were innocent you would
do something in the washer
she wasn't in the washroom hmm she
wasn't in the washroom
we just spawned it i don't know i'm
pretty i'm pretty convinced
can i can i have a moment starting to
stink cause
very demanding of the room's attention i
don't know it was so obvious
that i walked in on you
i don't know you're
feeling very distinctive yeah i have
nothing to say about any
please i would love to have a follower
[Music]
i mean it's still early in the game i'll
i'll keep an eye out
i remember
oh
oh yeah yeah rub that soap oh yeah
oh yeah
here remember guys hello cody zombie
hello
hello hello oh so does that mean it's
probably great
i
oh thanks
appreciate that like a buddy
all right but i would like to not be get
obsessive with the
i don't know with a good relationship
yeah no no no no no no i'm gonna watch
you girl i'm gonna watch you girl no no
no no no no no no well then i'm gonna
have you
okay
begging you around
[Music]
ah
i swear i swear babe
trust me
please protect me
uh to go to
oh i can't go from here huh
how do you put the meeting room from
here yeah
try
this
tasks
oh that's not it it's up here
ah
[Music]
gap room
oh
oh it's not here
[Music]
this way
where's the other one
[Music]
what
i don't know
go away shark go away shark
[Music]
no
okay okay someone got this
sauce
okay we've both been stop following me
stop following me
i'm scared i trust you
i'll trust any of you
i'm gonna i can't i gotta go this way
oh it's going this girl
oh
[Music]
oh my god what happened what happened
the writing was freaking me out a little
bit too she's been acting kind of sucks
what happened
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she's
[Music]
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know you
go for that kill
yeah she was insane
okay how is it okay that ina keeps watch
of you for protection but it's not okay
if i do that i don't know but unlikely
it should when in the very first round
when i reported when i reported ina
absolutely flipped her story and went
from the super meek i don't know where
i'm going to suddenly super loud i don't
know as if she's trying to protect
herself
to be honest i don't trust either of you
so
neither no okay that's fair
what both y'all were a little suspicious
okay okay
is that you're suspicious of both of us
and not one versus the other thing
you know she went to go do a task and
she ignored me yeah i was at the top
just now
but she did it but she might have been
here
when i cool
was because i kept bumping into her
every time
uh it was just three of us in total so
if one person uh left
it would just be two of us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina and i don't have a trophy
and i wanted somebody to be
my
watch mm-hmm
okay so wait are we still we're being
trying going together then
are we skipping
thanks for now there's still a reason to
design i don't know
put my vote on guru i don't really have
a reason so
i don't know
[Music]
i don't know being real
real aggressive here girl we're really
trying to put it on here
[Music]
yeah
she
still need to go to the meeting room
er
i'm really not good with maps
not here
and
lights
okay oh
hello
wait where's like those lights oh
someone got it ready okay
[Music]
sana
okay
[Music]
oh oh you can't go past this oh i was
just blocked by a
block fire
blocked by a wall
da da
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
bottom right
i just want to say something crazy that
girls and the clear have been uh
following her around and
i think i saw her alibi before
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
does that mean
so i'm pretty sure she's in the clear
too
santa's also in the clear we saw each
other and didn't kill each other so i
think son is okay as well
so girl you really could have killed me
that it's ina though
i mean i've ran into so many people i
have so many chances i didn't kill
anyone
what is your name no it's not let me
answer the question thank you the
microphone is in my hand uh because at
the very beginning of the match i was
singing the berries and cream song and i
went into electrical and right then and
there ina
beheaded that person
the story's changed get out okay
nice job detective you can't read your
own handwriting it didn't change i
[Music]
yeah yeah iris isn't in the
last time i saw crony
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
um so that was when the lights were
turned out
and i saw cali freaking out when i was
nearby
all right well i don't know what to do
so i'm gonna skip freaking out wait um
there's definitely still i think we have
no reason to make enemies you found the
body yeah
where'd you find it yeah where the
mannequins are
oh
watson why weren't you there flying
so easily
what do you mean
you're pointing a lot of fingers
you're really cool yeah you know
[Music]
no no you teased me i'm lying when i
didn't okay
i don't know she accused enoch and i
don't know
the story you didn't accuse her of
killing you just said she was more
suspicious yeah but now i absolutely saw
her cut this is my mic cutting out
[Music]
[Laughter]
not yet right my next task is in the
viewing deck
okay
okay what what's where's your next test
mine is actually a medical but
okay i'll take along you can go you can
go to medical go
okay
i was watching the security cameras and
ina and iris iris leading ina behind
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only ina came out
and then cronie came in and i said hi
cronie and then nina came in and i said
oh crony i'm gonna go see that body that
ena just left in there and lo and behold
there was the body of iris
oh well that's a very convincing you
know what was saying you in your defense
long live the taco
[Laughter]
wow girl i'm sorry i died did you holy
[\h__\h]
i feel bad i mean i never i never voted
against you
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around and i think that was
good enough for this round
i lost it this long
who's the other imposter huh
and why is it amelia watson no it's not
farewell
i haven't killed anybody
[Music]
a chance
to kill me
maybe i hadn't also had a chance to kill
me so neither of them are safe
watch somebody stay with me next round
you'll see
some got you good
[Music]
last time i was in the kitchen i died so
i don't want to do that again
all right where is everyone
not this i am dead of course i'm dead
because she's kino hi yeah
one question yes you can hear me now
right yeah i can i was following you
around and yelling at you but you didn't
hear me oh no i didn't
is it in the office
correctly though you should hear me okay
well i'm done with
yeah imposters you're
oh yeah oh yeah i'm like you the
imposter i got
oh yeah
sure
body over here
let the bodies hit the
bunnies at the foot
oh they got it
come on
what about here
sidetrack
scream crony scream
one okay so did any of you guys have
experience with
this mod like um does everyone
need to have the same
settings or only the person who makes
the lobby question chat is that's the
only room
uh
oh you can only change this in the
middle i changed my story when i did it
i never said that you actually saw you
know
all right what's their argument you did
see her take off the head and that's why
i thought it was suspicious because it's
kind of a change in the detail because
that's like a pretty big detail
on that side i did say that detail so it
must have been the microphone coming out
because i would not leave out that
detail
oh i need some space you're gonna finish
[Music]
oh
that's so funny
oh man there he is
[Music]
[Laughter]
the whole thing
[Music]
um was like so strong against
the very first round i was like that's
kind of sustainable
[Laughter]
you know right
yeah we can't even if enough is the crew
i'm just like maybe we should just vote
here
it's not my fault but can you give me an
imposter twice in her home
[Music]
next round
you know
can i ask anyone one question
does everyone have impostors here dead
uh checked because yeah work last round
i think it's the only person
i'm i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean
i died purely but that's the same
okay
only the host can change it yeah so
everyone should be the same
[Music]
play some classic music while you go all
the idols are here
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
hey
yet
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
no
[Applause]
[Music]
my
oh she's back
i was gonna pull up my recorder soon
it's definitely me all right cool cool
cool
is now suss
please what does it never mean you know
why is it about me why is it never you
why is it never mean wasn't it you
practiced
i even needed a stream to practice and
were you imposter then yeah once once
okay it with my memories but now um
i never had the imposter in collabs
you could have given me one of those two
times
is
oh man
i wouldn't mind doing like five more
rounds this is so much fun it is i hate
to kill someone in the washroom right
about now in five seconds
five four three
two
one
oh my god
oh
[Music]
is the elevator thing back
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
exactly
okay
[Music]
are you safe you fooled me twice
right what are you following three times
kitchen kitchen kitchen
because she's been doing tasks alone and
i keep on running into her and i can ask
for uh
as a detective a beacon of the law i
clear cali and gouda uh from being uh
imposters as i was with me and bae um
watson at the end i was trying to open
the door i couldn't open it
you're an impossible stupid card no the
card
who can't do something
a room
i don't
i have nothing to base my conjecture on
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's talking to you right now huh
oh
i see
[Music]
yeah i think i'm gonna skip but i'm able
to clean my hands
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i thought iris would be here because
she said cracker like it's hot
no
hello
wouldn't it be weird if you thought
imposter three times in a row
what are the chances huh
bye-bye
my uh
my
[Music]
i found ray in
we were alone and she could have killed
me but she just went off and did her
test
kindly howdy and i went on my way i saw
kiara and we were on the left side of
the map so this kill couldn't have been
kiara but i think it was the other
imposter who might i didn't even see you
know
[Music]
i was trying to get to the whatever it
was sabotage i forgot what was crash
course or whatever
i was in records but uh i didn't see
anything it was records
mm-hmm i was in records
[Music]
table with the folder on it that's the
wrecking room
yeah like i walked in from what wait i'm
not so sure anymore um
[Laughter]
[Music]
if you didn't see me but i'm pretty i
thought it was records it's like
describe it mm-hmm i don't remember
anymore it was but i'm pretty sure it
was records uh like are you sure i've
been there
no it's not then i take my vote back
where are the showers i don't even know
where the shower is pretty close to the
showers it's pretty close
and who are you voting for
with the
huh i don't even know where the showers
are waiting i don't know um
you haven't heard a lot from mumei or
ina yeah isn't it closer
okay i spawned in kitchen with mummy and
then i went to do my task in the uh the
bottom left thing of course called
uh so our suspects are iris and kiara
got it
i don't know usually usually the camera
would be like deducting and like
doing stuff but i don't know
can vote vouch for me right
i mean you didn't kill me
yeah and we were up there at the top of
the room where it's really easy to kill
people well i didn't and the sheriff's
got the same thing
though i'm sorry we have 10 seconds oh
i don't know i'm gonna trust my gun
[Music]
um i'm just gonna
i didn't i wasn't very convinced by iris
i was not convinced what's your problem
i don't know you usually like have like
if when you're on your crew that you
usually have like a whole like list of
things to like deduct but
i must have cut off i got to say usually
when you're crew man you have like a
whole bunch of like uh deductions in a
row but you're real quiet
oh she's gone okay
[Music]
don't follow me
okay
yeah
so
[Music]
don't like that why are you two
following me no i don't know
i'm keeping watch on iris
oh you're you're one of my suspects
we're gonna die
oh hi everyone oh hi
hello
keep your distance please please go wait
don't show this this thing is
where is iris going
[Music]
thank you
why are you thinking
why were you thanking ina nothing
nothing no no no no um why were you
thanking ina iris
[Music]
now we know who it is
right interesting let's uh i guess
uh yeah
that sounds about right
what no hold on
wait wait wait wait wait kiara's dead
yeah i guess
i need to you need to hear me out right
now okay so i was doing my favorite task
the potty task right elbow deep in the
toilet
and
uh kiara came in
and nina came in
kiara is now dead i was the one that
found iris's body because i left because
kiara and i said haha i did the sucky
toilet okay guys bye bye
and then i stumbled onto i was his body
and now he's
dead i was with um i was with ina and
iris and kiara and i left and i saw
callie and then now kiara is dead so
that will tell you
um
yeah i think that's good
i think it's either who are we voting
for uh iris or inaudible
[Music]
i don't know i'm trying to think
it was me kiara and anna and literally
seconds afterwards unless somebody came
in between them
yeah
i think it's iris too i haven't oh i
haven't voted wait uh
um i just voted for ina though guys so
if you wanna
make sure that we
yeah it's definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we vote off
um for each of us and then
we could call a report and then vote
somebody
[Music]
skip it
what the heck
[Music]
emergency meeting
i mean yes do it do it what did i say
about the law of pain
[Music]
um i'm not sure which one of you killed
me
i probably was iris but i guess it was
you ah hello
[Music]
it happened so fast
when you were like when you were like oh
how can i never get impossible i'm just
like
[Music]
i don't know i think it usually does
that um
among us like when someone like when you
play with other friends like sometimes
when you
it was just just now
oh they're are they running for the
what's going on
where'd they go
oh
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh man what a game
[Music]
well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
such a good i'll be a good girl the rest
of
you did them best
[Music]
[Laughter]
see my theories have been really
accurate
[Music]
gg
are we going back to discord i think so
yeah
this is
[Music]
yeah you know it kind of gets like it
kind of gets questionable when you get
it three times people don't even like
trust you off the bat so
it's harder as the game's going along
yeah you keep me three times yeah
i feel like i feel like among us does
that it keeps giving imposter to like
the same people
yeah yeah i was really surprised that
like you would assume that you would
assume that the reaper would be like the
number one killer of everyone but i'm
actually just the task master why yeah
i'm like
i do like the task
oh yeah i don't want to ask me kelly you
are so scared of death
i know right because i don't like yeah
exactly we'll see that's the thing is
death can't die so the prospect of death
dying becomes a thing it's quite
frightening
i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views
oh yes
everyone's fun yeah yeah
ghost club yeah the property is great
[Applause]
yeah i was like i was like okay if we
get a double kill like like this is good
but i couldn't say anything so i was
just trailing you around
i was like
but i didn't know i didn't know if you
were on cooldown or not so no no
that's why like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and then i see you went
somewhere else was like oh no no the
double kill and then i think yeah
[Laughter]
but you know at the same time like you
know the senpai's i i can't i can't go
and kill my senpais right away off the
bat
[Music]
you can savor the kill huh
right here i like that i like that way
of life good good
one well okay girls i'm gonna go through
everyone from top to bottom again to
give a goodbye one by one and maybe tell
me your favorite moment from today or
your favorite kill or whatever so let's
start with amelia watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite time that's your
favorite kill from today
okay uh thank you guys for watching and
thank you kiara for uh setting it up
again and organizing everything and my
favorite moment
uh i really liked messing with callie
that was fun yeah
i gotta admit that was pretty cool
you mean i mean saying that she's the
imposter what happened no she would just
outright say things like like i'd be
like are you gonna kill me she'd be like
yeah you're lucky my cool down is off
and like run away
that's another one for the archives for
me okay oh thank you amelia nixon bales
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again
thank you very much
my favorite moment wasn't actually in
game um it was when i went to have an
idol meeting and
the thing wasn't mayhem
i like it what was going on someone
please explain you know when you go to
the bathroom and then they play the
classic music bring music to your idol
meeting yeah yeah yeah
yeah it was it was like
that
was pretty familiar yeah
yeah without chaos to manage chaos
that's chaotic
it's even more chaotic when chaos is not
there and that's such a sad thing
it's very soon just to wait how what
freaking what
oh i'm not wait i i don't need to wait
right i mean you can
get a room
[Music]
my favorite moment has to be um when i
was trying to hold up the the cell phone
to get the cell service on the deck
where anyone could have killed me and i
saw sana come up behind me and i was
like holy [\h__\h] this is where i die
i was like oh hey callie and she just
walked away and she's like no i have to
do my task here and i was like okay so
we just switched spaces and we like
watched out for each other it was kind
of cool it's a bonding moment i was like
oh really
[Laughter]
yeah
it was really fun
thank you next up for fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and i
really appreciate it
uh my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
yeah i don't know i i think i prefer
indian posture too
being impostor is just so much pressure
it is
and especially
you can't really say anything because
yeah i said whatever i wanted
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you
i'm fine i'm fine i was saying i was
talking to my chat though about like how
i don't usually i don't have
conversations i don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not it's kind of like it feels
very draining uh mentally i guess
i don't like yelling at my friends
my favorite moments were
uh and i i'm asking clippers please uh
the various perfectly cut screams with
the proximity chat cali specifically
where everybody was terrified of me and
every time somebody would walk by me it
would just be blood kidding
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
uh complacement of some sort if there
are enough people yeah
you had a good one too
for putting this together thank you
thank you
my pleasure
i was
[Music]
thank you so much for organizing this
wonderful collab camera i love among us
to
i'm so glad bits was able to do this and
i i i would go for among us like off
stream anytime if we had enough people
i wouldn't like it yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
and also like
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me um i
really liked how callie you know when
she found fona's body was like it was me
boys
[Laughter]
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words
yeah that was my personal favorite
genuine very fun game
all the time
when you're imposter though i was i was
playing safe i was like okay if i get
all the aggro so maybe the other
imposter can go on a killing spree
i'm probably going to have to be
aggressive so yeah i've been going
killing and killing yeah
aggression is the way to go but i was
trying to clear my name and that was how
i got out trying too hard to clear my
name
i was yelling in her ear the whole time
amelia just laughing a ghost in my ear
oh yeah crony next doll
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
oh no no thank you so much for arranging
this
that's fine we don't need it yeah
freebie gm
the freebie gm
thank you so much to kiara
uh for arranging this i really love this
game and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
and
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so
thank you for that um
hello
thank you kiara for
organizing everything everyone says that
while you're
thank you please continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with you
i turned and i said wouldn't it be
something if you're the imposter three
times
she's like yeah that really would be she
just walked away
i was exploding i was like yeah it would
be really funny what didn't it be
absolutely drenched in sweat
you know has so much blood on her hands
today
i don't know i didn't get killed on many
in the last two games
yeah
i wrestled nina was just being very good
at innocence
well then
you know your goodbye and your your
favorite moments who was your favorite
kill maybe
oh well not the best putting a knife
through their stomach
well um it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
uh
uh cronie in the it wasn't the first
game or something where she was like
please don't kill me i was like okay
[Music]
intimidating though because cali was
every time when i was sussing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
he was yelling at me oh i'm sorry no
that's you huh
[Laughter]
no it's you know you reverse
okay
your goodbye and your favorite moment
please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too
i miss your voice
[Music]
we're so happy you are here today
my favorite moment as um
pretty much every time i heard kelly
scream
yes yes
spending time with all of you guys oh
[Music]
i'm sorry i killed you i love you
reckless ruthless you should next time
next time you should uh leave me leave
me alive because i
believe i didn't you guys say
she's so
innocent sorry
all right well um uh for me my favorite
moment one i had so many but i guess the
one that stayed in my head now is um i
think it was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was sussing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really
mad and then ahmed was like well i'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and i was like chilling with
ina as ghosts oh yeah about the better
curling uh just we're standing there
together as ghosts and then ahmed and
guna ran into the room having a huge
fight like this
that was good that was good
they were running in circles yeah
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was
uh
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm sorry
yeah i'm sorry about the
[Music]
was that present today
thanks for organizing it
thank you we love you thank you
thank you for appreciating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes
and there's a blast okay sure we could
do this sometime again in the future
yeah
[Applause]
oh project winter too
christmas is only eight points
really
you can do many people in jack box ah i
mean some of them i think uh one more
thing i kind of want to do is like
because i organized the ian id mario
kart tournament now that we are 11 ends
[Music]
is it just one of the one of the people
are going to be bots is that what it is
yeah well it'll probably be a bot i
think or you can just leave that one out
i think we can just go oh okay
okay
you join as far as mario kart is it time
for another training arc from home gear
let's do it do it time to unlock all the
parts well it is a past 5 a.m for me so
i hope we can uh we'll get our next one
do you have an announcement
sorry an announcement for
oh do you want to announce something oh
yeah yeah yeah
um i have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
uh full collab
focus
[Music]
details are secret for now but uh yeah
now you guys mark it down mommy yeah
girls and friends
yes i need to make that yeah this one
is gonna be amazing
[Music]
i'm just really saying it's genuinely
going to be amazing
yeah this is so much fun yeah
council to hope and oats english
and probably covers everyone
let's do friends
[Music]
okay english chosen
three
two
one
bye
[Applause]
[Music]
i love that thank you
you