[Music]
so
yo yo what up guys
hello thank you my child
i'm fine how are you thank you for the
red super chat thank you wow
yo how are you guys
we are uh how are you give me an answer
give me an answer your mama wants an
answer cleave
yeah yeah privet
good okay okay okay we're tired mama
well that's not my fault
um i would like to announce that
today i have not taken a nap
[Music]
however
however however
when i went downstairs to go take a
shower
and i put my bathrobe uh down
to prepare
[\h__\h] casper ran from
the the area where like my rice bag and
all that [\h__\h] is ran
from there over my foot like for an
instant i felt him on him on my foot
right over me and back into his little
hidey hole
and i legit i i got a [\h__\h] heart
attack i was like
i swear i was even more shook than last
time because this time he was closer and
he even ran
over my foot oh my god
i got like a [\h__\h] heart attack
so i i checked over um
i checked i checked to you know that
that didn't
that just happened two days ago when i
last saw him
what thank you for the super chat
i said i checked two days ago if you
follow my streams
uh closely you should you should know
that i saw him two days ago when i was
having an idol meeting
uh he ran from the same spot to the
other same spot
and that's when i noticed that there was
a hole there and i tried to cover it up
i didn't really have the right materials
to cover it up so
yeah when i checked today it was open
so yeah he opened up the the same hole
um i had some tape and stuff over it but
he didn't give a [\h__\h] about that tape
anyway so i'm calling the professionals
for real i thought that maybe with my
solution i could
i could wait a few days longer but nope
not the professionals have to come
[Music]
on
i'm so sick of it so sick of it
unbelievable and like it was just like a
split second
but i felt kim i was wearing slippers
but i felt him running over my foot
i felt it and that was
that freaked the [\h__\h] out of me that
freaked me out so bad
oh my god casper i'm sorry i love you
but please stop it
please
i do not feel safe
in my home no yeah
anyway um i that that was like two hours
ago
or one and a half hours ago and i feel
i feel um i feel especially
paranoid
[Music]
did i take my medicine i don't think i
did let me take it
oh my god okay we're playing among us
today it has been a while
i don't really i'm not sure if i
remember wait is is my pink what is a
good thing is it hyping a good thing or
is it loping a good thing i'm i'm using
the asian server right now
is is ping 90 like
should i worry about that
loping is good
a 19 is pretty good oh i found a about
19 would already be too high
oh okay okay so i am on the asia server
i don't remember like in the past people
used to say that with certain servers
something is wrong
but i don't really know anymore and i
don't know if that applies right now
anymore
um
oh yes
asa is normal okay how do i go private
what i don't know
what private private okay so
we're playing among us i have to say
this will be my first game in months
so um i i don't know if
i can really remember
much from last time
and also one of my goals today is to not
only play
on the usual the most famous map i also
want to try out again
one of the other maps but in that case
you guys have to have a little bit of
mercy on me
because last time when we tried one of
the other maps
i i got imposter immediately
and because i didn't know the map i
didn't know that i had to fake
doing the the first task at the door i
didn't know it
just because it was my goddamn first
time so so hopefully
i don't become the imposter and
hopefully you guys can teach me a little
bit about
um the other maps but first we start off
with the usual one
actually ah let me turn on this after
all
uh okay so i will show you the
i will show you the code
the rules are ruled
if you join once don't join the lobby
ever again everyone who joined
previously
and other among gameplays is welcome to
join again but only once
okay um
[Music]
and if you are in the game please be so
kind
to not uh watch the stream
turn off the audio turn off the stream
and
be fair be fair be square now i will
read the code
okay jacodo universe
read the conference you guys are going
crazy chill
chill guys chill we have enough time
okay we have enough times
calm the hell down calm down calm down
and rule number three yes tantra always
wins no
rule number three is just to not
troll and be an [\h__\h] and
vote me out for absolutely no reason
because then
the stream will be just over like what
if i can't play then there's i'm not
telling you guys to give me special
treatment i'm just telling you guys to
give me a normal treatment okay thank
you
so the code is never called you must
see like charlie uh
j like jasmine l like
lemons e like
europe zed like zebra f like something f
f
there we go
well there we go okay we have judas we
have a kiana sim we have chakra of
motion motion
kfb franz ay lmao dude you were the
first one hella quick
and wild card so we are 10 out of 10.
welcome everyone
oh yeah he says asian oh hello
well hello eggs
and close the stream plus
i haven't played in a while
so please go easy on me thanks
mate why okay
ready skip school to play
go go
that's not good also should i turn off
my oh wait you guys don't have an ingame
money we want an in-game money don't we
uh wait a second where's mine
[Music]
here we go we want in-game audio but do
you guys want complete silence besides
that
like we have my my usual music on
the background a little bit is it fine
now
this be okay for you guys this audience
me too mate good volume
okay but you hear the game plops pops
too
oh no i'm so sorry guys oh my god
i'm so sorry guys will they ever make it
in again
wait how why is it what what what the
hell what what what
what what what it doesn't go out here
ah
too bad guys well
okay um i'll tell you the new codes
f like frank w like
w b like boy
oh like orlando i like italy f like f
oh wait it's pretty much you say
like a lot of the same people well i
guess you guys are just insanely fast
sorry well let's go
okay took someone's spot it's okay they
can try to come in again
okay and how do i start again okay
the big the big start right there
is that is that rule thingy uh
no god
oh this is great i hope they have the
the stream closed is the real thing
in the way
[Music]
well i mean maybe this is easy because
at least i don't have any
um you know
any any any any there we go
uh keanu plays the game kiara
immediately forgets how to speak english
at least i don't have any ugly uh not
obligations what is what's
what am i trying to say at least i don't
have to focus on actually doing
something except killing someone
um which is not exactly my strong suit
oh oh yeah oh my god i have to go here
help me though
yes this is pc version of course it is
um uh
i was doing lights with someone
wait who was with me anyway
uh what so where where was this dude
what
who who reported anyway okay and she
says it wasn't storage
do i really care though i was dark so i
don't saw anyone
but
it was dark so wait it actually is so
dark that you don't see anyone
who is uh the other wild card okay i saw
yellow doing something in storage but it
was a while ago uh-huh
my casper jfp casper's not part of
jfp jfp sus
because albedo
jeff is always sus
don't don't trust jfp
i don't know skip skip volume
i don't think we were gonna get anything
out of this
i don't quite feel like um i am playing
my role
well just yet but
i skipped p scale of b
well that's it that's funny
well no one was no one was kicked out
nice
nice okay
wait wait oh i wanted to move off the
mouse but i remembered
i don't move with the mouse i'm going
away bye-bye
the i hope the other imposter is good at
their job because i'm definitely not
also i don't even know how to vent
can i see where other people are
oh my god oh okay i don't all my mental
clutch i never i never vented before
i never ever oh my god i never ever
vented ever
oh my god no no oh i guess i could
i guess yeah this one this is fine
this is fine
[Applause]
okay
i don't even know how to vent
i don't know how to vent dude
you're going to the usual room how do
you do it if you don't know how
what what is this stupid question stupid
question
i should have been one second earlier
with my venting then he would have just
uh
one run past me but i was i was
trying to figure out what event button
was
oh you're going to the usual room that's
for sure
well okay
ah the face being ejected
magical oh
where is that little piece of [\h__\h]
crazy all right what can i do again i
can sabotage ryan oh yeah
all right now i can i can do this
oh it's you
oh this is fun
being an impostor ghost is fun because i
don't have to
i don't have to help with tasks
[Laughter]
well can i do something again please
wait what do we want next let's do it
let's do coming what is that even
even
what is that why is there like a small
one there wasn't
also they still didn't find the body did
they wait did they
did they ever find that body
what is it guys wait there's so many oh
wait i'm not the only ghost oh my god
there's
so many dead people did you feel
anything
okay
what who do you think is safe
look out for yellow i think you saved
yellow is more says
no how do they know
they're probably watching the stream
i know that echo is still on i'm a ghost
i'm a ghost
thank you for the membership oh
can ghost watch the stream
sorry you may watch
the archives
wait where are they oh no are they
voting yellow out
oh no well that was a quick game
oh no oh
game over well that was that was quick
that was quick okay make it a new room
guys don't even try to join don't even
try i'm making a new room
thank you guys for playing with me don't
ever join again ever
okay new cards
hopefully next time i i'm not the
imposter actually i don't mind actually
i want to
try i want to try venting again k next
kiana
f like pride
h like hentai
j like
j and j like j and f
k f h j day f
no no no no dude as you're leaving
you're leaving you're leaving judas
leave leave bye bye also welcome
everyone else
welcome welcome
mama yes mama is here
kia is not sass is that a troll or
judas didn't get into the last game oh
really
oh i guess that's true
okay you can stay um
everyone close stream please
and uh let's open now
yay are you ready i'm closed okay okay
okay okay everyone else too
back green stop
being picky
oh they're actually oh they're actually
changing colors not that sweet so that's
that's kfb for you guys okay
well this is gonna be fun
oh wait someone was already killed
because there was just a countdown
no wait that's impossible also
i could have probably not done that task
that quickly i feel like
i should i help well someone's going to
do it right
[Music]
i don't know how to do this oh my god is
someone here now
someone here now let's kill someone
let's kill someone thank you for the
membership someone here no
boring why is everyone in the same spot
or what's going on are they are they
doing like a
conspiracy against me
where is everyone minadoka
check the cameras why would i do that
you are obsessed well nobody's seeing me
so oh hello i just hang out with you
guys for a little while
i have to do this again i feel like this
dude is looking at me
[Music]
this still gets me every time
okay one dead dude
what what what are you saying are you
saying you wear with me are you are you
are you saying
like yeah report it
currently an injection kill science
started following me in circles in store
which really sucks
i was just running wait wait i am the
imposter
wait who
even if i wasn't the imposter i would be
as usual
or just really bad at discussing these
kind of things even when i'm not the
imposter i just don't know what's going
on
i'm really bad at discussing really bad
among us i don't
i don't remember any names that i pass
by either
yeah that should be safe
me strong well that kind of sauce
actually
shadow where are you uh i i
still don't know what the rooms are
called but close to the swiping
i really don't know what the rooms are
called
yep yep yep yep thank you 2d
thank you thank you dude
what
what you don't have it closed
what do you mean you're gonna be closed
huh you don't have the stream
closed
i will kill you i am going to kill you
what can confirm which part which part
well okay i think everyone is hopefully
having the stream closed
well anyway who are we kicking out
skipper skip
cat he's scuff put
skull [\h__\h] i like that
whoever made that up nicer
always always scuff skf
skiff
okay yay we made it for one round
okay now i will i will kill judas
yep
[\h__\h]
was that sauce was that sauce what i
just did
the other imposter scared me oh my god
you escaped me why are you closing us
in here you want some alone time with me
no no i would grab a girl and fly around
in the universe and die
just kidding just kidding just kidding
i don't know i'm just scared to kill
someone i'm gonna mess up again
oh let's judas again let's look at the
cameras
i don't know how wait how how do i look
at the camera oh there we go
[Music]
i are those i never looked at the
cameras before actually
so where exactly is that
[Music]
so you should probably never kill
someone in judas jew that's what the
[\h__\h] were you are you waiting for me
you should probably never kill someone
in the hallway right
only in the rooms because that was all
the hallways
oh my god julius is following me though
what the hell is with him
he's not even doing anything
oh my god do this
you want to be killed or what what the
hell
what the [\h__\h] judah stop following me
what the [\h__\h]
i did i did not
how was i pretending it
oh my god this little piece of [\h__\h]
i had problems with the controls okay
what the [\h__\h]
but he's like he's he was
on purpose but to be honest
i said you guys should
treat me normally and
not troll and and uh
what's what's nerate doing in english
again uh
uh uh what's nidal in english quick
quick what's what's netaloo in english
target me but there you
go following me for like
for like two full minutes
and now and now saying
i am sus what the [\h__\h]
i thought we were gonna play
fair here
did not go up she started chasing me i
did not chase you
you were chasing me you were chasing
me i never chased you
never left in 41 hours
yep yep you're going
a bit crazy because of that
lack of sleep
yep for real
he died
okay okay okay okay okay see there we oh
there we go
there i got it we got him guys
okay
scientists they're not even they're not
even sustaining the other imposter well
that's nice
not even cyan didn't even cyan didn't
even
saya didn't even do anything
you have to kill they're about to finish
that oh my god okay okay okay and we
will kill judas eventually
we will kill him eventually so but like
judah stop following me what the actual
hell
[Laughter]
gotta go here oh my god
i can't even kill i wanted to kill
okay
[Laughter]
you have to avenge me
just do it just do it just do it already
just do it just do it just do it
oh crazy nonetheless
he was he was indeed crazy because he
was 100 targeting me
for no reason
right though am i right or am i not like
he was following me for a while
and he was like really closely looking
at the at the
tasks whether or not they were going up
or not that's insane he was stalking
me just because i am kiana
he wouldn't have just stalked anyone
else okay
the fun is over i'm gonna give you a
very hard time guys
you should be killing people you have to
kill people
you have to kill people oh
please avenge my death uh yeah yeah yeah
kill judas he's been stalking me
locked doors how do i lock doors oh with
this one oh okay
please kill someone quickly
oh oh i should close doors before i do
one of these things um
sorry it makes sense
[Music]
saying thank you though
no a body has been found
who could have possibly killed that body
what could it have been it's red
no oh no no no no there is no way
and you know this red took a long time
on o2
[Music]
do you rest come on come on i'm
i'm i'm rooting for you
[Music]
yeah bye is that behavior sauce
infrared ran from body i have to wrote
oh you saw
you saw red running from the body ooh
that is a little bit
yeah i believe lime over red
oh [\h__\h] we lose another round oh no
no
[Music]
and everything but her husband or him
i couldn't carry you to victory
i need someone who can carry me i need
someone who can carry me
please jesus why the hell have you not
voted yet
carrie
i am my own favorite comedian there is
no other comedian
we are always animes always
oh come on let me turn off my echo
it was too bad
okay opening new lobby guys
gg bar hello
that was pretty pretty bad again um but
why did i get imposter two times god
damn it i want sure i want to rely on
the others
help help okay new cult guys
new code are you ready
are you ready survey is asia and
everyone who is already in the game
please do not join anymore please be so
nice there is a lot of people who want
to try to join so please be nice
uh like
a like apple q like q
zed like zebra i like india f
oh
[Music]
oh welcome everyone
oh and one more nice there the knobbies
are filling up at least
like previously also my ping what what's
with my ping
previously i had some problems with
filling up the lobbies
because it was like bugging hello
uh oh yeah right they're censoring my
my my greeting oops
um everyone
closing
you're the one talking so the way you
write
is offensive to me very offensive
okay okay let go
okay now this time i will not be
imposter it's literally impossible i
cannot be imposter
please
okay okay i thought that she
automatically meant that i'm the
imposter
yay okay how do i do
tasks again like
okay swipe card okay this is a
i haven't done this in really in a long
time oh but there we go
i definitely do know how the controls
work
do i have to do that
first try yes move
also don't very do that i mean um
i'm i wasn't what is this i wasn't
hating on you or anything
please no one hate on judas it's just i
felt very stalked though is there any
task here no wait report
i didn't see anybody but i was able to
report i didn't even see it
i didn't even see a body but
i reported
same i couldn't report but didn't say oh
yeah yeah i want to see it can i can i
see it again no we're forced to be in
this window right now
hidden by okay maybe it's a bug though
yeah
maybe blame the pink
body can get hidden by a chair yeah
maybe
uh yeah yeah yeah
yes i am clean finally
i'm just i'm just trying to remember how
to do tasks
but yeah who could have done it who was
with me anyway
so i guess with me is uh the black
and uh who is with me
the brown one is also with me i think
uh oh you too okay
see i can't even remember i i can't
remember the names okay but i can't even
remember
the colors of the characters that are
with me
so i'm really really bad at this game
oh [\h__\h] sake tell me the code okay chill
there is no there is no meaning in
telling you the code
because we are changing the code every
time a game is over
so please chill chat i know a lot of you
are very passionate about getting into
the game
please chill the code is changing every
time after one
game is over
you're welcome to join after that uh
where i don't i don't know
how do i see my here we go what do i
have a swipe card
i might have to do the other one i have
to do the other one
oh no no no no that's not in eh this oh
i or that the green one is the ones that
i made
also what was i just looking at oops
i get stuck where do i have to go
oh okay okay okay
wait what am i doing hi
what am i doing what is this what is
this
okay
no they're gonna say i'm suss
look it's over already right i don't
even do i still have to do it
goddammit got them do i still have to do
it
[Laughter]
there was someone watching me right
was it was it savadado
who was watching me
so who was watching me they're gonna
think i'm sauce
it was b-shark yeah i am
too stupid to do it
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
oh well i don't i have no idea what's
going on
um i was looking at the cam while i
while i'm going to like i saw a body
people near okay what is your conclusion
double kill in lower engines
it's more sass when keanu does tasks in
a reasonable time
that's not true there's some easy tasks
and there's some that are a little bit
tricky i never had this task ever before
science says i saw purple at near 002
before so he might be clean
i literally don't know what's going on
ah
scuffle
there's three dead people
um and all of them are not people
that i thought would be safe like i
thought that brown and black are safe
but black is definitely safe
no one's talking to him why is no one
talking to him
black and science says i can't skip now
because
it's going to be dangerous yo everyone
so quiet
um okay
well i'm finally voting i just i just
need to trust you guys
tell me who to vote for
well everyone should give an ella ally
alley v
he's the one your body well what's his
what's what where
what were you doing
when body was dead
i was trying to um i'm trying to hint on
that meme
but i feel like i i did it wrong
where were you when when ki adam was
dead
i was a kill how did how did that go
how did that go oh my god wait who are
we voting for
okay they did it for me okay bye bye
bye bye where were you when kiana was
killed
and how did it continue
kiana is killed now
i have to go up
what is it what is it here yes oh yeah
this is an easy one
this is good okay i'm just chilling
something's down here the crumbs are
sabotaged
oh no oh where are they
well down here okie dokie
what do i do here
what i understand was that a task
was that a task okay we gotta stay
together guys oh my god
wait i'm scared of the blue one i'm
scared of the blue one
what uh
is it the blue one my blue is hella blue
it sucks as hell what
oh no not this task someone's gonna kill
me while i'm doing it
oh he was doing was he doing a task i
wonder
i'm running i'm i'm running i see a body
is that has that been reported before
no wait what the hell he was just with
me in the other room
what the hell wait who was there
it must have been someone who was
already there
and but i didn't see the colors i only
looked at the dead body
okay listen listen to me
i went into the thing on the very left
side
and with me just before i went
there was black so i was almost
following
black so when i get
there it's two people and one
dead body black
so those two didn't report
and did act as if they were doing
the fixing so i don't remember
the color color
well but it's them
possibly blue
at least blue more more
insulator
believe me wait what's bloom with me in
that room
was blue with me in that room right now
yeah okay vote blue
i will tell you the other one in a sec
but we start in the middle right so i
can't i thought we started off again uh
right where we left off
or do we
believe me to stress me i don't lie
my hips don't don't lie
we always start in the middle okay okay
also yeah he was like oh great she was
no i remember because of this uh
hairstyle she was the one who was
looking at me and black
while we were doing stuff oh my god it's
100 him
100 him but who is the other oh my god
no i don't i don't don't use chad what
do you mean i just shouldn't use you
guys
[Music]
is that right you can't
no skip oh my god no way
no way we cannot skip no no no no no no
brown sauce
bonita
but first blue
one after another okay
yes okay we gotta do this we're gonna do
this and i'm the one carrying
kiana carrying a bonita means pretty
okay so now
um what we do with this brown dude
should i call the emergency meeting
are we are we actually waiting for it
i can't but it's a crisis oh god it's a
crisis
i don't want to lose
[Music]
what what are you doing
where is it where is it where is it
okay okay thank you
yep uh out with the out with the big
dumb
make them mine
eh
what
what what is he saying
i understand yeah
i agree but i also don't understand
brown was indeed covering
a lot for for blue
you what you would have lost if blue
wasn't the imposter
bloom was impossible because the game
didn't end after voting
ah
well it doesn't does that make sense
what he's saying guys
why won't you leave the game goddammit
hopefully no
no anyway i'm voting for no now for real
we gotta vote
hopefully that was just uh thrown out
but
it doesn't add up voting
brown
hopefully we were right this time i mean
viewer could never be sus
because of obvious reasons i mean
shabbat shalom very pure
viewers
and are we winning
stop banging to join the game in the
chat it's not my choice
[Music]
yeah that was good wasn't that mostly
because of me
because i reported i saw that i saw the
first body
and i saw that there were two people in
the room and i came to the conclusion
that it must have been one of them and
then i came also
i remembered that i was i was with i was
with the first
dead body for a while and that one dude
i've already forgot the colors that
there that he was like just looking at
us
yep yep that was my win i think i
deserved that that was pretty damn good
even though i still had no idea what's
going on
it was because of me that we won this
game
yes
okay next one
are you guys ready actually
i don't really wanna i wanna try this
out but also at the same time i don't
want to because i have no idea
how they work uh
i still want more here
yes okay all right
new code please don't uh enter if you
have already
uh been in here before
okay i'm telling you the code now
triples it's fun is that the one which
is mostly outside i tried that one
before but it's so huge like
uh it was a pain in the ass
yeah i know you can only learn the maps
by playing them but the the one outside
the cold one
it was kind of stressful for me i didn't
know what was going on
oh okay that like zebra
x x a like apple
orange friend
set xx welcome
welcome everyone
[Music]
okay guys close
stream clocks
region asia asia asian region asian
region
not change has been like this since the
beginning
my mama is here let's go
let's let's go stream close okay
okay okay i will kill you guys if you're
not streaming
if you're not closing the stream also i
wouldn't mind becoming the imposter
again let's see
hmm
okay i have to do nothing here
oh no no i have to okay swipe
smoove getting real good with your stuff
how do i open the map again with a key
which one is the key are you
wait it's closed no
wait do i have to do something here
anyway
a q m are you guys just
saying random letters
tab oh
okay it's neither q na nor m
so it must be tab
okay what's up guys wait no
no
no no no no no
[Music]
ship ah but yeah she will respawn
quickly
but that's just a simp that's not watame
herself
yes
um wait who reported anyway
captain rex the the purple one okay
i can never really contribute to this
conversation
i don't know i don't know
i oh know
i say it's blue and um
it's blue and pink
for absolutely no reason i tell it's i
say it's blue and pink
black locked himself of chia to make it
believable
scuffle i know there's an
egg that egg
might be you soon maybe
i'll crack you on my head and you will
be dead
oh what's your yes yes please state your
concern
you should have stated it before you
voted
well now we never know that person's
concern unfortunately
oh wait what i just said was kind of
sauce
well if i was really the imposter i
would have never said something like
that so we're fine
that was basically me telling him i will
kill him next don't know
i don't actually have the power to do
that so don't worry about it
uh oh there we go we have something in
communications
let me try to fix that
oh yeah downloading that's sensitive
data
imagine they die and i said yep that
might be a problem i have to protect the
baby now
what where they felt when they were
watching me are they watching me because
i'm sauce
are they watching me
bottom left theta
i feel like they're watching are these
people watching me
oh my god
don't kill me don't kill me there we go
okay touching
is it over oh now it's quick
touch touch
[Music]
huh
orange
maybe it wasn't orange
[Laughter]
i was on my way to the card
swipey and saw a dead
body not looked orange but
i am orange so i am confused
i can i think i can clear black kiara
black kiara it's it's uh
you should use commas but okay
yep i am i am 100 clear thank you
thank you
[Laughter]
i am your father
sorry guys
[Laughter]
um what's going on
voice reveal sorry accidentally released
my voice released
revealed my voice
maybe i was never your mama maybe i
would maybe i was your father
for for since forever
so yeah what's our what's our conclusion
who could it be
so okay it's not
brown it's not me
other than that i have no idea
pink sauce that's what i said but i had
zero evidence that was just my feeling
when are you quiet yeah that is indeed
us
brown orange black and blue are safe
that seems um i mean you're saying that
you yourself are safe but okay
ryden pink are vouching for watching
each other oh
so it's you science wait that doesn't
it doesn't make any sense
interesting interesting logic
good that this is anonymous
no one by mine
it could really be white and pink yeah
that make a lot of sense this person is
smart
i know i don't have to go
no no no no i'm going to navigation how
do people even
like learn oh god louise here alone
how do people even remember the names of
these
i'm just checking up on pink checking up
on pink
just checking up on pink okay
pink okay okay okay
just gotta be a little bit careful now
you know oh pink is following me
all right i have to go up i have to go
all the way up god damn it
pink yourself oh
and my history meeting
pink took so long to press one button
interesting theory
oh
what purple tried to lock me in
brown i finished my task and i was just
following someone
panic much bottom engine so he can kill
what
oh
we could win the attack oh really
wait is that something an imposter would
say
[Music]
okay
yeah i think i'm close
too i just have to run all the way up
all the way out
go let's go
no one was ejected
oh yeah i wanted to be up here anyway
thank you
nice oh yeah i don't have time for this
[\h__\h] i gotta do something here
you guys go when you guys do it okay
do i have to do it go do something else
okay perfect now i go
does everyone have to go there
that was over okay there we go nice
nice okay please don't kill me
how do i use this whoa they're scamming
my sexy bonnie
stop it stop it stop it i'm an idol
how dare you say that information about
me up
openly publicly take a break what no
i don't have time to i'm just waiting
i'm just waiting i'm just waiting i'm
just waiting here for real guys i'm not
suss i'm just waiting i'm just lit
i have to do this i can't you think i
have time to grab a goddamn coffee
huh what i'm scared about no i'm so
scared alone
it's my last task
oh my god oh my god oh my god someone
protect me please some skin
completed
it's purple really you're not doing a
good job though it's still only three
people dead
oh actually didn't we kick one out of
those
no
is he gonna say himself
oh two
two of everything
i think is what i said
oh okay so yeah he's he was being
obsessed with me i think
i'ma stick to mama what do you mean with
that oh he's
is he saying he's gonna
why would you wait don't don't ask and
idle her wait yo
[Music]
i knew it they were looking at me being
scanned
i have to kind of censor that next time
i don't know what's going on are you do
you guys know what's going on
what is 992 lbs i literally don't know
what that is because i
speak in kilograms which you all should
adjust
to
i did turn off visual tasks
exactly also i am i don't know
ah 40 kilograms oh
oh yeah that seems about right it seems
about right
yep yep
oh oh we did kick someone out oh
interesting i have no tasks should i
just stay up here
because i got no tasks
like i said oh
wait where is it right here okay
yummy oh wait
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] uh two seven zero
five three okay
nice let's go back nico is nico seems
safe he's just uh trying to stay with me
because he trusts me
not because he's cessing me
[Music]
come on
we have to do something
i am dancing to shakira music
there is an old song which is a collab
with
shakira and rihanna it was like
extremely hot
what was it called again um i love that
song
[Music]
you know that one
you know that one it's so good it wasn't
rihanna it was beyonce
no no no no the one that i'm thinking of
is i'm pretty sure
rihanna i know my yeah i can't remember
to can't remember to forget you
[Music]
oh
that was so sexy too you're so sexy
they are so sexy we don't need another
dmca button i never was dmc a bond i'm
just
a band i'm just uh on purpose
challenging them
nice nice it was pink
see i said it at the beginning with
absolutely no grounds to why i would
think it would be pink
but i did say so
not as much as you can
that's what i like to hear
okay bye bye guys creating game
server is asa and uh
don't join again if you have joined the
floor
oh like orange f like friend jay like
junior or so i don't know v
like victory kayla kiara f
[Music]
welcome everyone egg
egg are you the egg from before i i
remember an egg
alita thank you for the red super chat
weren't you brown you were in the game
just now right
thank you egg
this is this is how i like to
communicate
top iq communication
i'm stupid okay uh close
stream leg
leg let go
not funny thank you for the membership
it's me right it's me no okay okay okay
okay that's nice because then i can tell
you about something
so all right what am i doing uh okay
let's go up first
here uh recently i have been using my
takanashi kiara uh youtube account
oh i am busy i want my dudes what is it
that's just hella fast though
oh wait you're just saying that you're
with the person who's called egg
we have cheese and we have egg we can
make breakfast
cheese egg egg cheese
chia egg is with egg chia is with
egg and kiara ink lime
sorry i just wanted to i just wanted to
throw myself in there
what
oh i don't know what's going on
what egg on
my head
what what what's with that number
is that uh yeah by number or no i feel
like i heard of that before
should i should i should i kick him is
really a buy
is it really a buy should i kick him
as long as i don't look it up this is
okay okay
okay
what aren't eggs really just that time
of the month day for chicken
what what
egg
don't know what's going on i don't know
what's going on wow so yeah i was
telling my story
um i was telling my story
i've been i've been on uh i've been
watching some stuff on
my takanashikiya account and thinking
like like okay our um some of our
um staff have access to
takanasi kiara account and well i mean
like some staff have have access
just for like safety reasons and stuff
when i was supposed to go up there
um just in case
uh you know they need they need access
so i kind of was like
uh i was i was i was ignoring the fact
that they have access to it
um just hoping that they don't check my
my history of
am i i'm totally ignoring that should i
go there goddammit
um oh it's over okay i was hoping they
would ignore
like not look at my history of videos
when i'm watching
because recently i've been watching some
really weird videos on
on youtube
i don't know how it started but recently
i've been wait a second i need i need to
swipe my card
i need to make some purchases um
i think it started with oh yeah it
started with i i i told this in my
brand's stream it started out with me
watching
um a video of some fishermen
and i think in korea some fishermen in
korea who just
always records his fisher adventures
which are not really adventurous it's
just really chill videos
of him hanging out at some kind of pond
that which is frozen and wait wait what
what report
have we seen that body before
can you report bodies that you that have
already been reported
i saw a body
now okay okay um
right side um where
am i uh o2
o2 so continue with my
black black black body
so continuing with my story um so
those were really cute videos because um
basically
cats were joining him um in in his
adventures the whole time like he was
just fishing and stray cats would jump
on his
lap and hang out with him and watch him
fishing and whenever he would get
one of those fishes out of the pond the
cat would like
paw at the fish and try to catch it but
he wouldn't give it to her to the cat so
i thought wow that's a tease
give her at least one cat and one cotton
fish
but he put all the fishes into some kind
of container and the cats were gathering
around around and everyone was like
can you give us some fish it's really
cute this whole channel revolves around
that
um so yeah uh later on
he he actually um uh prepared the fish
for the for the cats he gave them like
uh he grilled it and he
he cut it and and he put it self-report
excuse me no
yeah um i'm basically telling my story
i would never really i would never
i would never no he didn't grill a cat
he killed the fishes and gave them to
the cats to the stray cat so anyway
because i watched that video i started
getting um really weird
recommendations um like more
more animal recommendations usually
usually my feet was full
with what's the point of the story it's
the point is i'm getting all these
recommendations
and i can't stop myself watching them
like i was getting
recommendations of um of uh
like uh owl videos
and i i started watching this at this
russian channel
russian channel which has like over a
million subscribers and
is even verified you guys maybe know
that channel i don't know
um
and
yes y'all yes yes y'all yes yes this is
this is yo
yeah so that that person has like all
kinds of like cute owl videos where the
owl just like
is at the window um and and she opens up
the window
and wants to take like some some some
mail from the owl's mouth the owl
usually
doesn't give it away that easily anyway
i watched some more videos
and realized she doesn't only have an
owl when i'm supposed to vote
i don't know who i should vote for joe
doesn't only have an owl she also had
like
a cat and some really fat
frogs i think those are turds maybe
what's happening okay
and uh and and some lizards and stuff so
that was super interesting to see
why can i report why someone dead here
what the hell
what what the heck
happens when the kill was at the same
time as the round end
what the glitch
oh interesting okay
it's a glitch okay so yeah um after that
i started getting recommendations for
like frog videos so i was watching
videos of like really small frogs that
were like really colorful
and then i i got more recommendations i
i watched
more vlog videos and then i watched um a
video of a frog who hasn't moved for one
year
and then i watched a video um of a mouse
giving birth
and then i watched some hamster videos
and yeah i just it just keeps going i
can't stop myself
and i've been i watched also some videos
of someone keeping like um
a pet a crocodile like a small pet
crocodile
in his home in like a huge tank and i
watched a video where he
moved it from one smaller tank to a
bigger tank
and he was like showing uh around for
like 10 minutes showing around how he
moved the the pet crocodile from one to
another tank
and yeah yeah it kept on going what's
going on here by the way
yeah so yeah my recommendations were
really fun and today i had a talk with
one of
our staff members and i realized that
they sometimes
check into our accounts to use them
before
something and with it
telling story to my ch
chat sorry
what was i saying
[Music]
yeah what makes you sad of me
i was talking to one of my staff members
and then i was like wait did you did you
check my
did you check my video history by any
chance
and he was like no and i'm like oh okay
i'm
i'm just gonna quickly erase my video
history
no no reason why i would do that
it's gone now no evidence
no evidence but still my recommendations
are full
with these kind of videos
so i want to i was starting to think
when i get back to australia i want to
get a frog
what do you guys think of that like i
have i have cats
but i also want a frog now and i want an
alto but that's kind of impossible but
getting in frog should be easy
and i i can talk to them because i speak
frog
you know as my frog noises i can
communicate with them
so i should probably go to the lights
huh
there were some really cute frogs that
were really colorful
and they don't even need much and what
were they called pacman frogs or am i
going totally crazy right now
wait who died okay zion reported
and i don't know who died
i am at the very very
right
thank you for the super chance yeah
i'm really jealous that you have an owl
or that you are an owl i guess
yes yes yes indeed i was doing leaves i
should probably
be doing something else those are
poisonous rocks oh but they were
touching them just like
were touching them as if it was no
problem
don't think a frog is a good idea with
other press well obviously i'm not going
to let them around
really freely they will have like a
little little enclosure
cat food
is it
round husband i have carrying
i have not i was just a kiara i was he
should have passed
this so he's just checking the cams got
nothing better to do
if you're really australian then you
know frogs go la dee da dee da
they don't go gum gum gum what
is that some australian meme mate
which should i know that is that is that
a reference to an
australian meme or to an australian meme
now you're confusing me
i am confused australian or
australian
you're not getting anywhere here we're
not getting anywhere i should probably
help
i should probably try to help
i'm sorry i wanted to entertain
my channel you can
watch the archive later it's true
i am not afking i'm just i'm just
i'm just i'm doing what i have to do i'm
just not contributing
but am i ever contributing am i ever
contributing to the discussion no i'm
not
there is barely any difference oh you're
voting for juggle
oh is he gonna get kicked down
oh bye-bye hey why did you leave the
king
why did you you helped in the round i
was in a lot
yes in the last round i was pretty damn
good mm-hmm
what where do i have to go
we throw something besides leaves out
there i'm kind of worried about that
um sorry that looked kind of sass
believing there's nothing wrong
what is it
egg messing with me on life oh [\h__\h]
must be egg
i believe kiara egg
they're having a fight in their
relationship
i was i was shipping them real hard
this couple is wait are we voting on
someone
i think we're scooping i think we're
skipping
it's just so sad wait are we voting for
your eggo
cool oh oh oh [\h__\h] i scooped
they probably voted each other
it's your choice
you're you're you're going red
you're going with kiara egg why
i don't think it's kiana inc
no no no oh are you voting
he did that on purpose he's trolling
he's running yeah yeah he's voting so
that we get a tie which means maybe
okay could that mean something could
that be some
some really intelligent like
technique to win and there we go
okay
it's so dark again
don't kill me don't kill me don't kill
me
was right
lmao
okay new room let's go
okay okay sorry we're doing on the same
map
uh again after all and please don't join
if you have joined before
and we are on asian server and the code
[Music]
is
oh like romeo you like ufo
f like france is that like zebra
ff show me what you got guys
show me your speed
[Music]
welcome oh
is it
what scuffle it's called scuffle and
also there's a chair
ah cute names uh
elo oops
hello
welcome
getting more and more confusing each
time
okay
let's go let's go let's go let's go
okay i have a feeling i've got a feeling
that tonight i'm gonna be an imposter
that tonight i'm gonna be an empire star
damn it oh
[Music]
i wanted to sing my song i wish that
would have come true now
that's too bad
oh no oh yeah so fast
[Music]
wait wait for me wait for me wait for me
wait for me wait for me let me finish
this please
let me finish it let me finish it
okay i'm coming
oh no okay we're all good
just leave it to the employees
this dude is kind of scary
yes swipe
but did that not work
is he thinking i'm sus now [\h__\h] it
what what are you saying not enough
balance what's going on
okay that was one of you guys i know it
it was one of you
oh don't decline my card
i need it no so many dead free dead oh
my god oh my god
oh my god this oh this is yummy
yummy
yeah right the chair disconnected that's
sad
we will we will keep you in our hearts
what
don't ask who are you sassing
sir dark green i was stuck in the room
you saw me honestly i don't know but i
was stuck
oh that sounds that sounds a bit sauce
but a bit sauce but
scoop
keeping keep keep uh keep
uh what's that color called again green
keep green in mind
two died one disconnect
is that also some kind of crazy magical
number
that means something by the way the the
three four
go and so on
yes is it also yummy
can you guys stop with those goddamn
numbers i'll i'll i'll kick
you out next time no okay roofer next
time
if you guys don't if you guys have some
weird number that is your b
it's a wholesome one okay if it's a bad
one i will kick you guys out if it's
something like
if it is something like like like the
one from before then i will kick you out
we gotta stay family friendly in the
stream we've been family friendly
up until now we will stay family
friendly because that's just what kfb is
a family friendly fast food restaurant
ffff
oh wait that's not fff that's it's fff
f ffi family friendly
no we could do it we could say family
friendly fast food franchise that's five
apps
oh how do [\h__\h]
no
okay focusing i'm focusing now
also i had a nice neck crack crackers
now
no one was ejected
where are we going we're going down
[Music]
by um way tomorrow i have no stream guys
are you guys going to miss me
i could upload a video though i have a i
have a video prepared already
just in case if i if i um
uh if i need to if i feel like i need to
upload something
i have like another one of these tiny
videos but this time it's not it's not
something like m frog
it's cute and saiso
what's up there what is it
why was that blinking
okay maybe i'll upload that tomorrow
also
right now i'm i have uh invited
one en member and uh two
indonesia members for a four member
collab hey
i'm not gonna tell you who are you
telling me mixed signals not gonna tell
you who yet
so but i wanted to plan um a collab with
some mixed generations
oh no oh no
but they saw that didn't they didn't
there was a lot of people around here
why is he why don't you leave why you
leave what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] green
there i i i in the corner of my eye i
saw a lot of people running around
so someone must have seen that yellow
green running away from body uh-huh
it was green and green was sass
even before that nice nice
i i will gladly die for
the better cause because i am phoenix i
will revive anyway
nice instant revenge
ooh hello
can i help probably not with the
emergency test but i will help with
something else
i gave you my data please respond
[Music]
you you hit it how dare you kill the
danger
this is fun
what am i doing next oh
[Music]
nice one saving the day as per usual
sasuke don't worry guys i'm gonna carry
you
kiara erie wait what is this what is
this
can i talk to the dead imposter as well
what is that what's going on here why is
there a small baby
[Music]
yes i can yes i can green
anyone no
[Music]
why did we run out of time
did we run out of time
no no
[Music]
never dressed green ever again never
trust
green ever again okay guys
next game last game this game is the
last one
and after that we'll be bringing super
chat so good luck of getting in here
this will be the last one because the
time passes by so quickly it's already
been
uh almost two hours wow
last game season what if this was
sliver.io
that might happen but because sliver dot
io's
il is my addiction
what
okay the code is
okay your little [\h__\h] stop spamming i
will bonk you into
infinity bye
[Laughter]
and d like derek sorry that just
this is the first thing that came into
my head you like ufo
oh like orange q like q j like january
f like f
wow thank you for the red super chat are
we 10 out of 10. yo
chimpkin love oh thank you welcome
everyone welcome welcome welcome
welcome welcome no i was just saying
random names
it's just how i say frederick or fred or
or yeah
welcome
close the chat please
at the stream sorry why won't you leave
why won't you leave wait but still says
10 out of 10 are we 10
are we 10 okay
everyone get in line i need to count
you you stand in one line stand in one
line come on can you do it
stand in the line are they going to yeah
it's good job
except the green one says as always okay
one two
three four five six seven eight
nine and two oh i mean ten okay
okay okay nice
ten let's go go go
go go
counting my little chickens to make sure
they didn't
you know go somewhere
we have the lawyer well it's always good
to have a lawyer with me
okay well first of all we go here
just chilling
what what what you gotta go there and
help
oh no oh no
where is it what where is it is it over
oh no help me help me someone help me
i don't know how to do anything okay
there's someone here with me
yes okay nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
i'm scared to come out i'm scared to
come out
okay okay after the chicken after the
chicken
and nice okay i'll come out after that
wait it will let me out after that
anyway right if we start in the middle
again
[Music]
um
how did i know i vented i didn't even
come out of it
what should i say what can it work what
can i say then
i'm not i'm i'm i'm not suss
uh don't say anything okay i'm just i'm
just telling my chat another tangent
what huh
it's not me dude
you would know if it was me
[Music]
oh wait there's another dead person
oh
oh wow wait this is second kill yeah
that was from you
oh nice one i also didn't know
[Music]
i don't have any idea
yep you don't have any you don't have
any
anything she didn't
no one saw me literally no one saw me
oh [\h__\h]
no one saw me
i need a backstory yeah i'm just going
i'm just
going on attendance with my
viewers sorry i will focus
no one was a chick
we have to kill white because white is
very sus
and i will do my swipe swap
do i have to do that can i not do it
well someone else is doing it too right
okay i wanna help them after all
are we gonna kill that poor boy
a poor emma taco
he's watching me and watching me
is that did i take too long did i just
take too long or to to quit
so quickly was it too quick to look yeah
i'm too scared
i can't be doing anything here right i
mean i can
possibly no no i don't want it okay
that's okay that's okay i'm too scared
to come
out goddammit
yummy i'm too scared
okay with you it's fine
[Music]
you don't see me bent right you didn't
see me vent you didn't see me went you
didn't see it i know it
interesting okay oh i'll continue then
wait they're gonna win with the tasks go
go go
go go kill someone kill someone kill
someone kill someone you know
i'm gonna [\h__\h] this up right now oh my
god yep
let's go there oh yeah yeah yeah yeah we
have to go there
and do something and help
okay anyway help me oh god
[\h__\h] am i
come on come on come on someone come
here let me kill you
can't do anything
okay i should have killed that one
[Laughter]
you'll be here i'm too nervous to kill
anyone
but aren't they almost done with the
tasks so [\h__\h]
stop bullying
me
what's interesting kiana huh
if you have no grounds
then [\h__\h] i'm just gonna stay quiet
huh
chicken you better tell me your youtube
name afterwards
you're going to this to the usual room
you're ruining it i'm sure
there's one of them who is
see who someone loves me someone is
definitely stream sniping because
they were like saucing me from the
beginning for no reason
and they're like i know i know what's
going on should i just stay here
yeah i see they're just staying with me
i can't do anything anyway
what is it huh what is it you stupid
chicken what is it
what is it what is it you suck
stupid
okay i cannot end it like this we are
doing one more game
i cannot end it like this p
like paella f like frank
k like conrad
we like vienne
that like zebra f
all right the chair is back you were
allowed here because you got kicked out
everyone else seems new to me
okay if someone
is gonna keep the stream open
while playing i will never
forgive you
what what you mean we had something
special i didn't do anything did i kill
you
oh i guess i did yeah you were the only
one i killed
you're welcome doesn't it feel nice to
be killed by me
let's go
okay
i've got a feeling
that tonight's gonna be a good night
that tonight's gonna be me imposter
that tonight i'm gonna be an empowered
oh no
the cherry again
no the chair got kicked out again
no
rest in peace i feel for you
oh
that's too bad don't feel bad
you can you can join uh sliver. i'll
play together eventually that's not so
hard to join
[Music]
um
don't feel bad about it okay so guys
there's
two dead people
oh no oh no
that was really fast yeah
fox egg what is that fox
what where is a fox egg what were you
talking about
what what what what what
oh i was alone by the way right
[Music]
yeah uploading my
my loots okay so guys um
i was thinking i wanted to do another
among us
uh collaboration big one but i wanted to
do it this time with
um all i i wanted i
wants to organize a big big collab
i want to be the one organizing it so i
wanted to do it with hello live english
and whole live indonesia both
generations but that makes us 11 members
so
it kind of sucks
and just leaving one person out is so
awkward
but i know that there's mods where you
can increase the number of people who
can play
uh i just don't know if we're allowed to
use that
because for some games like sims or
minecraft
it's okay to use uh mods but for other
games
it's not so tolerated but i don't know
on what
what like who decides that and what is
okay and what is not okay
but i think it would be nice to have a
full indonesia
full english collaboration a big one you
know
so but then i was thinking if among us
is really not possible
what else could we do i guess we could
do like mario kart but
i don't know kind of bores me and then i
thought maybe we could do
a super smash brothers tournament
that that i would personally think is
funnier than
a mario kart tournament and super smash
brothers it's
groups of four but well
everyone can take turns and uh
eventually one will win
ah but then oh wait that that doesn't
work because not every indonesia member
has a switch
ah you're right not all of them have a
switch
ah so it can't be full members
oh god damn it that kind of sucks
[Music]
chess tournament nah
hey wait now we're double kill oh
i want to win
suspects
thank you for the membership maybe siam
what's up there's no cyan
he's dead
okay i think the people who talk about
venting
are nazis so i would say green is not
ces
i think it's um
should be maybe south report
i'm just lied about his position
remember that oh did he
ah
vote dark blue yeah he also seems like
not really um helping
he doesn't seem like he has anything
important to say
yeah i am vote blue
sorry
he he's not really like out of the
remaining people
yeah i'm also set up self report
ah
[Music]
i will vote run
i self report
because because he said he'll skip
in such an important situation where
there's only five people left
yep he says he'll skip in when there's
only five people left what the hell
we can't skip in such a situation
we gotta go for someone sorry
sorry
i was gonna go for blue
brown why did you say that i was gonna
go for blue unless you wouldn't
unless you didn't say that
ah he kind of made himself so suspicious
to me
also what the hell green
or lime i guess
oh no ah
ah i'm sorry guys this is this this was
the last game
i'm gonna read super chats now thank you
guys for hanging out i hope you guys had
fun
in
we are moving away yeah he shouldn't
have said that he will skip
ah too bad too bad
okay okay
sorry about that oh wait i didn't clean
up i didn't clean up
and the chat is gone sorry sorry let me
fix this i have to clean up
though
there we go and
there we go
and there we go
well let me close the game first how do
i close the game there exit
that was fun haven't played that in a
while
i hope you guys had some fun too i'll
have to read the the riser super chats
and the super chats from this stream
but we should be able to get for them
quickly
[Music]
one second let me prepare everything
um
maybe depending
actually mine
never mind
what what what what
uh shakira
yeah it's super chat time i'm just
scrolling scrolling
also we should uh do some hydration time
scrolling scrolling scrolling still
scrolling
ah there we go okay
let me put the thumbnail there so that
you know what we're reading at the
moment
i mean
ah actually yeah i
today i have the lineup like like a
little bit a little
bit less clutter what do you guys think
which one do you guys prefer
with the border or without it
it's just uh the border has my logo so i
like that but i also feel like it's
maybe a little bit too much orange
without without without without yellow
i i kind of get it it's a
maybe a bit too much but i liked having
the logo maybe i should just put the
logo there
without a border
that could look good
we should try that out
oh i was like where did it go it's so
huge
oh
nice logo where do we put it we should i
think we could just put it down here
also turning up the pgm a little bit i
hope it's not too loud but actually we
played we played this one
or during the gameplay so maybe we
should play this one now
a little bit change of pace much better
gets covered by the channel logo ah i
don't see that on my side ah
okay you know you know what this goes
this goes
[Music]
this goes here and the level of those
toes here i look better in the bottom
right
it looks much better in the bottom right
but if you guys say it gets covered up
that kind of sucks
it was covered up but not by much looks
like part of the logo
i guess yeah i guess i don't mind i'll
check i mean
at least for today i can have this here
and this up here
okay
okay gotta start reading a super chat
now you're welcome to stay and hang out
with me i usually
um do a lot of in between small talk
which extends my super chat readings
immensely
also i might drink some water
[Music]
myself
um
never have i imagined that by neglecting
slumber that the number of lags would
reach that funny number
though the moment has passed it did more
than suffice and as a funny number
custom i conclude with a nice
once again harbor line is on fire
[Music]
thank you and thank you for the nice and
pink super chat
lord evoke thank you in motion thank you
for the pinky as well
prizes streams best streams keep up the
entertaining stream random tangents and
overall good kia
experience by the way your tailstock
actually got me to play a game in the
series what for the first time
now i'm also in a rush to beat it before
riser 2 comes out oh don't rush it don't
rush it you shouldn't rush it
just go through it like like slowly
and enjoy it take it all in slowly
uh catwoman's wife i cannot help you
with that please contact uh try
contacting the
the contact form on the official home
page i don't really um
have any method to help you
but good luck this contact on the
contact form
they should be able to help you uh
i'll keep it short because you get this
a lot maybe look at crystals
never heard of it never heard of it
have a line down concern oh another wrap
from harbor line
oh breath is high the time for thickness
is nine the fake ties are
wait sorry sorry sorry five it's spies
i got back into my old habits
hope rests high the time for fitness is
night the fake flies are most tight
quite a sight for sore eyes any time
fake flies are inside is alright all
that fake is supplying best to remember
that right
but you you purposefully put
that word as often as possible as you
can in there
to confuse me it's like it's like a
tongue twister goddammit
that is a tongue twister but
a good a good wrap
thank you thank you soon hop online once
again danke shane with another super
chat no wrap this time
i just wanted to take the time to say
thanks kiara thanks for all the
enjoyment you provide for not just me
but for everyone who watches you made
the future of kfb being a long and
prosperous one
thank you i'm happy to hear that
although your your wraps are very
enjoyable it's nice every now and then
to hear something
such a sweet message
thank you so much
[Music]
but you always say how much you love the
samples you collab with and now you have
two shiba shiba collabs under your belt
how are you in for super the root
ending how long until we get some little
birds too
no why would it ever end there is no end
no i don't want it to end
[Music]
okay are you guys ready for some puns
potential even though there's a flock
ton of
other great funny people i was honored
that you would recommend
me to advise yeah who honestly crowl he
doesn't need it
his puns are excellent i know he has
more talent
than i do what
what enough
[Music]
you for a rat super chat thank you
wow saying i'm probably going to knock
out soon but i promise to catch the
archive
as soon as i wake up i hope you enjoyed
the game love you thank you
thank you i'm so glad people actually
take the time to watch the archives
thank you
i really really really appreciate that
thank you especially for ryzer streams
thank you that's very kind of you thank
you soon
hope you enjoyed it of course of course
thank you you sweethearts oh
there's so many yeah i'm sorry but
actually last week i
i did a lot of shorter streams so that
must have helped you guys with catching
up
hi tom wait i have a personal frog now
yay
also today wasn't that long either and
tomorrow i'm taking a day off tomorrow
no stream
and then the day after tomorrow i think
we're doing what are we doing are we
doing
are we doing minecraft today after
tomorrow
oh he's always been a frog oh it always
cuts off when i read the super chats it
cuts off early
so i uh with longer names i cannot read
the whole name
oh we're doing animal crafting on
wednesday oh okay okay i'm looking
forward to that
i haven't played animal crossing since
the summer
so i have not experienced the winter
time in animal crossing yet
[Music]
i'm actually looking forward to that it
looks pretty cute
[Music]
hmm
thank you for the red super chat oh yeah
i read that during the stream i think
because you said
i promised to super chat again when i
finished ryze and here it is
from debuted uh your love for jrpgs is
what brought me and this is exactly the
content that i wanted oh
i never would have finished this without
you so thank you i just want to see you
laugh and have fun i love you
oh you make my heart melt
thank you even though i'm a bit pissed
that you finished it
before me at least you can help me out
thank you that's so sweet
oh i'm glad that you
like me playing jrpgs because that's
that because that's my favorite genre
and it's what i enjoy the most
playing privately at least i feel a bit
pressured
uh during streams but
still i really really like playing my
jrpg so
i'm glad you enjoyed them thank you so
much thank you
thank you so much
[Music]
love jeremy juice i love you want to
start a new one soon have you played
tales of games i recommend them so so so
much like i'm for real if you have not
if you have not played a single tailed
off game
then i have to force you i've played
tense of symphonia okay that's not
enough you have to play more
play some of the the reason why play
play tails of some uh
berseria for example or um
celia hmm test of experience where we go
too yeah
that's eternal sonata count oh my god
that's so nostalgic
i think it does yeah i never finished
that game but i played eternal sonata
before
i really liked the art style and the
character design from that game
and the whole like music theme
[Music]
huh nice to have some tails off fans in
here
mister cats mixed thank you shadow
donkey shannon
daisy thank you speed freak thank you
pickled cucumber thank you about nexus
first time my awful internet has let me
tune into a stream live i'm
loving the comfy entire streams as
something of a comfy alchemist myself
you should really check out roon factory
when the fifth game comes out i think
you would really like it oh
thank you i've been wondering about that
serious
actually um i never tried it but uh i
i know about its existence and i wonder
about it
so if there's a new one coming out is it
coming for switch
maybe i'll give it a try
so are you saying that the atelier games
are similar to roon factory
yeah interesting
kind of but not really not at all oh
oh okay ah it has farming
yeah i think i've seen that i'm gonna
place
i'm gonna place rune factory but only
privately right
it's more harris moon actually but
fantasy oh i i
actually i want to check that out
thank you for the recommendation and
thank you for watching my streams thank
you
strowman dagger
[Music]
i have been summoned who daredev speak
of the sacred
relic oh hey boss
i don't understand the joke anymore
sorry you have probably you probably
wanted to make some kind of joke there
but i don't get it anymore i'm sorry
what was that about i wonder
how could you leave ollie on the beat
um okay so i've actually seen the clip
i did not know that she was doing some
kind of test
uh but yesterday i've seen the clip of
ollie
um explaining that she has been testing
the whole whole lot of english members
hmm um
and she messaged some random meme to all
five of us and i was the only one
who did not respond at all yes
but first of all let me say
that ollie generally sends
messages to all live members
not only once but several times so
she is a very very active
member
[Music]
writing many many messages to many many
members
um and when she sent me something
completely
random i i was i was
probably first of all busy
second of all i don't know what i was
supposed to say
[\h__\h] because uh she messaged me before
that and i did answer it but
uh this time when she sent me that i
don't know what was it
from some kind of video
she just wrote me so many messages
actually
[Applause]
she's she sends so so many messages that
i i'm just overwhelmed you know
ollie i am sorry
for not replying
lol
okay i messaged her but i did feel
um a little bit overwhelmed i have to be
honest because uh
she's like literally the only one in her
life
who just literally message messages
everyone out of
nowhere i was just like what's going on
what's happening
am i in danger
yeah she tries to um be friends with
everyone i think which is really cute
olly you're welcome to become friends
with me
don't worry i i i didn't which she
already replied away
and she's like always writing in caps
locked though
so i i i just apologize and she replied
in caps luck
no no no no please don't be sorry senpai
is busy so only on the stands
she's almost yelling and now she just
sent like a thousand
hearts to me she's spamming me
she's spamming
but she's still tapping she's still
topping oh my god
also isn't it late why are you awake
senpai okay so now here goes
if you wear true chaos and you would
know that i'm streaming right now
i'm streaming duh just kidding i'm not
writing that i'm just writing i'm
streaming only
ollie's so funny
she writes just the way she talks yeah
she's she's very very um huh
what what she wrote back with the huh
yeah oh you're missing my stream ollie
if she's gonna show up in the chat now
then once again
every time she showed up in my stream
she always showed up during the super
chat readings and she's always like did
i miss the stream
there she is
[Music]
you're once again late the the main part
of the stream is over
but someone someone in the chat asked me
why i ignored you or your message
so that's why we got to the topic
because i saw the clip only i saw the
clip
that you were kind of like testing us
called live english members
and trying to see what reactions you get
maybe maybe i knew that you were testing
us and sending us all messages all along
actually i did because i i did know that
you were sending messages to everyone
maybe that's why i didn't answer because
i felt like i'm not special enough to
you
because you're sending into everyone
doesn't even mean anything special
[Music]
uh do you own a switch
random question
[Music]
everyone was different ah everyone's
yeah i mean that that i um i applaud the
effort of sending everyone a different
video
[Music]
so do you own a switch this is for a
future
purpose uh future collaboration purposes
the viewers say she does okay
yes okay awesome okay ollie let's collab
sometime
[Music]
also only do you need a new keyboard is
your is your caps lock broken or
something
should i send you a new keyboard
just kidding i'm just stand it's just
it's just
i think that's your standard it would be
surprising if she wouldn't be in caps
lock
that's when you gotta be worried about
her
okay continuing my super chats
oh yeah uh the almighty hentai king
did i give you a kiss yet there you go
what's the rat i saw donkey shown the
weird name you have there
travel cane
next time you come to my stream you
gotta we gotta come earlier
you gotta come earlier not at the super
chat reading
okay
[Music]
yes matt
what it's a palindrome wait what is what
is a palindrome did i
did i say some combination of words that
together sounds like one word that i
shouldn't say
what did i say what's a palindrome
it's the same thing backwards oh
hell yeah you guys scare me again oh
was it alright indeed okay yeah that is
indeed the same thing backwards funny
i thought it was one of those things
where it's like a bunch of
words together that sound like some kind
of insult or
something i shouldn't say
what
palindrome not being a talent drum bugs
me wow
okay where were we bloop thank you mr
kaz biggs thank you
and kyle
bodies be dropping once our boss starts
popping like airless balloons her foes
bodies be flopping she's on a roll and
there's no signs of stopping victory's
edition in her full speed toppings
on fire
damn horrible line
purple i just just doesn't stop
powerline has to do a rap battle against
cali i want it i need it
i need it inside of her alive there is
no worthy opponent
it must be you harbor line you are the
one to battle
callie in a rap battle
yeah cali has been real quiet indeed
i i'm not hearing callie anywhere
[Music]
he stole my balloons thank you inside
question
tnd 203. tnd
with a blue height i don't think she's
going to
hear this super chat reading but thank
you i appreciate it thank you soon
thanks for uh checking out my stream and
sending a little bit of support thank
you very much
donkey sharon the planking clover duncan
thank you for pinky
also i did kind of answer your question
during the stream so i'm not gonna do it
again
ratchet fan three to one thank you snook
dove thank you
oh
fun fact as you know putting cold stick
old butter within the microwave and
watching it melt
will serve no purpose but it will look
satisfying
why thank you rosie
thank you we will never be part of you
10 to that actually
those words actually
will he make me doki doki thank you muda
it's nice to hear that
questions
and pickled cucumbers
[Music]
if she plays well-known music on her
corn cob does that make it popcorn
only the people who watch the attila
stream will understand what's going on
thank you
you're doing good even though you might
think you're not i struggled quite a bit
with the sharks but i didn't know you
could bomb the hell out of them until
you showed me
oh thank you
thank you okay um you guys gonna tell me
what the hell is wrong with the chat
today
i am turning on uh
i'm turning on what's it called again
flow mode
okay done
[Music]
no more speed sorry because some people
can just not behave
i've been seeing it all day today
[Music]
oh yeah members can still uh members can
ignore the
cooldown
static snake function 10 days since the
last atomic rise stream and it was the
last appearance of white kiara oh yeah
you wanted you wanted me to be white
again but but
i won't give it that to you that easily
white kiana doesn't come that easily
sorry pandaroni gaming thank you
inside question thank you for the
membership so
search master gaming thank you and
search master gaming
[Music]
while next time
daisy thank you mr cass
the dark anime
[Music]
we're done with raiza i accidentally
started reading some of the member
streams
membership chat only two but
okay moving on to the super chat of the
current stream
which i don't have the thumbnail for
right now i think
yeah okay gonna read the super chats
from the current stream
because i already read the super chats
from the member stream during the
mapping stream
any chance of you doing hearthstone
battlegrounds what i only know
hearthstone what is halftone
battlegrounds
i am interested in hearthstone but i
don't think i have space for it at the
moment because i'm playing a lot of
other games
but juniors didn't do anything wrong
we'll explain more on twitter
yeah i'm not saying you did anything
wrong
don't worry about within hearthstone
as long as suffering uh suffering
as long as something is covering my head
i am not naked
don't worry
[Music]
thank you for a red super chat wow
asking hello beautiful girl mama how are
you
you know
everyone always asks where is kiara
but no one ever asks how is kiara
oh thank you i appreciate you asking me
in the red super chat how i am
thank you you made it unstoppable
thank you actually yeah today
um today i saw casper so that freaked me
out and at the moment uh
my lips feel super super dry and
burning i think i need uh super senpai's
chapstick
also i feel a little bit um
out of breath right now
but that's okay we will get for the
super chat and then i can rest
yeah which is maybe my i might seem
a little bit uh low 10 a little bit less
hyped than usually because it's
a bit hard for me to breathe at the
moment
but i'm okay
don't you mean lip cream yeah whatever
you know what i'm talking about
yeah don't worry i have a day off
tomorrow and i'm planning to um
go and buy a jacket tomorrow for
my trip with cali because the ones that
i have are not warm enough i think
and i'm gonna buy some some nice shoes
i wanted to order those shoes online but
it didn't work
so i'm gonna buy them in an actual store
some some nice uh uh warm shoes that are
a waterproof so yeah
just gonna uh spend some money today go
some go some shopping
but it's uh it's necessary shopping for
for
the soon to come trip be careful wear a
mask i've been wearing a mask for
for literally a year now with no stop
every time i go outside ever since i
came to japan
last year i've been waiting a mask
non-stop
don't worry everyone in japan is wearing
an
a mask a mask
yep
now in japan everyone is
really like from even without you know
what's going on right now
even even normally a lot of japanese
people just
use masks just generally
so even during normal daily life when
you walk around in japan you will see a
lot of people
wearing masks it's very casual here
very normal so during times like these
but surely everyone is wearing a mask
and it's not a big deal
like they just accept it they just go
with it
[Music]
yeah there's also like a lot of ever
since uh 2020
um since there was a big need for masks
the mask creating companies producing
companies have really stepped up their
game and mask design
there's some really cute masks out there
like so many
so many varieties of masks like
literally
i think probably the mask economy has
been booming in japan
also the there's there's this uh whole
live concert coming up
um the bloom concert and they have a
mask as merchandise that is so
goddamn smart i mean it was supposed to
be
held offline in an actual concert hall
now not anymore but it would have been
super smart because everyone could have
just worn that mask and
uh yeah well nowadays i still want that
merchandise i want that uh blue mask
yeah i want that i want the blue mask
i'm gonna get it
oh my god okay if you're gonna continue
spamming
i've been i i put you into timeout for
so many times
if you can't stop it's not even only
today if you can't stop you know who
you know i'm talking about you i'm going
to
have to do more than just time-outing
you okay
so please stop i don't want to go that
far but please
behave yourself
yeah i know it's not always today
oh anyway virus thank you
[Music]
so besides the thing that i've stated
i'm i'm fine though so please don't
worry
looking for the top 10 father hog th
tankishan
[Music]
a name that i cannot really read i think
let me translate that
[Music]
maybe next the manga stream or even
today's stream when you say the code do
not let them join in until
i join first mark my words please
i thought this one ago i thought this
was going to be some legit
uh critique that i can use for the
future
i was wrong
willow the winds thank you for a red
super chat
i like your funny words chicken lining
thank you thank you
i don't know who you're talking about
but thank you i think you sent the super
chat to the wrong person
possibly uh i don't know is there any
chicken beetroot out there
but i'm a phoenix so it can't be me
but i will not refund your red super
chat that's for sure
that this is mine now this is your fault
thank you soon
her name is kiara what is someone with
the same name as me that's lame
let's ask them to change their name that
sucks i don't want
them to have the same name
that sucks it's gonna be so confusing
when i do some ego searching on twitter
huh
thank you for the game it was an honor
to be killed by tinto
heard unravel play as my life last
before my eyes i will also take full
credit for
for coining skfp i pay you for the rats
right yep
exactly you got it
someone who understands how kfb works
thank
god recently i have to keep on
explaining again and again
things that i should not have to explain
like for example what meat our burgers
are made out of
i am i don't i am not going to answer
that question
anymore
don't question anything cause i'm not
gonna answer it
i still love you thank you i love you
too
i wasn't targeting you the kfp discord
can vouch for me
regardless thank you for the game i had
so much fun playing with you is always a
fun time keep it up enjoy the rest of
your stream
don't worry about it i mean i'm not mad
at you but you were targeting me
you were targeting me but it's okay
it's okay you're welcome to join again
um in future streams like this
fight me slaver.io
that's where that's where i can truly
show you my power
thank you for joining in is
[Music]
i need someone to care for me proceeds
to carry herself yes indeed i did
there was one game where i was indeed
carrying was doing a pretty good job i'm
pretty proud of that i would like that
stream to be framed and put on my
uh that part to be framed
that the clip has to be framed and put
on my wall
guys i don't have much time the kfb
discord name is
no one will ever know
[Music]
foreign
it is indeed romantic yeah i agree but
uh
of course i can meet her she's with me
all the time
[Music]
he would like to announce something
attention all viewers and kiara i wanted
to say sorry
for begging to join i know i didn't
deserve this just a plain view who wants
to eventually be with youtube
viewers uh-huh
interesting i mean i understand to want
to play with us
is uh definitely something under the
last part of your sentence kind of
confuses me
yeah fair fair enough apology accepted
don't worry about it don't worry one day
you will make it in i'm sure
dominic thank you for the red super chat
elita
oli you were uh in the game weren't you
thank you thank you see you're paying me
for playing with me
amazing this is the kind of world that i
like to be in
this is the perfect world this is the
ideal word world people are paying me to
play with me
stocks i need a strong's emote
and not emote
something like this
[Music]
i need it
maybe like an arrow that goes like
knick-knack tick-tock tick-tock and all
the way up
if someone can make it if someone can
make me such an
animation please send it to me
uh 67 thank you for the pinky kiala is
with egg i knew that morning sickness
with something
i don't know what you're talking about
i wonder if chickens
suffer from sickness when they're
pregnant
wait they don't get pregnant they just
uh i guess they don't they just
i don't know can you call that pregnancy
can you call
plopping out those eggs pregnancy
so i don't know no because they lay eggs
okay so i guess they don't get sick
she admitted she's a chicken i did not i
don't even know how this works
how did i admit that i did not admit
anything
chickens white eggs if they aren't
burning what
eggs are technically their period so
it's the opposite of pregnancy
oh i wonder if they have some period
pains
and that's interesting very interesting
chicken crabs well i do suffer from a
lot of cramps every now and then
i hope they're not in pain
i don't want them to be in pain are you
guys in pain i mean all of you are
chickens
are you guys in pain
yes oh no
yes i'm fine yes yes constantly i'm in
pain
life is pain oh no you guys are having
period cramps
oh no this is so weird
thank you for red super chat chit chat
stream one
were you asking that because i was uh
going on tangents the whole time
wow thank you b i hear you and i will
not give you a chit chat stream anytime
soon but
i'll be having a memories only drawing
stream this week
where i'll be chilly chatting a lot so
maybe that will help you
and maybe that answers to your request i
hope so
abby every every super chat reading is a
chitchat
thank you thank you for your support
thank you so much
thank you really i appreciate the
generous
donation
[Music]
such an edgy teenager
ouch sorry not sorry
i enjoy roasting people way too much
drink it's junkies
you're phoenix after all
there you go it just makes sense i'm not
a chicken i'm a phoenix otherwise i
couldn't be roasting you guys like this
that makes so much sense this is why you
guys all end up in my burgers
eventually
[Music]
sorry never mind that was just a joke i
was just joking
i was just joking
thank you thank you mr
[Music]
what does that stand for indeed speak
br74n i think that's probably supposed
to be some name
britain
or brian but wouldn't that be
br 1 4n
i don't even want to read that super
chat i'll read it at the end
step by kitten gd ksp thank you for the
ransom for chad which is however
empty what what are you thinking
what what are you faking
a red empty super chat still
up to this day you guys do not learn
your lesson
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i'm so happy that you're still using
the among us aren't i made for you oh
you're welcome thank you
it makes a good thumbnail you wise
thank you
model among us with more people in pro
mix to chat jackpots party game is also
a great option
what what's checkbox party game
and the blue file thank you and now i
shall refresh
i just wonder am i am i allowed to use
the mods when i'm streaming
for among us like for other games it's
allowed for for this one i don't know
i don't know if i'm allowed to use it
then we can have a full
english and indonesia members
collaboration that would be so dope
right
i want to do that i want to organize
that
i i kind of already asked but
i don't really know
i will find out i will find out
it would be so much fun can you imagine
combining
all the whole live english members with
all of her life indonesia second and
first generation
[Music]
oh that'll be fun
light azura dancing every now and then
[Music]
she's learned well from ahmed did ahmed
do that too
mary do thank you wait i i read some
that i already read oopsie
[Music]
leave river dankeshen claro dankeshan mr
kaz big sanchez
for the super collab you're planning i
would suggest looking into the mod that
gives you more players um yeah i wanted
to do that if you could use it that
would be dope yeah
i agree blue rappy duncan
thanks for the streams too bad i
couldn't play with you but i had a very
good time crying while laughing while
you were panicking love you mama
thank you i'm happy to hear that i love
you too spanking hot thank you for the
pinky
danke
[Music]
these hips are lying no they're not what
the hell
what my hips never lie
thank you do you say that
the thing is not like um um
[Music]
if we want to do a full whole live
english and indonesia collaboration it
has to be a game that is
available on pc because some of the
whole
indonesia members don't have a switch
[Music]
no i don't think they're planning to get
one
unfortunately that means
no no smash or mario kart
apparently it's like much more expensive
in indonesia
apparently ah or they're hard to find i
[Music]
guess
maybe they'll get one eventually
[Music]
i apologize for something i haven't
played the game in a long time
oh
if you're reading this then that means
killer queen ferd bomb is in your ri
click what i don't get it
what does that mean
[Music]
why are some people laughing a jojo
reference ah
sorry i can't laugh about that
[Music]
um
oh good luck in your exam you can
thank you many people have recommended
that to me before you're not the first
one
miss vince thank you thank you thank
don't worry thank you for coming anyway
better late than never
[Music]
oh i see dominic k
optimized for streaming but i don't know
i never saw that is that the name
of the game like i have never
seen that that we have permission for
that
but if they're optimized for streamers
maybe we should be able to get
permission i don't know
cause you guys have mentioned it before
a bunch of times
dominique is
thank you i did not
i did not i mean if you i just said
that she she she
she sent messages to everyone so that's
why
when i was busy i mean i was legit busy
i
i just didn't respond because it was
just a video i didn't know what to say
but now i now i reply i mean wait let me
see when that was actually
[Music]
that was a around christmas i was hella
busy in that week
[Music]
i would normally never ignore a private
message anyway
oh that was when i was doing the the
tattoo cover
what's long and stuff
[Music]
yep i was busy
happens senpai's are busy sometimes
that's just the way it is busy busy
senpai
[Music]
no those are not excuses stop making up
[\h__\h] i don't like being like
put into some kind of
fake image having some fake rumors out
there
that i just i don't know i don't like
these kind of narratives
if it's a joke okay but still other
people are gonna be like
hey she ignored her her junior
oh she's such a bad person what the hell
just because
i ignore one message that's ridiculous
[Music]
i don't dislike anyone i love all of the
whole life members i love them
[Music]
sometimes life is stressful
not even kidding
pewter bread thank you and dark girls
thank you for a red super chat
wow hi cute
so many people are calling me mama
nowadays
i'd like to thank you for all the loves
and joy i get from watching you keep up
the work
great and although you may be synonymous
with bottom left i don't know what
you're talking about
that doesn't mean you can't be top right
because that's why you are in my heart
so much love from canada thank you much
love back to you
thank you very sweet of you
am i only top right in your heart am i
not am i not taking up all of your heart
[Music]
sorry i had to hydrate myself
thank you dark rose i appreciate that
i'm glad you enjoyed watching my streams
i hope to bring much much more joy to
you in the future as well
thank you harvard line thank you and
logical paradox thank you
thank your recommendation i'm currently
installing tiles of rosaria
nice nice that's what i like to hear
i want to i want to play that again i
cleared i cleared it before and i
usually don't
uh replay games that i already played
until the end i usually
never do that but with tails off games i
haven't played one in such a long time
because nothing new is coming out it
takes them ages
moana also there is a taste of dysteria
i never finished so i really wanna
finally finish test hysteria but i'm
kind of waiting
i'm kind of waiting to get permission
for tails off games
so that i can combine playing tails off
games with
work and doing do it during a stream
i know blah blah blah tale of hysteria
you guys don't like it but i still want
to play it
i i don't think it's as bad as you guys
say
[Music]
now i'm keeping an open mind and i tried
i i started it before
i just didn't finish it but
i really really liked what i saw up
until then
[Music]
logical paradigm jt mason thank you for
red super chat
oh wait yeah i'm sorry if this surprise
seems shameless i really want to show my
gratitude for how you
revive my creativity in full force from
a who's calling
i created a seven page short manga i put
my soul into if you don't want to read
it that's okay i think i already read it
i mean there's a lot of people recently
um doing some like comic style manga
manga style um uh
like things fan art
and irene all of them
most of those are really really dramatic
and
make me kind of sad but i appreciate it
hey some of them are really really sad
most of them are like about me like
dying
and and cali being like
i don't know kind of cinderella
give me some more romantic
more romance why does it have to be like
romans like with me dying
can it not just be happy romance not sad
oops sad romance why is it always sad
sad romance anyway sorry moving
i'm moving my microphone sorry anyway
thank you
i'm pretty sure i saw it but i'm gonna
probably look it up again
to uh get it back into my memory
well thank you i'm looking at all of
those thank you so much i think also a
lot of my
viewers have already seen it too hmm
[Music]
i'm going to be attending a fighting
game tournament today and your stream is
making me in better mood for the
tournament
good luck with that alice thank you sure
looking for the top function
is that supposed to be a joke i don't
get it if i take off your mask
will you turn into ashes i don't get it
okay no that's it
[Music]
to nine dunkishan
huh once again a meme you guys
using all those memes on me that i don't
understand
we don't get them
casper's blind friend thank you casper
keeps
oh my god
casper keeps bragging about touching
this girl's foot and i'm just like
mate where the [\h__\h] are you
[Music]
oh my god i love these these these
casper people
i love these mouse super chats
it freaked me out though like just
running past me okay
but running like right next to me over
me
away from me that
that was oh my god i screamed and i was
i was so shocked i was like actually
about to cry
for a moment i was just standing in my
kitchen
like trying to not move and i'm really
scared and freaking out
too much i swear magnus did nothing
wrong danke soon solves this
studios thank you and judas thank you
very much
thank you for the pinky
i did not confess anything what the hell
i didn't confess anything
[Music]
el vido danke chen pudding duncan walter
jackson
thank you for red super chat no is this
the one that everyone was talking about
oh no
okay let me read walter jackson you get
a kiss before i get too angry and
and end up not wanting to give you a
kiss
[Music]
cause i think that's what's going to
happen
a chicken ah chicken don't hate me
because i'm beautiful
maybe if you got rid of that old ye
ye ass hat maybe you'd get some reapers
on your feathers what the [\h__\h]
better yet maybe kelly will dm your bird
self if she ever stop collabing with
that shark or the
detective she's talking with chicken
what
is that a meme again
i don't get it
gta
[Laughter]
okay since it's a meme i will forgive
you
but kind of rude kind of rude i have to
say
pretty rude
you know i i played uh
some gta game when i was younger a
little bit younger
i played it a little bit it wasn't my
own purchase i probably played um like
my brother's
uh a copy of it i just played it a
little bit
um but whenever i would play it
i would i would get a card
and then just
drive around like a normal person
like i wouldn't i would try to not hurt
anyone i wouldn't i would just drive for
hours
i would just i would just use it as a
like a like a
driving simulator pretty much and i
would try to stay on the right side of
the road
and all that no wonder you call it the
car game yeah
that's what it is to me it's a driving
simulator
ground flip say so yeah
that's that's just i don't know i really
enjoyed just normally driving
but it was really hard to get a car
legally
i i was kind of forced to always steal
one and then i don't know it never ended
well but sometimes i would be able to
escape and then just
drive in peace and harmony
am i the only one who uses gta in that
way
just to drive like in minding my own
business
like a truck simulator
not really yes okay most people say yes
but i see some no's
i see some people saying they do that
too
ollie oh he's still here or
here again
not stealing if you leave it afterwards
[Music]
ollie
um let me tell you some things
about the human world stealing is always
stealing
stealing please be careful olly
we don't want you to end up behind bars
i don't know if we can help you out
there
we need some whole live lawyers to help
you there but
please be careful don't steal
it's not worth it it's not worth that
one chocolate bar
you will end up in in prison for 10
years if you steal one
chocolate bar understand
we don't want you to end up in prison
for stealing one chocolate bar
your fans would be very very sad and we
would be very sad too
it's not worth it
okay i'm refreshing my super chats once
more
and we left it off here nope
nope not here nope here spicy burrito
ducation
obesity client thank you soon
to thank mama for today's stream i can't
join the game as usual but still thanks
for the funny gameplay that makes me fun
make me laugh so hard you're welcome
thank you for watching
alexi mekela thank you thank you
thank you for the pinky this is a
blippering waste of money but if you use
this sum with someone special
cali i will be not so angry for myself
cause nothing is more precious than time
with your loved ones
i think you highly appreciate that idea
and fulfill my wish
why thank you you're very interesting it
seems like you have a
conflicted feelings about sending me a
pink super chat
one side of your brain is telling you
what happened to the chat
one side of your brain is telling me to
stop telling you to send me money and
the other one says you shouldn't do it
did only flirt with me
how if you guys spam it away then i
can't catch up
and not i can't read it
what did you say she said she wanted to
steal my heart
ollie
i would say i would be happy about that
normally but don't you say that to
everyone
don't you say that to everyone
i want someone who only loves me
[Music]
but we can be friends we can be friends
that's okay you can steal my heart but
it's like a friendly heart
i can't help it i sent everyone exactly
you
are in japanese we called it a ddd
that is
[Music]
i love anyone or everyone
doesn't matter like if you are
a fan of some idle company but you love
way too many idols you don't only
support one
then uh you are called a ddd fan
[Music]
she's literally already dead
it's okay i mean generally i think being
a ddd is nothing bad
but that's not the way
to win my heart oh we can be friends
that's totally fine
i have callie anyway i don't i don't
need another lover
i don't need anyone else your number one
senpai
along with everyone
that's what i thought
anyway alexi yes it will definitely go
to good use the trip is soon and
tomorrow i shall buy
some some fluffy what do you call
down down jacket oh is that what you
call it
a very fluffy one that keeps me warm
obviously i don't need it i just i i'm
out of phoenix so i can warm myself up
but i just
i just do it for you know the aesthetics
[Music]
dominic thank you i did read your uh
chat thank you i'll i'll check it out
jonathan koslowski
but i'm not thank you what the hell
you guys should know was it a rat i saw
thank you
thank you for the rat super chat
okay what's it this time what's what's
this meme
ah tanto don't take walter because he an
adorable
froggo what is us about sex
i was gonna say who is walter
maybe if you got rid of that onion hair
you go
you go wait okay maybe if you got rid of
that onion hair you got
you'd get some peckles on your tail oh
better yet maybe kelly you
call you your bottom left ass is she
stopping
with that time traveler or duck she finn
with
chicken what the [\h__\h]
uh it's not funny to me because i don't
understand
i know it's some meme but i don't
what do i have to look up in order to
understand this
[Music]
what do i have to look up on youtube
tell me
anything else lamar
rose franklin
all right
in real life comparison why is there
what's this real-life version
which one should i watch what the hell
is this
well i'm watching
i'm watching the gta v lamar rose
franklin in
real life comparison synced
[Music]
oh that's where that's where mikko
senpai said that word
ah
ah that's where that came from
ah but honestly what the hell
is not even proud because i don't know
the context but this is not funny
it's not even funny
you guys stupid stupid
stupid super stupid
wait should i play that game on stream
is that game hard can i play gta v do
you guys think i have the skills for it
do it it's not hard it's easy
a car game yeah i just want to drive
around
is it very sturdy focused
yeah i mean i like story but i also want
to just drive around
just want to turn on my eurobeat and
just drop on the highway
that's all i want to do but okay
i am kind of curious to finally play a
gta game the way it's supposed to be
played
play gta online paul
actually i should play sliver.io with
european music in the background
anyway thank you multiple account name
for the super chat thanks for jumping
into the joke i
see you are one of the educated members
i didn't think of you as such a person i
didn't know
i didn't know you were into those kind
of memes
you know more than me that's that
every now and then jacob 47
this is what you meant when you called
yourself elite kiara when did i call
myself elite piano
when did i when did i call myself up
i'm not getting any jokes today i'm not
getting any references today at all
[Music]
i mean maybe i did at some point like
what like one moment
ah when i told my shrine maiden story
why did i call myself that ah because of
miko's because miko senpai is a shrine
okay makes sense the connections
well i'm getting really hungry and sick
right now sick because i'm too hungry
but we're almost done thank you soon
[Music]
thank you for telling me it's a red
super chat i wouldn't have known thank
you that was very necessary please keep
on doing that every time you send
another red super chat please
i need it my first ever read super chat
thank you tanjo for all the laughs and
the feels thank you for the hard work
and effort you give
for the sake of peak content and big
thanks to all the kfb employees for
being fun and wholesome
to be around with i cove you guys
what does that mean again now what does
that mean
so what does that mean is
what is what does that mean
[Music]
a pre-chat meme
ah you guys had some fun again huh
uh-huh you guys are having maybe a
little bit too much fun in the pre-chat
huh
are you guys spreading the mindset of
hashtag woke hashtag yolk
properly are you
yes okay i will check up on that
i will have to really see if you're
really
spreading that mindset properly
by the way we're not a cult thank you
for the red super chat oral realm
wow thank you soon i appreciate it
you said i i love you guys to as if you
were saying that to the viewers but
i hope you love me too or do you only
love the viewers do you love me too
you love me too
my stomach is making loud noises because
i'm getting really hungry
[Music]
[Applause]
that's it guys that's it good night i
had fun today i need to eat something
and take some rest again and uh
it was a fun week with you guys i will
take tomorrow rough
and i'll be back with animal crossing
looking forward to getting that started
so that i have something to
just like chillingly play
off screen off stream i actually was
feeling like
like playing animal crossing recently
but i was like uh
i first gonna make a new world uh on
stream so that i can play it off stream
because i wanted to restart
so yeah looking forward to that thank
you thank you thank you thank you thank
you for watching today i hope you
enjoyed
uh playing among us i'm trying to get uh
this week to have a little bit more you
know
change in games
[Music]
and i don't know if i will get you guys
to um visit my island right in the first
stream we might just want to set up
everything and just get started
um but keep your bells definitely it
might not happen in the first stream but
i will
i will take your money eventually thank
you wild mixes thank you soon
don't forget to post your schedule i
already did
it's uh on twitter ah but i think
maybe i didn't post it in the community
did i forget that
i always like it's hard to think of that
okay okay i will i will post it in the
community
okay well then in german we say
[Music]
my schedule is pinned on twitter though
if you want to check it out
bye bye thank you for watching
[Music]
you