​
​​​ ​Watsooon!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get your grubby hands off my trident.​ ​​
​​​ ​H-Hey, Gura.​ ​​
​​ ​I wasn't going to take it...​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, I only wanted​ ​​
​​ ​to borrow it for a second.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah well, last time you "borrowed" it,​ ​​
​​ ​it was gone for 3 years.​ ​​
​​​ ​THREE SHARK YEARS!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was like 9 minutes in Ame time...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is it every time I see you two,​ ​​
​​ ​you're bickering like children?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this how a group of idols​ ​​
​​ ​should be acting?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, Fartson!​ ​​
​​ ​Idols shouldn't be stealing!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wasn't stealing it, I—​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you guys know it's March,​ ​​
​​​ ​and the Christmas decorations are still up!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what I was borrowing the trident for!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't believe it's been 3 months already​ ​​
​​ ​since the Christmas party...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's been 3 months since we've cleaned!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just think of it as​ ​​
​​ ​3 extra months of Christmas!​ ​​
​​​ ​That makes sense!​ ​​
​​​ ​Since all the time​ ​​
​​ ​spent with you guys is a gift.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's happening?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoaaa! Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ameee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh nyo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys, you've gotta see this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Wait for me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oi, when the hell did this get here?​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean Gura?​ ​​
​​​ ​We've always been interplanetary idols​ ​​
​​ ​traveling on a spaceship!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right, my dude!​ ​​
​​​ ​Humu.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhh... I think we hit something BIG!​ ​​
​​​ ​HEY, GUYS!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHY ARE YOU SO SMALL?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That is... abnormal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, she must have lost​ ​​
​​ ​her swirly limiter again...​ ​​
​​​ ​CAN YOU GUYS HEAR ME?​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU'RE SO SMALL!​ ​​
​​ ​I JUST WANNA—​ ​​
​​​ ​Exterior Compromised​ ​​
​​​ ​AHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​JESUS F***ING CHRIST!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaah!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAT DO WE DO?​ ​​
​​​ ​HAS ANYONE SEEN HER SIZE LIMITER?​ ​​
​​​ ​DOES IT LOOK LIKE​ ​​
​​ ​I JUST CARRY HER LIMITER?!​ ​​
​​​ ​M-MAYBE IT'S AT THE CLEANERS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe she left it here by accident?​ ​​
​​​ ​AHA!​ ​​
​​​ ​OOOHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sasuga!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, ladies,​ ​​
​​ ​looks like it's time to suit up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is some DOPE fashion,​ ​​
​​ ​I gotta say!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, Girls! IKZ!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Guh-guh-guh guh-guh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Does anybody have a paper bag?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah! Stupid jetpack!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ame... We need​ ​​
​​ ​a better way to do this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hahaha... Oh yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, everyone! Let's conga!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina, take the lead!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, I'll take the rear!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nya nya nya nya nya​ ​​
​​ ​nya nya nya nya nya!​ ​​
​​​ ​NYA-NYA-NYA-NYA-NYA!​ ​​
​​​ ​HEY!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guh!​ ​​
​​​ ​a​ ​​
​​​ ​Alley-oop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm! Sana's hair is so soft!​ ​​
​​​ ​We should be quiet guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think she knows we're here...​ ​​
​​​ ​But I thought sound​ ​​
​​ ​doesn't travel in space!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, that's right, Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​We could yodel and yell,​ ​​
​​ ​and she wouldn't hear us!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can talk in space...​ ​​
​​​ ​because I AM space!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, let's do this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, that was easy.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a worm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sana worm!​ ​​
​​​ ​hehe.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yatta! We did it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whew, I'm beat...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go back inside!​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mere li'l fella!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm smol!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes you are!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who's a widdo worm!​ ​​
​​​ ​We should probably​ ​​
​​ ​take her back to Council.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh, we can't just keep her.​ ​​
​​​ ​B-But...​ ​​
​​​ ​C'mon, Gura, I bet Sana​ ​​
​​ ​wants to go home too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! Plus,​ ​​
​​ ​we visit Council all the time!​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll always be mine​ ​​
​​ ​in my heart.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a space worm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, to Council!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​This one!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHO GOES THERE?​ ​​
​​​ ​Kronini!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, Kronster!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, hi!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our alarms almost​ ​​
​​ ​went off and sawed​ ​​
​​​ ​and lasered you guys​ ​​
​​ ​into tiny chunks and pieces,​ ​​
​​​ ​but Fauna said​ ​​
​​ ​we should disable them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhh, thanks, Fauna.​ ​​
​​​ ​Faufau!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys found Sana!​ ​​
​​​ ​She kinda, like,​ ​​
​​ ​almost capsized our ship!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sana was big!​ ​​
​​​ ​But, luckily your local​ ​​
​​ ​interplanetary idols came to the rescue!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I guess Sana forgot​ ​​
​​ ​her limiter at our place.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, guys,​ ​​
​​ ​for bringing her back.​ ​​
​​​ ​SONUVA BEACH!​ ​​
​​​ ​MUMEI IS CHEATING AGAIN!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! Hey, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​What's with all the construction?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, we're renovating.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're gonna add​ ​​
​​ ​a sweet bathtub that fits 5 people!​ ​​
​​​ ​That sounds dope!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our bodies are still​ ​​
​​ ​under construction, too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, after Ame's elevator messed them up​ ​​
​​ ​at the Christmas party.​ ​​
​​​ ​There you go little one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, don't get lost again, you hear!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sana is eternal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sana is an all-present constant being​ ​​
​​​ ​that can never truly be lost.​ ​​
​​​ ​But, thank you for​ ​​
​​ ​reuniting me with my friends.​ ​​
​​​ ​Being big can be lonely.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aww, I don't understand​ ​​
​​ ​any of what you just said,​ ​​
​​​ ​but you're so cuuute!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mission COMPLEETO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Otsu, everyone!​ ​​
​​​ ​Otsu Myth!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ots—​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​A-Ame?​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks like something near the ship​ ​​
​​ ​is setting off the radar.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it treasure?​ ​​
​​​ ​I could go for some sweet chains, yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh. We should probably​ ​​
​​ ​go check that out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aww, treasure?​ ​​
​​​ ​I want some!​ ​​
​​​ ​This looks important!​ ​​
​​​ ​We should go.​ ​​
​​ ​We'll see you guys later.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye-bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks again!​ ​​
​​​ ​See ya! ...Suckers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anomaly Detected​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder what it could be.​ ​​
​​​ ​It looks tasty...​ ​​
​​​ ​We are running low​ ​​
​​ ​on run time, my dudes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, guys, strap in!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ina, set the coordinates.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, prepare the jump!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sheriff and I call dibs on the guns!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​This place could be dangerous.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, Ame.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ame, which button is it again?​ ​​
​​​ ​This one?​ ​​
​​​ ​That wasn't so bad...​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAHHH AHH AHHHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Calli, Calli! We're here!​ ​​
​​​ ​O-Oh...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm cool.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sha-har-hark!​ ​​
​​​ ​You were all, like,​ ​​
​​ ​"Ooh! Ahh!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Grr!​ ​​
​​ ​Come here, you little...!​ ​​
​​​ ​Suit up, ladies!​ ​​
​​​ ​Radar's a-beepin' and we're goin' in!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whew, we made it!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's kind of hot here...​ ​​
​​​ ​Could make a good vacation spot!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh! We could put​ ​​
​​ ​a kiddy pool over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​And then... Oh, and over there,​ ​​
​​ ​we could put a cooler​ ​​
​​​ ​and have, like,​ ​​
​​ ​a bunch of drinks and stuff!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​A couple of beers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm! Some cold pudding...​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, Ina,​ ​​
​​ ​you've got the magic touch!​ ​​
​​​ ​Humu humu...​ ​​
​​​ ​This way!​ ​​
​​​ ​This place is kind of spooky, guys...​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't worry, I'll watch your backsides!​ ​​
​​​ ​It reminds me of the Underworld a bit!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ehh! Calli, I wanna go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, we've talked about this!​ ​​
​​​ ​The Underworld's no place​ ​​
​​ ​for someone who WON'T DIE!​ ​​
​​​ ​But, why not?​ ​​
​​​ ​I could sneak into your house​ ​​
​​ ​and surprise you, hehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​Like old times!​ ​​
​​​ ​What are you talking about?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, did you hear that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Eh... It's probably just the wind. Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​That must be it!​ ​​
​​​ ​It kinda looks like some sort of portal...​ ​​
​​​ ​Or a big ol' snow globe!​ ​​
​​​ ​I see something shiny inside!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whew... Whew...​ ​​
​​​ ​Just give me a sec!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh! Let's investigate!​ ​​
​​​ ​But, try not to press​ ​​
​​ ​any weird switches or buttons.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, guys?​ ​​
​​​ ​What's that big glowy rock in the middle?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe it's some sort of bomb.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to touch it...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, no! Watch out!​ ​​
​​​ ​What? Look!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm fine!​ ​​
​​​ ​Were you worried about me, Calli?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why you—​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, wow, it actually​ ​​
​​ ​feels pretty nice in here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too, me too, me too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Umm, I don't know if​ ​​
​​ ​we should go in there, you guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh! There's a little thingy here!​ ​​
​​​ ​It says...​ ​​
​​​ ​4...D?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh, I wonder what​ ​​
​​ ​that could mean.​ ​​
​​​ ​It kinda feels nice in here, y'know?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a, like a warm spot in the pool.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe, y'know?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm...​ ​​
​​​ ​If the radar is beeping, that stone​ ​​
​​ ​could contain some valuable materials...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's try to take it back​ ​​
​​ ​to the ship and scan it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna take it!​ ​​
​​​ ​No, me!​ ​​
​​​ ​This rocks!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't break it, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll keep watch out here—​ ​​
​​​ ​What the...?​ ​​
​​​ ​MUAHAHAHAHA!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys fell for my trap!​ ​​
​​​ ​What! Who said that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Show yourself!​ ​​
​​​ ​It is I, IRyS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here to deliver hope to the people!​ ​​
​​​ ​What does that even mean? Why—​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​My hand's stuck!​ ​​
​​​ ​Urgh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Mine too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why are you doing this, IRyS?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm just giving​ ​​
​​ ​the people what they want!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, ta ta!​ ​​
​​​ ​No-No, wait, wai—​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehehehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oof!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eughh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oww!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alley-oop!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you guys there?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't see anything!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's really dark!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you guys hear that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think we're alone...​ ​​
​​​ ​SQUEEE!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys guys, I think we're on a stage!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh mah gawd!​ ​​
​​​ ​A what now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mina! POSE-U!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh boy, I am not ready for this!​ ​​
​​​ ​My tail feels so real!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't wait to dance!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this mic on?​ ​​
​​​ ​Test test...​ ​​
​​​ ​Wah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Japanese fans!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pay attention to us in 3D!​ ​​