[Music]
wow
so
[Music]
wait
wow
so
[Music]
wow
me
go
[Music]
i've been listening to really nice cat
noises
sorry i haven't eaten
ah we had our a way out collaboration
so i didn't get a chance i'm gonna go
into the call
with the others but hold on just a
moment hang on
let's go let's go to the place where i'm
playing games
wait what
ah here we are here we are sorry where
we last left off um my pc got sabotaged
yeah there's a growly noise hang on i'm
gonna go connect with the other girls
hang on yes i'm ready
i'm going
hold on okay let's say hello hello
huh what about the bathroom hey guys
maybe don't continue because my
deadbeats are here
we're lurking now
i think so yeah um
[Music]
let's test everyone's volume everyone
say things
good everyone say something everyone
says
[Music]
that's what i thought it was a little
low oh my god
oh my god seems fine
no one's complaining on my side are you
good i think everything's good
see yeah let's see mario
kick oh you turn up at me
[Music]
is everyone already in the holiday mood
jingle jangle i mean it's all right
can we all meet up at the portal
everyone around here
okay hang on i'm turning up everyone
full volume
200 everyone oh boy
plan the voice is definitely peeking
okay that's fine that's fine you know
what
happens to the best happens to the best
of us all right
[Music]
let me turn down my mic okay maybe this
is okay
yeah everyone is like 200
[Music]
someone going back and forth in the
portal i keep hearing ina is that 200
volume
i have like 12 i think i have too many
but then again there's never such thing
as too many times okay
your house is looking good now
thank you amelia added a nice touch on
top i don't really know what i think it
looks
better
yeah i think i definitely made a big
contribution did you get rid of
my chickens oh yeah
i ate them oh wow
sky yeah you could say middle
i think the answer is clear if you have
to uh ask
[Laughter]
where's my sword here we go
i got a cat everything
he came out of the wall he just came
flying out of the wall uh i don't really
know how he did it
um and they just showed up someone
else's cat maybe
uh nope it didn't have a collar yeah
there's water
to your house yeah
why is it that when gouda walks all this
dirt comes up
you too amelia you too
i didn't come here to be bullied man
you didn't come here too but that
doesn't mean you're not going to be
i'm kidding is this your christmas tree
oh yeah let's go see the christmas tree
oh my god
who is doing that death
christmas tree
[Music]
i'm hungry
if you look inside this chest yeah if
you look in the box there's like a bunch
of different decorations and
shears you guys can make your snowmen
and they'll be alive
cool
here that have snow and they have the
pumpkin if you grab a sheer from the
chest and you
uh use the sheer on the pumpkin then now
you have a snowman you can take off the
pumpkin
whoa wait what that's cool how do i get
in here
there's nothing oh
[Music]
man and then you can take the pumpkin
off if you want to or you can leave it
oh my god i want it i always try
escaping i have to put a fence here
that's so cute is that a mod or is it
actually in game a feature
that's in games yeah
and what else do i want i try to escape
oh i saw that one snowman that you made
[Music]
was these snowballs what do i do with
them
uh you can throw them at people with
their life can i build another snowman
i messed up yes how do you build a
snowman yeah how do you do it again
right click with the sheer on the on the
pumpkin
like a few snowballs and you can make a
snow block you don't need like a
a crafting table to do it and then you
can um
put you down and put a pumpkin on top so
i actually
um i know you already prepared a lot of
uh
decorations on it but i also prepared a
bunch of pumpkins so that i can
also contribute so i want to put some
pumpkins on the tree yeah
it doesn't make whatever you want i just
picked some extra stuff that coil
snowman don't mind if i do
no oh but it's going to be hard to
decorate on the other side when there is
literally a cliff there
itself
look at that when i use the snowball it
just uh it
just makes me throw it yeah
yeah you gotta make it in the in the
blocks oh okay
when yeah when you press uh does it eat
i don't get it
oh no i'm out of snowballs no now
i'll get me out of here if you have if
you have a shovel you can also uh
you can dig these snow on the ground
really
what happens if i put a torch as a light
on
on the tree does the tree burn if i put
the toilet in here
glowy i can't put it i can't put it on
there anyway
but yeah we need to lighten the tree up
as well
yes yes set it on fire
no don't worry i'm not gonna say that
is there a color scheme we're going for
or is it just red
whatever you want whatever color i think
it's working yeah
oh i should bring it over the lights
bring some hollow that i've colored all
over you put them wherever you want wait
i gotta climb up this elevator thingy
should we build a star on top yes
i don't know it's like redstone lamps or
i have these shroom
shroom lights either work it's growing
so pretty
damn whoa eh no not the bread can you
not put the
scaffolding on a bush oh no
the ornaments i want to apply the
ornaments i want to put on like a
temporary
dirt block or something and then you put
it on top of that
why can't i use the red buttons does
anyone here
already have a tree in their home so you
put it on the side of the wall cali
oh can you do that
music do you mean i can put it can i put
them on the vines i wonder
on the grass it's not that's very
strange oh you got to put it on sideways
stuff like
on the wall oh
[Laughter]
this is not over yet
sorry it's okay
the crimson roots those also are not
that what a shame oh zombies
oh wait can we have a snowball fight oh
yeah like
yeah that's what i did before i was
hitting on there with something
right there i made a contribution it
stares right at my arrow
i want to get to the top is that ken not
yet
the words come in handy the ones i
taught you oh yes
delicious where'd you go
where'd you go oh boy
where'd you come from where'd you go
where did you come from cotton nigel
huh huh
there you go to the top of this tree i
see i need to bring some stronger
weapons
sarah hasn't spotted her yet
she's going she's going to get more
weapons
this is what christmas is all about
right of course fighting
fighting we're fighting around
the christmas
who did that oh no i need to eat
something
oh no oh no you need some steak
oh that might be nice actually maybe i
can at least put some bones oh wait no
hold on oh no now all these weird
rocks are in front of our tree because i
tried to make a big
a big tower so i could i could put the
star on the top
i've ruined it to just be able to like
jump around like if you come this way
cali
yeah follow me i think we can get to the
top like this
you just jump on the box oh okay
maneuver around the tree
it should be like a little stairway oh
okay
did you call a uh taco eats let's see
uh
how does it work thank you for the
steaks i got him now
wait okay my inventory is a little low
so hold on let me get rid of something
snowballs i don't need them give me this
i wasted it
i wasted it that's it
what is that what is she plotting now
i was just setting something on fire
don't but don't worry it won't be the
christmas tree
oh damn it i just want to put this bone
somewhere i can't
all the things that i want to put down i
can't put down when you press
and you you click on your inventory you
can drag it out and then just
drop it just drop it somewhere okay cool
yeah i'll do that
yes it makes a star with glowstone it's
like close
oh yeah yeah well there's also the
there's also redstone light but i don't
i'm not sure how to make it
woohoo
oh oh no i'm just going to bring more
scaffolding from home
or snowballs
they're just kind of floating well they
disappear i wonder
music
let us have a snowball fight that was
hard snowballs you goober
what the hell oh no the snowman is
escaping who's that oh that's okay we
can make
more push it back push it back
we're safe okay it's got the whole thing
here's zombie why are so many chickens
i don't know why you tell me why ma'am
[Laughter]
they also want to celebrate
celebration i mean they do eat a lot of
kfc
in uh japan for christmas yeah they do
i don't know what so why on christmas
but
i eat fried chicken every day
don't make it don't make it weird
i have some glowstone i have 28. i took
a bit of it
ah if anybody has redstone dust i can
try making a redstone lamp
okay gotta think
no i'm riding your house for redstone
dust okay
i forgot where i put it but it's in
there somewhere
oh fell down
who is hitting us who's shooting at us
now ladies let's all play fair okay
we're gonna be nakayoshi
yeah could you take a backstab
just not oh not towards the cliff
let me see this one uh i need a little
bit of room for the stars okay
thanks guys have i ever thought
have you ever thought of the theory that
enderman
might just be enma
oh our manager ah
certainly possible oh what
i'm gonna go play some friends surprise
that would be quite a twist
[Music]
what's your building i don't know
whoops i feel like you shut off the
lights
all the different types of lights yeah
look look at this
in my head but stop breaking here
i want to see how it looks from afar oh
yay
a little bit more yellow here
oh they're gone though wow
looks good looking good
i wonder if we could have like a few
more color variations
in the decoration although it looks kind
of cluttered now so i mean
should we add more hmm i think a few
more colors would be nice though
maybe i can have one yeah i think that'd
be good
i'll put mushrooms on it pink and
some of my fancy white glazed terracotta
on it but can i have it back when the
tree is on
mushrooms maybe maybe not because i got
them from far away lands okay
i don't want to lose them next we're
going to blow it up with tnt
they're really fancy that's a nice idea
i like that we can make lots of tnt we
can make fireworks and we can send off
the facts
but before we blow it up
there you go it's pretty easy oh blue
nice okay this is easy i can do blocks
the roots
i can't understand i can't make them
work i tried very hard
it's not working they don't want to go
anywhere ugh the style looks good
i'll take some of that little scuff but
we can improve it later
it's nice i can't get up the scaffolding
ow
it wasn't me it's a chicken
no no no no no i'll eat you don't blame
me down my employees
i'm very innocent it's nothing
of course yes innocent
little more legs
wait is it is the tree lopsided or is it
just me
i don't remember being like that but
it's possible that
i may have forgotten one side
i can't make progress how do you get up
there oh god
uh hold on oh man i can fix this
what did you guys want for christmas
[Music]
well you had to ask but what about
everyone else
oh wait do you need leaves i have like i
want a day of freedom
oh yeah leaves yeah you have leaves yeah
i do oh god
i need them we can make the tree even
bigger
you won't believe how many leaves ah
[Music]
no i'm at my house oh i'll come to you
my house we're gonna hide the
very mixed tree i think so
yeah this is fine you guys like uh when
trees have like themed ornaments or do
you like
when it's uh like a bunch of handmade
different colors oh
i like colors lots of colors it looks
like a more
personal flair to the trees i think
um
[Music]
are you are you guys even gonna get a
treat this year
i'm probably not getting one because uh
i i don't want to get rid of it it's
kind of annoying in here
i'm annoying yeah in you have japan
vacuum after the trees a lot so it's
easier to get a fake one
especially if you have pets and where
are you
because sometimes your pets like to hide
in the trees in the chest
thank you
when you have cats and a christmas tree
that's fine yeah
i had some kittens that were hiding in
the tree one christmas and it was very
cute
[Music]
it was adorable
okay
where's the door oh it was up
thank you thank you
[Music]
if i make the star a little better it's
going to be like bigger than stream
i can't wait to see oh wait it's
glowstone that means it's going to glow
i'm so excited to see you
good guys it's gonna be so much fun
i wish we could make like different
colored lights
and stuff can you oh we can make a we
can make stained glass
hmm oh i have a vanilla glass
nice idea let me go bring some
ah my trees
i'm trying to make it a bit more spacier
we can put even more in decoration it
looks so good from afar
it's so cute yeah nice
little goddammit cute threes are natural
they're not always perfect okay
exactly facts but them being
individually beautiful that's what makes
them special
exactly that's really true
i like that i literally have no idea
what i was just saying but okay
that's a lie you do you know
i'll play in the chest thank you
i only brought like two of each because
that's all i had left over but if you
need more
i have more at home
[Music]
how do we light up this thing glaston
can you light it up
i guess you can put it like in front of
a glowstone or something the light so if
you look from the front it looks like
different color maybe
what if we put torches on the tree will
it catch on fire
i wonder oh really
they don't even place on the on the
leaves oh i guess you'd have to have a
block
well what if you use something like that
what if you put it on an ornament
is it getting too much now what does it
look like still like that still it'll
probably
it's missing a bit of clothes over there
okay i hope it doesn't burn the tree
i think it'll be fine
should we put something under the tree
like a carpeting or something like a
tree skirt that sounds nice
tree skirt right maybe i can
all right
[Laughter]
the tree looks so yummy mm-hmm what can
what color should it go under the tree
guys red
oh yeah red okay
like i'm sorry i'm trying to move
up
oh i'm just gonna hurt myself
are you okay i'm fine are you okay
[Music]
wow i want to see hang on
oh that is so cute
oh my god wow looks neat
these are so cool
there's like a perfect spot for a
photograph there's some
i know the patterns are there can i mean
the decoration for the tree as well i
want to stay on here
oh my gosh
my armor yeah so you look you want to
see me naked in the photo
oh you want me to be there naked okay
[Music]
that's what i like to see as well i see
our tastes are very similar
that's why we are both business owners
taco bell and kfb
hell yeah exactly oh i think we could
use one more
stone way up there okay
[Music]
let's see let's see we can make a
christmas card and then we can sign it
and then we can post it
yeah nice idea wow it looks really
that's a great idea i like that
let's do it again happy holidays
[Music]
while i eat these potato chips i will
provide a view of the christmas tree
for everyone do you eat anything besides
potato chips
is there a reason too
and bread that's that's your favorite
food i'm gonna order some vegetables
later for lunch i wonder what i should
have for lunch wow
i mean potato is a vegetable right yes
yeah yeah before potato chip is
vegetable
healthy yes agree
i also agree that fried chicken is
healthy and pizza is health is not noise
oh oh we gotta sleep we gotta sleep oh
oh god
what was that noise that reminds me of
our first home
in my crap collab i'll shoot them down
guys
don't worry wait good or did you guys
shut them down one day's in there
and i have one button yeah buddy
oh my gosh somewhere
wow the skies are safe another day kind
of
i feel bad i wish i was there to help i
tried to go to sleep
you guys remember the first minecraft
collab where we all just got at the
start
yeah that was fine how times have
changed
how they have i guess there's a party
going on in my chat right now
oh yeah hi
[Music]
just reached 1 million yay
i knew it would happen soon
you did it
all right let's go i'm ready for battle
maybe we should sleep they
what if they destroy our tree yes
destroy our lives
we can take them thank you caleb
thank you i love you guys oh sweet
where is it i see it and then he spotted
i'm just going to sleep he's hissing oh
this isn't he had the cat i don't think
he likes the cat
oh wow yeah you know i think i'll go
ahead and
go to sleep uh are you sleeping or not
i'm gonna go to sleep
i go to sleep sometimes the best option
in a battle is just to sleep
i will i will i will also sleep i'm
sleeping on your cat's gardena
okay are you sure you can cause the
phantoms around
i think so i'm gonna sleep to the
calming
you know very relaxing from the ocean
some people don't like princesses
thank you everyone oh my god they're
still partying
party party party oh they're going to
burn to tax
disco inferno
[Music]
you're cute
second edition yes i love that um
you know how many cats do you have uh
yes alrighty
understood i see there was actually a
cat that looked just like the first
edition
i think it was girl's girl's kiss oh
yeah it's like the uh the three
different colored ones
you have such a nice house oh yeah yeah
yeah i have a lot of cats now i can't
really remember what they all
look like i think we're gonna have more
and more cats because of the
iron i mean i'm fine with that
they're so cute i want more i only have
one but i want me
i want millions of cats in my home
yes wait what is this can i ask what
this is
is this like
the photo zone for
tree's looking good it
really is i'm really happy with it
oh i kind of want to put that one he's a
little more red oh
he's just a little more red in my
opinion more red
just a little more red like bright red
like this kind of red
you know oh like red red red red red red
red red red red
red i can't
[Music]
oh good idea i have some red if you
would like to do it do you want to do it
yes please give me some red
wait hey
nice thank you
oh yeah i guess our elevators are gone
huh
oh it's okay no worries
it's all good in the hood i think i'll
just climb it the old-fashioned way
oh yeah there's some scaffolding who
tried to shoot me
while i was partying with my employees
who tried to shoot me zombies you're by
the edge
oh really oh really oh really oh really
good uh
you're gonna sound suspicious
you really think i'm gonna do that i'll
watch the archive i'll see
what happened there okay guys this is
unarchived
it's okay it's okay um it's okay i like
being shocked
it feels good yeah she's used to dying
yeah
i like pain i'm a masochist yep
okay christmas i don't look
beautiful i wish we could add one of
those how how do you
stop it my turn how do you call those
hanging things
yeah the hanging ones i tried so hard
but the vines work out yeah i've tried
to put them on
i kept destroying those my bed
[Music]
i'll bring him i'll go get him
are you talking about like tinsel that
you wrap around the tree you know
something like yeah
oh it's just laying down but we can we
can oh
but that's cool yeah why don't i hear a
zombie
is there anything you don't have i'm
telling you guys there's zombies
everywhere
i keep hearing them just like but
there's no there's no caves
careful they got arrows too they'll
shoot you you sure do
they'll get you i'm gonna get them in
snowballs
what's for christmas dinner by the way
oh
oh my god the sound of
the sound of snow when you walk on it
isn't it amazing
can't crunch up anymore cornstarch
exactly
you can only have 16 at a time it seems
good i have to tell you something
from this christmas buddy no no from
very close
deep into your eyes
[Music]
you look beautiful
i think these snowballs would do some
damage so we can have like an actual
snowball fight that would be fun
and we could throw we can throw some uh
arrows at each other so
we can hit each other with swords until
we die
maybe we should build that we should
build a coliseum
yeah for snowball fights oh good we can
fight to the death
ring yes i did
you bought like a fighting ring yeah
they fell over to my house
do we want to have a battle christmas
battle
i'd like a christmas battle forget the
christmas dinner it's time for the
christmas battle yes the christmas
battle that's what i'm concerned about
not your not your chicken bring us back
kfc and yeah exactly i'll just bring you
well
actually that's not really my job it's
kind of my job to keep you from coming
back but uh you could ask somebody else
you know just wink yeah just let us you
know
there's five for just
[Music]
is suspiciously quiet has anybody seen
watson
i'm in the tunnel
i'm going to get vines and i'll be i'll
be back in like four minutes but i
thought vines only take six seconds
okay oh my goodness there she goes
i'm so proud of myself
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
kiara you are on fire tonight
he's always on fire
i can't stop myself oh my god
i know my potato chip bag pushed it up
to them
yeah i like it
i can't do it that's right oh were you
going to make an attempt on my life
no you were going to make an attempt on
my life kusa you don't have a life
you're you're deaf
exactly that's the point which is why it
wouldn't work
i don't know why i feel like battling
good albums
oh wait are you guys oh so you're
attempting oh
this looks so good i really like it
adding a little snow to the top i don't
want all these circles ah
a frosted christmas tree nice idea
like guy fairy yeah yeah that's right
like that guy
tasting around the christmas tree
[Music]
oh i want to put some coming back yay
you killed him no man do your thing oh
he only
you gave him a life yes i saved him from
i don't know how do you put it down the
snow
how do you put it down uh oh do you mean
yeah snow
man or snow no the snow the snow on the
on the ground
on the it's like uh what is it not a
snowball
it's what you're doing right now you
take the snowballs and you go in your
inventory and you line them up in a
straight line i think
that's how you make them oh me what yeah
you just fill
your uh crafting sauce got it no balls
and then you get snow blocks got it or
you can get you can get like the little
little snow thingies i like that flat
one
yeah cool snow thingies oh yes
yeah there's no thingies
what would you call them they're like
platforms i don't know i guess that's it
and there's snow sheets yeah yeah yeah
oh okay like this
wait wait i need some white ornaments
too the torches remove the snow oh
no a snow carpet and
wait was made oh yeah
yeah they put lanterns i don't think
it'll melt them awesome
i think all the snowman just fell down
anyways oh
uh oh oh no more snow can you put the
snowman on a lead
oh it's a good question yeah can we put
a saddle on him
can we ride the snowman can we make a
snow horse that's what i want to do
hi he's so cute though he's so cute
mary mary
well at least there's still more and
more snowmen just jumping up and down
aha they're cute
they're the kids for our christmas
dinner
i
hold on let me lean back i got an idea
oh we should get the uh those red bushes
they're like holly we can put a holly
oh yeah yeah
yeah nice idea
i want a mistletoe yeah
i want it that's awesome where can we
put it
here it sounds
[Music]
are you making an igloo i'm going
i brought some red yes um
i had potato chips in my mouth should we
make lanterns for the
well i thought the torches look like
candles but like i was wondering if we
could make like bigger candles with like
oh uh
oh yeah yeah yeah okay we have so many
portraits
and then we have to mix up some of these
nice idea
here and this one oh they're coming
again
time to run
phantom oh my gosh are you fighting them
all right nice nice nice
don't provoke them oh i've got five
shots there's a fox here
uh grab something good oh maybe not i
can't drop
anything there's a cute box in here
hello friend
nice shot nice shock yeah
the tree looks so good from the distance
too is there a bed in the kitchen
so pretty
christmas cake oh that's going to be a
cake
yes wow we're making a cake too
cool i have a lot of wool as well
[Music]
yes shouldn't the ground layer be
i mean okay it's all going to be out of
cream okay
again why not but we could have it land
a layered cane good mm-hmm put some
strawberries yellow and white
oh the same on top it's strawberry
strawberry and then you're gonna have
the sides showing so you can see the
strawberry
plate yeah yeah you can build on top of
it
okay you have yellow for cake oh this is
a i mean i have pumpkins why am i
holding an egg in my hand while i'm
sleeping
does that look like from the side like
it could be
what we want it to be but do you have
yellow
carrots no one's sleeping
a layer of what
sarcasm um
you see this vine here yeah i guess
it'll blend in i don't know
it would hang you can hang it off of oh
okay oh
let's give it a try get on with it okay
let's see what happens
wow cool it makes an interesting
it looks interesting oh that's
i see they're only in green uh
yeah except for the ones from another
but i guess you can't put those on the
tree for some reason or maybe i grabbed
the wrong ones
weird oh the
i'll put some on the glowstone that'll
look neat
uh-oh i forget someone's hot i heard
something
oh no where is it
where is it
oh three o'clock by the tree let's go go
down
by the tree oh no i'm not good enough
who gets it who gets it
oh don't ruin our tree i have my battle
axe
before one two three
four come closer oh my oh my oh my oh my
yeah could just stop
doesn't even care about us it's just
chilling
you don't want to get afraid of the oh
my oh my god
is that a thing they don't like animals
are afraid of cats and like
dogs really
all the more reason to have lots more
cats yes get all the cats
thank you uh
kind of afraid to be near the tree right
now damn it
okay uh should we get a buddy
damn it i brought yellow does this look
okay
oh is that too yellow yeah i can do that
you can do that
okay yeah
one nice kiara very good
i'm gonna drop something for you
why is that
phantom membrane what is that cool that
sounds stupid
do you want it i mean you kind of killed
it no it wasn't really me
yeah i did yeah i don't know what that
is i don't want this sounds gross
that's good you can do it that membrane
oh it's usually repair electrodes
oh that's useful
[Music]
does anyone have an uh elytra yet
and then you can fly with those you can
do it a long way an enderman yeah
my chat says you should destroy the tree
how rude
i would never destroy the tree yeah
now we had like four that she got for
free
from this one in the lava oh hey i
didn't want to
now listen
our tree no get away from the tree
everyone
we lead them away kill it with fire we
will not do such a thing
go away i'll try and drag them away okay
can we can we
kill them with snowballs it's fine it's
almost morning we just need to
keep them distracted until the sunrise
[Music]
thank you snowmen i'm missing everything
that's dope how's this guy doing he's
going the wrong way man the battle's
this way what are you doing
thanks guys for helping you nice snowy
dudes
big snowballs put down the base
where do we start how many blocks do we
go
like right right here here
like where i'm going to help one more
hang on
yeah do it so that there's like one more
one um yeah yeah i could have sworn i
had one
one white block on the very edge i think
that i'll do
you got it no that doesn't work i need a
shovel kelly
yeah you only wanna do you want to come
up here for a second
for what where are you just to see it no
nice try you need to be a little more
creative than that arm
please yeah yeah a little more creative
yeah i'm gonna borrow a bunch
what is this i will wait for you
like this you didn't come to kiss me
i think we need one more here
no more here yes oh oh
are you actually making a proper thing
i'm in
there
beautiful i have i have these red
these red things here that we can put we
can use them as
as uh as strawberries on the cake
yes yeah they look like this is a really
nice bright strawberry yeah it's a nice
strawberry yeah yeah it sure does so
let's use those strawberries i'm helpful
are we done with the tree itself it
looks done
yeah it does i don't know
okay christmas cake no i will not burn
everything dude where's the pizza sama
what the
with your danny devito icon
no danny devito i will not burn our
christmas tree
excuse you they're asking the one person
they could ask
them phoenix right exactly
like oh i think i'm scaffolding closer
i have a little addiction when it comes
to fire i enjoy fire a little
[Applause]
they do another cake layer yes
who's up in that in that glass
i'm curious you guys sure do a lot of
things in this game huh
but they're all villagers they're
villagers will you burn it for 10
no no amount of money that you can
you're just going to be wasting your
money deadbeats you'll be wasting your
money
any more cake out hey
exactly this was a chicken leg that i
was hitting you with
are you guys hurting each other come on
no we're pretty full
you're pleased and having fun
it looks like you're high fiving each
other with your fists
got it
we're being good buddies and good
buddies like to touch each other
every once in a while what huh
what
what's bad about hatching what's battle
touching come on
i mean i mean yeah i can't focus
somebody's making the
the cake baking station hostile i can't
pronounce it
now we need we need more cream well
hello you know here
it looks really good i got the i got the
i got
the whipped cream
[Music]
of course we are what the hell little
bit of touching is
there's nothing wrong about that okay
where do i put these strawberries
[Laughter]
you burn it down for a scooby snack no
would you do it for two scooby snacks
well she's making three gosh now that
you said two
can i put the all right i think i think
we're good for the strawberry now
and oh you gotta do it like a like yeah
like a clock right like
drink drink and then going
i didn't take screenshots again looks
tasty
yeah was it f2 f2
ah yeah oh yeah oh yeah
we made it making off photos here what
i'm leaving this area i even i don't
even care about myself
what the hell no no photos like that
what are you taking a little off the
progress what the hell
wait do you only have to stop you said
don't don't you do that to me
because that's already
[Music]
oh
wait this isn't going to work uh
we gotta improvise yeah i got some more
strawberries
more strawberries one right right here
it really look like strawberries
yummy like huge
they have one for each member oh a big
one
big straws big strawberries
i know this is not a birthday cake but
should we put candles on top of the
strawberries oh nice oh that could be a
good idea do you think the strawberry
looks a little
weird hey who put that
i think it's acquired not exactly a
strawberry
will you burn down the tree for
unprotected hand holding with kiara what
the is wrong with
what i'm gonna cut down this tree any
objections
no no i'm sorry no no no christmas
kisses no christmas kisses
i put those trees there because i was
gonna hide anvils at the top so when you
guys cut them down they would fall on
you but it didn't work out
so yeah that would have been funny
though come on think of the contest
for the content yes
[Music]
oh wait i got an idea
hmm christmas steak
hold up i got a very special block i can
light on fire
ooh i forgot where i put it though
oh there you go a second cr if i made a
second christmas tree and burned that
one down
to make for a cozy fire well that's a
great idea
just make a bonfire
[Music]
this is cute
no you finish you
[Laughter]
like a chicken dinner uh-huh
wait bye-bye i
am
[Music]
wow that sounds interesting i want to
see
hold on it's nice in here
wow are you inside the cake beautiful
yeah what i'm just chilling
it's like the uh you know when you make
like a marriage proposal and then
uh
with me it's your it's your
it's your wedding cake ellie
this is how you eat a cake normally in
my country
would you rather burn the holo ian
christmas tree or kiss your wife
don't ask me question kiss my quote
unquote
wife kusa i don't
i spit it back out and i put it back on
the cake it's fine
oh that's kind of your slice
why are you guys scared of some shark
cooties is that what it is
that sounds so weird
[Music]
can we put some cats in the tree what
are you doing to my candle there
cats in the tree yeah that could be fun
if we put one of the cat like
put some cats on the tree like his
little decorations
i wanted yeah you know you have a ton of
cats right can you grab some put them on
the tree ah
i know we can do it we can get both of
them
we can go sledding
yeah on the on the ice there's an ice
biome at the end of ppp or somewhere
close
i have a bunch of ice i can't bring it
hold on i'll go get the ice
we can transform the fighting ring into
a skating ring
that's nice a little bit maybe yeah
that'd be pretty big yeah
[Music]
will you give me permission to build a
giant chicken on top of your uh
huh i mean we can build it together
because that's what i wanted to do
anyway
um there's a blueprint for it before oh
yeah oh yeah please
yes i got a lot of will uh wool as well
so mm-hmm let's do it together
yeah majestic chicken i'm gonna make the
ice glue
but the thing is we gotta make it look
like
a little bit like a phoenix so that my
my employees don't misunderstand
what it actually what we actually sell
but it's it's
laser chicken you know what i just
realized
the christmas tree is right above my
home i'll think about it
it's right on top of my cave nice
perfect
i mean i worked you can come see some of
it i worked on it a bit yeah
yeah i want to see yeah you can come
take a look i still don't have a proper
door but you know
we do our best zombies
do you like my ghost rider picture yeah
it's ghost rider i was
very worried i got super lucky i picked
it up as a gotcha
oh my god there's a zombie and then
there's in kitchen up here i'm
still working on it but bitching kitchen
is up this letter
is this your pet or chemical what is my
pet
that's my kitty oh the zombie oh you can
kill that what there's a zombie
it's time for food i have your salmon
thank you i have your salmon buddy hold
on
let me give them something i'm saying
your cave has potential
you're gonna have to i don't know
otherwise
she was told that before but she didn't
believe it i didn't one
i listen i just didn't want to do it
because they told me to do it
listen she doesn't want to be told what
to do she's a rebellious teenager
don't tell me what to do this is not a
face mask
let's get you uh a door okay chris
watson
thanks oh i'm getting ice but i already
have a bunch of eyes so i'm just picking
it up and then i'll be back in like
four minutes okay okay baby
door
yes callie i got the perfect door for
you
punching bag really love that salmon huh
shut up
listen i don't know how buttons work in
this game so on occasion when i try to
feed my cat the sam and i end up hitting
the cat with the salmon instead of
getting in this
i just don't play this game often
there's only ones i do
ina you may be a door it's a nice color
too
thank you nice a real door hooray
thank you so much would you say it's uh
adorable
how's everyone doing my god i can't i
can't
i can't you know
[Music]
i'm not gonna make that what i'm doing
there's not many people in here what the
hell they're reading sharks what's
raining sharks and squids
oh cool can i fight can i go kill some
more fish i need more food for my kitty
ah yay can i kill the squid too
need more employees here
not enough people working at kfc why did
everyone quit their jobs what the hell
i don't know ten show i think you need
to look at yourself mad in that respect
why did they leave i wonder i don't know
i've heard some stories
i've heard some stories i've heard some
stories though
tortured every now and then they'll love
me they would never leave me
for me or did the zombie not have a face
that would never leave me i think it was
just you
had a face for me maybe it was through
the back of their head
i couldn't tell it was looking at me
maybe i think you're coming in from the
side of it
yeah look how good this looks this is so
good i have some ink sacs
oh
i have some anvils nice
and maybe the cats will come to it do
you like it i've been told it's a finger
apparently
it's a very interesting hat yeah maybe
maybe that's how they say hello to
each other oh where am is from where are
you coming up
the uk is now they say hello
wait let me try hello i'm okay hello
hello is that how it sounds
[Music]
i will not let them be hurt by a stupid
zombie
god kill me i hate it i gotta stop
they'll they're gonna kill me
they're going to kill me people from the
uk i'm sorry i don't mean any disrespect
to that the aussie twang
oh yeah i can't do today
g'day there you go you've got it
i got the cowboy covered though with my
southern raw
it's real authentic
subscribe to my youtube channel
it's not working
[Laughter]
i love youtubers
you guys sound legit oh yeah
amazing
all right anyway how's that ice coming
along i'm almost back i'm in the tunnel
on the way back
i have 52 ice well fifty it's nice
cool maybe we can make a long slide or
something
instead he's got an egg
yeah he's gonna make us breakfast
oh wow i don't want that that would
probably taste really bad
no i need i want to see if i can uh
oh this house is so cool
wait this is crazy wow
those ink sacks
raw flesh i like collecting that
excuse me kiara i i
i'm just uh admiring your beauty when
the sun is
coming up you shine even more
beautifully than ever
oh oh my god
cutie oh we know nothing's as beautiful
as you might take
the cake looks beautiful where the tree
the cake is almost bigger than the tree
though
it looks really nice thick cake
yeah it's enough for everybody
[Music]
oh yeah you should probably get rid of
this uh yeah
thank you thank you new audience
do you see our delicious cake and our
beautiful tree
and where do you guys think we should
build i have all the ice but where
should we put
like an ice maybe an ice slide because
if you go really fast on the boats but
then
wait who is building something on the
mountain oh
which mountain oh that's good that's
so cool but it's what is good at
building up there
yeah nice idea can you go down ice like
that is it so slippery
oh you're right ina it's a cutting board
just
thank you thank you she doesn't like
that
she doesn't need one she is the cutting
board all right i'll
i'll put stairs let's go up there
okay heading on up
a spider oh well can you just be my
stairs up there
do you guys want something raffling out
what the heck man
uh-oh what's happening why are you
coming after me
amelia what is that x you're using you
ain't legged freak what's wrong with you
spider-man
we'll just use this
okay let me get some idea spiders have
eight legs right
[Music]
mostly yes okay
why
i like the view from here nice the tree
looks also nice from here it sure does
hi that's a weird treat
oh the tree on top of your house
looks very weird
[Laughter]
i gotta get one of those you guys are
nuts
i'm getting one and i'm getting um i'm
getting the same mic as
several of you because my one right now
is just better for music really
it's just better for music same go xlr
hell yeah
[Applause]
somebody do like this side with blocks
like either dirt or concrete and then
the other side and then
uh we won't fall off when we when we go
really fast
oh you mean like uh i need a little
uh fence to make sure we don't
die that's the way that might be the fun
part
who gets the furthest without dying
but with bodies
we'll do it over this uh this ditch here
you know so you guys uh
it's more fun that way the channel pick
up a little pool of water at the bottom
so we can like wee into it ah
yeah um or maybe i should maybe i should
it's a it's an icy diving board of death
yeah walk the plank that's fun
i'm gonna put a sharp turn here oh
[Music]
oh it got close i the leap of faith
i'm dropping i'm dropping a bunch of
boats if anybody wants to pick up a boat
something about you don't want to like
uh
you don't want to like put us put a put
some stuff on the side so we don't fall
off easily
that's what i'm bringing some dirt now
though guys i can
make this safe for us no wait i can make
it safe
this is not regulated this does not pass
the safety check
i'm a land boat wait i'm going to put
away my diamond stuff
somewhere
oh she could bumper you all don't be
fine
i'm making this i will make this place
safe i will make it safe so help me
and i brought that i brought extra dirt
so help me poseidon i will
oh my god
i'll get some water yeah
i'll make some what i like blue
yeah your color is better yeah it's
pretty blue it's very nice
good can i make this longer or will it
end there
get away go away
whoever falls off first is cool
platter falls off versus stinky stinker
stinkerton
yeah i guess something you know to ride
[Music]
oh
that's cool oh really
how do i leave it i just find that i
want to leave the spot
the curve here the curve kind of slows
down everything i want to leave this
boat i don't want to beat it anymore
how do i get out of it how do i get out
of the boat
oh no
oh
[Music]
oh we should i see scaffolding going up
my my my my mind
i'm sorry no my scavenger
my it's actually having fun
yeah it is unfortunately your boy
actually has to dip
out i have a meeting i thought it would
only be an hour 30 minutes for this
okay okay okay you guys can keep going
though keep having fun you guys can keep
going
like uh like straight so we can go zoom
and then just fly
oh yeah okay
okay okay so take a picture in front of
the uh
oh yeah before i head out yes
wait that's awesome nevermind if it was
here i was gonna
accidentally break the ice block that
she was happening
don't worry about it okay let's go uh
take a picture yeah
okay we go down to the tree
yes this is and we have the tree edge
the cake on the
picture oh we can probably find an angle
we can do
that cool i'm coming
i'll go too
time to take selfie oh it looks kind of
prettier during the night should we wait
until it's night
oh i think it's understanding right now
isn't it yes he's just telling me like
a minute yeah let's go on top of here
it won't get both of it but let's at
least cut the tree and then we can get
two angles
f5 f5 there you go
there we go yeah f5 is the change thing
yeah yeah you can probably do you want
to get rid of the
uh hud you want to take off your uh oh
yeah my equipment good idea
ready oopsie my buddy
i'm in yeah i'm here i'm coming
oh i got you dropped it should i what
should i do go get it
no if you want it'll stay there it's
fine
it'll stay there no worries hello
yeah oh it's all before oh how could i
have forgotten
maybe we can all uh crouch
how do you crouch
oh shift okay yes yeah
cool crouching in front of the christmas
tree it's perfect
okay maybe one more should maybe one
more person should be uh doubtful
let me uh shorties in the front
it's so confusing all right
all right down you go girl okay
okay okay one second it's perfect right
now
it's like not too dark okay crouching
how can i get rid of the ui f1 uh f1
oh the screenshot you know you want to
crouch again
what's screenshot again f3 f2 f2
okay other side cake signs
do we want to be on the cake
oh it's really easy let's just see
yeah this sounds good ready are you able
to get up
kind of that's
[Music]
we did it yeah now i gotta say goodbye
but you guys have fun okay enjoy the
rest of your time together
no i mean i think we're all on the end
yeah
oh okay she's not up here
we sure did huh i i i would suggest that
we leave the christmas tree forever
yeah i always i want it forever
i want it forever
[Music]
all right everyone goodbye see ya bye
oh my god they're here
oh no they're killing me they're killing
me
help i left the game please do oh
no i'm definitely dead i'm dead
it it
get it
get kid
[Music]