[Music]
e
a
[Music]
e
Min I forgot to
tweet oh
no I forgot to
tweet it's simple Mor AG just retweet
it hold on I'm rubbing my eyes rubbing
this sleep out of my
[Music]
eyes I thought we were so prepared for
everything here we are again
unprepared it
begins dot dot dot dot dot
dot
[Music]
K I'm
here
mostly hold
[Music]
on look at all that confetti look at it
go hold on I need to reset my face there
we go much better much
better
ah but I still have itchy eyes hello
everyone sorry I'm a mess yet again
howdy howdy birthday howdy birthday
happy howdy birthday hi more hello happy
birthday it's not my birthday yet though
but see that's why we're here right so
that you guys can say happy birthday
when it's time for happy birthday
right oh and I have something that I get
to reveal too that's exciting
[Music]
the timing was perfect Happy Birthday
Eve that works too so soon 51 minutes
away oh
man then when is it look at the
countdown that's why we have the
countdown dead beat
geez wait the reveal is that will not
the
[Music]
second not this second we might wait a
little
bit but we have Callin to do
Etc you can't read cie well you best
start learning I'm going to have to
teach you then I can't tell time sounds
like a lie that sounds
fake and we're finally here performing
for you my cute little
clowns I refuse to learn how to read
well that sounds like quitter
speak it's all about the right attitude
dead beat why do my eyes itch so bad
[Music]
it's got to be allergies I have eye
drops I have them context but I've had
them for a long
time hold on I won't be defeated I won't
be defeated I won't be defeated I won't
you won't get me hold
on cat fur
pollen trifling things to the Grim
Reaper take your time
thanks okay things feel much better than
if I if I just rubbed my
eyes hello everyone that was a very
long- winded intro I made you guys wait
quite a while I'm here I'm here I'm here
but I'm also I'm
winded the intro was long- winded and
I'm winded cuz I just got back in the
door I just settled down I just got back
I I was traveling all day long long oh
boy kept you waiting huh but now I'm
finally back back in business and and
back just in time to do my
[Music]
concert little time to unwind and
whatnot you
know except I decided instead I wanted
to do I wanted to go ahead and go
through with the countdown right cuz
initially initially I wasn't going to do
this I was just going to be like okay
let's just go straight into the concert
not do any of this beforehand right we
were just going to jump right into the
concert and be like hey I'm back
everyone come hang out come see
it but
um no I wanted to say hello I wanted to
say hello to you
guys cuz it's been so long I mean at
least to me it feels like it's been a
long time but but I thought let's go
ahead and count down the momentous
timing and and we can also talk to
friends as well I didn't really set them
up with anything like you know prompt
and stuff like that sometimes we do that
right we'll be like oh hey call into my
birthday call in stream and prepare
something like like what was your
favorite memory of me or what would you
purchase for me etc for my for my gift
um
[Music]
so too much brain
power
a yeah I just want to talk to them I
don't want to think about
something that's the sound of my brain
coming off of a
plane
Parts sweet
rhyming I did I did upload a bunch of
shorts though while I was faren
way yeah oh but I I did I did arrange
for a bunch of people I just didn't give
them a
topic I just told them that I was doing
Callins and and a bunch of almost
everybody was like yeah I'm going to
call in so I'm happy I'm happy I'm
definitely tired but I'm happy it's fine
the shorts for good there were some
really there were some bangers in there
I got to say is it a topic range
[Music]
birthday I'll make you work I'm a good
talker I can keep the conversation going
imagine every single member of Po
calling in
no
nope we'd be here forever for a million
gazillion
years um you're just going to have to
wait and see who calls in
but we we'll see we'll see if everyone
can if everyone can actually truly tune
in because it it seemed like everybody
wanted to but you never know when it
gets down to it like if you think about
it right PST is still pretty early in
the morning right even Yago even Yago
Yago where's my birthday message I've
been working really hard I've been
grinding I've been
grinding the past week not streaming was
tough though and that's right I didn't
stream even once not a single time any
streams appearing on my channel in the
past week or so not
me so it doesn't
count it doesn't count call in speedr
running click hello
goodbye just
Anu what's the point in that what's the
point what's the
point rude crude
dude
[Music]
boy but yeah I'm just going to I'm going
to go wait wait in the special call
center and be like hello feel free to
dial in if you'd like
to kind of thing you know know I thought
to myself maybe I should drink some
coffee to wake up for the dead beats and
I thought wait a minute I have a show
tomorrow can you imagine can you imagine
me being like um I have a show but I'm
going to drink coffee and not go to
sleep not to mention the jet lag but to
be honest I don't really think that my
body fully adjusted you know I just
don't think so also I see that we have
we have some lovely gifts from the dead
beats and I am wanting to I am wanting
to run through that at some point and
look through them but there are some
things that I need to I need to do first
I'm thinking that that we do it during
like um the how do I say birthday Super
Chat reading stream this coming week or
something like that um cuz there are a
couple things I need to confirm first
and foremost I need to confirm a couple
things first um and also I have to I
have to shoot it by management I I
appreciate the dead beats that have put
together so many cool things for me it's
so wonderful but it's just it do be the
protocol got to run it by management it
do be like
that it do be like nothing I could
do yeah but I heard something
about about a special Shinjuku sign unic
a vision I wonder if any dead beats will
go see it I'll be searching for
pictures hey can I show this thing on
stream
by people don't think it be like that
but it
do yeah the
sign I'm
excited
excited oh man and I see some presents
all wrapped up I want to I want to
unwrap them with you guys here though
cuz it's more fun that way you know and
don't worry I won't hide any of that
behind Members Only or anything like
that we'll we'll do it
afterward we'll do it after all that the
members only stream that we're going to
do is more of like just behind the
scenes after talk kind of thing Etc
wouldn't that be so silly if a bunch of
dead Beast prepared a bunch of gifts for
me to open and it's like well you got to
be a member if you want to see me react
to it so sad that would suck you won't
do that good advertising though yeah I
really wanted to do some extra songs
songs um you know was like an encore but
I didn't realize that you could do that
until it was too
late now I'm like well and I asked them
I'm like can I just real
quick I just stay in the studio for a
little bit and do some extra
performances they're like
no they're like we we don't have we
don't have time for that we didn't rent
out the time to do
it next time next
time
next
no they just say no it's pretty strict
to be honest there are a lot of like
strict things and rules Etc and if you
want to do something like that you got
to you got to say way in advance you
know cuz you know staff they can't they
can't stay extra late than later than
what they were scheduled for eight ball
says check again
later but since I want to make sure that
we read all of the all of the
consecutive supers right between this
stream and the next stream I want to be
able to read those and I'm like well why
don't we just look at the look at the
gifts then as
well seems like a good
idea but yeah exactly yeah it's not fair
to just drop out of the sky and be like
I would like to do an encore for members
only when it was something I only really
realized that we could do recently but
for the next one
you know we
will you know we
will yeah it's like understandable have
a good day kind of thing
right
anyway 40 minutes four is a good number
did you know that this is my fourth
birthday with
Holo four whole
birthdays I've shared with you guys here
oh man I'm like trying to think I can
probably remember every single one
the first one was pretty like how do how
do I say it wasn't that it was Bare
Bones I did what I could without really
having like properly shown my my 3D or
anything like that right it was still
fun we had a bunch of decorations lined
up and stuff like that
balloons we sang that was cool but it
wasn't like you know anything over the
top right the following year was a 3D
one
yeah that was cool I'm trying not to get
the mixed up with anniversaries cuz
sometimes I get those mixed up as well
dang oh hold on it's getting kind of
chilly here this isn't a reveal this is
not a reveal by the
way I'm going to go ahead and put on my
[Music]
sweater put on my
sweater I said I want to put on my
sweater there we go go oh I see some
dogs it's still early but happy fourth
birthday Callie Senpai I was about to
say oh my gosh isn't it so isn't it so
early for you but then I'm like oh wait
a minute you guys are running on my time
now hi thank you for the well
wishes a I appreciate that my dogs are
here what's up my
dogs anyway this is this is not a reveal
this is just a this is something that I
just
wanted and got commissioned it's my own
personal sweater Isn't it nice it's
[Music]
baress thank you so much for dropping
by did you see that that said he was
proud of you yes I saw that I almost
teared
up I was very happy I've come along way
since uh since since being on the
podcast um but it it made it made me
very happy was
heartwarming it was really
heartwarming I appreciated that I'm
really doing my best here busy chasing
our taals gum
gum do your best out there and I will I
will do my best to help out if I can you
know where to find me
oh
yeah they're so cute I want to be
helpful I want to be helpful but then at
the same time I'm I'm also figuring out
my own my own how do I say I need to
before I can help other ah my my
jacket's falling off before I can help
other people I need to get my own
together is what I keep telling myself
but I want to keep helping other
people as well I can't help it yeah get
my house in order you know my house is
actually pretty
good I will say it's well put
together sorry this is just a very silly
jacket it's definitely not a cardboard
cut out of a jacket to simulate
warmth oh I'm so glad I'm so glad I've
been helpful I'll keep doing my best
G soon enough you guys will be all
settled in and ready to go you know the
Ruffins are waiting for wait Ruffians oh
my gosh the Ruffins who are Ruffins
sounds like a combination of Ruffians
and muffins sounds tasty the Ruffians
are waiting for
you the Ruffins
[Music]
fans yeah I have two different versions
of this jacket by the way there's one
that has like patterns on the sleeves
and then one that does not but I'm using
the patterned one
[Music]
today
yeah oh man I really kind of want to use
my new thing um I want to use my new
special thing that I'm revealing for the
cins so maybe maybe I should go ahead
and just show it to you guys what do you
think I'm going to take off my jacket
take it off oo sorry now I feel
scandalous
okay all right fine I'm shy though I'm
shy I'm
shy I'm very
[Music]
shy but I'll show
you I'll show you
you here we
go here we
[Music]
go surprise
mother no lies
mother hot fries
mother hard eyes
[Music]
mother
yay hard
eyes
[Music]
motherucker what you
think oh
[Music]
beautiful do you like
them
wow they for Kiara
no they're for everyone that I
like everyone's
included don't disinclude
[Music]
people see even when I'm angry I can
show them to you or when I'm sad
[Music]
a look deep into
them
[Music]
anyway nice
eyes thanks I guess it was a nice
surprise I
suppose I
guess
[Music]
maybe get it cuz the word eyes
is
[Music]
anyway I can't help
it this just came to be I just learned
how to do this I just learned how just
in time can you believe
it oh
man just in time so I'm kind
of maybe a little overly excited about
it it's like I have all this all this
new found power all of a sudden oh man
all the different combinations I can do
oh what should I try should I
try ooh okay hold
on
wait how will this
look
[Music]
honestly
the it's a nice
combination I like extreme very very
[Music]
dangerous
get it be
careful what will she do
next what will she do next heart eyes
hot fries no
lies can she get any
cute don't get mad don't get mad they
called you cute just let it go just be
like oh yeah thanks like take a
compliment it's not it's really not that
it's not that hard to do just take a
compliment okay yeah thank you thank you
for saying kind things about
[Music]
me
anyway I'm having a little too much fun
with this I should stop I should stop
I'm having too much fun
yo
y cop you should
stop can't be
helped I kill
myself I'm
sorry do it have fun it's your day
really it's
[Music]
okay okay well since it's my birthday I
guess I shouldn't
apologize I'm going to be
goofy also because I'm a little brain
dead right now but that's okay okay oh
man how am I going to communicate with
people didn't really think this one
through um no it'll be fine it'll be
fine surely they'll understand it's a
wee bit of
silliness you
know and people maybe people prepared
you know birthday gifts and we can talk
about the
gifts I'm a good
talker I promise
I I
promise
we might be in trouble hold on let me
ruffle up my hair a little
[Music]
bit okay now I feel like I match my
personality especially right
now you're the best talker I can do
enough it'll be fine what am I worried
about
oh wait no I like looking
sleepy wait no what I really should do
oh what I should do is
this what I should do is
[Music]
this now they're normal that's what I
should do I have to learn the the
transition I have to learn how to do the
transition
right wild but still cute just how we
like it you sure
okay well if you say so then then it
must be all right let's go ahead
and let's go ahead
and get this out of the way and prepare
for calls oh I'm nervous don't be
nervous don't be
nervous it's more fun to it's more fun
to have you know someone to talk to you
know for for a birthday Colin although I
really could just just look at the chat
and talk to you guys I got to stop being
so introverted recently calm down myy
oh hey why does the timer
stop don't do that don't scare me like
that well I'll go sit in the
[Music]
call okay let me make sure that all my
stuff is
together uh system sound voice you can
hear other people's
voices oh it should be good to
go
yeah Cron's effing with it
classic
a
a all right now I'm just going to sit in
here and wait thank you guys so much by
the way for all the big support as well
I really appreciate
it thank you for dropping by to say
hello crony wants to show up at just the
right time she's
waiting oh we have a
caller
who G G oh I hear a g who that I who's
doing the
G um K it's h lives Phoenix
Tak yay um did it work did it work check
your Steam cie oh there's is there a a a
special treat just for me oh wait no it
didn't work oh dang it all right I'll
keep checking no wait wait wait wait uh
uh I'm so hyped now get a steam gift
though four items in my inventory okay I
think wait let's
see wait no it says I wait I bought it
for myself
I how does that happen qaa no that's
okay cuz I wanted it I wanted it for
myself too okay you play it you have fun
I'm so what is this what is this mystery
game no maybe it did maybe it did May no
maybe it did work did you get something
let me see I'm trying to figure out
where I would check I've got a bunch of
let's see new inventory item four items
in my
inventory maybe you got an
email okay um hold on I'll check let me
check my email because I bet I bet I bet
it's there I bet it's there I'm so
curious I'm pretty sure it worked cuz it
still says I can buy the game for myself
too a oh wait hold on oh nice wao did
you get me The Witcher wild Hunt
complete
edition yeah for
me wit for me yeah my thought it would
suit you also cuz I'm I'm currently in
like uh The Witcher binge watch uh
season at the moment and I was like oh I
want to play the game and then I was
like okay what do I gift to CI and I was
like you know what I'm going to gift her
The Witcher cuz I think she would like
it a yeah I've never played this one
before actually what the heck thank God
I was like asking around guys do you
know if she ever played the wicher
before can you imagine if I had oh God
the sadness yeah no I I was pretty
confident because Elsie Len said you
never did very confidently oh okay okay
lots of confidence I'm pretty sure
that's cuz I said it on stream at some
point uh I've never played that a but
it's like a long it's like a long
Marathon game kind of like open world
you don't have to play it right away
just anytime yeah no when you got some
time yeah once I destroy these other
these other Marathon games that I'm
working on I'm just glad to have it
though I mean I don't maybe I just want
to play it by myself I who could say who
could say no no play Don't stream we
have terms we have terms we do we do we
do you never know because you never know
some of the games that I want to play
it's like oh you can't so I'm like oh
okay I'm glad to hear
we can I played it before too long time
ago are there naked
people for now I can say in a Netflix
show there's a lot of naked people oh so
maybe on the game too qu qu qu qu yes
many people say yes yes there are oh God
scary okay that's fine I'll prepare the
sensor I'll prepare the sensor it'll be
fine it'll be fine oh nervous why would
you never watch the show either right no
I haven't is it kind of like game of
throny or like it it goes in that
direction I'm just I just started
watching it I'm so late to the party I
just finished watching the first season
and I was like what the [\h__\h] is going on
cuz it's so
confusing it's pretty good is it
confusing now did you finally kind of
get it or I I get it now yeah but they
say the the games the games are better
than the show is oh I heard that the
show got like a lot of good reviews
though right didn't it was it the
opposite you may have heard that wrong
was it the opposite was it the yeah it's
like so there's three seasons the first
one follows the books pretty well but
it's very confusing as to how they made
it then the second one they stopped
making it confusing which I guess was
good and okay second season was decent
but then third season they stopped
following the books and they changed the
main actor so it was like people were
really unhappy people say just play the
games or read the books I see well I do
want to check out the first season I
think for sure yeah you changed the but
you will be confused just like me okay
I'll just pretend like I know what's
going on I'll be like ah yes main
character yes I understand what you're
saying and then I'll yeah just pretend
yeah make it till I make
it thank you so much Kiara I appreciate
the birthday gift you're welcome just a
little inspiration of what you could
play in the future I appreciate it oh
man Marathon game for days let's go I
can handle it let's go I can handle it
you don't have to Marathon it you know
that you don't have to Marathon games
right I know I know but I keep feeling
like I just I mean it depends on the
game some games I feel like I just want
to keep playing it and then other times
I feel like well we really need to get
through
this yeah yeah I get it like especially
when you're close to the end you just
want to get get it in one go I know
we're like similar in that regard yeah I
think
so and then people always like don't
stress yourself out just go make another
stream go do another part I'm like no I
going to do it in one go 10 hour stream
12 hour stream oh my God just finish it
finish the game complete it yeah I have
too many incomplete games that I need to
go finish so I'm like dang I got to get
to work on those first what about Holo X
break huh I know I want to play it I
want to play it but then Deb be probably
be like hey wait a minute then what
about Red Dead what about Persona aren't
we finishing those yes we are but
sometimes sometimes I want to play some
other things every once in a while I
would say hola break is good for a nice
uh
once one time only two and a half hour
stream that's how long it took
me yeah just don't like you know f one
off like chill stream yeah yeah we might
do ex silent excuse me okay princess
it's break that's how we're supposed to
say it
Kiara no I will continue to say h x
break
live as you please K live as you please
you too you too okay all right now that
you finally your favorite number number
four four yeah I feel like I can just
kind of chill and have fun now it's nice
really four four years old that's what
unleashes the that kind of feeling I
think so I don't know what it is I feel
like I've been here a long time now that
I'm like oh fourth birthday I'm like wow
time has passed dang yeah I should just
be more laidback I
think yeah yeah what are your plans for
the year my plans oh boy I don't know
see I just talked about like I should be
more laidback but I'm like but there are
all these things I want to do right I
think I want to try and do more stuff
with Ian though like you know together
like big collabs together and stuff like
that you know even if it's like a bunch
of like crossgen collabs and stuff I
don't know just just more stuff with
each other I think yeah yeah please
please organize something I'm thinking
Halloween Mario Kart tournament would be
fun Halloween Mario Kart yeah Halloween
would be good I thought initially July
for like Freedom day but I'm like one of
the only underworld and Americans so I
think that doesn't matter I'll Celebrate
Freedom with you Freedom through Mario
Kart freom yeah Freedom let's go all
right if you say so that makes me feel
more
confident I'm always ready to celebrate
other people's freedom let's go let's go
free oh God chat's going off USA freedom
freedom USA USA USA USA I feel so
supported right now oh my go I support
your
American status uh yeah right back at
you congratulations on being American
yeah that's what we're celebrating yeah
I should congratulate you though you get
to eat really delicious food that I feel
like I want to go back and eat because
it was really good when I went to visit
you Austria yeah a you got good stuff
there some of the best food I've had you
are in the paradise of food right now so
Japan true true everything is good
yeah okay thank you see I see someone's
waiting yeah oh there there's somebody
waiting wow I'll move out of the way
happy
birthday uh I'll see you in that uh big
fry stream heck yeah see see you there
yeah later k but thank you for the game
by the way thank you so much yeah I to
play don't forget about it okay I won't
I won't let it rck you you know I I
gifted you a different one too right you
know that right yeah you gifted me um it
what was it
tunic was it tunic I think it was tunic
I'm pretty sure it was tunic tunic yeah
you got it for me okay you you got got
it I don't know if I'll stream that one
I will stream Witcher but I I just want
to play it on my own I
think yeah see you byebye byebye wait's
[Music]
gone
no [\h__\h] okay bye by no wait
no I'm it might have been Orie oopsies
wait Kiara come back it was Orie I'll
buy tunic and play it anyway but it was
aie I'll play both of them
oh there's someone else
waiting so maybe I won't be
alone after
all I gifted tunic to someone else that
correct that's right
Miss whoa hold on a sec I have a soft
voice in here hold on can you speak
happy birthday
almost a wait who 16 minutes H 60
minutes wait you mean 16 sorry whoops
okay sorry can't read I can't
read Falla welcome thank you for
dropping by wow I'm here yeah I guess
good morning to you good morning happy
birthday W thank I doodled you a little
a little something a little fresh Ms
paint
creation for
me that's right just for you oh my god
what treasure awaits me I'm so excited
okay I just got it oh this is so cute I
didn't know you were such an MS paint
Master thank you I love me some Ms paint
I can't deny the heck wow also
congratulations on your um on your very
first stream ever playing Minecraft I
really hope that you know you get big
someday and I'm going to say I was your
first fan thank you thank you I'm I went
out I got a better mic I hope it sounds
better now oh yeah
definitely yeah we're we're upgrading
we're going places instead of like an
Xbox 360 mic it's like an Xbox mic like
regular Xbox mic this time yeah like a
regular Xbox mic so people can can
understand crunch me nice I'm looking
forward to I'm looking forward to your
next stream I'm so excited let me know
if you need some Shader
recommendations oh my gosh how do you
even install a Shader okay it's kind of
difficult I I didn't know how to do it
until until I asked my my I asked my my
older stepbrother to help me and now I'm
real good with shaders that's that's the
way I only know how to install Sims 2
mods oh man dang you got to teach me
download seven zip and no not seven zip
wi Roar download wi raar right hey do
you know about Rose
Bud do you know about Rose Bud semic
know about rose rose bun oh my God I use
it all the
time all the time sweet
memories thanks so much for making me
nostalgic fa it's probably my favorite
internet era like yeah 2009 to
2011 it was kind of the wild west back
then it was it was the Wild West I feel
like before everyone knew what they were
doing on the internet it was just like
oh it's charm to it I know I
know cringe wasn't invented yet back
then no one knew what that was everybody
was just doing their own thing I miss
it me too I miss it so much Ah that's
why I really loved watching your stream
made me very happy reminded me of the
good old days I know I
know was pretty pretty good pretty
genius I know I feel like I could I
could stream like that permanently just
pretend from here on out this is how
things are yes I'm just going to pretend
like it's 2011 from now on and that's
just that's just how it is it's too
perfect I don't think the internet's
ready for that that kind of realism you
know how good that would be I know yeah
for shame for shame maybe someday
they'll be ready for
it I know I'm I'm just thinking about
like a vtuber whose whole concept is
like they exist in 2011 oh my God
actually a really good idea IDE I don't
know I know I know dang it someone's
going to do that now someone's going to
do that they're going to get really big
see it yes they only stream old
games what a good idea what the heck
that Boomer tuber I guess you could call
yeah with like the the really nostalgic
anime art style yeah the old school
anime style I'd watch that I'd watch
that all day me too me too let's go hey
someone do that take the idea just do it
I know please write that down
yeah wow thank you so much for dropping
by fun I appreciate the drawing I'm
going to treasure it yes happy birthday
thank you hold it close to my heart I
hope that you have a great wonderful
rest of your day thank you you too and
yeah you have fun with your your 3D
we'll do we'll do I'll do I'll GBU do my
best leg thanks a lot I'll I'll try not
to break my leg or anything like that
but you know metaphorically speaking to
do a good job you know what I mean you
know what you get it you get it fauna
take care I you I got you thanks so much
bye fauna have a great day bye see you
she's so she's so
nice so fun fun to hang out with I'm
always happy when I can hang out with
fauna fun fun H I feel like we grew up
on the internet at like the same time
too so like I don't know we get each
other somehow I don't know or maybe we
were just like around the internet a lot
in that time
period
Nostalgia I start
getting start getting drowsy daydreaming
about
it the saplings miss her already she'll
be back she'll be back
oh someone else someone else is
waiting we have another
waiter I see a
waiter a
hello
hello oh my God is she
[Music]
alive Ena no she was
sleeping oh don't
don't wake up on account of me oh
no I'm sorry if I woke your beauty rest
still am I still sleeping or I dead is
this the underworld it might just be a
dream you know it might just be a
dream oh my God w
w I dream was your
birthday oh my God crazy that's a crazy
dream cuz it's actually the truth Ena it
is my birthday your in was right oh oh
happy birthday oh thank you so much oh
my God are you oh my gosh I feel I feel
terrible cuz sleep is like the the
cousin to death so I feel responsible
somehow for this oh really you're
related yeah very a very distant
relationship but we are what like yeah
little no
fact like like the same family yeah yeah
yeah family tree but you know it's more
like more like a an eighth cousin twice
removed kind of thing so very quite
distant
really but I feel responsible for your
drowsiness I know so cool this whole
world M yeah you're very well acquainted
with sleep I feel yeah yeah we go way
back oh my God youa
sleeping sleepy sleepy just are you
you're not sleeping on the Flo on the
floor are you no not today not today
okay good please take it easy lots of
lots of rest you too C you need to get
lots of rest to you want the hardest
workers I know a need some rest too a
thanks it's my
[Music]
hobby you too it's my hobby yeah me too
I mean I mean sleeping I me sleeping but
same thing yeah yeah well I would love
for sleep to be my hobby someday but I
feel like that's a bit out of sight I'm
too ambitious have too many plans yeah I
should be like that but sometimes I just
want to sleep
yeah which is why I'm really happy that
you made time to come say hello to me on
my birthday yeah guess how many alarms I
said oh my God uh let me see okay I'm
envisioning your phone though you
probably have an alarm for like every 1
minute right every 5 minutes or so
H because I have a similar alarm system
you see
wow we have a lot in common oh I guess
so uh but when Happy Happy Birthday
Kelly I can't wait to wait wait for wait
for your live later today yeah I know we
worked very hard um iard there's
[Music]
aing yeah I think so and I'm really
excited for them to hear the song we're
going to sing together
it's it's really good let it be known
let it be
known no no you you did you did amazing
I feel like um it's it's just it's just
the the it's the meaning of the song you
know it's the significance right and I
feel like it's hard to explain it kind
of sounds like like you know when we
sang it together it I I thought this I'm
like this kind of sounds like Kids Bop
you know like it's it's but in the good
way
you know because I got really like kind
of growly and like low with it and then
your voice is just very sweet so like
I'm like oh it's like kids Bob all right
everyone's going to love
this it's it's going to be fun I'm
excited it's going to be fun I hope I
hope everyone looks forward to it cuz
it's it's I think it's probably going to
be one of the times of spoken or I guess
Sayang the fastest in my time really oh
yeah I guess it is kind of
yeah oh now you say it oh I hope I hope
you I hope you guys look forward to it
please check it out please watch cheer
it's going to be good it's going to be
great come see thank you so much for
saying yes
hard too
so just want to say you know
Kell
i
[Music]
w w
ke we'll get him next time Lads we'll
get him next
time okay I was I was not mentally
prepared to stay it in public so a yeah
one of my biggest Idols a me I can't
wait to see achieve this year
a thank you Ena i
w w it's my favorite letter W yeah W big
Big W huge
w w for w w okay
W you a wonderful wonderful ear too
and you as well and and yeah um together
let's have a fun year together yeah
together hbd to me thank you I almost
said happy birthday back to you even
though it's not your birthday oh thank
you thank you ever do that sometimes we
like it's like it's like when you're
going on a play and like have a nice
flight and you're just
like that's exactly what it's like I've
done that like five times already like
in the last last like 6 months well just
own it you know brain gets fuzzy like
that what can I say brain gets fuzzy
yeah yeah anyways happy birthday I'm
going to go say hi to your eight cousin
my eth cousin twice removed yeah yeah
tell her I said hi okay we'll do bye bye
new my happy birthday thank you you too
bye
n bye
boy by
bye it's like no you hang up Ena no you
hang up myy no you hang up no you hang
up oh man 3 minutes 3 minutes left until
the Birthday
Countdown oh man doky doie oh god oh man
what should I do for B for birthday
count I guess I'll just go or something
like that like Yay wooo it's my birthday
and then move on to the the next call I
think oh wait they're
here oh my God two
dogs they're they're barking they're
barking in my ear but it's so sweet it
makes me so happy hi it's still a little
bit early but I wanted to say a quick Hy
happy birthday a you guys are so sweet
what the heck I'm so happy thank you so
much for making time to say hello no no
no we don't have much time until the the
the countdown is counted down oh that is
true I do really appreciate it though I
know you guys are super busy right now
so you come in to say hello to me means
a lot to
me we're just really looking for it to
birthday life to I hope you guys like it
thank you amazing oh I've been working
really really hard for it so so I hope
that you will enjoy the songs are very
yanky and
intense so
enjoy
b b bow bow bowing for me shake those
pen lights and bow bow for me
please ta will be a wagon
yeah thanks so much YouTube oh my gosh
hey by the way I know I know how late it
is now by the way cuz you know we're on
the same timeline you guys you guys
better be getting some good sleep oh
yeah don't stay up don't stay up too
late don't stay up to late there's a lot
to get
done that's all right I know they can
take care of themselves I'm just being
silly tell that goes for you too you
have a big day tomorrow
me but I'm having so much fun can't stay
in your pajamas okay
yeah dang it now now we're having to
look out for each other it
seems that's all right that's fine I'll
take it I'll take it you guys are cute
thanks so much happy birthday happy
birthday by by bye byebye you two PE bye
goodbye there they go I'mma hop out of
the call for just a minute so that we
can celebrate together birthday I don't
know what to what should I do should
I what should I do for hold on I'm
trying to think what would be a really
good idea
uh let's
see um maybe I can
do I can play a song or something like
that like no please not un alive um
let's see oh huge W would be good H Coco
just blast it just make it super loud
like everybody's ears are just on fire
Clap the thighs what is wrong with you
yada I
refuse
I don't want to do
that I want to play a silly
song so that's what I'm going to
do oh my God 20 seconds left here we go
here we go I'm almost four in Holo years
I guess can you guys believe I'm almost
no years old here we go nine 8 7 6 5 4 3
2 1 hi happy
birthday bring it down bring it down
down down down oh that's not very high
hold on there we
go bring it down bring it down down down
down down don't got to worry we back in
[Music]
glory
break this right
[Applause]
[Music]
here I'm no years old anyway that was
fun that was a fun little a fun little
how do I say oh tangent a detour if you
will happy birthday thank you so much
everyone oh my gosh I saw I saw that I
saw that a lot of you guys you guys are
all sending your messages right now and
that makes my heart very very happy
happy thank you you didn't have to do
that but you did they know they know my
Mory they
know myy they know that they don't have
to do it you don't need to remind them
of that every time I know I know I don't
I know I don't have to but sometimes I
feel obligated to no myy don't do
that the voices talk really loud these
days
anyway there's really wow thank you so
much you you you guys can wait till
tomorrow you can but I will say I will
say thank you so much everybody I'm
super chatting and membershi now um also
because you know when we do birthday
lives and stuff like that we got to pay
for all of it like all that stuff you
know sometimes it ends up being you know
for some people's lives it's you know
more expensive than others usually we
rely on on things like supas from you
guys and and memberships from you guys
um to like I guess break even with it
and I think I think definitely
definitely because of you guys' support
I won't have to worry and so I just want
to say thank you so much for that truly
thank you cuz it's a it's a great it's a
great pleasure to be able to put on um a
show for you guys uh for my birthday for
such a special day so just really really
happy really really happy thank you so
much I feel like I can I can put on good
shows without you know worrying about
like oh is this going to be covered or
not thanks to you guys thank you so much
for that truly I'll keep working really
hard to to make it worth it for you
guys how has it been 4 years it hasn't
been 4 years but it has been four
birthdays I think I think no it's been
four I don't
know you are worth oh that's so sweet
thank you so much you guys thank you I'm
really looking forward to reading all of
your wonderful birthday messages we are
doing that this week I have I have the
plan to do it
I have the plan set and at that time
we're going to go look through um the
birthday website too oh my God it really
doesn't stop wow thank you thank you so
much you
guys thank
you awesome happy fourth birthday I'm
not four but I feel
for sometimes I feel for especially when
I start like talking weird like a baby
because all my brain cells died on a
long plane flight then I feel like a
4-year-old big
[Music]
time this is definitely your Year Kelly
thank you I want to believe that that's
true I'm starting to feel like it really
is though to be honest like just little
things here and there and you know the
way that that stuff has been going right
you know with like promotions and stuff
like that and and possibilities you know
like the anime ending and stuff like
that like that whole thing has just been
extremely exciting and fun and you guys'
positive response really really made a
big difference thank you so
much you know it's so it's so silly you
know scrolling around and seeing
comments saying I'm going to watch this
show just because myy is doing the
ending I've seen so many comments saying
that and it really it warms my
heart I feel like I'm doing something
right thanks to you guys who who else I
mean I know I ask who else there there
are a lot of people in in my company in
my group but right now I feel like so
special to be able to sit here and just
like see all of you guys' sweet messages
just fly across the screen like I feel
like in no other Universe would I have
ever been able to see something like
this
before all these really you
know amazing kind
words flying by
you know some colored some not
colored it really really means the world
to
me I don't think there's another life
where I could have experienced something
like this thank you truly thank
you I'll keep working hard but but not
too
hard every time I say that I'm like oh
deats are going to worry they like
myy stop working so
hard
but I feel like I've I've been making
you guys proud so so less stress in my
life since I've started to feel that way
right anyway stop being
sappy enough
enough didn't you say to kiar you're
going to relax for a bit I mean I say
that to everyone you guys to you guys a
lot especially but technically I'm kind
of forced to have that happen right oh
there's going to be like a whole month
where I'm I'm going to have to relax it
doesn't mean a month of no streams it
might be like a week again a week or two
of no streams to recover from
the knee
surgery but I don't think that it'll be
it'll be intense enough that I can't
stream it's just I'll be away from my
usual setup you know but then but then
I'll eventually get to um fly back to a
setup that I can work with it won't be
my my always setup it'll be my America
setup
but doctor
said can't fly so soon after surgery to
another country if it's like a quick pop
over to like another state or something
like that then then it's it's much less
risky and it's fine but yeah there will
still be streams it's part of who I am
right now oh whoa whoa whoa whoa why was
I moving it two frames per second that
was
weird
streaming I'd like to not move like a
PowerPoint for 2 seconds so my emotions
are overloading
me can we not do
[Music]
that hello there we go just a simple
reset um I can't not stream for like a
month it's just part of who I
am streaming is who I am at this
point I mean music is as well I like to
consider music to be the number one
right but the streaming is just who I am
you
know and so yeah yeah you'd miss us too
much
maybe yeah these days I do find myself
thinking a lot about like you know I
guess I guess one thing that I kind of
tend to do is I think maybe sometimes I
worry a little too much about you guys
you know not in like a mean way like I
should not care about my dead beats or
anything like that but I think I like
find myself sitting down and thinking a
lot about like what you guys are like
going through and and like um what you
guys like are seeing and experiencing
and I think I have maybe a little too
much empathy for that to the point where
it's it's not it's not healthy because
I'll just be lying down in bed stressed
and like unable to sleep like the dead
beats are probably in pain right now the
dead beats are not feeling good right
your paral for us is that the word that
word has lost its meaning I feel I feel
like either that or it has a gazillion
different meaning at this point it's
kind of similar to to other buzzwords on
the internet at this point but I don't
know um I need to stop being like that
because sometimes it does affect like my
sleep patterns and stuff like that I got
to stop I have to
stop stop it Mor that is the correct
usage though I guess so I guess so maybe
that may be but
anyway yeah what a roller
coaster of emotions but there's also
happiness that comes with that
too I just yeah I don't know you know
the world is full of people and the dead
beats Community is full of dead beats so
it's kind of a situation where you know
there's so many different people in the
world who do I make happy that's another
thing right sometimes I feel a lot like
I want to make every single dead beat
happy all the time I can't do that I
can't do that that which is why I have a
lot of I have a lot of admiration for
some Senpai like um for example I feel
like say say Senpai is like a really big
inspiration to me because she she makes
the things that she likes and and does
what she wants to do and she has this
aura about her right where like it's
like I do the things that I love and
what I want to do and if you want to
come watch you can you know I wish I had
the ability to do that that's like a
very special human quality I think I
don't know a lot of people like
that you
know people that have the confidence to
be that way you know enough belief in
themsel to be like I'm going to live
freely the way that I want to and make
things the way that I want to and follow
me if you like it and don't if you don't
want to you know she's the prince of Her
Own Story yeah she's so inspiring
oh I don't think that I can be like her
someday but I do want to follow some of
that example you know we're also just
different people so I don't think that I
can be like
[Music]
that but that's
okay cuz I want to find a way to to be
strong and confident on my own just
being
myself but I guess when I got into whole
I've I like found a lot more people that
I look up to and I think are really
amazing
[Music]
yeah I wasn't it's not that I didn't
think it would happen I just didn't
expect it to kind of come out of nowhere
cuz you guys know my story I'm one of
those people that just kind of stumbled
into all of this while knowing what it
was but not being like a a hardcore fan
of
it you
know
[Music]
yeah I think being in the first gen for
Ian maybe it's all right that that's my
story I feel like if I came in and like
say for example a sixth generation or
something like that and just had no idea
what I was doing or what Holo was that
would probably not be good but I think
being in the first gen it was it was
such a journey for me you know as one of
the first enens and
Holo oh yeah and now I can confidently
say say that I'm a I'm a big I'm as big
of a fan as you could
be of Holo I would say being in
it yeah it's kind of a crazy story when
I just think about how it all unfolded
and
evolved kind of crazy but I'm glad it
turned out this way and now I feel like
I'm on the right
track
yeah okay but did you frame that sign so
you say
CD some Secrets I will take to the Grave
we can respect that
[Music]
right got to keep some
Secrets get on my level of
[Music]
fandom well if I am a big fan of anyone
I probably you got to understand I will
keep it to myself I'm one of those
people that gets really really shy about
being a fan of my friend
it's not like I'll outright deny it it's
just that I will never talk about it and
if they happen to come to my home I
would definitely hide all of the merch
that I have of them sitting out there I
don't know maybe it's a pride I don't
think it is it a pride thing I don't
know I think it's less like it's more
like I just don't want to be creepy but
it's not creepy if you are outwardly
loving towards your Oshi it's just I
don't
know I don't
know just for me
my own my own secret
feelings I don't know I I just keep it
to myself I'm not a person that can that
can openly fawn over someone I feel I
can't I can't do it that's okay all
kinds of different people in the world
is it true that one of your songs is in
the new Suicide Squad anime yeah it's
the ending theme called
go-getters you'll probably get to hear
the full version or at least you'll
definitely get to hear
the the proper version of the ending uh
when the anime airs and I believe it was
announced to be
July so look forward to that full
version one please I mean I've been
listening to it on my on my phone for
the past like year or
so sometimes I'll just be riding in a
taxi and I'm like
hm maybe I'll maybe I'll pop on the song
shall we take some more calls maybe I
don't know if anyone else will come but
I'm just going to sit in the call anyway
just in case anyone pops by I'll be
sitting
there yeah years oh yeah about a
year a whole year of me sometimes taking
a taxi ride like listening to the full
song and being like yeah this is
actually a really good
song yeah you can kind of hear it in the
background of the convention stream it's
not like a a completely cleaned version
but yeah play your songs in public see
if anyone notices no no no no no no I'd
prefer to keep them in my headphones I
think but that's how I am with all my
music
right that's how I am with all my music
no matter what it is I just prefer to
keep it in my headphones
and it's not that I don't want to have a
conversation with people that are you
know maybe possibly also a fan of that
thing no no no no no that that's fine
that's fine I don't mind
but I I'm just I'm very
shy I've said that again illion times
but maybe it's because it's true I don't
know dead beats I don't know I already
think I told I think I told this story
already before but I was sitting on like
um a college bus listening to a band
that I won't name but I was how do I say
I was in that phase where I was
embarrassed oh hold on pause on the
story we have a
caller
on
on Happy
Birthday sh is here here hi
Shori hello that's me hello Mor KY
Shori Mori and shiori if you combine
Mory and shiori it's
shiori it's just Shori shim Shori works
better I think
personally yeah plus she's like death so
yeah exactly yeah also check it out I
got a jacket kind of similar to how you
have a jacket oh cuz I can't lunch you
mine huh exactly exactly this is kind of
like your other sweater that you wear on
stream thank you oh yeah yeah yeah you
just need the cat ears and we'll be like
twinning exactly wait you have cat ears
for ears I never
noticed well yeah I just put it on when
I feel like being a cat you can just
feel like being a cat really yeah yeah
wow you're on
a you're on a different level than I am
Shori that's awesome what the heck teach
me you just you just put it on you just
you just put on the ears want you can
use my cat ears yeah yeah oh okay just
like it should be coming in with like a
pin or something you just stick in your
head you might bleed a little but I
think it'll be okay sick sounds good I
mean hey might accent my hair to be
honest do you think um do you think that
you need to like be a cat in order to
wear cat ears like do you need to like
make cat noises and stuff like that or
do you just you're just a cat it's just
my default State just just permanently
sleepy always wanting food uhhuh oh
sounds good yeah a what about pets are
you a are you do you like pets do you
like when people give you like a pet on
the head maybe scratch behind the ears
uh I don't know about that I wouldn't
know but I own pets it sounds like you
are a cat then because that's definitely
how a cat would respond cat would be
like yeah it would also own pets no I
mean I mean they wouldn't want pats on
the head they'd walk
away are you offering Celly shh I'm not
I wasn't going to offer I was going to
see how she responded to the question
and then decide if I wanted to offer a
pat on the head I don't know I mean you
can if you want but I'll pet
back okay understandable it wouldn't it
wouldn't be
fair it wouldn't be fair if you if you
couldn't so I want
sh chat's going to be jealous though
they're going to be jealous that I'm
getting the Pats from you
though the ears scratch behind the ears
yeah all right but I hope that you clean
your ears I don't want to find gunk in
there more oh don't worry I'm one of
those people that maybe cleans my ears
too much to be honest I feel like oh
yeah same yeah with Q-tips and stuff
like that like I'll get out of the
shower and I'll be like time to clean my
ears again and there won't be anything
in them because I cleaned them that
morning like that's how much but you
secretly hope to find stuff so you're
like yeah look at that you know it's
like oh that's disgusting I like looking
at it you like looking at the the Q-tip
after you put it in your
ear yeah but there's like barely
anything there yeah I mean I mean
searching for buried treasure a I mean
maybe maybe that could be kind of fun
but there's never anything on my my
Q-tips sadly search for Tre you got to
let it accumulate then I think yada I
don't want to because especially if like
you don't clean your ears for a while
and then you do you'll be like oh my God
how have I been living like that how did
I let it get that bad dang look at that
steam achievement right here don't look
at
it no no no I don't want to I don't want
to know if there's something living in
my ear man living why would there
shouldn't everything be dead in there I
mean I don't know it's you never know
have you ever seen like some of those um
what is it like there sometimes um they
have those shows about people that like
have like bugs crawl in their
ear oh yeah I mean I don't know how it
gets to that point though I guess
they're just really unlucky I mean it
must it must be either that or like I
don't know maybe they slept and like
they got super unlucky and like a a
spider like crawled into their ear when
they were like sleeping or something
like that is that how Spiderman came to
be maybe the spider crawled into his
brain and bit his brain that seems is
more likely if you ask
me yeah I would think so oh but you know
we're actually not supposed to use
Q-tips on our ears really what are you
supposed to use yeah so you're supposed
to use this like liquid thing I think
what you're supposed to do is you go in
the shower you kind of just like lube it
up in there with the water and then you
do the the special liquid and it's
supposed to bubble in your ear oh okay
and then after a while you kind of like
lean out with the wax fall oh
interesting what the
heck yeah QP is usually for I think
makeup actually there's actually a
warning label telling you not to put it
in your ear but come on everyone I mean
who's going to listen to that like I'm
sure no one dies from that I have no
records of people I have a couple
records of people dying from but very
few people very few people die from
something like that so I mean should be
fine I thought it was like your inner
circle like oh no I'm so sorry that oh
no no no no one that I know yet yet but
don't be the first I remember this
person Billy Bob Joe died for ear wax
yeah that's serious stuff anyway I still
use Q-tips kind of thing I wouldn't
still be using Q-tips if that was the
case she worry don't you
worry
yeah but I mean I worry about putting
water in my ear because I'm one of those
people that has really weirdly shaped
inner ear canals so if I get water stuck
in my ears it doesn't come out for
days oh what what if you do like um like
a cartwheel do you think the water will
fall off I mean how many cartwheels do I
have to do though shiori I don't really
know if I have the stamina to do that I
can maybe do five okay so what we can do
is that you'll you'll be like uh flipped
upside down and I'll Hold You by the
legs until the water comes out how about
but what if the blood going to my rushes
to my head well I can't die so I guess
that's fine but I might start saying
some really weird stuff
Eternal doom and torture right here oh
my God I think that she's secretly
trying to torture me what's going on
here oh no it's not even a secret why
would I want to torture you though I
just think it's a a buddy buddy helping
a pal right here you know getting the
water out of your ears naturally thanks
a lot buddy pal I appreciate
it big UPS no problem buddy pal friend
of
mine completely innocent shiori as
always
well thanks for calling intentions right
here problem appreciate that I'm so glad
that you called I was I was like I don't
know I thought maybe it might be like I
don't know weird timing and whatnot but
I appreciate that thank you oh no I I
set up my alarm I just didn't know what
was happening like am I allowed to drop
in any time of course I didn't want to
impose on other people oh yeah my to
toachi are like very casual just like
call in if you want kind of thing so
yeah oh is it like a a one by one or or
should I like a scaddle oh I mean let's
see well let me take a a quick
look yeah you should add them make sure
that they're they're
alive die from earback yeah exactly I
did at everybody there's nobody waiting
yet but I don't know we never know who
will pop in you know you never I at them
10 more times 10 times are you sure okay
have about four times it's like the call
of death you know true four is a good
number if they don't respond by this
time they're going to die ah yeah
exactly if you don't like one of those
chain emails right if you don't forward
this to like five people who love God or
something like that then you will be
stricken down by the devil that kind of
stuff right yeah except for our Discord
I will kill you if you don't come to the
tots umachi you think they'll like that
you'll be you'll be banned temporarily
oh from my friend
yeah I couldn't do that to them I know
they're busy I know they're busy I'm
just playing around playing games don't
worry about it it's fine it's fine no
worries at all I know people are busy or
sleepy you know was really sleepy yeah
sleepy was definitely the case oh true
yeah sorry about the sleepiness no no
you're fine you're fine you know the the
world doesn't revolve around one
location after all it expands do you
ever wonder what it would be like if it
did though like if some countries just
had to live with the fact that like it
was dark outside during the
daytime isn't that already happening oh
true it is for some places yeah yeah
like I think there's an artificial sun
somewhere it's just like a giant light
bulb behind the mountains cuz they don't
get sunlight there oh
yeah yeah wow I wonder what it's like
living there any dead Beats live there
what's it like probably depressing and
cold maybe anyone who lives there I'm
just saying I mean I'm going to be
honest with you though Shori I live in a
home that has minimal lighting like I
have a bunch of Lights like I I got
lights everywhere but like whenever I'm
walking around I just turn on these
little lamps you know so that when it's
dark like I just want it to be as dark
as possible cuz I really love
Darkness right uhhuh that's why I'm so
pale hold on look at me I'm super pale
cuz I love the dark I have like fairy
lights for me I actually don't think I
like uh light bulbs that are yellow I
think I needed white because it's just
too dim and dark oh I see I see
interesting yeah like laboratory
lighting like a a lab rat yeah like
you're an experiment or something like
that oh no I'm experimenting other other
people that's you're the one doing the
dissecting of course mhm naturally oh my
God crazy wow I'm yeah definitely
understand I definitely understand the
type of light you're talking about I'm
personally more of a fan of like warm
lighting but it's dark if that makes any
sense like orange light but it's super
low I think it's good for relaxing but
for prod productivity I think like white
light is better true definitely that's
why that's why you end up staying up
super late when you're like at your
computer and it's got like bright white
light like going into your eyeballs and
stuff like that wait how long do you say
for your um at your computer for well it
depends usually now this is a special
exception just because this is the
Birthday Countdown but I don't usually
stream at this time as you know um
usually I'll like look at the computer
for maybe like 6 to 7 hours during the
daytime but I try not to use it at night
actually at all at all here yeah you
just look at your phone uh yeah my but
my phone has the special what do you
call it the nighttime mode
yeah it turns orange I think that's
called shutting it off no no that's
not I get what you're saying what I mean
is it nighttime mode is when the phone
turns orange you see dark mode dark mode
kind of different the phone turns off I
see I see on technically turn it off but
we never do that we never do we just
Doom scroll over and over and over again
but I've I've gotten pretty good at not
yeah like you know you just keep
scrolling
yeah you I mean it it's just like just
kind of like dumb stupid stuff that you
don't care about will just come up or
like depressing things that you didn't
want to know about and stuff like that
just shows up but you keep looking
through it why you know I you know like
the Twitter stuff has been really bad
lately cuz I look at um like oh
interesting tweet and then I look at the
replies and it's all bots of unrelated
things like I just want to see about the
panda that sneezed yeah yeah exactly you
go searching through like the comments
to find like some kind of like
interesting opinion and then it's all
Bots talking about other stories or or
check out their profile or like you know
yeah Mor and bio Mor and bio I don't
want to see that yeah sneezing panda
sounds cute what the heck give me the
source but then there's no Source it's
just weird weird bot replies see I mean
I think what what the Tweet was um there
was a panda with a child and apparently
if they have two children they'll only
focus on one child so the other one gets
uh neglected so someone gave this Panda
uh some sort of Apple I think and they
traded out the child for the other child
what so dang parenting is kind of insane
for pandas kind of harsh they're a
little hardcore about it what the heck
jeez this sad see and that is how the
Doom scroll begins you see something
like that and you look at it for a long
time oh whoops you doodle and the the
algorithm says oh she likes looking
sorry she likes looking at
this she likes looking at this kind of
thing let's give her another thing just
like that I think I need to start
spamming not interested in like a lot of
things I think that's totally
understandable to be honest I mean I've
gotten really good at whenever I like
start getting into that habit instead
I'll like go to my notes and like write
down like ideas for like shorts and
stuff like that or like or I'll just I
mean that's still using my phone though
so it's not a good idea but it's just
not it's not scrolling I like go and
like write like little memos or like
thoughts about things you know that
aren't aren't coming from an outside
Source things in my own head you know mm
and it makes me feel better thoughts
intrusive
yeah yeah but I mean I wonder how one
one how does one entertain themsel in
the evening like without um like I guess
a screen read a book you like books
right you mean like in the past before
people had things yeah what did they do
like sit around a campfire and like sing
or no I think they just uh well number
one they probably slept early because
they needed a daylight and you know it's
useless at night I assume they read a
book maybe they go quilting or they go
hide bodies it's one of those oh hide
bodies is murder another one of their
Hobbies you think well I mean for Jack
the Ripper I pretty much think so
definitely that was for sure his hobby
yeah yeah
true interesting maybe I should try
doing some of those things but murder
isn't really a hobby for me it's more
like my job so kind of don't want to
think too much about work in my off time
I think that's different though this is
like a an obligation it's not like it's
not like you're doing it because you
hate this person you're doing it because
something told you to go yeah yeah it's
just my job you know just going down a
list basically but like Santa Claus but
more deadly essentially yeah yeah yeah
exactly the Santa Claus of murder that's
me mhm yeah ho ho ho ho ho ho
ho no my God no please don't think of me
at the Santa Claus's murder you guys I'm
just following ORD that be a good
Christmas short though like you just up
a Santa and you're like ho ho ho dead
bead come over here oh no come sit on
my's lap slowly grab Scythe oh God
that's horrific I hate it but it's also
kind of nice no it's a good idea it's
funny it's amusing true enough you guys
like silly morbid [\h__\h] like that right
right guys yeah yeah I guess so look at
that guy okay where do I line up see
look at him now it's different from
Krampus I'm still delivering a Christmas
miracle it's just
death man I don't remember anything
about Krampus isn't that just like
Santa's evil twin or something kind of I
think it's a I'm pretty sure it's a folk
tale or like a story or something about
like the evil version of Santa Claus
who's like a demon dude and like oh he a
little red guy yeah yeah I don't think
I'm not sure if he's red he might be he
might be like a like a charred like tree
bark or something I don't know I kind of
forget oh oh he's His
companion he has a companion I thought
he had just like elves you know isolated
correct in the north of
Skyrim maybe who could say who could say
oh I see I think I think they work
together Santa handles good Krampus
handles bad okay you guys don't want to
meetus okay good it's it's kind of sad
that things get sort of like if they
just deal with bad people kind of like
Hades like oh no they're evil it's like
no it's just their job I guess yeah
exactly come on good good and evil and
job it's a hard it's a hard hard thing
to differentiate but when it comes to
you know work and hobbies I don't want
to think about my work when during my
off time so I prefer to keep murder off
mind you know when I'm off the clock
yeah MH for the most part that's why
streaming is fun but now streaming is
more my job than killing so that's kind
of nice I think that's a healthy
Improvement yeah I would say
yeah I would say do you like to read
though Sher do you like
books I no I absolutely despise and hate
books all right I can hear the sarcasm
in your voice I know I'm being silly no
no I like him um I usually like audio
books though because I have insomnia and
having a voice read to me helps me I did
read a lot before um during volunteer
hours where I had like nothing else to
do but yeah that's kind of cool I want
to try listening to some audio books oh
I want to hear you narrate one someday a
that would be nice I mean you could also
just pull up a stream and pretend I'm
reading a book true ah good idea archive
are by the way true yes I didn't forget
that I mean hey you never know you might
meet an archiver that doesn't like books
I'm a Reaper that doesn't enjoy killing
very much so you never
know wow my my kayfabe has been ruined
just
now kayfabe I've never heard of that
word I don't know what that is there's
only reality what is real that's true
that's true no wrestling here no
wrestling here we're just good girls
stop beating each other up in the middle
of a a room exactly exactly wrestling
term I don't know anything about
wrestling
po wrestling would be cool
though oh throw me in the PVP
essentially yeah but like you know 3D in
the real world let's
doing all right happy birthday Mor I'll
leave you in your your dead beats now so
you can chill out on your nice special
day awesome thanks so much for dropping
by Shor it was really fun talking to you
for a while yeah yeah s talking to you
too have a good death birthday
yay thank you bye-bye
peace there she goes there she goes that
was so nice of her to say
hello how kind she we I feel like I
could talk to shiori for a really long
time the subjects just they just keep
flowing it it just never
stops now we're going to collab again
pretty soon as well on her channel so
stay tuned for
that so that we can talk
more
again oh yeah she already told you guys
about it on
Sunday
yay I'm excited oh whoopsies that's not
what I meant to do I meant to go I meant
to say sorry I'm
[Music]
excited I'm already messing it
up come on myy get it right just
[Music]
once oh
well oh well shorty plus Chad cast you
know we actually do want to do
guests that's something that we're
wanting to do so so please look forward
to that I just got the brand new office
for chadcast it's been
renovated so the office is finally
completely
rebuilt and it looks really good I'm
super
excited yeah you know I wanted to to see
um if we could get some other stuff
finished before we start up again but I
think we're just going to start up again
anyway you know and maybe start inviting
guests yeah we'll start off with like um
other en members then maybe we invite
some ID members at a certain point maybe
we could do Japanese only Chad cast
episode and then invite JP members every
once in a while I think it' be
fun a that'll be nice
ah I feel so happy right
now isn't this the best spending
spending your birthday calling friends
that you hold very
dear and then having your dead beats as
well with I mean I don't you guys don't
have dead beats you have each other but
it's a different relationship right so
maybe I don't know maybe it's kind of
different it's a different feeling but
for
me I'm just really
glad
I'm really
[Music]
glad yeah yeah we're
Rivals if you try to steal dead Beats
from me I swear to God I will
boo I will Boco
[Music]
you very
hard we want to hang good news for you
is that I want to hang out with you
too but I also need to make sure that I
get the proper sleep that I need as well
so there's that can we share I'll think
about
it I shall think about
[Music]
it no we dead beats Sur Rivals of each
other in the back of the
family in the back of NES nondescript
comini you mean
all right all right Lads just keep it
clean okay can you promise me you'll
keep it clean is today dad's birthday or
tomorrow technically it's today but if
you live in the states it's it's
tomorrow but the concert is still at
night on April the 3rd it's kind of a
it's a weird situation just because of
time zones right but if you check it out
on my channel you'll see the the concert
I really hope you guys come to the
concert please
come I worked really really really hard
as the
Director and I will be singing and
dancing my heart out as well which I
think should be okay should be
okay I'm not exceedingly like tired my
body will be able to make it through
um I'll make it
through it'll be okay I made sure I mean
oh look at fa's little drawing hi there
aren't you cute sorry not tomorrow today
so April 4th right 44 day of the
Shinigami and since it's 2024 it's
especially special right 2044 would be
the most special day but that's okay
2024 is also really exciting it's the
Shinigami year I've dubbed it that for
myself because I want
to cuz I want it that way that's all
it's it's not really the year of the
Shinigami but I I made the [\h__\h] up I
made it up because I won it that way
it's
4424 um um so in Japan it'll be 11:00
a.m. Japan time April the 4th that's my
birthday um in the states it'll be April
the 3D at 700 p.m. PST that's California
time California time 700 p.m. April 3rd
it's coming up it's it's very soon
actually it's in less than 12 hours oh
my
God time
flies time flies when you're having fun
CIFA
[Music]
California just so you guys know when it
is I'm a bit nervous but it's good
nerves oh and there's something that I
also want to tease as well there be an
interesting little teaser I believe I
think it'll be ready by tomorrow I'm
pretty sure it'll be ready and some
announcements oh
boy there are always announcements
during
birthday you might want to tune
in yeah you know the typical bday
announcements right Mor's announcing
again she's doing a lot of stuff but I'm
really excited about the teaser because
it's it's something that I'm super proud
of and excited about oh
hyp I hope you guys liked my hard Eyes
by the way I'm extremely happy with them
I didn't know that they they were going
to be this
[Music]
cute thank you so much Mama for allowing
me to make this
expression I can look very fondly out at
those that support me and want me to do
[Music]
well sorry I'm trying to get some
screenshot worthy shots
in I hope you're you guys are able to
take some nice ones
[Music]
why
sadness anger is much more
[Music]
potent this eye is always so Twitchy why
why
n
why am I looking at you
affectionately I don't understand
[Music]
anything angry
affectionate anyway there's nothing in
my brain I'm surprised that I was able
to talk so long All Things
Considered can you blink with the crazy
eyes yeah
sure oh but can I actually do it no
they'll never close they'll never close
also they're not crazy eyes they're just
my wide eyes getting wide in
excitement but if I blink it looks like
this so not
really can't say can't say that I can do
that
[Music]
but these would be a nice kind of reveal
for like a Valentine's Day surprise
but no takes too
long I don't want to use them too much
though because I feel like oh no I don't
want them to get old too
fast I don't want to spoil their novelty
or anything like that you
[Music]
know it was a really nice breth birday
countdown I got to say thank you guys
for making it special for me I was so
happy to be able to to talk to some
friends and some friends that you'll get
to see
tomorrow during the 3D Live did you guys
see who the guests are we got some great
guests a skull pupils next that's a
really good idea maybe we should ask for
that next but I also like the sparkly
eyes too like big
diamonds but I hope that you guys had a
nice chill time together with me today
um and please please look
forward to the show I really hope that
you guys come check it out um just
because you
know I've
really I've really given it my
all and it's something that I've been
looking forward to for a really long
time so please come celebrate a really
momentous and happy time with me and
thank you guys so much for all the super
chats and all the support that you guys
have given me I'm so excited to read
them and also also to read the special
site that's also extremely exciting for
me um we'll do that together though this
week also there will be a members only
stream after the 3D so be sure that you
check it
out secret
guest don't think
so but you'll definitely be be surprised
by some things tomorrow so come for
surprises also so I say tomorrow but if
you're in the states then it's
technically today cuz it's morning time
for you time zones are hard but anyway
thank you for such a wonderful fun chill
time I look forward to talking to you
guys more because I feel like the the uh
the celebrations they never end the
birthday
celebrations we got a bunch of streams
revolving around birthday we have this
3D Live members only and then eventual
um coming this week I need to figure out
when a Super Chat and um and website
reading
stream
yeah also today for you true true it did
just pass the
clock Callie happy birthday what
[Music]
Miss
Senpai
nice
thank you Senai wow Senai
sticky ch ch ch ch ch ch
[Music]
ch I
love I
love it's wat though
watame watame is cotton can
[Music]
actually check it out my new
eyes ch
ch walkie
time oh no that's not
great I found a small glitch it looks
like you guys can see my my tan baral
strap if I zoom out though it's hard to
see no not my BR
strap y they asked me hey myy is
everything fine I said yep I didn't
notice oh well I'll have to hide my tan
bra strap next time sorry about
that thank you so much everybody I'm
going to leave now oh my gosh it's like
we're on the phone again with each other
we're on the phone again no you hang up
my no you hang up Debbie no you stop
that enough of that stop it go to bed
idiots not you guys I'm talking about me
and a deadbeat in this
situation you guys are
great no no no you no
[Music]
you I mean it this
time we to
me good night
everyone good night little
Mory see
you happy birthday
[Music]
my