[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
first
full collaboration but now we have
council so it's the first almost full
collaboration
of hallelujah
[Music]
discord support today and hopefully also
the viewers support today because uh
today will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting
event yay it's race day
[Music]
bad drivers
i may be a here driver but i'll drive
you guys nuts
we all seem very confident though yeah i
think we shall start with my
introductions of each member uh now
let's start with
from whole live indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
anja melvisa from hello life i second
generation
thank you everyone i can't wait what's
your what's your
what's my ikigomi um to not be on the
last last place at least
[Music]
so my motivation
tonight is um to show you my practice i
guess
oh show me what you guys
[Music]
next up how about
hi attention please and pavilio reigning
from whole life id generation 2. my goal
today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
that loud
oh you're gonna bring that up huh you
were quite decent
oh yeah
yeah i heard you were good you and iris
have heard good good good news about you
oh yeah we had a good practice yesterday
right right senpai
nice thank you for joining us
[Music]
nice to meet you
what's your motivation for today
oh well
i i want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
the last and the laugh in someone's
heart is that such a good thing
does it sound like a good thing
yeah okay
[Music]
hello hello everyone i'm alejandra from
whole life indonesia and thank you so
much for inviting me to this collab i'm
so happy though i'm so excited they go
thank you
[Music]
my motivation for today is that i would
like to have fun though although yes i'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
[Music]
second generation hi guys
motivation i plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motivation
[Laughter]
oh that's okay
we're already here you're gonna have to
dominate us
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
hey
thank you
and i think wait did i get
all the introductions from id i think i
did
all right let's yeah
the e inside let's start with iris oh
yeah hi russ it's iris hololive english
project hope v singer here um my goal
today is to get first place victorus
[Music]
thank you amy thank you for
participating
[Music]
thank you so much for having me here as
well i heard that you waited for
for yeah for me to come on by for that
yes thank you so much
that i needed
before you it was
an elf
that was german
[Music]
okay
you only played mario kart so far in a
member's only stream but that's about it
yeah i won and that one too
oh oh oh okay
i see oh then you might be the hidden
um winning choice that the one
horse dark horse
a wild card player
thank you thank you
next stop
[Music]
english um
um i'll do my best i think we have a we
have a fiercer competition to be not
last and to be first so i'll do my best
[Music]
and i was also
taking this very seriously in her
practice round so a bit scared of inna
i don't know
i'm still falling off maps it's fine oh
[Music]
[Applause]
then let's start let's continue with the
uh introduction from cal iop
maureen hello everyone my name is
callipe my parents are still asleep and
probably can't watch the news this
morning maury nice to meet you
because it's a bit early uh so excuse me
for that guys but i'm very excited just
to be here i really didn't think this
was going to work but it's great i love
it this is this is awesome
yes this is asmr cali
thank you kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and kind of uh
troublesome with some setups and all
that i'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispery and calm
might be a good uh thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
english and i'm kind of sick today and
if you're watching on my side i just
need to say this now
i've had some technical difficulties
very suddenly so i am made of cardboard
i'm sorry please well i it was not my
fault it's out of my control right now
so anyway
i'm png tuber domo somebody does a png
tuber let's race today baby i'm the wild
card today yeah
[Applause]
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so i think it's fine i'm cuteness now
because they want to look at me right
guys
we
welcome everyone i wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time i i
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and i'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so i i don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some uh more often in
the future so please don't stress
yourself out let's just have fun today
[Music]
thank you so much i think we will go to
the roof but before that let me say
thank you and the hats and the cards are
sponsored by nino ma inaniz
[Music]
all right let's uh everyone switch to
the rules image please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically
all characters all courses are allowed
however
if you choose uh please do not choose
random courses please choose a certain
course that you want to actually erase
but if that course has been used before
like if it has actually been chosen
before please do not choose the same
course again
already
[Music]
and
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistant i think you
can check by pressing why
why right
now
okay
how do you see it wait a second it's if
you press y and select your character at
the point where you select the card you
can press on uh plus
the plus button
and then when you see the the three
options on the right side if you press l
uh if if there's a
if there's a
sign that says no
then it's uh
auto steering off that's how it's
supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other ones you can ignore
yeah
okay
okay okay um
[Laughter]
this whole time so unless i have
something to say i'm going to be muted
don't worry if i'm a little quiet i'm
still here with you guys in spirit
[Music]
oh yeah then there's no more rules
there's basically just the system we're
doing the first cup all versus all big
mixer races
[Music]
we mute each other by the way during the
race and just to focus everyone on what
we're driving and then we get back
together and discord talk a little bit
then we go to the second cup which is en
versus id six versus six yes yes yes
that's when we will separate each other
in uh the voice channels by team this
one and this one we will actually talk
with one another if you wanna and then
we uh
give some comments together again when
we get all back together in the same
channel and then we do the third cup
with random randomly thrown together
teams no ian vs id but like all mixed
together naturally beautiful
yeah
what's the random
random random we will just like i'll
i'll count down and and then everyone
joins either voice chat room zero or
voice chat room one what if everyone
joins the same room though
[Music]
[Laughter]
just so you know the the those like team
cups will basically be
um
like the same
[Music]
as all versus all the difference is just
basically like if you throw items like
red shells or whatever and there is a
teammate in front of you it will not go
to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent driver
that's around you so yeah that's how
that team system works i think yes
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
mute yourself on discord if someone's
not ready then i will ask you why you're
not ready okay
bye
i'm gonna win this
bye-bye
okay wait guys how do you wait guys uh
how do you go forward in the game
you push the push a button you can't go
and move right now you can't move in the
world right now yeah that's what you
mean gotcha all right
thank you thanks guys love you okay love
you
too okay i think everyone's muted now
ah kelly simply sounds so sexy today
probably because it's really early okay
are you guys ready are you guys ready to
see me
when
when when
takamori at the end it's so cute
ah
i muted right yeah yeah yeah i made it
okay
uh 150 cc raised no teams normal items
well i think we're starting
winner salty
we not be salty okay we not be salty ah
let's go with the basic stadium for now
actually i haven't really practiced all
the all the
stages
yet let's just hope that it's not oh my
god rainbow road who who wants to choose
rainbow road for the first race
uh i wouldn't mind that i want to buy
the airport airport's fine too
i need a warm up i i haven't really
practiced today last time i practiced
those with
you know yesterday i was ringing it
right now senpai
uh victorious
at least you know just
at least hopefully i don't get dead last
it seems like everyone practiced a lot
though off stream so
honestly i'm not as confident i was as i
was like a couple days ago
yes cheerion everyone cheer me on i love
these accessories that you listen by me
they're so cute
okay we're good
let's go oh oh
okay okay
okay let's let's pay attention pay
attention
yes
i wonder who that was just
sorry
i have a red turtle wait what what's
wrong with my with my thing wait
hmm
i can't seem to
slide oh i was pressing the wrong button
this whole time okay okay i get it now
yeah i was pressing the wrong button
okay okay
i was pressing z r i'm supposed to press
r okay
oh i shouldn't have used that just now
ah
oh
senpai has a green shell it's scary oh
i really should be holding on to those
uh oh uh oh uh oh uh oh
wait who's who's
oh it's raining oh
oh sasuka reyna
senpai wait wait what's wrong with my
controls today i can't seem to drift at
all it's just me
or maybe it's because i'm just nervous
right now
okay we're doing this oh yes i have
nothing to be afraid about now
did i actually use choose like a
different card from the one i usually
use or something
i don't know the rain is like wow like i
can't see her at all
oh no someone's coming the bullet train
is coming bullet train
whoa i can't interrupt it wait
am i pressing something wrong today i
can't seem to be i can't seem to drift
like i usually do
okay
uh oh uh oh why am i eat all of a sudden
oh no oh no no no no no no
ah
okay no no no no we could still we could
still
we could still do this we could still do
this my tilt controls are not on right
am i using a different bike i might be
using a different bike
i don't know i don't feel comfortable
with this right now
can i switch my
oh yeah
wait yeah i'm using a different bike i
think
actually i'm not so sure anymore yeah
this is the one i'm using i was i was
using yesterday okay okay
uh
i still want to choose a mario kart
stadium
yeah i'm yeah i was using the uh what
you gonna call it the flame driver
yesterday right
number one in irises
yeah rita was brought up that
proud of that during the intro
was it the auto steer
did i have auto steer on no i don't
right
it was a bike right yeah it was a bike
i do use bike but i don't i don't think
i used that certain bike last time
cheap cheap
okay wait i just gotta make sure that we
didn't
okay what court course were we playing
uh before
oh did i choose the same place really
oops
okay
this time i'll do good i'll i'll do good
uh pr hopefully
okay yeah this feels better
[Music]
virus
yeah yeah
it's probably better if we just go
underwater
please
wait oops
oh that was dangerous
okay
doing good so far just hope that there's
no blue blue
turtle shell anytime nearby nearby
okay uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
is there any way to avoid this
is that ali75 the name player
okay it's okay i'm still
toward the front
please shut up
oh okay okay nice and calm uh-oh
nice and calm
just gotta give me a banana give me a
banana to protect my back no
i want a banana not this again it's
looking at the same area too
come on come on come on oh my god i'm so
nervous guys
i don't know why i'm being so nervous
right now
senpai i'm coming for you coming for you
senpai
oh no not another one no no no oh
abunai
okay
oh wow i'm surprised i won't hit her
oops oops
okay okay okay okay i have something to
protect my back yay
ah
let's go
let's go okay i gotta make sure i don't
choose the same course so we did the
market please everyone do not use cheap
cheap beach or uh mario kart stadium
anymore for your race collection thank
you okay i'm gonna try and remember that
but
yeah
yeah nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life
isn't there multiple beach
uh yes but the cheap cheap beach the one
that we just did from the ds version not
anything yeah
okay okay
okay are we doing team wait what are we
doing teams
uh we still have two races to go before
all this results
okay
wait oh what is everyone nice hat
she's muted okay
are we me oh sorry okay yeah we're music
what is everyone's uh rank right now
i was like sixth of the first race and i
feel like that kind of pulled me back a
lot
ah
let's start oh yay
we're doing the uh i forgot what this
car this place was called
speed race
your third now okay okay i'm third okay
let's get first again
and
get this win in the bag
i shouldn't drink my drinks myself
oh i should have gone there escape going
on the ramp
i should be holding on to this should i
shouldn't
i i don't really remember the shortcuts
in this map though
i hope i remember them
okay
yeah maybe i should be going this way
[Music]
maybe i shouldn't be holding on to this
for so long but
oh well
okay
who's in front of me
is there
i'm not so sure who's in front of me
right now
i wasn't able to get on the ramp
wow someone's really ahead of us
was it
i'm not sure
is that oh it's probably enough oh no
oh there goes ena
yeah maybe i should be ah
okay there was my star
yeah i i read comments on my practice
streams i'm like holding onto items too
long that's probably true
i should really
keep that in mind
wow
everyone's just shelling each other
okay we're going this way wait
ah where is ina
where is ina senpai
i haven't i can't see her at all
okay let's just throw it
this is the last lap so let's just go
all out
oops
[Music]
i can't see i can't see
it's okay second place isn't that bad
second place isn't that bad
yeah you know it's so ahead
i kind of want to know how she was able
to go that fast
ah
oh now you know first place okay okay
okay you could still do this one more
race right
one more one more one more race okay
uh i wonder what i should choose next
i want to choose something i'm confident
in but i'm not really confident
sunshine airport it is
one more one more
ah
yeah i heard that you know simply
practice a lot like with the ghost and
learning all the um shortcuts i also
learned some shortcuts but
i kind of forgot most of them
just like where were they again
yeah
i hate this place
i don't like this one of the disco ball
one
ah
i was playing the scores of rain
yesterday
it was just horrible
okay we're going we're going quick i
like the music though i have to say
music is very nice all right going on
the pink side
i wonder if there's like a shorter one
okay
maybe green was shorter
not too sure anymore
okay
oh
yeah
[Music]
okay
i just gotta hope
pray pray to the item gods that
there is no blue shell coming
okay wait
oh yeah so far so smooth
i should be talking more but i'm just
like so concerted oh no
okay let's get guys i got disconnected
ah rina got disconnected
okay
i wonder if it's the internet
oh yeah let's hope
let's hope this
that
this can
hit senpai i'm gonna go in the green
side this time
okay
keep my back
open
[Music]
oh
who said okie dokie just now
i did not notice that game effect
ah
oh is the game sound
okay
[Music]
i'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well
like this qualification like glass
but if you
uh oh
if you are oh
wow uh congratulations or everyone
cannot mute themselves now
yeah yeah
okay oh yeah
[Music]
innocent by speed
yeah
i think that's just how we're going to
take it it is what it is yeah maybe
so uh
let me let me just uh ina was number one
right
number one
[Music]
i i saw you kept on selecting rainbow
road why do you
you know
yeah yeah she practiced on that one a
lot i think that's what she was going to
do
you guys better be ready
there it is
there's no chance that we'll we'll get
it oh okay someone has to
uh yeah wait uh wait who was number one
okay okay no problem who was number two
though irish
[Applause]
[Music]
how did you manage to get number two
today i i did bad on the first race so
that really pulled me back but yeah ina
senpai was very quick uh
but i did my best i did my best
i'm satisfied
oh thank you
oh wait me and elena were first oh we
tied up wait
a
[Laughter]
[Music]
minute job good job
wait wait are we complete in the
lobby right now one two three four i am
in the lobby
okay i guess very complete
okay well then shall we uh continue but
muna senpai is currently unavailable
yes yeah we can wait
but i don't know my battery is 100 but
it's state low batteries i don't know
which one is logo
oh
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time i i think i think it
should be fine
okay
okay we're making coffee right now
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee all right
all the caffeine shakes already so
i'm banned from coffee
i was actually really surprised about
amma's driving too like i thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see who
played a game
a lot so it was like a really good place
and most of the races until the end when
i got
[Music]
if you would have shout casted how you
uh suggested uh amel because you're such
a good driver we need you we need you
all right then let's uh
okay ollie okay okay ollie is going to i
don't need teams are we picking i don't
mean like dodgeball no no i don't want
to pick that keeps me up no that gives
me really bad flashbacks i don't like
that
[Laughter]
and i don't want that i'm gonna go at my
full power now because now i'm fighting
for the en ladies
yes teamwork
oh
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
individual races yeah i was going in our
teams
now let's just warm up that was a
warm-up
yep
because inna and iris the two of the
strongest ones aren't ian wait me too no
he's in the bag
i'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news yes
morrison is a good asset to have i want
her team
will have to carry uh indonesia's uh
back
yeah it's okay
i will support it
i will as long as i get a good battle
after all this i'll be good all right
yeah i can
get disconnected again
yeah that's the main problem yeah
hopefully
oh i hope you don't get disconnected
everyone uh please split into teams by
uh i think let's just um ian go to uh
voice channel 01 thank you okay
hmm
wait a second
okay okay okay and just cali is missing
did kelly get the memo
i've never played on teams before but
like um you know for items do they
automatically um not hit our teammates
it only hits like an okay oh okay okay
it's really helpful yeah nice i was
wondering about that um well i've never
uh parted teams yet i'll see how we can
select that i think we will um
like every every a participant will have
a choice to witness okay which team they
can join i think that's how it works
let's see no more items no cpu all
vehicles race for races let's go let's
go
so watson doesn't drive off the edge we
should be all right
okay
[Music]
uh uh i'm the one doing this okay uh
playa was ollie right yeah no no wait no
no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no how do
i how do i cancel this no uh
if i have to
like you might have to
ah oh
it sounds fine it looks
[Laughter]
i'm
[Music]
okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again i think it's closed once yeah
thank you sorry
all right
[Music]
just drift as much as you can that's
that's how this works
yes but not overdrift you know you know
there they are into the world the bald
one in his back
she's unleashing her full power with the
baldness
that is that is raining i think oh it's
okay
okay all in the same
ground
wait have a complete one two three
six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
okay i think we're coming back he's just
doing a head count everybody's standing
still and i drive here
nineteen after oh yeah i think we are
okay um
[Music]
mommy
are you sure you don't want to say
anything
[Music]
this is how you do it
okay
one two three four
okay now it's even let's go let's go
random button there so for later we can
i can just do the random button we don't
have to do the voice chat thingy wait
we've changed now yes
yeah are we we're choosing different
again
a new map a new battle okay
which one do we all have confidence i'm
pretty confident in the sunshine airport
rainbow room
[Music]
not lose which rainbow road there's like
three different rainbows i want to do
wario stadium wario stadium
oh
[Music]
they're definitely teams
when did we push the go button on the
tube
oh
[Music]
people unless i don't know is was it a
green shell
oh it's probably yeah the green shell
just hit it does it i don't think you
can control it yeah you can't it's red
it's red it's red it's ready
[Music]
well i see someone right in front of me
that's interesting what
i think we're laughing
oh no oh no no yeah
oh it's okay it's okay
in front of me that's fine someone in
front of you on this road
items items items
like one come on come on come on come on
come on you wanna wrap your
perspective afterwards
okay we got it we got it did we
third place
[Music]
wow
bowser castle which bowser the new
bowser cat no no that's new by the city
oh the crown cup whatever it's called
mount wario or like the animal crossing
map is easy like easy as in it's like oh
no
you gotta make it difficult for them
cheese
cheese wait no
we gotta do something
um
no i don't like the cheese one no
[Music]
just has a lot of traps and a lot of um
obstacles and just got to be careful
about that
never mind don't stop um his evil left
oh
let's go
i was number one for one second i love
that one that was a good second
i like
[Music]
okay who's in front of us
no okay that's me and yeah okay so
everyone's in here and then okay that's
good that's good
[Music]
it seems like the flower does attack
someone
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
yes
whose song was that again
miley cyrus
can you have my girlfriend
[Music]
oh he's in front of
okay should i throw the red shell right
now
[Music]
that was such a bad timing ah
really bad time
oh i hate it when the lightning hits
when you're about to film yeah
all right
let's go
[Music]
oh no oh god
oh no
[Music]
she's
i feel like they're definitely getting
technical on us here you guys i know
yeah we gotta we gotta get our game up
they got nothing on us
we're good but we shouldn't jinx it
okay
rainbow road on the crown yeah rainbow
on the crown rainbow run on the crown
okay
what does that mean
oh we all have shiny crowns on our heads
look at us
cheese versus rainbow
[Laughter]
i feel like it's gonna be cheese yeah
it's too much cheese here
oh
oh oh oh
okay he's land why do they like that one
so much he says they must know something
we don't
robbie dana is probably really good at
that one that's why i choked it oh
probably trying to get the points back
we can't let them yeah all right no no
no we have a good head start still
yeah oh i've been a burnout
just kidding
[Music]
i didn't even know that was a shortcut
they know the shortcuts we're in trouble
they do they do
okay i'm still okay we're still good
we're still good
well that was dangerous
it went to someone else in front of you
which will be number 12 like
it's gonna be a long road for that one
right right here this is one shortcut
that i know
my white character i shouldn't have
listened
oh
okay well she knows the shortcut i see
how i saw it i just saw it i was like oh
yeah there was a shortcut here
at the very end
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no i'm going off track
okay
only iris is ahead of me yep yep
oh reina came
through the shortcut oh uh oh oh no no i
didn't have a mushroom to use that
shortcut okay she's first now okay
give me something good
oh no not a banana
i can't use a banana against rainey
[Music]
oh god okay no no no no no
no no oh no this is not good this is not
good guys
okay suffering together
[Music]
yeah the red shell worked beautiful ugh
by the way in the end rainbows
rainbow road rainbow road okay
[Music]
i think it will bite us in the ass but
we have enough so okay yeah i don't know
i'll do my best
i don't know that i don't know the
shortcuts for this so
i don't know any shortcuts but the
shortcut is just go down in space to
sana
sana will she'll carry us through yeah
oh i actually don't mind the airport
either though
airport airport is nice too i know the
shortcuts for that
oh we're getting right oh
okay
yeah as long as all of us don't get like
the lowered rankings we're fine
just don't fall off yet
yep
i keep falling off of this
[Music]
i think she's not gonna have no no
no here we go
oh thank god
okay okay
oh please please don't don't
this is so slippery
scares me
[Music]
it's okay we are one two three right now
yeah it's all of us okay um
oh yeah blue shell coming
okay that's fine
that was not me that was not me either
that's fine
that's close to me don't get too close
to me i have a rainbow on my back
okay let's finish
[Music]
oh horrible timing
i saw it
[Music]
oh
okay we'll get her okay
[Music]
oh yeah i see
i see ollie
give me a bullet bill come on
i just saw marina arena i'll operate in
front of me okay
oh that was the chocolate
oh that was the shortcut hong kong hong
kong
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go cali
that was the last one
[Music]
we're going back
uh what was their reasoning behind
choosing uh the cheese one and the baby
road
i like cheese
was somewhat in control there because
like it's gotta be a road where reina
knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
well
i wasn't the one choosing it well uh do
we have uh
some
comments from the winner ina it was
number one i think
uh yes uh i would like to thank pajamas
um
[Laughter]
for this
opportunity because of you yago i was
about to be like yeah go let's go okay
[Laughter]
okay so we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that i would appreciate that
okay yes sir
[Music]
what did we choose
eh
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be
like that so let's just let's try to not
choose the ones that we have uh raised
before okay and i will do the random
teams now actually there is uh we don't
have to do the voice chat thing because
there is actually uh a way to do it here
ooh
and then once the themes are selected
oh there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero
uh zero zero one what you want uh gouda
and anya
[Music]
and eufy
all right
okay here we go
guys wait guys we still have hope
oh god the pressure the pressure i don't
i don't i'm not really confident in
winning against eno right now
what's your favorite map
my favorite map has to be uh probably uh
the airport right now um sunshine
airport
let's go ahead and airport yeah airport
okay then how about we choose
where is it we haven't played it let's
go
[Music]
from
yeah it seems like yeah the other team
is is packed with like the really strong
ones i'm just like
there's like chiara reina and inaudible
let's go
let's go let's go iris i'd like to
apologize to you personally because i
kept bullying you in the previous round
i
[Music]
your way okay
oh it's ribbon road okay okay
where is it
wait i hate this map wait this one is
particularly hard for
me oh god i shouldn't have done that
over there oh
oh no oh no
it's okay it's only enough right in
front of me right now okay
[Music]
sorry
did i just
beat you what
oh yeah ollie's in front okay good good
good um
no no please please please
okay
we're doing good
[Music]
no
oh
okay
[Music]
oh no wait who's in front of me right
now arena and nina uh
oh okay
[Music]
that's not good okay i'm under this wow
but i'm not
nobody in here i'm so far away
[Music]
oh that was close that was very close
okay uh
second
uh ina i think i got first i was seven
i'm i'm seven
[Music]
it's fine
it's good it's good
uh
it's fine it's fine it's not that bad
it's not that bad right now yeah
yeah
okay it could be worse yeah yeah no no
only 10 points no no wait we're still
we're still in the race
i didn't like this map
that annoys me
yeah the airport the items airport yeah
airport airport please
all right
sunshine
it's okay guys
it's okay it's okay
i just gotta beat nina i just gotta pee
ina
[Music]
how much practice did ina do
you are our
so strong
amelia's invite can't you rewind time so
that we can like redo that and win isn't
that crony's job
what do you do for everyone just me
amelia's doing the watch right so yeah
yeah she can go back in time and
practice a lot
yeah right
for us
what is this
course what is this big blue i don't
know if i've ever played this one before
i think i haven't tried what is this
this one is like futuristic water
parkish
[Music]
okay i think i recognize what i don't
like is that the npcs keep harassing me
oh the ones in the map yeah
in the way
[Music]
oh i love
right now but this is very early game
it's not jinxes
yes
[Music]
oh there's somebody's acting flying with
bananas
well that's me
i gotta be careful okay
[Music]
oh wow that was dangerous
come on come on i hate it when they
minimize that
yeah thunder really destroys my pace ah
okay
i don't see ina come on come on i want
to see ina on my screen
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i see her okay
oh she's using a shortcut oh
okay i just saw her do the shortcut that
i've never okay
did
[Music]
ah
i should have studied more
sorry
uh
yeah inna is too strong
[Music]
um
uh i'm i'm getting really salty right
now i'm being very salty right now guys
ah
oh no oh no salt is piling up in me
right now airport
[Applause]
the yep will do us justice we'll ascend
it'd be embarrassing though if we get
airport and i still do bad at it
okay
i believe
let's believe
[Music]
oh everyone's to the airport
oh my god sorry
wait is this the third race or the last
race this is third right third okay
yes okay we got this we got this
we got this
sunshine
let's just hope that ina doesn't really
know this map but i probably she
probably does
i think she does yeah
uh
from like thunder and stuff there's no
way to really prevent that
i mean like if we got something
[Music]
oh god
okay i just want to get closer come on
come on
i don't really get how this music like i
have this like speaker looking thing i
don't really know how i'm supposed to
use it
oh it's like uh if there are like a lot
of people
it's like
okay
[Music]
let's just use it
i have a bad habit of holding on onto
items yes ollie go ollie
[Music]
let's see okay we got first down second
place right now i don't see inaudible
okay
[Music]
oops i'm sorry
that was close
[Music]
oops
okay we're in the same team okay
just gotta make sure it's not enough
yeah
okay
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
she got third
okay
i wonder how this looks right now
yes
yes we're ahead of points okay
in the middle
ah this is such a close battle okay okay
what are we gonna do next does anyone
have anything that they're confident in
music i'm very confident uh which one
which cup is that or where are your
stadiums
i got this connected oh okay oh she got
disconnected you'll be able to join
before we pick the next one oh wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait i'm gonna
join
which is music part
music particle kit
yeah
oh no can i can i join before it is ah
let's see and you can join yeah yeah oh
oh i'll tell i'll tell first run for it
it's not ready yet
right yeah people haven't chosen yet
there we go
wait did you realize we got the crown
did you get in yeah yeah we're like
ahead by six points
six points we gotta keep this up it's a
very close race
we got this we got hope
uh
okay
please not not the clock not the clock i
don't like the clock
[Music]
this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys uh ah
do you know the shortcuts for this
okay there there are a few shortcuts but
they're actually pretty tricky so i
wouldn't recommend them okay
yeah all right got it let's do it i
don't really recognize this place but
let's go
i'm gonna win this
oh no i just cried uh-oh
screwed up on the beginning
okay over here the piano
[Music]
here but it's really really pretty
shoot
okay okay wait uh
who's first right now i see ina in front
of me so i'm just a second reina okay
[Music]
because i saw
oh them
i don't like this map
oh no guru is in front of me
oh you're our last hope right now i'm
i'm doing really bad
i'm a zombie how am i my hope
it's okay
a lot of your kind so
we're good
hope has consumed zombie meat a lot so
oh no i see so many people in front of
me
[Music]
okay
oops
did i accidentally hit someone
okay be careful
oh no
i got disconnected
who got disconnected i got disconnected
good luck guys
destiny is in your hands
i got number one i'm gonna go watch one
of you one of your
perspectives to see what's going on um
so when i ate oh my god i'm last
ah
well it was a valiant effort ladies yeah
we tried hey that's two fours in there
i like it i can't say where is the game
[Music]
okay so we uh
i got kicked out of the room uh
[Music]
and we have two disconnections so it
kind of doesn't count
yeah yeah it totally doesn't count and
and when i rejoin like my points are all
reset
[Music]
yeah we got disconnected
i got disconnected like right before the
last lap
uh oh no that was me or my shark friends
after the wi-fi cables
[Music]
interesting that probably means that you
know the last round if if riso you know
got disconnected and the points got
deleted that means that the last round
uh final result is not really accurate
um
but yeah that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra encore for
fun
and yeah and i would like to give out
some golden juggles
we all want a golden yaga right
so okay they're not showing up on your
stream they're only on my name
but i'd like i would like to give one a
golden juggle to ina for winning almost
everything
[Music]
and i would like to give another uh
golden yagu um as uh to iris for also
being absolutely amazing
thank you
i bought it for the golden yaago
that's so shiny
another golden juggle goes to
dana for being i guess the strongest in
the id team holy moley
[Applause]
goes to gura for being absolutely the
speediest shark i've ever seen
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
goes to muna for being amazing
[Music]
i didn't see you that much on the race
but i think you were still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to omi
for being also surprisingly indeed damn
good yeah yeah yeah
yeah she got first place
[Music]
[Applause]
goes to cali for absolutely really you
know i don't you you surprised me you
surprised me callie i was i was looking
at you driving there and i was like damn
well what the hell man she didn't even
do practice arcs is she so good
[Laughter]
everyone thank you we will stop moving
don't mind me uh chat i'm not gonna be
able to fix that now i think one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
uh
wait who did i not give
[Music]
you were surprising me too sometimes i
have i had an eye on you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
you very yeah
everyone um i hope you all had fun thank
you um can we get like a uh last last
comment from everyone let's start with
uh anya
oh me
okay um that was so much fun but i have
to practice more if it's maybe next time
i don't know maybe
maybe
there will definitely be a next time
yeah yeah
there's always room for improvement
[Music]
kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commission you made
all of this stuff ina as well for
helping with the assets but like
oh my goodness you organized the whole
thing and it was a blast and i just
wanted to have fun with my friends and i
was able to do that because you
organized this amazing thing just thank
you so much for for working so hard on
it because it was a blast
thank you i'm so glad you enjoyed it
thank you
[Music]
ah
thank you i wanna say thank you also to
ina and kiara for all the hard work you
guys put into this tournament thank you
and i'm very i'm proud of myself for not
doing nearly as bad as i thought it
would and i would like to uh say that it
was probably because i fixed my switch
legs so i didn't have any lag let's go
gamers let's go let's go
i'll excuse i'm sorry watch and i won
though i can use that excuse
[Music]
even though you me played your game in a
long time i think yeah no practice baby
that's good raw talent raw talent shark
high school
well
sashimi
from the last place
ah yes so i'm just uh thank you for uh
organizing this i know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles but yes thank
you for this golden yellow i will
cherish it and talk to you
thank you thank you
thank you
okay i've completely disappeared i'm
sorry guys
okay i race close and commonplace
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament kiara and
thank you so much ina for the very very
cute assets
and
yes i will practice more
so that
we can i can get go against ena fair and
square very nice yeah yeah my goal is
now my goal is eena
yeah i'm really excited to do this again
hopefully one day yeah
thank
you thank you i hope yeah one day i want
to win against inaudible that's a big
big goal that's a big accomplishment yes
it's not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
i'm so glad i'm so glad you joined holo
ian because that's what made this uh
tournament possible yeah i'm really glad
to be able to join this wonderful
tournament being part of the cool kids
okay i'd like to say a very very big
thank you to tiara senpai for organizing
this i've organized it once and it was
really hectic so i can't really imagine
the links that you go through
for like logos and stuff
and even the thumbnails those must have
been hard and also for instance making
all of those accents so quickly
like you guys really um how do i say it
i really appreciate it a lot and i'm
sure all of us do so thank you so much
for your hard work it was really fun
playing with everyone and um i may have
not popped everyone but one way or
another you guys will all be honest
i forgot about that goal yeah
little bottom thing
[Laughter]
you'll get them someday olly you'll get
them
one day
thank you right
standby closing please
um first of all i'm thank you for you
kiara for organizing this thing and
you guys can stop thanking me
stop
i mean
i i don't think without without you
organizing we wouldn't be like this yeah
i mean it's it's it's rare to
gather all the whole life you're gonna
change yeah and together that's true
yeah i'm so thankful for that
and also
um
big thanks to inna 2 for making the
assets it's really good
thank you so much and i hope uh in the
future we can be like this again yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yes yes yes i hope so too definitely i
was thinking like maybe on on
like around christmas or new year's eve
we should do something else
perfect christmas party
okay
closing comments please yeah i'd like to
say a big thank you to
kiara for organizing it of course i know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and
like schedules is really really
difficult but you really put a lot of
effort into organizing it commissioning
like the logo and everything really
thankful um and everyone feel free to
use your hats and cards like in your
mario kart streams in the future yay
i was curious about that thank you
[Music]
and uh yeah thank you everyone for
joining us today like it was so much fun
like playing with everyone and uh
yeah it was a lot of fun it's been a
pleasure
operation this was a great cooperation
between uh kfb and taco taco bell taco
eats definitely
yeah
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speed because we're
fast
okay
closing comments please okay i know you
said stop but thank you chiara
everything
and
also inna senpai
thank you so much and i had a lot of fun
there was a little mishap there there
was a little disconnection issue but
overall i had a lot of fun and i would
love to have this kind of tournament
again in the future let's do it yeah
yeah
thank you
okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
closing comments please
okay so it doesn't end there i would
like to say thank you
[Laughter]
to to everyone here also especially uh
kiara and ina like who's are
amazing and also okay uh i'm really
happy because i can actually uh gather
and play with all of you guys here yeah
yes like
i'd appreciate more more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
i
i'd love to actually i would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much i
love you guys
[Music]
ah
well first uh i'd like to apologize
if i was salty if i cursed that you guys
uh
[Music]
you guys work really hard thank you guys
and thank you everybody for
participating it's really fun i know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and i had
a lot of fun thank you
thank you thank you
you know now that we have now that we
have hobo council we can like we don't
have to relay on these exact 12 members
anymore so next time if you want you can
do shout casting
shout out
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today um i hope i hope
everyone had a great time even if you
know maybe you were not number one
number two number three that's fine i
think today was really just about
getting together putting um two
communities two fan communities of hello
ian and hello id together and just
feeling united definitely and i am
always glad to um do stuff like this
again so i would gladly invite you guys
again whenever you have time for it and
want to join and i'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration um it's not gonna be an
ideal time for everyone so i'm so sorry
for the girls who had to wake up at like
six seven a.m or something like that i'm
so sorry i know it's tough i i it was
fun
i hope your mom enjoyed the tournament
[Laughter]
i would like to officially close the
holo ian hall id mario kart tournament
everyone
take care of your golden yagos polish
him every day he wants to be shiny and
sparkly
and yeah i'll see you guys soon thank
everyone thank you
[Music]
darkness will fade away
light will guide your way
hope has descended and you are not alone
[Music]
oh
hope will lead your way
i'm here
[Music]
[Applause]
and thus
my training arc begins for first place
victorus
will be in my hands next time
virus