[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
d
[Music]
oh my god i'm gonna get complaints again
for that kiki
[Music]
[Applause]
okay no [\h__\h] complaints now huh
hello
do you hear me
what up camping
i bought a new game i bought warrior
where get it together
yeah we're going to play a new game
[Music]
soon i want to play animal crossing
again once the
uh update comes out which was sometime
soon
i forgot the date
then i want to play animal crossing
again it's been a while
so
it's gonna be
you see you see i've i've received a
message uh
it sounded quite triggered
um
by the fact that i say
recently in my streams when i plan to
have them as a short stream that i say
it's going to be a short stream and ends
up not being a short stream
i've received a
triggered message that i
please may stop doing that
if i if i don't
uh
plan on having it being a short stream
then i should rather just not say it at
all
well
uh sorry but
it just happens and i mean it still felt
yesterday felt short to me okay it was
maybe not that that short but it felt
short and and
and
but maybe maybe time goes slower for you
because i don't know first because
you're freaking
around with time
stop stealing the stop watches stop
watches this is the stopwatch stop stop
stealing the watches anyway okay and and
and if you don't count the super chat
rating yesterday then it was short
i think for
my standards maybe
um
it's just hard
like yesterday okay i i i wanted to play
it a little bit less to be honest but i
didn't think that the character creation
would take me so long to like do them
justice
uh
so honestly by the time i was done with
character creation i felt like in some
way i was ready to quit the game at that
point but i would have felt like sorry
to end it there because there was no
gameplay yet that's why i decided to add
another hour to it
in order to you know provide some kind
of gameplay otherwise it was literally
just character creation what the hell
so that's why it ended up being a little
bit longer
i
am
not sorry
how how will i know how long this dream
will be sometimes the game is more fun
than you think it is and then you tend
to play a little bit longer and
sometimes talking to you guys is more
fun than i i was i was hoping it's for
it to be and then we talk a little bit
longer well it's your fault then it's
your fault for being so nice to be
around at okay it's your fault
let's go
[Music]
diamond city
diamond city lights illuminate up
hit game super pure takes flight
is there no voicing for this game
why are we aware inc
wrong
company can't take it
too quiet
my game is finished
it's all done oh oh nowadays it was hard
work wait until the
automatic showers sounds yes
yes
why is it so really quiet
maybe that's what's going on with it
[Applause]
my warrior does not know how to
communicate
did you say what
what
the mouth is satisfied
he says wow
how come inna hasn't played this game
yet
wait i think i know why it's so quiet
yeah yeah
yeah my headphones i turned them too
quiet
[Music]
i've never played this game before i
know it's been a
series that has been around for a long
time on like other devices
and and i guess the the whole principle
of the game is generally always
the same
like doing quick
very quick games and i think i remember
asking you guys
um a million years ago
like what kind of short games we could
be playing on my channel
and i think some of you guys recommended
warioware games but that was before this
game came out
and now there you go we have this game
isn't that wonderful what a coincidence
coincidence i think not
maybe i maybe i'm the reason why this
game was released huh huh ever thought
about it that way no didn't you didn't
did yeah yeah because it's not true uh
so how do i play this game one to two
plays i guess here's the story
really
let's get into it um i'm
alone
uh i live a lonely life
okay wario time to get to know him
donald
change the number of players here no i'm
fine
well do i just go a okay
is it too loud by the way
[Music]
we got a jet pack
what's this
oh i know i feel like i'm flying i am
flying
is it because i'm inside the game
who cares this is going to come in handy
[Music]
this video game maker is a video game
maker
oh
why are you
why do you wear ink
makes games
oh
that's his lore i just i did never know
that she loves garlic
and treasure and money i mean
who doesn't love money and i love
treasure too and i [\h__\h] love garlic
mario i love you
i think we're destined to be together
what could possibly go wrong oh that's a
good question all right let's go
why are you attacks in whichever
direction he's facing
uh-huh
get out of the way and push
and escape aha
i actually uh watched a little bit of
gameplay footage of this game so i kind
of know what uh that there's like a lot
of characters and each character has a
different way of attacking and but
basically i guess the controls are
always very simple but you get these
these quick challenges and quickly you
have to quickly think
and
to get through the levels yeah yeah
is this it is it's the level i made
[Music]
you need to clean the freaking bacteria
whoa
that thing messed up everything you
touched
it's a box
this is bad it's going to ruin my level
ah wait
chiario
oh thank you for for renewing your
membership and for joining the
membership welcome
i would love to play with others too but
this is only local and we all know
there's no other europeans in hell alive
maybe once i can travel to somewhere
i'll visit one of the girls just to play
this with them
what's going on
is that a note
why is that
what
why is that what look what does the nose
mean
nose meteor what that oh
one
hand
okay
orange
i'm so slow
what what's this
this lots what does this what
[Music]
i saved
hey cricket
this devoted student of the martial arts
dylan gently trains under
master mantis he likes meat dumplings
i love meat dumplings too
jumping is cricket specialty hold down a
to perform a high jump okay
um
oh i almost destroyed everything can i
restart this if i destroy anything or oh
wait i don't need to
he ah he jumps all the way to the top
oh
[Music]
okay nice okay i i don't know i like
warrior more but okay who the hell are
you 18 volts check it out
check it i'm here too
and get this i can throw this disc on my
head as many times as i want
and know what's even better
i don't have to move
okay that is a life i want to live
this overgrown school kid has mad
rapping and retro gaming skills oh
sounds like callie
he loves to play with his pin sized pal
9 volt
ah there's another one of you guys
eight involved frozen disc in whichever
here
[Music]
okay easy
push grab really
click on the fingers tanger i'm trying
to be
time to join forces it's the only way
come on let's tag team our foe
yeah
okay
[Music]
i almost didn't understand what you
wanted from me
don't speed up later
drop what the sword oh i thought you
were
why not
[Music]
boss stage oh god i'm not ready for this
i'm surprised i'm still alive
even
is that a garlic volcano
defeat eh
i'll try
not nice
i think i i think
[Laughter]
i was um
i think that was uh
surprisingly bad
wasn't that the tutorial
wait do i continue or start over i can
continue
i guess i'll start over
what i have to focus
i was trying to vote
it's my first warrior wagon yeah thank
you thank you for like you know
defending me mm-hmm
uh
did i continue okay
what the hell
it's a little bit embarrassing oh oh now
we get to do it in four lives
wait do i get to use the four lives in
here
or do i still
am i still not supposed to get hit even
once okay
nice
was that that height huawei
was that so difficult
[Music]
and
um
i have no excuse for that
defeat
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
you're very good at this game kiara why
are you lying to me
just to make me feel better thank you
come on
[Laughter]
i'm not used to using a jet pack okay
normally i use my own wings
this is incredible
it's like i'm doing it on purpose
my hands are sweating so much
[Music]
not sideways i don't know why he goes
sideways
it's my joy-con
my my my game my my pro pro controller
not my joycon
[Music]
i was trying to go up with that and i
was wondering why it doesn't go up well
now i understand i mean that's not my
fault what is that
oh
[Music]
okay okay okay meteor what the hell
soybean sample your concert is already
over
oh wait wait wait wait wait i think oh
that was close that was close that was
close
okay now that's that's a totally
different story okay
oh dear
bye
yay
yes yes
all right
okay now i can come out of my hidey hole
again because now i don't feel that bad
about it anymore
[Music]
don't be so hard on me
now you are you can't hide from wario
bunk
whoa the corruption
it's disappearing
hmm
i bet there was a game but they make
games act all glitchy i see i see so if
we get rid of the bugs everything will
go back to normal
[Music]
okay time to smash some bugs
cricket an 18 ball join the crew
a thousand coins that's a lot of coins
so far
so good i'm doing a great job right yup
yup yup
we can't get a girl next it seems you
unlock playopedia in the menu you
unlocked missions in the main menu
you unlocked crew in the main menu
we can get this girl
[Applause]
hello mario is that you
oh
my scooter it won't stop
hey
hey man cute
nice to meet you
work school and pets keep this high
school student busy she's also a big fan
of wario why who can say
wait orange hair fan of wario it's me
yeah i mean
it feels familiar
mona is always on the move so you have
to steer her in the right direction a
boomerang can be aimed the same way huh
aha
okay
okay so you can't stop here
okay yeah that's
relatively easy
ah oh oh after uh throwing it once i can
still like ah move it around really oh i
become the boomerang
[Music]
this is no time to rest we must keep
going
go go go go go go move move
that's live why is that a toilet i
what a mess my level looks awful
but inside the game did this
unacceptable let's go
let's go
oh ah how can you choose free
[Music]
wait i already forgot how he works but i
guess he stays in the same spot and then
you throw something
all right let's do these three
[Music]
she's got rich
parents
don't worry
you have the right to destroy the house
when your owner is gone yes
[Music]
she has an elephant
don't kill him
oh my gosh she's scary does that remind
you of someone guys does that remind you
of someone
you'll be
me no
oh they're gonna do the same thing again
coming back home
oh they did not learn from it
[Laughter]
they are masochistic i say
oh connect oh what what connect what
what what what oh oh oh
what what
what what what what what what good why i
don't get it
squeeze
squeeze squeeze squeeze
okay i can do that
why not that was that was okay that was
easy
match
[Music]
what wait that was not a failure even
okay this is this is something i can do
beautiful
watch out
uh uh what is it about to suck me up
piece of cake that was okay
okay so just don't get sucked up by that
okay speed up
[Music]
stress level
rising more
tidy
[Music]
let me do it again
one more
100 coins what if i start over is that
free let's start over like i i
completely messed up the first one
[Music]
there's someone back looking for me and
he's gonna take a piece ah
escape
oh oh
oh that was new
didn't have that one before peel pew
puppy
oh that was smooth
[Music]
looking good
next next
ring ring ring
[Music]
so
that's close close
always brush your teeth
speed up speed up speed up speed up
speed up speed up speed up speed up beat
up
[Music]
yeah what the hell
that was much easier than love wario
knock it off what
yeah because that is propaganda from a
different fast food restaurant that was
not cafe it no i don't understand this
one
i wasn't able to move anymore
[Music]
but she moves like constantly so that's
difficult to control in the beginning
quick thinking guys unplug okay
[Music]
let's
go
i'm ready
come at me what you what you gonna do
huh
what
oh no what memorize complete package
uh i don't know this
ah
was that right
how do i give it to you
[Music]
in the box okay okay okay okay
what what what what two boots ah okay
okay okay okay i get it i get it
[Music]
i mean
maybe
that and and and
shopping
oh oh but i need two hats can i take two
hats yes okay
and that and and
that
and
that and then we go down
perfect
[Music]
hey i have to redo everything because of
that no
oh we have one more life though
one more life
that one's very close okay a bag pot
whatever whatever
completely
this one
no not bad this one
the kettle the blue kettle
okay so far so good the cockroach is
back wait can i get rid of it
oh i was able to get rid of it uh wait
wait wait wait wait
one of these
and and and no you're on
these are difficult to remember
oh god uh okay three
kettles
one more
and
this one okay this must be perfect come
on it's three of them and one red one
[Music]
i did everything oh
took me only two tries better than
before
oh i'm getting used to it
so is her house clean now is everything
good now
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
good work everyone otsu moonlight
oh two animals oops they look like
a cat and a dog
yeah dribbling spits
that that does look like a cat and a dog
or or a dog in something else
[Music]
the games are puns and the title is a
clue
oh really
look at all of this corruption it's just
awful
yeah i'm starting to think it isn't so
bad after all
no mario how could you say that
he likes filthy places
it fits him very well is that a cat
mario
wow what are they looking for here
this taxi driving duo is happy to take
you from your front door to the far
reaches of space
the far is always fair and the fair is
always fair
play one and player two what if what if
i play alone who plays the other one
dribble player one always fires bazooka
to the right and spits player 2 always
fires bizarre to the left ah
[Music]
so i just
end up with a random one
what if i ended up with the one from the
left but who shoots left can i like
uh
doesn't bounce off the wall now
oh i guess i just have to push it ah
[Music]
i will uh-huh beat rebel aha
we took a look around there are messes
like this all over the place
the game bugs must have corrupted the
entire game
let's go let's go get some boxes
yeah
i have to choose him
all right let's do
oreo
mona
[Music]
dribble and spits out of this world tour
seven seven seven seven seven seven
whoa nice ride
my uber driver is finally here
wow uber driver is a poser a flexer oh
dear
that reminds me
of a different game for some reason the
looks of that planet
reminds me of two different games
[Music]
because i can't spin upwards close quote
this is going great escape
escape route from where where how do i
escape oh god oh god i opened the path
for him
i wasn't able to escape though yes okay
okay okay
[Music]
oh i can just move around it and that
works too okay
[Music]
no problem for me it counted i'm
surprised yeah give me give me crown
stand back from what
what do you
[Music]
it
there we go
no problem with munna
protect protect
that was a new one again there's so many
games escape
uh
okay
okay easy
piece of cake
[Music]
last time i missed that one
it's not even that difficult well it's
five now
i'll just stay here
[Music]
that wasn't fair
[Laughter]
erase okay
no problem good night sleepy sleep good
taco
big taco let's small dog asleep dodgy
okay
[Music]
oh
lunch
[Music]
that was brutal yup
uh oh my god protect
who who am i protecting
what
who am i protecting the guy behind me or
that little monster here
save okay
[Music]
i think i'm protecting the baby
okay
and just spam those bullets
[Laughter]
ah
i don't know what we were waiting for i
thought it was maybe like a time time
limited
thing thank you chad i didn't realize i
had to do that i did it first round
wow
[Music]
nice first try for real this time yeah
hi i got a high score guys
we can go left all right this is
dr cragler
and this is 9 volts ah the friend of 18
vote let's go get his friend done
let's go get his friend
oh i could get used to this
all this pushing is good it is good for
my training but can't you walk just a
little bit
oh he's pushing him oh
obsessed with nintendo games and has
some serious djing and yo-yo skills
oh
an intricate character i seek
i could i could never figure out how to
use a yo-yo
okay only upwards
press a to stop and shoot his yo-yo
upwards okay
[Music]
might be a pain in the ass to work with
let's go okay
turn around
what do you mean turn around ah
[Music]
oh
first
left
push go
one escape okay
now you're fine you say that now but
have you seen how i've been playing the
game so far
red right did you see that that was so
scary and so awesome
okay huh huh what's wrong with my level
is it broken
totally there's these bugs in the game
and they are chewing it all up okay okay
then let's go get them nobody messes
with my games
nine balls this is in the game now we're
gonna play with mona cause she's cute
and
18 volts again i don't want to play with
cricket for some reason
no worrio bye bye this is no more
warrior where this is keanu wear get out
of here wario carefree is taking over
what is cuties
[Music]
oh is that your friends can we get the
girl too
at some point
[Music]
high five buddy don't get lost
cute house
so sweet
indeed
bye bye mama
oh
[Laughter]
that reminded me of um you know that
that gift gift
where uh the the bungle cat bongs on the
table
i don't know or it also reminded me of
those of that meme with uh
where where i think that it looks
similar to that but they smacked the
table
uh for like a like a heart heart icon
hey what am i talking about you know
what i'm talking about i don't know how
to describe it
another describe describe it
what what is this
shoot yo-yo okay okay
oh
yellow i forgot the name of the color
[Music]
mario games on my channel before but i
would be horrible at it climb
okay
[Music]
okay okay i'm doing well i'm doing well
guys can you believe it
now comes the speed up though
create
[Music]
but just collecting it was enough okay
oh my god this game reference is so cool
there's so many
create path
[Music]
oh sorry i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
i didn't i i needed a bit more time get
caught or not get clogged get caught
no not getting caught okay okay
okay
spin
oh
[Music]
is this pikmin
which is greater
[Music]
i got squished but okay no problem ghost
is here luigi leave it to me you're
really bad at hunting ghosts just leave
it to me
deliver
delivery
[Music]
it was like if you waited one more
second it would have been delivered on
its own
[Music]
like those those dried onion breads to
me
donkey kong happy
[Music]
what
no
[Music]
oh yeah
i mean depending on which character you
get for which game it can be a little
bit more difficult
oh god let's play a game cute which game
did we put in there it looked familiar
you guys know which game they put in
there i just didn't get a good look at
it
but it looked familiar uh no no this
side this side this side purple purple
purple big fat cat
that's chocolates
chunky's friend may be smart that was
sunshine ah
cool ghost
ghost it's always there somehow
always there
[Music]
uh
you put me in that situation in that
position out of nowhere you expect me to
react correctly
[Music]
okay there you go oh my god at least
this time i was able to lead you to
victory
spin it
oh god
[Music]
was that enough what do you mean they
were already dancing
oh my god
[Music]
praise
it was so charming
what
[Music]
how much time do i have
i'm just not allowed to fall down i
guess and that it would end if i would
fall down
[Music]
what if i get more coins do i get
anything for that
[Music]
yeah he switched what does that do again
oh it's like
a cool down finally i have time to chill
and relax oh my sweet
[Music]
let's play a game like that sometime
oh i finally had time to break
boss fight bus fight bus fight
no that that one game i did first round
yes but i took a lot of time for it
youtube where was my notification
welcome welcome
[Music]
okay
wait what about the boss fight wait was
that the boss fight
was that the i thought that was a random
game
oh that's why it was like so like
chill and long ah
oh okay
i understand
ah cool
what the hell are you
oh am i swimming am i flying
power paddle paddle look at my flippers
go
hello hello dr krieger
indeed what's the gallium is going on
around here
that's the cracker down here
i don't recall my level looking like
this at all
ah you're here too extra ordinary
doctor what is that pose oh extracting
that pose also
he has a very sparkly head
this genius scientist is so good at
making mechanical
marvels he made a cyborg out of himself
[Music]
press a hold a to make crackers swim
through the air
uh-huh okay
so he basically just flies around and
that's his attack great ah
something's gone alright do you know
what it might be
yes game bugs have taken over they're
causing these glitches
do we have to tell this to every person
we meet and explain to them one by one
game books glitch is wonderful i shall
be sure to study them in my laboratory
i think this guy has some glitches of
his own if you know what i mean
nice roast wario
okay
well
[Music]
crangor and
i forgot how to play nineveh so let's do
anything
let's begin let's begin
in some way they're all the same
dr cragger's top secret factory
what is he doing in there
flat a boat test
oh
groovy oh cute what a nice maid you have
work
is this supposed to be a concert
[Music]
oh they don't like it when he performs
again oh
it's a party popper pooper pow popper
pooper potty pooper popper pooper
which one is it
okay
skate
escape
thank you cronie for saving my ass
of course
cover up
uh
[Music]
they're touching one another so it's all
good light
light
let it be light pose
[Music]
now please tell me your password
transport i got the signal i need the
password
[Music]
[Applause]
excellent
[Music]
unconsciously i didn't even know what i
was doing
reaction
i liked it
okay
oh my god
[Applause]
[Music]
that would have pierced me and that is a
stressful game indeed one clear path
[\h__\h]
[Music]
dodge
already oh my god okay we gotta do this
we got two lives left
can we first try this one too
crab
[Music]
okay is that sushi okay
assemble assemble
there we go oh
we're making sushi
i don't really like sushi that much but
i'm not the one eating it so it's all
good what about you guys you like sushi
that's a sponge
that looks yummy i could eat that
because that's not fish that was just
egg i think
uh
what you want bone sushi are you sure
no i like sushi
so she's good
i mean
i don't like seafood well same here
[Music]
[Applause]
are you proud of me
you see i am a genius
now the crainer join the crew
5 000. can we get over 9 000 just like
in the title
yes we can i believe in us
very proud of you thank you
okay
next up what what is that is that
just a minecart that we can get as a
member of our team let's play
always proud of potential thank you
it's a minecart
a minecart that's more like it
okay
we can cover a lot of groundedness
what do you mean are we going further
away
oh there was someone in there are you
the new friend we get
it's a robot
the acoustics in there are perfect for
color okay
mike
invented by dr craig or this kind of
looking rabbit robot has a great love of
singing
he does not have great skills at singing
well that's an unfortunate combination
of skill sets you got there mike
mike shoots notes upwards from his mouth
it's kind of cute that's all you can do
only upwards
and then fly around i guess
i get it
okay
[Music]
there you are i'm not letting you out of
my sight again you're coming with us i'm
fine
fine if i
must too bad there goes my solo career
oh [\h__\h] the voice sounds crazy with that
mike i guess you're in the team
and
what did cry girl do again
he just flies around right okay here
dream team let's go
here's bleed pain
yo welcome
let's begin we're on the lane
i remember this one yeah give me games
i'm familiar with please
uh okay
[Music]
that was so oh i didn't know he could
also go in the middle all right until
now he always went right
[Music]
was there a dog opening the door
i
[Music]
speaking of heights my high speed
monitor arrived today
i'm excited to use my heart rate monitor
sometimes it went on
wait
no oh
that's not enough
[Music]
how do i launch him what
i need to shoot the cannonball freaking
harvested there you go i did this style
we got one life left oh god i feel the
stress
well i mean come on
[Music]
that's manageable
vacuum cleaner got nothing on me
[Music]
maybe i should put on a mask today
before sleeping i haven't done one in a
while
this music just i don't know when you
hear that music you just know that all
is well and it's peaceful and life might
be worth living
it's probably unhappy about it reactions
he was happy about it
[Music]
what do you mean what there was nothing
to
[Music]
finally something
true
[Music]
is this game getting more difficult
okay stay here stay filled thanks that
was an easy one thank you
protect
check protect
i apologize deeply
[Music]
i think he went here
what just came out of that toothpaste
yeah okay okay
okay don't die this time kiana
don't die
steal back sail back give me crap yay
[Music]
tiny
okay one more one this time
okay
walk in the park
oh my god
i was
he shoots upwards but even though i was
right next to him it worked anyway thank
god
that was so close
my normal toothpaste again maybe i had
something in my eyes previously and i
just missed looks
bye-bye see you later
accelerating okay focus focus focus how
many
uh one two three four five
five
five five one five five yes
[Music]
toad is such a cutie pie
okay okay
i turned it down but it worked anyway
okay
[Music]
reaction he liked it
create shape
uh
this and
yes
now i'm nailing it guys
we're getting better we're getting
better finally finally
this is my turn
stick together
wait wait wait wait wait wait
okay well one life is okay who knows we
can give away one life
activated
[Music]
no i cannot take my time wait a second
oh god this uh
this shows me that the long years of no
practice of these games
did not pay off
uh
okay but we do have a lot of time 300
seconds or so
[Music]
just let me know the ball stage again
please we'll continue looking into the
boss stage we will also start over
if start overdose start over from the
boss stage or from before
i don't know why
go continue okay we got we got the money
for it
[Music]
i
again my long years of no practice
[Music]
and what couldn't say i wasn't gonna say
paid off though i was gonna say did not
are not paying off that's exactly what's
happening though so i'm right i'm not
jinxing i say i'm saying exactly what's
what's the mat what's right
oh my god okay wait
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's an easy mouth no way i don't
believe it
there's no easy mode to this game
[Music]
those right
but this makes me kind of want to play a
mario game
this game is good at like
like advertising other nintendo games
like i'm actually
interested
[Music]
in
oh they only come down when you're close
to them huh
okay
oh okay
oh daddy faded
[Music]
that was a
tough
minecarts we have arrived
so
good we survived
[Music]
mario world is free with switch online
oh
this game was really expensive though by
the way
well i'm not sure yet if it's 100 worth
it we'll find out cute girls cat and
anna
cute
how much was it either 49 year old or 59
year old
hey we found you
what's with all the bouncing you look
like a couple of tiny kangaroos
they're like they're like fleas
we can't help it our likes won't stop
jumping
it's probably just our super awesome
ninja powers
oh cat and anna together is katana
oh
smut
i didn't realize without the chat
i didn't realize
[Music]
funny these kindergarteners are not only
twins they're ninjas till
cat is a tiny bit older than anna
obviously obviously how's it obvious
okay so that's similar to another
character that we had before
boing boing
okay
[Music]
she's cute
listen
it's enough something's something really
weird jumped into a level
you can help us take it down if you're
not too scared
i'm not scared i'm not i'm not scared at
all no no no no no
who should we go with
we haven't done wario in a while we can
do four characters now uh-huh
um
let's do krieger and
i don't know we haven't we should maybe
switch it up a little bit that's the
cricket
i haven't used them yet so ready okay
let's see what happens with this team
[Music]
oh no
puppetry pop a train evil ninja
this looks like this one game that you
can play with your friends
what does that look like to you guys
this thing is there
it reminds me of something
hell yeah
i love nap time now prom is my favorite
time
[Music]
hawaii
they would be so popular
nice
nice nice
okay let's see what we got
shoot how does how does wario work like
again oh he just flies around and then
he sideways attacks okay
and this dude he just flies around the
feet
so cute i know how to feed boobs
[Music]
yes how could i miss so often
what
i was shooting so much
we're off to a good start guys cover
cover is that a cat's toilet
oh cover the poop oh um next time maybe
stop shopping
[Music]
cute
stop the cat is supposed to do that
though how do i stop him
oh i stopped him but i don't know hounds
down the door in my drink
these games are up silly
so adorable
what is going on clear skies clear skies
[Music]
oh this is so nice i'm so happy but i
only got one life left we're probably
gonna fail
roll up what do you mean roll up roll up
the
okay i did it
[Music]
why does it have a human face
what's happening what are we doing
remember i i can't remember i i don't
know
what
what am i remembering
crocodiles zebras
like
two zebras one lion
i think it was like maybe five
crocodiles is the number important
do we get another one question two okay
how many are there
who wasn't there ah the flamingo the
flamingo the flamingo easy
shoot me another one is this the last
one
who was there most of
crevices
i first tried it the whole thing
the mini game
boss stage oh
finally a victory for me this game is a
fever dream i agree
[Laughter]
i mean just look at this
game
cracking me up
finally finally a feeling of
victory we did it mission complete
cats
who's next
which weird ass character ah that one i
know that one from the demo i didn't
play the demo but i watched someone play
the demo
i i think oh wait maybe i don't
i mean i've seen them before at least i
think
and then we can go get this weirdo
and this cutie
ashley i'm coming for you
ashley
kawaii
once with his place it's so dark and
boring
it looks rather spooky
dr craiger is afraid of the dark
i am not my superior intellect is
incapable of such an irrational fear
hello
hell is anyone there
good grief
your superior intellect is a scaredy cat
oh my god
[Applause]
whether he's hitting the dance floor or
the gym this sports loving disco king
has all the right moves
his mustache looks funny
his nose is so red and he's got a funky
afro
all right friend
let's hit the disco
okay interesting
that seems rather
oh easy very easy i like that i might
use him a lot
oh i can't even go down okay
oh my dance floor
[Music]
listen up we can fix it but we got to
take out those rocking game bugs
all right all right game bugs don't
stand a chance against my death moves
spooky groovy
hmm
[Music]
let's dance
flapping my arms i began to pluck look
at me i'm the disco duck did you just
come up with that that's genius
who is she
[Music]
oh he lives here too
cricket
wow
that little girl goes to jail oh yeah
oh my god
[Music]
oh
nice
oh yeah oh yeah nice finishing move
yeah they did it much better indeed
i love that music
nice fail inflate
[Music]
go
oh i'm so sorry
we can do it over
[Music]
i didn't know what i was doing but
accidentally i did the right thing
oh that's water polo cool
[Music]
oh i just have to keep it up at the end
right oh no did i fail
yes well deserved i i deserve that
high high high let's go again hi hi hi
honey
[Music]
in reality i just
wanted to listen to this music a bit
more
[Music]
yeah
go go go go go go go go go go go go
[Music]
how does he work again
i guess you can either move the target
or destroy the
block underneath huh
uh what
oh
you're welcome i guess okay
you're not gonna win this game
[Music]
keep it up oh god okay no problem with
this character
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is a tough game man in flight
there we go
[Music]
keep it inflated go go
in the basket in the basket
[Music]
game honestly
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
i didn't let him rest
he seemed fine
[Laughter]
good that it wasn't less than free
because in the beginning i was just
smashing buttons
[Music]
okay come on
finally finally
[Music]
okay we have the
18 volt 18 volts
[Music]
this game is the end of me clear
oh my god i can't i can't
[Music]
don't use those don't use the boomerang
okay
um
[Music]
too bad
i'll just
i just continue
i know i'm broken
i feel defeated
change crew yeah maybe my crew is really
bad
who i just wanted to not make it too
easy for myself but keep like by always
using the same characters you know
because that's boring right
i don't really like mona anymore
[Music]
oh yeah i'll go with those
avoid nine vault and cat
oh okay okay
wait are we starting over oh god
pink one's not constantly moving yeah
oh
finally
[Music]
okay this one's not moving at all so
wait could this be the way to go
could this be it a one two three four
okay okay oh my god
[Music]
in the basket uh
oh wait
[Music]
okay it was a good try
i haven't played golf in like a million
years and that was even the one that i
played was mini golf so
[Music]
uh
i saw the whole picture you gotta look
at the big picture guys train okay so
this time i let him rest
as well
get to the green
oh god go go oh thank god
[Music]
they really like the golfing games don't
they
what
suddenly speed
how come i didn't do it before oh
my stage
we have arrived kfb
[Music]
more than one rep okay
oh i love that like climbing walls
what
[Music]
oh this might be tough
oh i can redo still okay
okay
uh i hope this is not too
long
oh they wear off oh no
oh
my god
go buddy you can do it
no no no no
i'm
go go
[Music]
oh
i loved doing that when i was younger
that was fun
when i was younger not not necessarily
in this game just now
wow
all right we did it we cleared the stage
thank you kfc
for your mental support
uh-uh that was groupie
jimmy t joined the crew
oh
we definitely stretched his body yeah
thousand coins
okay we have i i personally wanted to
the game portion for today to be two
hours so we have 20 more minutes left
and i wonder
if we can get over 9 000
uh
but we're at 7 900 considering the next
level will give me a thousand
we will be so close i need to clear two
levels i think
i say the corruption is particularly
pervasive here
i want to get over 9000 points
you guys like her don't you
i see it in your comments it's so
obvious
would you like more hair or me
ashley i should have known
joy and here i was finally having some
fun
oh she's not amused her what the hell
max ben everyone who said her
use
she is very cute
ashley dislikes
i like how the dislikes come first
cute stuff expressing emotions
unnecessary chit chat
guys are you sure like i know she's cute
and all and it's very charming but if
you were in a situation where you would
actually have to talk to her she would
be a very difficult girl to deal with
you would all have issues making her
like you
casting spells food and her pal rather
her likes
she doesn't even like talking
actually has spells in whichever
direction she's facing okay
come on
[Music]
[Applause]
oh that was a bit difficult good
okay
she's she's much like someone i know or
really
it's time to stomp some game bugs and
you you're gonna help us
why should i
because i said so and because bye fine
we don't need you anyway
please of course you do
i didn't know ariel we'll send that in
all right
volts jimmy t
and
cry girl let's try it let's give it a
try let's begin
what exploding banana
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
is that her friend she's not amused
oh depresso espresso
[Music]
me when i look at kfp
okay
[Music]
taco
i love donuts
don't let shinobu see those donuts
though aj oh dear donuts everywhere food
everywhere
nuts
[Music]
[Applause]
give me all the chords
[Music]
leave the candy
keep that tongue inside your mouth boy
cover it
up
adjust we're gonna fail one time but
that's okay just to oh
[Music]
i'm sorry or something like that
i don't understand
start over go tangerines oh you have
tangerines i bought a
couple of tangerines
a whole bag of them
oranges tangerines
makes our hands happy
where's the butter in the sauce can
someone give me some butter and salt
i mean salt i kind of have enough right
now maybe
oh god
keep it up
[Music]
before it was omorai
rice tea
now i understand
cherries
[Music]
tangerines
success
banana
come down
[Music]
that looks yummy nice too faster
it's okay
[Music]
whose birthday is it today it's only
someone's birthday
at kfp
whose birthday is it today
[Music]
uh
i think wait how do i
how would i shoot it i wanted to get the
very right one but it was kind of on the
way the others
yeah
bye stage
it's not your birthday at least you're
honest eh what what am i doing i can't
move juice
yes
oh wait oh god we gotta get it in the
middle [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
are we trying to get it in the middle
grab it
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
it's not that difficult come on kiara
[Music]
juice
okay
oh wait do i have to wait until it goes
down
no just have to
go here right
[Music]
now it's not filling up at all ah i'm
gonna have to destroy it afterwards
[Music]
oh
i finally understand the game
okay next next next oh
i got a bit too early
okay
[Music]
excellent divine yummy cream juice
i was stressed out there that was
definitely stress level over 9000 there
i felt it i felt it
oh my god
[Music]
whatever
we're hundreds 100 points away from
where i want to get so one more level
one more level guys and then
it's over for today
short stream today as i promised wait
where are we going
i have to do this one
okay okay okay
what is that alien
what is that
oh that's that way it sounds
eh
over 9 000 points and then it's over for
today yes yes
oh i'm
scared it really
oh no
he's an enemy i thought he was a friend
ah you name compoop what
what are you doing
oh no he is a friend this alien insists
he'll invade earth one day he's lived
here long enough to know a lot about our
culture
sucks up the things below him by
activating his beam
i've seen how he works before in the
demo
oh beam beam up oh those monsters ah
aha
oh everything oh
move oh wow
so carelessly
he's so strong
alien or he just has a strong ufo
my beam of tractoring it does not work
on this quincy yuck
listen
just stop on go away until we take out
those mean old games
i see
i think then ambulance will dispose of
these bugs with style oh
alien of culture okay let's do ashley
cause we all love ashley
and hmm
wario
18 volts
this is my team of choice hopefully i
will not regret my choices
part time ufo yeah that was a fun game
around the world with orbulans
tourist time my travel show begins oh
all right
[Music]
well this makes up for the lack of
traveling in this
year oh or he steals everything
oh wait that's what you meant with you
know a lot about our culture but you're
stealing the culture
that's not good
no
mario's
well that's not good no
wait wait wait wait wait
you can't do that's not souvenirs you're
gonna pay for souvenirs
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with him
i'm the quizzer i don't want him in my
team
stealing is not good
where to oh did i do it right oh
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
goes to the circus
build it
wait what's the other way around anyway
i thought i was going with common sense
here i guess not
prune what what does that mean
oh i think it's right oh my god
peanuts peanuts oh we're doing well so
far we're doing well extinguish uh-huh
oh oh wait oh my i got a bird where am i
where am i
actually i killed her
congratulations on your weddings what
what what
i don't understand what what what what
what 99. push it out
[Music]
well if something's ever stuck in your
trumpet let me know i'll help you
i'll come to help you
[Music]
um
all right
one more try okay one fails okay match
what do you mean match
what
no you cut up
build it
[Music]
jump through
forever
[Music]
are so adorable
we're alien now
yeah baby rock and roll
[Music]
i don't understand what am i matching oh
oh that one behind it
oh thank god i did it
you gotta be careful dory bear should
not stop it take a peek
okay
[Music]
um okay
balance i mean that's one way to do it
one way to extinguish it and that was a
nice reaction
[Music]
it's already fast enough watch what
fine oh he's here
okay okay yo yo
[Music]
where are we going
[Applause]
in any case just get moving
what
what what what
i was just supposed to get one oh damn
it
last stage we got two lives
what are you doing
oh you're letting the boat through how
nice of you good girl smart bub
let it pass let it fast okay i'm going
to try
wait i forgot how to do it yes
[Music]
wait
wait wait wait wait no wait up quick
[Music]
let it um wait i'm not quite sure
just like that
why was that so hard
i did the same thing thank you
[Music]
oh my god
oh oh fun what what what comes
[Music]
the end there come
i thought they were going to crash into
one another so i wanted to pick one up
oh man
i don't know i wanted to pick one up but
it picked up the the the
the bridge i misunderstood okay
can't you guys you must go
go guys
let it pass
you can see why i would think that right
thank you
all right this part i understand
understandable right it was an accident
i mean that doesn't make it okay but
it's understandable so bus comes now
and then there's another bus so i just
keep it down
okay
and and now
okay okay
stay there
easy
i mean if you think about it this is one
of the easiest boss levels
what
[Music]
what what what what
killing the bird is okay
i killed a lot of birds no i'm not i
don't know what i'm talking about
wait until the last moment well i'm
stressed out okay
i was too early
oh my god
it was not about getting the the boat
inside this thing here right that that
thing here that's not it right
[Music]
okay
very fast boat
go faster
no one has time for that [\h__\h]
oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god
what comes first though car or boat
boat coming yeah
okay no no car now
come
pass on this in london
gives me london vibes
did i do it
last one
well we didn't even have such a
stressful situation like we had before
that was
that that one moment where two cars and
one boat came at the same time what the
hell man
now it wasn't that difficult
the game took mercy on me
yeah way easier this time yeah
come
that on a fun boss game though i don't
dislike it
first i conquered the game box can i
conquer the world
[Music]
everyone join the crew welcome we have
so many now and we are
over 9 000
[Music]
i have reached my
goal for today
i
[Music]
don't count the time that i had in a
loading screen
then we really did it in two hours
we did
yeah thank you for watching i think i'll
uh read super chats
uh
just quickly i don't think there's much
so
you'll you'll get rid of me soon enough
don't worry just maybe stay another hour
just not that long would you would you
please stay with me
to hang out a little bit more with me
are you with me
are you with me or what you can finish
the game eh
what do you mean
the next stage
is the next one the last one
where
you mean i am about to finish the story
is that what you're saying
five more stages that's a bit too
too much maybe
there's a whole other island ah okay
okay okay okay
no no then i will uh just end it here
and read super chats i think
[Music]
wait one second i'm refreshing the page
uh the streaming page because
something's weird it's like
broken
that other island is a bonus
oh
well then i mean we still have enough
content for another stream of this game
then at some point someday some points
will we can do more of this then
and it's good to leave some over unless
it's like too little but it sounds like
there is enough content
for doing another stream
okay i refreshed why was that so
slow
weird
short streams can be nice and sweet just
like you kiada ah
by the way we have a members only stream
tomorrow
i think yeah tomorrow i'm doing the
practice sessions and um
practice sessions with members
not review members but with whole
english members
and i'm doing the members only
a manga stream yeah
you sound like good at and you have
something in your ears because i think
our voices are
very very different
unfortunately i wish i had a cute voice
like gouda
lots of the monks yeah for me tomorrow
it will it will be among us all day
all day
although i don't really think we'll be
playing the game tomorrow it's really
just um about
uh getting the
proximity voice mod to work for everyone
the better crew link voice mod
thank you guys
well well then let's read some super
chats
and we're moving over to
the office
where am i
here we are wait um let me close the
game this saves right i don't have to do
anything
i just
i can just get out of here right okay
okay wait i'm so big
i'm big also i'm cats today i felt like
being a cat today
it's been a while since i turned myself
into a kitty cat
been quite some time
okay
well i just want to stay on top of my
super chats because we haven't stayed on
top of them for a while recently
so i'm gonna
read them properly
and
uh what was i about to do
i don't know what i was about to do
ah music music music
i was on audio stack before the stream
so i have new music for you
pgm
i think i wanted to go with
actually i have five different songs
let's go with this one first
do
[Music]
this is so comfy right
yeah yeah
i'm i'm curious though it's like it's
like two different tracks that are very
very similar to one another they just
have a slight difference
and both of them are three minutes long
so this will play for a while and then a
very similar one will play and i'm
curious as to how it will connect we'll
see
definitely a vibe yeah feels like being
at my back porch watching the sunset oh
that sounds amazing
it was titled something like a music
that would play at a cafe
it gives you cafe vibes yeah
thanks for the stream heading off to
sleep now good night thank you for
coming
see you tomorrow maybe since you're a
member
[Music]
kiara can i be a manager at cafe no you
cannot
i am the manager
island vacation music type of thing yeah
also also that i agree
wait what the [\h__\h]
wait what
but i just opened my my page my my super
chat page it says
in german though it says your your
contents have been removed
because they are against our community
guidelines
[Music]
since this is your first
thingy this is just a warning has i have
i finally been struck by dmca
but do it wait that's not community
guidelines right is that
it
why why what check the contents
[Music]
uh minecraft
what what what what's the problem with
my
that's a
that's a really old stream i think
[Music]
what's the problem with that minecraft
stream
did someone just report this and
this is what happens
[Music]
where's the explanation of what i did
wrong is there a time stamp no no time
stamp
[Music]
which one
uh the one from 23rd july of phoenix
needs to fly is the title
what did i do
in that stream i
in that stream i i did uh
i got the elijah on that stream
what did i do
[Music]
oh if i do if i if i do something bad
again next time there's some there's
some
like i can't upload videos and stuff
what the [\h__\h]
wait but if i click if i click that link
like
the guideline link it says
dangerous content
or damaging content but that's all it
says it doesn't like actually say what
exactly and what part of the video was
bad is this is this how youtube operates
they
i guess it is
i guess it is how youtube operates they
don't tell you what the problem is they
just warn you when at some point they
delete your channel
they don't even tell you what the
problem is
what
it's the first time i've seen this
before
wait
what on earth
i got a sentence to genma
uh
it's german though
[Music]
but but is this like any
anyone can basically report a video or
stream and and youtube will immediately
send out a warning like this
does it not get checked by youtube
i think it doesn't get checked does it
no no
ah if it gets like reported by like a
lot of people
um
yeah it's german but uh
please check
an old minecraft stream got flags is
that the right word this is in german i
don't know how to describe it
one more debut stream let's go
no not yet they let me off
easily this time apparently thank you
for letting me off easily
got flagged for some reason
but
there should have been nothing wrong
with it
please refute
the end
[Music]
i think genma is sleeping though
yeah it's a strike
but but it's not because it's the first
one exactly
it's supposed to be a strike but since
it's the first strike this is not doing
having any effect on my
account wow
okay youtube
[Laughter]
man
oh man
oh hey tick tock gaming is subscribe to
my channel
what is this
funny
okay i was on my youtube dashboard
okay now can we go to my
super chats
yeah okay okay okay
i didn't
wait i totally didn't
repeat the song damn it no i didn't find
out how it
how it uh
looks
or did it actually loop was it already
six minutes
oh
okay anyway um
all is good for now
no need to be worried
supposedly everything is fine
hope you have a wonderful day thank you
gonna twitch debbie with ammo if you get
banned again
[Laughter]
no no no even if that happens we'll do a
quick revival easily simply it's as
simple as that
you can't take a phoenix down for too
long
that one time that i that my channel was
deleted and swiped off of the earth
that literally
took like only three or four hours for
it to be fixed again so
no problem i think
no problem
[Music]
okay let's read the super chats now
and
from this stream only yay
[Music]
sexiest video game characters
top five list well one of them would
definitely definitely be kisara and to
be
and
besides that my my head is empty right
now
so it's hard to say
[Music]
it'll guard i don't know she's beautiful
not really
i wouldn't put her in the top top five
sexy list
riza li leela yeah yeah what's her name
leela
that
oh my god that girl from from the riser
game
lila lila might actually be uh sexier
than ryzen
oh hell yeah she had those
insane thighs insane hips
[Music]
and mr cat's big standard for the pinky
hello you fabulous phoenix in the pre-en
days my favorite streams to watch were
super collabs like this full ian one
you've put together
you mean
in whole life or just outside the whole
life completely
you're taking the effort to do this is
beyond appreciated you're a gift to the
community birdie you know what you know
that
thank you
[Music]
now that the sappy message is done in
time for the silly one after seeing your
recent panic attacks in minecraft i've
taken the liberty
oh wait the lawyer casbix
of renegotiating the payment for your
participation in the peer pressured
outlast stream
it's definitely kind of a peer pressure
situation yes in addition to the
samitori karaoke which is a gift for you
both
i've also added the terms that that she
must promote your upcoming song shower
you with tate flirts and finally build
the big foot in minecraft do you accept
the terms my client what do you want
more for your asylum visit
um
[Music]
uh
i don't i don't want to like
force her to promote my song so i will
uh
not do that not have her do that
but
maybe she can
build the bigfoot yeah
or or we'll think of something else
because you're right you're right the
kinda okay is like a fun thing that no
one
no one suffers while doing that
everyone is just happy with that
while for outlast i'm definitely the one
suffering and being tortured
so
in some way i will find
some fair solution maybe
ours is already next week oh my god
sasuka tanjo's kindness
i'm kind
slowpoke
[Music]
kiana you crazy mvp you really outdate
yourself live translating today
every rip remix
i thought you were going to talk about
holotalk
but you're talking about that
oh my
[Music]
you are so far behind my friend
oh wow
every rfp remix was such a pop do you
guys remember that
it was fun seeing you vibe of kelly your
japanese fluency is a gift that can take
you far i believe in you
holy and really wouldn't be the same
without you so
slowpoke is so wholesome
slowpoke is like
perfect so wholesome and at the same
time funny and yeah makes me laugh every
time
i love snowfall
[Music]
until now until i found slowpoke in my
super chats i've never really
liked slowpoke as a pokemon
but i think now
thanks to these super chats
he might be one of my favorite uh
pokemons
mvp
i love you slow folk
let's see when you will be finally able
to react to this message maybe uh in one
year
the slowpoke have an exact one-year
delay
perhaps
was that stream one year ago
i wonder
is that one year ago or like more
more or less now
something like that
well then i guess in one year slowpoke
will be very happy to hear that message
from me
[Music]
thank you
i'm already thinking we gotta get a mona
helmet on your head for the next time
you play just like with the mario kart
heads ah
oh yeah yeah or like a i don't know a
wario um mustache and nose
that would be a good idea too maybe
[Music]
i'm not gonna play it again anytime soon
i wanna space it out so for
maybe when i have a weak ram like i
don't know what the hell to play
i'll squeeze another episode of wario
wearing
but when that time comes either if
someone puts something in the cars and
kiars now
then i'll use that or i'll make it
myself
if i don't forget it
p gate might have made something worry
or chiana related
ah
i feel like
somewhere in my brain
i know what you're talking about but i'm
trying to push it out of my memories i
think
i feel like there was something very
cursed there yes yes
oh oh no it's new
it's new it's not old
oh god
what was i remembering then oh god okay
i opened twitter and the first thing i
see is
[Music]
that
um
but then my heart
gets
uh
healed
by what thakuma posted
but but how do i
knock on my account download chips
unless i go somewhere
download twitter
those are so cute
wait one second
[Music]
[Laughter]
sending me a link
okay gotta be quick
be fast who's gonna be faster i can i
can i can
i can probably outspeed you back along
download there you go i already i
already got it i already got something
same video
here
yeah
wait wait wait there's a piece of me
don't leave uh properties
hi
you're so cute
[Music]
there's a chicken version too
that's so good
and i want to download the chicken
version too
kfb employee version
[Music]
thank you dr mom
and thank you p gate
[Music]
that's you guys
maybe i can do it maybe i can put it
behind the chat
[Music]
one second let me try
i mean the chat
that night is
it's so very readable i would say
it's so cute
[Music]
you know what would be cute
if if uh
takuma can you maybe try something for
me
the desks that they're like punching
slapping flapping can you make that desk
uh some kind of green screen
so i can put them
i don't know my head can you can you
give me the chicken
animation but maybe maybe instead of
having it um tilted you know what maybe
have it straight
so
it's not like angled just straight ahead
just a table the table should just be a
straight line
and then and then green screen and then
i'll put it on my head
and then it will be constantly slapping
my head
[Laughter]
i wanna see that
bunk bunk me forever
oh i guess i could i could yeah but
turning it around will like i can in obs
i can only turn it like
um
like
uh how many degrees is that
[Music]
i can only turn it like
uh
90 degrees or 180 degrees
i can't turn it that
um
[Music]
oh she said okay
you don't you don't have to do it right
away though don't don't worry
okay back to superchat
oh my
where was i
[Music]
ah here
it is not the time but i wanted to know
if you and perhaps every halloween are
planning to have planning on have a
phoenix form skeleton maury darkina ah
ah
well no not not that i know of no
would be nice and cool in the future
yeah yeah
right so freedom zephyr kitten
uncle red thunderstorm maxi king 92
oh that's a snack
you are a snack
duck
nagoyan
daniel daniel mason dankeshen finally
been able to catch a stream with being
so busy joined the membership as well
after all this time so i am super
excited about being part of the glorious
kfb viva la chiara hashtag we are not a
cult oh it sounds like the way you talk
it sounds like you've been around here
for the longest time
as if you've been a man member forever
welcome
[Applause]
thank you kiana what's your favorite
holiday
good question did i never answer that
because uh that's a hotel question
my favorite holiday
i guess it's just christmas
cause stuff like halloween you kind of
grow out of it
easter i was
i never
celebrated easter that much
although it's a cute holiday
but christmas comes with so many nice
things like the whole
atmosphere
and the christmas markets
the hot chocolate and stuff like that
and then the presents and the
decorations decorating the trees
everyone is supposedly in a happy mood
it's wholesome
yeah the christmas music it's just a big
big
festival
and i know it's like
kind of like a commercial thing
and that's why a lot of people don't
like it like my mom doesn't really like
it because of that i think
but i mean
yeah even if it if the reason why it
became so big is for commercial reasons
it's still to have it's so nice to have
like one kind of
um festive season in the year that
makes people come together so whatever
that's that's my
my
opinion
without christmas like
it would be so
boring
we need stuff like that in our lives i
think
something to look forward to
and since at the end of the
day and at the end of the year it's um
like
like after after like the summer time
it's like oh christmas is soon yeah yeah
definitely something to look forward to
but now that i think of it um new year's
is
probably also
[Music]
my favorite together with christmas
but
depending on
whether i spend new year's in my country
or in japan
it's very very different
and i think i would um
enjoy it more in my own country actually
because of the fireworks and
it's just a much much bigger event
somehow in my country than it is in
japan
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
the whole counting down outside lots of
people are inside somewhere it doesn't
matter but i remember when i was younger
i mean i have i have a lot of new year's
memories
some scary ones some good ones
but i remember when i was much much
younger
um we were
like before phones and all that were
like
every everything everyone was looking at
when people were still socializing
when i was very young and when winter
actually had snow in december
um
i remember with my family being up on
the mountain
on the snowy mountain i mean not like a
huge mountain just like a
small mountain
and on the edge of it
we were like sitting there in the snow
looking at the fireworks and
just waiting
waiting and waiting it was super super
cold but
it was a beautiful view and
yeah
it just was kind of special
being up there
and then there were times where
i looked
um at the fireworks
um
on like a on the bridge um
over a river although that one was
actually
in theory that was a nice
new year's but actually i was so young
there
and it was actually really dangerous i
don't remember much of it but i think
there was like
it was really dangerous because they
were like broken there was broken glass
everywhere
and um
i think
i got lost a little bit
and i was personally scared
to death
i think i remember being super super
scared because like everyone was drunk i
was so small there was there was a
broken glass on the ground everywhere
and people were like so scary
yeah it was so loud and
in fear that would have been really nice
because the location was really pretty
and yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah many many different
um
new years
and and one of the
most recent most special ones i think i
told you guys about it before
but um it was
the new years before i went to japan
um so that must have been 2019 to
20.
i think yeah
on the rooftop yeah of
like one of the highest buildings
in my city
uh
where we kind of
secretly
snuck up there
with rnt yeah
i don't know if i actually told you that
we weren't really allowed to be up there
but
in theory we were not allowed to be up
there did i mention that did i mention
that part
did i say that
did
it yeah oopsie
but it was so nice it was so [\h__\h]
windy up there it was so dangerous as
well so we stayed like
in the middle of the roof trying to not
um
get blown off of the ribs because there
was no fence up there
but there was no one else there only me
and rnt
[Music]
only us too and it was freaking cold and
windy
but we saw the
um the fireworks
all around us like when we look in the
front fireworks we look to the right
fireworks we look to the left fireworks
behind us 5x
365 okay now 360. 180.
everywhere
yeah that was probably why i was not
allowed to be up there because there was
no fence yeah that makes a lot of
sense no but but it was it was really
special
i wonder how i will spend new year's
this year
last year i was in japan so i couldn't
spend it with my friends i spent it
while i was streaming
so this year i will either again be
streaming
or
i'll be spending the time with my bff
[Music]
or with my family i'm not sure
my family is coming over for christmas
so
new year's eve is probably gonna be
more like a
uh friend thing maybe
we'll see
[Music]
but i will definitely do one stream at
least on that day even if it's not a
countdown stream
it might be a countdown stream just for
a different time zone
not my own time zone
oh yeah i want to be with my cats when
it happens actually i guess oh no
although i guess my my place is uh has
pretty thick walls so
they would probably be fine
and and and chonky's is probably just
gonna hide in my closet
if she gets scared so
i can always bring them um hell though
i'm not gonna bring my cats outside to
watch the fireworks
they're gonna get a heart attack
[Music]
nate duncation
i love this game to death i'd also love
to see you go for the high score
missions after completing the main game
if you enjoy it it gets pretty fast
nate
by looking at my gameplay do you really
think that i am suited for something
like that
um you even have a wario profile picture
so i see you are a big fan
i'm sorry i did so badly at the game
i hope it was still enjoyable for you
um
[Music]
cheryl
the red super chat you love them
actually thank you
thanks mate
kfb members yesterday
i asked kiana about the rumor i heard
rest assured the playroom does not exist
it doesn't have many things many things
that will
maim and kill you it doesn't have the
echoing gleeful love of tension mixed in
with the screams of mercy that fill the
air
so it doesn't he says clearly it does
not
even though he describes it so detailed
okay tanjo i said it can i leave now
it's scary here i almost lost my head to
a sword-wielding ape
as she already bit off three of my
fingers but i'm not you can't blame me
for what what am i doing to you
the giraffes are breathing fire and a
guy tried to kill me with an exploding
banana
oh [\h__\h] was that worms
please let me leave i'm sorry
[Music]
okay
you have
um i guess
redeemed yourself i guess
and i mean it's too red super chat so
you bought
the
tickets to go outside i guess
don't tell anyone that that's even
possible
[Music]
so now you're gonna be a good chicken
right a good chicken
[Music]
a chicken that follows rules and
guidelines
and does not
uh spread any weird rumors
right
yes perps jl i know you can do it i
believe in you
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you so
much
very very very generous of you brandon
wilson pankish in motion gym transition
lord evil duncan gt
cotton
road trip function
thank you thank you very much
hope to see the stream come back for
part two i'm a warioware fan love seeing
you react to the game the panic is
exactly what i expected and it was a lot
of fun really
did you guys enjoy it i hope i hope it
was enjoyable because i didn't really
have time to talk or anything
eden
today i finally became a delicious
bucket yo eaton congrats
yeah
wow
whole year eden
thank you for being part of kfb you've
been providing me with so much cool
stuff
i'm really really grateful for it thank
you
i love using these things thank you
without your assets
my my office would not even exist
probably hmm
oh don't worry for the person who's
going to bed or wherever you're going
we're almost ending
thank you for your support elvis thank
you for the red super chat
[Music]
i appreciate it one more damn stream
let's go but hopefully not i mean
i mean i don't want it to happen for
like a strike or something
that's just uh
worrying me because
i want that stripe to be gone
because i'm a good
good good potential
for a moment i really thought it was
because of a dmca thing oh my god but
they have yet to
[Music]
bonk me for that
but i've been jinxing a lot of things
today so
yeah
i don't know if you're listening but it
was probably bots reporting huh
[Music]
it really doesn't interest me at the
moment so i'm gonna
um
help you out there by saying you can
probably stop super chatting me with
that right now
i don't want you to endlessly super chat
me about that
it's
not gonna happen anytime soon i think
um sorry
i i don't know it it doesn't appeal to
me right now
[Music]
uh black friction duncan tom g duncan
looking for the tab thank you for the
recipe and also thank you for these
memberships welcome welcome welcome for
renewing your membership and for joining
for the first time thank you
hope you enjoy your time here we have
two members only streams this this week
so and just a small tip for going to the
doctor and being super cute today game
was dope keep it up charming chicken
chimking
thank you yes i went to the doctor today
actually the doctor
was
uh he took
way more time this time for me than last
time
last time i felt like really stressed
out there like he wasn't really
listening i guess
um but maybe maybe because
he's taking me a bit more serious now
uh how did it go well i mean there's no
like clear results yet because
he looked at my blood results
and
most of the things that were read he was
like nah no need to worry about that no
need to worry about that he also said no
need to worry about the
cholesterol because he said i'm still
young
you hear that
i'm still young
no need to worry about that he said
[Laughter]
and
[Music]
most of the other things he also kind of
was like nah doesn't matter
one thing that he prescribed me
something for was the vitamins because
he said yeah that's important
my vitamins were pretty bad
um hi casper
and then there was one thing where he
got worried
i think i didn't even mention this one
on stream before because i didn't really
understand it
um
there's there was like one
thing that was red and
and positive
that
uh i have to go get more blood tested
for
um
because it it's like so broad and so
wide
ranged
that
there's absolutely no way to tell
like this
ah eh
uh it's um
a
romantic disease
thingy but there's like a million
rheumatic diseases
uh so we gotta
go get more blood
it i don't know he was like just we're
sending you somewhere else
to
check it out
and get more blood and test it but it
could take a long time because
it's uh a procedure a whole thing
but it makes sense kind of
um
[Music]
he said that he might think that that's
why everything hurts
uh
but yeah there's so many different types
[Music]
he just wants you plug
he's not the one receiving it
i i guess i will kind of explain it a
little bit but it depends really it
could be it could be something that
doesn't affect
my shoulder and my
my my spine pain at all
could be something else completely
[Music]
um
and also like he looked at the x-ray but
he was like oh that doesn't surprise me
at all he kind of like brushed that one
off
i mean my x-ray definitely was not
perfect
um i have
bad posture so he prescribed me uh
another physical therapy
session
[Music]
so i have to go to those again
and he said i have to do
like
these exercises
for the rest of my life in order to fix
it
like it can't really be fixed
i just have to do it every day
so i don't know if which one it is now
it could be that
but i don't know it feels
it feels like the pain
is too much
for
it to be just a posture that's that's my
guts that's what's my what my guts is
telling me
um
well yeah we will see i think there's no
need to wear it yet because even if it
were some kind of
romantic r-h-e-u-m-a-t-i-c
disease then it's i think easy to treat
he said something like that although i
could barely hear him because he spoke
so freaking silently
i didn't
this time he took himself one more time
but i didn't understand 50 of what he
said because he speaks so quietly
i told him so many times i don't
understand him
i was trying so hard to listen but he
was wearing a mask
and then in between us was like a a
panel a glass panel
and i told him so many times i can
barely hear him and then for a moment he
speaks up a tiny bit but it's still so
hard to hear
[Music]
so difficult
i think i caught the most important
parts maybe so he gave me
the the vitamin prescriptions and he
prescribed me a physical therapy and he
sent he's sending me to
more blood tests yeah but at the moment
no nothing clear
about that so
no need to
freak out about it
and
a lot of people have rheumatic rheumatic
roidmatic i don't know how to say it
diseases
and there's so many that all of them are
like
[Music]
well i'm not too worried about it
the good thing would be that it is that
and then i know how to treat it and then
i can finally feel better
yeah rheumatic
yeah yeah although autoimmune
a disease something like that
it's very common yeah yeah
so i would actually be happy if it was
that because i just want
to know what it is and then
be able to get medication or whatever
for it
[Music]
so it's better than being in the dark
because i've been in the dark for so
long
and i've just i'm just so sick of it
so anyway that's that's what came out of
that doctor visit i'm gonna try to
um
get the blood test
uh again soon
but i have to go to a different place
this time that's like specialized on
that stuff
oh youtube
on it
[Music]
okay we're almost ending anyway so thank
you looking for the top
for the right super chat i'm fine so far
and um
we're back okay okay i'm fine don't
worry about it
and
yeah
just leave it to me
i'll figure out how to take care
of all of that
[Music]
i know
wish you the best thank you
have you ever tried meditation well yeah
kind of recently i tried yoga and it
wasn't really my thing
i don't mind giving it another try but i
don't think it's my thing but i've i've
made a commitment
starting from today
i don't think i can really do it every
day as
as well as i know myself but i want to
at least try
to do daily stretches every day because
a lot of people told me that daily
stretches helped themselves so much
so like just 15 minute sessions at least
once per day but ideally after i wake up
and before i go to sleep
i already found a video that i want to
follow on youtube like a routine
and it's funny because
i looked at the routine and it's like a
15-minute version of what we did at that
hotel
like
all of those moves that she did in that
15-minute youtube routine
the dude
in the in the hotel no it was a lady
actually the dude did the yoga and the
lady did the mobility and stretch
session
she did i don't know maybe she got her
moves from that video or they're just
that coming
that everyone does these same moves when
they're stretching your body
it's a very
popular video on youtube has a has like
2.8 million views
so she might have gotten in from that
video and made a one-hour version out of
that
[Music]
yeah so i want to try to do this at
least once per day
[Music]
and
yeah
i'm really
bad at
um
keeping these kind of commitments
like daily commitments i'm really bad at
that but i'm gonna give it a try
yeah so after the stream before i go to
sleep i'm planning on doing this
[Music]
just 15 minutes it's not that much come
on kiara
come on
[Music]
yeah i'll try
but
don't press me on it guys if i get super
chats every day asking me if i did it or
not i'm going to ban you
don't you dare press me on it
please
okay
[Music]
maybe once per week
at the most
petrochem vanishing frozen chicken
dancing thank you for the pinkie and
your first super chat i love the way my
aussie pilots her model and comforts us
with her cute voice
[Music]
why are you frozen by the way should i
warm you up should i fry you get you all
cozy and warm
with some breading around you huh and
some spices
should i get you hot
make you into a hot fried chicken
it will feel much better than being
frozen
come on
wait did youtube buffer again
[Music]
it's good now okay
hey but did it buffer while i was
reading the super chat should i rate it
again no buffer for me okay okay
no thank you frozen
[Music]
thank you for your generous first super
chat um i'm glad i have your support
just let me know when you want to be
fried okay
frank screw dankest and cocoon
avenged me
and spiral dancing spicy spyro is
something i
i wouldn't mind playing that's a bit
more colorful and cute
optimus prime thank you
[Music]
caesar village
thank you
yeah i will try um yeah i'll definitely
miss
days here and there
but
i need to try
get like a daily routine going and once
i get used to it
youtube did it
again what the hell
well which part did you not hear
i read the last ones again afterwards
primetime niche tankish and caesar
village thank you and thank you i'll do
my best
tanaka dancing for
oh my god youtube
everything is fine here
only some people have problems
okay
thank you
for the pinky are you hearing this or is
it buffering for you
will you hear me better if i yell
can i get fruit to you if i yell hello
can you hear me
[Music]
hello
oh you know what i was wondering my my
effects are kind of different today i
think it's because uh smoothie stepped
on my go slr wait a second
oh yeah that's way different
yeah cause she steps on like it looks
alive
she changed the presets
that's why it was so weird today
it's buffering again
you're hearing me or not
i don't need i need tanaka to be able to
hear this because it's his super chat
144 p works it's fine at 2 40 40. i
missed it okay okay i'm proud of you for
taking self-care so seriously remember
you're an idol you have to set an exam a
good example for all your fans
but even without me setting a good
example you guys are
probably living a like a more healthy
life than i am most of the time
you guys are so good on your own
you guys are doing a great job it's more
like you guys are sending setting a good
example for me
you guys should show me videos of you
living in the gym
so that you can also prove me that
you're actually doing it
instead of only complaining to me that
i'm not doing it
but i'm not working out well show me if
you're working out go go go send me
those videos
you gotta wear like some kind of t-shirt
that says kfc or something so that i
know that it's really is one of you guys
don't want to show your face no problem
wear a mask or cut off the face
censor it somehow no that's not an
excuse
let's get basically
[Music]
come done
you're sending it really
[Laughter]
while youtube is buffering you guys show
me how you get buff
everyone's buffering
noise
black friction duncan
[Music]
oh my
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait i
didn't think he would be that fast
[Music]
i need to test this out immediately
oh my god
you made a new one
oh man
oh you're so cute
oh it doesn't even need to be green
screen you're a genius
oh my god wait a second does it need to
be looped
no
oh i suggest there you go
[Music]
here
[Laughter]
get up there
get back up there camping how dare you
you can also do this to my cats wait a
second
[Music]
soft movie movie soft blah blah blah
yep
[Laughter]
no
good i'm happy
i'm happy
frog rockiana one yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
i want to stick that to my body so that
it moves with me all the time but
unfortunately we can't do that
you're you're my hat now oh yeah
oh you're so cute thank you mom
[Music]
you're my head now
i'm very sad but my best friend spy or
will not give up go spyro go spyro i
believe in you
spyro has bigger chances i think yes
thank you for i think that was a red
super chat thank you
and now we're ending it i'm hungry i'm
gonna
go warm up some food now
i have um
pumpkin risotto
from the supermarket
and i have also chicken teriyaki from
the supermarket
but i'm not sure if it's good that's why
i bought the chicken risotto as a backup
because i was like that probably
is gonna be okay
it's not frozen food though it was just
in the fridge section
and i don't know i don't trust food
where like meat is involved and it's
like
um
like it's usually means that's in like
those kind of like finished
prepped meals
usually
doesn't
taste that good if you know what i mean
so am i here
[Music]
wow they really want me to end the
stream like first it was youtube
disconnecting and now it was obs but i
think i'm back
this time it was obs before it was
youtube okay i guess i'm leaving
on youtube
they don't want me to stream
i'm getting bullied by youtube today and
obs
they're trying to kick me out okay i'm
done chill
oh star match wait i almost was about to
leave thank you for the pinky writing a
super chat that successfully makes kayla
say i am a
now k of stuns she did not realize it so
i need to send a nervous superchat to
tell her what she said that songs what
i don't understand but in any case you
did not get me to say that
you failed
try again sometime
[Music]
i'm being sabotaged yeah
it buffered again
tell him thank you for the membership
okay i guess i'm leaving well thank you
for the pinky star match really thank
you but uh people want me out
[Music]
nanka
i'm youtube strong for this platform
maybe it's because of all the bunking
happening here here and here and here
we're hitting the desk so hard that it's
reaching the youtube service
oh my god
all right then
goodbye everyone
see you in the members only stream
tomorrow or i guess other than that if
you're not a member i guess the next one
is whole talk
which i finished uh getting the
questions together today
yeah yeah yeah across the empire is
coming to hello talk so look forward to
that
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
[Music]
did i keep my word about the short
stream i think i did three hours is
short
no complaints today
[Music]
do
i