[Music]
okay
K hi guys guys I'm lost help me help me
T my
go I'm lost will you guys help me I have
a
map uh
here I have a map this is not a Japanese
folding screen uh F made really really
small downsized by 500 no uh this is a
map the closest thing I could find to
that looks like a map in
3D an old looking map it's not M be no
it's a just a
normal 3D thing with scuffed hand
treking uh we are playing a game
today where you have to find the exit
number eight and I think it's um
ironically pointing out how you can get
lost in the Japanese uh Subway
underground like I have also gotten lost
several times especially in Shinjuku
because there is so many different
uh what's the word uh Subway
Lines and then if you want to switch
because some are from different
companies you have to completely get out
of the thing and then go to a different
thing and then it's gets really
confusing uh
yeah
yeah my my hat I have my hat so anyway
guys we have to get out of here we have
to get out of here help me please maybe
with the support of this map
yeah okay does this game have any
bgm uh hi hi sorry sorry sir do you do
hey hey
dude okay
okay I guess I have to rely on my
map this is
apparently not really a horror game but
it can be a little bit
scary uh my map is blank
what let me look at it is it is it
really
blank my
hand let me
look yeah okay it might be BL it might
be
blank uh I I don't really know what to
expect I just uh guess that I should
probably remember some of these
things so that later on it can
be uh you know a a help a
guidance no wonder you got lost wait is
it the maybe maybe the other side no no
both sides are both sides are empty
okay maybe it's like if I pour water on
it you know that kind of ink that when
you pour water on it it gets visible or
maybe it needs daylight but in order to
get daylight I have to get out of the
exit first of all
so yeah okay let's
see there is some posters okay we have
we have a a dental poster we have uh
looking for um people to work poster we
have a dog l poster we have a all like a
legal advice poster I think we have
makeup exhibition poster we
have no reflection of
myself am I
real there's no reflection I'm a
ghost that is the the biggest problem I
don't think that the exit is the problem
anymore what if I go this way conour
what does Concourse mean in
Dutch can I run oh
yes what if I don't go forward what if I
go back what if it's
a
reverse
oh what if it's a reverse psychology
kind of thing I was going to say but I
know it said exit a that direction but
now this way it says Exit
Zero
what's sorry it was kind of weird the
blur was weird what are you also looking
for Exit 8 me too maybe we can share
information here no it's empty yeah I
know
but is there is it important like is
time of the
issue why does he scare
me time is of the
issue time is of the essence wait we're
back here but oh okay ah okay so this is
the circle if I go backwards it's just a
circle huh okay what about these doors I
feel like I'm so
tall okay let's go well I mean so far
it's only straight wait it's also zero
here
oh dude dude dude dude hey hey you I
think we're I think we're going in a
circle what do you think about that sir
what
if still no reflection he has a
reflection though this is the same
order wait it's a circle how you not Den
night oh it hasn't
started when does it
start
run run run run run run run it's still
the it's still the
same how do I start the
game haven't I started the game I will
understand soon okay do I just have to
do a few more Loops
until until
oh is this the whole game
read the instructions there's no
instructions there's no instructions
here
either wait oh wait wait was this here
before don't overlook any anomalies if
you find any
anomalies turn back immediately if you
don't find any anomalies do not turn
back to go out to go out from exit 8
okay do it yeah wait well was this here
before guessing not nambo Park M Junior
High School yo Temple n building Hai
Crossing exit
zero wow okay
so I see so it is kind of a circle but
if I find anything that's different from
usual gosh how many things do I even
have to like remember stuff like on
which days they're available or
not
also this light sound
this that sound is that
important no this not okay what about
you okay let's remember he has five
buttons on his
shirt uh black bag black shoes what how
many things I have to
remember uh five dogs one is a corgi one
is I don't know what and then one
another thing I don't know maybe labor
door and the
poodle uh Tuesday
1219 is this
important 5,000 3,000
yen
super wait that's today oh oh is that on
purpose oh this is over
already is there meaning in this
picture do I not need to remember this I
wonder let's remember these there's a
like a blue DJ picture there's a pink
one and there's a there's a yellow
one move move
F security camera in operation I Like
These Eyes this
is not how would usually look like in
Japan I think the rest is like pretty
pretty
much yeah uh three doors Two
vents no smoking
sign door this light is
on oh they're pretty OB oh okay free
free doors no smoking light is
on ah it's has one now but that's an
anomaly
no is that Chad what do you
think that's an anomaly right is that
considered an
anomaly no that's good ah okay so I
guess like it will go up anyway like to
two three four five six seven eight okay
okay okay oh okay okay okay
okay but I didn't even do
anything all I did was go for
forward one
two show me your
buttons five buttons okay you can pass
goodbye go by go
goodbye security
camera
doors the vents are the vents in a
different
position no dogs dogs same dogs same
date same operation
times same pictures yeah yeah yeah same
same eye color mhm
mhm looks
same okay let's go next is this random
by the way or is it scripted
like can I get the same kind of
playthrough as some as the others or
is
y is r ah okay so I could be like really
lucky
I should be so lucky lucky lucky luy I
should be so lucky
love two two
eight two doors three doors yeah dogs
same buttons button check sorry sir
please please hold hold hold I say hey
hey but I think it was it was enough
buttons it's random but until you get
each anomal one stay one
repeat
what what does that
mean same eye color same
pictures
same same same same same
same same same same same same same
operation eight eight
Dental no you keep you think the doors
get smaller no pretty much the same
vents same lights same same same same
same let's go
anomaly anomaly anomaly anomaly anomaly
[Music]
an anomal anomaly anomaly anomaly anomal
oh oh nice
anomaly anomaly is that even a real
word but how could I have known that was
the the the light turning off was the
anomaly right I couldn't have known
until getting to the point where the
anomaly started
right number
[Music]
three nice
buttons no anomaly no anomally I guess
this is not where anomaly would
be okay so it like happens like when I
go around the corner or something like
that
oh oh okay
yeah check my
map okay I think we're on the right
[Music]
track I'm not doing anything some
anomalies are subtle okay okay
okay okay everything the same so
far oh good good that I have a map right
what would I do without this map my
sense of direction is so good
uh button
check okay you can
pass dogs
same yeah yeah good good vents oh yeah
wait
yeah okay he's passing
okay send pictures all good all good
okay
what
what observant Joel what what
how why is it so easy speed running the
game anomaly anomaly
anomaly
y anomaly
anomaly what the
L what what this can't be so fast
huh am I having like an especially fast
experience like I'm even trying to drag
it out of like you know checking my map
that obviously doesn't say
anything okay same same same same dogs
same same same same same same same same
same it's probably never going to be
anything different on these except for
like if like one is completely missing
or something like that that would
be
yeah okay some jump scare coming up
right
right anomaly we went back to zero this
cannot
be wait wait how far back do I go around
the whole corner I failed what what was
wrong no oh wait if it's zero that means
I completely like got reset oh man
okay but I have to go past zero
again okay what was what was the anomaly
was it the way he was
walking let's analyze his walking he's
he's walking on the F tile side thingy
Row from the yellow
thing
he's kind of
uh well he has bushy
eyebrows he has a weird
mustache and he has five
buttons well
okay well I'm I'm kind of familiar with
all this stuff does
[Music]
it let's look at this maybe this is
important but I feel like this was all
the same this is a cleaning closet this
is uh staff
only and this says uh some electricity
room I
think well
okay one maybe this part is also
[Music]
important
also am I allowed to
run I can ignore that hallway okay he's
he's walking on the third
tile
okay I by do dogs
Salone five buttons and a nice
butt is this important 1 2 3 4 5 6 seven
eight nine flowers nine flowers green
eyes brown eye okay up for
exhibition what 1 2 3 4 5 six
S8 door knobs door
knobs don't look back
[Laughter]
you surprised me you surprised me dude
well if I find the accident I'll let you
know okay see you
later was somebody like coming out there
out of the door I wonder cuz I didn't
want to see it I did not want to see
it I can tell you
that
fertile
fence buttons and the butt all
right does he always look down does he
always look
down does he always look down
maybe he starts looking down as
long as I'm like when I when I'm not in
front of
him
oh
spooky no
really s thought it was
weird that's the that's the anomaly
really
right look at
me look at
me look at me you have to look at
me
bye-bye oh okay I will I will believe my
instincts then if you if this like was
an anomaly then I I'll continue
believing my instincts
okay he looks he looks nor see I I
noticed it though like so I I would say
you know that was was me finding an
anomaly see yeah now he continues to
look straight
yeah maybe I should also stay in this
part longer because like what what for
example if like another guy
comes and that is obviously the
anomaly but I
think I think it's all okay at least
until
here
okay
y let's
go bring it on dude come over
here how you doing today huh let me
check all these other things
too you got those buttons no my buttons
bab ah what you going to do to
me aha
I see
nothing he seemed
normal he seemed nor
normal normal normal normal normal
normal normal normal oh yeah no
Y unless suddenly a door opens or the
light turns off no no we're good
no what what was
wrong what's with the door what was with
the
door
what the door
knob okay I look at the door knobs each
time
now well that's not even though it's a
game bug because it was it is so cheap
the game
no
okay I checked more than just the
buttons this time glitchy face okay
okay interesting first I thought he was
like wearing some kind of plastic
mask
vents posters how you doing today sir
you got all the buttons with you right
yeah yeah want to look down oh no no
okay let's let's watch
him all right okay he seems he seems
fine what about the door
knobs looking from a safe distance but
they look
normal they look normal this part looks
normal okay
next
door right yeah okay okay okay okay that
that that was that was normal they look
normal now oh yeah oh yeah that was
normal what about now no
smoking don't worry I have never smoked
a cigarette in my
life could it be like suddenly he comes
like charging at me sort of walking that
would be funny
too
okay well Security check
passed what the is that let's get
out of here no no no no no no no no no
no no no that is not no oh my
God it was fine a good decision Wawa
good decision making
yeah chat please don't spoil otherwise
this game is done in 5
[Music]
minutes all right okay what if he
suddenly wears a a green
shirt oh okay
he's he looks all
normal
door
knobs don't open the door suddenly on
me okay I
think I think we're good I think we're
good stop checking his
behind just want to make sure he has all
his butt on his butts his butt
on we would want his butt to be off
[Laughter]
right
s this
n this how we doing today
sir what's with this reflection eh it's
kind of
sus you're looking fine you're looking
fine nice
shoes you don't have a don't you have a
jacket by the
way it's going to be cold
outside kind of freezing especially cuz
like the game obviously points at the
season December
okay so the hallway is fine unless
something suddenly happens but I think
what what what what did you see guys I
didn't see
anything why was my first run so good
and
now I feel like I'm looking pretty
closely at
everything
at least this time I didn't hear the
sound of the door
opening yeah cuz that's the
freakiest okay the door was
open
[Music]
eventually I guess I wonder how many I
wonder how many um anomalies there
are cuz eventually you just know them
all don't
you what is
now
looks
okay looks good to
go I think I
[Music]
think
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
again okay
byebye that one is too
obvious
what's what's it today what's it
[Music]
today
nothing door
knobs door look good floor looks
good ceiling looks look
good posters look
[Music]
good dogs look good this is
fine let's go
next yes okay okay okay okay back to
four back to four we're pretty far let's
not mess it up now halfway
through halfway through this
year
you like my hair it's so pretty from
behind right you guys should I should
show you my behind more
often I like my wings on my back they're
cute
right
okay okay
okay
looks
fine no what what what what what what am
I always missing just tell me am I
always missing the same
one or are they all the ones I miss
different
ones yes
yes I always missed the same one okay
don't tell me don't tell
me
[Music]
okay stop stop stop stop stop
stop
God that is scary that is that is scary
that's scary what the what the
H okay
uh yeah good to go good to
go what is the one that I'm always
missing now I'm like really
paranoid what could it
be
what could it
be here I don't see
anything I
think I think this is fine please say
it's fine yeah okay okay
okay
all good in this
[Music]
neighborhood but we got to
wait okay okay seems
normal
dogs
door I I currently don't see anything
but surely there's something and
probably the same thing
again
let me check yeah let's check the
[Music]
map okay okay okay okay let's go let's
go let's go probably fine probably fine
I'll never get out of here oh but it was
okay it was safe safe safe safe safe
H oh no hold on map still no no you just
don't see it it's just not visible to
you okay but I see
it I spy with my little
[Music]
eye are you going to
no no he's not sad that I am not
greeting him or anything like
that floor is normal doors
are
normal the light is
normal security camera
normal camera and
operation move move move f
you
seems
normal but no way that there's going to
be two normal ones after another
right 1 2 4 4 5 6 7even 8
n what what's with the ipul
makeup
art they
move wait maybe these ones
oh you guys are spoilering my dog but
there's two eye
posters you guys are spoilering me but
okay this is funny this is quite funny
okay okay okay don't don't tell me you
can only tell me maybe like oh there's
something wrong so just look for it
longer longer you have to stay until you
look for it until we find
it
floor all good I think but I'll I'll
check a
bit my my intuition is tell telling me
that it's
all
[Music]
okay but just got to make double sure
what about the door knobs people oh okay
okay okay okay okay okay I saw it this
time that's what you meant with
doorknobs before huh
[Music]
okay let's
go we're at five now we're past the
middle past
halfway
floor
vents
posters
guy
normal random door opening
no eyes not following
this looks
normal looks normal to
me isn't a
nor what the is that supposed to
look terrifying it looks a little bit
terrifying okay I I I found it myself
don't worry I just had to look around a
little bit
more okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
we're almost
there
interesting okay guy is okay
okay
this this room looks okay there's
nothing
here
sure this this one looks good this one
looks fine I don't see any problem here
dog is happy what else do you
want looks okay let's go let's go come
[Music]
on yes okay believe in your heart
believe in yourself trust your intuition
guys sometimes it is actually
correct
seven 1 2 3 4 5 six seven you make feel
like
11 I always I always have to look back
at him like that it doesn't mean
anything okay not interested in you just
interested in your
anomalies I have a anomaly
fetish apparently that I didn't know
about until
now she didn't see there was something
on
him can I still see it can I still
perceive
it
I'm not supposed to have seen that I
wouldn't have seen it or is it in the
room is it in the
room that is very
subtle that is very subtle
M okay okay
okay wait it's already eight no no no
no
no it was fake after all I saw something
at the end of the
room but this time for real for real
right this time for real for
real sir sir I think I found it do you
want to escape
together
no why
not free the OG
son he seems content content down here I
guess he can enjoy his
time I feel like there's no nothing
here feel like we good I mean I wouldn't
mind like being reset back anyway cuz
it's too
short wait or did I just get reset
because at the end you do get
reset or was it actually like a reset
because I didn't find something y we can
play more let's
go okay okay
okay okay okay let's let's for real be
um let's let's do a blind run for real
for real like I will not look at you
guys that doesn't mean you can spoil
anything in the chat though because what
if I
accidentally look at you
huh and then you say something and I see
it accidentally I'm not trying to
perceive your hints you know I'm not
trying to do it
purposefully
okay this room is okay okay next
[Music]
door there I get my charging but he's
not really running he's just like sped
up
walking he's in a hurry he's sick of
being here as
well like okay like stuff like that is
really obvious though obviously I'm
going to notice
[Music]
that this room looks
normal this room looks normal
don't tell
me
[Music]
okay buttons buttons
door knobs
ceiling ceiling looks good the eyes do
they follow me
[Music]
no
okay maybe I let it go too fast but uh
okay okay okay okay okay okay yeah now
I'm a veteran I am an underground
veteran
so easy clap
don't even need this map anymore throw
it away throw it
away yay yay floor
ceiling oh
lady on the looking for workers uh vent
door
knob door what did I see I saw my
future what what
what looks normal looks normal
it looks normal to me it looks normal to
me let's
go what why can I look at it now no it's
gone is it wait no wait
[Music]
what what what was
it
the posters are bigger maybe they are I
guess
yeah are
they
okay
how did I not notice that seemed
very normal to
me okay never mind never mind yeah this
is really small
this is really
[Music]
small
there
normal it's the beginning anyway can be
a little bit Yeah
risky I judge you to be
normal doors are there vents are there
floor is there ceiling is there guy is
walking normally for
now door knobs are
normal did he always have his shirt like
a little bit open at the top maybe
yeah all right
bye sudden door
opening sudden light shutting down no
[Music]
okay two in a row wor no anomalies
they're going easy mode on me but is it
really easy mode because like it makes
me doubt
everything being confident in nothing
being there is also a
challenge
okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay seems
fine let's
go what what what what is it this
time what was it what was
ity was it something about the
guy
I have no
idea you guys don't have an idea either
not none at
all camer R
true
[Music]
this is exactly why I always get
this lost in Shinjuku
man let it be a lesson for me in the
future never again will I get
lost nice nice nice what if this
suddenly is a dog a cat Salon that would
be
nice and that's unrealistic because cats
don't need a salon cats are their own
hairdressers
mhm
[Music]
yeah ceiling
floor watching me no door knobs I don't
know it's uh all
okay yeah this one's
fine
certainly I am sure
[Music]
mhm you know why I'm so certain because
of this
map
there's nothing on the map which means
oh my God the
poster there was just scary
post last
one okay no problem this is the safe
c um think someone's stuck in there but
that's not my problem sounds like a you
problem okay okay thank you for the
obvious uh hints game seems like you
have mercy on
me all
right all
right looks pretty normal to me let's
risk it because a normal one after an
anomaly seems pretty normal to me what
what what what
what
what are they big again are they big
again are they big I can't
tell are they
big are they I guess they're
big
why is it the same thing that keeps on
getting
me even after I found out about
[Music]
it let's remember this
size
okay
what what what what was the
problem how did I not
see okay okay I must have I must have
seen almost all of them by
now what the what the
what the
hell okay really be as paranoid as you
could possibly
be check everything size okay
guy okay door okay door okay light okay
eyes Okay Okay Okay show first one
should
be okay
[Music]
doors okay size okay smoking okay light
okay vents okay okay door knobs okay
guy okay floor
okay ceiling
okay map
okay okay
okay I think okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay poster size
okay
poster ingredients okay no smoking okay
exit eight okay door okay ceiling okay a
light light light light light light
light light light light I saw it I saw
it I saw
it checklist okay let
me where's my
hand okay checklist
okay floor okay door okay light okay
okay okay um okay oh
okay door knobs
okay eyes
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
floor okay
okay guy are you okay he's
[Applause]
okay
NY NY are you watching me me
no I
don't wait wait they're big they're big
they're
big they're big they're
big they're
big
yay
okay
they were indeed
big very big guy are you
big you're
normal you're just normal
light what about the sign sign
normal normal normal normal pretty
normal looks pretty
normal okay I believe it let's
go oh six six six okay let's be very
careful now we don't want to be reset
again
floor
sign camera
light door knobs size
size guy okay
looks normal to me this lady has no
weird face
either I think it's fine but then we
would have two normal ones in a
[Music]
row got to believe in it got to believe
in
it yes
okay here we go here we
go it's so close I can almost grasp it
with my
hand yes soon TM we will get out of
here
she okay he's
smiling
I made it I think I made it I made it
why is it here too because I thought
that was eight but I'll check again just
in case I'll check again just in
case why it's
okay last time I see you possibly
although I kind of want to see more of
the of the anomaly
I might even play again cuz I want to
see more it looks normal to me maybe if
I fail it we can see more let's
go I made it woohoo the light at the end
of the
title so funny oh thanks to the map I I
couldn't have done it
without
you you you you you but let me play
again I want to play again I don't want
to see the credits go away go away go
away oh they're really short anyway
okay oh was fast really nah not really I
don't think it was
fast but I want to play again
Mo because I want to see more
anomalies let's go
show me your
anomalies all good okay all right all
right e
e read read what do you mean read the
sign I know what
what rest one always normal read the
notice I have to not
is it like how do they know that I read
it or didn't read it this
one there are nine anomalies that I have
not found
yet oh that's what you wanted me to read
ah okay wait wait was the sign an
anomaly no
right
[Music]
what wasn't
one I guess it was was it it wait
what this the
[Music]
normal still
there okay so that is a little bit hard
to understand where it starts
okay having nine anomalies left after
the clear is that a bit
embarrassing like the amount is it not a
little bit too
small they'll try to show me different
ones right
surely yes a bit now shut up you try
escaping the hell of the to
underground you try it you try it
light looks good looks good looks good
[Music]
e do I always have to check that sign
sign now too ah
opposite I don't know if you saw but I
saw
it my eyes spied it wait what the
oh wait that is an anomaly right that's
an anomaly too
[Laughter]
right it's not the exit
oh this also kind of looked like stairs
to me now suddenly the squares in the
back suddenly also look like Square uh
stairs to
me here they're baiting me I'm not that
that desperate I I already I already
found the stairs before I'm only doing
this because it's fun you
know I'm doing this on
purpose I do not
see an
anomaly wait that smoking sign was that
always
there I don't think it
was I don't think it
was really okay okay okay
okay okay
okay
lights posters poster sence poster sence
okay face okay Lord
ceiling okay go next there's no way
right probably back to
zero no okay oh I was scared to
[Music]
look is my hat
single uh no cuz my hat belongs to me so
I guess I'm dating the
Hat
sorry to disappoint you oh turn back
turn back
okay
okay wait that was only obvious if you
actually look look back otherwise that
wouldn't have been noticeable
right found it that wasn't as obvious so
like if you look already up and then say
Oh everything's fine at the top and then
don't look up ever again then then
you're
okay
H looks
good yes oh I'm got to do it again but I
still have six more anomalies how can I
see six more anomalies when I'm already
at seven
huh show them to
me reveal
yourself
[Music]
somebody needs to fix that
light okay here there could be another
anomaly
here no smoking two Vans the poster
sides okay floor
okay okay okay all right what w he's so
big yeah he's big he's big
before I only said it as a joke but he
could actually be big there we go wait
this is the Oh e look at
[Music]
that why is a happening double it's so
confusing why is eight here
again this like the first time I'm H I
didn't make a mistake right
right oh I need to find a normal
eight a so okay
okay that's
confusing I wouldn't mind them showing
me all the anomalies then
until until I
find
it okay looks
good looks good looks good I think I'm
going yep second clear let's
[Music]
go the light is here once again to free
me
from the
terrifying darkness of the
underground
not you can't fool me no
more I've mastered
it I've learned how to read this
mysterious
map wait how many three more three more
let's
go
show
me nothing here I
think ah what was it was it the
picture size again don't tell me it was
again the picture
size no okay what was
it oh oh wait what is at the start wait
that was the start
right so
confusing okay first one always goes to
zero okay oh okay found one that thing
the floor
tiles two
more two more
anomalies
two now I'm looking forward to the to
the changes and to the maybe even to the
jump scares was it always this dirty in
front of the
doors looks weird to me
now
yeah this place looks
normal except for the dirt here really
oh well
okay
okay that was normal
indeed
okay H this room looks normal too but
let me look at the signs of the pictures
no that they're fine
ceiling that's
okay I think everything's
okay check the map m
are the doors too small no or are
they
oh it's a different
[Music]
kind
Maga
okay wait two more wait does that mean I
already had that anomaly before and I
didn't
[Music]
realize that's so weird okay
nice meet
didn't
count oh that's kind of fancy though the
placement of the lights is kind of
fancy not go shut
it yeah I technically missed it like who
maybe there's even more that I that the
game things I found but or like
encountered but I didn't realize it
anyway so they're still to me they're
unencountered
anomalies never said this word so much
as I did
today are there any flat earthers in the
chat you like the footsteps on
really what no because I was watching a
a video or two
videos from Jubilee about Flat Earth
like one where there's an odd man out
there's like like six seven eight people
uh one of them is a flat earther and
they have to figure out which one it is
and then another video where um it's
like four three four scientist no three
scientist versus fre flat Earths
discussion H I didn't quite get finished
with the the discussion video so I got
to continue afterwards I think this is
fine this one looks
fine I don't know Flat Earth obviously I
don't believe in it it's kind of crazy
not going to lie pyramid
Earth it looks like I'm groping
my I'm not touching my B okay what what
what you call calm down
okay calm down head it's so excited
because like there's another anomaly we
have to
find and my hand is looking for it in my
chest but it's not there it's just not
there this room also looks
clear
in oh what I follow me again yo yo yo I
was about to miss
it that was surprisingly easy oh I found
them all oh because this time I didn't
ah this time I didn't pass it
I okay okay okay okay ah I found them
all okay then then I think we can
say we're
done
[Music]
OD nice short
stream it's fine I have to cook and I
have to clean but I'll read super
chats quickly from today's stream cuz
yesterday I already caught up with my 3d
concert Super Chat so it was very very
efficient I mean not really but you
[Music]
know so
no it's GNA be short I'm just uh I'm
just uh going to read the super chats
quickly it shouldn't take too
long I only cook during witching hour no
no no I will cook before midnight today
[Music]
possibly
maybe I mean even if I say cook I was
just going to throw in some frozen Ika
meatballs shut bua into the oven and
make something with potatoes either
throw Frozen potatoes in the oven or
make some mashed potatoes and then make
the sauce um like most of it is not
really uh real cooking because I don't
have a hellofresh box for this week
so I'm just like until Christmas I'm
just going to
eat like I don't give a about
nutritions
anyway this game was fun um if there's
more games like this that are maybe a
little bit scary but it's more about
like riddles I I would welcome them so
feel free to recommend them I I for one
welcome this Overlord game yeah yeah
yeah why is this cable always in the way
no it's not the cable it's the
carpet game finisher ofan yeah it te me
res
evil
carpet I hate
you go away why did I move the carpet
why did I move
it let me move
it
okay okay that's a bit better
signal the
carpent the Revenge of the
carpenter I hate I hate them because
they
don't they don't realize what they truly
are they don't understand what the
intention of their job or of the m
they don't get it they just don't get it
the carpet
anomaly
yeah
uneducated I I would I would put like
Flat Earth versus global Earth First on
the same level as people who believe
Carpenters make carpets and people who
don't believe Carpenters make carpets
I'm I'm a globe Herer but I'm also I
believe in Carpenters making carpets and
if you don't believe that then maybe
you're also a flat
[Music]
earther just
saying just saying woo that was loud
sorry
sorry wait where's
my
you guys want
to
see uh winter version of The Girls
[Music]
Room the real jum
scare bit loud okay hey jingle bells
jingle bells jingle all
way
a okay we'll go here and I'll change it
from
here
jingle jingle
the oh what fun it is to
ride I have to maybe give a sad
update uh what the
I'm to give a sad update about
among us to
collab uh there's one more person who
dropped out
sadly so now it's minus
4 or 11 people but still still a good
amount no John Ena dropped out so
sad
no too
bad it is what it
is but I have one happy message I went
shopping for pants and wool and stuff
and I found the same exact pants that I
bought years ago many many years ago
that were eaten by Ms I I found the same
pair again and I bought it because I
liked it cuz it had a good fit and it
made my butt look
good
yeah
yeah no it doesn't have a hole it didn't
come with a hole that is the thing
that's why I bought
it pants are not banned
anymore I shall forgive them
momentarily okay let's see let's check
out the winter
version
wait hey whoa wait the the window is
open it's cold just it's snowing
inside if the wind and the snow is going
to come in that much I don't think it's
realistic for me to have the window open
but
[Music]
okay wait let me let me look
around yeah so the new things are the
snow outside I guess there's still
leaves can you believe it anomaly yeah
there's an
[Music]
anomaly oh wait the chicken is wearing a
Santa hat
cute and I guess the the lights
here can you see any other
[Music]
anomalies the toast light was already on
in
uh in the night version anyway yeah I
think that's
it
nice yeah the light is fli
ering no no no
no but I don't know maybe you mean the
you mean the Lights On The
Greenery oh yeah those are those oh they
have different colors green and red and
then they turn off
nice
I like it
[Music]
it's F
Frozen she's the same as
before but I guess that could explain
why she's so
still same as before
[Music]
though
no Chef hats
anomaly m is
[Music]
peeping I'm watching but I don't see
her is this another jump scare
[Music]
moment she's not
there no no no no no no don't make me
paranoid anomaly you're an anomaly no
sorry that was that was
mean I'm the anomaly I'm sorry I'm the
vtuber after
all W
rude did you guys check out yesterday's
Advent calendar video it was so cute
like
no it was the first it was somebody
appearing for the first time and with
that I think we had everyone appear at
least once except
GAA
yeah I I I don't think GAA will be in it
sadly I
can't um
yeah
sorry
[Music]
sorry so I don't know if I should like
include her in the finale because if I
remember correctly didn't I last
year
for the sock puppet
finale I had her in it but didn't I also
just use like recordings of
her just like in order to have her in
the video didn't like yeah I just used
existing op voice lines of
her
so is it going to be the same this
year oh was it Ena oh that was for Ena
okay Ena this year should be
fine I think I should be able to get
everybody into the sock puppet
video maybe maybe except for GAA uh but
maybe I'll just use a voice lines for
her
[Music]
then I went to buy Wool by the way and I
didn't buy any wool because I couldn't
find the right color
there was so much wool selection but
there just was no right color like I
already have a lot of colors still from
last year I have them left over but I
need black and I need dark blue and I
couldn't find those at least not black I
found like one dark blue that could have
been okay but then there was no black so
I was like maybe I'll order from Amazon
after
all I didn't want to order something
that I can definitely find IRL and
probably cheaper or like in smaller
amounts cuz like when I order something
so cheap from Amazon usually they sell
it in like bigger amounts and I'm like I
don't need so much wool just making one
sock
puppet yeah but I guess I I got to order
oh remind me to make my order because I
I can already start with like fuu sock
puppets and beu sock puppets but for
shii and for narissa I need black and
for narissa I need BL dark blue m
yeah for the
hair but I guess I'll just start with
for I think tomorrow I'll start tomorrow
I also have to write the story I don't
know what to write
about what I have no
inspiration I have no
idea what should I do I'm ripping off my
my lips don't worry
I'm not picking my
[Music]
nose oh don't worry it was like really
just small small small
small a parody a parody a par of
[Music]
what
Christmas what Christmas Christmas Carol
is a
story
[Music]
H free Ghost of
Christmas I know that story it's like
when somebody goes to sleep right and
then the like in the night free ghost
visit him separately and show
him like things he up about with
yeah yeah
H but how would
I that's like
really like who would be the guy who
would be the ghost and then I guess in
his dreams I can implement the other
girls but like who would be the guy and
the
ghost past present future
maybe that's four people how about I'm
the
guy and then C
Ina are the
ghosts and then in the dreams promise
and Advent
[Music]
appear your red super got what what do
you mean got
stolen
no because that's exactly four people
and
um yeah I thought maybe that would be
good and GAA can be like my
pet so instead of like let's say I have
a dog but it's GAA and the way it barks
is just
[Music]
ah that way I have myth implemented
perfectly
okay I will not cook any further because
I I'll I'll I'll make it a surprise
maybe maybe that will be what I'll go
for though thank you for the
[Music]
inspiration yeah should that should work
out I feel like I can whip something up
with that okay let's read super chats
from
today also thanks for the super stickers
on the last Super Chat reading Gino py
RAB and
gin and so let's go Anon m d unknown
thank you for the red super chat I
finally got my free year armor o free
nice joining your membership is the best
decision ever I still regret not joining
sooner thank you for all you do my Kami
you're the best best and I will be here
supporting you until the very end no
matter what love you
[Music]
forever
here
[Music]
heart heart this is this is a
heart just almost the heart maybe
like yeah thank you so much
unknown for your support congratulations
on three years that's a long time long
long
time but I know you will be here for
much much longer right
promise promise wait Pinky Promise pink
pinky
promise
see I can
barely I can usually barely do stuff
like this but today in fre I can
gesture wow so go here oh
[Music]
kiss
wowy Thank You unknown for everything
thank you so much I love you Jacob for
seven d Geral ra thank you for the
rainbow after your concert in all its
Sublime Glory I contracted a severe case
of wobble love feel like you already had
that before incurable terminal
transmissible and
[Music]
euphoric
transmissible what does that mean does
that mean you you can go from you to
other people the only treatment is
watching Mo waa hearing the fascinating
things she has to say ferociously
cheering for truly special talented
hardworking and wonderful OSI whose
dancing mesmerizes me with every
graceful step cheering for a girl who
beats back every obstacle and Rises High
a beautiful Phoenix as bright as the sun
someone worth Crossing oceans to cheer
and exclaim for someone who is always
full of surprises and blows past every
expectation someone who shares maybe a
little too much but whose honesty and
ferocity feroc ferocity feroc ferocity
fills my heart with pride someone who
has made this our favorite place to be
thanks for everything you do K I hope
next year brings nothing but joy you
deserve it all and more thank
you you deserve it
too we all deserve it we all deserve
love happiness joy success so honestly I
I I wish it for all of us thank you so
much for all the love for all the
support J
hope you're doing well is this in com in
in in total it's not a red right 18 no
not quite so no
kiss no kiss for
[Music]
you sorry not
sorry but it's a beautiful rainbow thank
you for showing it to me and for all the
sweet world words you be you are good
with words are you are you a poet are
you a literature
person teach me teach me the ways of
literature smug instead of kiss that you
can have
[Music]
smug no car for you
no
[Music]
Nole all the
way
[Music]
okay no wait not
not your name is hard to read too much
Katakana than you for the Super Chat win
thank
[Music]
you ah oh thank you yeah it's it's okay
Phoenix go go fall down and stand back
up really fast so don't worry about me
thank
[Music]
you
for
[Music]
lamber dun I'm just not going to read
that last name cuz I'm don't know I
don't know how to pronounce
it uh thank you for the pinky hello
Kiana good luck on finding Exit 8 also
can you greet me happy birthday it's my
birthday today December 19th woo
congratulations I can
CL happy birthday to you
yay yeah I hope you celebrated yourself
because you're awesome and you
should good job on you for getting older
keep growing Bolder as
well love Rush
reference become
stone have
r375 Mike H
Kronos the V weiro
Brar thank you for the r chat Mr
Scrooge I mean
t wait why why Mr Scrooge what I know
I'm supposed to stay in the usual room
all year but please it's Christmas I
want to spend it with my family Please
Release
Me ah
ah you don't want to be visited by
ghosts of Christmas Past future and
present do you mer well I might be
visited by those ghosts actually
now very soon but it might be too late
for you by that point
Ah that's why you said your Super Chat
was
stolen
[Music]
interesting what was his crime again
remind me guys
[Music]
please please tell me I'm
listening I'm all
ears
[Music]
oh he made me tell a de nut's joke
really and then there was truly a
followup you guys can't remember was it
really the de
nuts he did a lot of things right and
he's like he's kind of like asking for
it oh yeah he he he he claims he escaped
the usual room and then was smug about
it I can see
that I can see
[Music]
that delar are you here would you mind
ah there you
are ah oh you you actually saying it to
me d Mani mama and Rebellion are you
rebelling against me well at least you
admit your crimes here I'm guessing the
Gemma and the mama was like you trying
to bait me into a wholesome Super Chat
and then in the end revealing it it
wasn't about me probably something like
Dad
[Music]
well I don't
know
you know what I'll put you're going back
but I'm putting you
on no no no how about I give you this
offer and this is the only
offer you say you want to go to your
family for Christmas now I can let you
out and then what if that was a lie and
you don't actually go to your family so
how about your family family if you want
to spend time with them and if they want
to spend time with you they come to the
usual
room they can come to you you're not
coming to them they're coming to
you I think that's a good deal if that
was actually the
truth that it's about the family
visitation rights now prison
[Music]
visit your choice
they will perhaps if they behave they'll
be able to leave
again but they will be checked for
Ry uh for like in case they're bringing
something dangerous so they will be
stripped naked but chickens being naked
is not a big deal so they will be
stripped
naked before entering the
prison
mhm and if they try anything funky they
will be fried immediately and in front
of your eyes and you will be
watching while I put them in the hot oil
the sizzling hot oil I know I'm so
merciful you're so
welcome from my heart this is my gesture
from my
[Music]
heart thank you D star for your
understanding you c m thank you for the
pinky I'm an
angel see I I'm an
angel wait my other hand is broken but
see I'm yeah I'm angel I'm
angel
angel you got your F to the pinky
congratulations on your concert k I love
how high energy it was all the way also
your performance of the Japanese members
we don't get to see them that
often amazing Coro and dancing from
everyone thank you you're truly amazing
thank thank you for enjoying it for
watching it and for being there I really
I'm really really happy with how it
turned out and I I want to do more this
is just the beginning so please continue
supporting and surely there will be more
like
this thank you so much
you love love
love rice of
free to
you
[Music]
Evans than you love hey
D little
uh the great observation is that
wait is that the convenience store one
cuz that one looks scary that one looks
really terrifying from what I've
seen I don't
[Music]
know
Jazz
[Music]
wow
Jess
should I do a finger a finger snapping
[Music]
concert
wow yeah they already heard they're
already
red D this
Skittle think you found all the
anomalies the fastest in the end really
don't worry chat also spoiled everyone
else too so it's fair
y Mah Mah this information makes me
happy so you get
kisses take it glance thank you for the
red super chat Hi boss with this humble
Super Chat I have a request could you
please say the Katy Perry meme phrase of
a do you want to do you want to create
the meme or
something
let me try to say it um with
her so we have a perfect overlap
they ask you how you are but I'll mute
it
so okay let's go they ask you how you
are and you just have to say you're fine
and you're not really fine but you can't
get into it because they would never
understand like
that maybe one more time with more
emotion more
emotion they ask you how you are and you
just have to say that you're fine and
you're not really fine but you just
can't get into it because they would
never
understand too fast it is the same speed
pretty much pretty much same speed yeah
have a reference video are you okay I'm
not okay I'm not okay
they ask you how you are and you just
have to say that you're fine and you're
not really fine but you can't get just
into it but by Mumble bumbly bumbly
jumbly they ask you how you are and you
just have to say that you're fine and
you're really not fine because you just
can't say the
words beep blooper blooper real
stle they ask you how you are and you
just have to say that you're fine and
you're not really fine but you just
can't get into it because they would
never
understand nailed
it okay that's was good that was good I
am Katy
Perry I am the real one thank you for
the red super chat D class love you too
and by the way I know about uh you're
the one with the jiggle right
I know about it I read that by the way
don't worry I read it long time ago I am
aware that the jiggle is not
real but let's let's just act as if it
is but there was like some kind of
jiggle in the video that chy made for me
after like editing that footage that I
sent him um but maybe it's like more of
a clothing physics jiggle but it looked
good looked good
so I was quite satisfied with
[Music]
that it's real if we want it to be real
don't say that GL don't say it's a skirt
it's my
[Music]
butt thank you class
SP
observ yes it
me in the end there was there was
something wrong with his buttons so sad
I
wish I wish maybe even like having
something on his butt at some point
suddenly like a like a Boop would have
been funny I don't know just just
saying okay around K thanks for two
pinkies help you out just got back from
Japan oh it was my first time out of the
country since I was a small boy wow and
my first time traveling alone
W respect I wanted to travel the world
for a very long time now but I was
always the big chicken to take the next
step it wasn't until I heard your
tangents about traveling Japan Europe
and especially Brazil come to Brazil
that I finally had the confidence to do
so thanks for everything you do and I
hope to visit more places such as
Germany and Austria soon why was it
especially
Brazil thank you I'm happy to hear that
I hope you enjoyed Japan traveling alone
especially to a country that that you
don't know so well or you don't know the
the the language of I forgot do you
speak Japanese all cuz if you don't
speak
Japanese first time you travel outside
of your country then that's I'm glad you
seem to be
fine but Japan is usually a safe country
so in most situations so it was to be
expected Google translate was my friend
nice yeah and I think um like getting
around places in in Tokyo is really easy
or in Japan in general if you just have
um Google Maps as well the only thing
sometimes I even I get lost like when I
follow Google Maps is that like Shibuya
station for example when I'm actually
not going by train but with
buses cuz in certain hotpots like
Shibuya there's like a million different
bus stops they all go out in the
different different places and they all
look really like they're all really
close to each other and then on the map
in Google Maps it doesn't really like
you think you're there but you're not
really there when they ask you how you
are but you're not really fine with um
but yeah so I missed buses before
because of
[Music]
that
for yeah
so I
think if you're in Japan for the first
time or even after several times cuz
like look at me I'm the best example try
to avoid buses if you have to find the
station at one of the big hot spots like
Shibuya if you're like more like on the
outskirts and taking a bus and going
like into Tokyo then I think it's easy
and actually pretty
[Music]
comfortable oh by the way in case this
is helpful because depending on the
country I've noticed that like the
system of how to ride a bus even within
a country can be very different so maybe
it's interesting like I mean like where
do you buy a ticket do you buy it before
do you buy it in the BS
is there like a machine in the bus or do
you buy it at the at the bus driver Etc
do you does do they take cash Etc so in
Japan the buses there is two usually
there's two entrances but one is
actually the exit so don't try to enter
from the middle door try you always have
to enter from the front door this is
different in other countries like in
Austria you can enter wherever the
you want but in in in Japan for public
transport they always will make sure
that you have a ticket so by you
entering the bus uh from the front they
make sure that you paid because then at
the front at the bus driver you either
pee touch your your public transport
cart on the there's like a little lit up
little thingy you touch it there or uh
you can buy a ticket there with cash but
it would be preferable if you have one
one of those PE thingies because the bus
drivers they like to go fast they're on
a tight schedule they want to uh you
know they want to be efficient so try to
avoid playing with cash and then i' uh
um usually the bus has like only one
price I guess
so it charges you whatever like 150 250
or so Yen I guess in the beginning but
sometimes I've had buses in Japan where
where at the exit door there's another
PE touch terminal where it will
calculate how far you've been how far
you've traveled and then deduct it from
your card but that depends on the bus
you have to check if there's like a
terminal at the exit if there's no
terminal at the exit and you see like
people walking out of the bus without
touching anything then you're safe you
can just walk out the door
normally
yeah
that's that's when it's a bus that's
payment per Stu but it depends really uh
probably if it's like a bus that goes
really far like even out uh of the city
maybe then it would be a bus like that
but if it's more like a bus that stays
within Tokyo then chances are that it's
not per station but per bus
ride
noted you're
welcome yeah that's something I always
like I get nervous about in other
countries when riding a bus because I
like no idea like I feel like trains are
easy to figure out but then for buses
it's like
H can I buy a ticket at the bus driver
or
not cuz in Austria depending on the city
the bus drivers won't let you buy a
ticket anymore and it's kind of annoying
cuz then the but you can't even buy them
at the bus stations unless the bus
station is at a train
station so if you don't have a ticket
you have to buy it on the phone these
days seemingly if you don't have one
already but if you I'm I'm one of those
people who are a little bit far behind
cuz it's annoying I I didn't set up like
being able to pay it on the on the phone
cuz for the longest time I just had like
a a general ticket that is for a whole
year or
something but now I don't have it
anymore so if I want to take a bus and I
I need to buy a
[Music]
ticket you
know surely it isn't hard to shut up no
it's not but um
wow it's uh you know I wish we had those
IC cards in Austria where you just
charge them up and then you use them for
all public
transport I wish we had that
[Music]
here no we don't have like a chargeable
card but you can get a card that you can
use for any transport in the city
throughout like a whole year or you can
buy a monthly ticket or you can buy
weekly ticket and stuff like that but
there's no chargeable card we have the
same S card system in London oh oh
really I don't remember
that there was a card that you could do
for any transport and all interactions
oh like is that more like a touristy
card a card that aims for
tourists oh on that topic let me tell
you in case anybody is trying to go to
Japan soon Japan has had uh like
problems with issuing new CLE cards
those public transport cards that you
can use to do and don't think about how
much it takes to go to each
station but last time I went it was like
wow I was kind of jelly because I
already I have those cards so I don't
need to buy a new one and I always bring
them to Japan but now for tourists at
the
airport at least I saw it in Nita
Airport I think um there's special SOA
cards for tourists that are like
shortterm that I think either you have
to give them back after you're done
using them or it's only for a certain
amount of time and they have a special
design that's for
tourists it's really cute and I would
have gotten one if I don't already have
one yeah they welcome sua yeah let me
look it up welome comes like
a yes yes there it
is jingle
B there it
[Music]
is I brought mine
back they expire after a certain time
you got one of these a nice they look so
nice cuz the the normal one let me show
you the normal
one it's really well known it's just
this green
one with a penguin on top but that is
like the the kour version in in Osaka
you can get a c that's called eoka it
has a very similar design and then
there's another card that's called pasmo
that a lot of people have all around
Japan the pmo looks like this I don't
know if you can get a pasmo actually I
just hear that you can't get a sua at
the moment maybe also not a
[Music]
pasmo I think it's because um something
about microchips or something so they
have been not able to make these cards
H the standard ones don't expire no I've
been using mine for years and years
yeah and you know what so for these
cards because they're all the same size
there's like merchandise options that I
wish it was a thing all over the world
then I would make it into merchandise
but there's like sua or like Paso
stickers so I used to have like a Kai
collection um s
sticker it was the same size as the and
I put it on top so it had a cute
design and there's more stuff like that
in case you don't like this
design this one's really
[Music]
nice that is just an advice for anybody
who wants to go to
Japan uh in the near
future but let's see so and a welcome
Soo are essentially the same cards but
they're regular Suka requires a 500 yen
deposit while the welcome Suka does not
oh the regular Suka is also not readily
available due to Limited stock but you
can still get the welcome s at specific
train stations and airports
[Music]
easily okay but it's they like what's
the limit what's the time
[Music]
limit
oh the Welcome Circle card is valid for
consecutive 28 days from the day you
start using it upon receiving your
welcome soer you will also be provided
with a reference paper which you can
verify the cards valid Val validity it
is highly recommended to keep the
reference paper review at all times and
present to it present it to staff if
requested well it even says the card
expiration date when you
pee it on the
[Music]
terminals now we know so a month
who was on the C colle you
D you
[Music]
D who looks a little bit like
pom
P
yeah yes P
sister
that's why I was so happy when I saw P's
artist when I saw who it is I was like
oh my God oh my God my favorite cont
collection
characters let's
go still have my expired data SIM card
from Japan in my second Sim
oh too lazy to take it out
huh I wish Germany have that me too
Germany Austria why don't we have this C
system ah so many people use the trans
public transport
without getting a ticket because there's
like only like random
checks okay guys if you ever go to
Austria uh depends on the city I guess
but uh
underground
trains uh buy a ticket cuz the checks
are random at all random times and they
greet you at um the
exit
and for the buses you think you can get
in with no ticket yeah but then randomly
some passenger will will will reveal
themselves as
a ticket Checker and be like dude where
your ticket where is
it so yeah be
careful don't assume that nobody's going
to check it because it looks like it no
you might be you might be
Bamboozled okay let's go Super Chat
thank you kiun I'm glad you had a good
time and I'm jealous about your welcome
S card man give
[Music]
me thank you so much thank you I'm glad
you enjoyed it
[Music]
Le action 18 action for the red chat uh
I feel like everyone said everything I
feel but your 3D Live had me all choked
up so that kind of sums it up you're
still in my Koshi after all these years
and I'm seriously proud of everything
you've done in Hol love you till the
wheels Fall Off
K till the wheels fall off never heard
that expression before am I a
car thank
[Music]
you
love you so much thank you very much for
the support so many years and many more
together
forever together
forever my hands are going quite B
we're here for the long ride oh is that
why there's
Wheels is that
connected here here oh wait let me make
that sound here
[Music]
here thank you
acity Captain meow Bruce D last refresh
sh o you guys I thought I was done what
are you
doing Brandon
d p for the pinky I greatly enjoyed the
3D live on Sunday to the maximum extent
possible while sleeping at 5: a.m. a and
once again don't know what to say but I
can't believe I commissioned 19 waas
this year even if 14 of very glad to
call you my
comos yeah I keep on seeing them you
you're posting all of them now and I'm
realizing oh wow yeah you did commission
a lot of furry
waas well as long as they make you
happy they look pretty I'm just like you
know I can't really use them for
thumbnails but they do look pretty
they're good quality so I'm glad you you
like that I'm glad you like him you do
you you know there's no need to
commission stuff for the sake of like me
using it no if you want to commission
fan art of me that makes you happy that
is totally fine too that is
valid
totally all all good all
good are you going to are you going to
maybe balance the ratio a little little
bit more next year
[Music]
though trying to do a cool hand sign but
it's spazzing
out uh Galaxy D and Tass Mo thank you
for the big red Super Chat D let's see I
really enjoyed your concert it was
simply
amazing
[Music]
another pinky oh my
God stop it
stop
[Music]
stop how did you find me tell me more
tell me
more
[Music]
the
rapole the purple jigle is real just
want to CL oh
interesting it's
real all right guys guys I'm waiting for
an
[Music]
answer
what you got your parking your first
parking ticket
congratulations I
[Music]
guess
faor faden
fenor thank you for the pinky fre life
admission ticket forgot to send doing
the life it was a great show show
lurkers luring ah thank you I'm happy to
hear from lurkers
you you better come out of the Shadows
more
often I want to see you more often show
me yourself more
often you're so beautiful how dare you
not show me that more
often please
please
I'm begging you and you would see my
hands if it wasn't so scuffed but I'm
begging you begging begging
you no the shadows are not cool get out
of there thank you though I'm happy to
hear that you watched it and that you
enjoyed it but it was free you missed
this information I suppose but I
appreciate the support thank thank you
for the
donation take you D soon H the guard D
soon will punish myself severely I don't
deserve
you don't what shut up don't say that
it's all good in this neighborhood and
then red Super Chat oh my God you guys
are not letting me go strike
Dr W thank you for the red chat this was
meant for the end of the year concert
thank you was awesome Merry Christmas oh
it's your also miss out on donating on
time huh thank you doll
yeah it's all already it already feels
like too long
ago I wish I wish this could be more
regular but oh well you know then it
wouldn't be so special anymore thank you
very much and Merry Christmas soon to
you too strike WR your name is hard to
[Music]
say
thank you
soon and Skye than I'm going to go
now I'm going to go I see you
on oh thank you Sean see you on Thursday
for the steam stream ha I hope that
works
[Music]
out
if I don't get the okay until then or if
it will be flat out
theight then I'm well if it will be
denied then we change it to something
else but if it will if there's just no
uh
notification then I might switch
something
around
oh don't worry I have gift
cards of
like 70 80
bucks hopefully that will be enough
we'll just buy them games that are like
five
bucks
yeah
okay okay J say I'll be the same
byebye Wool Wool thank you
okay I'll go on Amazon now
[Music]
make sure to check the Advent calendar
in 3 hours 40
[Music]
minutes
oh dyra are you thinking about ordering
that because I think that one's a good
[Music]
one