[Music]
is
so much more is i love the line so
do me a favor
[Music]
foreign
on your keyboard
[Music]
[Applause]
come a little closer
look at this eye okay
[Music]
is
hey everybody hey hey what's bonnie's
oh don't worry about it don't worry it's
fine
all right i see what a lovely sight you
have some nice bones
examine the skirlings in that enospine
survived one day what a legend
hey we're playing don'ts live together
and if you guys don't know the objective
of the game you should reread the title
because it's in the title
we're supposed to not starve
see how long we can survive for and that
involves uh
foraging for stuff crafting not getting
lost
and working together as a team as you
can see we've already had some deaths
here over on the right
uh i'm doing my job a little too well i
like your skeleton i'll try my best to
guide them
but i don't know yeah emilia is the one
with the most experience playing this
game i think
[Music]
um
we'll find stuff you got to find carrots
and mushrooms
when it gets dark we can go back to the
oh it's getting dark now it's gonna
follow up if you look up at the top at
the top
right corner you can see there's a
little red section that's just like the
twilight
that's like a sunset it's not dark dark
okay
it's not dark
it looks like we're going north so if
you get really hungry you can collect
these seeds on the ground and you can
eat them mushrooms you gotta cook before
you eat them
uh or else you'll get sick oh no oh
and if you collect oh it is never mind
sorry my bed
i like my character he looks like um
like a tim burton character
like someone that johnny depp would play
yeah
i found some [\h__\h] yeah yeah oh can i not
have pumpkins oh yeah
oh the pumpkins those are pretty useful
so like you can use them for
like uh torches torches are really
important if you want to travel at night
oh what is this okay these guys are
angry they're aggro
i'm going to do that oh uh so what
happens
like around day 14 or so there will be
wolves that will try to come attack us
and we have to fight them so we have to
find wood we gotta find trees uh we
gotta find sticks we gotta find rocks
the basics okay
okay let's do this like minecraft yeah
it's like minecraft yeah
okay trees rocks and also [\h__\h]
yes uh the poop you can use to make
farms with to fertilize your crops
oh wow that's innovative
give me this grass oh my god
uh i think this is like a peninsula
thing i don't think there's anywhere to
go up here
okay we'll go back down we got to go
back down anyways to get to the spawn
can you get what you can catch a bird
and eat it but sometimes it'll only give
you feathers instead of giving you meat
ah that's a shame
what are these shadowy creatures what
can i do with spinach i'll collect the
shells oh
when the wolves attack we can hide there
and then they'll like attack them
and then they'll fight back sorry
my my johnny depp character is saying
i'm so
uh hungry i have berries for you if it
meet we'll we'll meet at the spawn
somebody's gonna share our responses
though okay i love that skeleton is
still just here
all right here's berries for whoever is
really good
thank you i have those thank you i'll
take them how do i eat them do i just
click them
right you can drag them over yourself
you guys want to stay in the light oh no
it's like
[Music]
i got confused
if you go to the spawn beacon and you
click on it uh
you can't oh you had six calories yeah i
did
were you supposed to make a fire oh yeah
i got it i'll come i'm going to wait
i think we're going to go i don't know
it's okay
we're okay i got fire nice i know we had
six
the next time when you guys have sticks
and flints you just find it right away
on the floor you can make a torch
nice i really want that cool nice that's
lucky
okay wait okay
oh my gosh they're so you can eat raw
carrots that's a good thing
oh and picking flowers if you find any
flowers it'll help your brain juice
oh brain juice cool i need a bit of wait
we lose all our stuff yeah we gotta pick
it up it's on the floor pick it up like
minecraft
flowers like where we died
and if you pick up 12 flowers you can
make a flower hat
also cool i want a flower hat
for my my little johnny's character
he would look nice in a flower a flower
hat i think pick this flower
would have to be the same flower i know
they just be anything
you guys just explore and then i'll make
a vase for us so
we don't hide when it turns tonight
again
oh give me that yeah
[Music]
girl you okay oh i'm bringing company
i got coffee how many are we talking how
many i think they got boy
how many weapons are i wonder how we
make weapons
i know
let's see weapons fight it's under fight
you can make a spear
so if you collect uh grass but i need to
make i need to make a
a science machine okay i'm gonna go back
to this flight i've got seeds don't eat
seeds
you can get this rabbit to come over to
our camp so someone can kill it
i guess we need to find our audience
guys i might turn loud to you now
because my audience said i'm too quiet
but maybe i'm too loud for you guys now
you're so good to me perfect now yes
okay
i'm glad where did everyone go i'm
trying to drive this rabbit over to our
camp
so that we can kill it how do we gather
what why can't they just be if you find
uh
like a twig bush it's like a little
thing sticking up out of the ground
how do i kill a rabbit a flower hat uh
you have to catch it so if you make
grass you take grass you can make a trap
and then you can trap the rabbit and you
can kill it with your bare hands
really cool if i make grass
oh you gotta collect the grass and you
guys have like red
okay i'm gonna make up what we need now
if any of you guys have flint and sticks
you can make an
axe and start collecting wood and then
with the wood
i can make a machine that can make us a
bunch more stuff cool
i don't i i have an empty elixir do you
need that
uh it kind of sounds useless
all right i'll go back to exploring then
i have a crystal ball i wonder if that
doesn't i got something that's useful
uh can i make the trap with paw fall
fangs fox fangs how did you pronounce
that
full fangs yeah it sounds like a
halloween costume
yes just
this house right now i'm too loud [\h__\h]
sake you're fine to me
are these pigs nice uh there are nice
pigs actually some
some don't attack you guys get satisfied
carrots
i'm scared usually pigs are like
carnivores so you gotta give them
something
okay hello all right i'll make a pizza
i got berry bushes i should have
collected more rocks
i need all right i'm giving you guys a
job
who's here i'm here hello okay you you
take that
you you guys collect the wood okay
go chop down some trees no no no no no
no no no we'll do leave it to me
oh there's a turkey can i light the
turkey on fire
can i will they let me in their house uh
no that you can't go in the house
i'm gonna drop torches at the spawn for
you guys okay or i'll drop one torch
uh you guys take care of it i think i
have i think i have a light
it'll do ah oh yeah if you have a
lighter you uh
might be able to use it okay i'll stick
with you then
okay okay that's good and if you guys
have any quick then
you can make your own torch too yeah
what does what does the flower do
uh when you pick up a flower it
increases your sanity
so it's good and you can also use it to
make a hat it helps your sanity
wow that's random on the ground right
oh yeah yeah you can get it from rocks
too uh if you make a pickaxe
you always get flip from rocks oh okay
i'm gonna i think i have enough to
um i need two pieces of wood and six
more rocks to make where's that ghost
permanent fire
who is that ghost oh that's like a
friend that's like your i think it's
supposed to be like your dentist or
something
did you see that hey look there's
something in the ground oh there are
many things oh
oh there's sticks what the hell
race dirty oh wait we can attack them
goodbye
[Laughter]
i ah build a campfire so i'm going to go
back to the base and i'll build a
campfire there
good idea yeah let's fall back let's go
back
good idea you follow the path you walk
way faster
i see it now let me out of the map
art style is very cute i like it it's
all it's on bro
wait what is that on their mind is that
okay go maybe with something we could
eat the most
it's okay i have i have six stones
oh oh you have friends can i eat this
mandrake
happy girl yeah but it'll put you to
sleep oh and not a huddle
i think you have to kill it i did it's
down nice wait watch
this you can turn that off uh because
you'll run out of fuel and you're
lighter i think i don't know
also you can cook stuff here so if you
have like the mushroom or you can cook
seeds to give you more
oh i have i have carrots
you want carrots you can cook carrots
you just
click it in your inventory and then
click on the fire with it
in your mouth wakey wakey
nice yeah you can switch
orientation of your character too uh-oh
okay everybody oh no i think we're just
gonna stay on the fire right oh my god
the shadow scared me that the shadow of
the tree scared me fire
i have one here i'll just drop what i
have because i don't know what it does
okay yeah we got a glove
there's a monkey paw what does that do
i don't know i have i found this i can
tell this
i think you can you can cook pretty much
everything
cool butterfly
oh somebody gave me carrots yes
yep uh you can make healing potion but
uh it's a bit difficult so like
if you find a spider web you wanna you
wanna collect
spider web from the spider nest and uh
it's kind of dangerous but once you
build
traps out of grass you can catch the
spiders and they give you spiderweb and
you use that to make a fishing rod
and you catch fish and then the fish
make they make good heels
oh okay they heal you yeah i got like
oh spiders that sounds really good nice
could be useful i don't think that i
don't think
yeah i don't think we can use that oh no
she just died i saw that
girl oh no i had a tentacle
that wasn't mine i don't know in a sauce
so yeah you're probably in the swamp
areas in the swamp area if you walk
by too slow uh there were tentacles in
the ground look at your stuff
no what the heck what is that
oh i'll take i'll take stuff i'll go
back to this oh your friend's
tentacles here i'll leave some what is
it
what is this hand
a hand there he's being a stage hand
it's like a table with
some flowers around it oh uh don't touch
don't take the flower
don't talk oh i but i did i did take a
flower oh
welcome back to the land of the living
buddha yeah
am i curious i think you're sanity so if
you check your brand
meter at the top you should be able to
see whether your sanity is going down
actively and if it is it might be that
the thing you picked up
okay there's a frog on my tail
sewing okay stomach okay brain
yes what is the other one
uh what stomach brain and health so much
more no not november
i can plant a tree i found some nuts
okay
uh yeah you some some of the tree nuts
you can eat them
but sometimes if you don't plant it okay
bad things will happen bad things
yeah i have to pick them up and i have a
full movement
yeah you're lighter oh
okay that's the only thing i could see
from there
[Music]
i brought you some wood oh thank you i
already got some
um but i'll pick it up if you just leave
it there nothing will be on like
minecraft stuff let's put it on the
ground
forever i'll put your lighter body uh
[Music]
no you gotta make a pickaxe left
that's pretty easy i bet you have enough
to make it leads to my new
berries jimmy
no goddamn why do the rabbits sound like
time to die
a turkey i found a big turkey kill it
i'm oh yeah i won't give up
i'm used to chasing things with sharp
objects uh oh
all right see we have a fire at the base
if you guys get there and uh
there's no fire you just put grass or
wood or anything that you can burn in
in the fire and it'll you know like
all that big one's just going home okay
i could really
fellas are the pigs dangerous
uh the ones who try to attack you are
dangerous
there are some nice pigs okay you'll
know right away
actually the pigs if you give them like
a piece of meat to eat they'll be your
friend
and they'll trap they'll chop trees for
you oh
we'll have a sweet of them let's see
where they're going
okay thanks if you guys are standing
near this science machine i made here
you see that new tabs appeared
on the left side so now you can make the
rope you can refine
uh you can make rope you can use that to
make traps and you can catch
bunnies and spiders and frogs thanks
an episode of dr stone nice going watson
probably literally carrying yes here's
what i was going to say
thank you amelia most helpful
oh wow oh
probably go lower anybody on some trap
oh you can use that
you just you just put it down on the
ground and it'll like be automatic
okay i'm gonna go catch some rabbits
it's gonna get dark soon so just be
careful oh these cats
okay mama oh my god
i guess we should collect some poop too
yeah i have some
i have five shits here we go
there five whole [\h__\h] i think
jamaica to make farms well you need the
seeds that you get and then
stones and fertilizer but uh oh yeah
right here food you can just make one
here
i love we have enough our camp is just
surrounded by skellingtons and ships
it sounds about right we can destroy the
skeleton so you can it feels like home
really i like decorative yeah they're a
reminder of our
our humble beginnings how about that
oh a backpack you can make it uh uh you
gotta refine your rope
and then i think it's under survival you
can make uh
not the candy bag no it might be grayed
out because it might not have enough
sticks to grab
on flying i guess it's not real it's
just uh just grass
i think there's a more advanced backpack
you can make with that can you make
things like
chests in this in this game so that we
can yeah you can make chests
okay cool because i have messages
i saw on the night is gonna
progressively get longer and longer and
so you just have to survive
you can kind of still explore at night
if you have like a torch or something
uh but it's better to just stay here and
cook or sleep you can make a sleeping
bag and sleeping at
in the night time it increases your
sanity levels if you're getting low
okay okay and
i think my salary levels are always low
what was that if anybody ever wants to
sleep there's a sleeping bag here but
it's better not to do it now because
it's going to turn day time and you'll
wake up immediately but you can do it
when it's in the red
the sunset time you can sleep then too
nice
i'll work on i'm trying to heal if you
guys want to fight stuff if you find any
spiders
you can trap the spiders you can fight
them
and then we can use the spider web and
we'll go fishing
oh yeah nice idea bye bye
all right we'll meet up again at night
okay sounds good i'll go do i'm
following you i'll go do some important
things okay
i love exploring do you have a trap
i do put it down anywhere around the
pond and then go
near that frog and make it aggressive
put it down
okay and now go to the frog and like
tease him you want to taunt him
and then he'll follow you and you'll be
ugly
nice words yeah and welcome walk over
the trap
past it tongue looks funny my standards
smell
that you smell like pond
i can make my flowers now you get frogs
like you can cook it and eat them oh
yummy
not raw though you don't want to crop
chicken sticks
i need some food where have i ended up
at yeah we gotta make a chest and like
store food in there or something because
good idea oh god
yes seeds kiara eat seeds you're a bird
you can eat
but seeds prefer fried chicken you know
i don't think there's any chicken in
this game but there are turkeys pretty
similar yeah
you can't run i've cornered him i've
cornered oh no
no it's in the water pick up soggy
drumstick
no it's in the water give me this i made
one you can make one too
guys if it's in the water what do i do
it's in the water
yeah so i killed it next to the next to
the the sea
and no fish it's not for you pick up
soggy drumstick no it's not for you
i keep running towards the water and
it's not letting me pick up the
nope oh uh yeah you can't go into the
water unless you have a boat
oh sorry kelly you're hardworking boats
yeah you can make boats and we can like
sail the sea but it's pretty dangerous
so i don't think we're ready for that
yet
pick it up as long as we have good eye
the sea is not dangerous for us
oh that's true it's pretty cool
somebody has to control the anchor and
somebody has to control like the
steering wheel
or like the sail or something like that
you can totally do that
she is made for that oh yes all at the
same time
i have many twigs yay
ah you desperately need food god damn it
uh okay i'll go back i'll have i have
some food we should
we should make some we should make a
crock pot
we gotta burn trees crock pot
yeah and you could you can put four
ingredients in there you can make all
these like different
recipes and stuff and then you can make
like cupcakes you can make meatballs
sandwiches and
fried turkey how about that fried turkey
try to make a turkey meal i don't i
think
you go you can make chicken nuggets you
can make chicken nuggets really that's
classic yeah but you need honey from
bees oh i just literally ate my honey
oh it's really good for heels so chicken
nuggets they give you like a lot of
picture
i did it didn't though it did not
that's not the honey by itself okay
oh well oh we're gonna build something
now
nice where is home
uh we want to make a functioning base we
got to have like
a food source we gotta have somewhere to
store the food
we gotta have defense stuff so if you
guys wanna like
that's a piece of stuff on the left side
make whatever you want
oh i'll help you find him not lost
i am not i got the money what are you
lost
i am already back i think oh yeah you're
here you're here
yeah i attend a girl oh my gosh there
you go wait
oh i should use the map i forgot
[Music]
maybe i have something useful for you uh
i have a bunch of rocks
and twigs maybe i should keep them here
and you can use it to build off if you
want huh this is kind of cool
are you okay gina uh we're back
okay we're good
uh if anybody wants to sleep if you're
if your brain juice is low you can pick
up this sleeping bag here and you can
start sleeping now but it'll take your
hunger so you got to make sure you got
like a
decent amount earlier i think i'll wait
with that
and not do it right now i'm really
hungry
i didn't notice how hungry i was i do
have one
uh chicken leg though drumstick wow
oh i'm gonna make chicken nuggets
i'm messing up the flames i think uh i
ate some bad weekends
didn't know i had such something so
useful the whole time
i can make a compass is that useful
we're going to pick
i don't think so all right i mean we
haven't we have a map so it's
why are these lanterns lit up are they
always were they always lit up
no i put them there a moment ago
why is the game audio getting louder is
that is something
i hear something too
oh i only hear the flies from the poop
yeah
i kind of wanted to stop
do you have any wood i can make chassis
away
i have a ton of i have logs yeah yeah
yeah
there you go thank you wow
i did a lot of chopping today
okay we have oh we have enough to make
one now we can make rope
chests okay let's put the chest over
here pick up flowers where are flowers
uh there there are some flowers down
south
and to the east also
get out check here but it's still not
night right now right it's still
twilight
uh it's about to turn tonight
fires really small huh i can make a fire
you guys
you guys ever have any wood you can add
uh
you can add uh planks to it and it'll
like make this big fire like this
nice oh i have planks i can make stone i
can make a chest
does anybody do we need another chest
this guy
oh yeah the chest the chest is
can i come meet you
there's a table following me the table
where i took the flower from
a table
where are you kiara where are you all
the way up here
there you are uh did the table follow me
though
i don't think oh what are you talking
about
but it was there it wasn't there i'm not
crazy
look at my table huh do you see my table
as well
something's odd here but i can't put my
finger on it it's just a table though
it's going to attack us in the night can
actually if you make a hammer you might
be able to oh
yeah oh that's what the yellow was i was
burning i was burning myself alive
i didn't realize oh you're standing in
the fire yeah i didn't know that uh
getting nice and warm really close to
the fire would do that
i could i have a job for you come here
okay
no i'm really looking like johnny depp
all right take this oh god
don't equip it yet but take it what's in
this tree
all right i'll wait don't equip it yeah
yeah
and now i want you to come over here
equip it and set these
these scraggly trees on fire oh
but of course wait wait
i need good chocolate baby bye disco
inferno
thank you oh i'm happy you finished that
yes
that was not i got you goddammit
i'll please something oh that's it yeah
is there anything i should be these
trees are on fire
what a waste of wood yeah you're telling
me ah
you can catch frogs you know have you
tried that before i can show you how
oh yes i did i got a chop
so if you find a frog by a pond you just
put the trap down anywhere near the frog
and then you
you bait the frog into into walking into
the trap
i look perfect now i can't wait to show
you all my hair
wow my ghost is so smart to kill it
kills my my frogs for me
oh yeah the ghost will attack your stuff
cool like i found vitamins
i love my ghosts my ghost is amazing two
flints
nice
nice thank you i think so too
looking good thank you where did i even
get my ghost from i don't know
i mean you don't have the post right
like i
don't know what was the question you
don't you don't have
you play the same character but you
don't have the ghost right oh yeah
because uh
if you there's like a flower in my
inventory and if i click on it i can
summon the ghost but i have i just
haven't done it yet i probably should
hmm
seeds
oh wait hungry i found a bunch of good
stuff
need one more flower hat
yeah let's all get matching flower hats
perfect
[Music]
83 but my hunger is still not very
good looking i'm oh yeah
pots now so we can make more stuff you
know did you want me to show you how to
catch the froggies
although i i i i thought
okay okay
let's try it what's here oh that's a
really scary looking giraffe thing
what was that what did you find here
what is this
i don't know why is all the audio
getting louder
is something am i dying what
uh that might be sanity what's your
sanity level set
up which one is that bringing hover over
the brain with your mouse we'll tell you
a number
thirty thirty oh okay uh where are you
come to me i'll give you a present
makes me sleep i found a man jacket
oh yeah you can feel it but yeah it'll
make you sleep if you eat it
is that what you think i mean i kind of
do need to sleep uh
here you go ah where's that
oh that hurts thank you
you're welcome getting done making food
we need to wake up
we need to kill rabbits we need to kill
frogs
and we need stuff to fill the crock pot
with probably should make some weapons
oh i have uh i have some mushrooms yeah
yeah yeah
any vegetables do you like carrots that
you find that's really carrots
yeah just let me hunt
i just need like a few more twigs and i
can make one i need three more times
here i have some i have five twigs
i'm useful thank you you're welcome it's
just a kiss
by the way or control click on something
uh you can have it
oh and then like oh okay cool
how big is this map like this is uh it
is
yeah it's pretty big gotta move your dog
[Music]
all right now if you feel the crock pot
uh usually like it's
uh as long as you don't put anything in
edible in there it should make
something suffer
if you put too much monster meat chester
oh chester yeah i thought that yeah that
wait who found chester
you that's chester is that goodness
i don't know what's wrong did you pick
up a bone
i found this
okay i don't know the following do you
still need some twigs
i know i have a ton okay thank you
um what's the chest oh okay
ah we can cook it there now okay yeah
yeah so if you put a bunch if you can
put like different vegetables and stuff
together
there you go different recipes it
doesn't tell you the recipes
me too i don't know
it's okay you can you can you can okay
wait why am i oh i'm hungry me too what
should we do i'm very hungry as well
can i eat the seeds uh wait do we have
anything cooking okay i'll make
something with you
okay yes chef please why am i so hungry
i'm just gonna put
monster meat in there oh the monster
means
uh oh does anybody have whatever maybe i
can cook it
i'll just
oh you guys can cook your seeds
if you cook yourself does that give you
bug more
more hunger oh maybe not actually i
think it does i
think it does what i was looking at was
hp hey
watson how do you make uh weapons
because i feel like if i had a weapon
then i could kill a bunch of things and
get us a bunch of meat
actually there's a spear right here on
the floor i don't know whose this is but
you see this spirit i'm standing next to
it yeah pick it up and you can use that
you can equip it you can attach them
cool okay let me see how i let me try
and pick it up who's
who's the hungriest right now what are
you what are you guys hunger levels
need rocks to make a hammer does anybody
else have a flint
but i see i see the rock i see i'm going
to take your rocks
i'm feeling refreshed i stopped like
really well
damn and i have full hunger now
there it is okay nice i can get oh
thanks
let's go sorry to have you make
everything watson
but i promise i'll kill a bunch of
things oh oh yes
it's gone never mind i was thinking i
think i can make you a spear though
where do i come i gotta get one
oh i'm super hungry let's see uh what
can i eat
oh we jumped over my trap thank you
cool who seems
nice nice it doesn't know oh piggy
thank you perfect i'll go kill some
things welcome
will they will they kill me for doing
that i wonder
um man i need
them no leave my ghost alone come with
me ghosty
come with me come with me don't kill no
no no
[Music]
wait so the stuff everything like
respawns every day
uh not every day there's like a cycle
some depending on what it is it might
take a few days to come back
yeah not every day
what the hell
is this winter frog so dangerous
yeah they take items from you too when
they attack you oh you're
joking
you're kidding me i found a spider nest
um
the pig is so nice to try to kill the
spiders for me
uh he killed maybe one i got some silk
oh nice yeah we can use that to make the
stuff
did that treat you like stuff stuff's
good
i probably shouldn't try to kill the
spiders on my own right it's probably
gonna
kill me uh you don't have to kill them
you can you can make uh the flower traps
sorry i don't always have flowers you
can make the grass traps and then you
can
uh put them down on the ground and then
walk into the traps
and oh i killed them oh i killed
all the spiders you killed oh with your
ghost
with my ghost and my pickaxe i got like
a bunch of meat and spiders
silk how do i make it
that meat you have to you can put like
one in each recipe in the crock-pot
otherwise it'll make you sick
okay hey uh amelia how does one make a
trap
to catch the rabbits uh you need
uh grass and twigs and then you gotta go
next to the science machine in the base
got it okay i think that's maybe the
next thing i gotta try and do damn oh my
goodness how do you catch a rabbit do
you just put the tracks on
yeah you gotta it's kind of hard to
catch one because like they're so
fast but what you can do is you want to
put the trap stand on the hole and then
put the trap like right on the hole so
then when they go back in and when they
come out
they they trigger the trap and they run
into it
damn he really hurt yeah i'm in some big
trouble because i'm super hungry right
now i'm trying to catch these rabbits
but uh
i'm sucking really bad gotta make a trap
watching rabbits is more of like a
long-term thing
like uh you can't catch them right away
you probably have to come back and
check on the trap like a day later gotta
check it out
eat the berries eat the berries oh
my dude it's fine i'll find other things
to kill
if you find um spiders you can kill
those you can kill frogs
the turkeys moles
there's like little mole wrap thingies
cool oh that mushroom is happy to see
look at that there's so many spiderness
i'm gonna die can we eat spiders
i have spider meat yeah oh but we have
to cook it with a recipe
yeah i'm going back now
and we can cook some stuff so we can all
eat yes let's have dinner two together
my ghost keeps like putting up a fight
with these spiders but it's
like killing everything legitimately wow
so strong ah i love my ghosts
i'm bringing home all the meats oh nice
one you know
yeah no but didn't die it's kind of dope
i almost killed it get in there
i can't bubble shoot
[Music]
okay uh i'll make food now thank you
chef
[Music]
the mandrakes are really good they like
give you i didn't know they give you
full hp
yeah so goofing up completely
thank you thanks watson uh okay i'll
make it up to you
i'll actually kill a bunch of things
you'll see okay
you'll see i will be useful
wait did my experience
oh it's a teddy bear i was wondering
what though that was nice
whoa oh so bright
and all my saturday's dropping too
lonely
god damn it always picking a fight
abigail
can we just can we just live in
happiness together with these
i wonder creatures the other way to like
unsummon the ghost because i i know
you have to summon it i don't know if
it'll ever go away though there must be
a way
if you guys ever need more stories you
can pick up this bone and
this little chester guy this little
monster doggie
he'll follow you and if you click on him
he has a storage
oh yeah rocks
nice oh nice i got tools now
babies progress baby
all right so if uh i can give you guys
some tasks if you're like what should i
do
sure what should i do i'll give you some
tips uh
your task is to go collect a bunch of
rocks and there's a rock
area if you go to the east and then
and you go south yeah so it's a whole
rock area
i don't know if you can see it on the
map but it's like a desert looking area
you can collect all those rocks oh yeah
assistant
okay uh how do we boost our sanity again
fish something uh boosting sandy you
have to sleep but if you are hungry then
uh you'll wake up immediately or you can
collect flowers
picking bars really happens with your
sand if you find anything ah
okay but there's a there's a sleeping
bag it'll be in the chest
oh oh i'm sleeping once okay good well
uh is it when as soon as it reaches
morning you'll wake up so you just wanna
next time when you sleep you sleep in
the red time
at the start to get as much out of the
sleeping bag as possible we can make
more those are really
um okay nice
chat does it looks like it could be
something uh
delicious all right time to kill things
uh
take out the butterflies if you guys
collect any vegetables or mushrooms or
berries those are things
uh that you can put in a crock pot i'm
not sure
yeah you just make it'll make like
meatballs if you have two meats in there
and those are really
healing nice
nope wait how do you put it
i'm going to put it in the crock pot not
my mouth
i think we might um be getting attacked
soon i thought i heard it yeah
oh yeah oh what is that what that what
what
you guys
somebody tell me why did you have 2 000
health
oh oh
no that's it uh does it happen to look
like a
giant teddy bear yes
[Music]
run north follow the path north and go
into the beefalos and like stand
on them i need more berries
[Music]
okay
it's gone okay i'm still looking for
flowers
i definitely need flowers
oh thing coming oh i don't have a good
feeling about this
i hear the
just come come up north follow the path
and run into the beefalo you'll be safe
okay can we kill the wolves yeah you can
attack them
sick you can make armor
or you can make grass armor too
oh they're they're coming grass armor
huh
okay i can make that oh
god this is so bad oh
dear run gonna hide him wait what is it
what is that noise the
the room wolves the wolves when they
start their homes
i made i made two fishing rods if
someone wants to have one i'll put one
of these
here oh my god
that's a wolf
[Music]
there are a lot of wolves
thank you for protecting me
i had like two wolves running up to me
but my ghost protected me
and now i'll go fishing nice hi kelly i
stole it
are you still alive you know oh it's the
wolf
should i can i fish anywhere or should i
go to fish somewhere where i see some
shadows
in the uh and you also want to fish in
the pond so we have upon
a pond pond pretty close to spawn
and you'll see how it works it's just
like finishing the game okay
yay die loser are you here you know
oh yeah i'm very far i just kept running
is flimsy right what
what that's quick
all right nice job kelly yeah that was
interesting
we got you yeah so and when you make the
recipes in the crock-pot you can only
put oh no oh no
i'm really not doing well huh oh why is
the earth shaking
can i eat this you can eat meat
oh i'm dead why are there meteors
oh eating the meat killed me
is immediate oh no i guess the meat must
have been poisoned survive
oh yeah
oh lol
that's okay it happens it's okay
it happens to the best ah only fish in
ponds okay wasn't that a pond ah
you mean the really small ones really
small
okay okay hold on one second i gotta get
the berries so i can make more
what was it crock pot oh yeah yeah yeah
in the crock pot
oh no there are wolves at the campsite
watch out should i come to kill them
yes i'll use
behind chester finally
did you suggest that name to the game um
there's free ghosts now what the hell
[Music]
hmm
[Applause]
and i want
can you cook never mind that's a stupid
question you can put a stick
in food but it'll it'll change into
something less uh filling
like only one stick you can put oh
okay can someone light up the the
crock-pot
oh i think it just goes automatically
once you put enough stuff in it
ah there we go no oh oh who put in those
carrots
i can build a shovel or a pitchfork
why did i eat it oh i ate the monster
meat
bad idea yeah you're fine i learned from
my
life i can make so many things i can
make an
axe i can make a pickaxe i can make a
shovel what should i make
i can make a pitchfork i can make a
razor oh
why would i want to shave my face though
my face is perfect like
that's a long shadow i think you can
shave your beard and like put it
up oh yeah right now
you know yes please now sure
why do you keep up uh
i want skins too
the server will drop you like some stuff
you can put like different clothes
we're talking about armor you want armor
no i want the skins
but also armor and i still don't
understand how i can make it back what
exactly do i need
it doesn't look up i only find thank you
what is that
okay it's a hand is
where is this game like what is the
story where what's the lord
i'm trying to survive actually i don't
know what it is i don't know maybe chad
can tell us
what's the lord yeah what's the matter
what is your lore
there is no lore
i wonder what we need in
uh we need to build an alchemy machine
but to build an alchemy machine
we need electric dudettes and you can
get those by like smashing
sometimes you might just find them but
you gotta like smash some stuff that you
find like the
there's like really weird gear stuff you
can you can make a refrigerator in this
game but
i don't remember how to get all the
materials for it
because your food your food has a shelf
life it will go bad
nice oh yeah
mine
faster
rabbits
you ate the berries you stupid piece of
[\h__\h]
oh my berry
i eat you as berries that's how it's
supposed to be hang on
i have an idea okay oh my god there's so
many
wait where is everyone i am
in rockland i'm in frogland
stay hydrated how do we stay hydrated in
this game
i got it did you also just get a super
chat saying stay hydrated yeah i did
me too that's spooky
at the same time they're telling us to
stay hydrated how sweet of them thank
you
thank you i need to drive the rabbits
away from where the holes are if i have
a trap here
anyway yeah i shall stay hydrated
no no no the other way rabbit the other
way
okay i'm making a bunch of food all
right have you caught anything
no turn it down another place i can get
a pickaxe
huh i will catch you if you need some
enough uh
i'm kind of far oh okay
you sure you'll find them in the same
area where like you find flowers
why not oh morsel what is this
oh my god oh my god
i thought i saw much stuff at the base
oh
yes i caught a rabbit
let me get my
i murdered it i can still use it
a pond wait drop that can i eat
can i rock and eat at the same time no
that was
[Music]
oh i'm fishing for the first time in my
life
my favorite okay i have two gloves can i
make something now
i have two abigail chill uh that's
something
all right we're making a rabbit tonight
baby
identity how many pickled peppers
i could carry they use those gloves why
can't i cook them
i have this wait uh cook what i'm trying
to cook the rabbits that i killed but i
only have two oh yeah
ah did you murder i have a i don't have
anything to put in there you need to
fill the rest of the slots it's got to
be four so if you have like berries or
carrots or mushrooms
one monster meat or one steak you can
put those in there okay
let me see what i can do yeah yeah
what is that i have more
more seeds oh you killed one
wait dress click something oh you can
put it in the crock pot if you want
it'll make
um tasty meatballs
oh yeah i really want meatballs now
hungry
i don't know how how how does it work
the fishing yeah it says hook and then i
click on it one time or
oh yeah yeah you
uh put it in the pond and then minecraft
i got it okay i never i never even uh
fished in minecraft
i got a fresh water fish now oh
here i don't want to eat all these
meatballs myself who's the husband it
has
it has meatballs too oh okay me too
there's nothing left i'm saving my
meatballs
[Music]
good idea i'll save mine too okay
you know you're so low
it's okay living life on the edge okay
if we find any spider glands we can make
like this
uh potion it's a healing potion we need
spider glands
allen do you need food i'm okay for now
i'm gonna wait until it gets real low
and then i'll eat my meatballs
yeah oh cool good idea i'm gonna catch
some more rabbits though cause that was
fun
you think just like green yeah
i brought some ice what can we do
make some tasty drinks um i think you
can make
like a you can use it in recipes i know
you can put it in the crock pot but
i don't know i think you might be able
to make a ice cream or like some sort of
drink with it too
you gotta have like a different ice
you can make cupcakes in this game
you gotta like look up the rest you
gotta like google the recipe
wait a saddle does that mean you can
ride stuff you can like
uh i don't know maybe
yeah a murder boat it's so [\h__\h]
kawaii
yeah not with a saddle
oh my god that was that was
funny-looking
no you did like a weird pose oh i messed
up
gorilla i'm just eating okay
your character is cute i'm trying to not
starve okay thank you i like that you
understand about hey there's nothing
wrong with starving we all have flower
crowns
except for you kiara and
[Music]
yeah gotta join the team i really want
to grow the beard so i really look like
a real johnny depp character
you can also then you can shave the
beard and like turn it into a jacket or
something
yeah let's build a boat what should we
do wait what build the boat whoa
actually i'm gonna go catch some more
rabbits but you guys
talk about building the boat while i go
catch these rabbits
i just think a bunch of wood need planks
oh
but if you guys buy two we need a bunch
of wood to make boats so
as much wood as you can collect you like
chopped ones
yeah yeah all right no that's my
backpack
finally i made a backpack finally
10 years later congratulations
just took me 5 million years birth trap
who would ever make a bird trap
that's no we're back
oh you're asking how to get a chicken
that's how you get uh some chicken you
get a little uh
chicken legs from them no no no no no
that's not a good way
no this is too much there um their area
oh wait i left the i love the truck down
there i wonder if anything got caught in
it
[Music]
murder town look at it
oh no dead all right
top top top
how much wood do we need a bunch wood
you can get
yeah okay okay
we probably need like uh
uh probably like thirty or forty
five points
i should probably store some more things
i still got all my silk and spider
glands
oh i can heal myself farm glands is that
for the heart or for the hunger
oh yeah yeah it's for uh healing it's
for we can make like a healing style for
anybody who's low hp
and you just it's really easy you just
need rocks and ash and i have some ash
so
oh first time with the traps on top of
the holes
yeah that takes a long time i'm just
supposed to wait for them
yeah you can get by burning down like
little bushes or grass
because anything you put on the floor
will probably turn into ash
oh do i burn it down with my torch yeah
oh you just want to make sure fire
travels like between things you got to
make sure
maybe it wasn't like
just hold space you can hold space and
does it
oh you hold space what yeah oh
i didn't know i kept clicking i don't
like that yet yeah me too
well it's a lot it's a lot more comfy
hello
no yeah that was a lost cause i got
vampire teeth
why does it take so long fishing
the burning oh yeah it takes water
damn number two rabbits
i'm starting to get that catching
rabbits
oh you caught a few yep oh but i'm sorry
i think i have a rabbit trap here eat my
meat kidding me
burning the tree thing didn't work ah
yeah you gotta you gotta burn like
little things like uh like
a grass bush or if you have twigs you
can
you can drop individual twigs uh i think
with
a button i see okay i got the grass
okay yeah i don't remember where i put
my rabbit trap oh no
i think you should you might be able to
see it on the map oh
good good uh maybe i have it
i found it right oh no let me give it
back to you
that's what i've been using this whole
time to catch wrap
no it's totally fine
you can have the meatballs that we that
we make with the
rabbits yeah you can have
gosh i keep going the them way
oh i was just like man i really lose
stuff so easy
gosh here i'm dropping it on the ground
it's only gone 25 left
[Music]
oh sorry oh you're good you're good do
your thing ina
do your thing i'm glad we have enough
stuff to put inside the pot
yeah just put a lot of berries i like
hunting it's simple and
and i can do it they're good
i never knew science is such an
important part of survival is this
literally doctor
i'm not wearing the potion in the menu
you go good at
the oh the uh it's under survival under
the little rope
it's like at the top it's called healing
south
ah okay got it
whoa twigs
goodnight whoa
wow i'm like a professional survivor
damn
[Music]
my what the wood other word i have no
one for you
i'm amazed with myself i think this is
because my mom was like a survivor mom
so
i think i learned it from him i have a
survival mom
really she taught me the ways yeah she
can do anything
with with no tools she survives in the
in the wilderness that's kind of cool
yeah my mom is a survival mom
you're not friends you're probably
watching right now
we're cool mom
[Music]
mom get the camera look i have so many
friends
all my stuff no okay how do i get okay
i don't know it's the third one four
three two one it's
oh it's hunger oh it's dead
i was trying to medium
i thought you needed eggplant for that
welcome back to the land of the living
good huh
all right present yeah this requires
more science
oh god why don't you make a little chat
the hands they're trying to steal our
fire you gotta step on them
okay
die
i remember when you showed me that and i
was absolutely terrified and
uh death is terrified by german fairy
tales oh my god look
there i have limits okay listen
i don't want this pinecone it's
interesting that things spoil in this
game too
yeah i gotta cook my monster meat
goddammit i need some
some berries i have berries i'll put
some i'll put
three berries in there okay
thank you oh yeah
okay another door a suitable place to
put
our water stuff i think this is no this
is not the ocean
what we might make another base by the
water because that's we're gonna put the
wait do you have my boat i took it
okay it's mine very nice spoil it
i'll leave it at the base
i gotta try it i'm gonna build it i
don't know what it does oh
one meat in the pot if someone wants to
add a berries you can make a crock pot
okay a meatball cool cool
oh
i just need some stone and i can move
stuff over
oh oh i'm on my way to get some snow now
oh stop wait yes don't you know where
are you collecting some stones
oh yeah i have seven rocks oh can i have
some
yes i'm on my way back out
i need my potions man that's fine
i'll survive because i have my ghost
let's go i'll leave them in the chest
i also have rocks if you want them yes
please oh
dirty that's nice yep
oh yeah i have a [\h__\h] ton of frog legs i
got 16 frog legs
if someone needs food i i got too much
all right well you can make a sand you
can make frog like sandwiches with those
fruits oh hell no
have you guys ever had real frog like
before
no don't they taste like chicken from
what i've heard that just tastes like
chicken
i tried it once but it was at like a
really uh shady buffet and it tastes
really gross oh my god i'm not surprised
have you guys said sure it was really
crock like
snails it was a frog like it was a frog
like yeah
yeah it's like
i prefer fried chicken but okay you go
with what you like
so what exactly do we need to make a
frog sandwich i got to the frog
i just put one frog leg in there already
i put berries you can make one sorry
um yay i have so much meat that we can
do
health is a little low though but it's
fine
my hunting is going does someone
want um some meat like
actual cooked meat
for now but maybe later we should save
it for now
melting ice oh no back up
trap go to my trap the meatballs are in
the chest if someone needs them
no darn it what is what is
oh eyes never mind in them but that
didn't even make a sandwich that made
the same thing as before exiting out of
the game
no no darn it
that was expected give me my trap i'll
continue tomorrow
i got so much meat
quick questions
so if i put four meats into the pot will
it still only make one meatballs for
everyone
uh yeah yeah so it's good to like uh
there's like a balance so if you put
like two meats and two vegetables it
should make meatballs but if you
put like too many vegetables and it'll
be like a vegetable based dish
but you can use filler like uh monster
meat you can put one monster meat in but
if you put more than one it'll turn into
like monster lasagna and it'll take away
each
lasagna
[Music]
unless it's fish then it makes fish
sticks oh
oh it's pretty sweet let's
um i'm confused because i definitely
killed three things today and i only
have a one morsel in my pocket
that's one okay what do we need to do
anyway there are two things in the pot
so
we can i was gonna make a boat but we're
not really close to the water so if we
made a boat it'd be like a long journey
which is not the
plan you ate them i ate them
i bet you know what i bet i was trying
to put him into the pot and i ate the
god damn it
fight me i don't see it
[Music]
yeah put them in let's try and make
something tonight oh it's already
cooking okay okay
yeah as long as you don't put anything
like weird in there it should make like
some sort of recipe
but yeah today i don't know why
cute noises everywhere
meatballs
we have like stored meatballs here in
the chest hold on someone is at my abode
i will be back in just a moment
okay don't die it's getting night now
okay i should go back oh my god
night okay oh it's still bright
oh that is okay yeah yeah
oh your sanity might go down but
it won't be too bad oh thank god i'm too
far away from him
anyway
ah there is an ocean it's to the north
we'd have to i'd have to make a new base
up there
whoa
we have any more stone without all the
sun and lots more stones who needs
ouch
oh wow thank you this is more than
enough abigail
i choose you abigail your turn
um
don't kill my ghost what i'm over here
oh yeah delivery i ate the ones
that wasn't me it's so crazy it was the
ancient ones
i know it
i have no responsibility for what they
do so
question when we make the meatballs does
it make one for everyone or is it just
one meatball
yeah it's just it's just one set of
meatballs it's like one dish
that's terrible that makes me sad we
should have enough for everyone
well there's some extra meatballs in the
chat so if people get hungry they got
food there
okay well i'm gonna go catch some more
things and kill some more things okay
that's what i can do
i'm i'm building another bank stuff how
is that
can i help i don't know what to do yeah
you can come with me get up
you help me make decisions about the
boat okay
where are you just up out up north yeah
by the beefalo
no don't go there don't
i found the ancient ones um oh oh dear
bye bye abigail
you're not gonna survive that or maybe
you are well let's try
one i will be for those of you i love
your
staring eyes
fine i picked a fight that was too
dangerous to me
yeah i got an interesting one i see you
i think
what the hell was all that i caught a
black rabbit
oh dead oh nightmare it turned into
nightmare fuel
vegan do you have any wood uh
i have twigs oh my god
okay i go get wood i only need two
that's because
is there any way for me to get abigail
my best friend back
what happened to her she got killed by
the ancient ones
[Music]
hey how do we make this my sanity higher
because i'm unable to kill rabbits now
oh uh flowers you gotta sleep uh you can
make a sleeping bag with grass
i think you just need grass okay cool
i'll do that
thunder survival guide
grass and a rope but you see refine it
though okay
sure i can make a rope already i think
well i could
if you made one once then you can just
make one again
uh-oh how do you make a rope with grass
do the rabbits look normal to you gouda
they look brown and fuzzy to me
when your saturday when your sanity gets
slow it starts to change how the
monsters
look oh yeah
saturday gets restored by sleeping and
picking flowers
picking flowers oh good idea i want to
pick some flowers my crown's got
gone too
i'm so hungry like uh outside of the
game like actually hungry i'm so
hungry thank you chicken kiara
go get some chicken and yeah after after
the stream
no more
[Music]
okay i get more wood yes i have an axe i
should probably
i should probably chop some darn it um
[Music]
okay i'll leave it at the base okay
there we go
[Music]
here you go thank you oh the flowers are
gone
good night good night
[Music]
hello i thought it would chop faster if
i helped but yes i don't
know if it does maybe it does kind of
seem like it did
oh my god that was a funny noise
i could really use a healing potion i
got like one heart left
uh yeah you can't oh but i think you had
a spider gland right yeah i still have
two spider glands left yeah
and you need to work did you get ash one
pound
you want to share that sleeping bag with
me
oh i would love to but it's gone it's
one use
yes i'll make you another one i'll make
another one
really wants it i'm sorry i wouldn't i
want to be helpful
that's okay i have a bunch of grass
actually i need two more grass
i have some here
here
we go thank you did we find out who's
best
uh whoever whoever picked up the bone
who was the one who picked up the bone
cena i
don't know okay he just appeared here
he's cute weird yes
i'm gonna you can take him yeah i
already have i already have
lobby yeah do you need that
i didn't take them i can make ash
that would be dope you just salute me
please wait
i need to pick more flowers huh
i wonder why the table hasn't tried to
uh f-word with us yet
i think i think you have to like maybe
it's because kiara took the flowers she
has to be near it
and when i step on the hands when you
see them
look how peaceful cali looks yeah
what's happening oh what is that
[Music]
appreciate yourself the sleeping child
oh no i'm real hungry
that's not great here let me see you're
losing just something yeah
there's me posting those meatballs in
the chest oh i ate one so there might
not be anything
cooked monster meat can i eat the cooked
monster meat
i think i think your boy might die i
give you seeds
oh thank you thanks
everybody raise your hands it's coming
to you
you always want to eat the seeds
that you that you're talking about
thank you and they are real hungry while
sleeping
oh good yeah is it like it's like a
trade-off you get more brain juice for
less
hunger i do have frog legs though
oh i should probably cook them right a
lot of wood yeah you can put them in the
crock pot
and you can put one stick frog leg and
then fillers like berries or carrots
mushrooms yeah i'm gonna draw some wood
here yeah
a bunch of frog legs at once i'm getting
more wood
thank you kiana i put wood in the middle
i fed you
my wife you have been fed
thank you for the assistance
[Music]
oh yeah uh we need gold to make the
little i have enough to make it but i
was just waiting to make it up at the
base up top because uh i'm making a new
base up there
uh i'm gonna make one right now if you
want to follow me uh i'm gonna make it
right now
uh where are you north i'm going north
follow the path
yeah planting trees
we did by the way reached one and a half
hour yeah we did yeah ah
probably a time it has been fun
we should do it again sometime yeah
one part two is that if we leave the
server is it gonna stay like that
uh it pauses as soon as i shut it down
so as soon as i exit the game everything
will be
uh exactly as we left it so we can go
back to that stage that's awesome
yeah but i actually don't remember it
should be fine
maybe it should be fine it's better
staying like that i'm going to challenge
this first one
not going to tango with this frog today
not today dance with me frog legs
save it for next time all right sounds
good
well do that one guru
nice job today guys i wonder what our
death counter was at
oh boy i mean there's all these
skeletons around us i don't know man
i survived 12 days what about you girls
i think you're probably the same
thing 13. oh i died at the start we all
died at the start
yeah we have it huh i think i died
another extra time
well we really didn't do a bad job i
mean
i would think i would have thought that
i would have done a much worse job but i
survived long enough
yeah oh and by the way uh if you guys
ever want to stream this game alone
there's like single player two
which is called don't starve and there's
like a lot more content in it and
there's like a different island and
different biomes you can explore just
like michael
that sounds fun i really like that i
sell this game too in the field it's
very nice
i'll definitely do that sounds good well
thanks for tuning in everyone
thanks for coming to hang out with us we
tried not to starve together
yeah thank you for watching thank you
thank you everyone thanks everyone see
you again real soon
have a nice night bye-bye this week's
gonna be full fun stuff so stay tuned
[Music]
bye
come
[Music]
so much
do me a favor
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
whatever that means
i'll get close to your mind
[Music]
is
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] it [\h__\h] it
[\h__\h] it