[Music]
Sing Out b again continuing this all
we'll start this new
refraining with memories and when the
cloud SK become bright let's reunite
[Music]
ready baby I would say today's podcast
on slight delay rubbing out the stuff is
really enough stck offing endlessly take
it easy what do we learn start a fire in
the hearts of the PC burn optimistic
focus on a quit F just new over old
trick stronger than ever and Never say
die I'm aware it's iric but we to
freaking lie dream to streamers to
entertainers to sound to young people
aiding New Dimensions we can bring
another mystery to
learning our exension dancing in we
ignite join celebrating in the that
we're creating there's another story
waiting through this world and beyond
our distant dreams have brought us here
a strong and yielding B guiding us and
with sleep will bring us moments that we
hold dear Time Rushes on and though
these winds may scatter us we'll keep
this promise when the moment finally
right we always find a way to
reunite I'm diving in again now it's
time to sink for swim let's try the
deeper in but could you hold
mying with everyone let's
keep time let's get and have fun body
just skap step and know that it's more B
years coming go so pretend I've got this
killing sorted listen I want a look cool
but I keep on tripping and falling guess
you playing the pool to hold up the Cara
or calling you count moment let us do
this Triumph is sorrow hope for tomorrow
we'll always find our way coming
[Music]
in every Universe we were always meant
to
meet I lead found search we will never
know to
be my wings will guide your hand as the
faithful days go by we will c a path
through a NeverEnding
Sky drawing us together I can sense
another wish is coming true each tyon we
we strengthened our cre me and
you sing again the cloud and skies give
way to clear we'll start this new
refraining
with memories another story starting
right here we'll keep foring ahead to
make us s all our own whichever F we
tread steadily journeying we know we're
never really alone if we believe
wherever they may find us our love will
find us every epic CH to we right we set
us on the path to reun
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
take off and fly the longer we wait
stronger it makes us as we fight every
Str to finally defeat this journey a
thousand years to me
[Music]
anded by rhy painted and wishes gred by
time our longest hes connecting your
those feel like Echoes of Ages gone
by made it spash but found I'm not free
a fish out of water bound to the Sea and
a reckless high tide but you right by my
side I bet This Moment's a way we can
ride come next songs across the
sky take off and fly the longer we wait
the stronger it makes us as we fight
every strength to finally defeat this
journey a thousand years
to wait the fire now mind burning inside
ring again From the Ashes every bruise
and scratches makes us feel more alive
we never give up never give no matter
what's ahead instead we'll CR the
worries
aside if there's the world for us to
touch your to see we'll make it
ourselves and make
memories there ain't a mystery our
brains cannot solve we just shine brigh
and TI or
rol connecting comes across the
wall take off and fly the longer we wait
the stronger it makes us as we fight
everything strength to finally defeat
this journey of thousand years to
me at the end of this world where's our
Fighting
Chance nothing's changing it's always
the same story stage with the de
different out a Happ for and those who
loved us up till
now I want to see a
smile find my way are you somehow take
off and fly the longer we wait the
stronger it makes us as we fight every F
strength to finally defeat this Turney a
thousand years to me
let's try it can't be denied the wish in
my heart is you right here by my side
strength is all that will need I Won't
Wait A Thousand Years to me
[Music]
yeah good work everybody h
we did it once
again hi
[Music]
guys we to a flying start already but to
properly kick things off welcome
everybody to whole up English myth
fourth anniversary live The Show Goes On
welcome
[Applause]
everybody yeah yeah thanks for coming
yeah well then let's start off with a
round of introduction so hold me up
[Music]
first let's do it first
you know the rules and so do I oh okay
it's shall be me um all right K hello
everybody I'm from Life English myth
you'll hear that a lot today so who is
next coming water oh me
okay me a song hi think you guys maybe
know who I am my name is Mor K from H
live English myth I am a virtual singer
artist Creator I stream I play games too
nice to meet you if we have already met
if we haven't if we have a high someone
take the mic away from me I'm so bad at
these I'm always so bad someone else
doing
who's perhaps okay I'm Amelia Watson
number one detective from
H and last but not least
good morning afternoon evening everyone
I'm n inan from well
obviously and together we are all
English I told you you'll hear it a lot
so if our introductions out of the way
feature us on the Vue we have
today out
stage's fourth anniversary look at our
songs our songs are everywhere our
Originals yeah that's pretty high some
Valentine
Stu we're stars that was really really
nice uh I'm I'm sure it's obvious right
everybody we we've got full Divine and
exquisite for The Show Goes On can you
guess what the f is anybody anybody hi
a tropical island vacation no no no no
no okay I got it underwater Sea
Adventure I for real what you definitely
that one I think so okay no I I don't
think they have good
either two Bone Heads drum roll though
come on Dr
roll it's
Broadway yeah and it's not just you know
a Broadway it's also a red carpet do you
want like do a cat fashion okay come on
ladies let's go let's go let's go let's
go
W fashion baby yeah yeah oh yeah we got
it nice that's what I really wanted to
do thanks all right that was pretty cool
too so along with the stunning backdrop
you guys I hope you will enjoy our grand
performance but it's not just any live
concert we've got a fun surprise waiting
for them don't l oh
surprise I'm a be I'm a
be we have a surprise yeah did you
forget already Ena you didn't hear it
about the
surprise I mean it's not a surprise if
we don't if you know about it play along
play along yeah we have a surprise guys
yeah we know about it course oh my god
well if you keep on watching until the
end you will indeed find out so in the
meantime everybody I ask you to use the
hashtag that is at the top right corner
of your screen to let us know what you
think about our cute performance tonight
and where should they post the
screenshots my
fridge post your fridge post them on X
formerly known as Twitter yeah yeah not
the not the
refrigerator spelling be ladies oh God
they
know everybody whole live English myth
now presents our fourth anniversary live
The Show Goes
[Applause]
[Music]
On 3 2 1 come on
hey all
right come on dead beats and Chum buuz
all together now come on
[Music]
something might last very long
ago in the
gra I thought I might drown and see a
butterflies headphones on hear that song
and open up my
eyes deep breath that fly away we go
each step we take a g so when is lost I
hope you know s every Mel just needs
place to
start and every dream needs
areaid each me on and your heart so let
the rhy got your
way
away with
me you'll
see you
[Music]
something I found spark life rainbow of
sound livs deep inside my heart wants to
fit for so long KN flow and now I know
now I'm right where I belong she
[Music]
deep breath and fly just be reality what
you believe listen with your
see everybody just needs place to
start and every dream
needra each me on light illuminates your
heart so at the r I've got your
it's
away with
me just see
[Music]
that's right I'm not just a phoenix I'm
a
t look at this
[Applause]
[Music]
W when we first
met I wonder what you think of me the
set it was a perfect mared day but the
time went by I forgot to hide the laugh
that came so naturally for lows and
highs I wonder why I ever thought you
would leave now no matter where or when
we are I know it's you I can count on
magical
myal nothing can stop us now let's go
tile T where the time
go how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock will stop
spinning
donkey donkey hi speed faster tell that
friends forever it's clear to see that
this Myster was
imediately you
[Music]
me it's been so
long since I love so hard I cried now
you came
along it happens almost every time that
I hear your voice and left no choice but
to let you know what you mean to me
spiraling time skipping for Treasure of
memories now no matter where or when
we're from our friendship's elementary T
close now you know now we can stop but
now let's go to
T where that time
go how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the will stop
spinning w w w w doy doy heart Beed
faster don't that PR forever clear to
see that mystery but
immediately you got me each day we're
older but the future holds is knock
knock knock for us to know yes go go go
before we know it so let's up the
question we can make each second T Tac
forever now or
[Music]
never that
time how should I know why it seems when
you're here with me the clock stop
spinning w w w a doy doy heart be fter
tell my D friends forever SAR to see
that this
mystery
immediately you that's right I'm Phoenix
I'm a grand look at this
alos
[Music]
fore
spe huh
H look at this soal Gem of the sea and
SC you see what I mean return to watch
know it ain't much know it
[Music]
shows foree
[Applause]
[Music]
so oh you think that's all
huh just going to leave like it's
nothing going without me I don't know
what you're thinking return to the Sea a
shark is all you'll ever
[Music]
be
[Applause]
[Music]
for hold
time to die bird it's your time to go
I'm going to get you
finally get over here over here stupid
bird that's what I thought I'm sorry
Neil what did I do you guys forget that
I'm a killer actually I forget that I'm
a
killer that was fun though how did you
guys like reflect that was dramatic
right dramatic yes I got to make up for
my lack of dancing skills but with
drama I I don't know it was really
tough it must of the SC right it is very
heavy it looks like it's not very heavy
but it's it actually weighs a ton I'm
just really strong you see but the way
like dancing around with it is kind of
dangerous yeah yeah sorry about that if
I accidentally hit you me curtains for
you but maybe that's what I secretly
want I'm we did reflect together we did
as our Duo song and what did you do I
did full
color GAA I love that song so much still
unreleased oh still un where is
it but I will say I will say that that
uh that was probably the hardest
choreography like solo choreography that
I've learned for maybe go-getters maybe
that's that was the hardest so that's
good you have to challenge yourself I
was happy to challenge myself to to
learn that and I still I still know the
movement
so you know the hip sway is so fun I
came imagine what about you what did you
sing I did I'm
a well you know actually originally when
they were like okay so we're going to do
the swiu you sing whatever whose song
you want to sing and I said please let
me know I want to sing I was like I was
like the first through shout out so I
know how much you love that song and I
loved your your bouncy movements with
it I like that you changed the lyrics
too I'm not just a phoenix I'm a ten
show yeah something like that something
like that it was cute saw this and we
finished it off with our reflect which I
think is made for to be you know with
two people it's a duet after all and we
make a really good duet so that seem
there seems to be a theme right there's
a theme Here of doing each other's songs
it seems so interesting well I wonder
what will be next because of that what
are your guesses who will do who and
like what song what you
thinking not okay so maybe your wish
will come
true well it's not over yet m
z so we got to pump up the energy just a
little bit more you guys keep it going
because there's so much more left let's
enjoy it together or else or else
remember I'm a kill take your serly guys
I'm so scared people forget that I'm the
reaper I'm crazy I'll come after you I
promise I'm crazy as you just saw anyway
okay how should we end
it get excited Takami
yeah
[Applause]
takam byebye see you later see
you
[Music]
for for
this m is undefeated until my Call's
completed let's keep on searching for
the treasure up to p
genius a miracle idea got to set it free
fantastic dreams are burning up inside
of me we turn the world around with new
technology here a laboratory cast upon
the scene into evil and of life right
into knowledge cre and six satellites
ideas can stop flushing out stop
thinking they might use a hand or two
I'm busy working in the night the Fire
King will bra the ocean while and search
sh a ruler of the invention that can
modify all reason once watched in
jealousy no somay I got to be next up
the throne I know what I
[Music]
go
oh
[Music]
oh no fell into the unknown let me bleed
in our all
alone no control a don't you dare
apologize turn my back felt cold KN
listen up cuz
advice you're at the time where out of
line it's taking
over like a renegade I for I'll make you
crying it down what keep call
[Music]
me taking the crown now you're calling
me King you're going to hear all
[Music]
don't back it up don't back it up keep
that aim I got thoughts that'll drive
you insane come over if you like we'll
have a lot of fun but I got a lot of
bite I do but I won make sure you don't
forget it and Army on my back say I'm
sick I'm just sadistic not living in a
li in the LI I want to see the way you
live it's taking over like a renegade I
for and I make you
cry tearing it down do just what i w to
keep calling me
a taking the crown now you're calling me
King you're going to hear him all
sing make on I want it all so give me
some more Flames bur me up down into my
core oh you wish stay down but then I
just
R you're not my
enemy baby you're dead to me hear my
voes screaming
[Music]
out keep
tearing it down what keep call
[Music]
me taking the crown now you're calling
me King you're going to hear
[Music]
ha
h
[Music]
h fore
[Applause]
[Music]
you best up let me in fake see
and
[Music]
Phoenix fore
for
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
with
round right
through those nights I never find me I
back to you inside this life of Life
there was Madness and the meaning never
lless we were screaming at the top of
our l
n never
died
how no
proof those Heights I'll never find
another chance to say thanks for saving
my life I was hopeless it was stinging
running roadless we were singing at the
top of our lungs to the N this city
never
died what was the root of it all I
couldn't say I used to jump and then
fall and it off without compl us trying
to find friends cuz in the end nobody
sticks around that's when you sh
yourself into AED place that you turn
around and found yourself in love the
nights Noam sling our own dreams just
what the hell was so funny off the wrong
tree stumble the fall miss the jungle
sing CU it's right we Mak the trou
running content and is history I can't
forget the time that we spent the
another Al
fend
disappearing that I can never be Let It
Go fade in Fade Out this crazy dream
without a direction floating aimlessly
there's nothing left back there for me
breathing but it won't stop the r
run right
through those nights I'll never find my
way back to you inside this La of light
there was Madness in the meaning never
lless we were screaming at the top of
our Lo to the mountain this they never
di was there
Chasing Fireflies between the S and
highrise left a trail behind to find a
was time of our Liv silent singer
overwork and under think in offices a
cough until off when you're late yet a
thought persistent Optimist who to be
afraid nothing wrong and writing songs
behind the L sh is the world the S place
without the words that you can B when
the ladder fell and shattered every bar
that we had play because the matter in
the end in the cage ands tired of
fantasy you're wishing you don't get to
say I miss you you watch your he into
the rear view mirror of the villain
betray stop the pity party listen you
don't get to be dismayed you don't get
to be emotional you're blessed to got a
made these the best to years of life
because you chose to make a tri
recollect the days you hoped and you
prayed for this what is there to miss F
Fade Out this Hy dream without a
direction roaming
aimlessly there's nothing left back
there for
pretend it's the end of a made up story
I'll
F no
proof those TI I'll never find another
chance to say hey thanks for saving my
life I was sess it was singing driving
roadless we were singing at the top of
ours to the numbness this city never di
I'll say goodby of the Soul somehow
there was romance in our s pain we've
got no chance in this light mze let's
hold hands through the night so fast in
this schol J till the
train time the same waking up now to the
real life let me day dream till the next
night I'll keep
waiting I'll keep waiting for you
[Music]
waking up now to my real life let me day
dream till the next flight johning so
long I got older now the crowd's gone is
it over is it
[Music]
over hello
everyone thank you for joining us
tonight thank you so how has it been so
far how did you guys like my rendition
of Kell's future Island it was amazing
oh my
gosh so cute so cute so
cute and I performed K's
K you're so cute you performed it so
well it's like Kiara
but and my piece was ena's Violet how
does it feel having your own song
performed in front of you I mean I love
it when you sing and you bring a new
energy to a song like
it and just now the three of us
performed the end of a life uh and we
want to make things fresh and exciting
so as you can probably tell we've been
singing each other's original songs
tonight and now we have two more songs
that you know you guys can en more
songs man but ladies don't forget about
the title of our life concert tonight
the show goes on and it will yes so
everyone everyone don't click away don't
don't I see our next song will kind of
Dev from our uh the shuffle that we've
been doing but you're going to love it
just as much right right that's
right well in that case let's not keep
our guests waiting up next is our
penultimate piece
Eno enjoy
one two
[Music]
3 like the flood lights let's begin we
start it's ride and Sh on
it Ste the show jump Jo go up so C the
will keep on entertaining in
hand it's our greatest moment yet
spectacle they'll never forget all a
party from D to D the show will go on
and on tell them that we're here to say
and spread the news from Tokyo to
Broadway
screaming we're boing
oning so bright now we're feeling all
right since the day we met we've all
been going strong so long and we keep
moving right
along so keep on dancing yeah you bet
ain't nothing going to stop us for a
perfect winter Harmony no matter
where don't you know we're going to feel
when it's ready to on another show
[Music]
there's a time to celebrate the mood is
fun and we're feeling
[Applause]
great from the Rapter to the AL
contageous laughter and our big
we'll slay them like we always do make
no bones about it when I'm with you it's
exis Lander in water we've never been
hotter It Feels So B we're friends for
All
Time come on to the T me
shake
Jo we the work of and the keep you in my
heart we
s
together mi
forever Sy of side and turning like
a dream another dream with me now it's
time to change the
key like the lights keep on with tonight
night and we've got a
h get in L me talk out it's almost time
to take another
B we stay on track you know the
other
dance the music will and on
and you
go going follow
on and on and heav show
[Applause]
[Music]
my
legs getting so that was
intense was a good time yeah well you
guys just listen to my's new song The
Show Goes On what did you
think very very yeah
Broadway we figured we stick with the
Broadway theme and make it something
like you know musical something that
would make everyone get on their feet
and dance and we Goofy dancing yes yes I
feel so goofy
today so gy yeah fun and the title truly
encapsulates what we think we really
want the fun to last forever
and and to make that happen all of us
and myth are going to do the best we can
and those are the feelings that we
packed yeah nicely into this new song
yeah and hope you guys will listen to it
a lot because it will be on the stream
platform
very soon uh so get ready to wear out
your speakers and also the MV is going
to be right after this we're going to R
into it be ready ready for that we'll
take it out yeah but that's not all
maybe another little
surprise we have merchandise coming up
more Goods more stands let's go no we
will not show it right now but it will
be um shown at the very end of the
stream at the ending screen so stay
tuned for don't immediately leave the
stream okay so we don't have much time
left uh I thought I'd like to hear what
you ladies are currently thinking who
wants to go
first all right
Shar all right girl split out of nowhere
I guess I guess she can do
that that's why she was so
excited it's showtime baby I mean it was
really good
right enjoyed it thank you so
much fun good time okay who else who
else maybe you else uh well well you
know it kind of reminded me of like you
know when we started together in the
past and with their journey of a
thousand years now we're doing all these
performances into the
future future fure
we're playing around too much
seg true Oh Me Oh gosh well I don't know
guys um I feel like I feel I just feel
like we've been through so much together
and and and I'm so happy to be by your
side
you that's that's not br
you guys don't like my theater moves no
no give me give me something whome come
fine fine fine I love singing songs that
I love with people that I love that's it
that's all there is to it I have a lot
of fun with you guys you guys are the
best and uh yeah before it gets too
sappy somebody else take the mic I think
everybody what do you think what did you
think yes well today I did a little bit
of mcing here I hope I did it well but
for me you know I realized we when we
joined our oldest Senai I think were're
around like four years right years into
the game and now we're four years
in we're like really proper Senpai now
and everybody got to respect us pay the
Senpai
tax pay up so all of these four years
hopefully more and and you know I want
to make more memories this was
definitely a big nice memory so The Show
Must Go On The Show Goes On indeed just
like the title we're going to do our
best so please support us listen to the
new
song and with that with that I think we
can gather together all right
together you guys ready here we go all
[Music]
right together
[Applause]
we're let's go
okay we're ready to greet the world
we're voting forward with courage to run
toward a brand new start let's go live
ping the distance across the sea
endlessly
cheerfully meeting Heart to Heart
[Music]
waking from a dream swept up into a
stream I make a wish and wait for my
queue how will we connect in this new
frontier we're journeying through in a
scene where no one's ever been with fire
colors bursting like stars radiant and
warm charged with energy that's carried
us this far
each s they feel brings a miracle to
life surely we've got to take that
chance we're running nonstop straight to
the top that's
right we're ready to change the game a
sh showcase creating a new place where
we can shine Day by Day spling stories
will
intertwine get ready to cross the wavs
we're voyaging forward with courage to
run toward a brand new state let's go
light reaching the distance across the
sea and the SLE follow me and we'll Turn
the
[Music]
Page breaking through the doubt we know
we'll figure out a way to clear each
towering trial sharing all our hopes we
can conquer any challenge with the smile
we link our hearts as we search across
the globe knowing no matter where we are
no matter how far we can be Stars let's
go I want to Chas the wish and
waveringly
standing out the Grand Story share the
Futures that we can see making that we H
take my hand and reach for the scream
all we need are great and dreams our
hearts and souls all fulfilled in the
world we
[Music]
build we're ready to seize the day
traversing the pathways the discovering
highways to everywhere step by step
Gathering stories that we can share get
ready to Le the way with each generation
The Shining sensation the dream un FR
let's make friends making a moment of
History joyfully follow me we'll connect
the
world they'll hear our song ringing out
over Hills and oceans our Legend grows
and
contines we'll carry on Starting Now
setting Hearts In Motion connecting all
of the
[Music]
world yay K kittyy everyone did you
enjoy the H life English myth fourth
anniversary Life The Show Goes On I know
it's hard to say goodbye but before we
go we have some awesome merch to show
you first up we have this the acrylic
block the illustration theme is Broadway
musical X retro outfits perfectly
fitting for our live show and it was
drawn by the amazing
Aki it's a two-layer design giving get a
nice step the thick acrylic makes it
look great just as it is all right on to
the next
one next we have collection cards these
cards have a special touch with a
translucent material and foil stamping
making them feel extra festive each of
us in myth has her own card so be sure
to collect them all all right next
up let's see ooh we got mini mascot
plushies each myth member's mascot has
turned into a cute plushy but this time
they're all dressed up with hats and
ribbons to match the live show how cute
and you can attach them to your bag and
take them anywhere you want let them see
the world okay what do we got
next next up is the cross body bag it's
a simple Everyday Use bum bag the inside
design features myths motive icons make
it super stylish perfect for carrying
the keychains around when you go
out thanks or should I say than soon
everyone I sure feel like I want to
collect them and I hope you do the same
and last but not least thank you so much
for supporting H life English myth come
catch us at the next show or stream U
[Music]
myth
e e