no
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
p
[Applause]
k
key I'm going to press it I'm going to
press it I don't really know what it
does because I didn't learn much about
pip pip boys pip boys pip boys in the
game H in the show but I'm going to
press it what what will happen if I
press it don't press it what will happen
what will happen
KY key KY howdy feel KY key kind of
sounds like something somebody in Texas
would say kick the key partner it's a
smart watch okay so I can do a lot of
things me pressing it will not make
everybody explode right before we begin
let's have a fashion
show um ignore my arms being detached
the arms with the pit boy are made by
Sky and the rest is made by blue so
we're having a little bit of a
collaboration ignore the extra arms okay
but does don't you do you see this
perfect booby
window that is left open for the clothes
amazing and then my hat is really cute
perfect for my round round head and then
we have uh uh what what what kind of gun
shot is that a it's not a shotgun cuz
it's really long right what do you call
that kind of long gun that I have on my
back H
mutant don't call me a
mutant well I don't know am I playing a
ghoul or so in in the game I'm not sure
what I'm playing but a rifle a hunting
rifle okay okay okay
okay I have so much stuff on me and yeah
in order to show everything a little bit
better I hope it's okay if I'm using not
full screen the game game doesn't have
the most beautiful Graphics
anyway so it's okay right to do like the
usual
smaller
screen yeah also I uh exchanged some
songs so disclaimer
um I I cannot no logo okay wait I can
indeed not really play it with the
original
radio it's not really
but uh I went on audio stock you know
how good audio stock is no jingle
jangle and I got a lot of blues and
country not country wait C I guess
pronunciation wouldn't be yeah uh kind
of songs in in my playlist it's actually
so good audio stu um it's basically the
same songs Just without singing that's
what it feels like
like I'm I'm sorry I know I know I
listened a little bit to Amy stream and
I was like oh damn yeah this radio is
really nice but I did also feel like
when you're playing this alone at home
with no watching no people watching you
then I can see how it is like very what
screen title what where that is like
very very chill and
vibing but where is my logo I see save
my logo it's very chill and it's a Vibe
it's a bob for sure but I think since
we're going to be talking and I'm
streaming you know I feel like it won't
be you know it won't be an issue
to where where did I save the last New
Vegas to have no no singing and not the
original songs I think it will be like
less distracting so we're
good I don't know where my saved logo
went let's download another one another
one so this is my first entry into
Fallout
series uh there we go I watched the
show but even before I watched the show
we already talked about playing this
game I don't know why you look
ridiculous say the right
chicken you're
ridiculous okay
uh it starts with like a really tiny
window but I'm guessing it's going to be
bigger right let
me where's my
game I set it to relatively
big like it's so small right
now y
show it show it to the
masses
OBS hello hello well I'll I'll go in
maybe it will then feel
like oh it did it did not become Window
mode oh no oh no please ah it's on the
wrong screen again here we go again same
problem as in a different
game
uh okay wait I can surely set it to
Window mode from here
display
uh
uh are you guys even seeing this it
covered my whole
OBS let me where's my
OBS here okay ah it's too big you can
hear it too where is where is where chat
help me where is Window mode you can see
some of
it yeah
I I think it already crashed because I
tabed
out did
it yeah yeah I think it
crashed let me restart
it wait wait wait so who where can I hey
exit the game H do I have to do it in
like the first
window
uh restart game and choose options okay
in the
launcher I thought it was Windows
huh Tab out immediately that's not good
for streamer streamers often Tab out to
adjust their chat window and stuff so
whoa whoa whoa wo whoo okay
options ah window I
here okay ooh
tiny
ah can I okay no I cannot choose
which which screen it's going on but
that's
okay just double tapping what double
double
[Music]
tapping this is surreal
why why people always say this about a
lot of games I say like they're so
surprised I'm playing it by now you
shouldn't be surprised anymore I mean
yeah F5 is my favorite button today
that's that's what I'm pressing on the
PIP boy I
guess so
okay
play I open on the wrong screen again
but that's okay I can probably
can I move it with when I Tab out are
you going to break on
me wait how do I
uh wasn't
it the arrow key up what's it called
shift and windows and then the arrow key
to the left or so will change the screen
right that it's
on I'll I'll go task manager again this
is not acceptable why are you on the
wrong screen go here please don't break
okay I think oh it's not broken yet okay
double
tabing what's double
tabing oh should I play with
controller posidon
energy sure no okay good good good I
prefer keyboard all right I think I got
it now wow except that it's a bit loud I
guess
[Music]
oh everything's so loud in my ears
wouldn't recommend controller okay okay
okay
okay okay back back back back so far I
like this intro
screen why does it say continue
I what this is confusing back there we
go
continue from my last saved
game yes
okay I don't have one I thought so
okay what's with my Pip Boy Color are
you making a game Game Boy Color joke
wow what subtitles would be useful oh
took the M the subtitles
[Music]
uh H they're are they are on or general
subtitles
too what what is general
subtitles I can change is that the
correct pit I don't know it's just one I
got you guys are like
correcting what what
hey somebody made this for me okay
General subtes are good
okay oh
okay then let's begin start new game I
hope my radio will
[Music]
work that's New Vegas or Las Vegas I
thought it was New Vegas
I'm
gambling I know that because of the show
where they they don't really go there
but they go
there I love the
show I hope it continues
[Music]
soon but this music I guess is fixed I
can't change that
is this going to like m is there like a
time
frame like when this is playing versus
when the show
is is it before Sandy Shores or after
Sandy
Shores show this is before the show okay
so maybe before Sandy
[Music]
Shores but already at the time when
they're starting to
repopulate Shady SS oops Shady Shady
Shady Sandy Shores what Shady Sands what
Shady Shores never changes war never
changes when atomic fire consumed the
Earth those who survived did so in great
underground
vaults when they opened their
inhabitants set out across the ruins of
the old old world to build new societies
establishing vill the people forming
tribes as decades passed what had been
the American southwest United beneath
the flag of the New California Republic
dedicated to Old World values The Vault
people left and the rule of law I
thought they were staying for much
longer as the Republic grew so did its
needs maybe just some Scouts spread East
seeking territory and wealth in the dry
and merciless expanse of the Mojave
Desert they returned with Tales of a
city Untouched by the WarHeads that had
scorched the rest of the world and a
great wall spanning the Colorado River
Colorado the NC mobilized its Army and
sent it East to occupy Hoover Dam and
restore it to working condition this
would be more easy to understand when I
if I knew
American society had arisen under a
different
flag a vast Army of slaves forged from
the conquest of 86 tribes 86 Caesar's
Legion Caesar's Legion four years have
passed since the Republic held the dam
just barely against the legion's
onslaught the legion did not
Retreat across the river it gathers
strength campfires burn training drums
beat
through it all the New Vegas strip has
stayed open for business under the
control of its mysterious Shady s did
happen says you and his army of
rehabilitated tribals and police
[Music]
robots you are a courier hired by the
Mojave Express to deliver a package to
the New Vegas strip I'm a c Courier what
seemed like a simple delivery job has
taken a
turn for the worse
delivery delivery you got what you were
after did we mean a Deliverance in the
show Crying in the Rain
P guess who's waking up over here door
Dash UPS I love his suit time to cash
out will you get it over with not yet
maybe cons kill people without looking
them in the
face but I ain't a think dig
you've made your last delivery kid I did
what sorry you got twisted up in this
scene I'm not released I'm I'm about to
be dead from where you're kneeling must
seem like an 18 karat run of bad
luck truth
is the game was rigged from the start
h i I suppose so well uh thanks for
watching
Everybody game
over I I tried
damn what
the
byebye thanks for
watching was
fun so I'm not the person aw that was
shot wow no I am I live I lefted
[\h__\h] whoa easy there easy you've been
out cold a couple of days are you one of
those crazy doctors no relax a second
you don't look like one let's see what
the damage
is scam doctor can you tell me your name
wah oh c corar wah can you say it it's
easy repeat after me w w w
w I can't say it it's quiet
now uh
should work better now what I'd have
picked for you but if that's your name
that's your name maybe more maybe
more w
w w oh oopsie no
effect
[\h__\h] why why do I scream why do I scream
we will never
know I'm dog Mitchell welcome to Good
Springs you are a doctor now I hope you
don't mind but I had to go rooting
around there
in I take pride in my needle work You'
better are you doing the push what was
it called PR PR push needle thingy was
this pit boy do is this my pit boy no
it's a Rob go a robco robco hey robco
wait it is maybe a pit boy just a
different
[Music]
one oh I am
Caucasian
thanks oh character creation 1 hour
let's go what the [\h__\h] is that if you do
bangs if if you're if you do
bangs then doing better
girl I I love that wave in that girl's
hair very straight
hair I like that pretty wave let's do
that
customize shape oh oh really there's
that much to
do you got
oh I didn't think there would be that
much at all I didn't even realize we
could change our characters looks at
all maybe we can have a 1hour
creation there's more hairs
a
uh ah uh custom uh what where where did
the hair go
[Music]
huh
where is after the face oh okay this is
just a preset
okay
uh oh
God I'm turning into a
ghoul slowly oh I can turn oh my God
go amazing
oh oh it moves with it interesting why
Why Stop
cheeks I don't really care about all
this she already looks pretty it's okay
but you can't change your eye color not
that I can really tell what it
is mouth cheeks jaw chin maybe the
chin forward backward broad recessed
uh-huh uh shallow deep uhhuh tall short
uh-huh I feel like it's all the
same okay ah eye color there it
is uh where's
purple let's go with blue didn't really
look like it
changed oh I feel like I'm going back
but I'm seeing things I've never seen
before that doesn't look like I age that
just looks like I uh my facial
structures changed and I got a tan
but I guess this looks kind of childish
now that I look at it maybe
like
here okay next a hairstyle oh
oh oh my [\h__\h] God I guess it's uh I
guess a lot of people have will have
[\h__\h] up hair because of
the
well
the whatchamacallit
radiation yeah that's what I was going
to
say
yeah I guess you're lucky if you have a
good head of
hair oh
really wait Iron Maiden oh yeah okay No
Nonsense nonsense prim and proper rough
night what the [\h__\h] it looks like a bush
it looks like actually
yeah sometimes my hair looks like that
after I woke up
so and I didn't even I'm not having
rough nights I'm just sleeping normally
I try to okay I'm staying with the
domestic
goddess uh what's this no okay uh back
ah the color
orange make me a red hair yeah
[Music]
yeah that's good thanks you actually
nailed that
game looks
good e did I
press oops yes well I got most of it
right anyway stuff that matter orang
okay no sense keeping you in bed anymore
let's see if you didn't turn me into a
ghoul did
you
please I want to stay as normal as I can
be why don't you walk down to the end of
the room over by that Vigor tester
machine there v test it ain't a
race oh I like this divider all right
tarle between run and walk push caps
lock uh which one was caps lock this one
oh
uhhuh this is cute is this the bger
machine go ahead and give the Vigor
tester a try Vigor tester we'll learn
right quick if you got back all your
faculties whoa what's
this I already saw a bunch of like
recommendations in the chat but somebody
a while ago told me what I should do and
I
forgot is that even
that oh wait no this is this is
something else this is just how strong
ah but I guess there's more then ah [\h__\h]
I forgot what it was uh because Charisma
is usually I think I think it was
Charisma that I was told to do because
uh it does something useful
damn it I don't know
anymore don't listen to chat you mean
the ones that say l uh that that is it's
useless or that it's
useful
Charisma luck is really good luck always
works oh maybe it was
luck huh I like these names Beach
jellyfish doughy baby wet n lightweight
average show Barrel CH of beach bullly
Cirus strong men doomsday packs doomsday
hulas is bigger
cousin
uh want that because it makes memes
what just pick your own stats it's the
most Fest
yeah uh how many stats I have what I
have
10 10 points
o okay let's say I don't know how much I
have to spread but let's oh
wait six points to go but here it's
already at five okay wait so there's
generally more I don't start from one
here perception oh are we doing a DND d
game or what perception a perceptive
Cowboy always knows when there's a l sit
stick of dynamite nearby oh when
enironment sneaking up on him explosives
lockpick energy weapons accuracy cups
range oh right I read that what it
affects well this makes sense kind
of I will be an unsuspecting trout I
like that
uh endurance you can't keep a good CBO
then not if he's the enduring T and and
not if he's got a six shooter the size
of alternation this affects your
unarmed uh Health resistance survival
oh do not Bend Place me with the
markings upwards
please
Charisma this affects your barter speech
companion and Nerf my companion
Doo you'll find there some smooth
talking cowbo out there that got
themselves a voice sounds like an
angel's
harmonica I can't talk like that called
leader who oh
oh
oh well if I wanted to be that ghou I
could be movie
star wait I want to see still what else
there is
intelligence no no
C smell always works well yeah this is
where we we're not sure was it was it
something yeah it was Charisma
intelligence a Smart Cow a smart Cowboy
is good at most anything from sucking
the poison out of your Rattler bite to
fixing your broken wagon axle this
affects your science repair medicine and
skill
[Music]
points
um sounds a little bit
important oh yeah wa maybe it was
Intelligence what do they mean with it
affects skill points do I always get two
skill points or
so was
this what does it how does it affect
that more Point more points for level
okay this is what I was told to put some
more points in
to you get more skill points per t Ence
ooh so it doesn't have to be maxed
and maybe let's be gifted or let's see
how much else I have to you
know guns sneak speed action point
regener action point
regeneration sneak sneak oh I want to be
a good
sneaker yeah let's be a knife catcher
for now luck what else is there ah okay
that's
it oh what are we currently on the
Charisma
again
sneak
luck oh it defects all skills Critical
Hits enemy mishaps well luck is good
some folks claim not to believe in luck
but when they lose in a d d duel you'll
hear the say that lucky son of a gun
that lucky son of a
gun Lucky Seven lepre Corn's foot 21
leaf clover two-headed coin flip well I
can't go that
high
uh gifted
intelligence oh [\h__\h] this is really
low strength
Str maybe a bit more strength
yo agility that much well yeah I'll need
it to sneak cuz I'm a chicken I'm a
chicken lower
Charisma the Charisma
haters let's put it
into one
here very balanced
yeah wonderful one strength one Charisma
uh agility
more this is look okay that's fine
perception is kind of trash
perception wait where was
it how much do I have in it oh I don't
know where it is oh it's oh I have five
in
it that's it's okay nothing's too low
nothing's too high I guess well agility
and luck is like pretty high but that's
okay maybe special oh smart
the way they put the letters
okay with luck like yours I'm surprised
them bullets didn't just turn right
around and climb back into the gun well
we know your vitals are good but that
don't mean them bullets didn't leave you
Nutter and a big horn are dropping what
do you say you take a seat in my couch
and we go through a couple of questions
your couch if C ouch
ouch I'm naked give me some cloes man
please all right I'm going to say a word
I want you to say the first thing that
comes to mind fun dog cat oh house uh
uh
uh oh there's
more house
house H cat house cat again
cat uh uh no uh okay it doesn't really
fit in here I I don't fit in here
uh b b burglarize Knight Ste CH Ste CH
Rob Cho what what what was it Knight ah
H
sleep it's there but that's so boring
wait um maybe we should do something
more fun
uh huh huh
sleep is so logical P Jo yeah uh dream
Bandit
ah
help swiss
cheese uh stab Crush
bribe uh vaporize reasonable reasonable
the Bandit is being reasonable maybe cuz
I'm
one stab Crush
bribe stab light says my guts to stab
into his guts
light oh light as it because it's heavy
ah okay well I I was thinking huh light
heavy no it's about the
light that I'm walking towards when I
die
light
light the heavy is like the dump answer
I
think but I'm
dumb mother
sorry cookie jar attention tattle regret
human shield
human whoa
oh oh my God these
answers what what is this
affecting Maybe Cookie
Jar okay now I got a few statements I
want you to tell me how much they sound
like something you'd say sound first one
conflict just ain't in my
[Music]
nature it's maybe I don't it
depends but let's
say let's say we disagree I ain't given
to relying on others for support I ain't
given to rely ah I don't want to rely on
others for support or I don't want to be
relied on what I don't want to be relied
on or I don't rely on
others you don't rely on others relying
on others okay
uh I don't rely on others agree well in
the game I would like to indeed not rely
too much on others I'm always fixing be
the center of
attention in the
game
ideally not I'm slow to embrace new
ideas
ohaba uh slow to no no new ideas charge
in to deal with my problems head on I
charge in to deal with my problems head
on well it's about survival man it's all
about survival almost done here what do
you say you have a look at this uterus
tell me what you see
[Laughter]
uterus uh okay we don't have that
uh not none of this uh
but why are you seeing these
things what the [\h__\h] where is the broken
chain I I
see nothing may maybe it's a chemical
reaction I don't know okay how about
this one that is sauron's eye and a
person on top of it I guess uh uh yeah
evil person oh she SE oh some piece of
Space Age Technology I see a prices work
of art I'm too embarrassed to what are
you thinking what what are you thinking
are you thinking it's a v
oh
what why would you be
embarrassed what did I say s well let's
say a ship at see I like that last one
that's animals that's two animals
actually that's a that's how cute it's
like this part is a nose and you know
it's a Boop boopy longy nose it's like H
I don't know what what would this animal
be um the ones with the long nose I'm
not sure and then here's just someone
sitting there uh these are the ears here
would be the eyes two bears high fiving
oh I didn't see this as the
hand but they do they have that no why
are you guys all suggesting
that
what a meeme but it's not even
here mushroom cloud this does not really
I mean okay I guess you're looking at
the white
inside a head on a pillow what Beed man
light in the
darkness well the only thing out of
these that I can say see is a mushroom
cloud well that's all she wrote and I
know I have to put my fum up to compare
it to you better just have a look at the
results okay see if it all seems right
to
you is this also like from my
answers bar harder 14 this skill affects
the prices you get for buying and
selling
items oh I can still change it the
energy weapon skill determines your
effectiveness of any weapon that uses
small energy cells explosive skill
determines the ease of disarming any
hostile
mines guns 22 guns determines your
Effectiveness with any weapon that uses
conventional ammunition lock pick 16
that's pretty low is it survival is low
unarmed is 2 seven M weapons 33 science
33 represents your combined scientific
knowledge and is primarily used to hack
restricted computer terminals it can
also be used to recycle energy weapon
and I don't think we need that much in
science do
we oh wait I can oh it adds more to
something
[Music]
M to access terminals yeah is that
important is that going to be
important repair you pick
free okay let's let's choose
them
H free to make extra extra strong very
important not necessarily you should get
guns yeah
okay determines how many hit points you
replenish upon using a stim
pack yeah
maybe allows you to maintain any weapons
in Apparel in addition repair allows you
to create items and gun ammunition oh
maybe
repair sounds nice some of you guys were
saying that before
too bless you thank you it's actually
supposed to be gunite at kfp we say
gunite thank
you uh well my sneak is already pretty
high increases the hit points you
receive from food and drink and also
helps you create consumable items at
campfires H I don't know what to do with
the last
one get speech isn't that connected with
Charisma I mean we didn't give it that
many points in the end so without
science you won't be able to access most
of blah I couldn't read the rest but it
sounds important you're you're making it
sound important
now the speech skill governs how much
you can influence someone for dialogue
or manipulation and gain access to
information they might otherwise not
want to
share science or speech science speech
lockpick speech is
good speech is never bad
spech substitutes
Charisma
okay how about repair science speech my
guns are already relatively
high and maybe with level UPS we can
still improve
this maybe yeah let's
go before I Turn You Loose I need one
more thing from you what I got a form
for you to fill out so I can get a sense
of your medical history you want to know
so much about me ain't like I expect to
find you got a family history of getting
shot in the
head yeah I wouldn't
know H what's this oh huh I choose two
uhhuh two traits or
none H the flamer that burns twice as
bright Burns half as long all weapons
have plus three chance to critically hit
but equipment condition decays 15%
f it all comes with like a bad
side wild
Wasteland unleashes the most bizarre and
silly elements of postapocalyptic
America not for the faint of heart or
the serious of
temperament
uh should I I was thinking should I get
the DLC or not I guess it's too late
now um
yeah I'm not going to pick it I was
already warned that chat will try to
influence me to do things that might not
be good for me and my experience with
this game if we want this sounds like
it's going to be trolling me a lot and
this sounds like something more for
people who played the game
before and I'm more experienced with it
so I'm not going to I don't know it
sounds like it's going to [\h__\h] up
everything
I don't I don't trust you with this
one I feel like you're not saying these
things in my best interest was it from
am no no no not from am am just told me
to press
F5 uh adds a few silly
things it just gags
what always go wild wastelands well did
I'm a pick Wild
[Music]
it's not bad please trust
us I'm going to have hallucinations
probably more Easter eggs well I don't
I'm not going to understand Easter eggs
am
I uh let me look at the other ones maybe
there's anything I do like more well
while using guns and energy weapons you
fire 20% more slowly but a
20% but it's not like it's turning into
slow motion
right due to a small size you have plus
one agility but your limbs are more
easily
crippled from frag grenades to throwing
spares you can throw weapons 30% faster
at the cost of 25% less range H not too
bad you have plus 10 action points but
your Reckless nature causes you to have
minus two damage
threshold
H it's more for second playthrough see
that's what I thought
yeah the wild Wasteland it's really
bad Kami Kaz don't do it don't do it for
first okay your Mele and unarmed attacks
do more damage but less critical hit
damage ah no I do want my crits what do
you think I put the luck in for your
good nature at heart oopsie what is it
uh more prone to solving problems with
your mind than violence you gain plus
five to barter medicine repair science
and speech but have minus five to energy
weapons explosives guns
[Music]
me I don't know these I feel like I
could make a better decision if I played
the game before before while wearing any
type of glasses you have versatile
versatile
glasses plus one perception I mean that
doesn't even do that that's just a joke
that's just a
joke it doesn't even do that much it's
not that versatile to be
honest don't have to pick yeah while
using guns yeah I don't have to pick
this
now I feel like these are all stupid
small frame is good okay but one only
one
[Music]
agility for being more easily crippled I
don't know if that is a a good
exchange that's 10% more one out of 10
is a
lot okay
G [\h__\h] is going to be bad for a beginner
right you know what [\h__\h] that I'm not
doing any of these I'm
sorry I'm sorry if that's boring to you
about does it I'm not going to be
manipulated by this dude or any of
you yeah vanilla Wawa straight edge
straight
edge yeah I make my own choices let's
go are you leading me out can I not stay
sir well thanks for helping me here
these are yours was all you had on you
when you was brought in oh really I hope
you don't mind not that I would remember
look I thought it might help me find a
next of kin but it was just something
about a platinum
chip well if you're heading back out
there you ought to have this they call
it a Pip Boy I grew up in one of them
vaults and made before the war you did
we all got one you must be rich a much
used to be now but you might want such a
thing after what you've been through
what was the experiment in yours
something taken from you and put this on
too so the locals don't pick on you
for was my wife's 21 I think she was
about your size and she hardly wore it
after we left the Vault felt it was too
Brazen nice I I do get a vault jumpsuit
even though I think the character is not
from the Vault
right I could visit the Vault oh let's
[Music]
go let's
go one of the best vaults what what was
their
experiment the place was pretty good
really yeah I'm a courier can Vault
dwellers not be couriers after they've
leave the Vault uh you shouldn't have
gone from uh what do I do now you should
talk to Sunny Smiles before you leave
town she can help you learn to fend for
yourself in the desert oh she'll likely
be at the saloon the saloon I reckon
some of the other folks at the saloon
might be able to help you out too the
metal fell Victor who pulled you out of
your grave anyway you ever get hurt out
there you come right back I'll fix you
up but try not to get killed anymore I
do have this feeling that I became a
ghoul I still don't really know
though no no no no hardcore easy
decision wao
that light felt like a bomb was just
dropped but
okay they went that
way where where's the Sal ah over there
maybe hello
FR howdy partner howdy might I say
you're looking fit as a fiddle uh I've
had FID
days oh you you duck me out oh wait
there's more answers I've never seen a
robot like how did you happen to find me
how did you end up in good Springs do
you know those who those man thanks for
thanks for digging me out I'm always
ready to lend a help and hand to a
stranger in
need is there a brain inside of this
thing or is it just uh
[Music]
mechanics I'm a
securitron robco security model 26 but
okay if you ever see any of my brothers
tell them Victor says howy so this is
all fake we're not having a real
conversation then [\h__\h]
you [\h__\h]
AI I want to talk to real people stupid
customer service man real people please
you cannot solve my
problem Oh
workbench it's an actual
workbench are we playing rust
yeah he saved your life yeah but like
he's like programmed to do everything
like he's not actually he doesn't have a
soul he doesn't have feelings he didn't
want to help me because he wanted to
help me particularly he doesn't give a
[\h__\h] about me does he please save the
game f five
okay hello easy Pete howy what can easy
Pete do for you something
hard why you call E P was a prospector
until I decided to settle here to get
away from the
NCR now we just take it easy and help
out with the Brahman and big horners
what's a prospector ah here like digging
for gold and
[Music]
silver nah N means I poke through old
buildings looking for working Tech thank
you for the membership gift some folks
just call it saling but never lack the
term way I see it salvage means it's
broken near worthless me I look for the
good stuff guns chems spare parts good
money in it mm good bottle caps in it
right don't get me wrong the ncr's got a
lot of decent folk in it it's just that
they make you part of them whether you
like it or not towns like good Prim
don't stay independent for long not if
you've got something the NCR wants still
the NCR keeps the legion away what's the
legion they're slavers led by a guy
named c ah it's the the ones that came
from the not sure how you're supposed to
say it a couple of years ago they tried
to take over Hoover Dam but the NCR beat
them back the NCR didn't or couldn't
finish the job why the legion's got its
strength back and is getting ready for
another round at the dam my money is
still on the NCR winning but you never
know I'll singlehandedly kill them about
Aries on the Nevada side of the river so
keep a gun handy you don't want to get
caught by them I probably
will the dam Powers a lot of New Vegas
and then there's all that clean water
lying in Lake me too do anybody who owns
the dam owns the
territory
okay nope had a pretty good claim once
way out east by the river but got run
off by Raiders eventually got too old to
keep going
out what's what's big Corners meat and
hide mostly can't put a pack on them
they just lay down until you take it off
what can find a bunch of Wild Ones high
up in the hills but got to be careful
around them they can put up a decent
fight
if huh do you know anything about Victor
the machine harmless no matter what TR
are you sure she thinks it's hiding
somewhere I sure it's harmless but I
think it's just a broken down Relic with
no place to be jingle jungle
jingle oh that I sing H maybe if it's in
that K program that we use thank you for
the red super chat
com unfortunately I had to get rid of
the radio songs but I replace it with my
own count country and uh blues uh
playlist
yeah the one in the fany suit seem to be
calling the shots as as much as I know
other folks in town might know more word
of advice though if you ever a catch up
with him watch out the man's got cold
eyes like a snake can't be trusted I
just
like cut out his eyes then the problem
is solved keep your gun handy if you go
poking around some of the abandoned
places around here like the
schoolhouse Critters move in there
sometimes okay how do I turn on the
radio maybe it's still too early cuz we
need to talk to
people oh hello Cheyenne stay
don't worry she won't bite unless I tell
her
to okay you said that's so monotone I
wasn't sure who you were talking to
uh uh you could teach me how to survive
in the desert I guess there's a thing or
two I could show you sounds like you
need all the help you can get after what
they done to you thank you meet me
outside behind the saloon catch me
outside how about that she looks like
she's from The Witcher I thought I was
playing Fallout did I accidentally
install The Witcher
whoa what the
hell is that my music that I put in it
could
be it honestly could be it sounded like
that
steel well the blunger is not going to
be worth it n none of this cleaning
stuff is going to be worth it but yab I
can't just steal things not now when
they're still nice to me
hello that doc Mitchell sure knows his
stuff doesn't
he that's all way too many strangers
coming into town these days no offense
you don't like strangers well I mean
honestly in the in the world like this I
would not like strangers either
whoa where is she
here kill dog wait is he pooping
now see the SAS Barilla bottles on the
fence there take this and try to hit a
couple of them okay take this she
says fire to fire a weapon push Mouse
one
oh I amim what what it's lying to
me well I am is amazing oh R&B to aim R
that's the right idea look down the site
what what's with this this a fake bottle
try crouching down and staying still
it'll help your
aim Nice Shot well that's a start but I
don't reckon you came to me to learn to
fight sasparilla bottles tell you what I
got to go chase geckos away from a water
supply anyway darn Critters are
attracted to it why don't you come along
all right uh I'm in follow me it's just
down to the southeast a short ways okay
let's go oh I'm still crouching
okay cute
doggle is that a
husky he he walks funny he's like a a
vipp what do you call vipp in
English can I run faster
please hold r
y be you scare
me I
can't seesaw yeah it runs like a
seesaw
see I think they
[Laughter]
saw funny what we're going
far I saved 1 minute ago
you don't wait you still don't hear the
S oh oh okay I have to fix something I
changed some things because of the
Blu-ray problems that we had behind me
there we got some geckos to clear out
bunch of little monsters is what they
are seems like Doc Mitchell treats more
gecko bites than anything else let's see
if we can get a little closer if we move
quietly we can get the jump on them more
likely to hit something vital that way
mhm okay
are they behind
here okay you're on what where give them
help well
where
what what
where what I don't see any
any I think I hear something though
maybe here
come
on
okay
search I
take uh take all exit
e did I take
it yeah
is there more
lady to enter Vats push
V what what's v pushing V but nothing's
happening speak of her again you can
press V for auto him ah so if there's
enemies friend hello how are you doing I
missed you so much I thought I was all
alone in the world oh man it's so nice
to see someone just like me here out in
the wild we have so much to catch up
about man I want to talk to you about
how I freaking
died friend I'll see you later friend I
got to talk to that crazy lady that
looks nothing like me unlike
[Laughter]
you good
friend girl is going to think you have
brain damage understandably right me
having brain
damage see you're getting the hang of it
there's two more Wells that still need
clearing you want you can come along
it'd be worth a few caps to me oh [\h__\h]
yeah shouldn't take more than a couple
minutes especially with two of us come
with me
okay the geckos are not
getting my why am I so oh there we go
are not going to get my water and not
going to touch my friend
where are
they the getos oh there oh you shooting
too
now wow nice
one oh oh welcome to the VA Tech
assisted targeting system or Vats
displays the chance you will hit along
with the condition of each body part can
attack your can attack accept your
actions should I be doing this
left click on the left or right arrows
to switch to a new
Target the number of attacks you can
make is limited by your action
points
oh what oh
oh no what uh
[Music]
oh then I don't really have to aim
anymore just roughly I
guess I did it I
suppose I didn't do it what oh the dog
was faster than
me no where'd she
go what where she where'
she where' she
go
[Music]
lady I don't know I I looked at the
compass I don't understand
here this
Arrow whoa who she's shooting something
huh
who the big but oh there there it
is feel like she'll be done Quest failed
Quest failed go what
H the the wait sorry I stopped moving
the
tutorial Quest failed back in the saddle
what did she die
no
no a
left hand like [\h__\h] oh wow what what
do I do I I I I no is this
bad that she
died she can die well I got
lost oh no
where's her
body yumy what about the bottle caps
reload
[Music]
please all
right we shouldn't do that normally
though it's
boring I keep on not
realizing that I'm in Crouch mode
shouldn't take more than a couple
minutes come with me okay I'll follow
you I'll follow you this time I lost you
last time I'm sorry I'll protect
you ah this one we still did
together this one I didn't run away yet
I think or did
I yeah
yeah oh sh uh well whatever oh did it
work
wa okay but like do I do this All
Time come on had some good shots now
sheesh or was that
assisted or did she leave no oh she's
leaving oh she's slowly leaving
partially limited by action point up to
you that was me ha I got good
aim yeah well they were walking straight
up to me why are you running in slow
motion
or what is she
doing what how is she doing that that's
some skill man
oh come
on wait that's a person I shot the
person ah they're dead I guess that was
supposed to happen I
think I don't need aim I feel like we
had this in GTA or so too where I just
didn't really use the aim
ever field hand outfit a cute outfit
let's go but I I mean does that cover
The Vault
outfit I can save the
lady ah Hell's Bells there's not a day
passes by I don't tell people not to
come here by themselves but I want the B
people your word just isn't good enough
for them then this happens well it's a
part of life out here best to accept it
but you did what you promised staying
out here with me here's my end of the
deal one more thing I wanted to show you
thought I might teach you about living
off the land and making useful things
for yourself
interested yeah all right then we'll
need a couple ingredients to get started
going to want some Xander rooo and a
brock flower Xander think now baby Brock
flowers growing up at the graveyard and
I seem to
remember s back in the day in my house
back to me and we'll get
cooking you don't have much to fear in
the Wasteland don't take aim at the
veteran whoa whoa whoo come San there's
some I feel like there's some are those
Korean super chats by different people
is this game really popular in Korea for
some
reason water should I drink that is that
radiated same guy okay
okay she's walking so slowly now where
are we going lady I
forgot water is
safe oh
that would have been so cool if I would
have gotten that shot
right why is she walking so we are
dismissed everything all right
no well let's just finish this first all
right see we're still doing something
then we can talk preferably somewhere
where I can get okay what are we
doing what she says we need to do
something without you or
what
here what am I
doing ladies and gentlemen you're
listen I think that's my radio
[Music]
ah Brock flower and exander root okay
okay
okay how how to
tap where would that be around where she
[Music]
is nothing here really looks
like what I need oh what happened with
my music
what
happened it was still on it didn't work
it broke it
broke marked it on your mini map on the
big arrows oh okay okay
okay is it over
this someone no they're not to
short I don't know why it's not working
you may revise your character
what no no I'm good I don't need to
change my name I'm
Wawa why what what is
that maybe wrong Quest I left her no I
don't want to leave her again uh I'm
just following the
marker this one or that
one maybe this
one well that's Mighty
far open your
map
how it's not
m is it always the pit
boy it's probably that one on the left I
thought it would show
maybe what what what quest
for the pipe
boy can I restart my radio is that like
a shortcut
to change the song or
so I'm back here again
what I have to really go this far to
find what she's asking
for hello
friend my friend's not answering me even
further I suppose so they won't she
won't jump when I'm like too
close there we
go tree
hello it looks like there's nothing
anywhere what a [\h__\h]
wasand quite
literally wasting my
time hold
R oh thank you oh thank you that's a bit
faster I'm just back to the city to the
town
what the
[\h__\h] I guess one item is here and then
one item is
there is this
not what are the red
dots
uhoh Well it can't be that
dangerous what the [\h__\h] they're so
small ah
ah
go
no
why you're supposed to be a pretty
mantis you are a pretty mantis just stop
fighting me I
can't you're too small I
can't no
[Music]
why was that such a pain in the
ass oh man the first one was still
decent oh
God okay wait this
way huh
H what where
did what is it like in
here or in the in the
house I have limited weight not a
hotel oh
[\h__\h] oh crytical
strike wait what not moving
yet thanks for showing me that like I'm
so
cool oh yeah be oh not again oh not
again I'm so
helpless oh thank God
it ni okay okay okay
okay okay you say I don't want to pick
up everything but maybe a few
things
empty is there nonempty ones
no activate terminal some terminals are
this is what you talked
about are protected and can't be access
accessed without a password if your
science skill is high enough you can
attempt to hack the terminal selecting
the correct password will grant you
access if your guess is incorrect it'll
be shown how many ladders match the
correct password oh that's fun look like
a little game Hangman
game four
tries set terminal
inquire well do I have enough science
for
this I think I do right enter password
now
uh huh what do I choose from what how do
I enter it do I choose one of these
letters pick a word but there are more
than four
letters
what it tells you how many letters are
oh uhoh what heading entry denied six
out of seven correct what six out of
those letters were correct
or
what I he ing probably
yeah
whoa enter no exact
match
uhuh uhuh disengage
lock granted
unlocking takes a while what again or
what the safe is
open do I
what do
I exit how
here is this a safe oh that was the safe
that I shot
who oh H I took it
all did I take
it I think I took it you're
dead Okay but wait I didn't find the
thing that I actually came for
Cup and the toy car I I keep on pressing
escape thinking that that's how I get
out of it it's
outside is it around here I'm
confused what does it look
like what the [\h__\h] that thing is huge
I don't know what it what it's supposed
to
[Music]
be a at the tree
chunk
what on the
stump what there's nothing there
how do I check the local map don't tell
me to do it just tell me
how I would have opened it if I knew how
it was not
M I looked right at it but it doesn't
give me any prompts to pick anything up
that's what I'm looking
for what what the [\h__\h] is it
what the
[\h__\h] what this what that blends in so
much and and when I look normally it
doesn't show me anything and the prompts
are really tiny
sander
root all right next thing is this still
the okay now we're going towards the
next thing oh there's another robot here
or is it the same
robot
hello hello Victor it's you
again happy or are you all called
Victor this looks like bees or
so oh they separated oh are they coming
after
me oh hello hello sir I should not be
shooting around so much here huh if
you're if normal people are walking
here it's just
dust well you never know it could be
toxic
dust in a radioactive world I don't
trust even dust anything can be mutated
it could be mutated mutated
dust I'm basically watching Lucy of
course you
are I mean any beginner would probably
roughly act like this and not know what
they're
doing don't say no that's not true don't
don't I don't hear any music ha
radioactive
h ah ah
[\h__\h]
scorpion don't touch
me waa it looks like a crab
scorpion bik
scorpion
nothing nothing on
you don't look behind
you where is behind
me
[Music]
be I'm a
be oh these percentages are really low
is that even worth
it oh uh-oh
get closer
oh oh did it get caught did did I get
it is oh
dear oh
dear don't shoot your poop at
me oh it got scared it got
scared hm is my is it really what where
am I shooting does it shoot lower or
higher why did I stop moving again when
did I stop
moving I didn't realize a bird
actually the aim thingy is confusing
me I think C is auto move
forward there's a special item
here die bastard die and give me your
meat juicy juicy boat fly wow butt meat
[\h__\h]
die okay I'm guessing the item is
somewhere
here was
this is this is this the item you mean
limited
edition snow Glo these rare prear
artifacts are widely considered to be
useless BS bar BS that rumor has it sub
collectors will pay dearly for
I found it I think but that was not the
thing I really wanted for the
quest
oh found it this time easier do I need
more than this one
no bring it to Sunny In The
Campfire all right let's go
oh this is the local map oh
well oh
well do you get like a mount
eventually where you can go faster
with like a
horse no no no Mount what the [\h__\h] is
that
unbelievable unbelievable
barel I don't know I I'm trying to talk
in a Texas accent but it always just
turns out
British I can fast travel back
there well that is extremely convenient
to be able to do that right from the
get-go wait did I go to the right place
she's not there then wasn't she going to
wait there or wait here
you waited for
me thank you let me see what you got
yeah these will do just fine just fine
all right now we're going to be making
something folks on the trail called
healing powder go on over to that
campfire now give it a try can we
have healing power instead of healing
powder just one letter or less come
on to drink some water
okay so uh
what I'm
going
what what everything all right
no until next time use the
campfire uh healing
powder okay I will have some leftover s
The Roots how many one hey that's not
bad see all it takes to make a recipe is
the right ingredients and the right
knoow sometimes it won't be a campfire
you need might need to do some work on
your guns and ammo maybe uhhuh important
thing to get is it's all the same idea
you just need to find the right place to
set up shop workbench or reloading bench
whatever mhm well I hope that's enough
to get you started I'm heading back now
hope I didn't miss anything good on the
Juke bus C would never forgive me your
dog hey do me a favor Trudy she's the
Ender up at the prospector kind of the
Town mom she likes to meet newcomers
she'd be cross with me if I didn't ask
you to poke your head in and say
hi okay is that a quest all right I I
take it as an
order is
that should I teleport there
yeah my broken radio is still
on my broken radio
why is it not
working why is it not working I named
ITC official is this only talking or
also music difficulties with it monal
line to game is Just Buggy Man I
prepared so many tracks I can play them
like separately but then I have to like
tab in and out a lot also music oh okay
wa I think
one Anonymous official told us a serious
mechanical failure would have been a
disaster because of the age of the train
and the scarcity of the replacement
parts these headlines were brought to
you by would it be on the first one on
the second 21 everything's better when
you experience it in a vault got some
Dean Martin coming up talking about the
greatest feeling in the world love and
these headlines were brought to you by
Vault 21
[Music]
Vault see I'm already
distracted party but wait I want to talk
to the lady let's turn it off for a
moment
moment it's too loud can I can I change
the
loudness of my music it's too loud oh
it's the
radio I
think you don't hand Ringo over soon I'm
going to get my friends and we're
burning this town to the ground got it
why is it adding tabs at the bottom of
my
game what am I
what press
uh
H oh okay thank you that now if you're
not going to buy is that like a cheat
code box or what the hell is your
problem I have no
problem what what was your problem
that's the real
question pretty much oh I found the
cheat
console well you've been causing quite a
stir glad I finally got to meet you
welcome to the prospector
Saloon what was with that argument looks
like our little town got itself dragged
into the middle of something we don't
want anything to do with about a week
ago the tra Ringo comes into town
Survivor of an attack he says Ringo bad
men after him needs a place to hide be
we figured he was just in shock so we
gave him a place to lilow we didn't
actually expect anyone to come after him
he's holed up at the abandoned gas
station up the
hill you mean murder him that's not our
way even if Cobb is scum he can Bluster
and threaten all he
wants is that what you want me to like
what some of the others like Sunny will
probably stand up for Ringo if he asks
for help which he hasn't personally I
hope he sneaks out of town one night and
takes the powder gangers with
him Chang gangs really the end NCR
brought them in from California to work
on the Rail lines problem is it turns
out that giving convicts a bunch of
dynamite and Blasting powder isn't the
best idea was a big Escape not too long
ago some of them stuck together so they
could make trouble that's what we're
dealing with
now
uh
what damn that's a lot of questions
uh what what do you want me to do help
Ringo if you able to get Ringo out of
this mess you'd have a decent reputation
around good Springs I'd even set you up
with a discount of course helping Ringo
would also make the powder gangers mad
and they've got a lot of friends out
there oh should I do
that is that like a main quest is there
even a main
quest yes up to me yeah up to you
do you want to I don't know sounds
dangerous but if I if that means I can
meet someone from the
Beatles that
sounds amazing like a once in a lifetime
chance don't know why you want to do a
thing like that yep you'd get on their
good side but people around here
wouldn't appreciate it one
bit okay uh I think I guess I'll wait
can I sell things her too Y what well
level
two ass sign 13 skill
points
13 you sell stuff next door ah uhuh 2550
7500 break
points I see
see prices you
get your weapon skill determines your
[Music]
Effectiveness gun to
25 would be better okay okay
okay and
yeah then this can be 25
too long Pig we'll work on
it I hear some radio that's not mine
lady oh wait
what you're choosing me you're choosing
me you're offering me new things to
choose like from these weird things what
the
[\h__\h] wait this is is different it's a
perk not a trait with each rank in the
Swift learner a perk you gain an
additional 10% to the total experience
points whenever experience points are in
oh more more
exp in comod you do plus 10% damage
against male opponents outside of combat
you'll sometimes have access to Unique
dialogue options when dealing with
people of the
opposite sags
it's really strong in combat you do 10%
damage against female opponents oh ha
outside of combat you'll sometimes have
access to Unique
dialog
spicy with the intense training perk you
can put a single point into any of your
special attributes wait what if I do
both of these oh oh I can only choose
one
okay it's exactly what I I think it is
oh really if the retention perk the
bonus is granted by skill magazine last
three times as
long we can pick both but
eventually you can pick the other later
okay thanks Trudy so does that count as
a quest now
it's a
terminal but I feel like hacking it here
while the people are here is not a smart
idea where are we
going
there where
what
Co the gas
station I don't think you picked
what of course I
did behind
you the
[\h__\h] I did I feel like I did what what I
I just what I can I can I choose it
still
I can't not take a perk
okay some people say I did some people
say I don't didn't some people say I
can't not pick
one is it
free let's
go that's close enough who are you and
what do you want with me an autograph
please
sorry about the gun I'm friend you just
caught me off guard that's all we got
off to a bad start yeah what's say we
start over with a friendly game of
Caravan oh you know how to play no is
that a card
game I don't want to play a card
game yeah he doesn't look very tough
though I hear he's afraid I'll shoot him
down from one of the windows when I see
him and he's right I'll have a much
bigger problem once his friends show up
there's no way I could handle all of
them in a gunfight mhm that's why I'm
here we can't be the Power Rangers
instead of the powder
gangers
but uh my Caravan was on the return trip
from California and heading back to the
company branch in New Vegas when we got
jumped not even to drop your weapons and
hands up before the bullets started
flying hey yo we put up a good fight but
there was too many of them I took a few
of the bandits down before I ran so I
figure their friends are out for
Revenge I'm going to lay low for as long
as I can assuming the town doesn't throw
me to the Wolves I've got no chance
against the gang on my
own I will help oh you need to okay but
this sounds more like I'm offering my
services for money and this sounds like
I'm offering it for free
all I've got left on me are a handful of
caps but you get me out of this and I'll
make sure the Crimson Caravan pays you
back you got my word yes yes I I will uh
consider it
or yeah let's sound not quite available
all right was there anything else you
wanted to talk to me
about no let's just do it let's do it
how we going to do it
yeah do I have to do the the
game he's chilling what is
it it's a two-player game and The Winner
Takes the whole pie you build a caravan
using the cards in your deck no game is
option the goal is to create Caravan
bids that beat your opponent's bids so
there's more strategy than luck involved
damn it it's why you won't see Caravan
in any casino too slow paste and more
importantly no house edge here take this
holotape it goes into more specifics
about the rules Hol life you'll also
need a deck so take one of my spares so
you feel like playing a game
no all
right goodbye yeah well so how do I do
this thing how do I help
him can I open the crates I'm scared
that he will take it as a as something
negative
well it's
empty turentine
you have some
ammo as long as it's not red
uhhuh sir you could have off offer those
to me as payment for the job when you
didn't
interesting oh that looks yummy I think
sugar
bombs I should loot all the s s s
Parilla that I can find
okay all right
whiskey
flour empty soda milk bottle oh
oh you ready to
go
oo
stick how do I how do I start this I
didn't accept the quest
okay don't sleep dude they're going to
kill you in you sleep you're not allowed
to sleep right right now what is it I
guess I have to ask this question
again all I've
got we'd just end up sharing the same
grave if it's just the two of us now if
some of the other people in town were
also on board don't worry I got bats but
[Music]
okay I was thinking him myself actually
who's going to watch my back while I'm
watching yours oh okay I don't need my
back watched chat is watching my back
they keep on saying watch behind
you uh okay start with Sunny Smiles
she's been friendlier than most around
here okay but is she the one in my
tutorial I think
so is she back in the building at the
Jukebox
probably jukebox
addicted but you're telling me I can
never get one of those
bikes why
not what a waste of
potential hi there sticking around good
springs for a while longer I suppose so
I'm going to help Ringo take on the
Power Rangers I might need your help say
no more I'm in
Easy joab talk talks about leaving us
alone if we hand over Ringo but I know
his type he and his friends will come
after the town eventually however
between Yi and Ringo we aren't exactly a
force to be reckoned with a lot of
people around here look up to Trudy if
you could convince Trudy to join us some
of the folks in town might decide to
help out as well do I need Charis I know
easy Pete's got a stock of dynamite
somewhere and Chad just got a shipment
of leather armor we could borrow talk to
them as well okay finally there's a good
chance we'll all end up with extra holes
in us so if doc Mitchell could cough up
some extra stim packs stim packs I feel
like stim packs were in the show too
yeah yeah yeah he was like oh I got I
got a stim pack in my
bag they
were h a silver tongue would help
convincing Trudy that we had a good plan
to win the fight would also help
okay easy Pete's Pretty protective of
his Dynamite you'd have to convince him
you know a thing too about explosives
before he handed it over well I don't I
don't think give is in Chad's vocabulary
even with the town at stake he'd still
make you barter with him I'm not good at
barter either I
think I H GE I also help sorry I didn't
want to ask you anything I wanted to go
and give it a try let's start with
uh her hello so you're planning on
taking on Joe Cobb's gang it's a a big
risk but I suppose you have to do what
you think is
right and there's an explosive magazine
somewhere
okay H you should help me take down the
powder gang bullets explosions lots of
fun speech 25 is that what I have or
what I need for this to
work need a saloon and store a good
spots to stage and Ambush if I had to
help
I need well I don't know how much I
have I have enough oh
okay I was planning on sitting this one
out but for some reason I can't help but
like you I'm with you let me have a word
with a few of folks see if I can't round
up some more members creating while
everyone does own a gun we could stand
to be a little better equipped a general
store probably has what we need in
stock okay
be careful
thanks so what next
uh you following me
now oh she is well I'm following
her was I supposed to get something from
you howy think
so here you got Dynamite it would help
us beat the Power Rangers too dangerous
going to kill all yourselves if I let
you touch it better leave then join the
gang and you handle
it so can I just not have it
then too dangerous sorry blow yourself
up blow your neighbor up blow the whole
town
up okay guess I'll die thanks
man so it's like limited what I can
actually get to help
me Hey sir you got the lever armor or is
that not you must be the one doc
Mitchell was patching up I've got plenty
of supplies for sale even got some if
you're hurting for caps
I've now just hold on I never voted to
take on the powder gangers that's a
thousand cap investment you're talking
about oh man I don't have enough for
that either
[Music]
easy
o do I have something else that they
said I should do that I can do oh oh who
I F the game crashed quick save find a
magazine might want to buy some
ammo okay let's see how much is the
ammo oh where'd he
go
sir
sir sir oh there you are W you also BL
into
everything you looking to buy some
supplies
yes can do but I need to buy the right
ammo guys which one is the right ammo
what do I
need I don't
know magazines under eight to
bump five 56
just uh this one
maybe how many and how much is
it oh I have I have 741 caps I probably
get all of
them but am I buying or
selling oh oh okay but I I'm buying
right
I have one out of 13 and I'm
buying no
cancel you'll be spending 90 free caps
oh no
Cy so
less maybe like half and I can sell him
some stuff maybe I don't know is you got
to you guys got to tell me what's um
what has value and what I want to
keep my junk what was the junk the B the
the the bug meat
stuff turn hides into belt uh-huh can I
sell the Mantis
stuff
yeah pre-or money I guess I can exchange
for real
money
okay okay uh I guess that was fine
pleasure doing business with
you take it easy now how do
I appar can consist of many different
types of gear ranging from clothing to
and armor to sunglasses and hats blah
blah blah blah
blah I want to keep wearing the Vault
outfit but I guess this is better
together
probably although this has like Mele
weapon plus two and speech plus
two higher the T
better what's the C
andd keep the
jumpsuit condition ah it's in a pretty
bad condition
[Music]
is this really better might as well keep
it on for the bonus right I I think so
too it's not much better if it is better
at
all I have a different gun too
okay but I'm using the rifle okay okay
okay can I see my perks ah I I did take
it we good we good
okay uh what did you guys say what else
I could uh
check
uh easy P Dynamite was a no the chat was
a no ah doc
Mitchell doc
Mitchell is where
here
yeah how to can I teleport there
no uh is it that thing up there I think
so we came from there
maybe Ro map to teleport oh okay that's
it okay what's
this doc I'm
back you have have to help me please no
one else wants to help
me I don't know why I'm I'm obviously a
protagonist I need to save the world and
you can help me with it welcome back I
had H you wouldn't need to come see me
again so soon what can I do for you
you're a good man so you going to help
me
right seems like wherever I go it's
always the same folks just never leave
each other alone seems like not much
good in a fight with my bum leg and my
supplies are scarce but I'll give you
what I can spare thank
you so can I get healed
here qu
okay
you seems like he can heal me any time
for
free what a
deal okay
then uh uh I go back to the gas station
I
think and tell him we
are somewhat ready at least I was H able
to hire one person with my
skills that's more than
nothing wake
up check inventory for skill magazine
what's going on did Sunny agree to help
us try to hurry
uh I don't know what it looks
like I don't think I have one to
eight I don't think I have one
[Music]
okay so what's going on
did well I guess that means we're ready
to go yeah unless you think there's
something else you can do no
unfortunately not all right
I'm time to look alive the powder
gangers are here to play many at least
six joob included it look pretty mean H
let's go I'll be set up near the store
let's hope that the gang doesn't manage
to make it that far
[Music]
y
y I mean it can't be that difficult
right is that one of
them is it he has a gun but he doesn't
seem to be one of them oh we're just
getting into
position you got you going to go
there howdy
howdy
oh where's my
gun come
on I should hide
danger
danger what aim
D's guys
[\h__\h] do I how do I heal Myself by the
way I died here A bunch of times I think
maybe I will too uh
use your steam pack well okay my weapon
is in poor condition and can do more
damage if repaired great uh uh
uh why where the [\h__\h] is I'm I'm just
going to shoot like this that stop stop
reloading it's so
annoying oh is that one of our friends
okay is it is it good are you friend
wait they did all everything for me
they did like everything for me it was
jamming for [\h__\h] sake I guess I did it
y I'm liked enough news of your good
work has been passed around that people
like
you oh I'm shun by the powder gang
Rangers oh well that's okay sh me then
huge favor for this here these are
technically Crimson Caravan funds but I
know they'll understand once I explain
00 thank
you not being able to pay me
now o n it's it's okay I'll stick around
for a bit longer but I'll be gone in a
few days if you ever visit New Vegas
look me up at the Crimson Caravan Camp
do that somewhere else I'm not at New
Vegas now is the dog
dead is the dog
dead no
hey there wait that that's that's not
acceptable is she not going to
cry I feel like I need to reload but no
this is how things are This Is War you
know the
dog I'm not going to take it no no
no what I thought this would be a little
bit more longer and the fight ended
actually surprisingly fast okay how do I
fix my weapon
here
[Music]
uh my pit
boy oh my pit
boy uh this one oh I have two I have
two
oh choose item to repair
with oh the same one oh I guess maybe I
picked up one now from the
people oh
nice oh
okay does that make sense it didn't look
so good e so I wanted to repair it too
if I have everything double might as
well repair it with the
doubles okay are we
good wow Cleaver how do I switch weapon
do I have to go into my pit boy for
that oh look at
me
wow what I have to go to my pit boy just
to change my
weapon
lame all right so we did it what now I
guess I'll talk to the girl about her
dead
dog let's console her comfort her I
mean is she
around Ringo thanks again for all your
help yeah
I can assign a hot
key
how where'd it
go
oh try die too
no no no no no no no I think I saw her
walking
too that's her right no that's Sunny SM
but try I also saw
walking that'll teach the powder gangs
to avoid good Springs in the future um
you're not sad about your
dog sure can take the Road Southeast out
of town till it hits the freeway prise
the town with a roller coaster straight
South can't miss it why do do a good job
of keeping the highway clear but I'd
keep your gun where you can reach it
easily you never know who you'll run
into off the road you'll probably start
running into hostile Wildlife my advice
would be to stick to the highway when
you
can sure what do you want to
know to get to Vegas okay uh just go
straight to no no no no no you want to
tell me about a shortcut or so H I've
been warned about shortcuts if you want
to know
anything well let me go until next
time I don't need to go through the
shortcut thank you I've been
warned don't go straight avoid the short
yeah yeah yeah I know but I don't really
I I so I remember like someone showed me
a map I need to go down better than up
uh a yeah cuz they were saying like go
up here or
so I guess they were I don't know it's
hard to say but I need to go down I
think okay but wait what how did she
mark
it what
Prim well I'll just follow the road this
way she didn't really give me a quest
oh I can equip the quest oh okay okay
okay uh inquire about your delivery
assignment with the administrator of the
moav express and Prim find the man who
tried to kill you all
righty here we
go to
Prim let's go goodbye
everybody it was a short time but you
saved my life so I saved
yours One hand washes the other oh you
know what time it is Radio
time it doesn't
work it doesn't
work
uh that's
unfortunate a't
it uh how do I uh
no why is not working I put my music in
there
oh
whoa what
well when I open Task Manager I I I
can't see my mouse it's just gone the
game stole my
mouse the game stole my mouse oh okay
now I see it I took my mouse back I'm
just going to I'm just going to put in
my music into
VLC uh
oh
think why does it load so
weirdly like I have
[\h__\h] all the Sims 4 games and
it's packages in there
huh okay
Yeehaw let's go
Supreme I'll keep it relatively quiet
because I if I have to stop it I'll have
to Tab out and that'll be a pain in the
ass each time so let's keep it quiet so
that it doesn't bother us too
much the
banjo how fun can I open this no we
should stay on the
highway a
highway I want to ride it all night
long some weird sound effect we good
we're
good go check your gra for it's too late
anyway my grave oh oh oh
danger stranger
danger
no oh Prim Las
Vegas what
it he's not red on your compass so it's
fine ah okay okay
okay it better stay that way there's
someone down there too I think oh no
that's just a corn cob or something like
that
dangerous corn
cob
oh more people there who are they if
they're friendly then can I talk to
them you scared the [\h__\h] out of
me who shot
me
what I steep on
mine what the [\h__\h] it said something
about the Powder Rangers but they were
not attacking
me my my
leg my
leg my leg my
leg someone help me with my leg
no Oh I thought it was like like sharp
things on the
ground yeah oh
radiation radiation jump
scare I can't really be helped Can
it can there be M's
anywhere that's [\h__\h] up
man St
pack okay let's learn how to use ah in
order to heal a crippled limb you have
free choices sleep in the bed find the
doctor or use a stim pack to heal
yourself and hardc block stim packs can
be used for General healing or they can
be applied directly to a limb uh to heal
crippling damage to
heal navigate to left click on the limb
to use a stim pack on the lim okay
uh stats
screen what what did they say
okay this one oh
oh
oh here doesn't doesn't look so good
here
either okay but I can't fix the leg for
real for
real wasted stop too much well
oh there's an
[Music]
enemy oh it's a cockroach oh and get
goes oh they're finding each
other oh where's my weapon where's my
weapon where's my weapon the
[\h__\h] okay they ran away
yeah oh another
one
[\h__\h] oh I did hit it
oh oh nice nice nice
nice
oh nice
it's it kept on running like it looks
like it keeps on running instead of
directly running towards me like to the
side so I thought I thought oh okay
whatever am I on the side of the NCR do
I like the
NCR hey where the hell do you think
you're going PR is off limit
I I I want to go though they're
friendly some convicts from the prison
up the road have taken over the town
that's up for me to the dead or in
hiding what's more there are two tribes
of Raiders causing trouble in this area
as well you'd be safer heading back up
to good Springs thanks for the
membership
[Music]
welcome we'd love to but they don't fall
under NCR jurisdiction even if they did
were in no no shape to protect
them we don't have the equipment to take
out the convicts and even if we did we
need some extra hands for backup you
should talk to Lieutenant Hayes he's in
a tent down the road okay just stay on
the west side of the overpass if you
don't want to get shot West Side what
where can you mark it on my map
he didn't add
anything what where continue this road
and stay on the west
side oh wait I ah [\h__\h] I have it on Loop
okay I have to Tab out one more
time okay
uh stay on the he means the area on the
left is hos this fire over the bridge to
your right I see a bridge here
but oh Oh I thought that was a dog and
he was shooting his own
dog does he need
help go to your right over here
he said something about a tent I
think loot his kill n it's just a
Geto
West what's this
do we have first aid stuff let's
go bobby
pin this maybe steady what's this what's
steady and very valuable usually you
should speak with American accent while
playing this not that I really know how
to do
one take it
all doesn't dirty water
sell steady is drugs drugs
okay good to know let's find Vault 22 I
want to go into a vault any
Vault oh are you the one I'm looking
for I can drop mail here how
fun oh or aren't you the guy from before
I'm Sergeant McGee of the new California
Republic army
if you want to talk about something
speak to Lieutenant
Hayes I'm from a hub originally but it's
been a long time since I saw it I'm on
my second tour here most
non-commissioned officers
are goodbye it's in one of the tents
okay maybe we should not go in with a
gun ah he's in here ah
oopsie oopsie
nice tent you got here I
mean the mattresses look disgusting but
fine right it's
fine
Haze sorry sorry the button is too close
to e sorry sorry sorry I'm Lieutenant
hazes of the new California Republic
army fifth Battalion first company
what's your
business I don't know honestly we were
sent out here to hold back the tie of
viix from the correctional facility as
you can probably tell we aren't doing
the kind of job we could be
doing Mission isn't a problem the
problem is with supplies convicts are
better armed and organized than our
Intel initially suggested I'm trying to
get some reinforcements here maybe some
guns with some Firepower but [\h__\h] things
are just going
slow most people just call it ncrcf
that's where is main quest guys a little
bit ago the convicts there staged a coup
kill the guard I don't understand what
I'm supposed to do been ransacking the
area I wanted to go to Prim and they
said no is this main quest okay not much
they've taken to calling themselves
powder gangers mostly because they've
taken to using the explosives meant to
clear Boulders As Weapons they got
organized faster than I would have
thought most of them at least thankfully
the small group in town here seem to
split off from Main Force so they aren't
getting anything in the way of
support I have some free no you don't
really have anything that I can ask you
dude don't get my Hoopes
up so do he didn't really tell me to do
anything did he I'll
sleep maybe does that heal me a little
bit
they won't stop me yeah but I don't know
if I
is now you got to cross the bridge into
town
okay I'll
try maybe I find some stuff no empty
maybe on the second
floor a
mattress
are oh this is
red
why are they empty
yeah then it's not worth taking them
right well
out by the way uh no never
mind I don't want to steal it's okay I
won't take it
then it's been a long Tour all I can
think about now is going back home your
face reminds me of some actor I
think look
funny I should paint it red [\h__\h] yeah
I'mma painted red is that a
mine that looks like a mine okay okay
okay okay okay now I have an eye for
mines folk how you don't if I walk
around it
it's okay okay oh okay now I have my
answer um even even around it it's
dangerous okay but it didn't hit me
right so why why can I not
enter what's the problem
here seems fine so
far it did hit me my HP looks full to me
but I honestly don't really
know should I
disarm am i
hidden
yeah wait didn't they say something
about yeah no no
uh oh I can disarm the mines I thought
you should you you mean you meant I
should disarm
myself I'm hidden am i hidden really
where are they sleeping
still should I kill them when I see
them
oh that's a person do I
kill yeah
he's not
red
yet or he's dead maybe he's dead looks
yeah he is
dead oh now he's naked too uh-oh oh
[Music]
oh too far oh wait
wait I'm scared I'm scared Don't
Panic y my health is already so
low help me help
me help help me
[Music]
a my health is low wait thing my game
crashed oh no I I pressed the thing
again wait okay ah it didn't crash I
just pressed to cheat console again uh
uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh how uh I just like use this or uh no
I I choose the limbs right I can't
choose this
leg I don't really understand this I
used them all I thought I had like a
million of
them can I eat the
steak drink some sod
pop sod pop the [\h__\h] is sod pop
[Music]
oh I get B caps from drinking them
nice how we looking
okay
like
oh you like that
shut what
ammo am I out of
ammo fre I'm out of
ammo
what I was so close I could have giving
him a head shot what the
[\h__\h]
uh
uh uhhuh
[\h__\h] come on for [\h__\h]
sake why don't you die was I too
far oh his head
dropped I missed
one who isn't this the rounds I use for
my big weapon and we got a stim pack too
okay this is
good so dangerous
so dangerous is there a lot more because
I'll be so
[\h__\h] I'll be so [\h__\h]
man doesn't look like it for
now roller coaster over the casino wow
wow never seen a combination like that
before should I go in here what's where
am I supposed to
go
here well that barely heals
is it okay to have
[Music]
radiation it's an overtime heal oh oh
yeah it's coming
now it has worn off okay the radiation
has worn off or oh no the healing has
worn off I
guess a little radiation is fine that's
what they say
okay I'm fully healed
now y it y b y I don't know what it was
brought you to Prim youngster but you
might want to rethink your plans Town's
gone to hell oh are you nice you're not
going to kill me why are you so red is
that blood in your
face Johnson Nash is my name husband to
Ruby Nash lived in Prim going on 8 years
now thick and thin I'm a Trader
primarily for what it's worth with
things like they are I also run the
local Mojave Express
Outpost what do you mean
no it doesn't look very natural to
me well I don't got any work right now
sorry to
say m ah I lost a package I'll tell you
whatever I can you have a delivery order
show lost
it wait are you guys making jokes when I
when you say I can't say that because
what oh are you joking you're talking
about one of them
packages that job had strange written
all over but we couldn't turn down the
cast some man stole my package a man in
a checker suit and some fogs did they
pass it this way well now that you
mentioned it a few nights back one of
the townies was out Scavenging for a
supplies he said he saw a fell with a
daisy suit come through with some of
them great con Misfits they was talking
about a
chip Daisy suit is that the pattern or
like is that a type of
suit I guess it's the type of
suit well for that your best bet is
going to be talking to de beagle since
they came to town he was keeping a good
bit of notes on them and he was slinking
around bison Steve when your pretty boy
friend came through he may have heard
where they were
going that cowboy robot had us hire six
couriers each was carrying something a
little different pair of dice chest
piece that kind of stuff last word I
have from the office it looked like
payment had been received for the other
five five jobs guess it was just your
chip that didn't make it God damn it and
I put so much skill into luck do the job
canell hope a storm from The Divide
skins him
alive wow well that's where you came in
uh-huh uh he canceled yeah got this look
when he saw you next down on The Courier
list his expression turned right around
asked me if your name was for real for
real for real I said sure as like a rain
you were still kicking then he turned
down the job just like that I asked if
he was sure it was good money no let
Courier 6 carry the package that's what
he said like the Mojave sort you out or
something one
out no idea sounds like you two had a
history for him to act like that and
turned down the money too hope he didn't
see any trouble in that package of yours
maybe thought your name was bad luck
enough for me to
say look there's a cowboy robot over
there nope different fell what I didn't
even see had himself a face on a screen
and he talked more like you or
me don't go getting yourself shot
so at least I'm not getting shot in here
am I
I feel so
safe howdy partner welcome to the Vicky
and Vance casino and
Museum who who were Vicky and V where
you B partner hiding under a rock
partner Vicky and Vance were this
nation's fourth or maybe fifth most
infamous celebrity Outlaw couple ever
that's who they was Prim slim here can
tell you the whole story if you can
spare a minute to hear the
tail have it your way partner maybe work
up your C osity by having a look at
thring exhibits like the genuine death
car advances machine gun genuine death
car happy TR car
there
howdy they want to shake my hand yeah
[Music]
I was more asking why you're read
because I thought maybe like they're
affected by some radiation or they have
blood on their
face the graphics don't really make it
look
natural and ah NAA Cola they had that in
the
[Music]
show I guess they couldn't get perms
from C caola or even
Pepsi
blood okay uh what what are we
doing oh man the bgm
is wo it's
cooking it's still telling me
to do to go to
the oh
uh to the hotel that's a hotel it says
Casino I should go into Maj Express
building first
okay it looks abandoned
though damaged
robot this is an advanced model model
robot with uh re forced Frame It is Well
weathered and appears to have seen a
good bit of action there's very little
in a way in the way of serious
damage I have good repair but do does it
does this does
this should I do something here fixing
the robot is really good
okay some servers and gy Gyro
gyroscopes thanks for the membership oh
H what would you like to do I don't
[\h__\h] know need to be recalibrated
replac but it looks like as though the
robot can be repaired repair 65 or
higher required
65 I don't think I have 65 and do I have
the the parts
[Music]
even probably
not without parts
sence 55 or higher required this is I
think I I don't think I can do
it
well I guess it's not MOJ cuz you guys
still keep on saying it
Mo uh Express drop boxes like this one
can't be used to deliver items to any m
j Express Dropbox that you've
discovered is that how you you say it
moav oh the J is an H moav move move
move that was far
off what's
that
cassero R Ruby rub Ruby's casserole does
it mean not that ruby made it but this
is Ruby
where is
Ruby well she's not
here why' you tell me to get in
here I think it's the casserole made out
of Ruby
yeah okay I'm going to that would make
it a ruby casserole one it was pretty
much that
okay uh oh oh
[Music]
oh oh
maybe oh I can do several yeah
B well thank you for standing still
caution yeah I
am
caution oh terminal maybe we can hack in
again how
fun it look like I I shot the
counter enter password now
okay uh
let's try with somehow two out of seven
correct let's try with
company zero out of seven [\h__\h] let's try
with somehow oh oh maybe maybe o and uh
e sounded one of the seven
[\h__\h] e it's even the o or the E maybe or
the S sir or just the S maybe just the s
back out Escape now leave the terminal
ah
ah try again oh I can try again
reset oh
easy are these new words is it a new
password
strange h
stamina s and I maybe send
no
consist look for brackets in the
terminal new password each
time the brackets if you find you can
replenish
what just Spam whatever and get
lucky it was so easy the first time we
got a good one right
away ah you mean these brackets together
not a single
one is what I have to find to replenish
what's
this what about this it's like several
ones a lot of them like that oh oh
hacker hacking to the gate 12 okay
veggies was one uh no veggies was
two D was
one no idea
I had no idea about this it
really
uh e you think yeah well e and then what
dealing four out of seven dealing four
out of seven e
deleting for both dealing and leading
was four out of seven
oh I I thought that would help me but it
didn't give
me a b a
bit should I leave the terminal exit
no
no no oh it removed one false
answer another
hold I was so
close to the
g wow
okay
a
uh Bandit it's m
manhood
stacked zero out of seven y so I what so
this one does this re
reset
yeah no it just removed the
dot oh the effects are random
oh so at this state I would wouldn't
want to try another one when I already
tried one or I find more I can find
more is it okay to try more of
those ah 0 to 7 is valuable oh I guess
so it tells me none of those letters are
being used
true
y found the exact match hey
hey
hey unlocking dot dot dot can I go is it
done wait wait where is it what thing
did I even unlock the
door probably I'm scared
oh I I picked up lunch boox lunch
boox tin
can people died in here
[\h__\h] coic head crippled not my head not
my [\h__\h] head ah
ah ah
a I have a super stim
pack H oh his oh his head oh
okay but my head not doing so well
either
oh ah he's so
close ah
d
[Music]
y why are you not going
to
Bastard die die
no
oh why does it take so long to kill them
I'm literally shooting into their
heads what the [\h__\h] man why wasn't there
two people originally
yeah B they have really [\h__\h] strong
heads man I want to open this [\h__\h]
again I didn't get to look
properly I pressed F5 just now don't
worry
we didn't get set back that much
anyway to to seven
studies it's like a little mini game
stained okay it's the
St it's the St state but not the a well
yeah uh order
I but not the a I guess
or yeah no
no or or it's the I and the S and it
could be
cide but then it would be free in this
one wow wow wow what about praise could
it be but then it would be then it would
be also more
letters oh
yeah if it's just two out of studies and
stained it can be either D and I or E
and D or
St but not more than that so what if
it's leaders could that be cuz it has
the D and the e but no the A and it
would be
free uh what crafted could it be crafted
no then it would be free could it be
wearing it could no it would be free too
could it be
guarded it could it could not be guarded
rebuilt no it could not be rebuilt could
be
blazing AI it could
it blazing what about studies then
blazing
I no it could not be blazing could it
no re rebuild rebuild where is
rebuild rebuild um
i e d no it cannot be
rebu because then it would be
more so it's only two out of seven
correct has to be
less
matches it has to be less matches like
okay uh what about leaders e
a d no no huh huh
sending e i n
no crafted a e no
huh got praise parties a i e
no h leader
fit
leaders I need to see it what headset
head e a e e a d
no
zealous E A
yeah in case of studies it would be you
and E Yeah
zealous no it was not zealous that's
also two out of seven
[\h__\h] ah let's find the hacking
the hacking guide thingy hacking hacking
code this one anything that's like more
together of the special signs right d
removed [\h__\h]
no oh this one dot removed
no this one too this one counts too
right that removed
no give me knes this one that removed
[Music]
no I'm spending so much time on
this how many of these are in
here maybe I used them all up
already
uh-oh it's definitely Seaside
the fourth row on this side on
this ah oh yeah it is
together oh replenished allowance okay
okay okay okay I can't like scroll up
that's bad
delas was it the EA or the oou
man
uh what do you guys think it is we have
a few more tries now
ceiling for
sure four out of seven correct ceiling
stealing is there
stealing stealing but that wouldn't that
be more than four out of
seven and that's that's probably not it
reading reading
probably that's compared to ceiling
that's one two 3 four no more three four
five n that's
five I don't think it can be reading
Seaside one two
three uh four yeah
okay are they going to Ambush me again
when I'm in
there I was safe yeah
unlocking click
saving door
opening waiting for
enemy
yumy did he see me
come
on Jesus Is there going to be more where
that came from no not for now
maybe
Dynamite let's go oh my God his
head oh my
God okay is there anything vable in here
it has to be what what's
menet oh it's a head part of a head
first eight box oh St packs and purified
water wow wow wow
wow
oo crispy real
bit no I'll take it all
thanks Red X is that good that's
probably good
right have you gotten better armor
probably uh appar no wait stats
wa wait wait what wait what where do I
where do I look
again I guess I do look here uh I have
so many now what the
[\h__\h] can I wear a helmet and a suit oh
yeah okay
dt2
um what's the best thing I have here dt2
dt2 dt2 dt5
powder oh it's the Power Rangers will
they think I'm one of them
maybe don't wear
it disguise as a me members of the
faction now consider you a friend while
enemies of that faction will attack you
on sight regardless of your personal
faction related relation with
them and also the yeah well for now
while I'm in here maybe it's okay I
don't
know NCR will attack you now well
well
well yeah for now and then take it off
when I go outside right okay okay then
they won't shoot me when I'm in here
right but then what am what am what am I
in here for if they don't shoot
me nice
though oh there's a key
an eyeball let's go search the eyeball
nothing search this eyeball nothing it
has seen nothing oh blood pack might I
use that for healing wait there safe I'm
blind a lockpick skill or a wait but I
have a key what about my key maybe it's
for this
no
no how what do I have to like
use if I want to use a key does it use
it
automatically did you unlock it from I'm
pretty
sure hey would be automatic uh-huh if it
fits disengage
lock don't have to do it twice right
unlocking dot dot dot and then it's gone
like I would think that did the
trick it didn't open the save man need
another terminal or come back later
yeah okay so you guys are not going to
shoot
me re re really can I rely on
that
[Music]
hello empty burnt
book pre-war book toy card
uh are these all
empty empty
empty what a shitty store zero out of 10
on Yelp [\h__\h]
this this could be full maybe no
empty oh star bottle cap at this one oh
I can take the bottle cap wa does that
count as the bottle cap the the the the
ones that you take as
money small
startup
hello what
what why I'm your
friend it's a special oh I see
well
well oh um why why is he like
this can I shoot two
people this is pretty
low but I'll
try
I what happened with your leg man it
didn't work
hard well still ended up pretty well why
did this happen I thought they uh
convicts I guess okay they are different
I thought it was only only the Power
Rangers in here wow should I heal oh he
got a stim pack and ooh
dt1 you got a lot of
stuff varint
rifle okay nice nice nice
nice W mole
rat 20 NCR
okay chill chill chill chill maybe maybe
we should eat something
[Music]
though all right it doesn't stack
right
oh Nua
Cola oh okay it's worn off already no it
does stack you're carrying a lot of
cloves yeah I want to sell them or I
guess I can repair some of these to like
combine them at least maybe they will
sell for more them do
they do they sell more repair stuff
sells more oh
[Music]
awesome oh this one too maintain oh
because I'm wearing it now
what
yo wow T
side Super
Trooper on maintain
repairing
pinging am I overweight or like where do
I see is this like my weight wait that's
my radiation right
or W ah okay we're still
good oh oh oh it heals too though that's
cool
oh can I drink
more H did it heal oh yeah
oh right radiation goes away right hold
it I'm I'm scared hold it
objection
oh slurp slurp slurp slurp slurp okay uh
which way do I want to go this kind of
scares me this
door oh
God wait okay they came from there maybe
I go this way first maybe it's empty
here
okay
y safe oh
yeah no way
Jose there's nothing ever in the garbage
ganss are you friend oh are
you uh
coughed oh am I supposed to rescue you
what what are you oh pickpocket Deputy
beagle oh I'm I'm here to save him wait
let's change clothes do you think he'll
get
it do do you think he'll get
it should I stop hiding you need yeah I
don't want to talk yet
or like can I not just explain it to him
while is cuffed while I'm wearing
this that would be
nice I didn't want to interact
yet he's cuffed so you can ask
him okay
oh did he see me oh yeah
maybe oh [\h__\h] like
that y it
[Music]
a kill him
why why why why why you die why why
would you die why will he not die
what the [\h__\h] is that 95% for
no what the
[\h__\h]
wait why they not coming
back oh man the armor but not on his
head whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa what's
happening I'm feeling funny
do I need to I'm I'm not that low on
health what is
happening my concussion my head is
crippled uh uh uh
y oh
y is this okay I don't want to overuse
it again you're still dressed as a thank
you for reminding me so should I change
it use a better weapon now okay uh we
can I mean I kind of like the
pistols
DPS DPS show me the DPS again 29
12 12 it's not that
bad use shotgun for Close Encounters
well I can't switch that fast also
because I don't know how to put them on
the
shortcuts I wanted to find
out you don't have a ammo
huh huh I need different ammo for for
the V the
V hold numbers 1 to n
oh is it on two
now what the
[\h__\h] I'm scared to use
that I'm pressing though but nothing's
happening hold then
click I'm wasting ammo
[Music]
uh
uh baseball bat was very efficient in
worms worms but I don't know if I want
to use it
here
uh does that change my short cuts if I
combine
these no okay
H okay it's cleaner now and uh okay I'm
not going to remember what is what
except I need to remember five is the
incinerator uh which one which one is
the Varmint
Rifle uh I don't
know maybe I'm just jumping
I don't even recognize it by looks this
is this is the
incinerator like that no I
don't nice shot was that what what did I
just use I I don't know what these
weapons are
really uh
oh there's another
one don't lose your head okay thumbs
up um the revolver the Magnum revolver
okay uh I don't know what I really want
tell me what I want what I really really
want where's the vment rifle
oopsie is this the V is it just looks
like the vment rifle
have I been
detected come
[Music]
here
what
sick is there
more can I can I
enter have I cleaned it
out yum
is there is there mines
no 360 no scope sneak crit yeah wow wow
wow wow wow wow wow wow okay I think I
think it's all empty now pretty
much before I I need I know I need to
talk to that dude just give me a moment
to see if I can find anything
interesting could be clear m
Min empty soda is there something
behind
no there's never anything in the garbage
can ah I knew it's always in the banana
stand not in the garbage
cans it feels like they knew something
was coming
Lantern hold tab for lantern
uh-huh so I hope this dude won't like
think I I I'm fooling him just because
I'm changing clothes I want but let's
let's it would be nice if he was so
smartly programmed that he would realize
I'm helping him I told you powder ganger
everything I know please don't hit me
anymore he doesn't let me go around the
corner and change my
gloves if that makes you happy wait I
got Lea armor now normal oh did I just
pick that up from one of the dudes I did
not have that before hey I'm a different
person it would be so very delightful if
you set me free he believes me let's
go yeah that's the strongest armor I
have now let's go besides the other five
DT
one he totally does not recogn ize
me no object
permanence pretty good for early game
yeah y lucky I hear you may have
information on some cons that came
through here with a guy in a checkered
suit my good lady I believe I may have
some information that would prove useful
mhm if you would just untie my hands I'd
be more than happy to share that
information I have with you can I have a
please oh no M I'll set you free oh
that's just marvelous marvelous I think
I'll be making my way outside the air is
a little close in here okay I'll see you
outside then if you try to run away
instead of fighting at my side I'll kill
you myself
wow I can do that
but stick with me okay I can say it
normally too apparently I don't know if
that would work though I guess not if
they offer me a speech
option oh well of course
I'd never let you find my you that
anyway right without it you lead the way
I think they're all dead though anyway I
don't know if I need your help I I
cleared it all okay you following
me yo there's a lot of food here I was
almost going to go without
it what's this I'll take it
are you following me there's a second
floor just return to the casino casino
is sorry I don't know I don't know
something scared me H I thought this is
the
casino [\h__\h]
scary he's not following
me no he is
okay just okay I'm
scared I'm scared
okay I already looked at that there's a
second floor but do we have to look at
it maybe
not what the [\h__\h] is this
door
scary optional I thought was the
elevator
ah if you want to loot
the second
floor but do you think there will still
be a lot of people
there did you save yeah I'll just save
one more
time all right we'll check it out let me
drink some
though there's quite a few up there m
okay all right we'll
try we have another dude to help us
after all right he's going to help oh he
can probably also die I
assume which wouldn't be so
good oh did he stay below did that
sucker stay below
oh not really
helpful I guess it's too risky to
you oh he's still here he follow he
followed me he just can't walk upstairs
I guess I had to carry
him okay sneaky
sneak okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay
uh
oh ah oh nice shot dude
what I shot so far from
him dude nice
he's really
good damn should I open this
door locked very easy okay wa wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
uhhuh I go sneaky NY NY NY NY NY NY NY
sneaking like a snake
[Music]
somebody
here wonderand
glue oh
toilet so far not so
bad this his journal gives you all the
info you need to keep the main quest
going oh really well we we would want
him to go
back you can see enemies for the oh well
you know um I I I want to play
realistic uh no but I want to return him
safe and
sound oh wow he's aggressive does he
have like unlimited ammo cuz he sure
shoots like he
does oh he's so good
wow andp is do help me dude you like
that oh wait I'm pretty good
too oh thank thank you I was I was I
could have done it on my
own
totally oh I'm okay now I'm really
[\h__\h] heavy
uh I will just uh
put something together
again wow I got an
achievement repair your Lea armor if you
can ah I
can't it seems I can't but I got a cool
desperate
hat
wow oh c reneer outfit field hand outfit
a
sure seems like that's it and then maybe
some armor uh
[Music]
weapons
mhm oh yeah I'm way below the weight
again good good good good
good
Cleaver I like the sounds it makes it's
like
ASMR this way buddy I already looted him
you're not getting
anything what whoa whoa whoa what what I
got to level
up and I I hear shooting
uh what did we want to get up I
think was it lockpick no I feel I'm not
sure but lockpick getting it up would
probably be good right yeah maybe it was
what we were going
for okay repair for the
robot speech
[Music]
240 almost
guns and science would all help you okay
if I can't get there
[Music]
anyway then a bit more
guns Effectiveness aka the damage I do
with it
had
enough come
[Music]
on
no he
died [\h__\h] should I I
reload I think my last one was well a
few minutes a while ago maybe he was way
too gressive he just went wherever the
[\h__\h] he wanted
to well is it a big reward if I bring
him back alive no is not
[Music]
important oh man oh man well he helped
me for a
while let's keep him dead damn why' he
go in
there
why
huh oh there we go should I take his
things it will they won't know right
like they won't think I killed him I
need the journal for sure right the
armor sorry I feel so
bad I I made him NY but I can combine
the
armor let's
go are these there some of them have
like similar names but kind of different
are these just like the same things
basically if it's offering me to use
those for repair anyway
long fuse Dynamite free armor check
Journal
[Music]
okay Journal journal what where and
items
H don't think it's
data
M this is most unusual the powder
gangers have visitors today I guess
there's a first for everything now those
tough looking fellows must be great cons
I recognize those funny helmets and
leather vests from stories I've heard so
what are they doing with that Dapper
gentleman who wears a checked suit I
wouldn't mind a suit like that they're
talking about heading South toward
nipton then West to Novak where they'll
meet up with someone uh-huh I guess I
could track them if I needed to but no
the town of Prim needs me here to Serve
and Protect thanks for the membership oh
my I think I've been
spotted yeah
B okay did that update my quest head to
Novak through nipton ask around Novak
about your
attackers beagle is dead find someone to
speak to about helping
Prim m
[Music]
maybe but okay like I I I'm scared
alone I'm
scared they just came from up there
man that's a side quest good
exp H if I knew where to
go yeah
be
y that looks good dirty pre-war business
wear maybe it looks like the suit though
has no DT though so we don't want to
fight with
it anybody there
no oh he
left he's kind of there though come on
fight
me where is he oh behind the wall
maybe I'm
scared oh he left he's
gone why is he gone where'd he
go you said no so he left oh good
understanding seems my Charisma is
pretty high after all oh
slurp slurp slurp
SLP around the corner
probably or down I think down maybe I'm
just
jumping do they show me on the compass
even when they're on the lower level cuz
like he's supposed supposed to be there
maybe I'm just jumping he's around the
corner he got to
be anybody
there oh no maybe he is down
there
easy that was a good position for you
for me oh dear my God
this
game
mhm biker goggles
cute okay we're good getting back up
there is
difficult
[\h__\h] uh how did I get
up before Oh from
here TV show was just like this yeah and
was
indeed oh
man W
jumpy Coca-Cola so worth it so
refreshing I watched this documentary
about a country that like or city
country or city where everybody just
drinks Coca-Cola because it's cheaper
than
water and it's making them really
unhealthy and it's kind of like [\h__\h]
up
because the I guess the the people who
sell it are you
know making money from it obviously
they're profiting from their bad health
so they're
just yeah they're just
like continuing hoping for it to
continue mhm
wait I'm confused did I come from
here yeah well I think I checked
everything
out as probably was a but not all of
Mexico right I think it was a city there
then or a village or I don't know not
all of it yeah just a city a specific
City okay yeah we did it I think K mus
let's go
back play start to play K from B
openings got to go home don't want to be
lost don't want to become snail where's
exit
uh this way this way this way no not
that
way yeah yesterday we watched half of
the season because I kind of [\h__\h] up
like oh my God I brought out all of my
[\h__\h] old consoles first I tried
playing uh the Blu-ray I got the Blu-ray
yeah iied I tried playing it on my PS5
then it told me uh wrong region I'm like
oh [\h__\h] yeah right my PlayStation 5 is
from Japan cuz I got it oh I got it oh
for
free
um huh is there terminal
no and then I brought out my PS4 and
then it didn't work there because
controller didn't work even though it
should have worked and then I tried
different controller and then I tried
keyboard I tried Mouse nothing worked
eventually we tried PS3 even I got my
PS3 but when getting the PS3 I dropped
my Wii U so my wi U might be dead but
not sure yet I didn't try it yet and
I've tried so many
things to get all of that to work so
Troublesome eventually we were able to
make it work on the PS
four was it or was it
PS3 not
sure yeah I revived all my game consoles
they never thought I didn't think either
that I would ever use them again like
this sell the stuff where I would like
to sell it yeah can I sell it at their
headquarters over
there but you was not built like a
GameCube I wish I had a GameCube Cube I
I used to have it with my family but I
don't know where that went they probably
got rid of it at some
point I just sleep I can sleep over
there right
[\h__\h] I thought someone shot me as long
as just a land mine I'm okay but so
[\h__\h]
thank God they're not really mad at me
or are they for not bringing him back
alive we don't talk about it I never saw
him it's not like I couldn't protect
them more so I just I
just okay am I fully healed from this oh
yeah wow should I talk to them about it
yeah uh
no I'm not sure you should be
here what makes you think you should be
here who could help him go back to the
other hotel ah Casino oh okay oh right
the casino care the people care about
him okay okay
okay hope I'm not going to run into
another land mine
I guess I could have maybe fast traveled
oh
well Vicky and
V who died we don't even know oh man
sorry I'm confusing things I thought
they would know he seemed like he
belonged to
them but yeah I guess the casino people
told me about
him m
I'm so sorry I bring bad
news howdy partner welcome to
the should that it's I guess it's not
you I need to talk to who could there's
something like I need to find someone
for something uh to help with Prim yeah
helping Prim find someone to speak to
about helping
Prim uh maybe the bank
hello steal pencil you think that'll be
mad if I steal a
pencil can you help quite a town we got
here no Sheriff gets murdered and Deputy
beagle dragged off for ransom to the
Bison
Steve that should bring back the tourist
he's dead so
sorry they will be mad over a [\h__\h]
penel hey youngster still hanging about
PR huh
[Music]
yeah
uh well I guess you're going to have to
find us a new law man yeah I suggest
talking to those NCR Troopers across the
bridge I also overheard the Potter
gangsters talking about some ex- sheriff
on lock down
there yeah okay that was what the quest
wanted me to do right what about Prim
slim could he be Sheriff
well I guess I never thought of that I
guess he could be Sheriff if you think
he could be reprogrammed for it I mean I
I I met a robot
who spoiler alert don't listen for the
next 10 seconds from
now a robot who uh uh was leading free
vaults
so spoiler ends it ends ended spoiler
ended spoiler ended spoiler ended
although was it even a real robot can
you consider that a robot I guess it
wasn't really a
robot
[Music]
and ah anything for sale well can I
sell
yes okay so I just sell my [\h__\h] again
right like
gecko gecko gecko
gecko Geck
gecko G although I guess that could have
been useful oh
well not PCO
Gecko and I I I sell these like outfits
that I don't
need powdered gang armor should I keep
it it wasn't really that help maybe I'll
keep it though if I need to go
stealth keep meat for cooking uh can I
get it back for
free oh wait that's the wrong
thing where did it
go get i c d e
FG e there
Hydra I don't even know what that is I
saw it too in the inventory
though do I need the tire
iron probably not
right no
okay what about
wrench it's not worth much though
Wet Stone or maybe that's for crafting
sell V varment the extra one right or
mine the one that I've worked hard to
repair sell all those extra cloes and
weapons you have but which ones do I
keep the extra one
okay m
[Music]
single
shotgun psycho what the [\h__\h] is
that ah baseball
cap plain
outfit
uh that's a drug what's pilot light was
that also a
drug Le armor iner hyd
you need to Hydra
more that's also pilot light is
junk
okay this one although I kind of wanted
to see what it looks like it gives you
speech plus five though maybe I should
keep it but my speech is pretty good I
guess I don't need
it but that's pretty cool if you have
low speech keep it okay okay okay if you
have low speech especially I can imagine
it would be good goodbye cowboy hat
goodbye bonus limp damage yeah I'll
salad though I might find new ones
caravaner
outfit biker
goggles think I don't need
them okay
I think oh ooh can sell the second
pistol that was pretty repaired as
well okay I can't think of anything else
to
sell since you could say keep your speed
at 35 if you were aiming for 40
uhhuh you can sell NCR money Oh I
thought that also works as money
a b c d oh where is it it's not under
n ah H these ones
ah oh oh you can use it at casinos oh no
it's okay I'll sell it for now maybe
we'll get more and then we can use it
again cancel TR did I did it a did I did
I do it wrong sure yeah wait did I do it
wrong I'm so sorry I didn't know I
thought it was already final I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry I'll try to be
fast B goggles C outfit uh Claver uh the
coffee mug but I didn't sell that before
actually
uh
hide uh uh oh what about this honey M
pod what is that
sell want this one
and this one and this
one this one and this one tell me if I
sold something wrong I've all made that
mistake I've done it a lot okay happens
a lot oh all that okay okay it's
confusing sometimes
storm chasee I didn't see that
before did I H Tire
iron trooper
helmet Toren timee vment
rifle
wrench was that about
it my hat your
hat you so sold your I sold my own
helmet wh which one was it h the
Stormtrooper
one
stormchaser the triop I what ah oopsie
ha
ha what would I do without
you cigarette cigarettes do they heal
something let's sell them
baseball bat beer baseball bat baseball
bat let's sell the baseball bat
okay
accept except pleasure doing business
with you thanks
bro so now I go back to the people over
the bridge
right howy howy how how you doing how
you doing
do you guys do Blackjack I love
blackjack or make the robot can I do
that partner welcome to the
Vicky reprogram Prim slim to serve as
prim's Sheriff using free fish and
batteries I don't have
that but with science 30 do I have
science 30
now law enforcement protocols reinstated
partner initializing use of force
authorization authorization found yeah
yeah wow wonderful I guess I did help
them out 430 XP for that wow level up
okay goodbye happy so this is done right
y w
you
woo what do we want to level up guns
needs one more right was
30 that it needs and a lock pick up to
or guns guns guns spe by
five 50 is the next but 30 is fine okay
science to 40 will take a while please
hold please please hold the line please
wait
oh there's different choices too now
though with the educated perk you gain
two more skill points every time you
advance in level
ah ah
ah was I not told to do
this previous I feel like this is good
with the comprehension perk you gain
double the bonus from Reading magazines
I haven't found any when you're in sneak
mode you gain the option to eat a corpse
to regain Health wow but every time you
feed you lose Karma and if the there's
Karma and if the ACT is witness is
considered a crime against
nature ah there were cannibals in the
Fallout show right but they called I
don't think they called them cannibals
they gave them some other
name with each rank in the Swift learner
perk you gain an additional 10% to Total
experience point oh got s so educated I
have fiends is that a canni is that
really the same thing they in correctly
called them
fiends they're in this game
too oh wonderful don't Point your gun at
him he's the
mayor have you no respect for your new
robot
Overlord I totally do no but honestly I
would I don't know maybe it's like a
different that is perceived differently
in this world in day and age oh no okay
I guess a a a a robot mayor could be
programmed to be very not biased so
maybe it's more fair but like and more
organized but then also like I don't
know it has its ups and its downs I
guess like in one way I I feel like I
would want someone who also has
compassion you know the the but who
knows maybe they program the robot to
have Compassion maybe you can do that
too but okay IRL right now I don't think
that would fly
in in in real
life he's a good Sheriff I'll trust him
I'll have to trust him okay
so we did that we can now go to Novak
through
nipton and find the man who tried to
kill me eventually Noak through
nipton that way over
here Novak out no not Novak
nipton we go here over the highway over
the
[Music]
highway uh is it this way I can't tell
yeah this
way no more mines
please careful on the
highway mo mo mo mo havy Outpost is must
visible place
oh my radio
sto I forgot to look it
properly
okay but did I say wrong again
Mojave move Mojave movei Mojave Mojave
move I don't know what I'm
doing
Mo oh there's a lot of people there oh
they're danger people stranger
danger he's not even using his legs to
walk I see that from here sus oh no now
he
is uh are we going to have a
fight you hear it from the NPCs
okay
sorry kind of scared me it says Cal so
even if I change my clothes it won't
help you have zero chance to hit it's
just 3e%
[Music]
here ah wrong
thing what oh they're not fighting
against me
right
oh I don't
know oh where did my rifle go on
it what was it again oh
I think I took it off of
that oh no oh maybe I didn't maybe it
was
that I sold
it I sold the good one well it's okay we
we
we I was looking at chats to see if I
did something wrong quite a
lot okay they're gone they're walking
away oh what do
you are you shooting each
other oh I think he shot the other
human oh
man the Viper gangs loot the bodies do
the NPCs ever loot bodies
I scared this is
hopeless oh because I shot someone who
was running away but I I gained Karma
couldn't It Be Good
Karma oh okay I didn't really know that
they would run away I thought he would
just run away a few steps and then maybe
shoot me
again oh it was good bro
okay Jackal gang
member thank you oh police
cars or never dead
dude
wow so much stuff is there people in
there hey yeah B what the [\h__\h] are those
ghouls
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait what the [\h__\h] what the actual
[\h__\h] the what
the wait I can't I can't
aim okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
what are you doing I don't know I don't
know
69 okay yeah B I panicked it was like
too close I wanted to go outside because
I can't I just the inside it just feels
uh not so good to fight in there also
I'm fine I I looked bloody but I didn't
take I didn't get that much damage
surprisingly Vats yeah Vats is a good
way to chill things down yeah you're
right oh Mama
Mia yeah I
panicked but it should be empty inside
now I
think what why did you guys not fight
the the ladies huh are you guys friends
H do you have a
packed oh wait can we hack something no
yeah no no
lame turn based RPG with
fats no no no I've played a lot of
turn-based RPGs is not quite like this
my new favorite RPG witch spring R is
very different but it is turn
based so you are
wrong oh this is bigger than I
thought why do I
hear why do I hear
bugs oh oh they're behind the doors
oh this is just like in Thief
simulator
probably oh rotate the Bob this looks
pretty similar when torque is applied
the closer the bobby pin is to the
correct position or Sweet Spot the more
the lock will rotate before the bobby
pin breaks only when the bobby pin is in
the correct
position will the lock rotate fully and
open you can also try to open a lock by
forcing it but if you fail the lock will
permanently broken and can only be
opened with a key oh
okay
uh I did
it that was easier than a fee
simulator I think oh bubble caps
clipboard
empty first
try oh oh chunky wonky walked by it I
That Shook
Me First Aid in
there I this
[Music]
ah oh not in here
either but another one of these oh
empty they're all in here
there's a lot of
them
oh
huh there we
go oh they're behind bars they're eating
a
human can they come through can I shoot
through for sure I
can oh yeah oh yeah they're in
jail I should get karma oops for uh
shooting these keeping them from eating
the
prisoner wait stop moving so much you're
annoying
me oh oh
wow are you are you scared stop moving
out of shock
W head shot on the
Mantis I can step on them
what why are you
dead what happened
wow six of Hearts tops uh okay
dirty water iguana bits King of Diamonds
Ultra lugs what is
this police Buton silenced
pistol and a St back
yo he had a lot of interesting things
Carin cards a sneaky gun y I keep I have
to treasure that one
let's never use it h let's never lose it
not use it oh
Hydra those are
explosive now that I see them like this
I realize they are explosive reloading
bench okay so how does this
work I don't know this looks
complicated tell me guys when I ever
need to use that oh ammo box let's go
those are drugs oh
okay straight Edge Wawa will not use
it
wonderful wonderful I don't have the
parts
okay well that went well
is besides me freaking out a little bit
for a
moment I can sell the drugs if you're
playing clean well I
mean it's not really like I care that
much about that but uh if I get money
for it if I don't need to use the drugs
then I wouldn't if they're not
helpful thank you for the 10
memberships did you guys see the
normally I don't really watch the Hur
but did you see the new hura with Ollie
in
it that was hilarious actually
her voice acting was so funny she's so
intense the zombie one yeah and now I've
noticed this is the second time
recently
that uh should I go there that they're
using non Japan members so I wonder if
that's now
becoming a
thing cuz normally you know we just get
one like debut 3D debut
hura and we were told yeah no more H gas
it's just it's just the W one but oh God
maybe times have changed a little
bit is it hitting it like sometimes I
really don't know it has to be hitting
it right like I'm I'm totally shooting
[Music]
it I can't see the
percentage oh hello
like I can't I can't see the percent ah
there we
go I don't
know just keep shooting how far at the
bottom from the
enemy wasn't there another one ah
ah ah H is it is it
hitting surely that's hitting right I
have to look at the body when I'm
shooting but yeah it's doing
something
damn takes a lot of shots
yo no I never saw a health bar I didn't
notice it like
that so yeah anyway maybe I'll ask if
they're actually going to do um
more oh oh NP Road rest job if they're
going to do more Horas with foreign
members so to
say would be
fun
okay I don't know if the poison glands
are useful but I'm taking them maybe I
can make a
poison
poison a
poison the music's music the bgms are
not really matching right
now can I cook or sell yeah I guess I
can always sell can give to
Ruby okay wait wait a moment so
is this where they wanted me to
go no not quite it's just a rest St
okay well we want to check out
everything we passed by pretty much
always interesting stuff to find what is
it in here a
store why is it so why does it sound so
dangerous
why when there's nothing in here oo
oo there's no nothing oh lockpick skill
of 50 W energy
cell yum yum deviled eggs are
you too
heavy uh
uh I'll eat one thing
and maybe I can combine some of I I just
took too many things
again submachine
gun what the [\h__\h] is
that DPS
74 10 mm pistol is that good too m
okay
oh I can't really combine much uh oh oh
oh oh oh didn't realize I had another
one okay we're already
below a journal mayor mayor guess whose
luck keeps roll
oh what
oh wa data
M I can hardly I can hardly believe my
life literally I'm a Gap a g I don't
know uh just now I was approached by a
RAB intense young man calling himself Mr
Fox yeah right when we were alone in my
office he let it be known that he is a
member of the Season Caesar's Legion
whoa he knew that NCR troops and pwder
gangers often spent time in nipon it
turns out the that the legion hates and
wishes to make an example example
example example of both groups the NCR
for obvious reasons and power our
gangers for harassing harassing Legion
raing parties yeaw on this side of the
river did it TR read this no no come on
it had at least a hint of of taxes right
please wait so what I couldn't really
take in the information what do it
saying
uh it's some
mayor right uh he's probably dead I
don't know what oh wait there's more
what I didn't have to think a moment
about Mr Fox's proposition before
accepting it all I have to do is
convince the PES to kidnap the NCR
troops at not when both groups are in
town the legion boys will scoop everyone
up don't isn't that a thing like they
kind of add a little bit of a sh to the
s or is that somewhere
else ha for this simple task I have been
offered 8,000 caps I could almost go
back to the and maybe that's not
it I could almost go back to the NCR
right away but who knows how much else I
might make off this Legion lacky
I'm going to start stockpiling some
supplies in the safe house between here
and The moav Outpost just in case I
decide to head back home in a hurry R
signing signed with Steady Hand on the
keyboard super mayor Joseph B Stein
F what so he was offered good money for
doing something that did not enter my
brain and this was where he stored some
of his things
help me
guys sounds about
right Y and what the [\h__\h] did I just
take
what what where's the enemy
set a trap for helping Legion oh like
basically
betrayal this thing what the oh I didn't
recognize
you I'm not I'm I'm not dealing with you
now leave me
alone didn't work out for him
okay well
what is this this looks interesting
too this looks like it wants to be
looted as well or is this also some of
his stuff nah right
oh what are these
sounds Magnum
round interesting
stuff
okay is this just m sounds is kind of
weird it's not showing enemy wait
actually no it is showing an enemy one
no oh I so
scorpion no problem go to the statu
statues St
statues bit Ah those over there
wow what does that
mean there's so much Beach GM in the
game now it's mixing with my own
bgm a lot of a lot of people lost their
[\h__\h] here
huh oh oh they're friends thank god what
the [\h__\h] is that
cow
killed are they running away from
me holy
[\h__\h] what wow is it what happens to
Radioactive cows oh my God that looks
painful wait it's got two heads oh [\h__\h]
I didn't even
realize oh oh he's like running around
with it like it's his dog or
so dude he's got two heads and all of
this [\h__\h] on his back feel bad for
it uh oh no I have to go the other
way what radiation does to MF for real
it says empty I know I still want to
[Music]
look not
yet turn
around
H statues for exp okay
[Music]
who built these and when is this from
the prear times no right it would
probably be
[Music]
destroyed man war is not good look what
it has done to this place look at what
it has done to America yo
look what it has [\h__\h] done this is
quite the Steep Hill oh my
God war never
changes is that supposed to like be like
all thing a lot of things in life change
you want something that doesn't change
War yay is that supposed to be like
positive sounding like hey let's go I
love war because it never changes yay
I wouldn't romanticize it like that move
Outpost isn't move
Outpost in the year
20271 oh the
opposite
okay because some people look for
something that doesn't
change even in the song
[Music]
she sings I want something that doesn't
change like you want something that
stays stable in your
life so I thought that was what it was
saying the desert Rangers of Nevada and
Rangers of the new California Republic
met at this spot to sign the ranger
unification treaty under this treaty the
desert Rangers agreed to be absorbed
into the NCR in exchange for NC's
protection of the Hoover Dam New Vegas
and sou Nevada against the forces of
Caesar's Legion
o
friends in here no
Foos no F right no mofo hello Sergeant
kilborn coming from the north must be
crazy to Brave those roads
[Music]
any work around here nothing I know of
but if you've come from the north means
you can travel Freer than most around
here oh really might check the barracks
someone might need you to hoof it
somewhere just be careful you go up on
the roof got a sniper watching the road
what if your gear is in need of repair
HQ is also worth checking out talk to
Major Knight he can help I can repair my
own [\h__\h] got a pin and plenty of
ink Outpost Mojave Outpost watching a
lot of nothing feels like a big Brahman
pin for Caravans
they've been stopped for a while waiting
for the roads North to clear or the
clearance papers to go through uh looks
like you've walked away so if you need
to shake the dust off head to the
barracks the bar is there not much but
better than nothing hm the
barracks watch yourself uh are you
saying is he saying these people were
waiting to get
through I think you've been waiting for
a long time
no the other side
okay
prospector hey there what's the prospect
hey there that's all you're going to
say what you going to say
more hey there hey there hey there
prepare to
stop well they also look like they've
been waiting a mighty while oh the cows
oh man
[\h__\h] Ka I
so they're so
[\h__\h] surprised that like dogs for
example still look normal in this
game or humans for that
matter where are the ghouls I want to
meet a
ghoul oh no the
pen wait did they did he say go in
here well ghouls are a
thing no you
don't oh you'll
see yeah I guess ghouls are the humans
that got affected exactly yeah who are
youi but what about the sniper I don't
understand don't shoot me please also if
I go up there they'll shoot me is that
what he
means sniper is friendly oh okay I can
talk to the
sniper
sheesh not doing a good job sniping you
should have sniped me you a courier if
so
this might be your lucky day if you
don't mind walking a bit and your eyes
are
good depends on the work I think there's
trouble in nipton no traffic from there
on the roads while I can explain that
away the smoke from the town I can't oh
I'm sure it's been hit what I need to
know is if they survived it might be
powder gangers with all that smoke in
the air oh no there's anybody left
they'd be in the nipon town hall go
there check it out let me know what you
find okay m why don't you go check it
out got my post don't think I wouldn't
go too if trouble's hit nipton Town's
got enough camping spots to rack up some
easy kills not about to have Jackson
bust my ass again though even if I came
back with Caesar's head rather be
sitting here than in a
Cell uh pay
me all right look at you I'll fired up
and ready to go there no here that kind
of attitude listen I don't want you get
killed for this so if you head there and
run into trouble I'm asking for eyes and
ears not your life all right
uh oh okay I got the
quest not much to tell one of the worst
posts in the NCR if you're looking to be
anything more than a babysitter full up
here but just enough so we can't send
out that's why you guys told me to go
here for before because I have to go to
nipon anyway ers
can't spare men for patrols
or mind yourself just to get the side
quest
[Music]
N I thought I would fight in
here so many crates empty empty empty
not empty so many drinks wait maybe we
can oh maybe we can sell some more
things
inside
probably headquarters hello
hello how you doing how you doing
Caravan citizen Pilgrim
or eh what just need something for the
log book keeping tabs on traffic
throughout the Outpost ah most L just in
I'm
AER if you're looking for the commanding
officer he's in the back although he's
got a lot on his plate so if you speak
with him keep it also if you need any
gear checked we can get you up and run
once you P out the work orders and sign
for the parts of course
D goodbye who sells me some who can I
sell
too is this a wrong place
Mushy
Mushy thought so didn't feel right this
one
[Music]
door hey h hi wow ladies l a lot of
ladies
ladyes Lacy new face in The Outpost must
have come from the north so what do you
have you have corn can I have your
[Music]
corn work around here might check with
Jackson in the main building ghost G on
the roof above ghost was not a I said
that though might take a bullet some
night when I'm going to the TR she was
nice there was nothing [\h__\h] about
her take a look okay selling some [\h__\h]
again
uh brahen skin outfit what E I get some
extra skills from this but I'll sell
it
clipboard cram cram the picture looks
like
corn is it corn
just think lever oh ah two-headed cow
lever I thought it was just humans lever
for some reason oh it's
spam empty
[Music]
empty do I need these
things they don't sell well but oh
wait yeah is this the number the 55 what
does the 55
mean oh this is
oh this is
ammo
okay
ah
jet AP +
15 yummy but I'm on a diet sorry
jet is a
drug we don't [\h__\h] with that at kfp is
men hats also a drug looks like just
normal medicine Charisma persuation and
intelligence
wow it's also a drug well I mean in this
is so confusing in English you call
normal medicine drug and you call drugs
drugs we don't do that in
German and it's also kind of weird to
call things a drugstore let me just tell
you that when I was not so fluent in
English yet and like I heard about the
word drugstore it terrified
me I bought like in whatever I should
never go into a
drugstore because that's like Danger
they're selling the the sussy stuff
there you could also say Pharmacy yeah I
would prefer if you said
that I keep on forgetting what this was
can I sell it or not the pilot
[Music]
light well yeah I guess you can get
addicted to any medicine but still uh
well not really I would still
differentiate drugs and normal medicine
like headache me medicine or
so uh okay oh that's the uh-huh
uh-huh rebound regenerate AP is that a
drug too you know what I'm going to keep
it just for you know
emergencies Square wall on the stick
where did the tail go I guess the tail
doesn't have much meat on huh so they
just rip it
off
[Music]
yum W they just ripped off her tail no
mercy she screamed and they just ripped
it
off they did not think twice about it
twice twice about it I can't talk eggs
[Music]
eggs I got a lot of money now
let's
go get the Vengeance I will sell tire
iron oh tire iron I have too many items
it's so like hard to like you know
sorted in my
brain wait it says
trash but that's
ammo did I just sell ammo before too no
right oh ammo Cas oh the cases I can
sell okay okay
okay
oh oh I don't even get money for that
[Music]
okay fine then I'll go now why is that
wow do they have like a light inside
[Music]
fancy people of New Vegas this is your
friend he fights for you freedom of
Ranger where are the where are the
people in the big big big suits like
from the
show will I see
them oh beds howdy
howy I will yeah the Brotherhood of
Steel let's
go I want to see things that I've seen
in the show
maybe there's other games that have more
references but yeah most people
recommended for me to play this game so
here we
are I missed a friend I ignored Cass
what
cowgirl I missed a
companion what do you mean with
companion
cowgirl is there cowgirl around here boo
boo preferably with just one head not
two I'm not really into that you
know kind of freaks me out you're not it
right at the counter ah is see cat
you're not a cowgir Oh you mean instead
of cowboy I was
expecting I was expecting a cow cow
bikini for some reason looking for
trouble I was expecting a cow
bikini that's what I was looking for
well it seems my my understanding of
cowgir has changed thanks to the
internet and the anime brain R yeah
[Music]
not my mind is not in the
gutter my my I'm just confused language
is
confusing
um no only looking around we'll keep
those eyes up and turning or I'll set
them spinning got no time for gawkers or
anyone looking for something I ain't
selling what are you selling how about a
drink and are we
[Music]
flirting that deep in the bottle is she
that drunk are you all right all right
no I'm not all right drinking to forget
and it's only getting me mad instead
whiskey always gets my temper up now
more than ever drinking used to cause
all sorts of trouble back West before I
punched enough people that is and they
learn to lay low in the whiskey
hit drinking helps you forget I don't
think it will will ever help me forget
you but that's also why I don't drink
because I don't want to forget you yeah
yes
move lost my Caravan heading north the
driver burned to Ash and they didn't
even take the cargo they just burn that
too my guess is Legion they're trying to
cut ncr's supply line and the move
Outpost is proof got us locked up
tighter than a New Vegas virgin no
Caravans
what new try arguing with Jackson about
it roads aren't safe he says somebody
who hasn't been to that old [\h__\h] up I
didn't need a Brotherhood scribe to tell
me
that who's Jackson NCR officer Trooper
whatever runs the place he's over in the
main building the one without a bar ah
Jackson won't let me head north it's not
safe and even though my caravan's gone
my Caravan paper are keeping me here so
if you came here for work my advice go
find the Crimson Caravan Branch south of
Vegas they can help you
out mhm will I get there automatically
anyway oh she gave me a quest for it
Heartache by the
number thank you I think that's all I
wanted from
you she was
cute she was indeed
pretty it's long ways
off wow okay probably not for
today make her a companion you can re
recruit her
what damn it I'm going back again
recruit her like to follow me around
now she can't
yet
yeah you going
to speak clearly from the
start or else you're going to be in
trouble I am the
trouble that you're going to be
in I have
guns wow I feel like I'm on the
moon okay now we're going over there
we came from there we're going
there I
think to
nipon hopefully I'll see some
nipples
[Music]
we or at least some cow bikinis that
would satisfy me
too wee
F5 oh yeah we haven't really crashed so
far I just fought we crashed but we
[Music]
didn't wait what this path
M you have no mods no no mods W
[Music]
Speeders
oo ants oh I guess mutated ants look
like spiders yeah B oh yeah B oh yeah B
oh oh right I can shoot faster with this
gun I didn't
realize I feel like they're leading me
if I look behind I'll see aund more of
these no we're good we're
good ant
[Music]
meat I think I don't need that thank you
although I could cooked
right
nah go up the hill behind
you but I came from
there what's this like a racing old
racing uh Road
ooh what do we have here looting
opportunities nipon Road pit stop oh
oh I see enemies but it's maybe just
ants or no it might be real
people
yes oh no oh
no Out
w wow armored as [\h__\h] you look like
you're out of the World of Warcraft oh
my
oh uh
uh yeah please it doesn't show
me grab shotgun who whoa whoa on what on
what number do I have it oh now I see
it
okay
um you guys have to remember the numbers
what do the numbers
[Music]
mean shotgun is useless against the
heavy
armor I'm having a shotgun right now or
wait don't I have like a normal pistol
right now he's got too much armor you
won't kill him what should I
run I have a pistol right now a head
shot would work though no maybe
not I'll try
oh switch weapon how do
I wao I killed her so much for not
killing
her
fire fire fire
fire
he okay I forgot how to open my I panic
uh uh why am I so
dead why am I so dead I feel my doy
doie HP
okay
maybe one more that's the only like
instant HP do no wait I can
take more food
doubled
eggs Super stim
Pack N I don't want to I don't want to
take
that you guys said it does kind of Stack
right wait how am I back to 12
y m
M click click
click w w whoo whoo whoo whoo whoo wo
like I feel like oh my God
y well I'm probably going to get some
stim packs from this right
ah wait what was the thing that heals my
a this this one for example AP then I
can do more of those shots
right is my
armor
no okay
[Music]
oh did it really recharge well a little
bit don't die
frag mine what the [\h__\h] is that I was
hoping for stim
packs
where
present there we
go oh he's armored but he's
crippled oh who I didn't even know where
I was shooting I thought that was going
to go past him oh one more no that's
just a that's just a ant okay ah we did
it yay Cowboy
repeater ah stressful oh I'm very heavy
so
stressful oh raid we're getting raided
thank you thank you for the raid I have
hyper chat on I don't see it
yby let's get rid of the weight right by
the
way oh my God maybe eat some
food nice it's not very much
though a bit more steak the steak is
cooked is it no is
it it looks the same I would think the
steak is maybe
cooked check if there's beds near but I
just kind of want to get rid of the [\h__\h]
I have so much can you ever like expand
the inventory so you can carry more
stuff it was a merry weather right oh
thank you so
much thank you um you can sleep to
recover there in the yell oh is it is
there a bed in there with a perk
o
ooh ah maybe we can combine something
here oh yeah yeah yeah
that's
good
okay escaping to V and to my inventory
is my
everything my one safe place Wasteland
wonderer
outfit jet ke
so much [\h__\h] ah I can already not run
anymore what the
[\h__\h]
uh
uh why do I I guess maybe I forgot to
sell like the shitty armor that I have
that I don't
need feel like I kind of forgot
that but this is good fixing up my
pistol can you equip the metal I have
metal
dt1
wa No More Level
armor dirty prear
bus she it's super heavy does it I guess
yeah that makes me heavy even if I wear
it m
guess it doesn't
change are these any weight
[Music]
no drop Dynamite you don't use it I'd
like to sell it
but I want to drop
something where is the dynamite
ammo
[Music]
maybe drop the big weapon
tab I
hear
oh I I'm I don't know is it okay to sell
uh to get rid of this here like just
drop it always save some good weight
keep the dynamite to sell M Maybe
the R I don't know I don't know I can
fast Trav ah well uh they won't respawn
right that'll be [\h__\h]
up wait I can still walk decently let me
exp
whoa oh
I did it
okay I'm a pro oh my God wait I can walk
fairly
normally I think I'm not overloaded
right now oh yeah not
yet those were the drugs sheesh okay
detected what do you mean
detected oh
okay is that all there was
here I thought you guys would have more
impressive
loot you had really impressive
armor I guess that's about
it want I get up the
house parkour parkour
parkour okay let's uh wait let's
teleport to we can sell
in the in that Outpost right that we
just came
from which was this
one
move
okay
slow where
she look at me I'm all
H what the [\h__\h] he just how can you die
from
that
ttle how can you die from that than God
it was me damage glitch from the
barrel I kicked you think it was me
no I didn't do anything just my luck
what will be this time the physics of
the
barel oh my
God I feel bad for him holy
[\h__\h]
uh wait sell oh yeah trade take a
look no you take a
[Music]
look uh the butter knife for
sure I need to sell those chitty clothes
and maybe I I'm just going to sell
this leather armor are we not going to
use it anymore do you think don't sell
the case what
[Music]
why they ever sell the cases what I
thought they're
[Music]
empty you can craft ammo of the cave oh
okay well at least it doesn't have any
weight so the Le armor I don't know if
it's like maybe better to continue using
the Lea armor just because it weighs
less or if we should always go for
whatever is the
best tell me tell
[Music]
me up to me I suggest leather
unusually wear metal
armor stick with leather yeah I think it
really is a lot of weight the leather
armor is 50 this like
Double
H I like if I was wearing this and sell
this I I can get back 30 weight that's a
lot pretty easy to repair too I guess so
a lot of money let's get rid of it
yeah and this one can go too I
think going to get rid of some of the
alcohol would you guys recommend
it h
[Music]
alcohol delivery for the bar I'm sure
they're happy about me selling that to
them that's exactly what they need at
this bar that's exactly what that
cowgirl
needs maybe then she will show me her
cowgirl bikini
eventually I'm sure she secretly has
one every cowgirl must have a cowgirl
bikini I don't no one else to
sell can I sell this Le pipe tell me if
not I'll get it
back sell oh yeah we were going to sell
the dynamite
sell the lead pip okay
Dynamite goodbye Dynamite okay I think
that's fine for now what about the frag
mine though scorpion
[Music]
glands mines are good sells sell the
mines
okay scor oh there
okay so much money maybe wait maybe I
should buy some oopsie should I maybe
buy some stim packs take a look with all
that money one guide
no buy
ammo oh I lost money what
why
oh oh she's out of money oh I gave her
free
stuff she's
oh
what
what what she should tell me that what
is a
scam [\h__\h] what a scam
you
[\h__\h] she scammed me can't believe it
they should warn you you told
me how much money did I lose I to still
have a lot of money it's
okay the game told me I didn't see it I
just clicked it away I guess cuz I
thought everything was
normal does she have stim
packs don't she has oh oh no she
has that's so
expensive well I'll take them at least
free
[\h__\h] it wasn't that much of a
loose you hope I hope you don't
know no I don't I'm not going to reload
for that it's not the end of the
world fine then
it's not the end of the
world where was I I was here
right but I have to put on my lever
armor go go go go go go go
go
there's
it but you're not an
enemy what are you doing here I was
about about to shoot you hello there
it's good to see a friendly face I
almost took you for a Raider I did named
don't suppose you care to trade missing
a few essentials and a screw this lying
just ain't in my nature what are you
going to rob me now I tell it to you
straight I've been following you for a
good bit oh this is just like in the
show
oh okay you're dangerous sword I get
that yeah I am I have some information I
think you'll find useful which made me
follow you for it's him it started off
innocently enough I was traveling as I
often do and happen to observe you
picking up one of those blue star caps
you didn't show any reaction to it so I
figured you didn't know what you'd
gotten your hands on oh Chad told me so
you can't scam me I'm leaving don't
follow me why didn't you say anything
then and there what's special about them
there's an old Wasteland legend that
says Somewhere Out There there is a
fabulous treasure from before the war
those caps with the blue star on them
the tail go are the key to that treasure
they're called Sunset sasparilla
Stars you want them eh nah I gave it up
years ago too dangerous and even if I
did still collect them I tell you the
same H there's people out there so mad
with the idea of treasure that they'll
attack strangers just on the suspicion
that they have some of those caps huh
are you going to be one of those
people no one knows money weapons water
it is or maybe was something of value
and that's enough to get people
motivated yeah I don't know normally I'd
think like he's going to attack me but
it seems to be pretty friendly actually
the more I talk with
him all over the place the easiest place
to find them is unopen bottles of sunset
sasparilla oh you'd think they'd all
have been picked clean by now but
somehow new bottles keep appearing in
the machine huh some say it's old FES
hoping someone will finally collect
enough caps to earn the treasure other
than bottles you'll just have to
scavenge you can find caps in the
unlikeliest of places and blue star caps
are no
exception wait so all the bottles I've
been
[Music]
opening
have had one of those caps on or just
some of
them have I been automatically
collecting
them it's said that the treasure is
guarded by a man named fesus and he's
the one who asked for the blue star caps
it's also said he's been around since
the war standing a lonely vigil waiting
for someone to come and take the
treasure off his hands that'll make him
pretty damn old but I've met a few
people in my travels who claimed they
actually met him and they weren't the
lying type either H okay don't
you end up trying to collect more stars
watch out for a man named Alan Mars he's
killed several people for this
St they are like manipulating the market
though because like who decides that
those caps have any value in the first
place they're just like normal caps so
just treat them as normal caps yo and
then we everything's
cool the veins on this
person it's not normal right these
people are they what what's wrong with
these
people is it
drugs sorry I double checked for some of
those bottle
caps drugs and Wasteland
combined [\h__\h] the Wasteland the
Wasteland
sucks I hate the
Wasteland what what where
where I hear loud shooting I guess it's
coming from
nipton oh yeah it's coming from
nipton surprised me thought I was going
to ambushed
again
[Music]
damn Sweet Home
Alabama where the skies are so blue
Sweet Home
Alabama I'm Coming For
You howy nip we have arrived we safe did
you see that that crazy [\h__\h] just
attacked me out of nowhere the [\h__\h] I
didn't see I was about to save why did
you show up when I press
F5 who won the lottery I did
it is that part of the
lyrics uh I even sang that song in K I
don't remember that as part of the
lyrics you I'll see oh okay it's part of
this any idea
why no none at all okay we've been
traveling together since I picked up a
few days ago and she's been friendly
this whole time we'd actually been
flirting a little when she suddenly
pulled a gun out and began yelling at me
to hand my caps over now that I think of
it though she laughed when I threw her
my money I think what she really wanted
was my lucky charm
necklace yeah every once in a while you
can find a cap with a blue star on it I
just heard about this rare so I started
kind of weird that I'm me about a r
since I thought they were lucky
ah 40 out of 50 o those caps are bad
luck why don't you let me hold on to
them for
[Music]
you hand them over what the hell I
will I've got you
now you like
that what [\h__\h] gun am I using
doesn't
matter I am evil it seems but we have
received oh some nice things oh I want
to read that
journal do I scare you guys did you guys
kill him too when you played this
game or is it just me no Karma loss yeah
no Karma gain either was neutral I guess
yeah you did
the last entry of the journal reads
things finally seemed to be turning
around I made a nice bundle of caps
turning in some scrap but in the last
time I passed and now I have a new
traveling companion her name is jacqulyn
and she's pretty cute I'm not going to
get ahead of myself there but things are
looking up and to think I was actually
beginning to doubt the power of my lucky
necklace
a he died in a fabulous pose man
man it's
posing okay so is
there going to be trouble here you don't
look like an enemy so far you need help
yeah who won the lottery I did
congratulations couldn't you just drink
it like
booze the [\h__\h] did you
do what are you feeling okay are you
kidding me of course you never felt
better I guess so you've won the
lottery what Lottery the lottery genetic
Lottery cuz you're hot as [\h__\h] Lottery
that
matters oh my God smell that air maybe
that flatters him you want the gentic
lottery that must be it powder ganger
what I mean yeah used to be sure you
used to be but not no more powder gang
is small time man I'm a winner I won the
[\h__\h] looking lottery I still don't
really understand what
Lottery later wow
what
what what the
[\h__\h] I don't understand but I agree I
agree but I also don't understand
destroy him should I kill him take it
from
me no I'm so
slow is he gone
is he gone he went that
way oh he's
there just let him go oh he's shooting
enemies like animals probably should I
kill him what the
[\h__\h] hey
you he has
nothing I so
scared
H who whoa oh that's why oh oh they're
having their own little fight well oh
[Music]
no got you now
just
wow wow thank you for being programmed
to react really [\h__\h] late to what's
happening
wow that's a lot of stuff you're
carrying that's going to make me really
heavy I'm just going to take this this
this maybe the water
uh yeah I think that's all I'm going to
take tell me if I was wrong to not take
everything well now we I didn't kill him
but I can still check if he had anything
he got the lottery tick I didn't even
have to kill him for that now I want the
lottery
yeeha he got the this armor don't I have
that too but mine was five wasn't it
I won the
lottery
yeeha that's how fast the tables turn
and the turntables you got to be ready
for it you've got to be ready for
it got to keep up
man you have to keep
up all right where the [\h__\h] did he come
from though this
dude kind of came from the side I look
more like Le I seem more like Legion
than NCR I don't know what that means
really so thanks I guess it's not a
compliment my pistol looking good m is
is that what I'm using right now the 10
mm no I'm using the other one let's use
the 10
mm wow
sexy okay let me remember oh
wa let me remember this gun is the the
strong 10 mm one I don't know why it's
strong but you guys say it's strong what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] who did this
and
why justice has to be
served I'm scared actually I'm
scared holy
[\h__\h] are they still
saveable oh wait is a powder ganger and
he's alive he see he's alive I can
pickpocket him oh oh there's people
there they're not marked as enemies
let me
save and they did say that's the town
hall I think they did say if there's any
people at the
[Music]
Town who whoa whoa oh they H they went
into fighting position because of the
coyotes need help from the coyotes or
maybe they no maybe they just took
position for no reason the coyotes seem
like friends after all
no enemies
yet uh it's not going to change
right don't worry I won't have you lash
your cross like the rest of these
degenerates it's useful that you happen
by I want you to witness the fate of the
town of nipton oh okay to memorize every
detail I'll share what's happened yes
and then when you move on yeah I want
you to teach everyone you meet the
lesson that Kaiser's Legion taught here
kaisar especially any NCR
Cesar I feel like this this will put me
in a immediately difficult position so
let's not say that what lessons did you
teach you to begin that they are weak
and we are strong this much was known
already it won at the depths of their
moral sickness their
dissolution hipton serves as the perfect
object lesson
nipton was a wicked place debased and
corrupt really it served all comers so
long as they paid propagate troops
powder gangers men of the Legion such as
myself the people here didn't care it
was a town of [\h__\h] for a pittance the
town agreed to lead those it had
sheltered into a trap only when I sprang
it did they realize they were caught
inside it too
yes and hered them to the center of town
I told them their sins the foremost
being disloyalty I told them that when
legionaries are disloyal some are
punished the others made to watch and I
announced the loty each clutched his
ticket hoping it would set him free each
did nothing even when loved ones were
dragged away to be
killed wait what what they did they just
win the life Lottery wait was the
lottery ticket just like who gets to
live or
so innocent hardly cowardly though they
outnumbered us that is yet not once did
they try to good that I have the ticket
now they stood and watched as their
fellows were butchered crucified and
burned one by one they stood and hoped
their turn he still died each cared only
for yourself
[\h__\h] as are all crimes if you feel
strongly about it attack us and soon you
won't feel a
thing one two
three I I suppose that is an option for
people who are good at this game but no
I will
[Music]
return so I don't really understand
who's the evil ones they seem evil but
they also are evil everybody's evil
right as they say they're all trying to
save the
world but in really [\h__\h] up
ways they all think they're saving the
world but by all they're they're all
doing it in a different way and so
they're just destroying the world
oh what what
the
what
what what what what
what shotg oh it's not a person there
it's a trap cuz I was wondering why it's
not moving what
the let's not open this
oh another one
oh uh what the hell time to eat
something yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum
yum traps and mines everywhere mines
too yum just sleep to heal oh what was
there mat's in
there what why am I feeling like this I
don't remember taking drugs is it the
radiation well I I I I think I just have
to go back right back back
to
uh about attackers
no return to range of
ghost yeah
my head is crippled oh I'll just heal
there
[Music]
b oh my head hurts
a I need some
aspirine yeah I'll sleep don't
worry soon TM IRL as
well I had recently I've been just
having the weirdest [\h__\h] dreams ever
I can't even say them to you cuz you're
going to be like what the [\h__\h] you're
actually going to judge me so hard I
don't know I'm not even going to
consider telling you but I don't know
why I'm I'm Dreaming such [\h__\h] up
weird ass things background just my luck
what will it be this time
uh wait what wait who who who am I going
to talk
to thought it was you ah wait no no no
no no the the lady on top U lady on top
where please stay away from me I can
accidentally Kill You by walking against
a barrel see the dead body is still
there please please keep a distance from
me I don't want to hurt you you check
out the nipton town hall yet yeah smoke
Trail's not getting any shorter it's
[\h__\h] up over there Legion this far
west you're [\h__\h] kidding me that's
not outside the Border they're moving in
and fast nipton wasn't the most friendly
town but all right thanks for checking
on that wish should set my mind to e was
traumatizing more on edge than
ever unless you burn the town don't take
blame that's not due things are going to
get uglier before the year's out well
thanks for hoofing it there and back
even if it was bad news wish we could
spare the troops to go hunting
but orders are to stay put [\h__\h]
mojave's going to hell and all I can do
is sit here and
watch
Mojave thank you for saying it out loud
for me that helped
me okay I completed the quest did I get
some experience points for that hey
hopefully so now we go through uh nipton
to go to the next place
oh I talk to Jackson did I do what he
wanted as well well who was
Jackson who was Jackson in
there I got Fame for NCR I can meet a
ghoul is you Jackson
no
Trooper is Jackson on the
bar guy with the shades and the mustache
you're not in here right
oh in this building oh wait you you oh
wow what a mustache
W looks like we got a new visitor in the
old Brahman pen not many people coming
here in a hurry only passing through are
those heart shap if you're passing
through You' picked a bad time Road
North has gone to hell and if I let a
caravan through they won't make it they
look like heart-shaped can you please
raise your hat a little bit I want to
see it
help now look I
appreciate you know what yes I could use
the help and you look like you can
handle yourself I need to get the
Caravans moving again that means
clearing a path North there's too much
crawling the assphalt up the road to
allow it
oh
H North that's not the way I got to go
right oh he's just clipping for his
cheeks is
it is is it do it and you get a good
rifle it's just a side
[Music]
quest really good rewards okay thanks I
appreciate it come back here when you're
done I might accidentally lose some
supplies to pay you with why you got to
say it like that just be honest that
you're going to reward me why are you so
t or is it embarrassing is it does it
have to be secret that you're giving
stuff to me why what wait what what's
why is he like
this just realized I can take his
things I'll just take the
mentats he won't need them anymore
that's for sure North he said north this
way wait where where are we going he
wants me to go oh let me Mark the
quest uh oh am I not already spreading
the word of the Legion atrocities I
guess not clear out the critters this is
the one right on the road to Iva
Lake oh
oh this this
way that
sounds like it's going to be
bugs not humans
talk to this
[\h__\h]
what him
him this
one something else you wanted
ah ah he also wanted to know about it
what there's no way we're miles from the
Colorado
they they aren't even waiting for the
dam to fall they're already inside the
borders we'll never stop them not at
this rate we're doomed yeah we're doomed
thanks for telling y'all even if the
news is bad I'll let the men know I'm
doom
posting it's my favorite thing to
do ah Cold Cold Heart completed there we
go oh level five
and what do we want to get up now again
uh what are we working
on repair speed repair like what what do
we
want always guns
o I do need more speed y I already
didn't have enough for like previously
they wanted like 50 or so
with the suit I can get up to 50
yeah
science I don't
know aim for 100 if you want to talk
everything
[Laughter]
out can I really talk everything out
everything m
okay
whoa I feel like I
didn't I don't know is it is it okay to
not balance it so well to like focus on
a few skills so hard is that
[Music]
okay
well like yeah medicine is really low a
lot of things are really
low you have to a New
Vegas okay not
a by the way next
week I'm I'm I'm kind of [\h__\h] uh on
the weekend I don't know if I can play
this game on the weekend maybe during a
weekday because on the weekend I have
off Guai and I have meet and gr and
performance is this the critters Day
mean
um but the thing
is
oh Dad it's like in the middle of the
night for me from Saturday to Sunday
like everything is like
free to what from like midnight to like
4:00 a.m. or so I didn't
realize that they were going to put me
in a time slot like
that like me and great rehearsal and
then performance it's all between
midnight midnight and like 4 a.m. [\h__\h]
man it
sucks it sucks so I don't know I I'll
have
to
be fit for that too so I I have to
really think about my schedule when
I get up tomorrow I don't think I'll do
it
today you'll get a schedule
tomorrow it's going to be B difficult as
usual it's not usual and not I don't
always take Mondays off sometimes not
always are we done here was that the
critters it's part of my job yeah but
I'm excited for Mee and GDs anybody here
who got accepted into the Mee and GD who
won the lottery
where are my lottery winners
eh lottery winners where you at
wow uh who won the
lottery who won the
lottery I didn't win but I will cheer
for you at the main hall thank
you lot was brutal is here I wonder how
many it's probably not that
many and nectar that sounds kind of rare
well maybe
not not me nobody's saying I I just saw
one person on Twitter announcing that
they won the lottery uh I mean I guess
it is a
lottery I guess it is a lottery did I do
[Music]
it I think I oh I did it
okay that was not far at
all I'm just going to talk with one
person for 25 minutes no it's probably
in total it's probably like an hour so
usually usually the time it takes is
like an hour
there's one meting green that would be
so sad no I'm sure there's more but I
guess they're not very
active sometimes in m and grads I have
like you know the the usual like big
fans who've been watching for a long
time and all that and sometimes there's
like really random like oh I I don't
really know you that well or I'm not uh
you're not even my Oshi like they won't
say it like that but
yeah it comes up in the
conversation appreciate the help I'm not
there like nothing else on the radar the
moment then I low key wish that the
ticket would have maybe gone to someone
who had me as their ocean but at the
same time I hope that by meeting me in
the meet and greet maybe they like me a
little bit more and will consider me as
uh a close close almost
or so maybe they like me more
so maybe there's people who just sign up
for all the meet and greets probably and
then hope whatever even if it's not my
Oshi I hope I'll I'll get
chosen closi
closy close to Oi
closy that sounds so
stupid yeah it's okay like as long as
long as you know
as long as it's not like full of people
like that there's no problem with it
there's nothing wrong about it as long
as it's a mix or so I'm okay with
it
yeah I I do want generally because my
the big big big Oshi fans the ones that
really call me their their one and only
true Oshi you know these
opportunities don't come often to some
like some also can't track travel so
much as others
so yeah especially for those who can't
travel much and I'm coming to their city
for once I hope they get those tickets
those lottery tickets I hope they win in
the lottery that' be the great Lottery
no more Skype well it was never Skype
that was um Zoom but yeah I wish I could
still do
those what if you're in my top three no
that that's fine that's totally
fine no I mentioned you might
accidentally get supplied and I meant
not allowed to contract mercenaries at
The Outpost I don't even remember it
that requisition for um I just I'm just
it it doesn't happen that often but I
just had this like one I have this one
memory in my brain hey where someone
came to my me and greed and and really
didn't
seem to care that much about
me and that confused me like why what
what you
what but it's a
rare coincidence I I don't know why that
happened though so I got something
cool service
rifle DPS 53 wow nice of him I have so
many maybe I can sell some can I sell
the varint rifle
now what do you even talk about right
cuz then in addition to that they don't
even bring up much to talk like any
topics or so so I still have to to make
this situation less awkward and I'm like
uh so yeah I hope you're having fun
today what have you been doing at the
convention like I'm still trying my best
to make the experience good but it's a
bit awkward sometimes but it was just
like maybe like this particular case was
a onetime thing fix up the service rifle
the service R is pretty good at this
point in the game okay let
me been doing a lot of good work wa wa
you buying stuff
no uh sorry wrong
person I don't know they probably just
like
um were like you know oh whatever sounds
fun I'll give it a
try even though I'm not a big fan it's
kind of
like they probably went into it with a
more loose feeling like when I was at a
comic conon and I saw really close
before it
was like ending I saw um The Game of
Thrones actor for what's his name
again uh and there was no line and I was
like well I'm not really a big fan yeah
Joffrey but there's no lying and and
getting an autograph from A Game of
Thrones actor I Love Game of Thrones
it's like you know cool thing so why not
give it a try my Lu but in that case
there was no line I was not taking any
chance from anybody else
so that that that would be fine right
that's not that's a different situation
but maybe they went into it with like a
similar
feeling like oh well that sounds cool I
might as well give it a try meeting
takanashi Ki take a look sounds
fun uh what what are we doing I'm
selling you
the varment
rifle goodbye vment rifle it was nice
having you since the beginning what else
are we selling
huh oh yeah she okay I'll remember she
has limited caps we're not going to go
overboard mhm
when they cost money I think don't they
always cost money maybe JY thinks about
you the same way
yeah I don't think
[Music]
so Cowboy repeater and service rifle oh
okay I'll put it in one of
my quick slots then
um I don't
know o yummy bitter
drink Atomic cocktail and ener resists
31 fire oh
wow wow
[Music]
can I sell this for sure
right the lottery ticket I guess this is
useless now no don't the hole is that
also like a
case I
huh I don't have much to sell I feel
[Music]
like I don't
know I don't really have
anything F then incinerator is heavy
yeah but it was fun using
it I'm turning into a ghoul what I am I
really is there like
a like a status of how close I am to
becoming a
ghoul no okay it was a joke I will take
it seriously like I don't know what
happens in this
game
uh what was I going to check just a yeah
I wanted to look at the
weapons first of all
maintain and
then the service rifle I I don't have
anything to repair it with okay we're
going to put this on
for I
guess and then the other one you said
was the cowboy
repeater what does that even mean I'll
put
you I don't know what all these
are where was
my where did I put the fancy pistol the
10 mm
pistol I wish it would show me like
which one I put where
I'm I'm going to put it I don't know
well let me let's see what do I have on
seven is
this ah seven is the cool one this is
something I don't
know what's this can is this worth
having on my
shortcuts or this one this is a 9 mm
right and this is the
revolver not bad
what repeater is better replace that
with the cowboy repeater okay
seven
okay there we go that's it so what's
next on our wish
list uh go to Crimson well that will
probably be later head to Nock through
nipton
I guess we can do a little
shortcut to
no man what if I just shoot them should
I shoot them we can talk
now appears to be near death to remove
them from the crust would kill
them yeah but I just want to talk
I'd be pretty evil really I already
killed people like
these should I enter
suffering but that wastes my
ammo maybe it is more cruel to keep them
alive I don't want to waste my ammo on
these
[\h__\h] got to watch out for
mines use a melee weapon I think I got m
H I might still have a Mele weapon I
guess there's Loot and lore around loot
interests me lore a little bit depends
on the danger I have to involve myself
in because that shotgun
trap [\h__\h] spooked
me that was not
nice but one thing's for sure I'm not
going to meet alive people in these
places right reloading
bench shotgun trap
no okay
beds
huh okay No Loot
here that's hilarious freak me
[Music]
out freak
I'll tap no no I don't need light I feel
like it's plenty of
light stop telling me if it says empty I
still want to open
it I don't want to open
it like isn't it the same thing when you
know you don't have anything in the
fridge but you're still going to check
the fridge the fridge is just you know
IRL
example you keep on checking the fridge
hoping for you know finding something to
eat even though you kind of know like
generally not only the fridge it's just
a human behavior to open things even
when you know and the thing is I don't
even look that closely I'm not opening
it with the knowledge that it's empty I
know I could have that knowledge if I
looked
carefully everything that's
written but I I
don't I just see I can open something
and then I say okay
open
m
oo banana Yuka fruit that sounds
yummy I'll take
it is that a
banana W that looks like
salmon that looks looks like
salmon alcohol good to sell what's my
weight right
now it's not that I can't read I just
like might as well open
everything well oh oh my weight is not
so bad actually cherry
bump
iron B Big Iron I've heard of
you is this you is this the Big Iron
everybody talks about probably
not you guys said alcohol where was it
oops
see in there I
guess no it
[Music]
it it's a clothing iron
oh is that what they're singing about a
clothing
iron
oh that's what I should be
singing was I in this house just now it
looks the same that's what I should be
singing when I'm ironing my
clothes since there's a lot of people
here seemingly that don't watch my
streams that much let me just say I did
an ironing hand cam stream before did
you
know did you know I'm very happy and and
proud of my unique streaming
ideas I literally ironed my clothes with
the camera pointed at the iron board
yeah trying my best to get rid of all of
the wrinkles for you for you no you
could imagine that maybe there was a
little bit of role play there if you
wanted to think like that a vacuum
cleaner interesting I guess next stream
is vacuuming
stream was I in this house before they
all look the same to me oh pre-war
spring outfit
aw that sounds cute I'd watch it I'd
watch
it but like I'd want to
use I should go in here I I want to use
um like a a vacuum cleaner for children
that has like these little pearls that
you suck in into your kuty children
vacuum cleaner I love to play with that
when I was younger hey
yo you're
alive your name is box cars what is it
this
time w
w whoa I don't know I just love it here
what the [\h__\h] do you think [\h__\h] that
was place I got to live but they beat my
[\h__\h] legs with hammers I'm [\h__\h]
crippled get it
oh I don't have any Med X maybe I do I
feel like I do why do I say I don't oh
[\h__\h] you're holding you just want it all
for yourself I didn't have any other
option I would give it to you luck
that's how I'm just that [\h__\h] lucky
you're looking at the second place
winner of the
lottery SW what they do with the second
place they let
walk oh it ain't like we came to ni in
the it me and my crew had it worked out
to kidnap some NCR had it all worked out
with the scumbag M we were going to
Ransom them off keep their weapons for
ourselves a nice
score well
o oh thank you Jay that's
sweet I'm glad position and next thing
we know we're surrounded by those
[\h__\h] Legion freaks morning good
morning to you they dragged us and
everybody else into the center of town
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] with a dog on his head he
starts talking about how we're bad
people he said we needed to be punished
for what we did not all of us but some
of us and then he gives everyone a
[\h__\h] lottery
ticket yeah that is some kind of weird
Kink he has probably what do you think
he started drawing tickets and that's
how people got punished first up was the
lucky losers they got decapitated guess
that's lucky cuz it's pretty quick then
came the crucifixions
God damn but those went on and on and on
third place Runners up got enslaved I
got the [\h__\h] beat out of my legs and the
winter they let go free third place got
enslaved so they
what yeah a bunch of those Legion [\h__\h]
dragged them off right away they were
headed east if you're feeling heroic no
I don't
know don't act like you'd be doing me a
favor I don't give a [\h__\h] wow h
oh I got a quest for it
though you can save them or buy
them saving them sounds like a big
trouble
[Music]
but him when his ticket came up they
burned him alive on a pile of tires
oh the legion happened what the [\h__\h]
it look like [\h__\h] the
legion like what I don't know man I I
thanks I guess
I your legs they don't look they look
normal well I guess you would probably
be elsewhere if they were really not an
issue damn but he needs help why don't I
help him why don't I help the guy who's
right in front of my eye like transport
him carry him on my back to bring him
like to an outpost or so to get some
help like if he can't move here and he's
all alone like he's going to eventually
run out of food and stuff can't live
from
bubblegum I can give him really really
it doesn't seem like I can give him
anything what is it this
time
later oh he would be there
enemy well we can pretend he's not maybe
he'll be so emotionally moved
by uh the help that he's been receiving
that you know then it happens it
happens there was an upstairs
oh how to
[Music]
enter is there a back entrance no
okay I'll go in
again
squizzy oh I guess for that
door oh I have to lock pick
it first time it broke yeah B
oh oh that was kind of weird are
you yeah it doesn't seem to be a a
compliment the legion Legion is just
like does the legion not exist anymore
in the show because I don't think they
ever mentioned the legion at
all toaster a toaster a chest
board I don't need your chest board I
have a Tales of a rise chest board that
I never opened
before it's ambigous they haven't shown
it somewhere else and maybe they show in
the second season or so oh oh it's
open Legion is fur the
East we don't know yet
yeah but this whole Lottery [\h__\h] that's
uh really [\h__\h] up why I mean I can't
really
explain that like if you use the the
logic of everybody's trying to save the
world and they're just doing it their
way you don't have to be this brutal to
do [\h__\h] like that that's just absolutely
messed up there's no explanation or
reasoning for that
H so NADA that tells
me that tells me that I have to go there
and save him save the the runner
UPS
uh that's what that just told me okay
wait that's pretty far though what about
the other
stuff um no this one oh this one's right
here okay I'll do the other one
eventually applies more to to the show
story yeah but I'm grasping on at straws
you know I don't I don't know I don't
know much about you know Fallout so I'm
just holding on to the the itsy bitsy
tiny things that I know from the show
wait what ah okay now it's telling me to
go here okay just wanted me to go
through
[Music]
nipton ha could have gone from here to
here okay so we will pass by this
first where is just to visualize it
where is
this uh not this this
one oh oh wow oh okay no I'm not going
there no no no no no
[Music]
no a lot of things hiding in these
mountains these mountains
nice people right people who want to
help each
other oh I see a bottle
cap and the crate that suddenly started
moving towards me oh that's a lot oo I
won the
lottery these things are moving help go
oh wa ghosts is that what I'm meeting in
the
mountains in these
mountains I found the ghost
oh you are enemy I want a sniper rifle
please oh I
can't land mine huh
[\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] I need to be more careful
for those kind of
[Music]
things my I don't have so many stim
packs shut them the what the month the
that's what theth the the [\h__\h]
that enemies are nearby oh
oh run oh no
no I am
man so they were not necessarily ghosts
I haven't say in a while I think did I
get the
quest I have the quest
okay
ah
huh thank you Auto sa for rescuing
me okay now I know what's awaiting me if
I want those bottle caps
H oh what if we try it differently is
that a
helicopter
no I want to climb and maybe Ambush them
you think I can do that like from here
or so is that
stupid try it I can yeah I want to flank
them
[Music]
maybe not from
here come on jump I'm telling you to
jump she just doesn't
jump why I know you can jump show me
those jumping
skills ah invisible
wall other side of the road uh oh yeah
wait
what other side of the
[Music]
RO there I didn't see a guy there but
maybe there is a guy cuz I was was
hoping to go over
there maybe I'll find something up there
too just sneak on the road on the whole
Road through the mountains you
mean on both sides yeah I thought
so would be stupid of them if they
didn't position them themselves on both
sides you got to have at least two sets
of eyes what the [\h__\h] is
this I don't see
anyone oh it's just
some yummy yummy
water probably some cucumber water I
would think I would
assume okay it's quite a bit further
ahead Mountain
do what the [\h__\h]
they're so
chunky kind of want to give him a
hug they look
huggable are
you oh I see
him where is your friend
you don't have
one surely you do right
[Music]
are why am I so
slow am I always as slow am I
heavy no I feel so
slow okay okay that Spooks me out freaks
me
out what the what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
you who what is he shooting at
me why is he shooting that's a grenade
launcher
dude dud
dude dud dud oh there's to N I have no
chance I have like no chance here I'm
already I'm I'm going to waste my
things oh
okay well I killed
them do I get the grenade
launcher grenade
rifle what if I just go back teleport
back heal my crippled things
and come back here they're not
respawning I think so no ammo damn it
they wasted it on
me barter plus five
interesting m
[Music]
keep that hat yeah I
will so cigarettes are good for
selling all right well at least I took
them
out it's just really really [\h__\h]
painful should I teleport back I don't
want to use up all my stim
packs man did the other guy also have a
grenade launcher I
wonder worth it if you find a bed
[Music]
yeah was that the other guy coming for
me or a rando just traveling through no
way right is the other
guy you should know where you put your
own
mines well you made things a lot easier
for me God okay where are the
m is that a
mine B
cab psycho I'll take that he had no
interesting weapon so maybe he wasn't
the big
danger save first
okay no I think the the other guy's gone
yeah that was that was probably
him okay
now after
all my
precious
loot no I want the I want
the this one oh it's starting to float
again what does it mean I guess the the
bottle cap just had so much weight to
hold down all of these cursed
items wait I need to be careful I need
to be careful I need to be careful is
there more mines I don't see
any these are just street lights or so
what is
[Music]
this I made the fruit but m
should I I don't want to can I will I
stay crippled even if I eat
food Cat's Eyes they reflect lights from
headlights so you see the
r wow high
tech is there a lot more danger coming
for me from there
I just want to get another checkpoint
other way the path is so
far where are
[Music]
we I risk
it keeping my eyes on the road and on
the mountains oh I see something you're
crippled you no no I'm okay jumping
maybe not be so smart when I have a
crippled leg but just having
fun this
looks this looks like maybe what we're
looking for I don't know is this place
safe safe place to rest
really don't fool me don't you dare
it is safe
okay what's this place called Another
Outpost or
so mush MOS
hello wow we got a fun looking place
here wolf horn Ranch a ranch
howy no one in here
okay I'm Healed guys don't you worry why
are you so worried Magnum
round is a Rancher dead or what happened
I'm oh wait the bobby pin I'll take the
bobby
pin no spoilers
uhoh uhoh
oh
uhoh soon what's
this corn no not corn what was this
friend another familiar face here it's
so rare to see famili your faces
man
wo wow what a farm
[Music]
Cactus go back to that
Shack did I miss
something you missed the gun there was a
gun oh I can take this why F rifle oh no
all just for selling I
guess on the stove it there's another
one there a clean a
chopper I'll take
it start another
one special Cleaver unique Cleaver oh
okay first unique weapon get unique that
you mean I can't find it anywhere else
and it's not from a quest either I guess
because I would think that my rifle is
maybe also
unique or maybe
not this looks like someone built this
and
rust okay a lot of this looks like rust
just because it's yeah well
abandoned friend hello are you the
farmer hey there are you going not going
to talk has a new sheriff that should
keep the powder gangers away the sheriff
that I
appointed it isn't it kind of corrupted
that I I I kind of singlehandedly chose
the mayor there was no vo V vote vote
where's the Democracy eh where is the
Democracy in
that this reminds me of near automat
this
road this road in particular hello s
nice ladies and
gentlemen hey there hey there
friendly that's why we need new NCR in
New Vegas well said w wow
wow what did I
say oh they sell stuff they're Merchants
oh uh you hey there need anything
teach me can I have a class in accents
with you I'm really bad at
[Music]
it Varmint Rifle
goodbye Grand
outfit barter we keep that one we s
this
no should I buy ammo buy some free
57 I feel like I bought them all is that
okay now did I buy the red thing did I
buy the r
thing I bought the gun
Oh e wait is was that
mine cancel cancel I'm confused hey
there need
anything sure restart here's what I got
you're confusing me you're playing a
funny game you're trying to scam me I
know it I know
it vment rifle go and then the
round I'm
[Music]
buying oh
all do we have stim packs stim packs oh
just one
wow that's hard out here hard to find
anything really I have two grenade
rifles should I just sell them cuz I
guess will be hard to find the right
ammo
okay
nice combine them
first
[Music]
okay ah let's sell alcohol and
cigarettes cigarettes alcohol
uh oh I don't think I really brought any
alcohol did
[Music]
I ree War
money okay for now oh
baseball okay don't go away don't go
away I have something exciting for you
oh this one you will like you might even
want to use it
yourself
sure 76 bottle caps cutting
cutting all right on your way
goodbye did it increase the sell value
it was not worth it oh W where are we
going uh little bit to the left over
there
ooh almost there I hope it will not be
too difficult I'm scared oh they're
shooting oh should I help them who the
[\h__\h] are they leave them alone don't
well at least I got my trading done
beforehand uh uh
uh
[\h__\h] oh no oh no
no maybe I don't want oh my head scared
me leave leave alone wait okay shut
the we can't risk this
um oh my God they're going to die
they're going to [\h__\h]
die you at least I can shoot you pretty
well
uh no
no that who I'm going to
die come on wo wo wo wo wo wo
w
Wait I act with
both I shot the cow I'm just trying to
help no I'd rather a dieo
[Music]
my dri will die kill me are they really
AG I I I'm leaving this
battlefield oh
no oh no oh no oh
well it is what it
is how am I
doing I'm okay actually W wo wo wo w w w
w w w w wo wo w oh oh what what w wo W
wo wo w Wait
wait okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay are they near can I
teleport
no I don't want to let them go but at
the same time oh yeah okay okay [\h__\h]
I holer a weapon to stop aggro can't
really do that now it's not too
late service rifle
equipped one St
pack
[Music]
and oh okay I took that by accident
but sure
[Music]
um
nice in Caesar's Legion infamy gain what
does that mean they hate me more are
they from
Caesar I guess Kaiser was
it w six
I'm not that happy either they hate me
more ah whatever I think they hated me
before
already oh
machete I feel bad I
couldn't I couldn't help them before
they died I couldn't help the traitors
they did
nothing Caesar
salad it's all I can think about
Legion oh they are using like is that
really Kaiser when they're even having
Caesar
from
[Music]
like is it that
Caesar but so it's not Kaiser they're
Rome
larpers what they even have a throwing
Speare wow 25
DPS I don't know looks heavy 1.5 that's
not that bad that's not that
bad
damn uh I'm going
to uh I'm going to
heal sorry I'm still lost in this
menu I I want to loot the tra this but I
it's so far I want to heal
first it won't go away
right
right okay not for
ages okay
unfortunate development
man I was I was like I have to I have to
be
more determined like if I want to
participate in a fight I have to go all
in but they were like mingling mangling
so much like I didn't it was like bound
to happen that I shoot one of them too
but by the time I was there oh
I feel like I they already lost a couple
of people and she was like in the middle
of the
fire is this
good bramen
meat drain small energy
[Music]
cell laser pistol Ah that's what the
what they were carrying do you need the
small energy cells for that
the mine has good value
mhm metal
[Music]
helmet 100 bottle
caps oh okay
heavy it's combination time
crafting
repair right I'm going to have two fully
repaired
pistols 10 mm
pistols that's all I can do I love all
these guys all these
drawings what am I
hearing freaking me out is the is the
still
alive Le oh wait should I they're both
six oh but these are even
less in weight but higher in value too H
May I'll just sell it I don't
know do not wear them oh oh yeah I guess
I you know now I have from like two
fractions that I hate and hate me back I
have have their armor I can cosplay as
them let's
[Music]
go well if only we had a merchant here
right now who I could sell all my [\h__\h]
too but I gained the stuff from them
so
H Barrel Cactus for Legion oh yeah
another one Night Stalker tail you see
I'm not going to take all your [\h__\h]
unfortunately you're going to keep the
helmet oh the sound was from my pit
boy sounded like grunting from a
pig why do you suddenly I don't know I
don't know I don't hate the NCR I don't
know what what did what what made you
think I hate the NCR
[Music]
I already checked the Brahman maybe not
both but they had
me i k oh I killed both the Traders were
NCR yeah cuz they were good people huh
I'm still heavy I feel
heavy they were not NCR who was NCR in
that
fight oh I'm crouched oh my God it's so
hard to notice that you're crouched I
don't feel like I'm much
lower I mean yeah the speed is an
implication
but oh friends can you trade too Trooper
Trooper
Trooper what do you
need time for me to go later why why
won't you join me oh you
change I separated
them I did say why won't you join me but
I got to go this way
[Music]
though yeah you were supposed to protect
these people these traitors you were
supposed to help them weren't
you and yet you did nothing you're
always too late you never show up on
time
oh here we go is that where the slaves
are this must be
it is this a fancy
rifle which one's a fancy
rifle
flamethrower what I thought I replaced
this one
F5
check wait this is the fancy Rifle
right okay here we go I'm just going to
kill everybody right oh wait
they're why are they not marked as
enemies am I wearing their
armor
no
huh they don't hate me enough oh shall I
give them a reason oh yeah cuz I can
also buy them right uh these are the
two w how many are there of you one and
two still neutral yeah maybe we want to
stay neutral for a while longer huh true
to kais kaisar you you say it wrong
that's so embarrassing for you how are
you making a whole theme Cesar
and then you dress up like this and you
can't even say it right ridiculous oh my
God learn some learn some Latin or I
don't [\h__\h]
know Italian even Italian oh wait a did
you say a it's
a pretty
sure oh true to
kaisar no no I would say Cesar in German
we say
Cesar watch
yourself they say it
correctly they're still just fools now
sell me sell me these uh slaves you got
there
please
oh wait wait a second powder p I don't
want to I don't want to save any I want
to kill them
all these are all [\h__\h]
scumbags now they don't deserve to be
[Music]
rescued but then what this Quest is like
rescue the captives
n what if I kill them
and leave them or kill them
too I guess the quest fails but I I do
kind of want the ex X EXP
I don't how do I even buy them I thought
that was an
option I will get good karma if you save
them
okay how how to
buy this doesn't
seem like there's an actual buy option
the guy in charge he also just sent a
[Music]
h
Huh is there another
[Music]
guy oh there's a couple more people all
right are you the the leader no they're
drinking nuca Cola like you
belong I mean what you just said made me
want to shoot you but I just pushed that
by accident uh but you deserve to be
shot for saying that where who's
shooting where whoo whoo whoa whoa W
whoo
huh oh
no oh he doesn't even have a gun oh he
did it hey yo what who are they NCR
Tripper you did it
wow
wow strong why does she not have a
weapon what the [\h__\h] strong
fists these nuts she she just punched
him in these
nuts they carries so much [\h__\h]
[Music]
H not a
whole
so H let me try to find oh oh wow let me
try to find the leader and then we'll
talk about
maybe buying them but you didn't want to
talk generates like you hold your tongue
wasal okay here you're you're you're
pissing me
off it's over it's
[Music]
over retribution
what the [\h__\h] is your armor made out of
Big
Iron I don't give a
[\h__\h] you are piss heads scumbags go [\h__\h]
yourself I will cut off your nuts move
this machete
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h]
off so
insulting I guess I got to lud one more
of you what the [\h__\h] Spar [\h__\h]
cosplayers healing powder oh ni it's
actually something useful Caravan
shotgun is that useful is that good I
guess we might as well sell it
V oh but I don't I can't wear their [\h__\h]
I can't wear it
better than
mine problem is I can't wear their
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] okay but
uh let's
see maybe I want to sell that separately
I don't know value oh damn they're both
valuable I'm going to go back and kill
those other [\h__\h] there on on top of
the hill as well and then I'm going to
kill the the
legion the the the the Power Rangers too
Legion and Power Rangers both I'm going
to kill them
all I have chosen my
side but I'm so
[Music]
happy oh I'm just at 210 now m
maybe one more thing can
[Music]
I what can I throw away
here drop
MK maybe the iron that's five way oh is
right click dropping
[Music]
it the this one the empty Suns do I
still need these
bottles drop the legion armor no I don't
need
them I'll eat something of
course I am hungry
right oh
yeah definitely good choice to eat
[Music]
something wait that was a lot maybe
let's wait a
bit while going
back it's their fault for pissing me off
I warned
them wait I can sleep in their bed can I
not oh yeah
I've lost
Karma what Karma I've never had any
Climer you're bed free real estate
[Music]
okay
okay oh they're still not counted as
enemies well that will make everything a
lot
easier h
you want some of that ab
ab
oh come on
a I'm out of
[Music]
ammo wait wait wait oh my
God y
uh uh
uh is this out of ammo which one was out
of
ammo 7 out of
48 does it mean I still have 48 or it's
loaded 7 out of 48 and seven is all I
have the service rifle is out of
ammo I yeah zero out of
zero 748 okay okay okay okay
[Music]
M I guess one
more maybe
um that should do the
trick
right V okay okay there's a lot of
levels on
this for your overwhelming monstrous
Behavior you've become vilified by the
community oh oh oh I'm so scared oh I'm
going to go to my mommy I'm terrified
[Music]
now what am I going to
do help me the cosplayers hate me now
they hate me so much I'm so so
[Music]
sad what's up Mach oh my God so much
[\h__\h]
[Music]
weight go W go
W uh free them and then kill
them yeah wait
did you see that Showdown just now I'm
going to free you you're going to be
free from all the suffering yeah what's
this a lot I have your loty ticket
here I'm taking it away you are not a
winner
anymore okay
[\h__\h] not worth
it he can tell them the tals of
flow the Monstrous
killer who is with the NCR
remember is there something in these
things
no the
NCR will take back all the Injustice
that you have served upon this
world and turn it to
Justice a you're sleeping so Heavenly
over
there ignoring all the chaos around you
it's okay it's okay I'm protecting you
my
friend the
gunshots Prim has a new sheriff they
were should keep the power good
gunot [\h__\h] the Powder
Rangers I just killed one of them don't
you feel freed did I wait did I get the
quest
did did you did you guys see if it cuz I
freed them and then I killed them but
was it
[Music]
too
oh was it too F was I too
fast uh wait oh yeah oopsie I'm looking
at the wrong thing no I that looks like
I did it
that looks like I did it I think
so oh that's my
bottles all
right uh then back to this
one
what they want me to go back here H they
want me to take that road except exactly
but I kind of
did do I just what if I just stand here
on this road do I really have to go all
the way back no I can ignore it no back
is
okay can I Mark
yeah then we go I I think once we reach
it's probably going to be the end of
today or I kind of should probably end
it now
already because it's
late it's just around the corner okay
I'll
hurry they're not going to it's not
going to be another like War situation
there right when I arrive they're not
going to attack me it's neutral
I would hope so oh I can see is that New
Vegas in the
background or is that
no just watch out for the dinosaur look
out for Godzilla what what what what
what what
what
Godzilla wo wo wo wo
wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo
oh
okay W rat where's the shooting coming
from oh
here what happened it's always so freaky
when suddenly shooting
happens is this no back was that
Godzilla oh oh l and my best friends are
oh my God they killed
NCR didn't
they and why is NCR so
weak they should recruit me I guess I'm
automatically
recruited oh
man where is
this they're spread out to f
yeah Boone bone bone
Boone what is
this Ranger Station
Charlie I don't really I really have
time to explore
this is there someone here where I can
sell my [\h__\h]
to Charlie Charlie Charlie you dead you
D me
what did I do to
you you can't be dead
right are you in here sorry for privacy
Invasion oh for a moment I thought I saw
his feet oh thank God Charli Charlie
Charlie steeping NE who the [\h__\h] is that
what did you do to
Charlie talk to me McCaron doesn't like
it when civilians wander into military
outposts so if you're here on business
better make it quick
you're telling me to
leave radio signal out here can be
pretty spotty because of all the hills
sometimes our scheduled updates don't go
through when it happens enough times
they send someone over to check up on us
lately we've been getting extra medical
supplies for some reason I'm a no rush
to give the supplies back
either
[Music]
uh I shouldn't have said anything in the
first place I'd rather not get you into
the habit of crossing the NCR i w cross
them I'm I'm I'm their Ally the biggest
Ally they have right
now see you around
man I I really need those stim packs
man you don't give a [\h__\h] about
me so sad am are my limbs
okay oh
motorcycle gas
tank if I need this guys I can still
come back here to pick it up and sell it
eventually I need a companion wait can I
can you actually get a companion in this
game that will like run around with
you
really I I hope I hope that companion
Wouldn't Die
like that other who was close to being a
companion of mine at least for a short
amount of
time I can get a dog
oh Cass is one of them the one who was
tending the bar not the cow girl right
Black Mountain radio signal phone a what
the [\h__\h]
oh the cowgirl ah okay
okay the best you say that because she's
a cute girl or you say that because
she's actually a good fighter does she
have like good armor that she brings
with her or what
oh that's why you were saying watch out
for Godzilla because it's a landmark I
thought I was going to be attacked by
something both
both okay there's a ghoul too I have I
think it would be kind of cool to have a
ghoul cool to have a
ghoul howy I'm a Novak let's [\h__\h]
go I think I don't know if we want to
listen to someone chitchat before we go
is there something important to listen
to
now now
back welcome to Nob
back howdy who are you well welcome to
you you look tired from the road why
don't you relax this spell let this fine
Town take care Oh So Sweet so kind I I'm
not used to this
kindness oh what am I doing I got to
thinking about making a good impression
and plain forgot to tell you my name
it's okay I see it's here I'm Genie may
I take care of folks here at the motel
long as they aren't troublemakers
spoiler
craw what wait am I I feel like Crawford
was C No No Maybe not maybe it's just a
similar similar
name a man check coat have you seen
anyone like that well he might have been
wearing a fancy outfit but he wasn't any
kind of gentleman to me had his nose
stuck so high in the air you couldn't
see it above the clouds city folk they
always think they deserve better than
what they got those hoodlums he was with
seem to know many for some reason he's
our daytime sniper up in the dinosaur's
mouth oh every seems like every little
village has their own sniper huh
completed find out from Manny Vargas
where the did I accidentally go to the
right person or could it have been any
person to talk
to watch out for strangers she the the
perfect person to talk to
steal dinky the
T-Rex I found the right
person or she's just one of them oh I
can have them thank
[Music]
you
okay all right then
oh that is probably a good spot we
played for 6 hours 44
minutes uh what am I doing
here okay
quit I I saved I click saved it counts
right
goodbye
[Music]
well man okay so my impression so
far I think I I like it all I'm
um I'm doing I think I'm doing fish so
far it's a bit annoying with the weight
it's like Diablo 2 levels of annoyance
because okay Diablo was more like space
rather than weight in the inventory but
still I need to do something about
that um I definitely have a big hatred
for most of the people in the game
except for the
NCR seems like everybody is just full of
[\h__\h] but yeah I I like it I think um
we'll continue
playing I didn't have any crashes either
so it's running
decently a backpack
mod in Fey I can get mods but I have to
get like every mod uh like permitted I
have to ask for permission I have to go
through application and [\h__\h] that's a
bit annoying so ideally I just want to
play like this if if if it's
possible glad you took the pew pew route
well I can't have these [\h__\h] cross me
like that can I
now buy DLC I was thinking about it I
don't mind buying a
DLC I saw that there were a [\h__\h] ton of
them don't know what they really
do there's perks that increase weight
yeah I need one of those is it this set
at like what level you get that perk as
a
[Music]
choice get the complete pack well it's
too late now I I bought the game on its
own three of them are big star DLCs okay
but I don't think I would like add any
more story to the game than than there
already
is if they add if they give me some cool
equipment otherwise I don't
know EXO staries you know this I know
this game is already plenty long I'm not
going to add any more time to
it no no no no no no no why not this is
plenty long
I don't know maybe if I get even more
into it for now I I'm I'm interested but
I'm not like hooked like oh my God I
have to play like every single side
quest I have to find every little secret
and all that
no nice gaming well thank you guys for
watching I I think I'm going to leave it
at that um or will I I should read Super
Chat I will I will I will
I wish I had a wild west kind of setting
right now but I
[Music]
don't guess we'll just go to my
office follow me
partner oh
wait the filters why are there so many
filters on me from
yesterday thank you for the fun stream
thank you for watching uh I don't really
have many tangents are still going on
now so sorry if it was a bit boring in
terms of w not telling you many
stories brain
empty what am I doing oh yeah here fixed
[Music]
chat I have 60 DM what's
happening
oh oh
H interesting I was sent something
interesting we're going to continue
listening to this wonderful marvelous
music or should we I also have I found
another nice bgm when I was going
through audio stock today found
something that I want to use for Super
Chat door reading
time it's also supposedly Blues but it
wasn't country enough for for me country
country they called it Blues
though in the
description oh I think it's so
quiet that L the interesting thing I
can't I saw coefficient posted a preview
of your
cosplay oh is it in my
hashtag oh
ohoh let me
see
coefficient oh it's not him wearing it
okay at least more coffee than the m one
it's more coffee than the m
one I wonder if they sell it in
like like his size in the first place I
guess they must have been selling it in
his size otherwise he wouldn't buy it
for them I
wonder the Wawa cosplay comes in all
sizes I guess you can also be the CEO
that you love so much buy this cosplay
to become one with
[Music]
her I hope it covers his butt well but
I've seen a lot of those cosplays um
that are like MK produced or so more or
less mass produced they the skirts are
pretty long and they also often they
don't even start on the hip but on the
waist yeah even though like if it's
really accurate it really should start
on the hip the the top of the skirt
should be on the hip and it really
should just be the width of like a belt
buckle
but if it's if the skirt is that short
on a dude then is a little bit
risky so feel free to go with the long
version of the
skirt yeah it's super low rise I mean I
I would normally not wear low rise
things it makes you feel quite
uncomfortable and uneasy IRL I would
say but low rise low rise pants for
example my whole life they were never a
thing I think that was like before I was
born lowr pants were a popular thing
with ladies to
wear I don't think I don't think I would
ever have felt comfortable in something
like
that I don't know I like highways that
it's just
comfortable and relatively you know
flattering because and you know you can
like hide it shapes you nicely
okay super
[Music]
chats super chats where are we
continuing
uh uh did I read the ones from ah I
guess at least the hor not hor quite but
the collab that I did
today and what about witch spring did I
read Rich which spr I think I did so
worms collab
yay okay
okay I'm glad it worked out in the end
and I think it was a smart choice to not
force the other game to happen I'd
probably have been I'd probably have had
troubles with that if I did
that natural waist jeans are for curvy
people low rice jeans are for skinny yes
skinny
people probably look decent but even
then like I don't
like I wouldn't like showing that much
of the the area of under my belly
button worms needs to happen more like I
think for a future six person collab I
think worms would also be a good choice
subu played it before really didn't but
I think they would all enjoy it and
yeah I think it would be a good
choice to just play worms again but it's
not going to happen soon I think it's
just an idea for the future to keep in
mind I'm going to make it happen at some
point waa makes everything happen oh
I've been asking uh for help like the
the you know the server setup for the
The Minecraft Project so that's also
moving on everybody said they will
participate so it's actually happening
and I'll have uh well I'll probably pay
for it possibly if they need me to pay
for it but uh they're setting up
management will set up the server
probably if there's no issues I asked
for it JMA was like okay tell me what
you need I'll I'll relay the
information M and I talked uh like
pretty deeply the other day yesterday no
the day before yesterday I think I
talked a lot to GAA it may have been
yesterday no the day before yesterday I
don't know anymore I talked a lot to GAA
and we both agreed that you know we want
to do more stuff with myth
again and yeah we talked about a lot of
things but she was she seemed very
excited about the idea to
yeah we're going to have fun I'm sure
I'm excited for it June it's almost June
it's already the end of M myth the
already the end of May what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] it's just like one
week
left yeah
B yeah B oh my God in June July we're
like halfway for the [\h__\h]
year
no oh God that's
it's
terrifying I mean end of
May look it's 26 what the
[\h__\h] uh close to your
birthday yeah yeah that's I guess fun
but uh it's just what the [\h__\h] why is
2024 already like halfway
through it scares me
H and I have a lot to do in the
summer so that scares me
[Music]
too you say this every year yeah it's
true every
year the year is zooming it's flying by
Yo before you know it's 2030 for real
for real add and reg about to be one
year old
wow damn for for Advent like ring gloss
I'm not that connected to them so I
don't feel so crazy about that but
Advent being one year old soon wow that
also feels very
fast hey hey no no not changing bgm
you're supposed to stay on that one
oopsy sudden
banjo crazy
banjo yeah I don't know I'm I've been
really enjoying this current not so
stressful time
because the until recently I've been
going from one thing to another to
another it feels like and then finally
all the stress lifted a bit on
me and that will continue as I said
before probably until end of June
is so I got to cherish these moments
when it's not so
[Music]
stressful the cycle of the grind yeah
it's it's
tough
but it's going to be an exciting summer
I guess h
M oh I was actually ah I was talking
with my sister because I
finally uh had some time to like go to
the Post Office and send the pens that
she really wanted and so I asked for her
address I just don't remember it haven't
visited her uh ever since a long time
ago cuz she moved a couple years ago
like I guess um but we've seen each
other but I just like normally she
visits
me but so I asked for the address I
prepared everything but then we got a
little bit into chatting
and uh I asked
her like oh what you going to where you
going to go
for uh vacation this year cuz she likes
vacations she goes here and there and
she was the one who went to Thailand so
I also talked with her a little bit
about
uh my talent experience like she asked
me about it I was like I didn't really
see
much and it was hot as
[\h__\h] but I want to go again some at some
point and so I asked her where she went
cuz I actually wasn't 100% sure on that
I don't remember I did not remember it
so well but she went
to a nice
Island not going to say where cuz it
doesn't matter but she went to nice
Island in Thailand and yeah we were just
talking a little bit about vacation I
was like
[Music]
thinking I wonder if we could maybe you
know go somewhere together but then the
more I thought about it the more I
realized I just actually don't have the
time for
it like I'll be busy all
of most of July all of August half of
September
maybe a bit more than half of
September traveling here and there doing
this and
that birthday
anniversary all kinds of things so I
threw that idea out of the window pretty
quickly but then uh we talked about
maybe in the winter and I was like oh
where could we go maybe I don't know
about that either but she wants to go to
the Mal someday and I said oh if you
ever go to the males then you can ask me
anything about it because it's kind of
become like a yearly tradition for
me now she said she doesn't want to go
to the males like this coming year she
wants to save money and then go on a
special birthday uh eventually and I was
like okay well I'm not going to you know
force myself into that
because yeah you'll probably go with you
know someone and and then she was like
no no you can totally come I would I
would like to have more people but I was
like well you know I I guess okay if you
don't mind and then uh I'll add another
Mal's trip you know I kind of want to go
every year because mes is going to be
gone at some point by
2050 by
so that tells me I have to go there more
often then I gave her a lot of advice on
well deeps already even though it's way
too
early
and and she also told me something she I
should have talked about this I didn't I
forgot this tangent I forgot it but I
wouldn't have been able to tell it
properly cuz I would have been
distracted probably she told me that in
Thailand she she and her special someone
did
get
themselves a diving
license my
sister I didn't
realize I had someone so close to me who
has a diving
license look
gasp uh so I asked her a few questions
but basically she said tell me more
about it another time um but also she
said she said I should like get the
diving license
not in Austria but actually in one of
the vacation destinations I was like
isn't it really expensive but then she
told me the price that she paid in
Thailand and it was a good price it was
a good
price and she said that like if I do it
in Austria it'll be in lakes and lakes
are diving in Lakes she said even in
Thailand where the ocean is warmish I
guess even there she felt cold after
like 20 minutes of
diving so our leges in Austria are
pretty cold as [\h__\h] and she said that
would be horrible for you that'll be a
horrible
experience um and it's just also not so
nice looking but yeah I thought okay
that's a good point but I think
I I know a solution but but yeah I I I
have to consider it because I was
checking the prices for diving licenses
the other day in Austria
and depends if I want to do in a group
or privately
alone uh but even in a group the ones I
saw were kind of expensive is so now I'm
wondering maybe this not necessarily
more cheap to do it in my own
country maybe not
H maybe I should do it in like a
vacation within a
vacation but then I don't know how much
time that will take up but my sister did
it within the vacation so I'm sure it
doesn't take up like too much time from
what I
hear the the Practical part of it it
doesn't take that much time
right might be cheaper in a place where
there's more of an in industry around
it many of my friends got the license in
Thailand oh yeah my sister said even
though that was a uh somewhat hard to
reach Island where she
was uh they even had like German
instructors licensed instructors
there Germans speaking
Germans for the div license so that's
pretty impressive I wonder if that's
pretty
common
H so
H I don't know where to do it now I'm
kind of torn apart where to do
it south of Japan generally I feel like
Japan would be expensive but with the
Yen being so cheap
then I guess it's not maybe that
expensive I got to look up prices for
diving L and maybe I can get someone
else uh to do it with
me I wonder if there's a Japanese member
who would go to like Okinawa with me for
like maximum a week although honestly I
don't know if I want to do the like Fury
part part of it in
Japanese I wonder if they would uh have
an option to do it in
English I feel like in Thailand and so
on they would but in Japanese I almost
feel like they might not have
[Music]
it well M no we already I already
cleared this up after the Hol talk
stream because I didn't want to get your
hopes up we talked about it calmly and
realistically even if she wants to do
something with me for have a nice day
it's not going to happen the Su in this
summer probably not in Autumn either
she's like pretty planned out and booked
out so
[Music]
yeah yeah I could consider Japan for
it I really wanted to go snorkeling in
pan but I don't know if I would have
have time
this uh summer I'll have to figure it
out I'll figure it
out H what I what I can do is like at
least go test it out in Austria there's
a place I found where I can test it
without getting the license right
away snop they call it in
German water skiing no I want to go
diving water skiing looks so cool but
kind of freaks me out looks
stressful a sniffing course yeah yeah
yeah yeah in German we say a sniffing
course we sniff snuff if we want to try
an activity or so
out
I how do you call that an English again
I feel like I heard a word for it
before Endless Ocean well I don't need
that you think that'll help me for my
license I don't need that I played Dave
the diver I finished Dave the diver I
was a pro at Dave the
diver trial course I guess so trial
period M period sounds like it's longer
usually oura who is it are just like one
an hour or so whatever short something
short but yeah anyway I should start
reading super chats but that's my little
tangent about my
sister and vacations and males and uh
diving there you go there you
go but a that's so cool because like I
don't know anyone else who has a diving
license and now I I realized I could go
diving with her like if we go
somewhere I I would have someone to dive
with if we do go somewhere
together
H crazy coincidence yeah I guess she's
the type to Tri try something like that
out
H that's nice
you know that sounds like
[Music]
fun cuz you know I tried to get narissa
to snorkle with me and and she tried it
but then she didn't want to do it
anymore so she would probably never go
diving with
me uh it's like I mean snorkling is
really harmless easy but diving is quite
a bit more challenging and difficult I'm
sure and and
yeah really Next Level it's not for
everyone I guess
so
M so finding someone to do that with
you is a challenge on its
own if a person can't handle snorkeling
they should probably never even try
diving possibly yeah crony says she
wants to go diving really well she's so
[\h__\h]
far but I smelled
her all the way from Poland I could
smell her recently that was nice I'm
just
kidding I smelled her
presents sniff
SN
okay we're gonna Read Super chats from
the collab today that was fun
the
gires
girles
yay Nissa and Mum really didn't do so
badly for not even playing the tutorial
or so they got into it fast and then
mumi won twice
[Music]
wow it's so weird for me to be up at
that time though
because like I I lost my tiredness
pretty soon after I started talking to
them when setting up
everything and then after the collab I
was like all right I'm going to sleep
again so oh yeah sorry Sorry by the way
uh who did I yeah I said sorry narissa
I'm sure it's like super late for you
and then she's like oh what do you mean
no not at all it's like 300 p.m. and I'm
like it oh oh yeah right right right
this isn't my usual somehow it felt to
me like it would be Japanese prime time
or so a little bit later and and like
afternoon for me that's how it felt like
for me cuz that's how when I would
normally stream or you know I would get
up like at 10 11 and then stream like a
little bit later in the day that's how
it felt like to
me
H yeah but it was if anything yeah I
guess it would have been late for M
mumi 7
a.m. 7
a.m. maybe I could try to do the next
worms collab while I'm in Japan because
then at least we can cut out the
European Time Zone Pro
problem if I just have to think about
like Asian time zone and American time
zone then because six people from a lot
of different
countries going to be difficult so it
would be probably the best if I did it
while I was in
Japan sorry yeah you've been chosen as a
sacrifice just for one stream it won't
even be that long probably just 2 hours
you
know yeah got to group up as much as
possible yeah
yeah okay let's read super
chats py monkey cougar
D oh happy birthday
well thank you all for my happy birthday
and but remember I love you all just as
much oh wait what did you send uh a
message that's your birthday as a
member's message or
so it sounds like you already said it at
that point and now we just thanking us
for congratulating you you're welcome
Happy
Birthday op than space waterful thank
you thank you good morning
this yeah I woke up at like 6:20 like my
alarm went off at
6:20 and I was actually
lucky that I woke up
because I don't remember changing the
sounds I must have I must have done it
accidentally when changing the time but
I changed my alarm sound to one that you
could easily sleep through and Miss
completely
H dangerous
dangerous it was like so short and so
silent and so
unnoticeable it was just like like a
what what was
[Music]
it wait
oh how to play these sounds oh well
whatever whatever I was trying to find
the sound to play it again but yeah it
was just really subtle but my brain is
so smart and wakes me up even with the
most subtle
sounds you're still using the alarm that
you asked for me oh
really that's so cute so cute we're so
we're talking every morning
then we're talking to each other every
morning yeah smoothie by the way because
somebody mentioned if jonkers woke me up
that's smoothie normally but she's been
definitely uh way less annoying than
during the times when she was really
annoying like she will sometimes still
wake me up but not that early
and sometimes she will also give
up relatively easily and then I continue
sleeping a while longer it's not so bad
really it's not bothering me
actually thank you smoothie but she's
still I don't understand after so many
years of me consistently feeding her
every morning and every
evening like she still meows so
desperately for it
endlessly even when I already have like
the food in a plate and walking towards
her Bowl she's still
like like I'm already on the way you saw
the food you saw that I put it in you
smell it probably already what do you
think I'm going to do you think I'm just
GNA throw it out or eat it myself now of
course it's for you why are you so
dramatic like I'm giving you the food
you know it I'm doing it every every day
for years you should know by
now what's with this
cat I'm so lucky that jonka is just is
so simple and she doesn't want anything
really but Kibbles but sometimes I still
give her you know little snack because I
feel bad that she doesn't get anything
else she just doesn't like wet food but
she likes the the lick
thing she wants her food now yeah but
you're getting it now stop me alling
you're getting
it so
weird and oh yeah my mom slept here uh
the other day right and she woke up
before me and then the cat smoothie
meowed a little bit at her she would
have probably given up uh after a while
if my mom would have ignored her because
she doesn't give up with me but she
gives up with
others and my mom then proceeded to make
her food but um I know exactly how to
portion the food for my cat so that she
doesn't have like waste really I figured
out the exact portion size cuz they sell
uh wet food usually most of them are
like in 85 G of bags and I've realized I
can portion I used to portion them in
half but then she would still have
things left over so I portion those
small packs in uh thirds three thirds
one FD in the morning one F in the
evening one FD in the next morning and
so on then I open a new bag um but my
mom gave her I think two FS there was an
open bag and I had one F used already
and she gave smoothie 2/3 and it was
like way too much in there
and I it's weird like it's the fact that
it's too much combined with it's not
given by me
like if my mom gave her the right
portion I think she would have maybe
eaten it uh but my mom the fact that it
wasn't me and it wasn't the right
amount once my mom put down the food she
took like a few bites smovie took a few
bites and then just left it and just
didn't eat most of the food and this
happened a few times now that my cat
smooy just wouldn't really eat the food
when other people are here uh for me no
matter what brand if it's wet food she
usually eats any brand but then I come
back from a vacation or a trip or so and
whoever took care of my cats they're
telling me Oh by the way she really
didn't like this wet food so I bought
different one I'm like she does like it
I think it's like she's just getting
picky when there's other people and also
they're kind of like it's weird but
they're because they're portioning it
wrong she's like thrown off you know
she's like this is not right and then
she doesn't want to eat it and another
problem
is sometimes they don't pick they don't
they just put the the next food in the
same Bowl where there's still a few
leftovers like you know in there that
are like dried and stinky and then she
will also not eat it so I keep on
telling them please give just I have so
many bowls she will not eat the food so
portion it right and then put it in a
fresh Bowl otherwise she's not going to
eat it and she's still going to meow at
you yeah not always but sometimes
M my cats are the opposite they always
eat the dry food and leave the wet food
oh well then if they leave it then can
you just not give it to
them smovie is a princess well no if you
think about it I wouldn't want my food
to be served on a plate that had the
food from yesterday on
it so especially if it
stinks it's understandable we don't want
that either as humans
no
so you know there's cat things
complicated she makes it my cat this
movie she makes it more complicated when
there's other
people taking care of her
unfortunately yeah sorry sorry my dear
cat
sitters yeah get this nasty bowl out of
my face exactly but it's fair yeah
that's just
[Music]
cats so where was I oh yeah smirky danan
Andreas danan Prince of Denmark danan V
faction thanks for the red super chat
birds of a f flock together so I expect
lots of flocking from all the birds
tonight flocking flocking well there was
a lot of flocking together in like the
pit in the second game and even in the
first game I feel like there was some
flocking
[Music]
together so I I hope that was fulfilled
in a satisfactory way for
you vaction s satis
vaction
B thank you for your Super
Chat and then G thank you also for red
Super Chat burp Supremacy thank you so
much I think I saw you immediately join
the membership after your Super Chat
thank you for that
too I appreciate it thank you so much
also is that a doo in your profile
picture he looks
small and he looks very fluffy so that's
cute simply D
FR space wonder and py
[Music]
and now we have the super chats from
today which by the way shout out to
chy I asked him to um make put me in the
same pose with a helmet and a gun h a
revolver as you know in that picture I
didn't end up using the same background
because I was using that first I was
putting myself over it over the dude but
then I don't know didn't look so good
because of logo placement and stuff so I
ended up using different background and
just kind of recreating it with
that but yeah wow
wow
wow nice thumbnail right fredd
thumbnails they hit differently
sometimes cuz I can be in all kinds of
poses and recreate poses I like
[Music]
it nice one thank you I put some effort
into
that you guys were noticing it I
see Wasteland W
yeah that's
me okay um we move on to today's Super
Chat scroll scroll scroll scroll
scroll oh okay here we go FL happy boy
thank you for two red super chats Mama
Mia
dun
wow not long ago I had this entire
franchise on my list of legendary games
a Ki couldn't be convinced to play at
gunpoint but so are GTA and AOE and I
loved every second of you playing those
on the stream that's what I've been
telling you like you guys kept on saying
that about games throughout the years
that I ended up playing so
hence my gratitude and hype levels are
off the scale right now there is only so
much of this game that you can
reasonably cover during the series oh
okay you at least are understanding that
I might not do all of it you know but
still I'm sure you'll have tons of fun
delving into into the Fallout LA and
shaping the fate of Mo heavy move with
your morally unimpeachable
actions what does that mean morally
unimpeachable
do you think what I did today was
morally unimpeachable I feel like that
was very very understandable I have
observed the
situation of you know several fractions
and I have decided after an objective
observation that NCR so far are the only
ones who are not
[Music]
bastards and so I've chosen my sides
yeah you can't question it okay if that
is what unimpeachable means then yeah
okay okay you you get it you cannot uh
question my actions they're not
something you would question anyway
because it was the right actions anyway
e killing our best friend
Doo I feel like I uh in in in the series
uh the NCR was already gone right so I
didn't really have an impression of it I
tried to understand some stuff because
they did touch upon NCR a little
bit uh
yeah but I I I don't think I was able to
give myself an image about
it they will be bad well I can see that
uh I think that's probably a spoiler
telling me that but I can see that
happening like in the end everybody is a
piece of
[\h__\h] and maybe I have to choose the
Lesser
evil if it's just not good
either we
[Music]
see a few are just bad yeah that's what
I've what has been conveyed to me so
far just like in
Witcher in the
show was I able to see that
happening yeah I guess so I guess so
because they all wanted uh what was her
name again and and they wanted her and
you now you have to be
like I guess we'll side with the the
witch witches and wizards or whatever
yeah Silla mhm guess we'll you know get
their help we need someone they also
want her for whatever reason blah blah
blah
[Music]
blah the Roman larpers [\h__\h] them oh my
God what the [\h__\h] they're so lame
they're so
lame they're so lame anyway thank you so
much Flappy boy I hope you're going to
continue enjoying it when I play it
again thank you for following and
watching today through my journey me in
the wastelands on my way to New Vegas my
round roundabout way way way to New
Vegas
[Laughter]
K okay well yeah well well I'm not going
to talk about that anymore about the
pronunciation KY stamps than logical
Paradox than so 94 thanks for the pinky
you're not in uniform K where is your
power armor ah yeah Power Armor was the
the big the big armor that I saw in the
show right yeah I don't know I I'm not
I'm not one of
[Music]
them the Brotherhood of
Steel yeah what Max wears
even though he's not supposed
to you meet him
later
Enclave
Enclave she's not going to e that Super
Chat was a reference the whole
phrase yeah well thank you for the Super
Chat though Prince of
Denmark with a sound an accent Kick K
key oh thanks for writing it like that
definitely sounds like a unique take on
a battlecry like y y
yay yeaw partner Yeehaw to you
too I can't I can't I don't know
how final F fcy James
[Music]
love
bre you look like certain follower ing
game what are you saying I look like
someone in game
me crusty D sick Freds ah you mean my
tweet I just had that idea because I saw
on Twitter I was just scrolling through
and I saw someone you know the typical
thing where somebody writes here's a
Fred because it's a Twitter Fred and
they already warn people uh that it's
going to be a whole fret so don't look
at just this tweet there's going to be
more so I thought M
Fred how about I give you a Fred here's
a Fred and then I post the emote but
then you would think that there's a
followup that there's a whole Fred after
this no no there was no Fred it was just
a Fred and then I cut it wow wow wow
sick Fred indeed thank you crusty Fred
shut up shut up there's no friended
there's only friend
big difference between Fred and Fred
okay can't you hear it clean your ears
or you need a replacement of your ears
huh one is Fred and one is
Fred I don't even know which one was
rich just
now
F Five Nights at Freddy's
oh one is Fred and the other is
friended oh
[\h__\h] man who thought of the th eh who F
who f o u g h
t who fought
of th
stupid s 17 b32 d y d Apper gaming
D Garden Park
D the steel D the steel D and yeah
science was helpful I I did feel like I
wanted access to those terminals I was
not able to resist so that was good gaku
sangi dun the steal again danash the
keeper of
dragons you made me realize that's one
thing to look forward to in the summer
realize again we're going to get a new
season let's
go house of the Dragon let's go I'm
getting so much exciting things I'm
getting two new bakuga D Seasons this
summer I'm getting House of the dragon
and a bunch of other things rings of
power and eventually there should be a
new season of what was it uh I always
forget this one
what is that other
show that's kind of in the same yeah
real of
time yeah and and maybe even another
thing that I forgot oh yeah Witcher wa
although we don't know anything about a
new Witcher season probably I don't
think we know that's not coming so soon
Vikings at some point
Vikings there's still Seasons Oh you
mean
Valhalla huh Vikings
Valhalla
was Viking I watched that
recently yeah yeah that one ah with Olaf
Haralson ah that
okay [\h__\h] Olaf haral son man I hate that
guy King Cano is cool though he's cool
he's cool in my
books the B yeah B
combination there was a teaser for
season 4 Witcher oh recently or what uh
screenshots with Liam hensworth
really oh was there an actual video
teaser maybe I saw did I see
it one piece next year next year
no this year
I do not accept anything
less I not I don't accept it I don't
accept it you can't tease me like that
and then just not deliver the next
season within a reasonable time
frame they didn't start filming what the
[\h__\h] strike has been over for a long
time now get to
work get to work now
D the steel Dan H the P come for the of
I want to listen to The Fallout New
Vegas version jingle jangle jingle you
sing see I haven't heard this one yet I
I was listening a bit to am's stream for
like maybe 5 or 10 minutes I wasn't
really watching I was just listening to
the vibe to get inspiration of what I
need from audio stock don't think I've
heard the jingle jangle jingle
I got to listen to
it it played in the radio a little bit
oh really faintly in the background o I
turned off the radio for a
reason why [\h__\h] jukebox betraying me
bamboozling
me I I think generally it's fine
um I'm not going to get like in trouble
but yeah thank you so so much huie come
downar
D how did you know that I was going to
say that oh hovie sent another pinky
press V with the bat system you don't
have much to fear in the Wasteland yeah
don't take aim at the veteran NCR Ranger
who has occasionally worn black armor
you won't face them now but don't come
at them from time to time what do you
mean that even if they're if were
friendly the moment I aim at him he
would take it as a fret
[Music]
a
FR a a
FR veteran Rangers are the ncr's
badasses they're so cool h
well I'm looking forward to making their
uh making their what's the word not
accomplice
uh making their uh
uh acquaintance that was yes thank you
for the tips
H Dax Jaden Dan and Honolulu also thank
you for the pinky
uh
uh was it was
[Music]
it aim aim aim are you saying K aim to
me in Korean
letters
yell yellow yellow yellow
lol l
h you little
[\h__\h] you do
you did you just say Kus Taco aim to
me can't believe
it Pablo
[Music]
P my aim it was okay it was okay I
pink thank you for the pinky the steel
danion the steel
Dani dush the steel dushin wow a lot of
like just but judging the super chats
there's a lot of new viewers or like
unusual viewers who are excited about
new
Vegas you can see the things I shoot at
you burrow into your skin
e d the Ste D na called D for the pinky
since you're kind of like our stream mom
would you be cross if we don't poke our
head in and say
hi was this in relation to something
specific that I said
but yeah you always got to say hi to me
no matter if I'm your mom or
not oh the NPC said something similar oh
ah well Nathan of course you got to say
hi but I wouldn't worry about that with
you you're going to say hi
anyway thank you Nathan the steal D cops
d for the pinky jingle jingle jingle oh
well you're able to hear it in the
background sorry I couldn't turn it up I
would love to turn it up louder
louder You' been here since 2020 I just
really love New Vegas a thank you well
I'm glad I could like kind of drag you
out of your dark
corner and hear from you directly nice
to have you around
lurker the
steel and
[Music]
mad
kitten the steal
Dan gorp
Dan hacking Min Game T tip look for ah
yeah thank you for this that was really
helpful
chicken Berry G if you think aiming down
the aiming down AR aiming down the sides
right click is hard to line up a yeah
yeah you can turn off true iron sides in
settings to have the game just zoom to
help yes I think I think I understand
what you mean and I think I would prefer
that uh I honestly don't know where it's
shooting when I'm right
clicking I don't know what I'm doing
there yeah remind me next time
M I just want the the normal vision but
if it can zoom in with that that would
be
nice cuz I think my aim is already
decent um the only problem is that often
they're too far
away it's also not very precise because
your gun skill level is kind of low oh
really regular chat for 2 years oh well
the super chats always make people stand
out OB L well thank you so much and take
it monkey
d space wonderful D toys killer
Productions
D oh I think I know what you mean
because of the perks yeah lunchbox
[Music]
than Prince of Denmark Dan fock
Dan
duh who want Carlos rodri St for the red
super chat hi wa I finally got my first
job it was a bit scary at first since I
get anxious speaking with people IRL but
I was able to overcome it and you were
one of my main motivations now I can
finally send my first red super to my
beloved oi love you wa thank
you wow congratulations your first job
that's
exciting W is it like uh like a so to
say proper job or is it like an
apprenticeship or so like what I
did that was my first job of an
apprenticeship I wonder but whatever it
is I'm I'm sure you're going to do great
I'm sure it's going to
be you're going to be good at
it so good luck even though you don't
need it I wish you all the best I hope
you can still find time to come to my
streams even if you have your first job
now make sure to make some time for Wawa
than than you for the red super
ja the
[Music]
steel maybe
it's one of
D May no I don't think I'll take it off
but it'll be a bit complicated when I'll
be streaming JT
D thank you
oh don't worry about
it don't worry about oh I I I understand
the rest was in a membership a members
message don't worry about it you can
always say hi even if you just
[Music]
Ling thank you [\h__\h] those legionaires
J is it actually like
free like does it
really um if you side with like Legion
for
example can you actually like side of
the Legion and then say [\h__\h] you to the
NCR and like the game will be fully
influenced by that and changes
directions because of
that
oh because the NCR seems kind of like
the main thing
so
far the game will warn
[Music]
you
not well it seems like I've already made
my
choice oh don't fall for the NC
STS wait wait chill right now they seem
nice to me so you guys should not feel
like NCR is evil evil cuz I don't know
that
I don't know
that it's not well well developed that's
what I almost thought yeah that probably
even if you can do it
then it's probably not the the cannon
route to take so they maybe don't put
that much content into it or
so if you choose Legion or so
just not a big fan of the government in
came or
IRL py
Danish Sean R Danish C be Danish Cruz
Dan action ich Dan thank you did I make
good progress am I already ahead of
am did she even play it more than once
maybe
twice when I looked up am Fallout I only
found one
stream and that was relatively
short oh she did 11 times oh really it
only showed me the first
one oh really she's continuing okay okay
okay just SP a lot of time in between I
guess like with her other plays like
Oblivion or
[Music]
whatever
yeah she played DLCs
too she finished
it oh she actually finished she fin
finished the DLCs but she didn't finish
the main
story see that's what would happened to
Me Maybe n maybe not quite like that I
would like put more effort into like
finishing the game within a reasonable
time
frame
probably but still it would extend it a
lot lot I guess
so oh she played it a lot uh she played
it a long ago on her own oh private
[Music]
time
oh SP wonderful than soon Unwritten than
py D the gamer cre D spank thank you for
the rest of chat my cats are the
opposite they always eat I already read
this thank you sping time always nice to
talk about cats with
[Music]
you black fruit
sh oh this your favorite
game
really wow okay well good for you the
steel Dan the steel Dan death
Dan m thank
you one day may your Phoenix Flames give
the legions leader an early
orania yeah
[Applause]
kill the steel d m a d for the pinky if
you turn off super chats next to NV
stream you can use the radio like am
did gray area
this a weekday stream sounds good if you
need the weekend off oh and since you
mentioned paper Mar P would have beat it
in two long streams yeah I saw she was
playing it if you were curious about the
games
length I think I'm not going to play it
on stream after all cuz I'm watching
dendo play it and it's spoilering me
anyway and I don't
know just by watching him I'm like not
that interested in playing it
myself it's not bad but it's like I
don't think I would get that uh into it
as with the Super Mario RPG that we
played yeah yeah yeah and we have enough
going on right now
anyway
[Music]
yeah no you would trust
me I don't
know I'm I need which spring r
and
Fallout and then eventually Witcher and
ah other things want to play AOE again
want to play This and That Then
Minecraft Minecraft has a like two week
or so project is also coming
up I don't know about playing it yeah
not really interested to be honest
yeah Minecraft dungeons 2o
yeah uh
actually isn't
that I kept on talking about Minecraft
dungeons but I just bought it
actually
um the other day cuz it was on sale and
and I I was like he didn't I buy it
before what the hell now I bought
it Stella blade f was
crossed I I requested perms so far
nothing well it's Sunday so probably
nothing will have changed but let me
check yeah no I looks looks pretty
bad looks pretty bad I don't think I
mean not bad it's just like no
no no progress
nobody in Ian has ever streamed a Sony
game I still wanted to try it's not I
don't
know it's not always impossible I would
say damn I would really like to play it
I want to I want to see those shiny
butts please
please FL Dan you are
Dan because tax
taxes are kind of
necessary uh and uh m d I did I did and
Ohio enjoyer D back in high school and
University I would play default games
with my closest friends for hours with
different routes and skills doing
commentary the whole time
a that's sweet sounds like nice memories
you have there partner
[Music]
yo
same but with
Skyrim Cinderella time press I got to go
and I got to cook
actually I hope it will be
simple you've never seen this
screen I mean recently I've been using
the girls talk screen more than this one
but this is are you for
real hey for real you got to come here
more often it
seems yeah I'm turning back into a
pumpkin oh
no a
pumpkin why
pumpkin because orange when did you guys
decide it was a
pumpkin could be
anything but okay I'll take it why not
carrots okay guess I'm and pumpkin and
pumpkin I'm going to go now see you on
Tuesday schedule tomorrow on
Monday and yeah maybe I'll record and
probably not no I record some motion
sometime in the week maybe actually n
I'll be busy with ofai stuff
[Music]
n what's tomorrow schedule
day no stream no stream I think I need
to clean up the room it's still the same
as yesterday
it looks so messy and yeah I need to
prep
stuff and in German we say
Al
[Music]
vay
ye this outfit is so cute oh smoothie hi
oh my God what what
hi did you
hear
hey don't go away did you hear you
heard she's like what the [\h__\h] is this
mess you soon didn't clean up
[\h__\h] such a
mess okay she's she's ready for me to
end my
stream she's like
you have the permission to end the
stream now and then make your
food and then make my food
okay bye-bye
[Music]