[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
ah okay
[Music]
oh my god why do i hear an echo what
oh my gosh
oh because i'm watching my own stream ah
that makes sense hello everybody okay
i'm egg can i hear you say kitty
[Music]
cute very cute
we are here today to play
a famous game called overwatch
oh wow
yeah and ahmed is gonna be overwatching
me
that's why she's above me
she's over me
no you're not over me right you're just
above me
oh yeah yeah yeah i'm the i'm over yeah
like you said just overwatching yeah
teaching i guess yeah once again
let's see if i'll do
better or worse than paladins but yeah i
got the i got the famous paladin's
announcer here unfortunately she's not
an overwatch announcer but who knows
yeah not yet could happen one day
maybe for uh two million
yeah yeah
two million the celebration will be
overwatch
also we are once again flexing the twin
tails they are very important in fps
games to keep your balance you know and
they help it's like on a body point when
you when you're a child remember you
have training wheels yeah i had the
training wheels now the twin tails are
like training wheels
yeah i could see that okay okay for our
brains yeah makes a lot of sense now i
only played the tutorial i never played
overwatch ever before
so
i'm gonna be [\h__\h] guys
uh get ready for
it won't be that bad i mean who's your
like mane in overwatch
in overwatch
uh i would switch between playing uh
this character called anna and she's a
sniper but also a healer and her shots
heal and do damage or the heel teammates
do damage to enemies
and also lucio he's really fun he can
skate on walls i think i heard a blue
he's also a healer
yeah he's really cool and diva who's
really cute he's probably seen
[Music]
korean idol
yeah
okay i've i've been uh
i've been recommended certain roles
but i think we should try out several
ones
and we started out
with only us two or what
yeah so i thought it'd be a good idea
before we hop into a match to do just
like go over the different characters
and stuff
and uh get used to them so you can
decide like what you want to play
uh so now we'll just enter into a game
and get started i guess right
oh oh
monkey
wait how do i ah
oh there's there's a cute hamster
that's the wrangling ball oh cute
what would you so like on the on the
left side it's all tanks and then you
have damage and then the support
characters like
yeah if you have any questions about any
of them i can uh
i can let you know what they do
which one is anna that you said do you
like uh she's the blue supporter i found
her
oh yeah
and a lot of aiming involved
i wanna i wanna go for the damage damage
oh
she's so cute with me
she's so cute yeah she's cute
and within the damaged dealers who do
you think would be good for me please
choose a girl
uh
may that you hovered over is pretty
friendly so with her mouse one you get
to freeze people and they turn into a
block of ice temporarily
and then with your right click you can
snipe with these uh
projectile
uh
little icicles that come out and they
shoot and you can head shot people with
them and it does quite a bit of damage
ooh okay i'll give it a try
oh that was nice okay it doesn't even
load
oh i can still change here i want some
in here huh yeah yeah you can change it
as much as you want and uh it's not like
we're in paladin since you've played it
before
uh you're not locked to one character
you can choose whatever character you
want but when you are playing in a game
you are locked to usually one of the
three roles tank damage or support so
you uh yeah you can only switch between
those when you're in a game
okay where are you
i'm outside waiting for you
oh i have to go outside oh i thought
this was like a waiting room
and there would be a countdown no okay i
mean this is just the practice we're not
going to kill you
itself but if you want to try shooting
me
yeah stop running
no please don't oh yeah
[Music]
does she not freeze people now yeah
that's weird
that's weird oh you have to hold it you
have to hold mouse one when you now i
see the replay i have to walk back over
there so hold on give me a second
hold it
yeah continuous
come here amy
where are you a deer
oh i hear you
you're really happy i hear you
hear my step
hey hey i'm on the idle game you're so
heavy oh there you are hello
but you didn't kill me you don't get
eyes you don't get frozen
uh the icicles don't freeze but they do
a lot of damage when you head shot
right here come try freezing me try
freezing me
no no no no oh
yeah
yeah wait did you have to spray it i
heard i think this is tea bagging
really
i think i think i figured it out
maybe i should teach you how to teabag
properly
you know you know and just yesterday in
russ i finally found out what um
360 no scope means
because i did a 180 no scope and i'm
like is this 360 no scope and then the
viewers told me no if anything that
would be 180 and i'm like oh my god so
cool i finally understand i kept on
saying that like without understanding
what it meant
you're really bad
[Music]
mouse one only left mouse click only
hold it i hold it okay ah
and then in a game you would head shot
because they get frozen
so the same thing happens i freeze in
this one
but it's a wide area
when you know it's a big team fight
happening because there are six people
on each team okay
okay
come again
please come again yeah yeah can you can
you get closer to my spawn so i can i
don't have to walk all the way just keep
going okay okay go past the big door
yes yes oh is this it
yeah this is it
i'm gonna
kill you
no
no not if i kill you first
okay well we'll see
are you on your way
hey i think i'm here
i hear your foot's going
don't you want to see the rest of the
map oh yeah i guess so
you're so noisy
oh
[Music]
you look jesus
that's my turret
that's why you told me to come over
okay okay wait wait we should try
another character if you want to try
since you tried to damage character i
mean you could try whatever you want
pretty much i think it's good just to
test out like a few different ones diva
i play i'll get somebody who heals
okay
so i don't have to die oh diva is really
fun uh so with your shift you can fly at
people and it does damage and you can
also go like oh but it's pretty short
you can bump people with that like here
try to fire me wait wait try and fly at
me
yeah
so you you bumped me back and you also
did some damage
wait what's right click
uh your right click is your rockets
they're on a
like a little
meter you should be able to see it when
you shoot them
huh
oh sorry sorry sorry not right click uh
that just uh stops
it project i was like here i'll shoot at
you oh do it
oh
sorry
so yeah it's it stops uh bullets and
anything that's coming let's shoot again
should i guess it
i want to see the difference
okay
okay so it's just a block basically
yeah yeah
but you can block like you know that may
old that you threw earlier
if if you're doing that uh while enemy
made
faults you can like swallow her ultimate
so as you can see like her
diva's regular shooting doesn't really
do a lot of damage true holy [\h__\h] and if
you press e you can do rockets and if
you do them really up close they do a
lot of damage okay try your rock kids
it looks like the drink that she drinks
what was it again not dorito juice she
eats doritos yeah mountain dew
ah
all right so yeah she's she's a good
tank player
but uh she's also really like easy to
kill and hard to
for healers to keep healed up if that
makes sense
she does quite a bit of damage if you
know how to use her
i can't even fly
up like what i can escape
can't catch me
[Music]
oh i'm already so low on health what the
[\h__\h] no
oh so there are health packs throughout
the map you can pick those up
or if you go back into spa players who
play a lot they know where they are
always right there's always a yeah
there's always a big one over here on
this one oh wait go away that's fine
okay i don't need it i'm healing already
all right so i'll kill you so you can
try another character
you should try this oh okay so her
ultimate it does a big explosion in the
area if i wasn't hiding behind something
it would have killed me but a cool thing
you could do with her ultimate
is you can press shift you know how you
can fly
you press shift into the air and then
use your ultimate and it sends her mech
to explode like in the air you can kill
a lot of people like that
just like a big bomb that you send into
the sky
i kill you
okay so once you're down on her
you can uh just shoot regularly
her gun does
quite a bit of damage too yeah you don't
just die i don't just i just get out of
my mac
yeah and so the more damage you do
you can charge up and get your mech back
[Music]
so i have an extra life
but but i have less hp now i guess
yeah yeah
oh i don't have the e attack anymore i
see
and no she only has your gun oh you can
press press b to melee
[Music]
she did damn
the meg yeah you could just kill people
like that too uh all right go jump off
the edge
jump off the edge why would i just so
you can respond
okay
oh nice scenery where are we
think this is in australia well
those are real places supposed to be
real places
yeah yeah most of the maps take place in
real places although yeah this is called
junkertown because it's one of the
characters is australian and his name is
junkrat so
i'm gonna play brigitte now because
someone was begging on their knees for
me to play brigitte okay
yeah she's pretty fun too but she's just
a healer right
yeah she's a healer but she's more of
like a melee healer like she's really
close combat she does quite a bit of
damage
uh and people who pretty much like the
healers are balanced so that if you do
more damage you're gonna do less healing
for your team
but you can still be like a support
character you do some amount of healing
and you also provide shields uh i think
myself okay
uh
it's
i guess you know a healer is kind of
hard to test out one versus one but
uh so
this is okay like uh
chloe yeah
i think if you uh shift with it you can
hit me from far away
well
yeah it's like a whip
oh whoa
wow that does a lot of damage over here
are you just weak yeah
uh wow yeah the healer is so kind of
squishy is what they say
[Music]
oh
cool
yeah it's cool right so it does like a
short stun like if you do it again when
it charges up you'll be able to see so i
can't do anything in that moment
hey so she's she's you're supposed to
use her in close range
yeah because she's she's not gonna do
anything like against the sniper there's
some healers that uh
that do a lot of uh can do quite a bit
of damage from far away but you can't
really do that much how do i heal
uh so you can't really test it right now
but you with e like if you use it on a
teammate it'll give them like a quite a
little bit of health i don't think it's
that much but it's more like a burst
healing and you have to like direct it
at a player specifically and how do i
have to aim well or does it like
automatically no it's one though yeah
it'll it'll auto do it
you see the area around my character
usually like a yellow circle
or no i guess you might not be able to
see it but for me i have an area uh
effect of healing but yours is just you
have to click oh yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
oh your ultimate uh actually i don't
remember chow chow what does the
ultimate do again
maybe he'll probably like rally
heels per attack that she hits okay oh
what are these these normal attacks heal
my teammates
i don't know if it heals your teammates
it might heal you though oh
both is a area yeah it's a aoe heel area
of effect oh stanford
oh move faster and provide armor to
nearby allies
oh it's not actually healing yeah
oh yeah it's just yeah yeah
you can't really tell right now yeah
enemies with your flail heals nearby
allies that's my passive attack
yeah
okay so it heals everybody who's close
to me
wait why am i being healed this is me
healing myself
oh so you see on your health bar how you
have like the yellow part that's the
shield
so you give people shield but if they
are low on health it does heals instead
but if they aren't low on health then
you provide them with like extra shield
in their bar
oh i think cool remember all right we
should try another character
okay
maybe one or two more and then we'll try
to play real games okay
there's a tracer tattoo
okay yeah yeah try chase's turn orange
and she has a cute butt just like me
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
what is she she's really
damaged
yeah there she is yeah damage so with
the tracer she's pretty fast and you can
shift forward you have three shifts and
they reload after a certain amount of
time
i actually did that in the tutorial
and if you jump off the edge
you can see what i'm talking about you
could jump off the edge and rewind and
you'll go back
uh like a few a few steps oh my god it
worked it works
nice save that you got to jump off and
press e
yeah yeah you only shifted back right
yeah i guess so
what
yeah and you recover health so if you're
it's like she's going back in time
temporarily so watch it i'll wait until
it loads again
all right so i'm going to do some damage
to you
all right no no press e
so now you see how your health is bad
what do that again shoot me
i think you have to wait for it to kill
me here come get healing over here
[Laughter]
[Music]
it didn't rewind
enough
wait so so right click goes
right click and shift is basically yeah
they're the same they're the same
it's just they're two different buttons
for the same ability
ocean doesn't have as many skills as uh
borgeet
yeah because she has a lot of passives
but tracer's just like very
straightforward oh
for about a powerful sticky explosive
okay interesting oh yeah so you can try
sticking it to me i'm going to die but
we're actually here do it now if you
have it
i'm still at 60
so she throws it and you just if you're
close to somebody like this close it'll
get stuck to them if you're aiming at
them
but uh otherwise it just lands on the
ground okay she can still do damage but
it's not stuck to them
santa tracer is like a heavy aim
character
oh you have to aim pretty well
you're so fast
yeah it's because this character can
switch between healing and the speed ah
oh god i'm getting dizzy
oh my god yeah tracer's she's super
fast-paced like you pretty much has
tracer you're just like running around
and zooming and
going very fast
okay oh no i just killed myself from
that how is that possible
because it's when it's a bomb
i shouldn't do damage to myself
that's what pretty much every ability
that's like that does damage to
yourselves you have to be careful
it doesn't damage your teammates though
it only damages you if you mess up okay
i'm gonna try one more who should i try
what do you recommend
who do i recommend yeah
uh well you haven't tried well let's see
you tried two damage characters and one
support you should try another tank why
don't you try the hamster since you
thought it was cute
okay
hamster time baby
crazy hamster oh god the hands almost
look like human hands
if you press shift on him you can roll
indefinitely as a ball oh
that is awesome
that reminds me he has
like a spiderman ability he can grapple
with a hook and you can fly around like
a like a wrecking ball
what would that be
[Music]
a shift
i'm sorry right click right click
i need to get out of the ball okay wait
wait
no you can do a while in ball form yeah
you can swing around you just have to
connect and now you can swing
swing
swag especially if you do it like at a
higher like if you shoot up here at this
thing yeah
you have to hold it i think
okay
one more time
what for to be a wrecking ball again yes
if you're doing it in the middle of like
a big team fight you'll uh you'll hit
the enemy team and it kind of like
pushes them kind of like how diva you
know when she flies she does a little
bump it's like the same thing oh that's
that seems hard to
get like a good feeling for
yeah you can also launch yourself into
the air if you have momentum so if
you're going really fast
this might be a good place to do it if
you're rolling through here and you
shoot up
sorry
that's okay roll here and shoot up okay
yeah at the like roll really fast get a
running start and then shoot up at the
roof and you'll be able to like swing up
how would i shoot up
oh oh you mean a shoot with the the
spiderman skill yeah
that's just
that's just the
yeah
that's just me having fun enjoying
myself let me see how that yeah
people use it as their advantage like in
a fight because uh obviously there's a
respawn time so you want to get to a
fight faster people use it for momentum
like that
like right now i'm using momentum to
escape
on the walls and i get a speed boost
mm-hmm and what else does this dude have
whoopsie
oh
slam into the ground below that down
below to damage
and launch enemies upward
yeah so that that swinging ability if
you swing up and then you use that smash
ability it's like a ground pound it does
quite a bit of damage
but it's kind of difficult to get a hang
of
you could try here i'll stand over here
i'm stupid what what you can do it
through here
so uh hook onto the bridge and swing up
and i'll stand here
you can slam me
slam me slam me kiara
okay
oh [\h__\h] i'm i'm gonna keep on forgetting
roll back try again and but am i
supposed to do the e i'm not i don't
understand what the e does
uh ground pound isn't it the ground
pound chat it just doesn't really
oh it only happens when you're in the
air so you have to roll
and then press e and then slam oh eat a
shield eat a shield oh you do slam chat
control
control control
ah okay you got to swing down them in
the air okay
okay
that's not in the manual
[Music]
they landed right next to you but that's
the the hitbox yeah you almost killed me
it really didn't do damage
yeah yeah i'm like at 31 then you yeah
you turn into normal form and shoot nice
all right wait i want to try
i'm 100 now
so the ultimate uh you just launch a lot
of little tiny balls in one area and
they explode when people get near them
so it's pretty good for like people say
crowd control when there's a lot of
people in the way you want to get rid of
them
where are you
i'll dance
oh no
and this squeak was good wow that was
that was strong damage
oh i can't teabag you as a hamster
no i guess not no crouching
okay
i think you're ready for a game on a 6v6
i'm not sure which which one i
feel the most comfortable with
okay if you want to try more out of mind
um
i want to try out ash
okay
pretty cowboy gal
yeah wait she sounds like callie
i could hear that yes i mean
not the voice really just the accents
that she uses
yeah yeah okay what do we have let me
look at f1
the viper
semi-automatic rifle halt of zoom in
increasing damage but and accuracy but
slow rate of fire oh
bob deploy bob he charges forward and
knocks enemies into the air
oh
then attacks with his arm cannons and
coach gun
last enemies in front of you and knock
yourself backwards
uh-huh
dynamite throwing explosive okay
well first of all let's see how far that
goes okay
you can throw it up because it'll curve
off
look careful
so what you can do also with the
explosive it's pretty difficult but if
you throw it you can shoot it mid-air
and it'll explode otherwise it's on a
timer
oh people can get away pretty easily
this is like so i'm sniping you
yeah yeah so when you do it like that
the fire rate's slower but if you hit
fire so you can shoot without zooming in
you can spam it really a lot
yeah but obviously it's less accurate
oh it's pretty slow
what is this attack
what is this one let me see again ah so
you bring out a shotgun and you have a
jump back
yeah yeah knock yourself backwards okay
okay i'll kill ya
wow
yes it does damage and uh
i kind of like her
yeah she's pretty difficult like i don't
really like playing her because you have
to focus uh on aiming a lot and
sometimes overwatch is just nice to turn
off your brain
and just
shoots other stuff
i see it limits me
just aim for the chest aim for the chest
nice
yeah
[Applause]
no one will stay in the same spot for
that long for me
you'd be surprised some people are bots
oh
i heard that team fortress 2 was full of
bots and that's why we shouldn't play it
uh yeah sometimes
but you you'll be in my team and you'll
protect me right amen
yeah yeah
maybe we should try a character that uh
maybe chat wants to recommend you maybe
if you guys chat today
hold on let me see
oh i might be able to switch teams
reinhardt winston
fast all right
blaze mercy and i'm gonna play pharah
okay
so this is a pretty popular combination
because they can both fly oh
where's that pretty lady now i'm on your
team
so i'm gonna fly up into the air and
you're gonna look at me and press shift
and if you hold space you can hover so
you can last longer
oh
[Music]
and now if you press mouse 1 while
looking at me it'll connect
usually you have to hold it but there's
a setting where you can put it on toggle
it's much easier on your finger
and if you press right click instead
you'll do damage boost so now when i
shoot stuff i'll do more damage so it's
really popular combination because i'll
fly and shoot people then you can fly
around
that's cute
yeah
ah should we do that that's so titty
yeah we could try
and then you'll scream at me like
[\h__\h] heal more [\h__\h]
no no that would be that
probably of the other people would be
yelling at you since you're pocketing me
like where's our heels
yeah inside we have traffic today's my
first day at work man
okay can i heal myself too
ah no i don't think so no she doesn't
have any self-heal
okay what's um i think she might over
time i think she might generate heels
maybe passive heal yeah yeah you got a
passive heel ah
it's pretty slow though so it's not all
i can resurrect
a dead teammate uh yeah so
if you resurrect you can only resurrect
within a certain amount of time and then
it expires
oh
gain the ability to fly abilities are
enhanced cool automatic weapon
clearing the area okay
so i cannot do any damage uh you can
scroll and pull out your gun
yeah her gun is pretty much the same one
that diva has i think it does quite a
bit of damage i like using it
so you can you could fly around and just
shoot people if you wanted to
wait
oh can i only fly when i have uh yeah so
even on the ground you can shift to
people so look at me and press shift
i've got you
oh and one thing with mercy is pretty
popular is you press shift towards
somebody and then you
like slingshot off of them by holding
space and yeah see how you went further
oh
it's really useful in a fight especially
when somebody's attacking you and you're
trying to get away you can fly to your
teammate
oh so
oh the flying the l shift was only
possible because i was looking at you
yeah yeah
so now i'm in the air so you can fly
towards and hold space and you'll cover
for a little bit
[Music]
where does it hurt
why does it hurt do you need healing
heal me cara please please i'm trying
but there's nothing to heal you're
already perfect the way you are
okay another thing you can do oh so her
ultimate you just get to fly around like
as much as you want for a certain amount
of time wait which button people hold
that l shift to or uh you'll just be
automatically flying around so you could
just like press space and float up and
uh
yeah i guess you'll have to wait until
your
ultimate's ready
i'll do some damage to myself please
heal me
she does a lot of peeling she's like
the strongest healer i would say she
also doesn't really do any damage
hi i like this duo
yeah best friends forever duo
it's kind of hard to play pharah
sometimes so
we can try like some games with it but
if there's like a really good sniper
is kind of hard
okay okay then i i will try out mercy
and that other character that i just
played before
ash oh yeah yeah yeah yeah okay let's do
that
oh wait can i request a character for
you to try yeah
okay i'll go back this character is uh
the character from this map junkrat
oh you want me to play junkrat
i don't know why i feel like you'd be
pretty good at junkrat here i'm gonna
switch teams again so you can do some
damage to me okay who is jungkook
someone that looks like a are you he's a
damaged character
[Music]
okay he looks like he is um ready to
perform in the cat's musical on stage
so if you're walking forward with him
and you
try your shift it's actually like a
a bomb with a really short timer so you
can launch yourself up in the air when
you trigger it with right click
oh oh so but this bump doesn't do damage
to myself interesting no no
but your your i think mouse one does do
damage so
that you can spam that one wait don't
kill me
i have a normal shooting too
high
uh
nope just bombs
so if i get hold on the heel before i go
into your trap
it's just bombs
just bombs
but you can throw like your left shift
and you can damage people with that
because it goes pretty far
you just spam with it pretty
much okay
seems easy enough i'm coming back so i
can show you
yeah he's really fun to play you just
launch stuff over walls or like into
crowds i think my bear trap is a little
bit too obvious
yeah
i mean it actually for you
it looks obvious but for i think the
enemy team it like sinks into the ground
a little bit oh okay
so this barrier that this character i'm
playing has absorbs damage and then
turns it into like more power for my
my abilities
if you're playing junkrat against this
lady
she'll just absorb all of the shock
guys i got you
[Music]
okay i think we're ready for real game
right oh god okay i hope they don't hate
me and then
try to find me irl and kill me there
because i was i wasn't too good at the
game
it'll be fine what the heck
there's a game
there's a game in the game browser
because there's custom games and one of
them was naked anime girls which i've
never seen that before but
okay
i'll do my best
[Music]
i don't so uh when you play a game mode
like i said before you're
you're uh
what's the word i'm looking for you're
like trapped in one
roll so you have to pick what you would
rather be so i usually just put flex
because i don't mind being healer or
tank or damage but it's up to you i'll
i'll do
i'll try damage now
i'm nervous i'm so nervous
[Music]
to be easy
are we just doing like a versus game we
don't have to like hold a base or
anything
um
it depends what map we get so each map
has a different uh mode it's either
payload or capture point okay so we'll
see
okay we'll see okay
[Music]
thanks guys you guys are so sweet
please be nice to me overwatch people
fps players are scary
yeah well so we'll go into a game while
we're searching
so this is just
a quick
wait is this quick no okay so this is
just start to test some other characters
if you want i'll do i'll do ash now okay
and i'll be [\h__\h] at it my business
right okay what was the second okay and
then bomb and then
okay
wait oh are there other people here
already are we already fighting yeah oh
uh we're going against real people this
is just a death match so
it's just like it's something to do
while you wait to get into a
yeah this is just to practice different
characters if you want to try something
new or just this is just to get kills
there's no game mode it's just
free-for-all
good warm-up you know okay
[Music]
i'm right next to you oh i tried to
block a bullet for you sorry avenge me
avenge me on me
but then when does the real game ah
eh when does the real game start letting
that stand if this is just practice what
i mean
oh uh sorry you see that the timer at
the top it says time to lapse so we're
just waiting to get into a game
okay
you could try lucio and skate around uh
he's really fun you can get it hang for
her an idea of how he skates cool lucy
yeah yeah he's green
yeah he's frog
no
no no no no
no no
time to change things up time to change
things here
i have zero wait what does the number
six mean is that my ranking and i have
zero kills
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's easier to get kills when you're in
like a team match because then uh other
other people you know get in the way and
they help you get killed and stuff but
this is just solo so
good practice good practice
[Music]
at least i threw the dynamite and i
think that did some damage
oh nice
and believe you'll get a kill oh wait
the the cryptics person is playing the
same character oh i should have got a
different skin
oh no no
no no no no
no no no no no no maybe i should turn on
voice jet so they would be nicer to me
if they hear how i'm panicking they
probably
probably just cursing you or something
and i'll say [\h__\h] you
you little [\h__\h] oh yeah i get toxic here
fire
someone there
that's cool i was already
don't fart into the room
yeah bottled fire is what it is
did you use your ultimate oh you almost
have it
[Music]
yes your ultimate you want to put it in
like a big place where it'll get it
that'll hit a lot of people okay
maybe i should play like a sniper that i
feel like that would be like more
a calm
situation sniper oh yes i can stay in
the distance and and slowly
look for my target and
hopefully no one will find me
does this gun even reach the targets
from this distance
it does does it just it takes longer
it's not like um
there's there's a few different terms
that people use in this game like hit
scan or projectile what that means is
that hit scan doesn't his scan doesn't
take like much of any time at all to
reach
okay you know it's destination but
projectile has airtime
like for ashes when she's using uh iron
sights that it's hit scan and then
no the other way around
how does it work i forgot i know what
hit scan means
[Music]
forget everything you know
oh man they need to
like assign me to matches where only
newcomers are they don't really have
anything like that do they like some
system that sends that sees like oh how
many games has this person played or so
you i think usually for like queuing
they do try to
cue you with new people too
but uh
yeah it's taking a while to get into a
game because usually if you try to queue
as damage only
it takes a long time because everybody
wants to play damage nobody wants to
play support or tanks
because there's so many people
yeah are we starting our match soon or
what
uh hopefully nothing wrong we just have
to wait to try to get into a game got my
ulti ready
nice yeah you should do it somewhere out
in the open
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
that was not effective
is that a sniper character the dude with
the boat yeah yeah
yeah inna is pretty good hanzo his
name's hanzo and
uh yeah he's got a bow his abilities are
pretty fun to be honest he also has this
uh that was not scatter shot which is
still scatter shot oh no
yeah i don't remember tell me
hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
whoa hmm how do i do that do i just
stand on it
oh
hello friends
being friend please family friendly
friendly that's me it's me you're not
friendly
give me one kill please i am missing
this i only have fun
come on you can do this
oh [\h__\h] i got me too
please i need one
so it's not so embarrassing
[Music]
was gonna kill that person
don't change things up eh reload button
there's a reload button doesn't reload
automatically uh you can reload before
but it does reload automatically i steal
the kill i stole a kill probably
well there's so much going on look oh
we're in a game wearing games oh i got
kicked out though
yeah yeah it's okay we're joining a new
game yeah i thought i got
not chosen because i wasn't good enough
[Music]
oh yeah uh
oh i'm also damaged that's weird
uh i feel like i was really bad at ash
maybe you could play junkrat or may if
you want i don't mean but i already
forgot how to play her i think
okay
a ghost
ready for battle
yeah
now we have people that heal you and
people that will protect you okay
so this big guy with the hammer at the
front um
did you see him he's got a big shield
you want to try to stay behind it
but it does run out of health but he'll
say a voiceline he's like my shield's
running low or something so you got to
hide after that my my l shift was just a
big
aoe freeze right
uh that's your ultimate so your left
shift is like a continuous freeze and if
you freeze them for long enough they
turn into a icicle and you can headshot
them with right clicks
okay
oh wait what the [\h__\h] i never tried that
out oh oh sorry sorry your left shift is
an ice block and uh you regen health the
longer you stay in it ah
so if you if you're about to die just
press left [\h__\h] sorry uh
mouse one is your freeze okay
[Music]
someone there
shoot aimlessly at anything
where's the tank where did he go
oh our tank he's uh he's up top there's
like a little uh corridor that we're in
right now or we're on the balcony we're
going on to the point sort of
uh on the right side
oh i could still change hero in between
huh yes you can again
no no i need to get used to this oh my
god
[Music]
music playing in my brain
okay i'm here now i'm like close to you
oh god
yeah you want to wait for your tank
because uh he can help block a lot of
damage so he's here now so we'll follow
behind him
finally
where were you tank so if you see their
healer she's on the left side you always
want to go for their healers because
obviously they're keeping the rest of
the team up and then
okay so that's junkrat's ultimate you
want to try to just spread out
okay you can shoot at his tire if you
see it it's like a big traveling bomb
but i think somebody else got it right
now i got killed where were you when
kiana was killed
hold left click okay
i hope yeah so mace she doesn't really
have a long range um
unless you're using right click
so you can shoot pretty far
someone left the game and the voice chat
is it because
they were so pissed
yeah they probably just got disconnected
plus somebody else can join mid game
because we're in quick play right now
okay
there's somebody already joined
i'm hiding
behind the big boss protect
oh
i gained an orb of harmony what is that
uh oh that's our our healer's um ability
it uh gives you healing passive healing
[Music]
try to get the point
i'm really bad at this
it's okay it's okay you could try uh if
you want to try a different character if
you want
oh you could keep it because you almost
have her ultimate 60
yes i'll keep it
what was he again
uh there's so many things to remember
yeah that's a lot to get a hang of
you get it
[Music]
okay one of their damage is down
oh no we both got caught in that
it feels like i couldn't move anymore
yeah so that's her ultimate it's a
little gravity ball and it just pulls
people in and then oh they just shoot at
you
[Music]
hey skilled pro gamers i can't tell
besides amen who's obviously
very skilled
you're playing overwatch a lot down
there
uh i used to play a lot but
not in a while
and i don't see the enemies where are
they oh there uh there's a pharah up in
the left side he's flying but she got no
mirrors to try by clicking her
right clicking okay
yeah so it's like a sniper pretty much
we got the points which means we get to
push the payload now
[Music]
push and push this seems familiar i know
that from paladins oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
futuristic car in the world of warcraft
world kind of weird but okay
yeah well this is just a blizzard world
so it's like their entertainment or
their uh what is it called
theme park yeah it's like a theme park
nice i wish that existed in reality
yeah i bet they wish they did too
[Music]
okay sorry guys it's too much for my
brain
it's a lot it's a lot to take in yeah
there's so much things happening why did
i spawn here
i killed so much oh
nice
every time uh we push the payload to a
new point we get a
new spawn area
someone's shooting
all my ulti is ready but um
it'll be good to use it during a team
fight when there's like a lot of people
or when we're yeah you'll see
[Music]
they're coming out of spawn they were
still spawning so now we're gonna go
into the team fight probably pretty soon
so we get to oh shoot no all right when
we all come back when we all come back
did we all get killed
uh yes
beautiful at least it's not only me wait
for me i'll wait for me
oh what is that paris ulti classic
blanket
she's really easy to kill in that mode
if you're not in her line of fire but
she like uh snuck up on us
that [\h__\h]
60 seconds
oh we have
pretty mercy oh
i want to be a healer i feel like
sniper or healing may be better choice
for me
guys
oh now would be good to use their old
after they oh
after oh be careful behind okay that
would be a good time now because i
already did it i i froze some enemies
okay nice
i bet it was helpful there's a pharaoh
behind oh mercy
it's okay we still have two minutes to
try to get the point go go go go oh
[Music]
so i heard overwatch 2 is coming out but
what what's gonna be different
uh well instead of six v6 it's five v5
oh
that's it and that's the only thing
nah they changed like some of the
characters they added there's a new
character
and
yeah they just pretty much like
redid some of the characters abilities
and stuff and how they work
[Applause]
[Music]
a 1.5 an expansion pack all yeah yeah
and they're gonna make it free to play
but that's pretty nice too bad i just
paid 40 bucks for it
maybe we should watch two years like
yeah maybe we should have done it in in
october this collaboration after
overwatch two comes out who's around
here damn boy
she was just hiding and waiting camping
here's her ultimate
oh man i only have 60 seconds
[Music]
um
no i'm just so [\h__\h]
it's your first game it's your first
game it's understandable
next match i'm gonna play something else
[Music]
zarya she knew who she was dealing with
she wouldn't have dared
to hurt these idols
what the [\h__\h] is that it looks like some
kind of
eh
pokemon
no the golden
whatever
oh the tank
the paint surprise
yeah it's so it's pretty good though we
did pretty good for a first first match
please don't show me a list play of the
game wow yeah so this is a
a good idea of what his alt does oh
that's tired he just explodes
well 15 player kill streak
holy macaroni
he was on the roll
he can be pretty strong i will leave and
then uh now we'll go again and now you
can re-pick your role
okay i'll go support
maybe people won't notice how [\h__\h] i am
if i support
mm-hmm
jean-claude is the most aimed duco
friendly
oh okay i will give junkrat a try to
then later on
yeah yeah he's pretty good for damage
home
i'll i'll try mercy
yeah yeah it's just she's good a lot of
the healing characters like the someone
of the ones that you didn't try they do
quite a bit of damage as well as i don't
want to do damage i'm not made for doing
damage
it's understandable understandable
you want to do death match again while
we wait although i think this one's
probably a pretty short cue
oh why you think so
ah there we go
uh because you're not queuing is only
damaged because if you put only damage
then it takes a long time to find a spot
okay mercy let's go oh no someone else
is doing mercy
should i do something else done
yeah yeah you could try uh lucio if you
want or you could try
uh your tab bridgette oh god ah she was
the one with the flail right okay okay
i'll try
i hope i don't disappoint
what was that okay so this close flail
and then distance flail and then shield
and yeah and shield badge
shield bash was uh however
i haven't got shield up maybe i don't
remember what
oh wow right click and then left click
i've seen
it
oh but it takes a while what are you
getting at
two and a half
oops
so that's good if you want to stun
somebody especially because like what
happens a lot of time in overwatch games
is people flank they come from behind to
try to kill the healers
so you want to protect our mercy pretty
much she's squishy i protect mercy
yeah well she better get behind my
shield then
oh wait what
what don't worry it's a sniper
what
the door opens and they sniper
yeah
what the [\h__\h] how did they even see her
i don't see anyone how did they get
there that's [\h__\h]
wait ah she's just she stands up top
four where are the enemies oh here oh
god oh god
oh
but i think i knocked someone out
it's really satisfying to like uh
snipe somebody with your long range
flail
you can kill people if they have low
speed they're trying to run away
okay snapper killed me but i got pretty
far without dying let's go much better
you're actually getting work done yeah
yeah yeah it felt different it felt
definitely different
the spamming is working
where's everybody everybody died uh yeah
i definitely died
i'm on my way um i'm here to save the
day once again
let's go
nice triple kill let's go
okay you did a triple kill
yes
hey yo what's up
dad i just helped
where are the people
uh hanzo's up top on the right oh you'll
see them there's little
entrance to me
oh
where do the [\h__\h] stones come from
what the hell
his ability raises you up into the air
and then slams you down that was very
dramatic i liked that one that was
beautiful what
i was resurrected and eliminated
yeah mercy good try mercy good try i
appreciate the effort
ready for more
let's go
yo that was out of this world
dragging
like a dragon
thank you
oh i have my ulti ready where was ulti
again don't have time to move uh so it's
like good for when we're about to push
into a fight like uh now would be a good
time to use it
really rally let's go rally
yeah she's pretty tanky
[Music]
oh a tickle a little tickle in my
armpits
it's
this is my card
oh once again amen and chihuahua
bringing cars
to other places
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] what are you
who are you
nervous
nerf this oh i heard that before
yeah
famous phrases i need healing that's
from this game ryan
yeah oh not really tsu kind of did it
first oh [\h__\h] behind me grandma
where are the people
was i shot in my back
probably yeah it's good to wait for your
team to be back so that you can uh
use them as a meat shield pretty much
yes okay
fresh meat
nice but mercy
take this
she just quickly disappears as if our
thing didn't mean anything to her
died
looks like the same thing that diva is
using
all right we got one minute try to get
it
oh i'm gonna come back
i guess i'll switch but they're pretty
good
but you need an extra tank better tank
there's somebody behind who's gonna alt
so watch out
folder behind okay behind
yeah oh [\h__\h] what [\h__\h]
oh how did you know
oh
i hear him somewhere here it is
triple kill
oh baby
yeah as soon as you get your ultimate if
you're still alive you gotta use it
now we just have to stay in the car and
try to get it as far as we can hopefully
to the end
careful hanzo's a top
do whatever he wants
yeah we're dead it's okay good try good
try
maybe our other tank was throwing
because they wanted diva nice block
clutch shield defeat but yeah
better than before
yeah second game second game it doesn't
count
oh whoa
endorsement
that sounds like good teammate
what
i got an endorsement from you probably
right no no it wasn't for me it's
somebody else on the team
[Music]
mvp
hey
all right if we just wait in the queue
it'll put us in the same you're okay
with playing healer then
or did i have how are my stats guys
2000 healing done career average is 2500
cubia pesos right this doesn't mean it's
your first killer game
oh
didn't look so bad to me
love green colors love green numbers no
no
no red numbers
i think you did pretty good a second
time
playing a game
i got goal game already have time
game game oh nice so fast
i don't like this map so much
oh
select snowy
now you can play mercy if you want to
try oh okay okay
i didn't even get a chance to like
re-choose my category but
okay yeah if you wanted to re-choose uh
we could
next time we're on the side are we are
we the dream team are we doing the
tattoo thing
no no because i'm also a healer okay ah
true okay
uh
i can go towards someone and then i can
float okay
and then uh i can connect to heel with
left and i can
ride for storm and damage but like i i
don't even so far i haven't like looked
at people's hp at all like
i kind of need an eye for it because
people's names are small and it's hard
to see it
yeah you get used to it how do i know
who to heal
everybody's like
i'm so panicky
usually you can see like their little
health bar and you can even see it
through walls
um as a healer sometimes or they look
green they'll look like a different
color like they need healing where's the
tank by the way the one on the horse
body or
yeah the one in the horse body that
looks like a digimon and then the big
pig guy's name's roadhog
oh [\h__\h] she died
you can resume
[Laughter]
yeah they have a bastion which is a
really campy character he just turns
into like a little turret and ames you
can't even move in that form
i mean don't die
how do i resurrect e
oh can i move while i'm resurrecting
yeah you can move around a little bit
just not too far i think
the iron mccree this guy oh sorry this
said jesse
his name uh he's very
very squishy so you gotta keep healing a
lot probably
who just seeked
yeah this guy with the cowboy hat oh
yeah okay
yeah i've been healing cassidy sorry my
brain i'm scared to go any further
there's like so many people shooting
scared
two parts of you
big baby big fat babies
okay i'm the healing on my healing yes
this dude just healed us so yeah yeah
good good i have to just hide hide hide
sebastian he does like a huge amount of
burst damage i'm so sorry can i revive
you oh no i can't
why can't i not on it
oh there's a cool down
or there's if you don't get it in time
where does it happen potential best
healer
how bad am i
who's on there mccree was just or sorry
cassidy was just asking for more healing
yeah oh okay
this dude
no this squishy guy yeah yeah yeah
that's what she got yes i'll get squishy
i don't know we're not gonna be able to
get past this point i think because uh
we have two two uh
hit scan people but
we can't get past the shield to kill
bastion
maybe we'll get some ultimates going
uh swisher guys squish you guys squishy
guys squishy guy
squishy guy yeah he gets well
i feel like we're only four people where
are the uh where are the other
achievements
um doing nothing dude
maybe i'll play something else to help
push
i'll keep you alive don't worry 60
seconds okay if a roadhog has his
ultimate then i can use mine with his
ultimate trace is coming to town
your finger hurts nice and heels dude i
haven't seen him in a while no i'm not
fine
i got hooked she's rising now
sanest overwatch playing me
doing great with the healing yeah
oh [\h__\h] yeah do you have your ultimate
i'm gonna send you in to get some kills
it's like a lost cause almost out of
time
all right
go shoot people go shoot people use your
gun go to people go shoot people
[Laughter]
what
wait
was i on the right gun no i was
i felt like i was on the right gun
that's okay it's okay so usually like if
you play um competitive in this game you
would switch sides but because this is
quick play
we already lost the game but if it was
competitive then we would play defense
instead
and try to win
okay play of the game
resistance spider bongo that does damage
to everybody on your team or like uh
damage boost like just what your right
click does
she's got a little gravity thingy to
pull people in
yeah she's got a little machine gun who
was the
the tank
oh it's too late
where is it
what's the tank well
what character our tanks or their tanks
our tank
our tank was a roadhog and an odisha but
we just would like die instantly because
of the bastion what was that the name of
the person
oh
i don't know why the yellow one the
fifth one okay
what are you gonna do i gave him an
endorsement
oh nice be nice
okay
and now you can change if you want you
must or you can put flex so
you get whatever
uh what should i do
with you i'll do flex i guess
you can always try a new character you
don't have to do something that you're
you kind of know okay
i don't think it's fair to judge the
tanks there probably is new yeah it's me
but i think they were doing fine but
what do i know
oh our tanks
oh yeah the previous tank
yeah our tanks are doing okay they
couldn't really do any damage like
enough damage to get the shield down and
kill the bastion
uh so i blame it on our dps as always
you always blame it on the damaged
people
okay
um
shield girl what is your best self bring
it
yeah yeah yeah yeah i mean it was a lot
of spamming um like left clicking right
click left right
shift shift oh sorry to impress ready oh
okay i was just
thinking thinking hard about yeah yeah
yeah how to look cool
okay
how do you feel about the game so far
get
some
nice
stressful i feel like
paladins was a bit easier
for some reason don't know why
but maybe that's just maybe i'm just
imagining it
it's it does well done i think my mic
has been doing more buzzing sound oh
yeah it does feel easier um like with
hitboxes i think they're more
a little more generous sometimes
oh i'm a tank oh no i'm i was bad at
every tank
uh
oh
no what is an easy tank
i was so shitty at them
that's fine no no i suck at the hamster
okay zarya is usually what people use to
pair up with the shield guy with his
name's reinhardt and uh our other
teammate already picked him okay
so you could try that how do i
how do i do a good job
okay so when you're about to take damage
or are already in the middle of taking
damage you press shift and you get a
shield actually she's not very
friendly we should play diva i think
yeah diva would be good for this map oh
no can i still change oh okay yeah yeah
yeah you can still change okay i just
think zarya's
kind of like a more advanced stuff yeah
okay well uh at least yeah
steve i didn't have much
like
different buttons to push
yeah yeah it was elsa
oh god oh god oh god oh god oh god why
did i why did i do that why did i do
that
oh we're attacking something what it
died
you can push people off if you boop them
with like your fly
you can oh yeah right okay
shoot them off the map if you wanted to
try it just don't fall
capturing capturing
oh baby yeah so this is control point so
we have to get three of these to win
oh there's somebody behind she's
shooting rockets so you can use that uh
little
projectile thing someone behind i didn't
see anyone she's shooting rockets she's
flying around
[\h__\h]
get her get her where did she go
all right push too far and he died so we
got to be careful because they're going
to push on points
we just stay in here in that room
uh yeah we're gonna die we'll we'll push
it again probably from the front
stay on it as long as you can okay
yay
but was not so bad i survived for a long
time oh wait i'm still wait what's
happening oh i'm just off my robot
that's what i was dead
[Music]
i forgot that
diva comes with two lives
yeah yeah
all right so they finally got the point
but we got it to 75 so that's pretty
good yay
oh
wow oh my auntie is ready oh yeah what
does my ulti do again
it's a big bomb so you want to send it
onto site you can do fly and then use
your ultimate midair and it'll send the
bomb okay like it'll keep the momentum
up
uh fly and then alt so you can send it
in or you can just do it where you're
standing you don't have to do it like
that
right
yeah you gotta kill your pillow
we got the point back nice
there's somebody coming in from the
front
oh
just charge up your old as soon as you
can have another neck
you leave the mech okay
oh then i'm gonna go help these guys
i'm alone i think oh no i haven't fell
asleep oh no
oh no
it's okay they're coming they're coming
and your teammates are here so yeah just
stay on the point as long as possible so
we get it to 100 percent
oh dragon kills me
you were live for a long time though
someone guessed that anna
what i'm not doing
anna
re-engaging
i'm doing quite good really
ah
oh we got it we got it nice they got off
the points even though they were here
why am i so slow
motion
oh ah
the round ended oh
so it's uh best of three finally not the
loser but okay okay let's go let's go
let's go let's go
let's go again wait to get into the
fight i got uh better at diva
because they were like
crowded in like one spot most of the
time so it was easy to like
hit some people a little bit
yeah yeah not so difficult because like
when i was trying to hit you
yeah when there's when they're all
grouped up it's much easier because the
spread on diva's guns they're pretty
wide i am
what
round
where are we going this way okay
let's go
oh that dude has a really original name
i kill you wow so intimidating
my map is really tall so you can um fly
up and stuff like that there's a little
platform somebody behind on your healers
[Music]
hit me
like a
[Music]
oh
oh really low nice oh
wait somebody
ah
all right let's get it back to us but
now i have uh my ulti ready
we got the point this time okay
yeah i was tanking good
i think i'm supposed to
i'm on my way
i'm coming
wait is there friendly fire in this game
no okay good i killed someone
yeah i kept the point up for a little
bit just try to get on the point stay on
the point as long as you can
uh because the percentage goes up even
if uh oh nice crying
[Music]
oh yeah your rockets are really powerful
so with your rockets you definitely want
to try to go for the head because you
can kill somebody like squishy really
easily usually what i do with divas i
fly and use the rockets at their head at
the same time
[Laughter]
almost 60 percent
[Music]
yeah don't go in until everybody else is
there okay okay okay i follow you
okay you're okay
is that nice a little taxi service oh
yeah i'm a sexy
oh is this okay can we go in uh not yet
just wait for the ultimate
um
yeah everybody had to back up because
that one guy altered
so usually when you hear like the old
voice lines you just want to back up and
hide pretty much
i just don't see it coming normally
uh is it okay to go in now
yeah yeah yeah go and go
we're trying right now to get the point
usually as diva uh because it's really
easy for her it's easier for her to kill
like squishy people so the
healers i haven't even seen their
healers uh whenever you see them try to
you could always try to go from behind
also if you use this little side
corridor
like right now they're brigitte over
there it's quiet for once
[Music]
yeah so they're pushing in the side here
oh
where did you come from
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
i got some loot box or something too
[Music]
yes this is the enemy team ferret i
think uh uh
would you say now in this game i was
very obviously the noob or just not that
not that obviously i know uh no i think
you did pretty good
i think that obvious yeah
[Music]
bye bye all righty
mama
okay
uh yes you can re-pick your roll now if
you want
i just put everything it's just like
gotcha but usually you get placed into
supported tank every now and again maybe
damage
that's that's okay i'll do whatever oh
yeah if you have a loot box oh we're
already joining the queue right now you
can do it open it after
okay
thank you guys so sweet
yeah really good diva for a third game
thank you i i almost want to play her
again because that felt pretty easy but
i should yeah i gotta do it no one else
it's up to you you could always like
even if you're playing her and you only
played her once you could still try to
get better with her
oh i'm attack again okay then i'll go
for the involve
then i will have to go for diva
but is it the same kind of um
like we have to protect a base again or
do we push something
so now we're doing payload we start off
with payload
so with payload you you get it to each
uh point in the map and usually there's
like three or four and you just have to
push it all the way to the end and then
you win
okay
push
now that i finally know to push e
i will push it more often and i will
just use it on the the fin characters
because the fin characters are usually
the fl like i mean
not
obviously not always but more likely to
be the flimsy ones
yeah yeah
it's good
squishy
i can't wait to get into the fight was
that what happened
yeah it was that's the woman from
voiceline if you hold uh
what is it oh see if you hold c there's
like different emotes and different uh
voice lines
you're my kinda
oh my god
this would be such a disaster if there
was friendly fire
yeah
are there like fps games like this that
uh have friendly fire
um
none that i can think of even with tf2
i mean
there's a team based game but it doesn't
have abilities
uh
mess up your teammates with the
abilities
but it's a much slower paced game so
it's a little different
[Applause]
we got the payload to the point nice
damage
thank you
there's no one to shoot
the hanzo on the left sides be careful
get him get him get him kill him go
ahead and walk it and walk at him
oh everybody's dead
no
i can't rescue right now sorry it's okay
it tried
at least
by by me taking the shot i was able to
protect you um
yeah yeah
my protector
that was on purpose of course i would
rather
die than have you died
yeah
oh yeah baby i killed the tank
i think that was a thing
oh [\h__\h] oh my god went somewhere else
oh everybody's dead
back up faster
nice mindset for a tank right gotta
protect the healer
and a healer should protect the tank to
be honest
what no what
you're the tank you need to tank damage
protect each other
yeah it's teamwork teamwork i heal i
heal
now
[Music]
trying to we can't i think i think when
roadhog gets his ultimate i'll
completely use it recently
get a good ultimate oh your ultimate you
could send it over to that bridge
so
fly and then i'll trigger your okay
come back
[Music]
me and that mondo guy
we keep on
having
these banters it feels like
oh yeah
because yeah it's like tanky tanks
i always go apparently for the tank
because they're just a bigger target
yeah
the good thing is with your fly you
could fly up or behind and pass people
and you could go in the back and try to
take out some of the squishies
sorry i'm a lot of what you're saying is
not entering my brain
that's okay
[Music]
oh he's always coming for me i'm on his
hit list
feel like our uh damage if we got like a
junk wrap we could do
we're down
ew
he'll kill we just need some kills
yeah so you should go after the hanzo
because he's just sitting up there doing
whatever because our damage does not
have a lot of mobility or doomfist just
isn't going after him because he's
scared yeah
that's something you could you could
target him is that the one that was on
the second floor
uh yeah he's on the second floor yeah
okay
yeah there was actually a good play
really what did i do i don't know
no idea what you're talking about well
i'll take this we're all here we can
push in
[Music]
little [\h__\h]
assistance i'm assisting i'm assisting
yeah yeah you're doing it
i'm looking at you doing something
damaged as long as i've survived outside
of florida
here with the hanzo he's trying to snipe
you
how do you know you got ice everywhere
i'm waiting for you
oh thank you thank you
ma'am
almost got to sleep
mundo
okay
hold the button when i'm mini diva okay
i okay i have my um thingy i will do it
correctly now
okay yeah so you're gonna shift to fly
and as you're in the middle of the air
then press q okay do i have to you want
something
yeah you want to aim it like up as
you're flying so that it goes to the
ceiling oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay
keep it uh upwards upwards but not maybe
not nothing dude this dude this [\h__\h]
why am i dying
so just do it up and above the payload
i did it did i i don't know
i i
i think that wasn't quite it
it's all right
nice try nice try
get with them all
it was him this time
yeah
he was just sitting up there nobody was
doing anything about it
[Music]
you don't want to watch i can
exit this is
making me
feel aggressions i've never felt before
in my life
what does it make you want to do hey you
got a card
oh what what what did i do objective
time
yeah that means you're on the payload a
lot that's good
we have to end on a win right yeah we do
uh yeah i'll go to a quick idle meeting
now okay i'll be right back okay
speed idle meeting
[Music]
what should i do next guys
i feel like i got into the groove with
diva more than
um
others because of now i played her like
two or three times
open my loot boxes where are they i
don't know where they are
how to open my loot box
i don't know how what is this
brows while waiting
uh
loot box oh
is there like skins in here open
wow
what
i was saying to ami when she sent me a
friend invite in the game
i was saying that the sound you get when
someone invites you as a friend is so
dramatic like it's a real accomplishment
oh that's a skin night it's a real
accomplishment that you got a friend
invite congratulations
i love it it's like
so motivating oh victory pose i'm
opening loot
boxes okay now i see anything cool
not really i don't know i don't really
know what these things are
i got like one skin but it didn't look
that special
oh
paladins had better skins
fighting words
okay
back okay and
let's look at the hero gallery
sombra waiting for group members to
select a role what alma selected one
didn't we oh i selected mine i think
um brigitte and diva were my better
tries i would say and mercy i don't know
was i decent at mercy
oh
i thought you did pretty good sometimes
just as mercy it's hard to like out heal
so much damage at once
so doesn't it
especially if your team isn't doing
anything back to the other team so
yeah it just wasn't a good composition
i want to play brigitte again
oh did you you could pick only support
if you want uh isn't it too late now
now it is okay
well well if we lose again then we'll
have to play again anyway oh
certain someone is squealing really
happily because they really wanted me to
play her
try out the new skin oh did i get a skin
for her
did i
uh you can equip it where it says select
skin if you do have one ah
oh
well that's perfect i got a skin for
just the perfect character i'm purple
now
cute
it looks good
you look funny
looks like no that dude looks like an
ultra
ultra beast from
pokemon
oh yeah like a mega evolution yeah or or
uh
yu-gi-oh okay no more like digimon yeah
yeah yeah
yeah i could see that
some other weird
weird
it's like a centaur
best interesting yeah she's also oh
she's a beetle skin
i heard someone talking
what didn't i turn it off
actually i'm gonna start testing testing
once for free
oh
turns you i know i thought we turned it
off maybe
maybe you only turned off like one of
them because there's team chat and then
there's magic
oh it did well that's okay
i forgot to play this thing
ow what
stefan erkel that's a very german name
and it sounds like his real name
my moira was talking
i think
but they don't hear me right
healer
okay
boyfriend's not doing any healing
okay now she is
oh we got it what is that what is that
something which was sticking to me
weird purple ball
oh
god of a meatball
that
this is lovely of the world
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
oh
what i killed someone really how did i
feel again
i have percy to heal oh yeah i forgot
about it thank you
thank you thank you keep the payload
keep pushing the payload because we're
pushing ahead okay okay okay getting
some kills
oh they switched to winston because i
was so good
oh
my gosh
just chilling me and glitch here
there's no enemies ahead
yeah we're killing all of them
you're getting all the action watson
yeah share some with me
what a boring night just kidding
i already had a lot of action this is
nice just just going
to the end besides the control point so
we have to push it too
oh finally dead oh me too
that's not good all dead
yeah if you press tab you can see like
uh other people's ultimates and stuff
sometimes it's good to like combine a
few
[Music]
[Laughter]
for each kill you do on me
you think i let that one go
[Music]
oh
what is my ultimate oh yeah
[Music]
um
are you healing kiara oh yes
always always
[Music]
where are you
go home i hear someone else i think
4.5 months usual room
[Laughter]
you sure you want to continue this yeah
all right now we push oh we have two
shield tanks oops
double shield is really good it's a good
strategy
so focused key was so focused
is like one of those games where you
kind of just have to
kill you
my stun
did i do something
yes
i have my rally ready is there still
time yeah three minutes
uh-huh i'm coming stay alive hello okay
uh
we should wait uh because our both of
our tanks are dead we're still coming in
so don't don't push it
oh i'm scared
i'm scared oh they're coming at me oh
thank god
i don't really shoot our damage i kind
of wish we didn't have a smash
damage dealer
use your shield use your shield you can
use your shield in that uh instance if
you have it
yeah oh no
i'll keep on using it
[Music]
oh mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy
all right we're on the payload winston's
trying to go behind
the heels
i think i gave you some healing oh yes
yes oh oh no
the dragon came from me once pushing it
for now
okay we got to kill oh i lost someone
oh i heard some person again back in the
fight
at least he's not talking so much
dang okay
we can't lose this one
we got one minute left
we gotta group up so just wait to push
in because both your hands are down
what happens is we push in too early you
get killed and we get it's called
staggered getting staggered so we spawn
at like different times wow
it's good just to wait
sumimasari
uh unlike me that just went in
uh cause some of our teammates were here
our fair did old but
50 seconds left
so usually like at this point a lot of
people will switch to characters that
move faster
oh is that oh
where are the people
what's going on
who's the other healer of the world
um
oh because we have a moira but frigida
bridget or i don't know
she doesn't really do that much healing
yeah right
yeah it's kind of hard to keep people
healed with it
uh
the other team had a pretty high damage
output
or keep us killed with it i mean
[Music]
yeah they say that to everyone every
time like people are dying
oh
famous paladin's announcer amelia watson
of course gets the play of the game
who else could it ever be yo look at
that action
well not too bad now we have to play
another game
yeah yeah that's fine but did someone
rage quit there at the end now people
just leave when the game's over oh
when they see there's no no choice
but to lose
yeah
okay i will
i will i will no let me tank i will tank
because then i can't choose diva again
and then we have oh yeah higher chances
of winning
you also it might be a good idea to mute
the voice chat you just go in sounds
doesn't do anything weird
yeah i thought i did
real voice chat of team voice chat oh
[\h__\h]
oh
whatever that is okay
did it save danto
okay that should save automatically as
long as you just skip okay
okay so
usually diva and winston
are really good team up so this tank
this big guy you're gonna follow him his
lead
and uh just target whoever he's
targeting pretty much the monkey
yeah the monkey
target
targeting
yeah yeah so follow him and then shoot
at him okay true to what he's shooting
at because they he can jump forward and
you can fly forward okay it's like a
good combo sometimes but you don't have
to it's just a how people play it
mm-hmm okay
what let's do this don't forget to press
it
oh there goes there he goes he uh got
kicked or he just left
so right now we're down on one person
but they're coming back so i'm the only
tank right now
yeah
[Music]
no
okay we have another one another one
same kind of monkey
[Music]
what happened
where's the heels on this map i forgot
huh
oh we got a sniper
we have a sniper nice
you should watch her if you die because
she's got a really shiny skin and
there's a lot of things you can look at
although it's a bad idea to have a
sniper right now i think
at least now i'm back in my makeup
trying to skin
[Music]
steve ring re-engaging
let's go
bye
oh tank hershey's tank
yeah he's always got him
time to read more thanks for the healing
come back winston
oh so there's a sniper okay so with the
sniper it's also good if you try to
target her because i don't think anybody
else can get to where she is if you see
her you can fly at here
go oh we can always try on the next one
mm-hmm
we will win no matter what that's wrong
this is what happens you get
you get caught in the cycle trying to
win yeah oh i can win the next one i
kind of next one really if that cycle
goes on for too long then i would be
worried about my gaming skills
break the cycle
all right game face on ah i hear you
this
cute healer
where are you
you look like a
night elf from world of warcraft
uh no no you've asked me wait did we
talk about this no i'll try it a little
bit once i think i tried it
yeah not really
i feel like we talked about it the last
time we collab really ah because maybe
paladins look so much like the
[\h__\h] foil
all the time
graphic style
[Music]
oh yeah
they're a max down
okay uh we're kind of winning here
[Music]
that's a good thing emma you sound like
it's a bad thing
no no it's a just kind of hard to tell
because we didn't have the point at the
time i was like oh what's happening so
somebody has to stay on the point again
to do it faster
okay they're pushing on the point right
now
my cat's blind
yeah yeah at this point with all the
gates up yeah you're on it okay
i'm scared someone would suddenly snipe
me
uh now you'll be good there you're
pretty tanky anyway so if somebody
doesn't stand through it'll take a
little bit more okay
hi what's up yes
oh
friend
where are we going
i should be happy right now we're just
watching where they're spawning from
okay
whoa
so much going on somebody's behind uh
oh no winston come back okay we lost our
main tank so let's get on the point try
to stay on it as long as possible
because we're gonna fight right now
get out of here
can't catch me can't get no no no no
can't catch me can't catch me
whoa
i did it
fight anyways
[Music]
should be fine uh
we're about to get the point though so
we're gonna fight here because they're
gonna try to go for the point but you
can move forward uh too late okay we're
on here
okay as soon as you get it just try to
use it fly up into the air okay you
don't need it oh it doesn't carry over
like paladins it does
oh nice i got the first or second round
yeah okay one more one more
let's do this
we can do it i believe
now this map is can be kind of difficult
sometimes
looks nice though
yeah we're in busan
oh still
yes hmm
isn't this a place in um
korea yeah busan is in korea
oh
i want to go sometime
oh it's a nice place
[Music]
it does look nice in the overwatch map
let's go
oh i can totally read that it says
kikity everybody what's up
keep on zooming here
fun
[Music]
lucy morbin yes i was moving
should i stay
oh yeah stay for now uh we're coming
back right now i just took anyway i just
i will just shoot
okay uh just stay and try to live as
long as possible okay oh god oh god
three of us suddenly someone
someone got me i think from behind
okay
well well well
if it isn't jeremics once again
what the [\h__\h] is that
just jumps on everyone all right so get
the point to 40 not bad we just have to
retake it after or try to keep on it
yeah stay on it as long as possible okay
yeah
okay group up group up just wait don't
push in yet
it for a monkey
this monkey this monkey is crazy
ah i died dude you guys should wait
until i get back try not to die
don't push in yet all the way okay
i try to get a kill obviously
doing this like you don't die so we
don't lose any more people
[Music]
oh i fell down
all right if you hear that sound
i hear nothing
okay
oh i feel like we need more explosive
damage or something okay we're winning
i'm gonna go tracer with her now we just
have to live it's just so oh it's a 2v2
and our team's low that's got my old
thing and then i did
two versus two hmm
yeah probably tiny more but
my ulti is ready
okay you want to throw it up into the
air
guys you did you did it okay
[Music]
oh who is streaking
the monkey behind you here right now
now we're gonna have the last fight
pretty much
okay
oh i should get back into my robot i
almost didn't notice thanksgiving get
into the robots
okay okay
i'm not scared
oh we lost one
all right we might have another fight
they're gonna catch it right now and
hopefully we can get to it on time
otherwise this is good
we have 10 seconds to get to it pretty
much
they're all capturing it our tree's
going to stay on point but she's just
shooting at a shield
tracer
let me go
let me go let me go
[Music]
our tracer really
i think our genji was what did she do
dead wait
oh yeah she got her stuck no
ah we were so close
yeah we're gonna play again if you want
nice cool match yeah but i'm on
one more one more where's the wind i
need the wind
um give it to us
open it
okay
where did my little box go
there we go open
what did i get what did i get oh
oh
what is that ah a skin for some
cool looking
reinhardt oh
joining game
oopsy
now
[Applause]
so we're defending so i think this is
our first time defending oh uh you know
just keep them off the point pretty much
okay we can win
okay
sounds possible
yeah so this is the second point there's
two points and we have to defend one and
if we lose the first one then we defend
the second one if we lose that one we
lose the game okay
gonna follow where everybody is running
to
yeah usually people defend right here
kind of where this bridge in this little
circle areas with the pillars
that's where we defend and we try to
stop them from coming in these arches
but they can also come in on this right
side over here so this little hallway
oh okay
yeah yeah but we're trying to stop them
from getting to that point okay okay oh
okay
the junkrat spamming from above you can
uh block his bombs with your right click
i think i killed the junkrat
yeah it feels like a tank oh i'm trapped
in tram oh no it's a john grant trap
probably right yeah
i can see
when junkrat does ultimate you're gonna
hear him say something i'll say it when
his old thing i'm gonna look for his
wheel and try to shoot it because you
shoot it before it explodes
oh big sleep
oh lord i killed him again what a weak
rat
careful there's another trap behind you
i shot it don't worry okay
[Music]
mommy
[Applause]
you had no chance there one versus
wanting that tank
that has gotten so much better oh really
where do we go
oh my sleep
all right we might lose the point here
already
we don't have any heels on the point
[Music]
uh
on this way
oh eh
where is this where everybody is where's
out here ah oh [\h__\h] yeah and the point
on the point
okay come back come back come back for
that wait it's fine just die just die
oh [\h__\h] oh hi sorry
[Laughter]
he i feel like he waited for me for a
second
we have to defend for four minutes
the same place
i see this the place bar is fun okay
i confused them by not doing anything
probably oh what is this yellow jelly
ah that's uh forbidden
uh that's the guy who built the turrets
whenever you see their mercy you want to
go for her because uh i have my ulti
where did i shoot it to
uh oh so what you can do don't do it yet
but you can fly down the middle area
here and then just
launch your bomb or fly straight up into
the air if they're on the point
and then launch your bomb there's a
junkrat behind inside this area
[Music]
i think we can do this
i hope so we still have to defend for
three minutes so they're gonna start
using ultimate soon like the reinhardt
probably has his ultimate right now
uh damn i shouldn't have used my old
five player kill streak
oh i killed someone again
nice
tell me when i should use my ulti
uh okay they're gonna start pushing
you should probably do the thing where
you fly straight up and then launch it
into the air okay
like where if they're stuck pushing on
this bridge where i'm standing and moira
then you wanna
fly it across the bridge and do that
not yet when they're all kind of here
now now it's a good time sometimes okay
i forgot how to use this i think
i don't think i did it
it's okay
it's all right
yeah because if you if you just use it
while it's like down on the floor people
can just run away from it but if it's up
in the air they're like where is it
where is it you catch them by surprise
where where where where
are we are we lost can we still do it
uh i don't know
maybe maybe
uh we spawn right there so it's good
but it's a little difficult
to kill them because we have to wipe all
of them
and take them a long time to get there
but
[Music]
okay our lucio's is delaying a lot we
just need to see if we could get a kill
this actually would have been a good
place to use your oats if you had it and
you just got to try to stay on point as
long as possible
um
[Music]
i think it's lost no
no
height advantage over
no yeah because all we had was a tour
but we made our tourbillon's on fire but
yeah
well we held strong for quite some time
yeah yeah i think um it's a hard map to
defend
oh
um
[Music]
one more
gotta get a win
yeah
plus it's just a practice it's good
practice yeah first time over watching
and then you think the way i am now
would i be ready to play with the other
girls
yeah i think so
would i not be dead weight
no no no no oh yeah everybody's pretty
good well i think i'm the only one who
plays pink but you do play a pretty good
eva
who played a pretty good diva
yo you played a pretty good debate
was nobody else using diva
uh just me
oh
maybe i'll get some kiwawa in diva
outfit fan art now
oh
i can see that
i can fold
okay we're doing the same thing
defending again
yeah ready
okay same thing except uh oh they have a
payload this time so let's stop them
from getting the payload to the end oh
i feel like this is a pretty good map to
defend though oh i like having the first
point okay
all right
this this thing i'm defending
yeah so they have to capture the point
and then once they get the point they
get the payload but they come through
over here like right i am playing mercy
uh-huh it comes from this bridge area so
this is the only way that they can get
in but they can also come in through
this uh
little corridor here okay
so i should stay around here
yeah yeah yeah usually people stay
around here but i don't know why we have
a winston on this
usually reinhardt's pretty good for
defense
[Music]
i think
they saw i was so dangerous so they all
went for me
[Music]
this is practically my homeland
oh oh thank you
for reviving me
we are breaking down
[Music]
okay right now i think i'm being pretty
bad again
we're waiting for our team to come back
okay it's okay
we still have people here
might be able to raise your head
you know i don't think so
oh
[Music]
are we losing our objectives
not yet
nice we picked up ah there's somebody
chasing me somebody behind inside the
room yeah ah she was on me for so long
what the heck
[Music]
all right
okay
if you could
fly i need to raise my up i'm above the
point not yet wait
uh
fly up now like where i'm walking
through
now you can get high up high enough
that's okay
he got one kill on our winston's bag
hey
eliminate the taco is that a viewer i'm
not a lutheran
taco sounds very suspicious to me
oh yeah in our team
maybe was it our team
sassy taco
have you ever had octopus before
yeah i've had it i've had uh no let's
say okay
i think that's the first time i had
octopus actually
i don't like octopus but have you had
takoyaki or just some different kind of
octopus
uh
oh
now it's quiet actually surprisingly
genji's too far
all right the reinhardt has the olds to
try to stay away from him around the
corner
hurricane that's you she's fly up and
i'll use your ultimate i'm gonna die
okay
[Music]
because i'm i'm mercy i can fly to you
when you fly up which gives me like
protection because uh
yeah yeah that's what i told you before
when you're on the point to try to fly
up so i can fly to you ah that's all you
were trying to do
so i could get to the point faster and
try to heal
[Music]
okay
i was trying to bunk them by flying into
them but
yeah
because there were so many i could do
some aoe damage you know
yeah yeah you can sometimes but yeah
it's just like a one and done thing you
just bonk them once
at least we spawn right by the point
we're defending but now we have to
defend it for four minutes
oh
at least i escaped nicely this time
because i saw him coming up to me
who was that who was doing that uh the
bastion this little robot guy
i shouldn't go further than this right
no no it's a bad idea
they spawn across the bridge though
holy [\h__\h]
all right we just have to protect the
last point
what i must have my old cycle
having an ash at this point i'm thinking
well ash
wanted to switch oh yeah because the
other team i mean we have one on our
team
we have to touch the point we can't let
them get it to the end
[Music]
hey nice
i'm not ready to sleep yet it's before
midnight
so we can't get off the point if we get
off it at all they're gonna get it we
just have to stay on for as long as
possible
not a baby anymore you
all these games are really close really
oh pretty close oh that character looks
so cool to viva
oh yeah
[Music]
any longer but
hmm
oh nice little next one though really me
too yeah
i've got a feeling
[Music]
that the next game is gonna be it
that the next game is gonna
be it
the next game is gonna be a win-win-win
till next night
let's play overwatch
i'm going to learn fbs
announcer
[Laughter]
go go go go
this will be the one i guess if i switch
to any other character now i don't think
i can
really
do well so i'm once again once again
going for the diva
i know okay this is a good diva map too
hopefully we get a reinhardt i think
that'd be good yes i think there's good
diva maps and bad diva maps is it
because like the
it's a bad diva map if there's too many
obstructions where i can fly well
uh usually when if you're like playing
defense on a control point map i feel
like diva is kind of hard to pull off
um but like because this is a
control point map and it's got a lot of
open air that's why i think it's a good
map for diva because you can really fly
around a lot
why is
[Music]
there's a ball that spawns here on the
table and if you hit it properly with
the oh he's got it every time yeah four
three
two no time no time
where are we going this way
i might suck at throwing balls anyway
okay
we're in nepal beautiful yeah it's nice
all snowy
sorry i'm looking at the scenery but i
shouldn't be looking at the scenery ah
sorry
get your behind so i can't
we're gonna be going after our healer
all right i was taking bullets for mercy
but she still died
[Music]
yeah so that reaper can do quite a bit
of damage to hit to you but if you just
right-click him
a lot of his damage disappears i don't
know who the reaper is but okay
time to raise my atm
[Music]
uh so he's uh he's the guy with the hood
the with the black hood
oh i don't see any colors right now
oh and he has he has shotguns all right
i'm gonna wait okay
work with me okay okay lucio
what's in
you guys tell me re rape is the guy with
the edgy voiceless and all that but i
don't know where all the voices are
coming from like what yeah that's
understandable
i need to like play all the characters
probably to really see who's who yeah by
like instinct
wouldn't have done that
oh what
okay that alt's gonna win us this point
at least but careful because this
reaper's probably gonna have his old
tooth yep
ah
give him his half he's half
and kill him
no we have the old i mean we had it
okay we don't have any healers up right
now
oh that's a diva oh
where is she just trying not to die
right now
i'm sorry i'm gonna die
you say try not to die and that's when i
died
almost almost
can only do so much healing as lucio
we have the point for a little bit at
least
where is our healer i guess she was dead
guys it was too late i need healing
oh at least now we can group up
that looks like a dead healer
oh shh
oh um ah
wait don't question um okay like
arguably here now
and then we're gonna get ready we're
going on the side you can uh fly in your
alt from like one of the sides if you
want wait i'm dying who's shooting me
i need a thing
okay we're pushing inside our front
i'm scared to go in but i haven't
i'm gonna try you can just fly it you
can just fly in over like you could fly
in from here and you would just stay
here
oh still gotta work on the landing
i think that was very obviously placed
all right just wait to push in wait
because uh we're just not doing it right
now okay i guess
okay we're waiting for our damage pretty
much all right we're gonna push it now
okay
the reaper the reaper's still here oh
he's wearing a white cloak right now
he's not wearing a black hat he's got a
little sombrero
with when he alters like that when you
hear that die if you right click him
you will block like all of his damage oh
[Music]
we captured it back i think
yeah yeah now we're just gonna win it
all the way they were right at 99
yeah holy [\h__\h] that's dangerous
so they use their ultimate i think
they're wait have they had a diva for a
long oh yeah she'll probably have her
ultimate she hasn't used it yet
they don't really have too many big old
smiths
[Music]
when you see him you just you gotta
right click him because the people
attack him but he does like a lot of
damage to the reinhardt and you can't
really do anything in return
okay we're gonna lose this one i think
but we're gonna stay on the point for as
long as possible oh good
nice try nice job we got up
to 73
or so
yeah we can get we still have a chance
to get the next one oh reinhardt's going
for the big the big ultimate oh
our do we have a reinhardt is that our
yeah okay yeah you tried
[Music]
still have another chance
oh
[Music]
joined the game well that sounds like
someone with confidence
he goes into game and he's like hmm
uh so we're placing our damage okay
mccree
or cassidy i keep calling the wrong name
sorry
oh no
here we go be careful with this map you
can fall off there's a pit this is the
point
so just be careful try to save your fly
just in case you can fly out of it okay
where do i stay
here on the point on the inside
[Music]
uh i don't know where i'm supposed to be
up here
olivia no olia
[Music]
oh you seem like i don't care
okay
i'm contesting
who are the people who have like a pink
name sometimes
sometimes it's not red not blue but pink
oh hmm
is the racer in the inside room
comfortable
[Music]
we lost one of our damages so we're just
trying to stall for it right now
yes
was trying to hide but you can't hide
from takanese i got my eyes everywhere i
stalk my own employees like none other
am i not why should i stay here i'm the
only one contesting
yeah yeah it's fine we're building a
percentage we're just trying to stop
them from pushing right now okay
easy i know that's our okay their team
is coming in and dying nice
keep them coming
[Music]
oh no our winston's dying behind reaper
percent we just need to capture one time
so goof up training today
[Music]
come on come on come on we can do this
i'm here
i
this room is chaotic
it is
this map is like really popular to push
people off
careful reaper on
[Music]
we're just trying to stop them from
getting on the point pretty much right
now you have to win the last point
yeah yeah yeah yeah yay i think
i did 90
of the work this time
i got three gold medals golden limbs
objective kills and healing boy where
are my medals i'm in
price tab do you have any maybe you do
oh
i love your new album you got one
uh really i don't see it as an app for
objective time uh yeah cause i was
standing there all alone yeah you
captured it
oops i pressed my speed it was too early
where are we going oh i shouldn't go so
fast i don't know where we go
you guys go first
i come
afterwards is
i got stuck on the wall
sprint oh no yeah i just grew up all day
[Music]
standing
yeah somebody's waiting for reinhardt
all right let's go
you try pushing up top i guess here
well this map makes me want to go skiing
it's already september ahmed it's almost
winter
almost
anniversary time too
yeah in like
one or two weeks
trying to heal should i go down oh no
yes yes
engaged
it could not really help our right don't
catch
[Music]
oh no we have a hammond okay
are we grouping up for
yeah yeah we're grouping up
all right quick quick come on let's go
our hammond is
all beat for him
oh
[Music]
what happened to our team
gg
they're all such gamers
what do we do about this should we eat
more doritos and drink more mountain dew
yeah yeah maybe they'll fix it
damn
but it's fun
[Music]
i
i will
i will let you go it's okay
i see this whole experience as a win
ah yeah yeah we can set up the overwatch
collab and this time i can be part of
the kid
yeah if anybody else wants to play yeah
new overwatch team
yay
thank you for teaching me a man the
second fps game that you taught me so
far
yeah now you have to master them all
okay
this is fps arc no no no no no no no no
actually more or less maybe it's the
third fps game i don't know do you see
it
i guess none
rust is not really fps game but it
definitely has some fps features
you taught me that game too yeah russ
yeah russ has a is a fps
um you got some kills right
yeah you're a good teacher amen
thank you so much
next time i can take off my twin tails
already
yeah yeah take off the training wheels
and then show them oh it says we're
joining the game
oh how did that happen
oh well it's hot it went up we have to
play
[Music]
everybody's sleeping
it's 7 a.m in japan
so what are we doing this time
okay so we're capturing points so we're
on the attack so this this map i feel
like is pretty easy to win and a lot of
these points especially the last point
is really good for diva to fly in and
launch her ultimate
if i ever get that right
you'll get it i believe
who would ever destroy a gaming center
like this
yeah you could just break a bunch of
stuff it's really satisfying yeah
this song reminds me of when we went to
the game center um oh yeah
you did my makeup did i ever tell you
guys chad that emma did my makeup and
she lends me her clothes
did i tell you that story
is uh our disguise
yeah
tiara's orange hair stands out too much
yes
yeah i did
okay
yeah yeah
i'm gonna give me some really amazing
clothes
and she did my makeup kind of dark
i think they were trying to achieve some
kind of edgy golf look with my face
yeah yeah yeah
this guy is part of the disguise
having a hammond is like on this point
no
ah i wish i was playing tank too
i'm sorry
[Music]
easy as a tank of course they just come
for me okay
tony
am i doing anything oh yeah
oh
my god
try to get on the point just fly on here
and we'll defend it catch it okay we got
it we got it
[Music]
nice we got some kills
where will they come from
uh we're going to go to them because
we're going to capture the point okay
we'll walk is really long if they die
now we get the last point which is right
by their spawn okay yay there's a few
different ways to push in ah it's like
[\h__\h] with us let's try up top
my ulti is ready
okay you could fly it in i'll show you
so you could fly it in from right here
like a ryan
[Music]
from there too yeah so so you want to go
here
don't go around the corner but there's a
little entrance there it goes on to the
point oh you have to do it right now
don't do it right now wait [\h__\h] it's
dead
or you can just do it from the beginning
or you could just fly there and then
drop it
it's probably better
uh
fly and drop it in the middle of the
point not yet
oh you gotta kill okay no that was
swiping this my from my normal diva gun
i didn't know what to expect i didn't
know what the inside looks like
oh okay
you come down
oh come on okay we're on the floor
wiggle we can get it we can get it
you wanna shoot his tire shoot the tire
it's gonna come out of the left side i
think i can shoot it
there's a lot good
they said she's from switzerland
yeah
here a lot of damage get rid of
all these people no i guess not we can
always come back in um
waiting for us to go in oh no
going in
am i going in
all right uh push well okay yeah we'll
go to the top
oh
[Music]
it's actually me
no no this is this is not true the play
of the game was takana
something's wrong with the game it's
bugging
it's supposed to be me
yeah it's a bug it's a bug that's why
they are bringing out overwatch too
there's too many bugs like this
uh-huh they never showed a real winner
and to be like that sometimes
[Music]
that felt good right at the end i got
the triple the quadruple
yeah wow
nice job
we're not joining a game again right
automatically no no no i stopped the
queue
okay yay well thank you very much for a
lovely fps evening it's exactly midnight
now so now now is a good time to
be forced to sleep by whoever that was
again
yeah yeah
yeah nice job thank you for inviting me
and i hope you had fun playing who else
would i invite
only one place
i mean who plays over what no no no no
just amelia
the only one i could ever ask to teach
me a game a noob like me
in my mind is amit
the only person i can
i feel like
she wouldn't mind holding the hand of a
noob like me
that's yeah i don't mind generous sweet
kind heart
yeah have fun thank you
thank you guys too for watching
and and being so kind about my shit-ness
you guys are so so sweet you have a big
heart all of you big chicken you guys
are so sweet and encourage encouraging
yeah
well unfortunately um a certain chicken
is now being sent to the usual room
a long long long time
next time you should try to be on my
team how about that
yeah and there's a higher chance that
you'll survive
the match
not be sent to the usual room well uh
i'll probably
see
you um again uh in either
rust or in perhaps maybe an anniversary
yeah
yeah yeah it's coming soon september is
the month coming up
hollow myth anniversary
yeah i was so shocked when
uh somebody wrote to me on twitter to
remind me that
um it's september therefore
uh rings of power is now out on amazon
and was like what it's [\h__\h] september
is that the show you were telling me
about that's yeah the lord of the rings
um prequel i guess
yeah cool i watched the first thing two
episodes today
oh yeah yeah it was
it was fine it was i i liked the the
draw the dwarfs especially i think they
were in oh
yeah like dory is your favorite
and i genuinely really like the dwarves
and there was like um um one one scene
where
you surely watched one of the rings
right
oh yeah i've seen him there was one
scene where apparently
uh
wait it was
kimberly was that kimly who was running
around uh as a as a baby
with a bucket on his head or was that
did i misunderstand or did they say
did they say someone no it must have
been him it sounds like a cute easter
egg
but maybe i thought they said
maybe they said gumly ah another
ancestor ah almost gimli so close but an
ancestor of kimberly gumly god that's
kimly's dad oh
yeah so you could see like kimly's dad
gumly running around as a child was
really cute just so so foreign so i like
these little easter eggs and seeing
seeing the like some
characters like um galadriel she's like
one of the main roles of the show
um you remember galadriel
uh she's like a really really really
scary elf lady with two shocking eyes
and blonde hair and she she's like
there's this one scene in one of the
rings where she goes like
she's really angry
she's so scary and in in rings of power
she's less scary because she's younger
and not so not so frustrated yet
no she's already frustrated at that
point
yeah before she was like mind broken or
something yeah she's not mind broken yet
i guess this is the show that makes you
go mind broken
oh
okay okay
she's going for a lot of [\h__\h]
yeah my mom said she
my mom today sent me a message
really [\h__\h] on the show
[Laughter]
really bad
but i think it was fun it wasn't that
bad unless it's entertaining probably
right yeah and better than like you know
a lot of other shows something you know
yeah yeah i get what people are saying
but anyway you know um it's it's i feel
like right now it's such a like luxury
that you have to appreciate to have
an a lord of the rings prequel going on
at the same time as a game of thrones
as well
and also
in i think november or so
uh i don't know if you watched this one
but i just recently very recently binge
watched it wheel of time
oh no i haven't watched it is it good it
i
i did enjoy it it wasn't the best show
game of thrones is better but it's it's
at least also like kind of in the same
like category you know
similar genre
and the second season is coming out in
like november i think so right now it's
like boom boom boom and you face all
these fantasy shows and it's like mamma
mia thank you
oh i was waiting for some new good shows
yeah
we love time the books are much better
isn't that like always uh the thing with
like tv shows the books are always
better
yeah i was just watching one called the
sandman which is also based on um a book
and it's really terrible but i kept
watching it anyways
i would too what is it about is it also
like fantasy
yeah it's like fantasy it's about this
guy that he's like the lord of dreams
and there's like a dreamland and okay
apparently it's a comic that's good some
people say it's good i thought it was
really terrible
it's the show i don't know about the
advertisement yeah
um oh maybe i'll watch that one too
interesting yeah yeah give it a try
the aragon movie was better than the
books i i heard of that my brother read
the book back in the day when we were
young
i never took a look at that never
checked it out
anyway no it was oh okay people do not
agree with that one opinion
yeah aragon i like the book but when i
watch the movie i don't even remember it
movie is not better
do not let them feed you lies okay okay
well see the thing is i don't read books
therefore i can enjoy the shows on tv
and the movies even more i will not be
disappointed because i read the books
yeah but the movie at least for aragon
it doesn't go past anything but the
books like you complete the series it's
like uh oh i guess it's the opposite
with game of thrones because they
actually complete it whereas the books
haven't been finished yet oh
i see
i'm i'm really happy that like you watch
these shows too because uh
the other day i was like so excited when
we were we were playing rust off stream
and i asked you if you watched the new
game of friends spin-off prequel
and you said yes and i'm like oh my god
finally because i asked so many people
uh up until that point how did you watch
the the new game of friends show did you
watch it did you watch it i was like no
yeah well i don't i didn't even watch
the first game of front show oh
yeah i already watched the second
episode too
[Music]
what did you also think it was better
than the first one or do you like the
bloodshed yeah i thought it was better
than the first one but i still don't
really like the characters all that much
in general i don't know they're just
meh not really that appealing to me
but uh i'll just keep watching don't
worry dave we'll all die soon and then
we'll get a new set of important
characters that's true they will kill
them off very soon probably
so don't you don't have to get used to
them it's better to not get used to them
that's true that's a good point
all right uh thank you everybody for
watching today i'll see you guys
tomorrow i'll be oh i think i'll be
playing
um
aoe2 tomorrow oh yeah isn't there like a
thing going on oh
not yet oh yeah oh yeah
yeah muna was trying to set up something
therefore i am going to play
age of empires how about you are you
interested in those kind of games
what is that like rts or something yeah
a really famous old one
playing it probably yeah
actually um just like yesterday i was
looking up um german like games that
were made in germany because i was
thinking about what to play on my german
channel
and and then i was reminded then that
there's a very certain
oh youtube
ah youtube dead
hey we're back we're back okay i was
saying um i was looking at german games
from germany for my german channel oh no
still so we back then we'll be back okay
and uh i i i was reminded that there was
a game
an rts game a very popular one called di
sila the settlers the settlers settlers
oh do you know that
no i've never heard it the only rts game
i've played is i think tropico maybe is
the rts yeah never heard of that one
oh okay but yeah the settlers is like
actually pretty pretty popular i think
in that genre it's just that the new one
that they're um about to re or they want
to release that has been oh yes
yeah they keep on releasing new ones but
the very newest one that they're about
to release is apparently not gonna
it's not looking very good very
disappointing so far
but the previous ones are really good
and i remember them too from my
childhood yeah yeah maybe we're gonna
try to play i don't know i'm like really
uh it's hard to
i wanna play something on my german
channel that makes sense because it is
a german game all right um
i wanted to play gothic
but
oh
perm stokol you know gothic
one day hopefully i think i've heard of
it it sounds familiar it's a classic
i think you would like it because i
think it reminds me of um
uh goddammit i was a game you played um
um skyrim and that kind of those kind of
games oblivion yeah somehow gothic
reminds me of it
oblivion yeah yeah yeah
graphics very very old but they they
there's a like a remake kind of
but the classic is best it has the vibe
yeah i thought so too similar same vibe
kind of similar vibe yeah similar world
feeling
anyway so that's why i was looking up
those games yeah um
i should try skyrim maybe i should
play libyan oblivion
yeah it's uh
this elder scrolls game that came before
skyrim oh
no i i was actually
eyeing those games a little bit at some
point actually no don't play oblivion
yeah you should play skyrim instead
why much
it's because of oblivion it's it becomes
difficult because
when you level up everything is like
really hard to kill skyrim is more
balanced i think it'd be better for you
to play as like first
first time yeah
play
know fallout i was eyeing that one too
will you play fallout 76 with me yes
i was already eyeing fallout but you can
play that together
uh well it's it's not a story game
called 76. it's kind of like rust but in
the fallout world i guess yeah
we can do that pretty much exactly that
yeah we should do that sometime sometime
let me look into it because i don't know
if the servers are okay good or whatnot
also i remember that i wanted to talk
with you about something so you don't
have to remind me but we're going to end
this video so that before i forget it we
can talk about the thing that i wanted
to talk about yeah yeah right okay okay
okay guys thank you for watching and
enjoy when we say
yay
hope you enjoyed the twin tail fps too
[Music]
you