[Music] I've
been looking for a
place where I can say it's special
[Music]
Why did you choose me?
Your laughter
stopped '
Cause you're amazing
[Music] I
feel like I can't lose No matter what,
you're mine  Your voice was ringing inside
[Music] I'm
scared, I'm nothing, but can I
do it? Let's go together, but how can you do that?
Don't you sing a song with a blank face? It's
not you. Jump in.  Let's go to our world. Will we be
able to meet the feelings of the world? I want to sing, I
want to dance. I want to laugh as much as I want to say,
in our nameless world.
[Music] We
can get lost in it. Because we're with you, we'll change.
Now we're
looking forward to it. I
want to drink.  But
[Music]
I'll sing about your future. It's
okay to cry. I'll
hug you and go to the world I want to see with you.
[Music]