​​​ ​Kiara Fried Phoenix stonks are going up...​ ​​
​​​ ​But in this day and age,​ ​​
​​ ​the smart move is to go low-risk​ ​​
​​​ ​and diversify your revenue streams.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​It'd be good to have a new branch​ ​​
​​ ​focused on maximizing profits.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Phoenix Burger​ ​​
​​ ​New Item​ ​​
​​ ​Heat sprouts with beansprouts!​ ​​
​​​ ​We got an order!​ ​​
​​​ ​Two double-cheese phoenix burgers,​ ​​
​​​ ​with extra virgin olive oil and​ ​​
​​ ​no whipped cream.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come again? Say that one more time!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't! I forgot!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here're the two​ ​​
​​ ​double-cheese phoenix burgers,​ ​​
​​​ ​with extra virgin olive oil and​ ​​
​​ ​no whipped cream!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't that​ ​​
​​​ ​the quarter-pounder phoenix sandwich​ ​​
​​​ ​with garlic and vegetable oil?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Make the call, boss!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't have a clue!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our menu's too varied!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nobody can tell the difference anyway.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's just serve this.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's my sword!​ ​​
​​​ ​Drive-thru order's ready!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's my shield!​ ​​
​​​ ​Customer incoming!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, for...​ ​​
​​​ ​Get over there!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gah!​ ​​
​​​ ​We've lost a burger!​ ​​
​​​ ​Serve it to that customer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're out of phoenix!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss!​ ​​
​​​ ​That customer's mad at us!​ ​​
​​​ ​Urgh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm doing my best here, you know!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me go cull some customers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mission failed!​ ​​
​​​ ​Help! This is like herding cats!​ ​​
​​​ ​You called?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okayu-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you have any hamburgers?!​ ​​
​​​ ​No, but I've got rice balls!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whose order is this, anyway?​ ​​
​​​ ​Believe it or not, nobody!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boss!​ ​​
​​​ ​Our review score's going down!​ ​​
​​​ ​No... no!​ ​​
​​​ ​2.5...​ ​​
​​​ ​2.0... 1.0...​ ​​
​​​ ​Our page's been deleted.​ ​​
​​​ ​My... My restaurant...​ ​​
​​​ ​Learn your lesson from this​ ​​
​​​ ​and stop working yourselves to the bone.​ ​​
​​​ ​A-chan...​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course a restaurant like this​ ​​
​​ ​would go under...​ ​​
​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara debuted this week!​ ​​
​​ ​Look forward to next week, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!​ ​​