[Music] I was
using this BGM, just like that. I
like my voice. Sorry. It was
included.
[Music] It was
included. It's okay.
[Music]
Hello everyone.
[Laughter]
[Music]  ]
[Laughs]
Hey, you're making a great voice. Hiccup is
cute. I want you to sing it one more time.
[Music]
Whois it?
I'm Koro Nekomata's
only colleague, and I
'm on the other side of Ogei again.
Why should I do it?
[Music]
[Music] I
want to do it
Chiara-
chan Air Ho It was funny That
video from a little while ago was really
funny and I
wanted to laugh, but
since it wasn't muted I
thought I'd have to hold back my laughter.  That's
interesting. I
'm Chiara Takanashi from Hololive English.
[
Music] I can hear it. [Music]
Ah, that's nice.
[Applause]
So, time has come this week.
Yay
[Music]
Let's see what happens
[Music] I was
thinking about
something like, "I read that for the first guest and the last guest for Kokoro Senpai. Um, something like that. I purposely
invited that last guest to be the first guest."  I
didn't think that much about it.
[Music]
But I
thought it was too small so I made it bigger. I'm sorry.
[Music]
[Music] I wonder if I'll
let you do that.
Wait.  I'd
like to take a look at it here
Watch the stream Or do a screen class Oh okay, let's go over
here and
see it together in the image you sent me Well, a
new costume just came out, right?
About this, a little wee but
Les  Didwin is already
coming.
[Laughs] That's
pretty scary.
[Music] We've
reached the very limit. I wonder
how far I can open that zipper. When I
breathe, something happens.  It
moves, does
n't it? It moves when you breathe. Yeah, I remember a little bit of that. After I did something, I took a breath on top. I remember something like that. When I said yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, it doesn't really move. What's
wrong with that? It's the
first time I've heard of that HH zipper.  But
somehow, I thought that the live tree was becoming more and more amazing.The
fact that I was watching and knowing all the details wasn't
something that I noticed, but the
people of Samniness Samness.
As someone else told me, that's right.
Kea-chan isn't a pervert. That
's what I mean. Life is good. That's
why she even takes off her pants.
This video is crazy.  Even
though it would be perfect even if I didn't have it Oh yeah, it's
true Ah, I see. That's it. Hey, hey, hey, I've
been waiting for this.
Erotic Live Izu
Menu Elle Live
Ah, a
comment?
[Music]
By the way, that
tiara's new casual outfit that she's wearing is
actually a little transparent.
She's
wearing a swimsuit underneath.
[Music]
But I can't take it off. I
can't take it off.  Hey, the
top is a
little bit. It would be
a bit dangerous if I took off the top. Tomorrow,
Marin-senpai
won't be shown on the stream anyway, so it's mostly because of that.  It was made
so that it could be taken off, right? That's
right. It's
detailed,
clever, and clever. Please
leave a comment if you like.
Chocolate Bikini Check Marine Bikini.
Check it out. Just hold it like a pore. Well, I'm already
wearing it, so check it out. The shop
name will be in a bikini.  They say it's only a matter of time. Do
you want to see it
? I looked up Monkey in a Bikini on NOTHANKYOUevolc. I don't know what it is.
[Music]
Wait, I'll look into
this. It's
really safe. It's a little
bad. It's terrible. This may be the name of the company from now on. I
don't want to see it.
[Music] If
Yago wears this, the
tiara will be retired.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Okay, let's go to the next NEXTme. Is
there something like that?
Um, Ok, then this or this one.
Marine Impulsion
pmis, so this is okay.  I'm
finally thinking about the distribution of Marine's proliferating bodies quite a while ago,
and I wonder if that's
where it's coming from, or something like that
imitation of Marin-chan's voice, or something like that, or something
called the Narikiri List.  The
reason why this is appearing in red right now is
probably because Marin-senpai told me that my voice hasn't been coming out lately, so I'm going to read various people on the broadcast and speak in my place. Hey, I see.
Recently I've been
watching all of Marine's broadcasts, so I've been watching all of Marine's broadcasts, so I guess that's how it got across to me,
but it really makes me realize that Fubuki-chan has
grown up more than Marine-chan, and
Fubuki-chan
has a better voice.Marin  You
can do a lot of things other than Senpai,
Fubuki-senpai, and maybe
even Chara-chan's boss. I
tried playing Fubuki-senpai before, but I
wasn't really satisfied with Chara.
Because they're Japanese, if they're
serious about
it, I guess so.Hmm, that's
right.I'd
like everyone's voices to be broadcasted on everyone's Hololive.I think it can be done.I think
Weapon Senpai can do it.
[Music]Maybe we
can do it.Alright,
let's move on, that's
fine.  They're pretty similar, but if it's just one word, it's
easy to do.'' I
feel like they're similar because they're kind.Ah, I
see.That's what it means.Maybe it's
Marine.Hmm, that's it, that Rain cat is
so much like Marine-senpai.  I
did
n't know you were good at imitating Marin-senpai. Eh, [music] I can do it. Some of them haven't heard it,
but I think I've definitely heard of Mio-senpai,
so I'm sure Mio-
chan was also good at imitating Marin-senpai's voice.  I feel like I'm good at all kinds of voices,
so I'm saying I was really good at it
[Music] Let's
find out
[Music] I
want to have that kind of talent as well
[Music]
Right
?
Next up is Neck Marie Polka-chan. They
might look similar
.
Ah, I've heard of Tai-senpai and Match-senpai's. [Music] Yeah, that's what I
did with that one. It
was pretty good. It's
suspicious.
Hey, this place is already here.  Yeah, it's number 3, so I'm
not that good anymore. It's
getting suspicious.
[Music] It
's a
shame that I haven't seen it. It's a shame, is
n't it? You're suffering. Oh, come on, this isn't that, that's that, that's
what I felt before.
I'm suffering because I had to imitate the captain's voice on the broadcast.Ah,
when I listen to the scary things my seniors say, it's more painful for us who listen to them.But I do
n't know, I
see.Here's a
list of all the members.  That
's what I wish they would make. Yes,
that's why it's a marine marine proliferation list. It's
nice, it's nice. It's
good to imitate everyone's voices.
Hey, I
didn't do that to my dad. I
understand twice.
Hey.
So what kind of conversation did we have?
I said that it would be great if I could eat delicious food and thin food. If I could eat it, I would like to share it. Then,
Marin-senpai, I asked him to
share it. I
don't understand English, but I know that
you are a pervert.  Okay,
Yaoi
, I'll show you the book.
Someday, I'll show you the
English HSBOOK.
Oh
no, there's no such thing as "too many." Let's
look it up.
Voice Love, Voice Love, Japan.
Even though it's a word, I can't understand it in Japanese.Everyone in Japan says "Voice Love", right?That's why
English words are used in Japan, but
Japanese words are used in English.Yes,
I
don't know what that means.  I'll
pick up on the meaning too. I'll
trust you if you explain this to me. It's
Marin-
senpai's birthday, so congratulations to Amelia-chan. I hope you
eat some delicious food, and someday I'll see you again.  I asked you to show me the
Voice Love book,
but Mainichi Senpai said, ``Okay, I'll show it to you.'' Also, he said, ``I
know you're a pervert.'' I
can speak Japanese well, and that one
from Delete's Ship View.
Up until the name, it
was normal for the host to explain things to the guests, but since Pajamas started doing it, I wonder if
it's the other way around.When the
guests explain things to the host, it's like,
Yaoi
[Music]
Japanese
Blu
I like it, I see, it's
OK.
Anything is OK. Anything is OK.
Next yes.
Next is that. There
was a rather mysterious tweet, so I
would like to introduce it to you.
[Music]
Introducing a lot of cakes.  When he eats, he
becomes a glutton, but
his voice says that even if he eats a lot, there
is no problem because the Pi scene is zero.I
want that Hachama to be big here.This is
amazing, this is
amazing, but please write this in a fake tweet.
Actually, Crazy-chan hasn't changed it. It's
fake.
No, but, but, my brother
seems to be into math lately, so he's been broadcasting math,
so he's changing things like this.
Please tell me, tell me, tell me.
Mathematics, no, no, no.
Yes, I do
n't like it, everyone. I've
had enough at school. I don't want to do it anymore. I don't like it. Let's go.
Like, like, like. Let's keep going. Let's
just
wait and keep going.
Follow us and see what
's new.  It seems like there
was some sort of video out there, but what does
this mean? It's something
before something starts.
It means rising, or it
gives a feeling that something is about to begin. This
English pre-rule makes sense.
It sounds like that other word.
[Laughs]
Like, let's
see. Let's
play it.
[Music] It's
a bit buggy. It's completely buggy. Let me
take a look at it.
[Music]
on the day [Music]
[Music]  ]
This is deep
[Music]
That Iris-chan is talking like that.
This is the
new member Ice-
chan.
[Music]
[Music] I
prefer the GameCube. I
don't understand the GameCube.
Nintendo's
[Music]
[Applause]
Cheer up! Cheer up!
[Music]
So cute
[Music] There
were so many memes about Hube, that's
all.
Let's take a look at them right away.
[Music]
That's what it means, after all,
worshiping the Cube will become important for Holo
Live fans in the future.That's what the Cube video was about.  Well,
before it was released, the
chat went like this.The
fans of that live show
were like idiots, treating the cube like a god.What's
so strange about this, Cuba?  There's no such thing, right?  It
could be the Cube, so I'm
looking forward to seeing how it turns out.But
maybe it's different, maybe from the Cube.Maybe
new members will be born, or maybe not.I do
n't know.
[Music] We're
all fighting against cubes.
Today, we
're against cubes. Hmm, we're against cubes.
Instead of fighting, we
want a stronger opponent. A
different cube is already strong. That's not
true. But for now, the
cube is.  It's already a mystery  It's all about
[Music] It's
like someone who understands cubes understands everything.
If I had to say something nice, it would be 3. Isn't
Japanese cool? It
's tingly. [Music] So I'll have you take a look. [Music] That's right.  When you fight with a cube, the
attack using the cube is
definitely like a Donkey Kong game,
with Donkey Kong on top and a
barrel
below.
Well, it was a duty like throwing something, right?
Why is the character
trying to climb up? That's certainly cool.
[Music] You
say you're creating a story,
but Ame-chan did a game like this.  Yes, that's
right,
that's right, that's what happened last time in this mini-anime game.It's
like I like it in games like this.It's
raining, so I'm
going to give it a shot.I'm
really bad at this game.I don't know what kind of game I'd like.
Eh, RPG
Sales
Tales and Tells are similar to Obseries
and RPG
Jammer. What are you talking about?
[Laughs]
Everyone, let's go. Let's go.
Let's have a look at it. I heard that they
made a 9-minute movie called I Pig Inciting. But
this kind of thing is
different.
This is the wall, the cube,
this is the implication that Shia-chan is the final boss,
that kind of thing is dangerous, dangerous, dangerous,
dangerous, this is beyond LINE, this is on LINE, this is
dangerous, bad, bad.  It's
okay to be scolded by your seniors, right?
Don't say anything funny.
[Music] I'm
calling you chan. I'll
get a DM from my seniors.
Next time, I'll
cook some food for you and get your forgiveness. You're so kind. You'll
probably forgive me. You're smart, you're
smart.
[Music]
Dice Steak, Dice Steak is the best. It
just happened to me. It
just happened in another world. I'll
explain it to you. What will happen
when it comes? It seems like it
happened in that world where Cube Cube has evolved.  That's right  The
cube
was a religion, and Iris-chan, let's
end it,
love.
[Music]
Pear is a
legend. The legend of Roari-san is happening, and the main character is fighting against that cube, a dark organization. I see. She's the heroine, but she's
actually a bit...  Even if you say that you're a yandere, it's just because there's
something going on that makes you angry.
That error is from Holo Error, so I
think that means he looks like a yandere.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Other than that, it was a pretty good explanation.Other than that,
it
's just a pattern that is often used, but by the way, this is that drama that you can
watch on Netflix
called Community.It's
not a drama, but
it's a comedy show.  It
's a screenshot. It's often used as a show.
It's a situation where someone looks a little
weird, but when they get home, they've turned into a huge crow.
If it's chaos, a lot of things are going to happen, and I'm going to get angry, so
that's what it is.Oh yeah, I have
n't been looking at my computer for a few hours, and then I
open up the Internet and a lot of things are happening.I
can't see how everyone's feeling.
[Music]
Everything's turned into cubes.  Well, I
see, that's what you mean.
Well, the
community
has nothing to do with it, but it's interesting to see all kinds of people of all ages
going to that university
and, yes, about
to graduate.
This is something you can look forward to after you watch it. I
don't want to spoil it, so you can
look forward to it after you've all seen it. That's
right. Now then, let's move on to the next one, everyone.
[Music]
Next up will be this meme.
[Music] I
remember when Ame and Gura
said they wanted to play a simulation game.
I told IMG that this is what I imagined. Oh, I'm
talking to someone, but
this is what Ame-chan
decided to do.  So then Gura-chan was
like, what?
What are you talking about at 9 o'clock? Well,
this is it.
Gura-chan
knows that Neame-chan can time-leap. She
thinks that Ame-chan will time-leap at 9 o'clock and predict something at 9 o'clock.  I wonder if that's what the story is about.I
think that's possible, and I think it's interesting.Oh,
but it must be different.I
see, that's probably true.I do
n't know if they say that in Japanese either, but for example, 1.
When I say there's something at the hour or 3 o'clock, I do
n't mean that there's something at that hour, but that there's something in that direction,
so when I
look at that clock, I look at that mouth.
There's something going on in that direction, so
Ame-chan knows that, and
since she's on that plane right now, she's
telling her to be careful because there's something there, but she can't
tell Gura-chan.  I'm always
asking what's going on at 9 o'clock.
[Laughs]
That makes me happy.  I'm
looking
in the other direction. Look, there's something in the direction of 9
o'clock. I told her to look in the direction of 9 o'clock, but
instead of looking at her mouth, Gura-chan looked in Ame-chan's
direction and said, ``What's there?''  "
That's right,
there's something about that," means that they don't
really understand that there's something about that fork. That
's right, these two people have that kind of
dynamic.
Dynamic Beeching America
[Music] The
Witcher Pink Quiz iswith
now
butPE
Super,
I see, I see, I
like the idea of Hachima being a smart guy
[Music] It
has a lot of different meanings
[Music]
[Music] I don't
know what to call my senpai, but I don't know
[Music]  ] I do
n't know how dangerous it is. You
can call me courageous.
[Music]
That's what I said.
Actually, it's so funny. This is so cute.
Well, basically,
especially when it
comes to
our family, we're a couple,
but we're pretty cold when it comes to other people,
but this time I'll talk
about Iris-chan, when it comes to the new member.  It's so much more amazing than
usual that I read about us on TV. It's
okay, it's okay to read about me. It's
amazing, it's like a
delivery health. Yeah, what's
wrong with you?  Right?
[Music]  It
's jealousy. It's not
jealousy, it's actually a formal name.
Even the English fans
were like, ``What's wrong with Mr. Crab?'' That's
why it's different from usual. I
see. I'm
not jealous. I'm not jealous.
Nya, you two,
get along well.  Just give it
to me. It's interesting. It's definitely surprising. It's surprising.
My
new member, Ice-chan, is very impressive. I saw something about her,
but Airi-chan...  I
watched too many of those memes, and the
meme's impression on me became so strong
that I was like, oh, there was
that kid with Kana-tan and Towa-chan, oh, that
happened, that happened,
that's what's
popular now.  I often see Ice-Chan's meme.
Her son is not a son,
but a
daughter.
[Music]
That girl speaks Japanese very well.
Seriously, she was also fluent in English.
Yes, that's right.
Kiara I might be even more fluent in Japanese than Kiara. I
didn't think there was someone with a voice that exceeded that of a character, but there
it is. Yes, it
's shocking. Shocking. It's
okay. Hansama and I are two people.
That's right, because I'm an Otonalian. I'll
confront you in Japanese. Hachamo:
I see. I'm starting to feel a bit competitive.
Tahaichoma Oh, that's
right. I
see.
Well then, I'd like to go to the next one right away.
I see.
[Music]
What I would like to see changed. This has been
going on since Amir's debut. Now, Ania's
drawings are very
distinctive.
Well, it's
pretty
funny when you paste something simple and funny on someone else's face, so I've been doing this for a long time,
so I decided to make
my brother the face of a Hololive member.  The
idea was to paste it in, but the face
of Ice-chan that appeared recently
looks a little too real, so
if you change that, it will look like this, so
it's a really scary and funny face.
There was also a mimo that I put on top of Ma. Seriously, I'm going to
find it again and do it again. That's
how funny and weird the scary face of Anya-chan looks. Scary.
What did you find?  I
want to see it, I want to see it, I'm sorry, I'm on it.
There's this too. There's something like that. Oh
no. This is different. I wonder if your mother
knows about that deli. Another one that's
been popular
since before we got married is the
members of Hora Live.  I
decided to turn it into something like a hachama, so first I decided to make it look like a
hachame.It
turned into a hachame.  It's
not that I like feet. I
started to like feet when I saw something interesting on the stream. Then I used my feet to control certain pressure points. I was
playing games with my feet, and before I knew it, he started liking my feet. I see. I feel like I'm going to
fall in love with Japanese clothes.  I
'm doing that. I
love putting my feet on the desk. Oh, that's interesting
. It's nice to be able to do a great pose. In a
sense, I'm
Mim. In a sense, that's also true
.
There's a lot of things going on, right?
That's
right, that's why I'm here. I just
mentioned it earlier. There's
one more thing, including the future Izu Yandere incident.
There's a video that recently appeared on Hololive, so I'd like everyone to take a look at it and
watch it.  I think, ``I'm not good at this.''
You're
making a holo error. You're
doing something really good. It
won't be scary if everyone just looks at it.
Now, let's
start. What is it?
Management?
Ah,
[music]  For
some reason, Mr. Red Heart was appearing on the screen.
You weren't
there. It wasn't Ha-chan who was also shown there,
but Mr. Red Heart. It was a
lie.
Seriously?
[Music] That's
scary
[Music]
Because we were friends,
Senpai
[  [Music]
It's okay, I'm
scared. It's okay. I'm
scared.
It's Senpai.
Sarah-senpai. I'm
scared.
Tell me when you're done.
[Music] What's going on now? [Music] I'm
scared of school too.
Okay, a world of peace. Really,
there's nothing right now.
Always,
forever, always That's my friend, right? It
's scary
[Music] It's
scary
[Music]
[Applause]
Look, I'm not good at it. Sorry, it's okay. You can wear pajamas. Look,
Hoora looks like everything's fine.  That's what it feels like. What do you
mean by "all live error"?
What on earth is going on? Hey
, what, what, what?
Seniors aren't just scary people.
So why did this happen?
Maybe there was something wrong with that.So let's take a look at the last meme.Okay,
now the last meme.What
does it mean to be in contact with Ponbeen?
Um, um, no,
explanation.  It says "I don't need it." I
don't need an explanation. It's a
future advertisement.
[Music]
Tara's advertisement. Is there something going on tomorrow
?
I see. I
see. Hai-sama is always like this.  It's
much deeper than this, it's scary,
everyone's been scared from the beginning because they're broadcasting something scary.Haa-chan,
stop it, but this time it's
not Ha-chan, it's Sora-senpai.It's
painful.Ah,
that's kind of surprising, Sora.  I've become a senior.
[Music] That
's the
director of Holo Error. Maybe it's Hachaman. I do
n't think he'll
be able to direct a horror film like this now.
Well, that's right.  It's
probably not what I was aiming for, but even if I end up in that horror role, it's a mystery message of abandonment. [Laughs] I'm not an actress or anything. I'm pretty sure I can't
say anything for too long. What are you talking about? Let's
take the audition.
What should we do?  It looks like it's going to be a
big deal.
How was it?
[Music] I was
thinking, uh, that's a little new. Ah,
um, but my head
is able to interpret, but I'm going to explain it. The
explanation is,
Okay, Japan.
Even though I don't speak Japanese well, I
didn't really understand mathematics, so it was a relief to be able
to buy and sell things in my head.From
now on, I'll have to ask Iris-chan, who is fluent in Japanese, for help.  The only
guests I can invite for the Rateship View are
those who can speak both English and Japanese.Now
that I've been doing it for a while, you'll
learn Japanese as well, so it won't be a problem.That
's not the problem.  That's it
Buying and selling Mim's material, that's all.
[Music] I
think if you read the English-speaking world, like Horror English, or Indonesian people, you'll be able to get a general explanation.
Well, I'd like to read a little bit of this. It's nice. I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for reading my head. I was really happy.
Holotalk
is probably the same, but
Haa-chan is also the one who comes to this.  I was
wondering if anyone would come,
but on the contrary, I wonder who's going. It's
okay. Ah, that's good. That red, red heart is good. Even the pigeon. I have no choice. Let's go to the heart. Raku
[Music]
Shimi
No, can I call two people? Can I call two people?  I wonder if they'll
do that.
But it's totally fine. I might as well interview the two people I wanted to see. I
wonder which members will be there, Achamato,
Red, Red,
and that one,
Matsui-sensei.  I'm looking
forward to it. Thank you for coming. We're also looking forward to it.
This week's
ship poster is
Chip Potter.
Thank you. Nice to meet you. Bye-bye
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music]