first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
a great Wanderer
[Music]
I'm walking
before my
eyes
[Music]
three two
sleep talking
bro
[Music]
he notori
heart Challenger
[Music]
Sparks
favorite night
[Music]
will zombies
do you
love hate all the same if you know Play
It Again
[Music]
first album
[Applause]
[Music]
it's my not birthday it's my anniversary
free year anniversary
[Music]
I have a plan of things that we're gonna
be doing first
of all I wanna show you I'm celebrating
myself
appropriately
[Music]
forgot to put on gloves
okay it's okay this is a cake I
mentioned before uh zombies
um it's the it's a really small cake
maybe you can't notice it yet but it's a
really small cake it's usually for
children yeah it's called the Benjamin
all german-speaking people will know
this and maybe maybe even outside of
German speaking people I don't know
um but it's a really cute small sweet
cake that I used to like a lot and even
as an adult like all my friends who are
also adult we all just love this cake
we all just love this cake yeah
I want to start off
by cutting the cake oh camera is working
beautifully Yahoo
um
totally my cake yeah uh I'll I'll just
it's uh it's from omoket I think right
that that it was a stand I have to cut
through
[Music]
oh it's um strawberry and chocolate
flavor it's generally just really sweet
I freaking love it let's let's take a
bite
huh
wow even I even brought out my my light
my LED light uh today to make the cake
look better
um
good decision I haven't eaten this cake
in a long time
that's a good decision to get this out
they're like confetti on top a little
bit crunchy it's made out of sugar it's
really good too
foreign
[Music]
a few hours ago
from the freezer section and then just
put it in my fridge and it was the
perfect amount of time to like unfreeze
it kind of
I don't know what it is about this cake
that makes everybody even when they're
adults go back to it
oh look at that
ah it's not pretty I love my I'm so
happy with the camera one of the best
purchases I've made recently ow
um
people back but there's so many other
cakes I think there's just a childhood
memories and
um
the fact that it's like small and good
you can get it in any
it's loud really you can get it in any
supermarket
oh I doubt that it's loud but okay
I'm turning down a little bit
looks really good not gonna lie banana
for scale
um
I have a banana for scale but here's my
my Wacom pen for scale it's it's really
small like smaller than the usual
um cake
like a whole little cake
it's funny you say that
but yeah um
maybe really really really really really
slightly some
frozen nests in there like it almost the
chocolate pie almost feels like
chocolate ice cream
but that's not a bad thing right
nobody's complaining about that
oh wow then what happened there
I'm just bite off the apart little
literally bird food
do we got a piece
I mean
if you're fast at the moment I still
have so much left of this cake
if you're fast and you you come over
here quickly remember I'm here Peck
ah come on camera I know you can do it
no you want to focus on my glove instead
ah come on I praise you I praise you
what do you want
whatever ah wait choking
[Music]
sweet things make me so happy
man I've I looked myself I
I had a swimsuit on today because I went
swimming you know doing my swimming
wraps recently I looked at myself
in the mirror and I realized
I've I may have gained some weight
recently
a little bit I've been eating so much
like
pancakes for breakfast with uh a lot of
Nutella and berries maybe I've been
eating too many chicken nuggets recently
too
and lots of chocolate yeah maybe I
should cut it down a little bit I've
been letting myself go a little bit
after just eating whatever makes me
happy recently okay it's just a little
bit of a slight change of weight okay
okay it's just slightly okay
if I eat the whole cake alone I don't
need to cut it right
oh but that's not a challenge by the way
I'm eating the whole cake is not a
challenge we have other challenges today
[Music]
but I can't be eating a cake or on the
stream because I have many things too
[Music]
oh
oh look at this beauty
um
[Music]
I put that back into the fridge okay
let me turn the camera off
oh sure we'll need it again
it's off now by the way we'll need it
again in a little bit later
[Music]
they are about to start
thank you
all right all right all right all right
all right
a rattle rattle rattle rattle right all
right oh by the way one thing uh I think
people have seen this background before
but I maybe only showed it like once
because I wanted to figure out what to
do with it
but uh yeah it was also in the in a
little video I think that I recorded
I had a freaky Wawa something with
froggy Wawa but let me just show it to
you here and it's more or less full
Glory
hi hi
[Music]
it's the the other side of the office
isn't that pretty
[Music]
wait let me move myself around
param
nice it looks so clean except for those
particles that are flying around that
probably make will make some people
sneeze and alert their allergies
but I'm fine
so I'll add the boxes what actually it
still gives me a really clean impression
anyway
now the theme of today
as you may know by the logo kionute
where's the logo layer there there
overcome
[Music]
[Laughter]
and the pictures are like the images
whatever in the logo already give you a
little bit of a hint of what we're doing
today
um but we're still not getting right
into it because I actually I have I have
I have things from you guys that I
thought
the best order is to go through your
guys's things first um fans submissions
or gifts uh and so on go for that and
then we'll move on to the next section
so
and let me bring back the album
advertisement It's gotta be there guys
uh let me just say right now uh my new
album has been released like what two
weeks ago or so and my first album point
of view it's on Spotify iTunes Apple
music Amazon music etc for digital uh
digital listening if you want but you
can also buy a real physical copy it's
not gonna be available anywhere besides
through uh you know the pre-order right
now afterwards there's gonna be none
unless I mean I don't know and it's not
gonna be like general sales so you know
link is in the description but also
pinned in the comment if you want a
physical copy the physical copy even
comes with a special Sparks
metal remix
[Music]
so yeah that's that and then and then
and then
we start with
what is this it is a PDF that was sent
to me by kfp
uh through janma thank you it looks cute
already
this is like a like a cover I guess
what's happening here it's so cute why
why is you crying oh wait I think I
understand ah because there's like it
continues here and we'll see it on the
next page
um 44 pages
[Music]
actually can I change that setting
it says capture cursor curse cursor I I
did set capture cursor
oh it doesn't show though oh well but
yeah the guy in the back the chicken in
the back is like summoning something but
I don't know and he's the other one's
really embarrassed they're back the
other one in the back is like sleeping
cute and then oh
oh yes this belongs together
that's so pretty
who through this
that's so pretty that's one of the few
most beautiful artworks I've ever seen
on myself
notes for our Phoenix Muse
nice little girl who made the logo
Spirit snare probably right the the two
girl person for Logos
who I discovered the hair
I am like a I'm like a talent scout oh
my god I've discovered so many like
Creator people that then other en
members start using
yeah not even I I would say even
Japanese members and ID members
partially anyway this is pretty cool
it's a pretty so shiny it looks so nice
what is it I like this this little these
little icons he has third anniversary
fan booklet project from kfp to Kiara
are you guys kfp or are you Kiana if
you're none of that then you're not
allowed to look
you guys are all kfp right because I'm
Kiana
so as long as you can feel you're good
okay uh opening message
[Music]
what day is it today Tuesday
pick my hello beep is arriving I can
ignore it right
let me oh no I'll ignore it because they
just drop it if you just ignore it
they'll just drop it whatever let's say
I'm not home okay shhh
go there or not because I have to wait
and then just drop it there
probably fine I've done it before
eh we the kfb cannot believe we're spent
three glorious years with our Idol
got a typo there to celebrate how
amazing you are
oh wait now now they're calling me okay
I'll be right back
[Music]
thank you foreign
thank you
okay okay okay okay okay
ah worst timing worst timing wait wait
to celebrate how amazing you are gave me
from all around the world got together
and made this fan book
we have so many talented artists who
love you and decided to draw for our fan
book
love you artists in total more than 250
messages in four different languages
eat them
it better be German English
Japanese and
what I can only really read those free
are they Korean too
our messages are about which original
song is our favorite and about how
amazing you are as a singer Idol and
motivator kfb know that you're studying
Korean so just in case we have a cheat
sheet at the end okay so that's the
fourth language yeah
we didn't need a trip to the usual room
to write all of these messages we all
truly love you
[Music]
why did you have to emphasize that we
wrote all of this without Free Will eh
hello
you're making me look bad here right now
you are truly our ocean and this is
notes for our Phoenix news
ah look at those cute stickers to the
members stickers
all right let's see I don't think I can
read the messages on stream but we'll go
for it like a little bit you know the
credits
whoa
oh this is like new art that they drew
just for this ride and I didn't upload
it yet because I didn't see it before I
would have seen this
wow so detailed so pretty with a nice
Phoenix in the back showing you exactly
what I truly am thank you
thank you Carly this is gorgeous you can
you should upload that afterwards though
that's so cute it's heart Challenger
themed oh wait so this is Hino Tony
fiend and this is hard to understand my
second single
you should draw properly like this more
often
[Music]
what I mean is that normally you're just
doing like smaller sketches
do more do more this is so cute
affection Destroyer hey it's heart
Challenger okay
[Music]
with the Sparks art oh that looks
amazing those boobs look really nice
they shaped
[Music]
sorry what
they're really really vibrant I love it
that's so nice wow
oh I'm just noticing some details
wow thank you this upload upload do it
oh oh put some money with the fever
night art wow I also like same thing to
you from somebody I see so much like
smaller ad from you but like look at
this stuff like damn
you should I like I love your Mimi
smaller art but you should do also more
of this
when you do it it's just freaking
amazing this is really cool
foreign
[Music]
loving each other or I don't know what's
happening
that sultry look though
a little bit a little bit concerning
what's going on here huh
I love this though I love it I love the
two different color variations man I
wish I could like you know wear them
here right now like this like those
colors I wish I had those variations for
real for real love them
job and here comes the messages huh
this is the team that uh created the art
and the book Etc
well we hope you know the join you here
you're so cute the stickers are so cute
I like the design too oh
this is from Emily Cafe's love messages
oh this is outfit yeah it's the ikotova
outfit
[Music]
I always love and Fan Art when there's
you know my kfb chickens in there
because they always look so cute in
their uniform
[Music]
oh my God they're so cute
thank you oh
I see it that's so cool with the like
stickers of what song you choose
Sparks do you fever night
okay okay okay and you're telling me
there's like 250 messages oh my God
okay yeah wish me luck going for this we
don't have time for this now but we will
I will I will look at this this is
really well made really cute is there
something like on the last oh
wow this is cool it's kind of cool who
did the graphic design man
was this some extra art
cute
yeah this is not
no I've seen
have ever seen this like the the cosplay
I saw today
and the Dora one I feel like I saw it eh
did I see them before are they new
have okay
yeah I think so
yeah
thank you for creating that I will look
at it closer after stream we have I have
a tight schedule I can't look at it's so
closely now sorry about that I'll get to
it next from the submissions I have
I already spoiled myself because you
guys you need to when you do this I I
want to be more surprised you don't put
the name of the person in the video file
name and maybe don't like maybe the
first second have a black screen or so
so I don't I don't spoiler myself
foreign
wait I wonder if my sound settings are
correct uh it should probably be fine
takanashi wait wait
[Music]
it's Alyssa Milano oh my God oh my God
oh my God oh my God wait this is
probably double double audio though let
me do monitor only that should work
better oh my God oh my God oh my God
she's so pretty what the
yeah you know I've been recently I I've
been talking so much about Charmed
because I did a binge re-watch of it
from start to finish it took me like
three months or so yeah she is the
Phoebe of Charmed okay that will
probably say uh everybody who she is
let's start from the beginning
Thai takanashi it's Alyssa Milano and
this one she calls me by my last name
ah one more time
yeah it's Alyssa Milano and this is a
cameo made just for you from KFI the
audio was small for you right let's do
it again
Thai takanashi it's Alyssa Milano and
this is a cameo made just for you from
kfp
um and I hear you're a YouTuber and
you're having your three year
anniversary yes so good job there
because I wait did you guys tell
someone that you know that
we have something in common no
how hard it is to hold an audience's
attention so congratulations on that
um also I just want to say thank you so
much for being but she probably doesn't
really want to remember her own um wait
to go back on that
um and also I just want to say thank you
so much for being
a Charmed fan
um that show meant so much to me and it
was
you know shot in such a pivotal time of
my life
um so it will always hold this special
place in my heart
um and really sort of formed who I am as
a person as I'm sure
uh your work and your channel has
informed who you are as a person
totally get it and I get dedication and
um I'm just very happy for you so happy
anniversary thank you subscribe many
more to come and be wealth and God bless
oh
Brittany what the hell
they're pretty and oh my gosh she's so
sweet
can I watch it again
it's actually
probably because officially my name
starts with takanasi so maybe she thinks
like that's my first name but doesn't
Kiana sound more like my first name hey
takanasi
but I guess sometimes you call people by
their last I'm like hey Watson right for
taganasi Kiana it doesn't sound right
but it's funny if she does it I I feel
Charmed by it
and this is a cameo made just for you
from kfp
um and I hear you're a YouTuber and
having your three-year I wonder if she
knows what a v tuber is anniversary
so good job there thank you I know how
hard it is to hold an audience's uh
attention it can't be hard on that
um and also I just want to say thank you
so much for being
a Charmed fan
um that show meant so much
to me
you know shot in such a pivotal time of
my life
um so it will always hold this special
place in my heart
um and really formed who I am as a
person as I'm sure
uh your work and your channel has
informed who you are that's that's it
does totally get it yeah and I get
dedication and
um I'm just very happy for you so happy
anniversary happy for me many more to
come sounds very different from when
Cali says that to me
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry I had to watch it a second time I
noticed different things and she said
the second time
me because you sent me a message she
loves me okay I have more I don't know
oh my God
now who what where
okay okay okay whoa
whoa whoa wait I'm just throwing this
into uh OBS now so I have to like sort
it out oh my God Kira hello hi oh my God
oh my God yeah we had some Vice Gumtree
and now we have the one and only Frodo
oh my God I can't believe it
um oh my God
okay go
go Kira hello
Moshi uh this is for you I think
oh hi
foreign
hello hi Elijah here I hope this finds
you happy healthy and well uh
congratulations on three years streaming
it is your third anniversary
um as a virtual streamer what an
incredible accomplishment troll streamer
um you have a very very devoted fan base
in the kfp yeah who believe that you
have only just begun and that will reach
even higher Heights
um and they will be following you and
supporting you and lifting you up uh not
unlike Sam did for Frodo
um for many many many more years to come
apparently actually speaking of Sam Sam
provided or Sean Aston uh provided a
birthday uh message for you
um so I uh I round out the duo by
wishing you congratulations on your
third Eliza did you see did you see the
you have to go and watch and uh close to
London they're doing a musical on Lord
of the Rings right now you have to watch
it I went to there to watch it on the
first day in the premiere day and it was
really good like I totally recommend it
to you the guy that plays you is like
you know he's got the Frodo Vibes 10 out
of 10 recommends so would you please go
um lots of love tell them my
recommendation brought you there I will
check it out I actually just had a brief
brief look
um at your uh at your your stream and
your profile and just trying to get an
education as to who you are
um you sound incredible
when your fans even more so in terms of
their love and support of what it is
that you're doing
um and keep it up keep up that good work
thank you and keep streaming and you
will carry on
um lots of love to you Kira thank you
congratulations be well
can I stop streaming now ever when he
tells me to go on
it's so funny okay okay okay
I'm trying to remember did did uh Sean
say my name correctly back in the day I
wonder
yeah
thank you so much it's amazing my mom is
probably watching right now and again
jealous just as she was last year when I
had the the other message oh my God my
favorite yellow ostrich
oh but he's so so sweet and he's so
beautiful oh my god wow wow
wait there's one more what I didn't even
I didn't see yet I'm like only like I'm
trying to avoid looking I'm not saying
it I'm not saying it okay okay
I'm not saying it who is this who is
this I'm not seeing it yet I'm not
saying it I'm not saying it I don't who
is this oh
okay okay okay
oh my god oh
that is epic okay wow let's go
well hello there Kiara
let's go of course it did okay for
people who don't know this is an actor
Yannick Truesdale from Gilmore Girls who
is playing in really iconic character in
Gilmore Girls she's like the the French
accent uh reception guy who's so funny
who's always like sarcastic I love him
his banter is so funny well hello there
Kiara
happy Third Year Anniversary streaming
online chicken thing that sounds
so exciting Doug Hood reached out to me
because he tried to get me to work at
the front can't tell you that could he's
the one who
is forcing himself kindly to watch all
of camel girls because I told you guys
to watch it oh my God
you're so sweet if he whatever chicken
thing and of course as you can imagine I
declined but you know
you know you don't want to join is that
what you're saying wait what because he
tried to get me to work at the front
counter of tfp whatever chicken thing
and of course as you can imagine I
decline but you know
it's exciting
chicken online
[Laughter]
doing purposefully his Gilmore Girls
character being like really
disinterested and and and sarcastic but
I freaking love it if I don't know it
doesn't matter if he's acting right now
or if he's like really just like you
know being himself I absolutely love it
in three years oh
congrats yeah
I love him so much this is exactly how
he is in the show oh my God I feel like
I'm Lorelei right now this is exactly
how he talks to everybody oh my God okay
this smiling I wish watch my cam that's
psychotic well hello there Kiara how are
you it's Michelle
happy Third Year Anniversary streaming
online chicken thing that sounds
so excited Doug Hood reached out to me
because he tried to get me to work at
the front count of tfp whatever chicken
thing and of course as you can imagine I
declined but you know
it's exciting
chicken online three years oh
congrats dear
oh my God I love so much
I'm gonna cry
you're so funny now I'm gonna re-watch
Gilmore Girls again that's it that's
that's you know I I needed after I was
done with re-watching Charmed I I was
like what so what am I re-watching next
uh that's what I was at at the moment so
now I know I'm re-watching uh Gilmore
Girls again let's go
holy holy I'm so excited
thank you guys so much oh my God
oh my God okay
okay next next we are on the schedule
I have a letter
I don't know how I can get emotional
right now because I'm too freaking
excited uh but you know
I'm gonna read a letter to you guys okay
um it's it's not a big deal okay
[Music]
dear kfb
for three years now we have been going
for fake and thin every day I spend
thinking of ways to entertain you and
make our time the most special when I
started out I didn't think that I could
do this job longer than one year or so
and surely there were times when I
wanted to end it before
but I love this job despite its
hardships and more than that I first and
foremost appreciate all the love and
time you guys have given me so far
all the dedication and support means so
much to me
that it washes away all the tears and
stress
I have done so many things that I wanted
to do but there are still so many things
that are left over
I'll work hard to make everything work
so that I can probably look back on my
experience with no regrets ever and
while I do that I help kfp will stand by
me even when I'm not the perfect gamer
or singer or even person
every day I try my best to become better
at what I do and I hope that ever will
reach new as well as old fans alike
three years is already such a long time
but I hope you are ready for a couple
more of me
thank you for continuing to be a source
of happiness and fulfillment to me thank
you for giving me a place to belong to
and loving me the way I am for highs and
lows day by day
let's grow bigger fly further together
you have all my gratitude
takanashi Hira
yeah
what it looks Hardy oh I had it so loud
still oh my God I'm so sorry did you
hear it properly though
sorry I had I I had it so high because
of the videos
could you hear it
yeah you could read it on this side
anyway so good okay okay
it's just a little leather just I
thought you know I cannot do an
anniversary stream about writing you a
letter
good
honestly I wanted to ride it longer and
longer and longer but I kept on running
out of space and I kept on extending
this page
but yeah I had to keep it at a decent
length so
um
with that leather I think for before we
go deeper into the challenges let me
sing for you the most fitting song at
the moment from my first ever album
[Music]
I'll sing one song only for you guys for
now
please listen to
brush
[Music]
a while since we started don't you think
what about by now a certain feeling
sinking in but yet we we're growing
stronger as time goes on and I can think
of ever letting go
[Music]
you're in my heart you'll always
to you
even in the dark times
[Music]
every moment I'm waiting patiently for a
new surprise A Perfect Memory will keep
it's always making us Bolder though
we're getting older these times will
live forever
[Music]
I remember it's all worth the while till
now from the side beside you I'm free
and I'm home finally wherever
[Music]
away
and you see me
[Music]
without you I'd be undone
oh
[Music]
wow
every everyday
[Music]
all right
hey
[Music]
thank you very much now
that is enough of
warming up now we are going to do the
real thing guys
as you may know ideally
both for my birthday this year and my
anniversary I would have loved to show
you guys 3D performances
um but you know not possible at least
for the birthday that will be moved to
later for anniversary I don't even know
but I really wanted to show you guys
something special on the actual day
[Music]
um and I thought really hard about what
to do and I thought one thing I can do
is maybe take some Vlog like videos and
challenge myself to something so this
past week I've been out quite a bit
to take some footage on my own
um and cow cards and Jackie helped me
with making it even spicier it's spicy
also a challenge later
but yeah
that's pretty
after all now hold on
[Music]
um
um there's two relatively long videos
for you to enjoy I will be quiet while
uh you're watching it I'm somewhere in
the background watching it with you
um yeah and then the third challenge is
live so let's go let's go let's go let's
go foreign
I hope the um audio will be correctly
routed I think it should be fine enjoy
enjoy and
Welcome to our first challenge of today
I am inside this book where water was
born by the way it's a nice pretty city
in Austria that's neighboring restarting
because I think the audio was double yes
Welcome to our first challenge of the
day I am in science book where Mozart
was born by the way it's a nice pretty
city in Austria that's neighboring
Germany I went with a bus for about 40
minutes to a little city called
sanctuation and surrounded by lakes and
mountains yes very popular area for
paragliding
scenery already very beautiful on the
way there weather great as well pretty
hot actually yeah you can see some cows
and Farms all over and that's already
the fusion sea I think which means we're
getting super close
uh and yeah yeah isn't it beautiful yeah
are perfect perfect I'm excited well ah
that is most likely yeah that's already
the Wolfgang sea where I'll be going
what I'll be flying over and yeah here I
arrived already I was pretty nervous in
the beginning well but you gotta do what
you gotta do
so by the way I reserved this online
beforehand and asked for permission to
film everything so all good there yeah
when I was when I entered I was going
very nicely by my partner and the boss
of the company partner as a flying
partner because I'm not flying alone of
course you can't it's not allowed and
but yeah they gave me an eight kilogram
backpack to wear up the mountain okay we
are going to the up to the mountain now
the name of the mountains
I take it
let's go
oh
[Music]
it's like we're going skiing oh let's go
this is what we're bringing up to the
mountain
still a little bit up there it's really
hot but nice weather
yay we made it oh
let's
take a look at this View
fruit heart
s
I wish I could land right in the lake
afterwards
because it's hot but
we gotta land on grass
that is this outside game look we're
carrying this huge backpacks
what's inside only the
perfect lighting only the Paragon stuff
okay so can you can you tell us a little
bit about our flight time and so on
mm-hmm
[Music]
around the mountain and then over the
lake and the land oh thanks again yeah
excited
do you ever have accidents
yeah yeah oh the one piece it's real oh
okay well then that makes me feel safe
it's so Steep and my backpack is heavy
for at least for me because I'm
weak as
she suddenly said we're stopping here
this is
take off area
[Music]
oh God
I don't know if you probably don't
really see it on the video but it's
really steep
no it's gonna be okay I have a
professional with me
it's gonna be fine yeah oh I got a
helmet too right okay
so she said we're both pretty light so
we're going to start earlier and we're
gonna have a nice light Landing
[Music]
it's gonna go well
okay okay
thank you
[Music]
one flying let's go
one so beautiful
the wind is nice holy holy oh
okay
yeah
okay I'm holding the camera but it's
secured I was scared to drop it but it's
secured we're getting really close to
that
mountain right now
she is in full control
wow this lake is which one the voice
and then behind it that's uh the moon's
all a very famous very famous
I saw some birds flying around us but
generally we have
free airspace
[Music]
wow
it was so scary to take off
but it happens really fast so
wow
[Music]
look how beautiful Austria is
let's land in the in the lake
see the others
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I got really sick right at the end but I
was able to hold it in right when we
were supposed to land
but I made it she even had a little
little plastic bag for me that I was
already opening up so I was struggling
with uh the the takeoff a little bit but
was that like pretty normal that was
good what really because for one moment
you were still saying push uh pull but I
was feeling like I was like stuck in
like one position I couldn't move on
yeah this is what I said the the strong
force coming you should just go over
I'll try to okay to continue I felt very
weak
okay
and Landing was wonderful even though I
was about to throw up but now we're
waiting for some colleagues they're
still up there they they took up so late
admiring them all right let's get up oh
yeah that was quite an experience
I think I can now say
I Can Fly
just like
a phoenix
oh look at them whoa one of them was
making like crazy crazy Wheels almost
oh I think we were flying pretty calmly
yeah so
I think this is better than bungee
jumping
um
satisfied and now
now I need some food in my tummy
yay challenge
couplet
[Applause]
ah the end is still sudden okay okay no
that wasn't the Shaded bear I'm just
like saying because I don't think I
could do bungee jumping because like
first of all it feels like a jump into
death and
I don't know it doesn't really like you
know you can't really take into scenery
I thought this is perfect because ah I
mean it's still really scary it was
still very scary like uh during the
takeoff like until the takeoff and the
takeoff was really really nerve-wracking
but then you can take in the scenery
really slowly and it's really pretty and
like the air is really nice I don't
think I could ever do bungee jumping
yeah it's the plastic bag single what
kind of questions
nothing
like also skydiving some people when I
said I did something that has to do with
flying some people were like baby I went
skydiving but skydiving is also a thing
that I don't really feel like I have the
courage to bungee jumping and skydiving
nah like this is I think the limit of
what I can do
yeah the lady was so nice and and really
like made me feel very welcome and and
relieved she was so so sweet and and and
so knowledgeable of course and I think
I'll tangent a bit more about it
um in a future streams
[Music]
yeah takeoff is like it happens so fast
did you see my hats flew off
detail in editing
um but yeah
um it happened so fast like Oh and it
felt so like I was I was trying to run
because she told me to run but like at
some point I guess when the parachute
goes like up into the air that's when I
felt like I I was I was trying to walk
but somehow nothing was happening I felt
this like force pulling me back and I'm
like what's going on and she's like run
run and I'm like am I this up
because I'm not actually moving like I'm
I'm staying in the same spot what's
going on like I thought I'm doing this
really wrong and we're gonna fail for
like like a split second I thought this
this is I'm doing it wrong we're gonna
crash or something
yeah then then it actually really
happens so fast so uh yeah it's not
really a big deal I think I could do it
again
and I didn't get sick during most of it
only until the end uh at the end like
she did like kind of like bigger and
quicker and more curves because we had
to land in a certain spot that's yeah
probably what did it to me like all the
sudden curves even though she like still
went so easy on me like I saw the other
ones who went after us they were doing
voila crazy lots of crazy fast curves
like sheesh they were spinning and
um and at the end I was really so close
to throwing up so she gave me a plastic
bag and I asked her if like it ever
happens that people throw up and I don't
know okay I understand I wasn't gonna
tangent okay you can hear more of this
another time
all right
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was it was
incredible
incredible that was challenge number one
where I learned or proved that I can fly
yeah one of the things that I thought
maybe is one of my lacking points in
these past three years my flying skills
so now I've proven myself challenge
complete complete yeah
yes yes okay
then this last weekend I filmed
Challenge number two and this one has an
opening from Jackie and the rest is
edited by cow card the paragliding video
was fully done by cow card as far as I
know even the 3D hands and all that
isn't that so cool that's so cool it was
so good I need to do more of these Vlogs
now I'm so excited
okay Challenge number two
um this one represents the tent in the
logo
hey
all I can say is
so what
Google and I are going out she will
return later but I will not
I'll also be taking a personal day
tomorrow
and perhaps the next day
you want me to ask where you're going
no wait gooda will be driving me deep
into the European Wilderness where she
will then leave me
Uber die
or to survive
the choice is yours
foreign
okay guys take two welcome to the
European Wilderness I am here to
do a survival challenge I will prove you
guys that I can survive in the
wilderness alone because
well I am a warrior and warriors can
survive anywhere European wildernesses
tattered in all these dangerous plants
that will hurt you they will burn you so
be careful this is called a European
brand Nestle it's a little and the
first thing you want to do is find a
good place to put up your Camp don't
forget your tools of course in case
something gets in the way or something
attacks you be careful in the wilderness
now let's continue down this sunny path
here you can see a nest that wild boars
have created I'm Legit this is really
I'm telling you this is true this is
actually perfect for us because all
these little sticks and stones that they
have brought here for their nest we can
take as materials for our
campfire perhaps and if you want to know
proof about them being here
this this here is one of their Trails
okay this actually looks pretty
promising here this area
is providing perfect amount of shade for
a little tree to feel more comfortable
here and I even see some stones that we
could use uh for the fire later here
like one of these even with a little
snail on top with that little bugger
maybe I try to put some salt on this one
yeah just like the French people as the
first time I'm opening this but you know
of course orange tent first step we will
lay out
the canopy and unzip the flippity flaps
these things
this easy easy
of course it's only easy for someone
with a natural survival Instinct like me
stick them apparently I'm through here
okay all right oh
just fixing up the tent poles here well
they're really cute little ribbon yeah
it's taking shape just like the people
back in the day and in in the Stone Age
I brought the rest of my equipment we
have the sleeping bag and here I'm gonna
place a little light and we have some
some stuff for cooking let's take my
trust roofie knife
and
open up my sleeping bag it will never be
this small again
and now we have this fluffy
I have successfully captured US Foods
you can see in here ah I captured baby
chickens hello and they're called
Franklin
and uh Margaret oh Franklin just pooped
that's okay I was really lucky in the
first place to find such wild wild
rabbit animals yeah my goal is to get an
egg out of them
and maybe some meat sounds good sounds
good I have spread
some snack for the little babies
look at them look at these babies
oh little cheeks it's you guys so I'm
back to report a success story they have
created this monster egg compared to
their size it's about their their size
but yeah they totally laid this egg for
me perfect breakfast for tomorrow all
right little babies
um there's only one more thing I will be
asking of you so you know in the
wilderness you know I have to take what
I can get because we don't know when the
next Food Source will reveal itself so
I'm unfortunately I I have no choice
it's time say goodbye my lovely chickens
yummy fresh meat
yeah this will be great for a little
soup for
dinner I'll try to get some potatoes and
some carrots I'll see what I can find I
am on the lookout for something oh I
smell it oh what is this oh
some wild
vegetables this smells like potatoes I
think I smell potatoes oh no there it is
oh we've been lucky it looks like an egg
but it's the Egg of the Earth this is
looking like some
fresh natural
parsley over here have you heard of the
European carrot oh
this one maybe
doesn't feel like being made into a soup
today
I didn't
Beauty
oh oh yeah that's that's a bunch that's
a whole bunch of them some smaller ones
too but that's okay we don't judge I
have found
another great source of nutrients here
this is called
paprikum
beautiful beautiful very tasty vegetable
full of vitamins of course I think we
can clock that one out after we kill
there you go and what do we have it
looks like an apple almost or a pear but
no yeah this is what's nowadays they
like to call a paprika yes have you
heard of that before
oh what do I hear a fresh source of
water oh my that is perfect to maybe
clean our carrots right here I wonder
where that's coming from must be coming
from the mountains
oh yeah oh yeah that's a really strong
oh flow oh wow excuse me Mountain can
you be a little bit more careful thank
you uh maybe we can collect some of that
therefore our soup
and carefully
okay oh by the way I prepared uh um our
fireplace a little bit uh oh there's a
snake
it retracted its fangs all right guys I
thought it would be nice if maybe for
our dinner time we had something like a
spoon so I'm gonna try to make a spoon
out of this little piece of wood that I
found
[Music]
what do you think guys looks pretty
finished to me
um
um all right guys the worst thing that
could happen when eating this soup is
that I could like choke on it so let's
cut it up a little bit
foreign
potatoes mmm smells really good and so
crunchy as well look at that
here oh falling right into it oh yeah
the technique has to be expected from
the CEO of a big fast food restaurant
but of course I can cook more than just
fast food I've collected some wood so
I'm gonna start you know in like a
pyramid shape I'm gonna build this just
like in Good Old Egypt oh
oh oh wow an apple oh oh must have come
from here in German you know we say the
Apple Festival
so this could be indeed a good breakfast
it's actually the first firearm ever
building to be honest with you guys
how does it look where I'm gonna put the
pot is another question but we'll think
about that when the time has come what
do you think
oh I have found something that resembles
those mysterious red fruits that mume
keeps on talking about look at this
oh
oh there's a little ant
get out of there
get out
[Music]
you little
I squashed it here we go itadakimasu
it's super sweet wow
that's nature guys that's Survival did
you think I was actually gonna make a
real fire with sticks and stones now of
course not
my finger is still awake noodle noodle
fingers oh
[Music]
that was easy start a fire today don't
stop don't stop just go your own way
beautiful beautiful
I didn't bring anything to grill
properly some kind of stats instead I'm
just gonna pre-grill the chicken get in
there with a nice stick oh yeah
foreign
all right
there it goes
here maybe place it right here
I'm gonna give it some time to cook
the soup oh is looking more and more the
way it's supposed to look
wow
what are you saying it looks a little
bit different oh I don't know what you
mean chicken soup
mmm
oh it smells good here comes
our dinner
itadakimas good work getting all those
ingredients good job me
oh
oh yeah it's pretty hot oh wow a little
bit of chicken and carrot
I thought you know the egg that we
received from the cute chickens chicks
we're gonna boil it for tomorrow I'm
gonna just eat it together with the
Apple I think that's
my day
started really early so I'm actually
really tired already and the tent is
closed we still have a little bit of
fire out there to protect us I'm gonna
get into the
into my sleeping bag now and then
as we say in Minecraft
[Music]
ah guys
good morning
oh let's see
oh
sunshine is back the night was scary but
ew
well go away I don't want to step on you
it's disgusting this is literally the
most disgusting thing I've ever seen I'm
gonna eat my
cooked egg and my Apple for breakfast is
honestly enough for me honestly I have
enough of being here
breakfast was good
I'm gonna get rid of this tent now I
really want to go home I feel like
mostly the sounds are relaxing sometimes
there was something weird maybe but how
do you make this smaller again
I did see like one one Jaguar
when I was in the tent she was waiting
I'm just gonna assume it's a Jaguar lady
hey let me do this without gloves really
quickly
cut this part she was like sitting like
around here
staring at me directly
but when I opened my tent door she like
wouldn't really want to come any closer
I was really careful I was making like
these sounds like
if I try to get closer she uh
would do a really small quiet hiss at me
maybe she wanted to protect me maybe she
was thinking about eating me
who knows honestly you oh it's a weird
deal
what the is that it has like a
little Spike on its tail
overall you know I think when I was
younger
I went low-key camping before but I
don't I don't know this it wasn't really
the real deal so now I think I can say
I went camping and I would do it again
[Music]
no way please
I think like I wanna uh next time I
wanna go like camping maybe with a
friend that would be more fun I'd do it
again and I would say woohoo I would say
challenge complete
oh God I'm gonna step on all these
disgusting I'll say it now for real
slugs uh there will be one more
challenge what will it be
stay tuned stay on
the stream to find out you you you
okay
[Music]
wasn't that amazing oh my God
I love these videos
I'm so happy with them with the outcome
wow wow wow
once again completed another challenge
yay hey
only one more challenge to go can you
believe it I'm I'm just getting better
and better oh there's something
flying around I I I have learned so much
in the wilderness I am I feel like I've
grown so much and I'm like pretty much a
different person now honestly yeah
uh those slugs were disgusting the
snakes the snakes were disgusting there
are so many especially then in the
morning because of like everything being
like I guess more wet
um it didn't rain but yeah I don't know
it gets wet like more I can tell in
German we say Morgantown then there were
so many of them like I had to be so
careful where I was stepping and yeah
once again I'll tangent more about this
later on I suppose
um
in another stream I'll tell you more
about it if you want to know more about
it
did you wake up feeling sluggish
videos alone too oh should I maybe I
will
um I might I might because like you know
a lot of work was put into them I bought
so much equipment for that second video
for the camping one I bought so much for
the camping itself and then I bought
like a new camera you know I already
have this nice camera that I showed you
the cake with that's a really nice
camera
uh but
um I want something that I can mount
easily on my head or on my on my chest
um and then um I bought something very
similar to the GoPro which I talked
about before but that was yeah this
whole Adventure was expensive
iPod
you know the camera I can hike in your
future for more Vlogs like that and it
was really really uh nice to use it the
insta 360. yeah that's what I was using
not a GoPro similar to a GoPro but not a
GoPro camping in the backyard excuse me
what do you mean that was the wilderness
that there was wild animals there was
wild fruit wild vegetables wild
fires that I made
wild
snakes wild chickens yeah there was
Jaguar AKA a black cat
[Music]
oh that was it was never really really
fun experience so this challenge I have
once again honed my survival skill
yes so flying skill survival skill
[Music]
wild imagination excuse me
oh my God okay but far we go into the
last challenge
[Music]
I want to maybe
show you something but only if you
promise me that everybody who has
Twitter will use the hashtag free years
of kfp
to let people know what's going on
please
I'm just gonna change into some
different clothes really quickly
[Music]
what is going to happen
hi I'm back
bye hi
hi
so
yeah
[Music]
to get into the mood sing one more song
for you ah what the eh
hey hey
that's not that's not supposed to be
there yeah that's better okay
[Music]
okay we we
one more song Until I show you something
and then one more Challenge and then
merchandise reveal but not going on sale
yet let's go
everyone says that love is just like a
dream
feel like a mountain from the heat Love
It Feels So Serene oh yeah oh just like
that you know just how it goes
don't ever stop or you already know
you're
[Music]
good good good
loves you plus me
[Music]
for me
foreign
[Music]
for me
let's take it
I'm going one two one two three
[Music]
keeps going you know me
pineapple reveals
[Music]
surprise surprise surprise surprise
surprise surprise
[Music]
[Laughter]
hi guys whole life summer is not over
yet
though here it is right in front of your
faces
it's finally
finally off the blouse
that always had the swimsuit right
behind it
when we were asking ourselves why not
when hookah Papa Drew it so carefully
sugoite
and then two years ago
whole life summer came back
two years ago last year huh yeah last
year whole life summer came back
the girls wearing swimsuits again
Japan girls so I asked why not me
and they said
I don't know ask again next year so I
asked again next year which is this year
and now
[Music]
finally we're able to free the wildlife
three years of kfp yay
yay
yay posing for you guys I'm so ready for
the beach
isn't it getting spicier and spicier
don't you don't you feel it too oopsy I
got rid of something what happened
what did I do
[Music]
mess something up
I moved something
what did I move
this no
ah
there it is
there it is okay
yay spicy
wait I'll scroll out a little bit too
so this is how it is
this how it is
[Music]
okay
the wine was so free
[Music]
free
okay so spicy so spicy I don't know if
you can get any spicier than this but
yes it can one second let me
turn the camera on again
but for this I'll need a little bit uh
of preparation time okay I don't know
five to ten minutes but what the shorts
the shorts are staying on the shorts are
staying on on
sorry
I don't know if okay Papa Drew what's
underneath the shorts oh
okay
camera should be back
oh
yeah there it is wonderful
so
um
third challenge
as you guys may know I am very very bad
with anything that's even slightly spicy
Kiana
is
[Music]
and I mean I don't mind I just you know
live with it
but sometimes you know people make fun
of me also and you know
you know
hmm
well okay that's me too
so I'm prepared something
hot chicken flavor Ramen it's a Famous
Brand foreign
from Korea Burdock's spicy spicy Ramen
stuff this flavor is you know they're
all spicy but this is not at least not
the maximum level spicy okay it's still
spicy though I talked with Ina about it
you know probably ate like all of them
before and she like asked her like is
this sufficiently spicy for me to be a
challenge for me
uh you know because I'm like really
sensitive already I don't want to die
but I also want to suffer but not so
much that I die you know I want like
this this I want to hit the sweet spot
or should I say the spicy stuff spots
yeah
no but it may not be too much for people
who eat spicy food regularly but I never
eat spicy food and this is yeah
sufficiently spicy and sufficiently
suffering
yes inan is approved
and store clerk approved
um so I just have to prepare this though
I just cooked uh some water behind the
scenes while you guys were watching the
video uh I just have a question for
people who ate this before uh maybe
Korean Nikki
um
this I I drained water right first I how
long there's no instructions I didn't
see any instructions but
yeah for how long do I put it in hot
water because it's not with a cup it's
just this Packaging
[Music]
flap
I don't know I don't see anything under
the flap three minutes
because it's dry right you drain it it's
like yeah like like
grilled noodles or so three to four
minutes okay so I'll put this like in a
in a in a bowl
for three minutes with hot water then we
drain it and then we put all the spices
on top after we made the noodles
foreign
[Music]
about them
now I'll have to go somewhere to Drayton
as well
[Music]
okay I have like one of kiwawas
famous
uh plates and some
hey
oh yeah I need to bring the yogurt um
yeah I have some yogurt and I do have
also in worst case I have ice cream
in the freezer I would have liked to
have a deeper uh plate but this is all I
got oh it's probably fine though because
in the end we're draining it right we're
draining it
so
for that this is my first time ever
eating this but apparently it's really
well known why did I open it like this
okay let's do it like this
oh
okay the noodles themselves look uh
smell totally normal like no particular
flavoring yet
why did I open like this one I was
like okay
laughs
okay I got it I got it
oh
wait there's all the packages
underneath hello Cat you're not welcome
right now
excuse me
may have sounded like cat food to you
but it's not
that we have the Bulldog powder this is
Carbonara flavor but Ina told me it
doesn't really taste like carbonara at
all it's just kind of like creamy
apparently there's another one that's
called creamy carbonara or so that's
like even creamier I don't know why
there's two carbonara flavors but yeah
this is the I think this would be the
hot sauce that that the thing that makes
it spicy
sauce and pull the carbonara flavoring
powder
interesting what what I dropped
oh good okay now hot water we're just uh
drench it right
John
I just boiled it by the way
okay is this enough
it's like almost flowing over I can't
pour in much more but
cover the
what I have to actually cook it
oh
[Music]
okay watch three minutes
oh
is it not like the yakisoba and all that
cover the bowl
what
what I'll be fine right as long as it
gets like
okay that should be fine I mean
[Music]
as long as it gets
as long as it gets let's go
some I mean wait I mean there's like
there's like so many
um like Japanese like uh uh like instant
noodles like this where you just pour
hot water of it then you leave it for
like five minutes and it's fine
look I just find this look the same way
what do you mean what
did she goes
[Music]
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
there's I can't find any instrument is
on this I watched a video though from
some influencer I swear that I looked
there's no one struck oh there are
the flight under the flap I thought like
here uh can you see it like I thought
here but it's here oh
what does it say add noodles into 600
million millions of boiling water and
cook for five minutes
please remain eight tablespoons of water
um
well it's fun
fine probably
how are they doing should we check
sure sure
I can't fail a challenge it's getting
it's getting softer or should I go and
quickly cook it
girl
the sauce comes afterwards I know that
micro I can't no no that's ridiculous
ah but then I'm away from the PC
[Music]
you're lame
no
oh no not according to cake I'll go I
thought it's so hot though you're
saying that this is not good enough it's
the same the same thing is it not look
how like wet the plate got
[Music]
oh that
all right I'll just pour it with the
whole liquid I'll pour it into a pot
I'll get it cooking
my my my stove gets hot really fast but
I'm just plug in slowly because there's
so much water
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay it's like pretty uh soft already
but by the time they're okay by the time
I I put it into the pot now we wait
did you enjoy looking at the Wild Ones
while I was gone
yeah I took it off you missed
eyes
oh God damn it I thought it was just
like only others man oh
[Music]
it's okay it won't take long it won't
even take the full what was it five
minutes
yeah why don't you want to take the full
five minutes because it's already like
you know you know you know
don't mix the sauce with too much wine
yeah it's sad
eight tablespoons tablespoons are the
smaller the big ones right big ones you
have the reserve one instrument
I have to no it doesn't say anything
it doesn't really say so but maybe
that's what they want me to do
but
quite spicy for me you just had it for
lunch
that's optional okay you don't stir fry
okay okay uh I'll I'll I'll I'll check
I'll check on the noodles stay there
guys
thank you
okay it's heavy it's very much cooking
and the noodles are so fake
it's so so soft well
I think I'll give it like what maybe
60 more seconds I don't know one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen
uh 16 17.
18 19 20 21 22 23 24 25 26
27 28 29
30.
31 32 33 44 45
46 47 48 49
[Music]
for fifty one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten five
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
yeah okay
foreign
[Music]
are you still here guys there we go I
mean I don't know if that's like the
right amount because I actually didn't
have any clean tablespoons so I just
guessed
a good amount
the wizard done yes they are
they look uh maybe like they're a little
bit too soft but okay well first let's
add the I'm so scared maybe this was the
most scary thing more scary than
paraglia I think I don't know we'll see
we'll first add the carbonara powder
banana
hair what the go away freaking cat
hairs everywhere
special
okay let me smell
um
I see I see that is definitely not the
spicy thing
[Music]
now I'm scared
I'm so bad with spicy things you don't
even understand
oh
it smells nice though
smells nice
for now
[Music]
and I have to add oil
okay let's leave a little bit
that's that's fine that's plenty that's
plenty
okay
[Music]
mixing time
that is all of it no sorry I'm gonna do
it like this
there's so many cats here maybe the cat
has will help
to like
you know undo the spiciness
but I do have a vanilla yogurt and ice
cream in the freezer
whoa the color looks like it's a nice
pasta right now more like a cream tomato
cream pasta what are we cooking we are
currently we've reached the last
challenge of my free challenges first
was paragliding second was camping in
the wild
and now it's overcoming my
yeah
disability uh that comes with spiciness
so
now as I look very spicy I have yet to
be able to consume the spicy I just am
spicy right but I I need to I need to
consume the spicy okay I think I can
smell I'm like pretty far from the plate
but I think I can smell the spiciness
now
is the time
well I think it's time
uh
do I have to
but I mean it can't be enough said it's
like sufficiently suffering
it's it's here it's here it's here just
a cheap ass
uh
vanilla yogurt
I didn't want to get the basic natural
run because I don't like the
non-existing flavor of It yogurt
[Music]
it's really wet here
I'll go for it now
I'll go for for this bite okay it's
quite a bit I'm I can already promise
you I'm not eating the whole thing
probably
oh
[Music]
oh oh
oh
my whole mouth is tingling
but
it's okay
[Music]
okay I think I
think I'm okay
ah
I'm okay I'm okay oh
why is I'm burning my tongue
[Music]
um
when it touches the tongue it's like
it's way harder than it actually is in
terms of temperature that's what it
feels like
[Music]
me
I don't want to eat this like
um as my dinner also
but I think
I can take it
[Music]
oh
it doesn't
it doesn't taste like carbonara though
no
[Music]
I hate spicy things
but my problem like when I visited Korea
last year
I was like that was so such little
choice
of foods
because everything was spicy everything
good girl hoe okay
why why so long why are they so long I
want shorter I can't
wait
[Music]
no no not more I don't want anymore
no
[Music]
my nose starts to run now oh
no no is that you're like spicy food
don't you
did you have Bulldog before
can someone catch my nose
[Music]
but
I think I succeeded
it's it's pretty good can they make it
look
no spice please
thank you
ah yeah
I think it's getting stronger
[Music]
my lips are burning now too yeah
um
[Music]
marvelous oh the yogurt is really good
I love a good vanilla yogurt normally I
don't eat yogurt but
why am I even looking so angry I'm more
like this right now
I don't know what do you guys say are
you gonna like make me eat more of this
I mean I probably could
[Music]
yeah I I'm not finishing that no
I I mean I don't want to mix I don't
want to get rid of that oh
the vanilla is oh no oh oh it's it's
only covering up the spiciness in the
moment where it's in my mouth oh oh it's
coming back to me and I didn't even take
another bite
[Music]
I don't want to get rid of the vanilla
flavor though
finish it don't waste food you I
don't care about it this is it this is
this is an exception okay
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
um something dropped on my fight
okay
[Music]
um
right now
so
suddenly the spices inside my mouth is
kind of gone
that's weird
am I numb
I've become so numb
I can't feel it there but it's in my
throat
[Music]
flavor on its own is fine it's good
oh
Mr spice hi
I need I should I should have brought
tissues
[Music]
it could be worse I'm I'm pretty sure it
could be much much worse if I would have
taken the more spicy ones I actually
bought another package uh it's the green
one that is I think jajang flavor
and and Ina said that one is more spicy
so I didn't go for that one
oh oh I'll come back
[Music]
I think that's awesome no cramp it it
can't be
[Music]
um
my nose um
[Music]
uh
hello hello
[Music]
um
ah
suffering I am indeed
sufficiently suffering my oh around my
mouth ah
like put oh God who want my mom why is
it worse when I'm not eating it
ah
yogurt let's go yogurt
yeah gourd Yago is protecting me
[Laughter]
hold up
um
no I don't want to no
no
thank you
[Music]
he's all fast and soothe it
I wasn't I wasn't planning on eating at
all
I can do a few more okay okay okay
can I drink some water I know when
people said I can't
[Music]
um what amazing okay I feel like I need
to like
should have bought milk after all but I
don't really like milk on its own
okay
another another one
oh
wow
[Music]
stop sticking together oh it's getting
like really sticky on the sides
give me something don't go don't go away
[Music]
it doesn't even look like it's getting
worse but it is I swear
a little bit
[Music]
no
ice cream yeah the cake the cake do you
bring the cake would help
I want to mix those flavors though
it's disrespectful to the cake
no no
[Music]
um
no I'm done I'm done I'm done
[Music]
I'm done
I'm tapping out
[Music]
um
I think I need to go to hospital
I have a third degree sick burn
[Music]
no not challenge failed if anything I
completed it more than the camping
challenge
[Music]
I'm fine guys
do you want to see my merch
so the thing is that the merchandise
because right now it's like late in
Japan
um
so I can't think
uh yeah sales okay here's the thing okay
uh uh
[Music]
merchandise sales will start at 9
00 am jst uh which is like 2 A.M my time
which is in four hours from now so make
it up in in your mind your time zone
plus four hours is when the virtual goes
here and we have uh
limited limited signed version again so
just uh wake up for that I guess
7 P.M CST uh-huh good
okay and let's look at the veggie nice
it's you know I I at least plan it out
so that I would sing only before this
challenge do you see what I did there
because yeah
try singing like that that's actually an
interesting Challenge on its own
um so
let me get your focus onto
uh this uh
[Music]
where is it
ah
um
anniversary celebration on sale
September 13th jst third anniversary
merch complete set
so uh let me
let me be happy again I'll show you the
smaller things first like one by one
let's look at it one by one okay
cute no you no you
up okay
[Music]
and pen
it's a set dude I really like this one
it's a little notebook small size A6
size that you can bring anywhere so you
can write notes but it also has a little
calendar inside
um
yes and it has little Wawas on all of
the pages small Wawa helping you take
notes maybe you can bring it on your
travels as well because it's kind of
travel themed and it comes together with
the pen pen
[Music]
um
use it together it's all travel themed
it's a ball open yes
so
A6 small size it was difficult to decide
but I thought I thought smaller is kind
of cuter and we're talking about small
Wawa here so
cute right
oh it's calming down by the way
ah nice nice good I don't want to go
back there anymore
[Music]
next is okay of pack me yeah I thought
of these names your new favorite
back yay
it is a turquoise backpack I thought I
will not do it in like you know mainly
orange this time because we already have
a lot of orange merch and I thought
um especially like my male audience
maybe would appreciate a color that is
not orange for once
um yeah yeah yeah and an inside is a bit
orange with a with a cute pattern and
there's a rubber rubber yes rubber kfp
charm attached to the side and yeah
there's mesh Pockets at the side that
maybe are stretchy so maybe it should it
could fit maybe I don't know I didn't
test this but it could fit maybe a water
bottle
um and yeah and there's several
compartments it got a kfp rubber patch
as well on top the rubber charm rubber
patch cots
[Music]
you know it's the same color
tatas right now
yeah I am excited to see this one uh in
like in person at some point I'm excited
you don't mind wearing orange yeah but
you know it's just nice to have
different colors for once right
so next we have oh yeah and also volume
approximately 13 liters I don't know if
that really tells you anything but yeah
next
[Music]
yeah so as you can tell by now by the
latest it's travel themed so there's a
nice rubber also rubber
um luggage tag that you can put on your
suitcases or elsewhere I guess uh I
guess you could maybe also use it as a
pass case and put it on your bag and
then put like
um like in Japan they you know they like
to use for like a Subway like traveling
with the trains you have this like car
that you just tap maybe you could put
that in there I feel like it would be
the right size but whatever normally
it's supposed to be on a Suitcase suits
it's rubber rubber rubber
really cute comes with the little paper
inside to write your name address phone
and email I guess and the cover
copyright local on the paper
cute
so and then if you buy the complete set
purchase bonus you get a Polaroid this
time I thought maybe I'll try something
that I didn't do before which is a
Polaroid it's kind of small but I
thought it would be cute because it's
like very I don't like to give you a
sign Polaroid and this is what you'll
get yeah and then I suppose if you get
the limited one you get like the real
signature from me on the Polaroid I'm
not sure what I'm signing
probably the Polaroids then
yeah yeah because also now with the
birthday ones we have the postcards that
have the stamped signature and we have
the postcards that have my real
signature
yeah limited now you'll have time to get
ready for this
and as I said in four hours now it's
three hours and 45 minutes when it will
go on sale
[Music]
foreign what Wayne can fly too
wait no wait no wait no why no where did
you see wayna
oh my God I missed it what did she say
you want one really
the luggage tag yeah Wayne also traveled
a lot so it's useful
um
so back to the beginning
so we have these items small Wawa and
Note and pen that comes as a set a cave
pack me your new favorite backpack which
will be very spacious and uh you know
good for traveling we have the beach bag
but now we have the backpack yeah I
think uh you will want to use it for
different occasions this one is maybe
better to bring to conventions or really
just every day I wanted it again I
wanted it to be very
um you know not not too much in your
face like hey I'm I'm a YouTuber fan if
you know you know but if you don't know
then you know it's just a normal
backpack yeah very subtle and the cute
small luggage tag and the Polaroid style
bromide card for uh the full set and
limited edition is real signature from
me on top of that hey that's my number
tonight is for the Third Year
Anniversary my my personal solo
merchandise
[Music]
yes yes yes yes
yeah
and with that
it concludes my
beautiful beautiful third anniversary
stream I prepared so much for you guys I
I really hope you enjoyed it I was like
really really worried about what to do
until like recently a month ago I was
like what the do I do on my
anniversary like
I don't know what I can do anymore that
I haven't already done without 3D I'm
like but here I tried my best to make it
entertaining and the videos I'm so proud
of them I'm so happy with them and they
were like great experiences so I might
upload them separately
um feel free to watch them again when I
upload them yeah yeah yeah thank you so
much to cheggy and especially Kyle
carrot who like worked so much uh until
uh yeah until today in a short amount of
time to edit the videos with me yeah
thank you so so so much
yeah yeah you guys are the bestest and
thank you Spirits now for the logo that
turned out great to exactly how I
imagined it and wanted it thank you
yeah and thank you to kfb for all the
lovely gifts the videos are crazy
the videos are absolutely crazy yeah
I'll I'll try to continue to give back
to you guys
um and do my best as I said in the
letter
uh in the upcoming year the fourth year
we are now entering the fourth year
members anniversary is also coming up
soon
and also uh 1.5 million subscribers is
coming up soon so exciting times are
continuing don't forget to also stream
uh my album to support my music if you
would be so nice
the album is also currently still
available for physical
yoyaku physical purchase physical
pre-order so you could bundle it but the
album is supposed to be sent out way
earlier than the third anniversary
um merchandise so if you want to bundle
it you save some cost and shipping I
guess but
then you'll have to wait longer for the
Sparks dark remix
yeah yeah but it's exciting times
prune through from the first day until
now and going forward it will it will
hopefully be
continuously exciting I hope uh things
will go well for me and for you guys
going forward and man three years sounds
like so crazy and it's so magical
and I'm so proud
to have been able to do this for such a
long time
and I hope I can do it longer
so yeah I'll do my best please continue
supporting me
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
this is like almost like for for
European times and for Asian times it's
more like the day after tomorrow well
actually now it's tomorrow in Asia so so
uh so more like tomorrow
we have the myth five hour uh
anniversary
relay as you saw on my schedule
um
let me see if I can pull it up again
[Music]
this is it
this is happening or actually in about
24 hours
uh it starts on Kelly's Channel then
after one hour we move to my channel
then after Now we move to Ina's Channel
and after Now we move to kula's channel
and after Now we move to ahmed's channel
it's kind of going through the night for
me
yeah it's probably gonna be more like
six hours actually because the last one
on Amazon's channel is going to be a bit
longer and yeah we might be announcing
something during that stream though
during those streams too maybe uh but
yeah
yeah if you want to celebrate myth three
years with us then that's where I'll see
you next
year
I might be the first right to be doing
uh anniversary stream today I think Ina
is doing one next and then after like
the solo ones afterwards it's Cali I
think I saw she has a reservation up
but then we'll do the collab ones too so
you know I think myth was able to get so
many people into vtubing three years ago
or after the free after like you know
maybe after one year or so
um so I hope you guys will check us out
maybe even for the first time in a long
time yeah have some fun with us
and we will try to entertain you as
always as we like to do
um
you guys are the reason I'm here and you
guys are the reason why I'm here oh my
God oh my gosh what the coincidence
thank you for being here today I'll see
you again and in German we say
I love you guys
[Music]
bye bye thank you so much for the super
chats I'll be doing Super Chat reading I
guess I should probably do one
[Music]
thank you guys holy
yeah I should probably do it its own
stream holy thank you guys you guys
are incredible thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you from the bottom
of my heart for giving me a place to be
and the reason to be
and the motivation and oh my God I could
go on and on
thank you for everything
[Music]
maybe maybe next year
we can be together again bye
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]
make sure to tweet something may it be a
screenshot or just your thoughts with
hashtag free years of kfp and make sure
to be ready for the merchandise we were
unable to do it during my stream this
time but I hope you'll be ready when the
time comes yeah
foreign
[Music]