[Music]
so
what is that memo
huh
that's so old i i haven't used this
screen in like a million years i
then i had to like clean up some things
here
okay
that was i guess minecraft really really
old
i'm 3d
yeah because i was pretty in the music
video
hello everybody
ah unfortunately i cannot present myself
to you and my
uh white or black outfit
but
you can
i guess turn down the saturation on your
screen
and get rid of the orange if you want to
but why would you why would you orange
is nice too
um
i'm gonna request it i don't think they
will do it and even if they would do it
then they would probably take a year
uh but
realistically speaking
oh it's fine um even if it's just a
thing for the music video we're gonna
celebrate by singing do you a million
times and then um
and also in between i guess i could talk
a little bit about do you
do you want to
hear some stuff about you
um
of course you do
yeah
thank you thank you soon everybody so
far for the support
on my new song
secretary
[Music]
new song did you like it do you like it
do you do you like it
i don't even have to try it comes
naturally
oh yes we do we do
i do
i thought so
okay
let me put up
the jacket
oh
just for
promotion's sake oh [\h__\h] speak
you
small here there you go remember uh like
more than a year ago we did this for
sparks and since sparks is by the same
person
[Music]
i thought
we might as well continue the
celebration
i didn't do it for free or not i know
but you know i thought you know
tradition because i did it for the other
kira song so
yeah i think that was more than a year
ago yeah
ah so i'm gonna sing for like two hours
i'm not sure how many maybe i think last
time how many attempts did i get in 20
i feel like it was like around 20.
i'm not sure how many
we can fit in this time because this
song is either longer or shorter i don't
even know didn't even look at that
it's a banger isn't it oh 22.
it's such a banger do you is such a
banger but before we start talking i
should start by singing it once at least
okay
uh
let's go
it literally starts with let's go just
want to wear my lyrics
there we go
[Music]
it's a very busy song actually just
honestly i don't think the song should
be sang along alone that's why i got
another kiwa to help me in the music
video
but don't have that today
don't have that luxury now
yes
i have to sing it alone but you guys can
sing with me
[Music]
there's something special about you i
see you i know it's true
[Music]
i can break through and that should
scare me but i don't know baby
[Music]
if you know play the game maybe
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i just can't resist you your
love hate all the same if you know play
the game
[Music]
oh
pick me
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
it should be on your country spotify
uh whenever it turns midnight
is it already midnight there and you
don't have it yet if yes that's a
problem
or it's just not midnight yet so i'm not
out here you're saying it's like i ate
more hours okay
5 a.m
but you see it right on spotify don't
don't tell me there's like a problem
here
4 p.m 10 p.m okay if it's past midnight
and you don't see it let me know because
then i know someone's [\h__\h] up
and
anyway let me like make this bigger here
like my new song they like my new song
it's been in the works for so long
cronie
do you want to hear it again crony
[Laughter]
do you do you do you
one one for crony
oh thank you cronini
do you
crony
okay one more maybe this time i won't be
swayed by the harmony that i hear in my
instrumental
[Music]
and that should scare me
you kept
[Music]
oh
you crony's eyes are like a spell
i can break fruit and that's just scary
but i don't know baby's captivated
[Music]
you decide
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm always coming back
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
i tried to fit in her name as often as
possible without losing the lyrics
completely
credible slabs oh thank you crowded
oh such a fun song
[Music]
that was um do you by the way if you
haven't heard of it yet it's my new song
coming out today streaming services
midnight in your time zone whenever it's
midnight check amazon music hopefully
spotify
itunes and so on i would hope
blessed rooney
what song is up next ah i think it's do
you
do you anticipate never do you
i have some ideas for some spin-ups too
by the way also i i got some you know i
have these old backgrounds do you
remember these um
this one remember this one
or this one
i used to use this back in the day
oh oh this one's the holy holy stuck
kiwawa one stuck can't move anymore
please save me
ah i'm in too deep and i love the rush
yeah
and then we got this one
oh this one's new i think no no this
one's not new apparently i had this one
before
wow sparkling
ooh sparks very sparks
oh yeah this is the wolfy sparks
background
remember oh yeah this one's new
we're in the matrix now baby
let's sing to you
[Music]
i don't wanna stop here
playing question roulette
[Music]
there's something special about you
you all know it's true
[Music]
i just can't resist you your eyes are
like a spell that i can break through
and that should scare me but
[Music]
oh
you got
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
love hate all the same if you know play
the game i just closed all my windows on
the screen
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
making me
i'm always
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
all right all right all right stop the
dj stopped at me was like i didn't
really close it i just you know
sometimes when you move a window and
then
everything else just
like minimizes itself what the [\h__\h] why
would you do that so annoying i'd have
to open
uh
so i got a reply from a
considered holocaust but god damn it i'm
at the states that whoever i ask it's
like schedule problems like
uh
there's like three certain people i'm
trying to get into my whole talk problem
a program and uh
like one member i asked and then
the whole communication process took a
week so then i had to move it to the
following week and then the following
week
was ng for them so then uh
i asked another person of those three
people if that following week which is
actually next week sunday saturday would
be okay for them but their schedule also
doesn't align um so i think it's gonna
be another week again
oh i'm so sorry guys uh
i
i want i want
i run supervised whole talk but oh man
ah
um
wait
now this current guest
is trying to gaslight me
saying like
oh yeah we'll talk that's it i think
that was on something like that before
and i'm like no you were not
[Laughter]
no indeed um
you were not
let me send a sample though a sample
okay
nice keyboard noise that's not that's
not the good keyboard
i i just brought up the archive
christmas bgm though might be coming
back to us again soon
because holy [\h__\h] it's been getting cold
maybe it's cold outside
oh
i had to do your keyboard asmr oh just
tapping along to the
yeah yeah now i want to do a different
um i don't know if i can really tap
along to do you it's really busy but i
mean i might not have an idea i'll try
one thing
do not before do you
um
speed up version
let's see
uh it
doesn't make me go faster for the two
hours but uh
i might as well try you know so let's do
here
i have two different speed up versions
in vlc
let's see this one
okay
oh by the way
was the audio balance good so far though
it's hard to tell because it's really
loud in my ears
oh i feel it
i don't want to stop it yet
[Music]
your eyes are like a spell that i can
break through and that should scare me
[Music]
if you want me
[Applause]
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
how can something so wrong be making me
feel sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
yeah
that
at least the beginning
it still felt like this could be it this
didn't feel that off yet
but i promise you when we go backwards
it will feel off again
and one more one more speedia version
oh
gotta go fast
gas guys guys
guys guys
do you
guess guess guess
okay so now i think this one was 1.2.5
but this one will be 1.5
unless wait does it go from
right let's go from here and then
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
all the same
oh
[Music]
making me feel right breaking me down
pick me up
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
oh my god
no time to breathe
damn
oh god
it's cena
let's take a break and talk a little bit
about um
uh do you do you want to talk do you
want to take a break
i'm talking a little bit
oh my god
do you rape
i was like like super hand banging but
my 3d doesn't capture my forward motion
with my head as much as it should
sideways is pretty good
or like if i go like like like this yeah
but only my head not so much
um do you need a break yeah
you guys are gonna annoy me with that
for a long time aren't you and do you ki
mama do you
do you do you do this do you that do you
do you do
[Laughter]
my pose is like 180 and me too
mine too
do you do you say you do you know [\h__\h]
me like you play but no i never read the
same
[Laughter]
let's talk a little bit about do you
um so
maybe you remember that oh man let's
let's turn on some btm though maybe you
guys remember
this is double
your hair is double or
once
double okay
[Music]
ah
so okay do you remember
blue
do you remember
uh when i was on the vacation with reina
in
i looked up i guess it wasn't may
may i guess i felt like it was earlier
but in may
i
i first received the demo
with like already the same singing in it
and all that
from kira for the song
while i was on vacation i remember i was
like me and elena we were sitting on our
balcony above the water
and in the night in the dark dark night
on the i think it was i think it was our
first night actually
um and we were like just chilling there
and looking at our phones and then i'm
like oh nina i just got my
my my new song demo
that i was at this point still planning
to put out for my birthday
uh
but yeah it didn't work out like that
but i i like listened together with dana
to the song to the demo and we we were
like damn
[\h__\h] this is a banger holy [\h__\h] i was
i was like shocked
chuck had the
yeah
because
when i
requested
another song
um i basically gave
kira the producer who also made sparks
like
some
references to what i wanted it to sound
like
so obviously we went for a k-pop
direction
um
yeah i gave like examples of like i
don't
know
because i really love einstein's songs
yeah
um i don't know like how much of that
inspiration is left in the song but it's
definitely like a k-pop banger now
and i feel like
due to it being like inspired by that
like like by by k-pop idol groups
now it's a song with so many lyrics that
uh it's a bit difficult to sing alone
like that's why i need backup vocals
because um even like already in the
beginning there's like overlapping
lyrics
so yeah it's very busy i wonder how this
would have been
uh like if like an actual k-pop idol
group got this as a song
to perform and like how they would have
separated the lyrics maybe who knows
maybe one day i can
[Music]
like in a in a concert or so i can do a
special rendition where i sing it
together with other girls who knows
yeah um
i was planning on releasing it like
like a in the week of my birthday or a
week after my birthday or so
um because now here's the thing the
reason why it came out so late is
basically
uh
in terms of music alone we could have
probably released it already at that
point
if we wanted to
but i wanted it to come out with the mb
and then you know originally
um my birthday concert was not supposed
to be made by kanauru but it was
supposed to be made by um you know my
own company
um but that didn't happen
and i also you know had a lot of
troubles finding a
studio and [\h__\h] many travels
and
uh
yeah so then i i had like i felt like i
had no choice and had to ask hannah ubu
but i already had kana ubu planned for
the mv at that point like we were
already talking about it
um
yeah
was already planned and then it was like
oh can't do both at once have to
prioritize
yeah
uh
even even by prioritizing the concert
you know it was still
not much time as you saw because a one
hour concert is more content to make
than
a song
so then i had to
sacrifice my new songs timing
and
release it later on yeah which is
unfortunate but gave us a lot of time to
make a lot of improvements and [\h__\h]
which i don't talk about after singing
to you one more time
do you
[Music]
surprise
do you
oh [\h__\h] still sped up no no no no
no i don't want that
this will sound kind of slow now
probably
[Music]
there's something special about you when
i see you i know it's true
gotta get in your eyes
[Music]
your eyes are like a spell that i can
break through and that should scare me
but i don't know baby
[Music]
if you don't play the game baby
[Applause]
[Music]
your eyes
same if you know play the game
though i can fight the feeling
[Music]
all right
is
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no it's so short
i i i think i had a stand before
and now it's so short no no ah
it's like a floating microphone well
all right microphone you get a break
we got a full body version
[Music]
full body
but maybe maybe we can go to my stage
to a stage you want to go to a stage
oh
all right
[Music]
when
i see here this is where i left my mic
stand
oh there it is
there you are okay now i can put it
together
how does that look
wait we need to we need me to be behind
the mic i i am going to i think i
remember that
yeah yeah like this oh yeah
oh yeah
okay stay straight
just honestly if you just look at this
like that
i just look like my my my life 2d
version right is so on point
just look like left to d
oh but i can go like this
okay
this
this should be about right
photo realistic
indeed but you know what version is up
next
we went faster then we went back to
normal now we're gonna go slow how about
that
but like
hmm should we go 1.2.5 slow or already
1.5 slow
slow
down
let's go step by step
i am
there you go
no idea how this will feel like
[Music]
got me
i just can't resist you your eyes are
like a spell that i can break through
and that should scare me but i don't
know baby you're captivating
[Music]
hey all the same if you don't play the
game baby
[Music]
so you can't save me i'm
[Applause]
[Music]
but i don't know baby
you decide if you want me
[Applause]
[Music]
me
pick me up just
like do i'm always coming back
[Music]
[Applause]
and it felt like it took five years away
from me
that felt so long
even though that was only 1.215 but it
had good vibes yeah i felt especially
the
the chorus had like a good
good bounce
do you do you say you do
do we want a slow
acapella version how about that
do you slow acapella
yeah rhythm was still nice i agree
but for dad i want to change can i
change can we switch it up
[Music]
we're not
at crunchyroll expo oh is that me is
that me oh hello
okay but i want to change the matter
do you
[Music]
i need to have everything at my disposal
a few logos here and there won't hurt
okay
[Music]
i'm waiting by the way my dear musicians
for remixes
you know exactly what i'm talking about
right
did the drum drum the drum
then yeah yeah the drummer yes i want to
hear the drum version
i want to hear the reaction it's always
nice to hear the reaction in those
covers because he's always like he never
heard of the song before and then he's
like wow this the songs last oh wow i
didn't expect that it's like an
interesting life reaction at the same
time
by the way two hours is not really much
of an endurance uh in terms of streaming
but like singing the same song over and
over it can get boring so that's why i'm
just leaving it at two hours okay
i'm gonna try
acapella but wait my songs
let me
uh where were we just now on the stage
right
stage stage
here let me just pick up really quickly
on the songs dunk your [\h__\h]
you didn't say that you didn't see it
you just did not see it
oh god my throat is already dead haha
let's go
let me sit straight for this one
yeah you do not see
[Music]
i don't wanna stop it yet
playing russian roulette
yeah boy as soon as i saw you
i
knew it baby it's you oh yeah now got me
left drunk i'm knocked down down down
there's something special about you
when
[Music]
oh girl you know it i
just can't resist you your eyes are like
a spell that i can't break through and
that should scare me
but i don't know baby you're
captivating me
and in the end you'll let me go
love hate all the same if you know play
the game i'm locked up up inside no i
can't fight the feeling and i won't try
love hate all the same if you know play
the game baby you'll decide if you want
me then shout it out right now
love is just a game i can't complain i
do the same
oh do you
do you
say you don't feel the same spark me
like a flame i know i'll never feel the
same oh
do
[Music]
don't ever let yourself fall in you got
it cause love's just like a toxin the
way pain is so common your problem i
can't solve it i'm just a fool in love
know that it's more than a crush
so you can't save me i'm in too deep and
i love the rush yeah
i
just can't resist you your eyes are like
a spell that i can break through and
that should scare me but i don't know
baby you're
captivating me
and in the end you let me go
love hate all the same if you know play
the game i'm locked up up inside
no i can't fight the feeling and i won't
try love hate all the same if you know
play the game baby you decide if you
want me to shout it out right now
love is just a game i can't complain i
do the same oh
do you
do you say you do
feel the same spark me like a flame i
know i'll never be
[Music]
got me breathless i am i'm by you
nothing day how can something so wrong
be making me feel so right
breaking me down down pick me up just
like you do
i'm always coming back to you you you
love us just a game i can't complain i
do the same how
do
[Music]
do you do you
love me too
[Music]
do you
oh that was the first try if i
like you know kind of planned it out
maybe maybe that could have been more
more emotional
that was fine yeah
maybe maybe you know i think with
hinotoni
someone made a jazz version and then i
sang on top of that maybe someone can
use this version and make a jazz version
out of this the other way around
i have uh i can't breathe that's my
problem today there's always a problem
asthma be like [\h__\h] you do you want to
sing [\h__\h] you
that's okay that's fine
[Music]
i can't breathe in deep but that's okay
only small breaths are loud with this
song anyway
oh thank you guys thank you guys for the
super chats by the way
i um
i might do a super chat reading tomorrow
so that witches can can take off all the
anniversary super chats at least
yeah yeah but i also i will upload the
schedule for next week so don't worry i
was just kind of waiting for the whole
talk
confirmation and now i have the
confirmation that's not happening this
week i'm sorry i'm sorry
oh one more hour halfway through we're
kind of slow this time i feel like we're
slow because i also want to tell you
about you know
do you do you
so
let me turn it off actually let me i
want to tell you a little bit more
um
you know tangent first do you do you
the whistle version
um i can whistle but not that well that
i could continuously whistle for like
three hours three minutes 18 seconds
but
anyway
let me bring out some busy ammo
oh that's so loud i'm sorry
[Music]
wait i thought it was slow that it
slopes down
ah back to normal please
okay now
okay so
one thing
i guess people
maybe want to know about is the decision
of making
uh do you
the girls
me
you use it again
into two colors
so
actually
that was originally
like merely a decision of like how um
like you know i wanted to do a 3d music
video so i can show off the dance
because if we go kept up then we go full
kpop
with choreography i wanted to dance but
i figured that my default outfit in
orange with the belt and the hats and
all that it's not gonna look good for
this style of song where i'm trying to
be serious you know
so i was like discussing with genma i
asked if it's possible if it would be
allowed
to change the colors of my official
outfit for a 3d music video
and then i was told yeah i should be
fine actually in theory
and then i went a little bit further
because once we got started i this is
why uh preacher was in the special
thanks because preacher was i didn't
know who else uh so i was like pretty do
you do you
have the capability
of like recoloring my model are you able
to do that so
thank you preacher
and then
you
uh then
you know i got the like um first drafts
i like i told i gave like a sample i did
something in photoshop i think
and then i
yeah we tried some some different
patterns like um different colors
like i changed the blue into the pink
and then the orange into the white but
then
uh
you know question was like what to keep
the same way and what what exactly to
change
and some things worked better than
others so with some trial and error but
then i was like
you know it still bothers me to have the
the belts on
it just
it just doesn't work with the concept so
i asked can we go a step further and
remove the belt is that possible and
recoloring as well
and surprisingly it was possible
so we basically just drew
on top of everything and then there is
no more belt
amazing i mean the belt the belt is
still there but like the the
the
attachment you know the attachment on
the belt and the attachment on the on
the chest we got rid of that
and then i asked to get rid of the chef
hat as well
[Laughter]
um
however it still somehow sneakily made
it it's made its way into the music
video which i saw i noticed pretty late
on that in some scenes
uh like i noticed like three four days
ago i noticed ah got it
my hat is there
why
but i didn't want to annoy kanauru with
you know
fixing that because i wasn't sure how
much effort that would take so i was
just like okay i guess whatever you know
what it doesn't stand out that badly in
the white outfit
so
i was like
it can't stay justice once um
it did not happen with the black outfit
um
yeah so i think with the black outfit it
might have bothered me more but in the
in the white outfit scenes generally
everything was very bright and so on so
another little white hat
didn't
bother that much yeah
yeah yeah it can't be contained on you
rico looked awesome right i was really
happy with it that it like looked so
good and then in combination the the
black and white outfits in combination
with
um the
backgrounds that by the way were also
uh
highly directed by me
i gave also a lot of samples from kpop
videos like oh i want the backgrounds to
be like elegant and big and like have
this kind of structures like i don't
know huge curtains whatever i don't give
a [\h__\h]
you know big big big clean
surfaces um
yeah
yeah yeah yeah so we got that
going pretty well
now with the black version i had like
some struggles i wasn't sure do i want
the sleeves to be black as well do i
want the socks to be black as well
oh but yeah
i think i think the way it uh was in the
end is the most balanced and like at
some point it just looked like too much
like
a little bit weird
i think this way it has a good balance
so i really like the black and white
versions uh
and thanks to that like actually
originally i was just hoping for one
version
uh and then i was like how about we try
i don't know which one was first black
or white but then i was like how about
we try the other way and then i liked
both so much that was like maybe we can
have both in the music video because
kpop music videos usually have a [\h__\h]
ton of different outfits and i mean it
takes a long time
um
for
like 3d outfits to be created so i
obviously didn't have the resources or
the time for that for this music video
so i had to do something with the outfit
that i had
at my disposal
um so we played around with that and it
worked out so well and then i had two
outfits for kangaroo and he was also
like what do i do with this as he
tweeted out today
but here we go even further
um
at some point you know i was like uh i
requested a choreography to be created
by kiana again my choreographer
and
well you know uh like we started talking
about what i want what i wanted to look
like and i said wow i wanted to look
like a k-pop choreography again i gave
samples you know
i said i want some recognizable moves i
wanted you know to be very k-pop-y um
but still like feminine and elegant i
don't know and again i gave i zone um
samples could love izone
[Laughter]
and um
[Music]
uh you know kiana knows k-pop very well
so she captured that very nicely
but at some point i was like in the
early stages i was like
maybe we could
have
a choreography
that is
like
we've made like like two different
choreographies
for two different people
so
um capture it twice two different parts
and then put it together in the music
video
um and then kiana was like yeah you know
what i mean we could do it but then the
more i thought about it about you know
than having to learn two choreos
and also one choreo
for like general use when i'm dancing
alone
uh i don't know overall it then felt
like too much of a complicated thought
i was like discussing
how we would put that into the music
video but i thought it would fit well
because we have a black and a white
kiwawa and what if they dance with each
other but have like different
choreographies you know but that they
come together well but you know i had
this idea but then i thought
maybe
maybe too complicated
uh
yeah so kind of ditched that idea
it was very ambitious it's not
impossible and maybe in the future i
will i will do something like that maybe
yeah i just i just kind of you know i
really like um choreographies where
there's interactions but as a solo
artist
not being able to do that it's kind of
sad because like through interacting
with each other there's so many so many
more new moves that you can come up with
and then also since the song already
sounds like it should be sung with more
than one person and it's so busy and has
overlapping parts i thought it would be
perfect you know those were my thoughts
but then i did the idea because it was
too much
so however
i don't think i ever um
i don't or did i i'm not sure i don't
think i ever
talked about this idea with kanaroo
and yet he made the two cuavas dance
with each other
at in the music video which is so cool
in the end and
they still they danced the same choreo
but i thought it fit so well especially
when they were dancing towards each
other rather than facing frontal
when they were dancing with each other
in like a circle
oh oh it was so hype so nice yes
ah that was really cool
and then you know that kind of tied in
again with the theme of like
having two two colored monochrome
kiwawas and when i look at them i think
of
yin and yang
and that's why i came up with this um uh
jacket idea by the way that was my idea
had them posed like this sleeping next
to each other
you don't see the whole picture but
originally i wanted to have a bit more
of their body shown so you it looks more
like yin yang
but yeah this was the best we could come
up with yeah my idea was you know we
balance each other out and
blank and wide
yeah
yeah yeah yeah nice cover thank you
yeah yeah i i put a lot of thought into
all of this and uh i think it turned out
like a really really nice
balanced um final result
yeah and um
since the song was already done in may
uh
i already like i mean the mix took a
little bit longer but i was able to
dance with like the the demo tamp
uh
with
the lovely voice
of the lyricist oh my god her voice is
was so cute i was like what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
we should just release her version
because it was so cute but thanks to her
i was like able
to
i i did copy a little bit of her singing
style because i thought it was so cute
and and it has you know a really sassy
vibe you know the wrapping parts
don't ever let yourself falling you got
it because life is like a toxin
those parts i kind of got inspiration
from the lyricist um
she has a really pretty singing voice
very sassy too
really sweet voice
and then yeah with that i started
practicing the choreo and then that was
another one of the things that was
recorded at amish studio
yeah
but there was way more time to like
process it i guess like
uh i thought i thought there would be
like some scuff again and like early
versions of the music video
um i saw
like the fingers were like bent over
like do you know the part where they
dance with each other and there's a
close-up of of white quinoa and black
kiwawa and they have their hand reaching
out right
and they're like do you do you say you
do
that part the fingers were like
completely bent over backwards like as
if they were broken and i'm like okay
well i guess
oh i guess that's fine
but somehow
by the end of it by the final version
that was fixed i already thought this
was it but
wow yeah somehow somehow
we got it fixed
um
yeah so
overall like
glitch-wise nothing really bothers me my
hips maybe are a little bit dislocated
here and there
[Music]
but
besides that high quality thanks to
giving ourselves all of us a lot of time
uh as much time as we need
to finish it up nicely i wish i could
have released it earlier of course but
whatever this is fine now it's out now i
can finally continue working on other
things and now we will sing do you
okay
[Music]
how about that
remember i should go somewhere else
how about we go
[Music]
i'll go to the usual room
i barely ever use this place so you know
gotta make use of it let's change gloves
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
i fix the chat
it's a yeah oh it's a new usual room i
yeah yeah some people may still not know
it because i didn't i only showed it
like once or twice
it's a bit of an over-the-top usual room
with a mecca behind me
yeah anyway
[Music]
yeah i don't wanna stop it yet playing
russian roulette yeah boy as soon as i
saw you i knew it
got me love drunk i'm knocked down down
down there's something special about you
when i see you i know it's true
gotta get your eyes now now now if it
ain't you baby
oh girl you know it i just can't resist
you your eyes are like a
[Music]
know play the game i'm all locked up
inside though i can fight the feeling
and now i'm trying
if you know play the game baby you
decide if you want me
oh
[Music]
so you can't save me i'm in 2d when i
love the rash yeah i just can't resist
you your eyes are like a spell that i
can break through and that should scare
me but i don't know baby
[Music]
and i won't try all the same if you know
play the game baby
[Music]
got me breathless i am by you night and
day how can something so wrong be making
me feel so right making me down down
pick me up just like you do i'm always
coming back to you you you
[Music]
is
[Applause]
another one another one in the bag
wonderful
are you feeling comfy in this room guys
comfy
do you feel comfy
do we want it
[Music]
[Applause]
who the [\h__\h] wants to sing that because
it's gonna be off-key you know the thing
is like i can make my voice lower but
then
you know i'll it won't fit with the
music
do you
um chris i will call it cursed i don't
know why you guys always call it wine
it's [\h__\h] christ
[Music]
hi hi so like this oh my god
no
no i don't know
it just [\h__\h] sucks
i hate this
right you wanted it
oh [\h__\h] you know this [\h__\h] really [\h__\h]
me up cause i hear a different key in my
uh ear
[Music]
it's so [\h__\h] up
i don't wanna stop it yet
[Music]
like when i did um
wide but then added a
tune to it
how does it what does that sound like
just sound normal now that's funny
i guess it doesn't like work together
okay
blah
[Music]
if i just sing higher it should work
right
[Music]
now there's something special about you
when i say you want the
[Music]
i don't know what questions sounds like
i just can't resist you your eyes are
like a spell bag
[Music]
if
i just can't resist you your eyes
[Music]
love hate all the same if you don't play
the
[Music]
game again
reality
[Music]
[Applause]
making me feel sorry
i'm always coming back
[Music]
[Applause]
oh someone [\h__\h] killed me
no
i'm so cursed god no no please no
uh casper and satan are you [\h__\h]
kidding me this was
you asked for this okay
it was definitely cursed i think it
lived up to its cursedness
what the [\h__\h] was that
okay i want to do a version where i
focus on the harmonies how about that
there's not revenues for the whole song
but quite a lot of parts
let's see if i can remember the
harmonies
we have like half an hour left
do your harmony
it's focus a while since i recorded it
so i don't remember all of it but
they're slightly you can slightly hear
them in my instrumental so i'm trying to
listen to it
[Music]
i just can't persist you your eyes are
like a spell that i can break through
and that should scare me but i don't
know baby
[Music]
is
[Applause]
pain is so common this has no harmony
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
i think there were more harmonies and
some are also not even in the instrument
also i can't remember
one more normal
do you
do you no not normal we do bubble bubble
version
[Music]
which means
wait
i need to
i need to bring out my pacifier oh no
oh
[Music]
wow
play
[Music]
[Applause]
is like a milky milk
[Music]
maybe you decide if you want me
you have to support my neck
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
ah
cursed
meow
[Music]
wow
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
now
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
meow
[Applause]
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
oh
yeah confused cat this
i
love cats so much
i love my kids
i love them so much nothing is more
blessed on earth than my cats
they're the cutest cutest sweetest
bubbles do you frog version oh dear
uh how about
how about the anzu all-rounder version
so we have i can do frog
i can do elephant
i can do a dog
coral
chicken
what else can i do out of nowhere
maybe food food
sheep oh yeah
okay
maybe maybe
oh valley girl oh god maybe we'll do a
valley girl version okay as well
afterwards okay okay do you want me to
do chicken [\h__\h] you
shut up
horse ah i don't know how to do a horse
i haven't done a horse yet
okay we'll try with these couples
do you do
do you even zoom
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
uh
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
oh
what [\h__\h] am i doing
[Music]
[Applause]
i tried i tried to try
in the end or somewhere around the end
it was just making random noises hoping
that they would sound like some animal
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh man
i didn't involve
duck
dark noises goddammit
oh man
my family disowned me wow
[Laughter]
why no
yeah i think some parts even sounded
like what a fox would say
the fox basically says anything
okay normal version we need a normal one
we desperately need a normal version to
um
make up
like people who come in and they're like
this is your new song what the actual
[\h__\h] we should like make it up for them
and also i want to change room again
change room
[Music]
how about
german stage
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
didn't take over my oh wait no no
actually it should be there it should be
there
yeah there it is what's the other thing
here this one oh
for my german debut
i used it the other day
okay
chet is back we're using all the
backgrounds oh maybe i should change
to
uh german german chihuahua i i did not
prepare a german version i am sorry
maybe another time
builds to this tool
i'm ender is this off no i'm spiel
i can come up with something
i could probably come up with something
it's two weeks too
but not now
i'm not ready for that
okay
[Music]
there's something special about you when
i see you i know it's true
gotta
[Music]
your eyes are like a spell then i can
break through and that should scare me
[Music]
do you
you
[Music]
[Applause]
and that should scare me
[Music]
oh
how can something so wrong be making me
feel sorry breaking me down pick me up
[Music]
we have like 10 more minutes of do you
do you wanna hear more do you
yay
thank you by the way so far you guys
have been very supportive of my new song
i hope
to see
lots of more support and if it's
midnight in your country then please
start streaming it on your streaming
devices so that i can make sure that for
the coming songs i hopefully also have
a better budget
yeah this one was a quite
expensive endeavor
i went quite a bit over budget but i
think it was worth it yeah
yeah you know all these creators
ah
i just i just love working with them
tiana always makes great choreographies
i'm so glad i found her
like i didn't i didn't find her already
you know her from before yeah
and um
yeah kira you know since sparks i was
like i want to work with kita again
surely sometime
but not every song obviously not every
song should be from kira even though i
feel like there's so much potential
kira and kiara but yeah um if i would
put out a full album of kita songs i
would probably be broke
yeah um but worth it i think for making
my my kpop dream come true and kannado
also like in combination with
the nice choreography we made a dream
come true a perfect
perfect k-pop music video although i did
definitely have to um
uh get kanodo to hold back quite a bit
like i think the first draft he sent me
it had like still so many
kfp references and all that in there and
you know i love i love having references
and memes and stuff but for this video i
wanted it to be really serious so i had
all that
kicked out supposedly
no chickens no eggs
no random whole life references
um
yeah i feel like almost sorry because i
probably held him back because i'm sure
he likes to put in a lot of funny things
um and that's like like part of like the
reason why when he does these videos
because he wants to make funny videos
with references whole live references
but when i i held him back i'm sorry but
you know for the sake of this i think
i think uh we both agreed that having a
clean
elegant look
uh turned out really well and and like
one of the reasons i wanted that is
because i wanted it to be mainstream
friendly the whole song
including the music video
i wanted it
to not be weird when you show the music
video to someone who is not a be tuber
fan or who is not into that kind of not
even anime perhaps maybe even
i wanted it to be as
yeah
mainstream friendly as possible for that
purpose
to maybe
i'm getting some more people listening
to my music um
so please listen to it and show it
around i don't think i don't think you
have to be ashamed about you know this
song
no i know not at all
music videos
[Music]
maybe in the future we'll get again some
music videos with some funny references
and all that but i i i just wanted to
fit the vibe and the atmosphere of the
song
[Music]
sometimes meme version yeah i don't know
if kanoru has time to make another video
like that
i know the very busy
but if he wants he's welcome to
release a more mimi version
i'm actually planning to upload some
youtube shorts
in the coming week
uh
with
you know some you know you know like
those tick tocks where you dance like a
part of the the
chorus or so i want to do that so like
we'll be using the dance data that we
already have
to make some videos like that
they're not
created yet
but
they should be relatively easy to make
yeah nothing special just like a
no camera work just a normal video where
i'm dancing the choreo
and you'll see it a bit more clearly as
well but also just you know hopefully
the algorithm will spread it and then
people are like oh this song is nice
also this this choreo is nice maybe
maybe
ah i don't have a chihuahua tick tock uh
maybe i can get on the whole life tick
tock um
yeah
cause home life has a tick tock right
we put it on there and then hopefully
it will spread and people try to copy
the choreo that would be cool
that would be sick
um
that would be so nice you know like
marine senpai also did something like
that and actually i think some people
copied it
some people
did make tick tocks to her
hey hey
[Music]
you know that one where she sways her
hips
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
even if it's just a few people it would
be cool although the choreo is not so
easy um
[Music]
one can try right good luck good luck if
anyone wants to try please do
another
order
okay
now let's sing another one
do you want to hear another one we're
almost at the end
do you
screamo version if my throat wasn't
[\h__\h] sorry i can't deliver i just have
to sing a normal version
oh val oh god okay i can try
that don't ya
actually a lot of parts already sound
like uh belly curl
valley attempt
like oh my god
i don't know if it will get across so
well when i'm singing
because i have to follow the melody but
i'll try
oh
[Music]
if you know play the game like stop
upside though i can fight the feeling
and i won't try love hate all the same
if you know play the game baby
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
love hate all the same if you know play
the game
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
got me breathless i am for you
how can something so wrong be making me
feel so right
calm down
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
no oh god that was paintball
oh dear stop making fetch a bang
it's not a thing
oh dear god can we just be number for
once why don't we have to play these
games
do you
how about a
oh we're oh no we're almost done
no
how about ah
[Music]
no how that was that was basically fetch
how was that
i was thinking of doing a longer version
but then i wasn't sure with this song
because it's like so busy if i could
really manage a longer version
i could probably do three hours but no
it's midnight now almost so
let's see
i mean the last one should be a normal
one
this is a new song called do you what
british accent version oh [\h__\h] hell i
don't know if i can do it i can try
how does a british person say ooh ooh
i don't want to stop but yet
[Laughter]
there's something special about you when
i see you i know it's true
[Music]
sorry
so you can't save me i'm in too deep and
i love the
[Music]
you kept
love hate all that same if you know play
the game i think i got that one down
[Music]
[Applause]
how can something so wrong be making me
feel so right like this [\h__\h] accent
it's just wrong wrong wrong
i'm always coming back to you
[Music]
who do you do
[Applause]
[Music]
you want me
god
i'm so sorry that was
weird accent
this is called a weird accent
everything else would be an insult
okay
last one
[Music]
i don't wanna stop yet
no it's true
[Music]
i can't complain
don't ever let yourself
so you can't save me i'm in too deep
[Music]
me
if you know
[Music]
oh
how can something so wrong be making me
feel sorry
[Music]
oh
oh my throat really hurts you know this
song gets really high in the chorus
singing that so many times
now i'm dead i did
do you do you just want to go to bed and
watch some netflix
and cuddle with quito
yes yes
thank you oh my god okay tomorrow i'm
making the schedule tomorrow if that's
okay it's already some there somewhere
there in my google calendar but um i'll
make the graphic tomorrow
and
oh god i'm so hungry too
a schedule coming up but in the meantime
please watch
do you stream do you watch the mv stream
it on streaming services please please
please please
please
would you please consider streaming my
new song
a lot
so that i can
continue making more music
please if i can't go outside on youtube
online
it will come out on streaming services
if it turns midnight in your country
um
thank you
thank you worked really hard on this one
gave it a lot of time to become perfect
the way it is now
and um you know made my kpop dream come
true so please please give it lots of
love
yeah
thank you soon i'm so hungry does
youtube music count uh i think so
probably
your passion show thank you
[Music]
it was a very eventful day
uh
but yeah
i think i think finally
being able to show uh have everyone
listen to the song and hearing you guys
feedback and it was a nice
nice end
yeah yeah to this arc of creating do you
and now
uh for a while
i think there will be no more original
songs because i will
start working on an album i guess
i think i'll guess i'll start working on
an album
properly
yeah but it will take time probably
i don't know also in the coming week i'm
assuming the myth song will come out it
should
it should come out
so
more music though more music don't
forget to
um wait for that and then support that
should be out on cali's channel when it
comes out um
yeah
yeah it might be on the 25th perhaps
[Music]
mm-hmm
and it's on kelly's channel
anything about covers yeah i i on the
side i i will try to um put out uh for
blood
soon hopefully
the art is actually done
and i mean i know this song so i can
sing it quickly then it really depends
on the envy and the mixer um yeah maybe
maybe in october end of october maybe as
like a halloween cover
would be nice because i think the like
four blood is not spooky but it has kind
of i think still a fitting atmosphere
because of the blood you know
yeah so i'm aiming for that
um
thanks for listening thanks for
celebrating together
do you release ya
[Music]
have a nice evening yeah have some sweet
dreams listen to do you hope you're not
sick of it yet i've listened to it a
million times more than you guys did and
i'm still not sick of it
okay for today i'm maybe sick of it but
but tomorrow we can go on
thank you
ah wait oh [\h__\h] i forgot
uh
[Music]
and in german we sell videos in
bye
[Music]
do
you