[Music]
[Applause]
I
[Music]
oh hello oh my goodness guys it's been
it's been a long time guys oh it's so
good to meet you oh my god I've been
I've been held hostage
for for
ages it's been it's been I don't know
for how
long thank
you two weeks almost yeah oh man I I
yeah I was afraid to stream because if I
streamed I knew they were going to kill
me they were going to kill me like no
joke am I I'm safe
now
oh yeah but I'm I'm done now I thought I
was done when I was like oh yeah I'm out
of this joint woohoo and then they came
back with a bunch of other homework and
I got so b i i I told you this story um
in the collab yesterday but I was so
bummed out that I was just working on a
booknook until like 3:00
a.m. yeah and then now I don't know but
I think it's okay to stream
now yeah anyway Let's uh let's
start
okay
H oh God it's so
loud
what I have no idea how to play this
game welcome back we missed you I missed
you too I never thought I'd say this but
I really wanted to just
stream
oh I really just wanted to play games I
just wanted to like do things have
fun huh
yes I am ready to
spawn oh God the sensitivity on this is
insane hold on uh give me give me one
second
uh wait hold on uh audio okay good yeah
audio is good I don't know if we're
going to use like um proximity chat or
not are we role playing I don't
know
um what what just
happened anyway uh where what was I
going to do I was going to do
this okay oh and then turn off motion
blur cuz uh there was motion blur and I
don't like
that uh
uh H
off oh good okay I think I got a friend
request what about vsync I don't know
the it's pretty
peaceful my my computer isn't like
busting V SN off does that make a
difference
okay V
s
off yeah I think I'm in the server am I
not supposed to be in the
server should I get out of the
server open challenges window
why okay these challenges aim
you uh pressing a track
a and then w
sick okay plant fibers wood and small
stones go
uh
okay it's
gone e oh maybe I just press
e no
what the
heck oh I'm already Gathering wood this
way oh okay I'm I'm already doing it I
guess just punching it out of
existence
punch well this is one way to collect
things just like Minecraft I mean yeah I
guess but it's just that it's unexpected
coming
from such a realistic
game
what oh that's a rapid
dog oh wait
ow
hey hey hey hey
hey ow
bro I'm going to
die
already can
I bro what
the why is that dog so
strong e
spawn near my
backpack oh I came back from
life where is my
backpack playing s minutes to shut up
oh that's plant fiber why is it not
Mark is it just so obvious that they
didn't mark it you know what it's so
easy to gather stuff I might as just
oh
ooh what a
reset what
o wait no no no no it this is my invent
what am I
thinking oh my God no wonder oh God what
was I
doing are you thanking tonight I don't
know um I've been thinking a lot these
past few days by myself I finished save
the
diver uh I finished arcade
Paradise yeah I finished arcade Paradise
it's uh been so long
and um I'm still playing Dave the diver
is that me is that my dead
body I don't need my
body
okay double you no Tab and then
W no
W okay sick
now okay
what was the quest Mission thing a no e
q e d
f no that's
text
W why oh thank
you bro why why why is it not q q for
quests duh um okay track a
all right
equip I have to drag it can I like
double click it
no all right Pine
Forest what
is Pine don't go there that's a crazy
dog oh this is definitely
Pine as it's going to take a while
how do I know if other people are on
this server I'm pretty sure I'm on the
server press
M wait am I the only person oh oh God
okay wait I am other people are around
it's just I have not
did I do
it where'd it
go
why oh
redeem okay I got experience points cool
okay some tools using your empty hands
stop I hear a
dog what's
this ooh wait punch it
punch okay this taking forever never
mind cuz some
tools are better than others
using your empty hands to collect wood
and small stones is fine but a good
Stone wait I already did this oh Harvest
small Stone how do I do
this
this oh this
one oh I did it okay
okay
why redeem and then
redeem and
track okay when
warn uh blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah
tab primitive outfit W hey that's a w in
my book okay and then wear this how do I
wear
it wear
this wear
this I'm wearing it now oh
no how are people sending me friend
friend
requests what how how is everyone I'm
naked I'm not naked I'm basically naked
how
what how are they how are they doing
this and the Allies I have
allies since
when press press
W press
W this is
forward why are you playing solo well I
heard that you can only be in the voice
chat um when I bump into someone and
right now I am not bumping into anyone
so
press Tab and go on the far right to
click an
envelope there's an
envelope
this
oh oh cool okay okay okay so this is all
like accepting
gotcha
okay
B
equip equip
oh
oh wow I'm doing
it map should be m of course okay
good wow nobody is around that's
amazing okay
why redeem and
redeem I don't have to click it I can
just press W what am I doing uh a
a okay
tab Club
W and then have this and now I'm going
to why is it bloody whatever
why and then
W and then
a can't I just like accept
everything why do I have to build a one
by
one okay
what is it running towards
me kind of
slow
ooh okay now I'm I'm going to craft a
stone
Arrow hey
h
h ammo is
here and then I shoot how do I shoot I
shoot sick
okay then why
w
www
o good job Survivor you've proved to be
capable with much potential we have
marked your map with the nearest White
River Outpost location there you will
find a Trader where he can buy and sell
goods and trade stories with one of our
friendly citizens welcome aboard Noah
okay
on screen
navigation oh there it
is so let me see
this okay aim with this and then that
okay
wonderful okay
sick I don't know how to cancel I just
switch
weapons revenge on the dog I didn't
really have much it's okay the dog can
just
live or should it maybe I'll just kill
it maybe I'll get some meat out of it
but then what if the dog has
rabies that's not good
then all right okay I'm going to craft
some more uh arrows
I don't know how many I
need wow people are so
Advanced wait hold on isn't this a good
thing that there's a base nearby then I
can just loot that place first
okay that's uh that that was not a good
sign I can't see my stuff maybe a
despawn that's a zombie I'm going to go
okay
so everyone's probably around where the
trador at so
oh
H there are a lot of traitors I
see they're probably all around there
I'm kind of far so once I go I'll I'll
be able to bump into
someone no I'm pretty sure that's it see
like look at the top
right says I'm getting closer
can I
swim can I catch
fish
no you are oh
what
huh B what's v v v v v v v v
they did say that the proximity chat
here was
broken it's working for everyone
else hold
on hold on I got to check
this
audio enable voice chat
Mumble
positional needs to be enabled within
the Mumble client what is that what does
that
mean they're in
Discord okay oh okay
well look here boys we got ourselves a
real life hero and now he wants to be
paid
Yeah Yeah by or bu no well there's a
[\h__\h] door why don't you use it hey
don't be mean land claim
block land claim block land claim block
okay okay good where is everyone
map I have never seen anyone around
here I am playing a single
player
unintentionally where is anyone someone
died
here I thought you can only join the
Discord call when they're around I have
not seen anyone as the
thing look at the map and zoom
out what the heck why are they all the
way over there
wait where' they
go wait hold on everyone's there
everyone's there what the
heck oh
God which way am I facing um okay go
straight from here
can I can I put a marker it's a good
point probably I
can save
Waypoint
what report
no show on
map did I do
it no I
didn't just right click
quick
wayo
oh okay
hold oh no
okay see they're probably using text
because they're not close to each other
right why else would they be using
doesn't make
sense it's okay I will join Discord when
I bump into
them because that was what they said and
everyone's together which is why they're
in the call at the moment there's a
bone so I will join when I meet
them okay does that sound good Probably
sounds good to
everyone what's in the farm that's a
very good question um I feel like oh
this one's dangerous um
no that was like two skull points I
don't think I can do that yet
huh wouldn't it be funny if by the time
I get there everyone's
gone that would be really funny
okay
punch loot the house on the right don't
tell me what to
do but I'll check but there's probably
going to be a skull point there so
oh this is okay this is doable
okay
what
die
ow wait they're really
strong ow wait hold on they're really
strong I can't do this
I think I'm still a bit too weak for
this
ow okay surely this would be okay right
there's no one oh there's no
one why do I feel like it's already been
looted
why are they
open oh
search
ooh okay those are feathers I don't need
that
[Music]
uh h
that um that was not
cool uh-huh yep okay
yep uh
ooh what's this break okay no I'm not
going to do
that no that thing wasn't dead I saw it
breathing why what happens when it gets
dark
the monster has
[Music]
come well I mean they're already around
so should be
fine wait that doesn't make any sense
how come there aren't any during daytime
but then suddenly when it becomes
nighttime
oh my God I think those are people
maybe
humans are these
humans oh these are humans okay now I
can finally go into the Discord
he this way point if he wants to trade
he should come to us that's right he's
not going to do that I
think by the way
hello oh
hello oh I found
people
yay
wa wait you guys are all wearing
something why aren't you wear where's
your hat there's a hat yes put your hat
on
what over there
it I will craft you a hat oh oh wait no
I see a hat oh thank you yes put it on
Oh
yay civilized
down down I he's
not
yay why um he's far I don't know how to
share the way Mark with you guys what if
you s like a am I missing I can send a
screenshot gloves I'm missing gloves oh
there it
[Music]
is e the craft anything just
yet
there land clim box
wa me is this our Base by the way
yeah we should probably do multiple
campfires what is this land claim
Block it's our home base now with this
basically zombies won't spawn around do
you see it I put it in the channel of
the map what if we all put our land
claim blocks like around each other so
they won't spawn with an a yeah let's
let's protect the house okay yeah I
don't have though so where can't do
anything how to make land claim block oh
I have a land claim block um I don't
know where to put it though uh it won't
let me put it
anywhere they already claimed this land
yeah is there a maximum to can only one
person claim a
land I don't know how are you cooking oh
this is that's not me that's Kelly here
maybe here right out a way to F this oh
yeah I can't put the land clim yeah it's
a pretty it's a pretty lar I'll just put
it here I am dying of
hunger we need to unlock the
re let take look at claim this land put
it by the river
land maybe here oh we need cooking items
oh we need cooking
skills
thank youus is put at the fireplace
can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking and a frying can so we
can actually here here
yeah oh I found a I found a cooking a
grill outside the house I don't
know some water we have some water in
our inventory here near trees and rivers
is there a town
nearby uh there's a town very far
[Music]
away o at the hell
that's to eat scary food this is
nice oh you guys have a nice campire out
here
wonderful the idea that I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different
[Music]
excursions that would be
greator
I'm
here hover the
river she's here here here I don't know
what to
do well I I think I'm going to focus on
finding
[Music]
food CH too if anyone wants to go on an
ex I'm going to collect items I'm going
to gather stuff so I'll stick around the
house
okay I will debate on what to do I might
debating uh how how
how is it
here a cornmeal oh can I eat
this yeah realistic it sucks huh find I
can't eat corn meal I can't oh I
can o yummy
cornmeal you have
to eliminated
um how
evil oh dear why what a terrible
person I think you need a pot c a
bedroom okay bed yeah me too oh
there bed where did I put bed violence
between our allies is concerning very
concerning how do I know when I'm not
hungry how much do I have to eat I have
harvested what theck okay I think I'm no
longer hungry soon why why
why I'm sorry I don't mean it what uh I
don't know what to do oh oh I hear
them I don't need it I don't need it I
try to get oh I have to sleep inside
about my stomach
okay uh
someone zombies I'm going to try to like
build walls or something I don't
remember how
to oh we're not supposed to sleep
outside but it's so beautiful the stars
look beautiful no sleep inside stop
talking to my stomach that way how' you
that's
awesome I mean to be fair we don't have
closed doors nor windows can we sound
oh oh that's not
good
oh what
happened what the anyway I think I build
a building block I hope this item is in
use
ter you can't what the heck I can't man
building is hard
I just destroyed us at this
point see so% bad compared to zero
building
block double why do I have so much
wood my
first I'm hoping to just put a block
here so we don't have Windows that
people can see us through good idea
people yeah these zombies can't watch
us watching our sleepovers what kind of
weird thoughts know
weird weird dots or weird
thoughts swear okay that's the building
block okay can I open the door or
no help there's a weird
zombie M there's a weird zombie outside
M scaring
crony a candle what's this I know where
to put this no fear huh ladies I know
who to
Woo you're not afraid of
anything there you go I hope she do we
need any more doors
anywhere I think we're good I think they
all look pretty
healed how' you Bo them up
Kiara I just want to place a door
somewhere
where oh this is
Minecraft
yeah wow we have camping songs the
acoustic guitar how do I craft it I have
a
kazoo oh hey there's a deer here we can
eat unless it's a zombie deer come here
deer a can we just
nap it ran away you cannot sleep like
Minecraft
sadly oh no it's evil
Minecraft more Stone nice I just need
more
wood do I heal if I sleep at
least no what's the point of having a
bed just I
beating
things I'm low on stamina and I'm
thirsty so much is wrong with
you you guys experience thirst and
hunger you got to turn it on here weird
at the right you see a bunch of wood
make sure it has fuel and then you just
turn it on like
this does this building block even do
anything we have curtains that should be
good destroy a broken block BL I don't
know the difference
I have to join a party um a recipe I
think how do I join a party you can join
ours Oh
yay uh allies wait no
party like a
variant invite
meori can invite everyone right I wait I
received a party invite oh sick uh I get
too I'm currently not in the party I
can't aim and arrow
yay thank you and
then just press
buttoni you need a party
good do I need a party I think I'm in
a
yippe yippe
[Music]
man I am thirsty my character is like
never satisfied wait how do you
experience
hunger what oh
okay so
privileged I know my
invent oh now I'm hungry okay
welcome to the
gang the bone knife
haries is it safe to go outside yeah
it's safe yeah you can go out okay yay
one it's not too bad right
now because it's day one why do I need
to build a wooden door though dog with
glowing eyes you think that's I'm so
excited I think so are you sure it's not
hoko
bow oh that's not a good
sound shift a click or shift
click
Shi oh wait oh my God claimed area
unless they allow you have a
curtain place to can you not build in
the house
area somebody in my chat just wrote yeah
we can't Place anything in a claimed
area but I don't know they can allow it
apparently I place
stuff I blocks oh hold R okay let's try
with this one no it just
rotates oh if you like do
this hey that's my stuff wait I I
thought it turned into a wooden
block I'll just I'll just pick it up oh
I got to repair it I'm sorry get animal
St anim I thought it turns into wooden
BL
see trying to cover up our
uh oh yeah yeah like that yeah yeah if
you
want y if you right click with an axe I
don't see any animals I prob need to up
yeah go hunting wait really find that
bunny I think you just need a stone
axe oh don't you need to like upgrade
with stone really like I have the axe
yeah or
maybe
oh oh you need more wood I don't have
enough wood I guess oh5 uh I have 87
broken
oh so thirsty anyone got a
pot no we don't do pot around here no
pot here I'm out of here not in this
household you will we all starve without
that
pot that's a maybe you should do
something about
[Music]
it how do I pick this
up I can't pick this up what you trying
pick oh a block this block that I placed
down it punch
no I'm not getting St from this try
using an
axe God damn it I have to break it why
is everyone
dying oh thank you so
much okay I'm thinking may we should go
get a pot a pot yeah we
should not because G wants it want a
pot let's go to the farm and see if we
can get a pot what if we die
maybe not at night we're willing to take
oh God the zombies can crawl on all
[Music]
fours okay I'm leading it to you see you
guys getting down oh my God I don't have
stamina are you down no no I'm just
really
tired oh there's my base I'm I'm eepy
weepy weepy everyone's dying
I think just having my base cloth would
be
good just want to fix my stupid Stone
EG oh it's just gone gone can't that's
why I need
Stone
uh I'll get some scrap
metal is that you hitting the car oh
yeah you know it girl you and your
vandalism oh yeah car my way I'm going
to destroy it man what if it's like from
Pixar though you're going to get us in
trouble
oh they so naked watch it actually sedan
why I I got a magazine for like making
cars from a
[Music]
zombie that in a maybe oh I already
learned it I'm hungry again oh my God
right you're the car person now that's
your job I am the car person now let's
go
supp that's not a good
sign
scary I have too many all right I'm at
the farm in case anyone wants to play
Harvest
Moon okay is there a monster there yeah
it's really scary probably oh it's
breaking it down
oh that's a big
one I'm hiding in a big that's a big in
it it's a big
one uhoh why people dying yeah I'm
trying now make the stone
axe I mean I could have fixed one
probably um I think it's
over what's wrong what happened I think
he can have it he can keep it he not our
house I'm shooting him I'm shooting him
get
him oh he's dead oh no he's not dead
okay he just faked
it how many arrows can this guy ow ow
all right I'm heading back there oh God
okay I didn't want to use this but I
suppose I
will oh I'm I love the corn response
okay I hope I don't miss this what the
wa you have a gun I didn't want to use
it you have a gun where's my other Arrow
what the heck I stole all the
arrow oh sounds like a
clicker all right I'm heading back is it
a lot of zom zoms no we got rid of him
he's gone now there's a bit
what what are these noises I'm
so oh yeah that's the dude that was
chasing
me oh crap I'm out of
stamina
bam oh no here you get him the front I
get his back I'm
infected what you're infected we have to
kill you
now infed with ligma what's ligma
thank you Lima I wonder what it
is oh man here eat some corn maybe I'll
heal you you think it will I doubt it no
but it tastes good we can eat some
popcorn some corn corn or some popcorn
corn M yummy sounds really good all of
that do a house you guys but I want to
wait till it's daytime before going
there I trust you even though you're in
infected oh thank you I think in the end
we'll all be infected eventually that's
sweet that's good to
know she's giving us her
Lima yay you don't want it uh I it I
feel you already have it I mean you
already have it gigy no it's not yet I
haven't been corrupted
yet all right then it's about time I
must stay away from me I won't get L
much
[Music]
today hi
bombs you seem very knowledgeable can I
borrow you for one second in the voice
chat okay I am moving to three okay oh I
hear zombies why do I hear
grunting that's me place a
campfire bro what what are you doing
here get a room the pap that's where we
live I don't know you sound constipated
though oh no I'm I'm thinking right
now wait she's not in this one oh never
mind anyway
Oar huh okay must have been the win must
have been the win oh there inside the
zombies inside that's not good that's
not good how do I drop this how do I
place this
down uh guys we went on an adventure but
we didn't really find anything so we're
back a a I'm sorry oh sorry well welcome
back you did good is this really our
home we broke through the
door the good news is found cilia cilia
oh really yes
I fought that was from the
zombie like oh my
God no no I thought it was for the
zombie I thought oh my God this guy has
a lot of loot
wow how do I get back
[Music]
my I have to go to the traiter again huh
you
read it's okay it's okay if I find now
you know has a backpack
that's well yeah if I if I find two more
magazines I'll give them to you I'll
donate them to you no worries no worries
it's
question do I
get how do
I I use an ax for iron sure about that
probably have to find a rock
and
it just a stone pickax is fine sorry
Stone ax I guess
or something what cute frame oh I can
make grilled corn now I
find how can you make the grilled corn
baby that I Ed a magazine to learn
cooking skill and now I have cooking
skill
up I want to find a
magazine oh okay
I I need a cooking grill but if I if we
have a cooking grill I can cook the core
I think there was a grill behind the
house you need the cooking grill at the
fire so everyone can cook then yeah I
think the best way to go about the
magazines is probably to like share them
in the sense that like oh okay one
person does all the cooking one person
does this because otherwise we're not
actually going to level
anything I have I have two skill points
in cooking already so I guess I'll hook
she's going to be our cooker let me
y I have coin I'll drop it give me your
I should also look around chest the how
do I put this candle down I can't
place got the right click left
click I'm going to Fone wants to to
f to VC I'm going to get materials if
someone wants there
punch
okay am I supposed to be punching corn
do think yeah yeah punch the corn and
then you get it but but they have like
not dead corns so the green ones oh God
damn it yeah most of them are
dead that one looks alive oh thank
God did you say we had a c somewhere no
I didn't see it um I'll leave although I
am
hungry do we have to steal a cooking pot
or something yeah yeah it's I
think oh we also need to find a source
of water and like to boil it with a
pot okay do you guys want to try going
to oh my
God I'm it turns out I haven't read your
magazines oh really okay oh you can have
them back here I put them in this crate
here the magazine something that
anybody did they disappear afterwards
yeah they disappear
after thank you I'm
trying
corn oh
[\h__\h] whoops I didn't mean to say
that I mean oh shoot oh no oh darn oh oh
gosh
darn goly oh
golly thank
you
nice hey
big together the club is better know
Club crafting skill okay okay I'll go
with kie if anyone wants to go Callie
and I are going to the
farm I'm not going to survive with I'll
the farm soon oh my
goodness can you guys bring like food
and water I'm
dying make the stone a and will go fast
oh food cornmeal you can make
cornmeal what is this and then you
eat I have a feeling we're going to lose
all of the resources around the
house how do
why how does one eat
eat it's like you're learning how to be
human
[Laughter]
again how does one get hungry where do I
put the
F I'm
[Laughter]
learning where is
it how does g just let me know you want
to go somewhere okay if you see on the
map I'm at a gas I'm at a stiff tool
station wow we should go to the trader
and do quest to though the trader gives
a lot of
stuff okay I yeah I went to the trader
before and he gave me a gun really far
one yeah it was on the way on the
way I spawned quite s and that was the
trader it sent me to all
right I think it's safe to go alone to
the trader uh at daytime it is after I
explore this stiff tool area I'll come
to okay yeah I'll
join okay we all have the Traer in the
same location though I think
sotic okay okay oh there's a snowy
area I want my snow we to
be there's scary dog in there what
bright red alpha eyes no it's the alpha
dog all right I'm uh making sure our
home is up to base or up code or
whatever than
par there's a castle up there we'll have
to have enough wood
though do we have enough
doors oh nice we do have never have
enough doors honestly
don't I actually used doors to slow them
down
pretty there's a
castle CLE yeah in the snowy area oh my
God that would be good for later see
down what do we need for the T yeah my
Char is so thirsty I am also very hungry
right now yeah don't be hungry I sick of
it I just don't know how not to be we're
sorry we are commoners we're
peasants how does one become hungry oh
okay now I'm very hungry I
guess you have learned the ways of the
the common folk ah yeah so this is how
hunger is yes unfortunately
shov oh oh no I'm
hungry I am searching toilets don't
worry I'll find food can you find water
in there oh I found some water in the
toilet let's go oh no anything is
helpful can I
eat you okay yeah we're trying to get
resources yeah we're trying to help
you for the resources you can leave them
in a crate will all be sharing them okay
if we get the cotton plants then you can
make them into bandages and
heal oh this is not
good how do you ever heal from an
infection you don't you
die just accept it do not get
infected I'll accept it you're dead good
to know maybe you just have to have
really good Hy and it goes away
eventually I don't
know I have accepted this way of life
a why there so many dead
corn I don't know what they can be used
for but I have a feeling that they're
all good maybe I can make more doors
what antibiotics and honey honey honey
are expensive
do we have to kill them kill the bees
yes K the zombies yeah do we have to
what are you a zie
apologist I don't know I feel like you
know they might not be that bad they're
trying to kill you only answer is
kill I'm going back home where is home
where is home home is on the map press
thank
you no problem when gets scared Common
Sense kind of
disappears I hear zombies I just let's
going back I'm just killing one it looks
like the weather is turning gloomy oh oh
very
yeah half 7 a.m. or 7 700 p.m. in the
game I think 7 a.m. 7 a.m. okay I think
it's 24hour clock okay good oh scary
yeah I know many of you guys are scared
of this yeah they killed my family I
know how can I make a f that's so
unfortunate I I can make a magazine for
that would be a better idea yeah uh I
think you need to make a farm plot block
you need Rotting Flesh for that riding
zombie zombie yeah I so I think you have
to get the zombie and maybe if you
destroy
them oh they're in another voice wait
hold on shouldn't be that hard to find a
zombie in the rain like
[Music]
this hello hello hi hi what are you guys
up
[Music]
to killing stuff
a may I may I have the agility book
please yeah sure let me find a way to
give it to you hold let me drop it okay
agility and then I found a medal Journal
do we have a medic yet oh I want it to
do medic if that's
okay use it I I'll wait until the until
we reunited with the others because
maybe someone else already used some
thank you so you can keep it for
now do it for now okay do you guys want
to try going you know when you look at
the map the RO do you want to try going
further east if we can find any
buildings sure well there's one house
that we haven't looted that I actually
open in this F okay okay oh that's our
BAS where is base and then we
go back to the
baseer
yeah the base is um do you see the red
green square on the map where we are
like right next to it it's like a really
big Square
yeah rectangle looks like a Swedish flag
or
something and
then the th Ro to the west and then
there's one little building with like a
little Loop and that's where our
building is our house oh okay yeah thank
you I think I
know you want to follow me I can take
you to the place that I busted open okay
wait for me I'm sure okay we'll walk
slowly I have a RP
walk I don't
know but I think she's talking about
this rectangle
thing yeah I still have this candle cuz
I don't know how to throw it out and
like you know I had it in the house so
so I wanted to put it back but I
can't oh see see rectangle I told you I
know my
stuff
what so like this thing is kind of
getting on my nerves right now the hold
wood door like what do I
do where
is oh you can replace a broken
door oh wait in that case I'm going to
be really
helpful wa hold on okay I got this um
wood door oh it's
ugly oh
oh you can hear the fan oh my bad see
it's been getting kind of humid lately
so that's why I have the the it's not
the fan it's the
dehumidifier so yeah let me do something
about
that there we go
okay let me
move crafting Under Pressure oh god oh
we can plant
trees first was for
planting okay okay oh this is cozy we
going to go without I'm so close I'm so
close to home I'm coming okay let's just
Farm some resources for now we all right
I see everyone is split up oh there's a
building BL
okay
okay so what are all these storage
crates are they all just like stuff that
we can call our
own no it's from other people probably
yeah I think everybody has their own
little storage grave for now
okay I just put the I put food in one
storage crate since we'll all be like
hungry so hungry we are
starving seems like I can name it we
have a lot of rocks we can repair it
right if you guys go near the farm
please collect more corn okay please
please okay a
pot oh
we
close ah oh we can label the
crates let us know down down when you're
good do you want to go
to V tree okay let's do okay
let's Okay this and I don't even know
put that candle there I am so hungry and
so thirsty and there are so
many
people monsters GG I mean this in the
nicest way possible but everybody's
starving GG you're not the only one
here only one Starving in here and I
need you to give me your food I'm not
feeling so well
either by tax by tax I am I am starving
personally about to go forage for stuff
cuz all I have is corn and I'm sick of
it
stick of corn yeah although if you go to
the farm please collect more I'm going
to go to the town hope uh hopes of find
but please get me more corn where do we
get
water you have to find a river and then
I think you still might need pot or a
water bottle to collect water from it
are you kidding me right nown can you
turn snow into water maybe you can drink
from oh it gets heavy
here all right I'm about to one off see
you guys goodbye goodbye have a great
one how do I craft the tin land M no
that's not what I
want corn
Pizza I don't know about corn
Pizza
[Music]
plant corn is a luxury you should be so
glad you even have corn
is it safe if zombies ever
come oh let
see I found a
hospital a hospital a hospital who wants
to go to the hospital I want to go to
the hospital we can cure your ligma here
yay they up the supplies oh okay
cool
Hospital oh wow you were really far oh
am i d
yeah I found a town I was trying to find
a grocery store but there's not one in
here oh there's a grocery store I love
shopping I love shop we can shop at the
hospital it has five death
skulls oh wow wow I that let's
go I love
that I'm sure there's food in this
Hospital of five
friends I am going your
way yippe
[Music]
yippe so gigy did you already do the
like digging Quest from the the traitor
yeah I did the digging one you're so
fast I walked yeah walk oh on the way to
you guys I went there how did you you're
so damn
girl he gives you a
gun so friendly
yeah gun see that's
nice maybe we should get guns before we
go into the five friend hospital or we
should just go in you're on your way
I'll
wait well well then let's get
digging rather than the gun i' prefer
some water and food but okay maybe maybe
at the hospital they'll have water and
food they might yeah you're in Deer
hosital you would expect the hospital to
have
water see oh that would be a welcome
sight more dead than the zombies yeah
compared to the zombie oh
[Music]
no that would be
terrible ooh
purse oh what oh wait oh that looked
like I don't know that looked like
Chanel
maybe they do Rob the zombies of their
no no no there was a there was a purse
lying around oh
me some Louis Vuittons
maybe at them
Gucci who died and left his Prada bag
here for me oh that's
crazy at this day and age of the
Apocalypse wow
apoc I'm very hungry your maximum
stamina is reduced how do I know
that oh I love the Chikorita residence
the
bananas is that Chita
yeah I learned about that one today what
why did I pick up an office chair
Chikorita how's my inventory this borita
chor Chita
bananas I'm eating a raw
egg what's the go in this Quest so yummy
do I just deep dig deeper and deeper
until I find something yeah you
basically just dig down and around in
that Circle until something pops up for
you sometimes it's pretty far
down damn I'm hungry and
thirsty I mean this in the nicest
way we're all suffering here
I'm
not maybe we should just convert to
zombies now I decided to stop
suffering oh that's a spirit thank you
yeah yeah yeah I'm out of stamina this
zombie is going to take me out of my
misery
die maybe life with a zombie is easier
maybe maybe they don't need like water
and stuff so I'm not
dying getting
closer I can probably drink
glue GL probably did you do that when
you were a
child well I'm thinking myself a grave I
[Music]
realized come back
is the trader evil and they just like
trap you into building your own grave
and once you're deep too deep they will
like cover it up like you you would
covered up in never mind I think there
is treasure maybe they weren't
lying oh they were not lying why would
they lie to you in the apocalypse I
don't know maybe you were in in with
them and and you were just trying to
kill everybody I would never you could
sandwich
oh my God there's a dead body here this
awesome I'll drink that the front door
is 3,000 HP
strong don't worry I'll break it
open are you
sure yeah by the time you get here it'll
be
open okay let me try right
now do I go back to the trade or
no thank you
f are you on your way to the
trader
o sorry that wasn't even on
purpose
yeah sometimes you just
oo sell your garbage okay
[Laughter]
sorry I'm I'm working on it I thought
you said to tell it was done I'm I'm
don't turn
away she'll be done
soon just get so tired hitting this door
me me
too
hi just it's just so hard oh oh it's
open
oh I think I'm dying to what oh
goodbye you don't
die
ooh okay oh he gives you a choice gun
what did you take uh gy did you take a
pistol or a rifle I took a shotgun
oh she
Liv oh that's a lot um this is not good
whoa everyone's standing up
ceiling whoa that's crazy I'm getting
out of
here my friends it's my
friends uh your friends are a little
aggressive don't worry I have something
to put them out of their misery I missed
run it's okay I didn't have any
expectations
you you should have expectations I could
do better I can do better I will do
better I'm sure you can maybe just not
today oh hello
ow oh I had shotgun shells oh
oopsy how come I can't drink the rain
water why am I so picky
how are you so picking the
apocalypse I thought it was
zombies it's just out
on they made
it sell your wood you can easily get
more oh wait I can drink
water what water just just look up at
the sky and it slowly replenishes um
your thirst no way really yeah no really
try it no
no
no person is busy okay I'll try
it no it doesn't
[Laughter]
work why
would what is wrong with you you sick
freak is us being in the apocalypse not
enough for you you have to play with us
too what are we like little respect
I'm just getting wet I just cannot
believe you would do such I'm terrible
to us you hear the
herak oh you think being thirsty is a
joke KY did you do any other quests like
the or the zombie okay I should I'll
stop here
you
should wait wait you know what fauna's
on her way here so I wait for f to
dig and
then maybe we can all we can do we yeah
questy
yay if only it was a shortcut to get to
the trainer maybe we should bu our house
next to the
trainer right just move in somewhere
else we're not that attached to the
current house are we I hope not
no oh oh my God what the heck
better what mm if you're in the same
party you can share Quest
mhm close it close it close
close hungry again what is this this
human bodily functions can I buy a bread
or something from you sir please
[Music]
I have 39 Casino tokens nice what are
you going to do with that I want
food but it's
expensive you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
like what is
that so scary
my
bad first you lie to us you Sak up on me
you get off on caring people lying to
people oh
no oh a sham sandwich I hope I don't get
diarrhea with this m you probably will
oh search fancy toilet I Live Another
Day what does sham mean I've been eating
those for a while now um it means you
will if you are not lucky you will poop
your pants oh oh
H I only know sham marriages I only know
sham wow sham wow sham
marriages oh my God there's a
person you mean a dead person oh my God
there's a dead person I see dead
people
canit and this is so expensive like in
an apocalypse can you not have some
mercy why are they burping oh ew they're
like I don't know yeah why was there no
grocery store in this town how did they
get their
food I guess I'll look for my own food
if this guy sells for so
expensive crazy guy hi oh how is how do
you say it again like I'm home I'm home
youim no that's
[Laughter]
the okay we got some stuff you have food
yeah we found food 30 me we we Hunters
we have
Callie as as
the I I will say you are the leader of
this group am I um wouldn't you say it
would be very much smarter to like move
to a house that is closer to the
Traer good idea
I bro you guys are blocking my
way you're
welcome oh no sorry yeah kind of
aggressive full
of just uh life's hard maybe we can make
a second
house and move everything yeah yeah I'm
going to keep these shot shells though
yeah any goodies that you find just dump
them and I think everyone should get um
a bone knife at a certain point because
they're really
useful KN and then I'm going to make a
magazine crate and please only take the
ones that that you think you want to
kind ofx yourself on I personally am
doing like a fortitude strength thing
but for example there's like a
journal NDS okay freaking nerd what do
you guys have you have you found any
other journals so far an academic
one
cucumber what call she's a
scholar poter all right she she
did she's the winner of the spelling be
so true does anyone want to try going to
the trader so we can do some Trader
quests because I feel like that's where
the food and stuff will be easiest to
get and
water water would be very nice I
definitely need water but first can we
get a snack can you get a little snack
first I'm very hungry can you guys who
you're at the house when you go to the
Traer can you bring some food with you
to share the only one that can cook from
us is bi Bo and I don't know where she
is right now
so oh we need more chefs and I'm so
thirsty oh I'm so thirsty I'm so thirsty
so bad but I am about take this take it
take it okay so we let's wait wait let
me ask what people's doing one sec I'll
be right
back oh thank God what is this feel much
better
desolation have food please you know I
could probably cook some eggs though yes
eggs are
easy how do you like your
eggs dang it
Benedict bened cumber batch oh nice I
think I'm out of
I love my eggs like that also ladies I a
farmer so if you find any Farm relating
things let me know cuz I'd like to start
a farming a little farming plot
okay plot until at the trader area you
mean farming magazines or something like
that no uh farming yeah farming
magazines yes you're right that's
correct thank you I do have one
blueberry seed by the way yeah seeds
collect as many seeds as we can we're
going to need them I have a
potato you have a potato you have a
potato all this time you talk about
hunger and you have a potato I have one
potato yeah we can share this potato
just like what we all take a bite yeah
it's dire times I don't think that's
going to change
anything okay I have begged and is on
her way and she will make us all food
yeah and then we can go an adventure to
the Traer and see oh I found
coffee disgusting you have
coffee you have
coffee why me you find like 30 meat oh
who was that was it you 30 meat meat I
put you
have cooked this reaction is genuine
the other ones they were fake this one
this one's genuine this one's genuine H
wait so how do you get water from a
river you just like how how do you drink
it I'm punching it but I don't get any
water yeah you punch water to drink yeah
oh to get
water when it's raining look up and then
it's been
bred we've
beened that's despar
right yes ladies yes you were even there
when we've been through this and you
judged crony for it
what these other people in this call
don't know that yeah I don't know what
you're talking about what do you mean
talking yeah
no you're just
sing well what what did I say actually
happen or are you guys messing what I
have diar no like it did happen
you have a lot going on with yeah a
didn't know you were going to Dr like
that I was just raining out I what it
said does somebody have Golden Rod
flowers safe space every
should oh my God there's a diarrhea icon
on the screen I don't want to see what
that looks like
jeez whoa I want to see that yeah try
eating some more sham sandwiches
oh you'll get
there I'm s wait so wait but just the
flower is not enough right you have to
money you have to you have to oh I'm
infected uh I need to take that's okay
we'll kol you when the time comes don't
wor no I for infection I've just been uh
eating honey in the tree stumps it's
really efficient good idea oh I see the
diarrhea symbol now oh you got diarrhea
let's go diarrhea guys yeah
let's go diarrhea
maxing yeah let's share a toilet
together you know isolated as
survivalist for such a long time that
it's hard to gauge is that is that
romantic are they flirting I'm not sure
I think it's bonding for sure yeah it's
dire times get it
home I brought you girls ever ever
coming to the I have I dropped like 30
meat on you I can make bacon and eggs
and I can make boiled meat so thank God
blessed the heavens yesing
let me cook we're so lucky we cook
yay can you make tea too
bio um let's see with the golden
flowers oh I found a golden rod flower
oh I cured my a weapon or to oh you can
make purify water as well oh please make
need that yeah
basic if you have murky water I can
purify it I have that too I think we
have some
wow that's cool okay I'm going to bacon
an egg we have two murky water I'll drop
it for you here you go y
yay all natural murky for the merest
reasons M yummy what that mean the yeah
actually it's okay since we're near a
river with our empty bottles we could
theoretically go near it GA water and
just like boil that endlessly I hope wa
you guys have bottles I don't have
bottles infinite water trick where'd you
guys get bottles your M just open your
mouth look you can't anymore why would
they do
that what about glass jar split a stack
I'm blind I think right
I'm just going to do a quest now then
okay
okay oh I figured out okay thanks have
you seen tra yet if anybody has any more
cooking books uh please give them to me
I will give them to you I do think I
don't actually know if it's like super
important to be honest I don't want to I
don't want to Railroad and be like oh we
have to be super careful when I have
when I don't know but this is just like
my inclination but maybe I'm wrong so
just be you yeah I am I have some Golden
Rod flowers can you boil them so that I
can drink
him so that we can drink
him thank you how do I give it to you C
I'll just drop it okay and I also
C I'll go for medic if you want to give
me the medic thingy what too expensive
theal put in the journal crate is over
here where the journal crate so I need I
need one more level in cooking if
anybody has
any cooking magazines cuz I can't make
yet
okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144
coins I don't even know where to get
coins damn Earth we get coins that's
crazy that's crazy my diar is going away
on some thank you sir anyway did I take
the clothes I'm happy for you meat right
now I found some acid if you think that
can help your stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I
guess oh beep do you want to put the the
cooked food in this one the storage
which one the right one and we should
try to figure out how to make a farm the
one that the one that you're looking at
yeah are where I need to go for my fetch
Quest when did you take this Quest oh I
think you're sharing cuz we're in the
same party
I'll complete it for you don't worry
well how are you already there oh I was
just walking wait I don't think I can do
it for you doesn't let me okay I'll wait
inent there the moment took it oh you
can label the
boxes okay I'm on my
way what you cook oh we can make we can
make glue I can eat glue no no no no no
that's
not I'm just me at the moment okay
awesome sleepover surv yeah I love it
you look like
the instead of watching horror movies
one item instead of all the items guys I
don't I know movie right outside our
door control oh water yeah control I'm
sorry I got to drink some that's okay
I've been dehydrated
water
control am I finally like not
dehydrated no I'm so thirsty as
heck yeah why can my skin not absorb the
water from from the skin why not cuz
you're dehydrated the glass bar just
disappear that's
stupid why why would the glass disappear
after using them I might just going to
crack out like cards now
raining well too bad we can't drink it
can I open my mouth yeah opening your
mouth yeah yeah yeah you just have to
look up at the sky oh my God drank all
the
water you still are you still at the
quest oh yeah I think you are please I'm
so thirsty and so
unwet am am I
I can't tell if they were
kiding no we're not you just you have to
wait it's very
incremental I've already
drank spooky
storm okay I'm going to start what
should I do is anything we can do at
night oh oh
cry oh cry o I love cry me too supplies
in here I hope the mushrooms grow inside
there
what are all
these here what zombies what's wrong
there's here okay where
is uh no I think she's the
quest it me doing
one oh way okay I'm
behind I missed all this bless you it's
very scary
oh maybe I can't Farm
here I farm a rotting
flash yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm might be man I can't make my hops I
hope you enjoy my the trainer for a
quest if not it's totally fine yeah go
to the I didn't want to I didn't run to
rush I just thought if you going to do
something else why can I not use it I
got to go
there um is going to take a couple
minutes to cook but I put I put
might be one
upstairs me me
ym
me
wow look at
my that's the
option that's all I can right now
I it's okay it's
okay now put one back
I stab the you're going to eat my you're
spiled eggs it's so nice and dry okay
I'll cook some eggs too I'm I'm dying do
you have
water the T in my mouth no no you should
be here you should be here am I am
I wait should we go into a VC the quest
yeah we can go okay yeah which one two
what
Cilia oh I want to go to the chair too
okay I'm outside chopping some
wood whatc should we hop do you
think uh
nice we can take four let's take
four
okay and
[Music]
then and then
we back hey welcome
back has home been
good home has never been
better we almost didn't make it
back let's cook the eggs let's cook the
eggs I don't have our eggs let's our
eggs oh yeah do we have a cooking po now
it seems like we
do yeah
yeah nice and I have gas can
too treasure hunter yeah we got a gun
too
yeah let's put it all in
there Marky water oh I guess we need can
we boil that the Marky water maybe maybe
we should boil that yeah yeah do we have
anyy water oh what about that what about
that what about that with this no let
yeah should we drink that we're
thirsty have water
drink um can you do you know how to cook
the spoiled meat spoiled egg spoiled um
if it's spoiled it's probably not a good
idea hello rotten rotten Maybe not maybe
maybe not I don't think so the rotten
fles can only be used for farming maybe
I farming yeah we looking for
it what should I
do I have a ninja to found
somewhere it's
okay okay I'll just put it right here
can't make it yet can't make it yet oh
that's right we wanted to farm the
cotton bam oh we need to swe the sou
farming
magazine
oh disappoint sick how do I find a
magazine why is there dub step
okay what's going on there
wowow need tra powder where can I find a
magazine mailbox um I think it's dark
now it made an omin sound it's night
time now why I got to keep dying I hear
I hear hising I I watch
hising I hear zombies here are they
outside the
door hey can you guys boil some
water
um yeah maybe not right now
are they at the
door where no not yet but hope
soones we hear some very scary sounds
it's okay don't worry I think they're at
the door now they breaking down the door
I think
[Music]
no they're breaking the door Dar a
darn uhoh well I go find them
well too late you do your best oh you
can't just give
up it's
okay well that's probably not a good
idea I'm using my other don't have St
on is outside safer I don't think so I
don't outside safer it's not safer it's
not safer everybody they need to be here
to prot oh I missed
ow oh
[Music]
be
beasting spawn on my
bed uh let's do on my bed and what
happens my oh maybe I shouldn't have
spawned on my bed
we have weapons in our box yet right
take out the weapon spear spear spear St
ax you want the stone a
uh I uh I
I I um I would help but I don't have
anything just going on top of our bed we
going to wa on top of our bed and attack
when they are here yeah we have the
upper ground yes we have the top bunk
top bu Advantage yeah oh no use the
spear not the axe oh god oh no there's a
spear I got the spear okay I think is
saf now H bunk advantage
get off the top the
to is open maybe a knife would be
good better better oh that's not good
our get all dirty we it later oh no
everybody's
dying come on that's all part of the
process I want Tov oh home sweet
home I think it's time if you want to
come and join us in the bunk bed oh he
disappeared I thought he was starting to
move again the bunk be oh only could put
some stones in front oh I can't see
where I'm
going I think this is
upstairs why did the zombies go away
wa 8 a.m. dying is so much
better I hope the ship ends at 8 a.m.
yeah I feel like where is everybody else
they should have been protecting
home critizing
every the house you know night
time loser
[Music]
a here we are we protecting the base by
hiding
[Music]
the
hey the top of the top of the
bunk oh what the
heck babying
[Music]
my heads leave me
alone one more clothes I still not here
yet can I
eat oh I
can't
it's make it Downs maybe good at the
stairs I want
my I do like ITP is a good combo
yeah level
two let's spend this skill points while
everybody else is
dying there piano being now
uhoh let's build the door take
sck the
door okay maybe I made the door I have
no sticks where did the sticks go oh I
think I think I carried them with me
what this do did you do
that oh it's a stairs okay the sticks
are on my oh oh I can also like that
that's
cool is friendly fire on can you attack
me
yes ow okay thank you oh oh I'm dying
a how do I the door actually no this is
a good idea Raa come back here
can you kill
me of course it's my pleasure what kill
me ah
yes oh we don't need a double door just
a wood door
sorry no thank
you that way I can be completely cured I
did a mistake I'm placing the door
that's okay
all right there we go I don't know if
that's the right kind of
door oh I need to repair
my
axe that's kind of effective right cck
with the axe
on right cck with the
axe just need one more
[Music]
bone let's break the door
oh I fixed
it what are we doing
here yes what what are you doing I'm
breaking this door oh cuz it's kind of a
funny door because I
misplace how do
I what do I
build I can't get in the house now I'll
help do
then oh
okay
good look at
that y the other doors maybe we should
try to make like let me check if it is
like oh this door we could put a
door that's a door yeah now that has a
door d everywhere do I want to fix
everything I want to fix everything now
can fix the windows coffee
maker yummy we have coffee seeds so the
fact that we have a coffee maker means
that there is a possibility coffee could
be consumed at some point which is wait
maybe I should
just chill out for a
bit
off well maybe our our door is okay yeah
I think this is my bed
yeah yeah this is my
bed should put
a I know that I'm
infected oh you're infected do you want
me to kill
you are you
sure it's okay you can just ask I can
kill
you you you want to kill me I'm
okay are you sure if that's your only
desire in your life I can make it I
don't have any
[Laughter]
desires well in that case I'll keep my
life for now okay let me know when you
don't want to live
[Laughter]
anymore I'll tell you when my time comes
okay that's good
let me just take some of my
stuff 18 is
good oh it sounds bad yeah I think we
should probably get the door going then
M what door the door that you just
ruined because I wanted to put a door on
our room yeah I don't think we can yeah
we can you just put it wrong you sure
yeah I told you this you didn't spin
it's not daytime yet I'm not sure you no
it's still
not okay good good
good no no no now you no no no now it's
wrong it was good for a second yeah yeah
yeah there you go oh B's Dead Oh huh
well it happens I
guess has their
moment see and now we're even more
protected
yeah door let's put more do in other
places like a door over there you know
lots of hiding spots
doors oh there's a door there too
there's a lot of doors that we didn't
even know
about this is this could be repaired can
you repair this door dark how do I make
it brighter in here wow it's so dark at
night we had a
lamp fire
the
fire turn on turn
on I have to give
it
weapon much
better I'm trying to level up but I
don't understand how that work better
yeah let's go take a look at our skills
open
the um which one's stronger a
sledgehammer or a spear Sledge Hammer
but spear has distance but Sledgehammer
if it's a big one it has distance
no you're
so I want the skill for seeds
[Music]
yeah I want to get better spear to read
the
magazine what why am
I why am I Dr for breaking things faster
oh is very good
then let's use
oh I'm good now okay I'm GL
you it's horrible outside it's raining
too we haven't went upstairs M should we
go upstairs
theer do we not have any more
sticks Maybe not maybe not oh you got a
punch for
more let's fix things I want to fix
things
probably TR f
why is everyone dying are we out of
sticks I don't know maybe they're
fighting
something check our
inventory kind of want to go to the snow
area
but there's a castle there yeah there's
a castle
there yeah maybe it would be a good
place to take over but I'm not sure if
it's worth
it I see well
maybe this is
where I go to bed for tonight and we'll
see you all
[Music]
tomorrow we're going to buk for now oh
yeah
yeah hopefully it will let's close the
door and
hopefully everything works so here
[Music]
yay I will see you tomorrow for more
days oh good
night good
luck if you want to go to the castle we
can go together apparently that one's
really difficult oh
yeah well we can go later in a few days
well let's go explore
somewhere else of let
me I'm not sure where but like we can go
to have you been to the
trader have you been to the trader I've
been to the trader oh yeah I've been to
the trader I was I still have to do my
quest but okay we can go to the trader
then sweet let's go okay okay it's close
yeah and then we can probably explore
from there yeah where you at
I am at home I'm in my
room well it's time to get
a oh what a coincidence I I have all my
stuff there
too yeah yeah see this is my corner oh
really
yeah we share the room together W you're
nice what where is your bed you don't
have a bed huh
you don't have a bed I have a bed I'm
carrying it with me because wherever I'm
going I'm already home oh that's smart
yeah no it's not smart if you die you
just die it's
not okay okay I'm coming I'm just going
to bring with me some glue because last
time I
needed and okay okay I don't think I
need anything okay let's go let's go
let's go let's go
where also
Chad that's my bed cuz they're all
already taken okay you
silly anyway party yes let's go party
yeah party uh can I going to make a
party with you I'm not quite sure maybe
you have to accept
something ah I see I have no idea how
the party system works okay never mind
uh no no no no no I got it I I think I
got it this oh left the party you left
the party now what yeah wait but I
sent but I sent it to
you
weird I don't
know uh
KY please do me a favor yes kill me what
what why because I have low HP oh okay
bye see you
soon it is what it
is come on let me respond okay I respond
my
bad yeah I'm ready to go
do you need to die oh no I'm good I'm at
full health let me know okay let's go uh
store is over oh store is this
way okay wait no store is not that way
sorry uh store
is it's this way this way this way
Trader yeah Trader we're going to the
trader right yeah we're going to the
trader I mean yeah I need to do that
quietly which is very clol okay let's go
let's
go
yay very nice oh apparently you have to
leave the party and then I invite you
okay let me just do it how do
do I don't get it
so Tab and then uh
players and then there's like
um party thing yeah oh leave okay I did
it I did it
yeah
oo yeah let's go yeah woo that's what
I'm talking about
woo
nice my God I be the player here I got a
knife yeah bone knife very good it's
very
fast yeah it seems like the durability
isn't that good though yeah but I think
it's pretty easy to C you need like five
bone yeah I don't know where to find all
that though like maybe in
houses ew
e why are you out of
stamina we're
alive running we're still so full of
life there's nothing for you to run out
of stamina for I like I like the way you
think about it yeah I like your mindset
exactly wow you like the way I think
wow not a lot of people tell me that
thank
you yeah it's nice
wow you think I think positively or
something I think you're very positive
person that's actually crazy wow I don't
even know where you got that idea
who oh wait there's a house here oh wa
where are you I'm going to come to now
oh this this
place you're pretty far from
me oh there you are Oh no you're not far
from me oh there you go thought you
opposite side oh this is
iron oh than
you we can
share sharing
is
yeah oh my God we're going to make so
many great things with this wait uh oh
yeah this is no this is lead this is not
iron oh well we're going to make so many
great things with this regardless can do
you can use um you can craft with it
still good what the
heck oh yay okay now let's go kill some
stuff yeah I'm looking around to see if
there's something we can steal from this
place
no
nothing oh I was dead oh nice empty
Rusty
no everything is G probably someone
already been here oh everything's
already
looted no so
sad well so selfish they took everything
for themselves I know sharing is caring
and they did that what's wrong with
them it's messed up it's messed
up okay we're going to go
back taking a b in this
weather it's
beautiful it's like the little things in
life in this
apocalypse you like like going
to and have a bath no I hate
it oh good yeah you know I like looking
at the ocean I think it's pretty but I
don't want to be in it you know no same
I don't get people enjoying the bath
yeah cuz your skin gets kind of dry and
like it feels kind of
icky yeah and plus like you don't know
what happens there
true
like yeah um I was talking to my friend
um oh wait yeah I was talking to my
friend and was like oh you know maybe
Hawaii would be really nice to go cuz
um you know we were just talking about
vacation spot since uh uh Kiara pitched
the idea before and I was like oh Hawaii
maybe Hawaii and then my friend was like
yeah there are sharks
around really yeah I don't think sharks
can I mean sharks are not that dangerous
yeah they're really not that dangerous
but you know just uh just her suggesting
that that's a possibility I am not
excited what is your favorite vacation
spot or like your
ideal vacation my bed ooh
oh you're bad yeah I can do anything in
my
bed pretty true yeah like you know if
you get really lazy you can probably I
don't know door Dash or something and
then you can you know play games and bed
uh oh my God there's a snake oh my
God everything kills me here
oh it's dead it's
dead dis yeah I got something I got and
meat yeah meat not
bad nice nice look at us go that's cool
oh I
water
water I mean that's still something why
was there
blood uh because I found a body do you
want some bones by the way I have
some can I just have
one yeah uh I don't know how
to give you that that's way too many so
give me give me the the ones that you
need sorry ones you use them give it
back to me oh okay uh I don't know how
to split
them you
know that's uh
okay uh how many did you give me again
okay okay here you go thank you thank
you bless
up the quest is very
close yeah find the B the B supplies
oh to use the shovel wait where'd you go
here where's
here uh wait I come I come to you no
you're running away no no no what here
behind you oh okay
[Music]
okay okay let me start the C
oh okay what is
this
Lance I need to oh you're terraforming
wow yeah that's the you you dug in a
square
hole Yeah I'm very precise I like to do
squ wow so
specific
[Laughter]
oh I need to dig around to find supplies
apparently it may take a
while this is my
[Laughter]
hole well don't
move okay guess they did the entire game
that's fine the entire game like this
yeah yeah
is maybe I can make it
bigger really no this is already quite
spacious oh but you cannot even lay down
what about your
bed no I like I like sleeping like
this feels like I'm in
space okay oh I found it no no I didn't
oh my
gosh am I doing the right thing I don't
even know
oh takes a
while are you sure this is a place
yeah it's like a big yellow circle
around this
area let me
see not
yet uh do you want to help me what if I
steal your achievement though is the
thing a I think that it's like
luch or is it chair I think there is
like a chest or something okay it
says
oh yeah find the
supplies we got a big
deeper thank you
yeah Dream
Team this kind of therapeutic
oh I found it oh what oh here you're
getting closer to the treasure says yeah
yeah yeah
yeah found
it y I got Sandwich Water flashh and
River supplies
W oh okay not bad that's pretty
good let's go now we go back to the
there yeah let's
go zombies around ignore them
yeah are you sure that food isn't
expired or
anything the
food is rotten so we cannot eat it
unfortunately but I have some meat I
have like six row meat
hey that's something yeah and then we
can cook him
later y me yum
yummer okay we go this
way can we kill him now now I just want
a steak Yeah you can kill him no don't
don't kill the trader no don't kill the
trader we need
it oh I can get pie of
bundle re rle bundle machine gun bundle
button bundle shotgun button
bundle what should I
get I don't know I think I'll
peek shotgun is
cool I mean a shotgun would be nice
but like where would you get ammo or
something you
oh gry do you want do you
take do you take more jobs from this guy
or you just
like oh that's is my second
time oh what is your quest now my quest
is just whatever goes
I
see
okay oh now I find the buried supplies
okay that's great we can we can make it
if you want a job from me you a lot
of my quest gave me a shotgun so make
yours
too yay thank you son of a
[\h__\h] that thing is really
rude Who Do You Think You Are he keeps
wearing at me oh yeah is a little rude
that's fine kind of want to kill him no
no no we need him it's the only human
here gives us
stuff
okay all right where is this at tracking
Quest where do you see your quest
actually Q I think now mine
is oh where do you see it okay let me
check
so
429 M away which
is how do you find
it let me
check oh yeah I see it there's like a
little exclamation mark on the map pleas
ah I see oh intro buried supplies and
tier one buried
supplies yeah I supplies
okay I guess um I you and then I don't
know if it's the same place so let's go
yours and then we go mine oh thank
you okay uh we Farm These y
oh does it yeah like the shotgun is
pretty good for
zombies oh so it's uh more beneficial
for you to complete the quests yeah I
think at the beginning is very good to
complete the quests because you got
materials that usually
cannot
ah by just crafting also we need to find
a magazine uh to probably unlock more
stuff for the shotgun oh yeah that um
you have to loot the houses
more yeah I think I'll go later
yeah okay don't don't don't do that yeah
yeah okay I help oh thank you
[Music]
yay it's quite it's quite relaxing it's
like it is
Sim I love power wash I'm really excited
for the new update
actually I never
I never tried it but you never tried it
oh my God okay so so the thing is I
always watch people streaming it because
it's so relaxing for me to watch but I
never actually streamed it so maybe I'll
give it a try maybe yeah like it's
really nice it's like a good like zatu
kind
of oh man I'm out of stamina
oh yeah I'll
try yay
I love those kind of games I love like
no thoughts head empty kind of games
they're my
favorite yeah yeah like you don't have
to think about anything it's just
therapy
yeah you know what I mean I don't like
games where like there are too much
stuff to think about yeah you got to
think too much it's like Man games are
made for relax
not for stressing out you know you would
think you you would think but for some
reason I play a lot of games that are
suffering
yeah I bet you do
anyway what do you mean I bet you do
like you you you you you play games that
you need to suffer even though you
prefer games that
empty
yeah yeah where the heck I play horror
games when I don't like horror games is
the
same do you get scared of it though I
hate it yeah
really yeah
dang it's kind of kind of
bone do you like or
games I don't but like it's October so I
should probably play a
bit oh my God what is your supply
apparently it's oh sorry oh you found it
I found it
nice
okay what oh there's a zombie behind you
neighbor it's okay don't care about him
let's go let's go yeah it's a waste of
our durability let's go to mine as well
so we could oh yeah yeah uh let's see
right
there oh wait this yay let's
go
okay wait
what
what why is it not tracking
track track okay oh it's tracking
okay is it the same position as mine I
hope so I I hope
so make
sense oh okay maybe we are going the
same direction probably oh be careful
here don't break a leg
or break a leg you know break a leg on
not breaking your leg break
[Music]
leg
funny I am pretty funny I am you're very
funny actually don't say
that don't actually say that oh okay
sorry you are funny a thank you yeah I'm
like one of the more funny and unfunny
people that I have met in my life yeah I
got
you do you really get me
though
no okay it's here okay same position
okay sick okay good oh hungry
again if you H kill you the Hang oh
thank you I'll just like put down a bed
oh wait you don't have your bed never
mind I can craft
one oh yeah actually that's true but you
can also spawn next to your back
by I mean I can but I don't know
if it's going to be good for
you you don't have a place why is it so
Square too many questions for me too
many questions
well if I don't question things how
would people
know they don't
know I'm thirsty is a
bless
oh that's also one of my favorite things
one of my favorite quotes ignorance is
bliss sometimes you don't question
things and something sketchy is going on
you turn a blind eye yeah yeah
I don't want to
know you get it wor it is it is you have
to like stay in your lane otherwise like
they're going to get you like
something's going to bite you back and
it's like oh you know things could have
been normal things could have been
better if I just didn't know anything
kind of thing you know oh yeah it's like
yeah it's like when you eat something is
yummy and then you don't want to know
what how they
made yeah or like it has way too many
calories or something yeah I'm not
looking at
this wait getting closer to
treasure get oh over there
then I don't
know man why do I have to be so hungry
oh God get away
ow don't worry I'll I'll
help
[Music]
die die stay
down yay
woo nice what do you get out of it uh
sometime you
get R FL I think I got some bones out of
it I'm not quite sure I may be
wrong oh H there there people here
oh
[Music]
hello my stamina
man yeah I need to drink water but I
don't actually have PL water yeah I
don't have normal water it's just murky
and that's going to make me sick when
did I have so
much okay
whatever can I do something with this
many
clay what is this treasure oh my God I
don't know
maning
forever I'm out of
stamina open oh I have a p shot gun and
ammo cool I open the box right
now hey
nice there was
box so like when you deliver the quest
to the traiter they give you a box with
a gun
ah okay you get to see a
moment where the heck is it
man where have any
can I eat Ro meat no uh I mean you can
but it's better to cook
it you'll probably get
sick you
here oh oh good job no no no no not yet
not yet yeah not oh I I'm clipping
through wait I'm going to kill those
zombies okay hold on I will
help no
problem why so many I don't know
ow oh my God I'm dealing with two
zombies here
well I'm dying I'm also
dying I'm dead you're
dead
yes stop eating
me ow dude I can't even kill one zombie
come
on why are they so rough
[Music]
I'm let my backpack again and help
you right
really yeah okay I come to you now so I
get to help
you you go
nice yay
what oh it's still alive yeah it's still
alive let's
go oh
they're they're coming this
way there's there's more behind you no
worries uh did you craft do you have a
spear I think a spear might be better
yeah I'm using the
spear nice
okay I use both I need to
repair oh
boy yay
oh she got
ammo what yeah some Dres they drop items
oh that's
good okay now they
dead nothing
okay oh it was my arrow oh never mind oh
it was my arrow
okay where were
we here oh wow we went
far wait I don't see this Mark anymore
yeah I don't see it where'd it go did we
lose it hope
not it says we
failed we failed
no we
failed
yeah never mind let's go to the
tror wait can we redo it or no maybe
maybe if we talk to the Traer we can
redo it
a
[Music]
man oh because I died he failed
I mean there were way too many zombies
as the thing so or maybe there is like a
time
limit
maybe
me because it it asks you like when do
you want to start the
quest but it's okay I mean
like we can do another too many yeah I
mean there are too many zombies man like
I don't no yeah like either way pretty
sure one of us would have died
anyway
yeah o is that iron yeah that's iron
yeah I'll
help good job oh I have coffee
meat this I need more space in my
inventory I'm throw this out
man I get so tired I'm so tired all the
time oh so someone says the treasure
hunting quests spawn zombies as you dig
so that's to be expected appar
uhuh yay nice
why' you drop the clock
fragments oh yeah because I doesn't got
enough space home uh in the
inventory yeah I had to drop
something where am I give me a better
Quest now Trader or CR is going to kill
you I mean can you actually kill him I
wish you cold but it's an
NPC
oh apparently the quest disappeared too
so we cannot repeat it oh it's so
fair man this guy I think we should kill
him
I hate this
guy
well I think we need to kill this guy
apparently you can also like get the
same Quest on all day so maybe if we go
back tomorrow we can find the same quest
ah so it it resets over time but in the
meantime which one what do you want to
get like now I have clear zombies Fetch
and fetch I don't know what fetch means
exactly
um well like before you accept or well
like go to the quest area can you kill
me later after I hand over this quest of
course thank you you should you should
oh yeah yeah I think oh no no yeah I'm
okay I can kill you my pleasure thank
you well like they're all busy talking
so going to have to
wait I get in line talk to him
anyway
really
yeah just need to find the right spot
conratulations here's your reward
sucker shotgun
ooh
[Music]
rifle
cornmeal I don't know if I should get a
shotgun or a
rifle M I can show you the shotgun and
you tell me if you like like
it I'm equiping
now so this is the
shotgun
yeah it looks pretty
good well I guess I'm going to have to
pay you now it's it's a Mori
okay let's get this one then okay do you
have any
jobs buried
supplies oh wait there is a supplies
Quest can't refuse yeah I don't think I
have I have just clear
zombies fetch clear zombies fetch you
must be half a zombie already or got
[\h__\h] for brain which one which one do
you want to do then clear zombies
or
fetch we can do clear we can do fetch I
don't know what it is though I got some
[\h__\h] work for a [\h__\h] up like you
trying
oh that's kind of unall for you got it
oh no no no he he was just
being really
rude okay so what if what if we do try
clear Z me is okay the closest one it's
like 500 work to do if you don't mind
getting your it's a deal disappoint me
and you'll find yourself on the wrong
end of a road do you guys doing a fetch
Quest oh we're
doing
doing oh wait wait wait wait
zombies zombie
first then
you want to join
us oh
wait okay um so when you die yeah are
you able to spawn near your backpack or
something yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh
okay sick okay I don't have to put out a
bed
okay
nice eliminated the crony
sick I hope this doesn't fail the
mission or anything no no if you haven't
started it doesn't
fail okay
sick
okay wait can we accept like a qu more
than one Quest at a time so we can go
with Mor
maybe uh maybe oh yeah no no no we can't
oh we can't oh we can't okay never
mind
okay
uh
where
are
my wait hold on what huh what am I
wearing armor oh yeah I am yeah you when
you get this
okay sick all right let's go yay okay
let's go oh one second let me oh wait
wait Kelly's coming with us right no K
is doing the fet quest right now and we
cannot accept multiple quests at the
same
time
okay
so oh wait oh
this hey okay this
one uh 400 m
away I don't know what it is let me
see uhhuh oh there you go I see
it it's over there let's
go I'm going to the question mark h i
shouldn't have jumped too much I'm just
I'm so used to it
take your
time you can have multiple Quest but you
can help with the quest oh can we up any
way wait there's a level system in this
game I don't know that yeah like
apparently I still have to understand
better but there are also skills skills
um tree that you can improve
and you can upgrade so like if you press
Tab and you go to the you know the
little guy with the graduation hat yeah
yeah uh there's like this kind of skills
tree and point system ah yeah yeah and I
still have to understand what it is so
right now I'm upgrading the
spare and oh yeah yeah yeah comb back
perks actually that would be a good idea
I do I have two skill points so I should
probably use
somewhere where'd you
go huh where'd you go me yeah oh okay
there you are you were in the top of
me why are you
jumping yeah oh okay okay how
oh okay I don't question
it are you
ready yeah
okay
a oh I I got a skill that allows me to
see
animals oh yeah I did that to pretty
cool I know but I haven't found any use
for it yet oh
really well
that's
cool
yay when you
crouch yeah but it usually just says oh
no
tracks I to be fair I haven't seen any
animals around so oh there something
here no we could look bu this house yeah
let's
cool it's a very pretty home oh wait G G
lives here for really
yeah oh that's
cool uh I guess there's nothing to loot
then yeah maybe she miss
something no I don't think
[Laughter]
so okay
yeah no I don't think there's anything
around here
no yep it's
clean what if I steal her
St you
could yeah you come I
mean let's
see yep empty empty empty empty empty
are you in the house or no I left
okay yeah yeah okay okay there you are
okay yeah let's go yippe yippe yippe I I
can't wait to shoot with my
shotgun PE PE pew pew
die
murder oh cool house chicken there's a
chicken there's a
chicken come
here oh my God come here
yes I got my Chien W
hey congratulations
man oh my God it gives you a lot of meat
I got 11 no six meat
whoa hey yo let's
go are you loing the house uh yeah but
uh there's a place where we can start
the quest oh yeah yeah yeah you want to
start
yeah it's here it
says I don't know how to start e Oh
e okay so we need to clear the
area how do we clear the area I guess
what the zomes are going to arrive
and um
I guess we need to kill the Zombies hold
on this
it no
[Applause]
uh let me just check the
quest head to mushroom mining company
and clear the zombies this location
could be useful to our oh clear the
house oh we have to enter the house
okay I hear here yeah
yeah yeah maybe it's in the
basement oh yeah it's right here oh
hello
oh oh my God this weapon is so
[Applause]
slow
e wa this thing would not
die okay stand that takes so
long okay this shotgun will sell super
nice okay should I shoot
it oh never mind don't waste it don't
waste it okay let me like find it there
you
go there more
yeah there's more
up get out of here
like
okay is fast
dang
oh be careful this is one it's
fast oh oh nice not dead never
mind why is it doing a ballet I don't
know
but yay yay it's so impossible to kill
him they're so
durable
hard one is locked let's go here
bathroom
I found my water
e
yum no yum
[Music]
yum let's
see oh wait never mind
I need this don't think so I thought we
cleared the area what what else is
there uh I don't think so because there
is another door come here come here on
the kitchen oh come here up up up
oh
what hey y oh my God there're s
distance oh behind you w w wo wo whoo
whoa what
what got you y bro I can't move bro you
so it blocked me
you
died no does it say it
fail not to
me okay no I think I did
it okay that's good as it says it fail
to you yeah it probably failed for me
but I don't want to spawn and then ruin
your quest potentially so no no no it's
done for me so you can
spawn what if I spawn back and then it
it only fails for you no it's fine don't
worry okay
okay okay so I'm going oh I found some
cool items some nice Lo
here oh my bag
my
bag do
I
and what else why is the lock oh oh yeah
basement
oh what what what what what what what H
you
okay
oh yeah I'm good oh oh first a bandage
okay what's the point I'm going to die
anyway oh I found a medical journal cool
oh hey that's nice you can read
it why is the music on is oh my God I
don't
know wait where' my bag go wait you
don't have your bag yeah wait is it on
the other side no wait what where is
it you died here though do you can you
see the the the bag
on on your on your map oh it's
floating
oh okay
okay well that's
[Applause]
okay okay so I actually already looted
here and I found uh a head
mod I don't know we going head mod it's
called waited head mod I don't know what
it is and then if I can show you I'm
going to drop it for you so you can to
see it and then I found a pip button
oh hey that's really a good
weapon and then I found some medical
first eight
minutes what
that could be like a head gear that you
can use by way it's night so maybe we
should either wait or we can yeah we
should probably wait just
wait we can also you know what we can do
with this house because it's pretty
close to the no it's not close to the
tra there but like we can probably craft
something in here too go
down I don't know if that's a good idea
we could use this as a second base maybe
could now that we secured it and the
doors are locked
so yeah it's like pretty secure for now
let's see under St oh there is more
loots here more oh sick there is a diee
thingy oh yeah yeah
yeah and
Bones oh food yay yeah let's loot
everything
what is the
sound
Ambience oh
sorry
look let's check the skill
points let's see what we are I have no
skill points available
D this place is pretty
nice
yeah it's pretty big too maybe I should
have this place as a
base this seems
nice I'll have it in the
Attic okay why the music got to be so
ominous though I don't know it's quite
SAU uh
athletic perks
oh what also I wonder I don't know how
you can um up uh like get more points
for the skills honestly it's quite weird
maybe should we should kill more zombies
but I don't really get it I don't
[Music]
know here oh
okay I guess it needs more
space
[Music]
um okay so XP from kills or building and
crafting oh okay okay so it's actually
pretty good it's pretty convenient to
craft and build
stuff okay let's do
it I guess technically this going to be
the inventory spot so don't need to
necessarily destroy
it oh yeah by the way we have to do our
land claim block so I'm going to make it
now so we can claim this land Oh
yay the music is still
om I place it
here God damn it
yay yay it's ours
now
woo let me see what I can
craft surely I can put it
here h
I don't want to place it in the middle
of nowhere
though
oh fine I'm going to make some
chests what did you position the
chest um I'm just using like the one
that I already have at the top do you
want to have your stuff here too in the
Attic it's
safer where here upstairs oh
upstairs
okay uh actually oh I'm going to put
everything here
yeah we can just share
it of course
how do we upgrade the the trap
doors oh we need to close the
[Music]
door W hatch oh it's not that
secure it's a very nice
spot yeah it's
peaceful what is Reco
oh you need iron I have iron oh you have
iron too I thought I had iron too here I
have iron here I put it here oh
yeah right click with a hammer I don't
have a hammer
guys what do you an
[Music]
ax where oh I can craft I can craft a
hammer ah
reinforced yeah okay I reinforced the
door good
job
yay wait do you have extra wood by any I
do can I bur off yeah of course I have
quite a
few it's
cool and I make a Hummer
is it
outside yeah yeah yeah that's outside
oh yeah there are a lot of zies around
we can kill them as well and get some
exp later like if we die
here nothing
true actually I'm going to play the
b
i yeah ooh we should have like a cooking
pot here too we can like totally have
some stuff going around do you need
something for the cooking pot I don't
think I can craft
[Music]
it
okay okay it's still struggling
oh this is kind of difficult
um you can maybe put it on the other
side here um can you help me destroy
this thing yeah yeah it doesn't make me
[Music]
P use a shovel on this oh there you go
uh shovel
oh yeah you're
right yeah and then you might be able to
place your stuff in the in the
middle oh I did the bed here I place the
bed here oh nice okay
oh does this
do oh yeah kind
of wait did it climb up no no no no okay
I just heard something struggling I
don't think they can clb
slime
right this is a really nice spot yeah I
like it I like it it's pretty safe
too okay
sick all right let me put some of my
stuff here
too
uh building
blocks this this do you have animal
animal fat animal fat I don't I don't
even know what that
[Music]
is
FL yo this is oh kind peaceful yeah I
can probably make a
part let me make a p oh I think it's
trying to come in
[Music]
hold
[Applause]
[Music]
on
yay
[Music]
yay good free exp y
yay okay and then where were
we
iron H I need where I did I use up all
the iron no no no I took it I was trying
to get the I I can put it back oh okay
okay can you I cannot interact with
the I put it back and I was trying to do
the cooking pot but apparently cannot oh
why I don't know why uh maybe I need a
magazine to learn the
recipe or do you need a
campfire
oh I can can make maybe you need a
campfire first hold on let me like uh
small Stone I made one oh you made one
yeah I'm going to position
now is this safe to position in here
should be
okay put it
here go oh this so cozy
[Laughter]
man
oh the cooking pot
now uh let's see cooking pot
right oh yeah we can boil water oh wait
we need cooking
pot oh how do we make cooking pot I have
like forged iron so I thought maybe that
could do collector o do
collector
pots let me try again pot oh cooking pot
okay there it is iron oh 31 iron and uh
six clay I think the iron oh oh no no no
it doesn't make me do it for some
reason wait can you give it to me yes
that's it I'll put it
here look done I wonder why it doesn't
work hold on what oh man them again
don't worry I take care of it no it's
okay we worry about it when they come
up oh we need a forge for this
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Forge
and Hey where's my shotgun work
station be careful
oh that's a light uh where's work work
station
work
work you good I am
okay you're going you're kind of choked
up man okay okay I feel better
now why can't
I is it because my shovel is
broken I mean my axe oh see a I go
downstair I want to check the situation
okay you feel free to close the door
okay plant fibers and wood
oh there is also TV
Co the
couch oh it's so cozy
yeah I'm going to put the
camping back okay and then okay it's
morning here oh hey let's
go 9 mm
ammo uh yeah
yeah and
[Music]
sort yeah oh this is so nice okay okay
oh we can also close
this what is this no cannot use
it do you see
any
no d
okay let's see let me reinforce
this okay good there a key next to the
door
and oh yeah you're right I cannot get
it and then
this did something happen no like I got
the
key oh oops I got a key of the door and
I could up I could open it but now I
don't know how to put it
again
um just take this and then coffee beans
I don't know what I'm going to do with
that and then
this I can probably just die honestly so
I'm just going to put everything
here it's
backed let me check I can probably build
something around to
[Music]
protect
yeah oh man this is so
cozy it's like
home yeah it feels very
homey I just want the the the cooking
part so I can cook
too yeah
yeah oh we need a
door yeah I I I I'm crafting
doors
[Music]
okay oh oh iron cell door that's
cool need do iron
door
yeah oh all the doors are broken I need
forging iron but okay I'm going to put
like wooden wooden doors anyway
here put it
here I have five forged
iron oh really yeah uh it's in the crate
upstairs okay I could get it now I'm
going to position this door first I need
to break this one oh how do you lock it
uh so I think it's either back
or I want to break it anyway oh this
this
bucket don't worry I'm going to put I'm
going to put more doors new
doors oh
[Music]
cornmeal there we go okay new door I'll
make a new door on this
side
yeah except I put everything God damn
it it's difficult
position is he okay I don't know it
should be
okay
okay okay oh yeah yeah it's okay it's
okay at least it's
locked okay kind of
works um I'm going to go make some iron
uh iron door too
[Music]
okay IR why is it
pink does pink cats no not
you here oh God
no oh I need more forged iron how do you
make Forge
tyon uh you need a
forge and we don't have a forge yet
[Music]
yeah is that that door already
reinforced I don't know do we need more
iron I I have the iron I think oh if you
right cck you can take half of the
supplies a
sorry okay no thank
you no thank you okay the iron I can't
find it anymore I lost the iron do you
see the
three iron should be
I don't have do we use all oh no no I
see it I see it okay
okay I need to unlock the workstation I
I'm going crazy I need
workstation wait oh this is already
improved oh it is already improved
workstation I need a magazine I
think oh we got to explore more then
okay yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah let's go visit Traders can we go
back to the um uh Trader first yeah yeah
let's go okay
okay H Let
Go
magine magazine I me the works if I if I
unlock the workstation we have a lot of
things we can do yeah and like a cooking
pod would be really good then we don't
have to kill each
other is a
solution that's another house is this
looted already I don't know you want to
check oh wait I think I no I think this
is where Gigi was oh oh is the same one
yeah I think so oh okay
mind
yeah oh yeah yeah I recognize the with
truck okay let's
go I hope the trade is going to give me
something nice this time the the the the
weapon was so helpful though yeah the
shotgun yeah yeah the
[Music]
shotgun though like I feel like it
doesn't do that much
damage no but at least a long distance
weapon
so oh my
stamina to relax
[Music]
hey
hey okay this very CL on me there's
always way
[Music]
oh here we are oh by the way you can
mark the Waypoint on the map just to let
you know so you in Cas like you don't
need you don't have to check the map all
the
time oh yeah the Waypoint yeah you can
mark the Waypoint so you like find the
way pretty easily yeah yeah oh my God
damn you smell like the dead you better
have money
okay rewards what do I
get Crafting skill magazine bundle guess
you ain't that damn bad after all oh I
want this
one tracting improves weapon
[Music]
handling grilled meat probably this one
honestly you just called me damn [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
listen up jackass you want work I
thought you I don't like you you're
turning me down I ought to put a bullet
in that name's not important well I've
had enough you I don't like you you're I
don't like you either I ought I got some
[\h__\h] work for a nobody tells me no get
this son of a out of my side which one
should we clear oh my God I got so much
so many so many um
magazin oh I got home cooking weekly
okay let me use it I got work to do if
you don't come on getting your hand
where I wonder if I can share one with
you I have two bathe before coming to a
job
interview oh wait whoops I I can share
one with
you how do I abandoned my
quest
a what did you got what quest did you
got I got I have tier one clear and tier
one
fetch
okay let me check if they have any quest
for me they don't have any job for me
what
why the the list is empty maybe it's
back or something
[Music]
he says I have no work at this
time
[Applause]
huh ah CR uh I have take this uh take
all of this hold on why the magazine
because I have more I have extra oh no
no it's okay it's okay like if I finish
the quest I can I can get him so that's
all no because I already I already used
them I'm not going to do anything with
them yeah you can later nice stack
though no no no take it take it take
it it'll be useful in the future no I
already read
them you you read them
again it it Stacks oh it's Stacks yeah
yeah yeah oh really I think
so I don't think so I I I thought it did
no nothing
happened really oh
well I'll
try
okay oh yeah you can actually start yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah right okay oh okay
okay thank you I didn't know I thought
it was
extra
yeah nice nice okay uh let's see the
quest I have I just have oh no I have
the F oh I think because you got the
quest
huh and we are in the group shows to me
as well oh maybe because I haven't
accepted the quest but I can still see
on the quest
list so I have tier one Fetch and tier
one
clear right
now nice
okay look we can do the tier
one fetch I think
sick let's
go hello there Travelers hello oh hello
hello Quest are you
questing yeah yeah do you want to Quest
together yeah heck yeah yeah let's go he
says he doesn't have any any quests
right now though oh it it says the same
for me but then I joined uh like in the
Cron's party it shows the
quest in my list as well so maybe if we
make one
party oh we can share the quest yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah let's do it woo okay
I'm going to invite you
then
cool
uh people and
mor okay I said
okay
um I have to leave the party first oh
can you invite me one more time of
course oh God it's so
expensive okay I'm in Mar I think you
have to leave your party as well to join
us leave it yeah yeah okay how do you
leave leave uh so click on the party
icon and try to click on leave
okay players oh no I'm not in a party
right now let me
my
yeah I got I got a quest just now as
well oh yeah Quest started yeah Quest
started okay okay I see them now
[Music]
mhm yeah if you click on your Quest
Leist you're going to see like
everyone's
Quest
okay why won't he let me see his
inventory are you glitched again I don't
know what's going on that's fine let's
make more money together and then maybe
I'll try and buy something yeah we got
about 30 minutes after all so let's do
something hi gather
okay gather shall we we shall ladies
ladies let's go
uzoo go this
way is this a clear Mission we're going
to kill zombies heck
yeah oh yeah I finally found a cooking
Dr like can make grilled Co what is this
like Tick Tock boom
effect I don't know what you're talking
about you hear something
strange wait uh my can you kill me first
because I have very little
health and I'll do it I'll do it I'll do
it all right you sound oddly excited
about that she's a murderous type tell
you what oh can you kill me actually I'm
also low okay yeah I'll do it thank
you awesome this is why Friendly Fire is
on friends it's very helpful sharing is
caring sharing is caring you don't need
to kill me though I'm good I'm good
really yeah I'm good
although I could be at full
health think about
it yeah you know you could be at 100 HP
yeah you know go ahead take me out grony
take me out back really what's your
what's your health right now 68 okay
yeah I help 69 thank
you ah my ladies I can always trust them
I can always count on them
now I understand why you guys were
killing each other it all makes sense
now yeah yeah we were doing it out of
Good Intentions oh wow how sweet what a
what a kind world we live
[Music]
in all righty on my way
back yay oh are you guys doing uh little
hand stands together making a little
human to Totem
po yeah
yeah maybe I can join it's a little
difficult with three
people but I bet it's possible why don't
you jump on me and then you jump on
people oh good idea yeah oh yeah oh okay
here we
go oh that was an awesome idea now look
we're can I can I jump with you guys on
can
you oh wa wait let let me try Okay
no no look at us effing around when we
have a
fre can't be help can't be
helped also oh there's apparently an exp
debt from dying actually
oh oh what does that mean pretty sure
that you have to get a certain amount of
exp Before You Can level up again but I
don't know if they took that off for our
server oh hm I hope so we'll have to
see they might not have
only after level six okay yeah be
careful after level six you take a
penalty oh it's
okay we at level
three yeah be fine wait how can I check
my level uh if you press Tab and go to
your character oh okay thank
you all right we're here we're here time
to clear yes in the mines the mushroom
Mining Company get my gun ready I'm a
little low for some
reason okay oh we here oh yes ladies I'm
ready oh yeah okay I'm ready I too am
ready let's go let's
go let's
go how did that happen e it's like a
blood big blood bag bursty yeah it's
like
gushers didn't we just do this one
people yeah we did just do this one but
I guess we oh be careful be careful
watch
out yeah killing zie my
favorite
yeah hell yeah be careful to don't that
because I think you're going to fail the
quest don't die if you die it's very bad
oh oh nice one okay
oh there's still another
one good job ladies yay
teamwork yeah what the heck where do we
go next down here vible knows the
way oh it's crawling ready o
mushrooms oh no I need to repair my my B
stick hold up I love mushrooms
ah oh whoops oh
yikes good job
team of
here we
Harvest
yummy uh oh here's another
boy okay Mario Mario actually doesn't
like mushrooms or something
anyway what are you talking about oh no
nothing nothing
wait Mario isn't Mario the guy doesn't
like
mushrooms Mario doesn't like mushrooms
oh I mean I guess that makes sense
because he keeps like killing the people
yeah it say so in the Mario movie yeah
oh makes
sense
ow I'm going to drop some shotgun parts
for you you can have them thank
you
[Applause]
yeah man that was rude team cuz we can
help each other with the things that we
all want to individually excel at you
know
yeah oh I guess we can go up from
here wait what was like wait you guys
there's a ladder there's
a wait oh oh mushrooms for
ouro okay
uh-oh ow oh
sorry a little bit of Friendly Fire
oh it's okay my vision's blurry oh I'm
losing blood alive wait what the
heck it's okay it's okay my knife makes
people
bleed I got an achievement for killing
zombies yay get the goodies ladies wait
wait for me a splint
ooh oh we got to destroy this one this
one gives you Goods you think so yeah
this one you got to break
it o nice motor tool
Parts haars oh there's a lot of shotgun
ammo here Cali you want to look in the
boxes yes thank you oh these do armor
parts I'll just keep collecting
them thank you
y good job everybody we completed the
quest let's get the F out of
here
ow oopsies don't Hur other
ladies I am on my last
leg oh
God it's okay we'll be fine there should
be no zombies on the way out it's not
night time yet or even close so we'll be
okay
yay please I want to go down the hole
okay there we go L
first okay wow I'm a
lady that's
right just just ignore my giant beard
and
ball it's just a look right now you know
it's the highest fashion at this moment
for a high class lady
let's go get some money let's go get our
rewards yeah I want I want I hope I can
get the magazin to learn the workbench
workstation oh yeah that'd be very
useful I'm looking for it maybe the
reason I can't accept any more Quest is
because I already accepted this Quest
yeah you're on you're on a quest already
probably I don't know how to no I didn't
go a quest
either I don't know why well return to
traitor now yeah it says to go to the
Traer so let's go why is it still
exclamation mark yeah but I think we did
the the the quest anyway let's go to the
Traer yeah let's just go back trust the
proc yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's cool it's cool place of
interest is on cool down oh top right
okay gotcha daily limits to Quest oh oh
oh I see can't have us getting too
strong too
fast guess it makes
sense what all the wood we got to really
fortify our base tomorrow before the
rush that's going to be the biggest
thing we got to do fortify I think the
first thing I'm going to do tomorrow is
just cook a bunch of corn so we just
have a big supply of food oh yeah do you
have any recommendations of what to do
tomorrow yeah so there's going to be a
rush I think that we need to stay at the
house that we've already established and
fortify it so try and just protect it as
much as we can gather as much ammo as
possible and pray we don't
die and tomorrow it starts an hour
earlier correct yes
okay okay okay thank you for letting me
know oh an hour early I thought it was
an hour
later oh it's an hour earlier so that uh
kiaha and Cecilia can join a little
easier
you can do whenever you want it's just
that's when the server will open okie
dokie hey jackass can well I guess I'm
going to have to pay you now that you
did
it wow it's really not a lot of stuff in
here tools digest what's
that may harvesting tool yeah I need
[Applause]
that we
do I I can pick another Quest do I get
the clear zombie maybe or fetch what is
fetch I don't know we tried to do fetch
but we died before we could figure out
oh okay I do clear zombie
[Applause]
then water cooler ooh LGE pipes Plumbing
fixtures appliances ooh a real stove to
cook on maybe someday okay that be nice
okay nice get a
beer
okay I'm going to hold on to my money
there's nothing I want right now we
already have all this
stuff wow he cursed at yeah he's really
mean you say that so
casually yeah he's just a main
guy s off shotgun mod schematic that'd
be really
awesome well need a little more money
[Applause]
who wanted to be a farmer did you want
to be a farmer Callie yeah oh right here
I'm dropping this for you oh thank you
what's
that oh a farming book
oh yay I've unlocked tier one cotton we
can grow
cotton stone tools quality
too
o three out of
20 yay oh my that's cute paint brush
[Applause]
nice you have two points
available
lucky lter is
good okay I'll get this put away your
weapon unless you'd like to die in my
store o Harvest more crops that's
big this is also big pain tolerance
doors don't need them now this is also
big pack mule nah I'm just going to make
Pockets skills Yay good job do we have
time for another
quest uh what
time what time is it call us in a little
over 15 minutes I think we can do it the
take too long yeah yeah I just can't I
can't collect any more quests sadly oh I
have another quest uh okay let's do
yours it's
uh
clear you want to follow me heck yeah I
do okay let's go let's go it's not too
far right no it's like 600 M away away
that's not bad
yeah all right let's do it
yes for
survival what kind of weapons are you
guys using I'm using the bow I like it
oh do you want B crafting books I have
you have it I like B I forgive I forgive
you for
being here you go very nice of you thank
you's got she's really Scavenging she's
got all the goodies yeah yeah I'm
picking I'm picking the crafting books
as
rewards so we can up our skill s smart
can someone kill me oh oh sure yes I
level six right I live B no I'm
not I will give you an honorable death
oh wait a gun would be a waste of ammo
oh
okay a good
point nice sick thank
you I'd love to be able to punch zombies
in the face yeah but I'm more of like a
club girl more of a shotgun
girl what's wrong with archers well when
you're far away and you're trying to
attack them and they shoot you with
arrows and then all their dudes fly
forward with big swords and there's a
freaking archer in the back it's like
you got to aim for the Archer first you
know that's true I like archers I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm just really not an
Archer fan oh I mean I like archers why
why you yeah you play a game and an
Archer I have oh and they're in the way
back of the pack and they send all their
buddies forward with their swords you're
cool with
that yeah as long as I'm on you know
their side oh well yeah if we're on the
same side that's one
thing isn't this the same one we just
did is it is
it yeah is it
oh or is it further that
way out of range and we fail that's not
true they're all right here well let's
go toward the one you have the one the
one that
ra
has is is a different place it looks
like on follow me girls follow me okay
trailer do you think we can eliminate
the stuff in
there could look at
that goodies are in there
oh this would be a nice place there's
nothing there's nothing here wait wait
for me I'm a little bit behind it's okay
I'm behind you the trailer trailer
doesn't matter I'm also behind oh yeah
it's here it's here I think we're all
behind right now I got I'm over cucumber
so I might be a little slower that's
okay we got to wait no the quest is
actually over here what yeah my quest is
over here exclamation point right it's
over there
what follow
me wait no I'm in the wrong group what
the
heck it's another ear oh yeah these are
different people yeah I was like yeah
they all look the same so I was
confused oh I probably made it there I'm
going to wait here for you guys where
are you guys at good time oh
uh over here this this way this way
yeah where is this way oh oh you guys
with uh who else is there is behind you
Kiara Okay g and his FAA with them I
think I wait for you guys here yeah
we're just chilling here all good they
fell for the same group that's really
funny oh that's why they said hies a you
got come to with other people so silly
really
Ah that's
okay an eye out for bird nest for Mass
producing arrows oh yeah if you like if
you like to shoot uh arrows as an Archer
just keep your eye open for for bird
nests cuz they've got all the feathers
you yeah yeah I got all the feather yeah
yeah yeah I will take any 9
mm bullet I will take all your shotgun
shells my guy
oh this should be pretty easy The Smoke
House we got to smoke him out oh yeah
I'm going to hit him in the head this
time I promise guys I promise let's
smoke them
yep oh yeah I think we're all here I
think yeah I'm I'm I'm waiting
here are you wait where are you oh there
you are where up here there we go Quest
marks right here yes exactly do it yay
time so maybe we got to get them to get
angry they're walking around getting all
up in their stuff up in their Turf
maybe
oohay with the area oh there we go they
they're the red points on the map I'll
take everything and show you
later oh red points on the map there's
zombie Birds oh okay oh boy hello
grandpa yeah head
[Applause]
shot oh got the birds need to get the
okay nice o what's
this ooh medical journal SC
nice there should be another one around
here yeah there's there's one in the
tent I think oh this one May oh this one
yeah yeah this guy
this I found some 99 mm
[Applause]
bullets thank you which weon uh sorry
which weapons are you using I'm using
pistol so I need 9 mm okay if I find
I'll give you that's I have
bullet hey bio I found home cooking
weekly oh that would be useful
ooh there also a five shotgun here if
you guys
want I already have one so I'm good but
thank you let me dump some
trash hobo stew okay we're done with the
quest B
Vehicles throw that throw
that hey bio where are you yeah I'm
behind you okay right here so you don't
get confused with the other items this
is for you uh let's see six
n cooking thank you
B har
more I can make I can make tea now we
can have a tea yay tea you like
Wasteland Treasures Volume
7 I don't really know I think it's about
constructing things does anybody like
building stuff
building stuff Builders here I'm Not
Sure Shot level two oh wait what is it a
better one oh we get honey from this
this is
awesome a where by chance did you find
the shotgun from
before from the quest oh did you get it
as a reward yeah you get to choose which
weapon you get to have oh heck there is
a pipe shotgun in here oh where'd you
find it B uh here in the tent yeah on
this armor pile or yeah ammo pile is it
level two it is level two oh I'll grab
that
then and get that
repair there we go wow I didn't know
there were different
levels interesting oh okay well we'll
hold on the shotguns so we can give them
to maybe people that don't have weapons
tomorrow during the Big R yeah yeah yeah
yeah
good idea nice job let see if we can
clear this Quest we did team yeah let's
go back to the trader okay good job team
we did it we saved the city good job yay
yay
y
y got to find a more reliable way to get
ammo though for sure yippee yeah if we
can cross it that would be good oh
surely there's a recipe
somewhere yeah
maycraft you just got to find the
magazine for the specific type of
Amo it would be nice to be able to have
a
forge yeah maybe we can build one though
there should be some time maybe
tomorrow oh apparently you make shotgun
ammo with paper so I guess Callie
collect
paper I didn't know that I just threw
some paper out of my
inventory oh well we'll get him next
time oh we have some paper like at the
main base oh yeah yeah oh paper and what
else I wonder maybe we need the recipe
for
it
yeah I wonder like if there is a fastest
way to uh Craft um sorry to raise your
points for the skill tree like maybe
farming zombies is a good way M that
that's to level up your stats stats but
like for like skills like
crafting um and unlocking crafting like
recipes that's
magazines yeah what about um the
challenges though the daily challenges
they're not daily challenges not daily
but if you press y all those challenges
yeah if you complete them you also get
exp for your skill
te well spamming spamming these Quest
seem good too because these these quests
have uh magazines as
rewards
yeah quests are the best that's the
that's the thing to remember is quests
are the
best very funny to do with friends by
the way like I think doing quests with
part is way easier and
fun way easier to level up I think
ha gunpowder I'm finally here
yeah tra taking a
look what you got big hitters I could
use that for my club wheel didn't we
agree first job was going to be free DN
I got
gunpowder I got gunpowder I got we're
going to have paper eventually corn I
wonder if he has
pellets Wist that could be good nerd
[Applause]
outfit
yeah let's
see get the job on and then interested
in shotgun oh I'm level
four does anybody here need bullet cas
this definitely give you diarrhea not
yet but I feel like we'll need it if we
were to craft
ammo yeah going to get some bandages I
got tomorrow cooking weekly cooking
magazine B Bo if you need oh okay I drop
it
here D I wanted to give him a
present you're going to give him a
present I know
that guy
sucks I I met I met the other Squad oh
but I think they're a little bit weary
of me because I pointed guns at them
understand do you have
any I'm getting lots of lots of ammo
stuff I wonder when we can make ammo
though that's going to be big yeah
that'll change the game did you drop the
thing oh yeah it's here it's here one of
them is just trash so don't it w I'll
take bullet casing just in case it can
be used to make bullets oh yeah yeah I
the inventory full that's why I have to
put it
there pleas good up everyone today
y we only have about 4 minutes left but
good job everybody
yeah so good glad doing great oo woohoo
so that nice getting some good
money PCH PCH PCH PCH PCH very excited
to continue playing with you guys yeah
fun well I'll see I'll see I'll catch
you guys on the flip side then
whenever see you guys tomorrow okay see
you guys tomorrow tom
byebye by bye bye-bye bye
byee
a thank you guys for coming by it was
fun and I hope
[Applause]
to fix my sleep schedule soon cuz it's
been a mess
yeah and I can't wait to do the
challenge yay I finally get to know what
it's
like
[Music]
Yay like for example yesterday I was up
until 5 did I already tell you that I
don't even remember but yeah it's a mess
all right
but okay see you guys
tomorrow yay have a great one guys yay
I'm going to try to sleep earlier
M
okay
[Music]
byebye same time tomorrow I oh know um
because they said it was going to be an
hour early
so
yeah but it was fine
[Music]