DET
[Music]
A
that
[Music]
H
T
[Music]
Ta
This turn is brought to you by Misao
[Music]
Masu Dub
O
[Music]
every
alsoThereisSpecial
EXTRAattheendofv
makestay
for
every
backdayisthe20epeI
thoughtknowforthe
20THepeIneedSpecial
forguysand
areSpecialTalk
EPbringtotheoneand
onlythatLet
metalkasI think I explained it as usual at first,
so listen to it.TalkisLIFEtalkwith
thep
andlyJapaneseHLIFE
tal
TALENTBR
asesVI
ost
Takahota  This is an interview in English.The
purpose is to let people from overseas know more about Mr. Yago, who is mainly a Japanese talent while he is still alive.He
will be a talent today.It
is brought to you by the host Takasekihara.So,
today is 20.  It's already the 20th time, so we've
prepared a special guest.For the 10th time, I
think it was A-chan, and for the 20th time, it's Yago.So for the
30th time, it'll be the same.I'm already
worried, but it looks like it's going to be hot.Today's
Ehoro.  TalkIhope
everyonewillenjoy
todayHTalkforgetby
thewaysinceAVery
SpecialEpisode
PleaseUseTheHASHthe
hasagHTalkevenin
EnglishorinJapanese
toTweetaboutWhatyou
seetodayWhatyouhear
todayMaybeevenwith
somescreenshotsHashtag
Holotalk on TwitterI'd
love to hear your thoughts and screenshots.
Thank you very much, Yago-
san. I'm not very excited.
Well, it's not my first time,
but this is the first time I've talked properly like this
. I see.
[Music]
LIFE Today we're going to talk about Hol Live and
a lot of things about Ya-san.  I would like to find out more about it,
but are you ready? This is my husband.
Thank you. Yes, but first of all, I would
like you to introduce yourself. I would like you to introduce yourself,
either in English or Japanese,
please.  Yes, HMyName
Tani CEOofcorporation
our
prodthankforinv
me I'm sorry I
made a mistake Ah yeah I made a mistake I should
say thank you for invitmetotalk I
can't do it Oh no no that's perfect You're a
wonderful guy and you can speak English pretty well
Hey, I thought of this myself I asked you to
teach me a little bit I
can't help it  Yes, that's right.
Everyone knows Yago, so I do
n't think he really needs to introduce himself,
but I'd like to get to the questions right away. Well, that's the
first
question.  But what kind of activities have you been doing lately
? Well, lately I've been
doing a lot of work for the company, like
conducting job interviews, deciding on company policies,
and thinking about how to improve the company's organization.
Yes, I see.
[Music]
says
aswsComp
ORC
orimpr
[Music]
That
's a perfect answer, so I'll move on to the next one. No, Yago
's name is Yag.  I'd
like you to tell me the origin of ``Yago''
Well, ``Yago'' means a platter.It all started when
Mr. Thread couldn't read the valley in my name and
mispronounced it as ``Yago.''
Well, I actually knew that.  Just
in case, I heard about it, Subaru-senpai. It was quite a while ago.
How long ago? How long
ago? Quite a while ago, right? About two years ago, two years ago.
Before that, I used to call Mi-chan by her book name.
Until then.  I guess I
didn't really get called by name during broadcasts, but
that has changed quite a bit.
Especially lately, I've been introducing some kind of merchandise,
or appearing in a few videos of some weird super bit.
Mr. Yago has been appearing in various ways recently, but I
don't feel like it's a little tough at Momosha and now.As I said
earlier, what kind of work do you
do?There are things like filming and recording.  Oh
yeah, I also do photo shoots. I
'm a model
. I'm a super model.
Thank you very much. I'm so thankful. I see. I
don't have any bad feelings. I'm glad
it's all of you. It's
very helpful. Holoto.  To
be honest, at first I said jokingly that I would invite Mr. Yako for a day,
but I
didn't think he would actually come.Thank
you very
much.
agylongtimeAGtried
toreadHISnameonam
butShereadthekanj
wrongThereislike
severalwaystoread
kanjAsYouMightknow
andmademistake
instead
ofandfromthereonIGU
EverybodypickedUpon itandIasked untilcallhiminstead
ofand
rightnowhesooften
SocialMedialike
showing
merchandise youothermers
streamslikefor
feelingshesaysNohe
isveryhappytohelp
outWhereverHeCan
WheneverHeCanYeahso
helikestohelpout
likethatandiisaid
thatIoriginally just
saidthatweshould
invitejagasajoketo
mytomySTREAMWHOLE
Talk
butYeahIthinkit
wouldreallyhappenI
thinkhewouldsayyes
butHEREWEAREHeis
Partoftalknow20TH
Episodesoreally
happyaboutthatand
thenIsaid
Sorryforbutsaidthat
Thereare
surprisinglySome
peopleWhoknoweven
InsideoftheCompand
have
Specialprep
foralsowantESP
person
Watchfor  I'd
like to take a look
at the first one
[Music]
have
Yes, this is an amazing design.
Wow, this is written on the shoulder. I
think it's very nice.
[Music]  ]
It stinks, it
stinks, it looks stinky It seems like Yamume-chan doesn't know about Yago-san. I've
seen this and that. That's right. I've seen that.
Ah, I'm sorry my little one
said something like this.  I don't think you really know
that, but you're
such a forgetful child, so I'm sorry.
Yeah, were you shocked when you saw this?
Well, that's probably true. He was moving so much. I didn't
understand. He was probably wearing a mask too.
[Music]
Now let's move on to the next question.THENEXTQuestionPlease
tell us about your activities and work before founding the company.I
see, since I graduated from that university...  When I
first joined a game company, I
worked as a game producer.
After that, I joined an internet company, and
before that, I
started my own internet company.
Yes, I see. Mayof guadfromuniversity JO ofwasworkafter that ofLOCAL inform serv ofedBusinessand managedturn, the last one is the Internet service company.
OkSothatnotsame.  Well,
how many years did it take from when I graduated from that university until I was able to do the cover
? If I say that, I feel like my age will be revealed,
but I don't want my age to be revealed,
right? It's been quite a while since I graduated from that university.  That's right, I'm going to university. Yes, I'm pretty sure. I
'd say it
's a conclusion, but I'm going to explore it a little more.
What's your
average work day?
What is your schedule like?
Tell me in detail.  Yes, this is what I
do after I wake up, right? In the morning, I
wake up around 7 o'clock and go for a run, and then I
go for a run every day on weekdays.
After that, I have a lot of conversations three times a week.  After studying, I
go to work around 10 o'clock.Before
I go to work, I have A conversations several times a week.Well, I
study about 3 times.Amazing, amazing, yes, yes.After
that, after going to a meeting, it's like that.  I
do about 23 interviews a day, then go home a few times, and the
rest of the time I'm doing my own work.Well,
my job is
thinking about the company's strategy, etc.  Work
Yes, yes, I see. I get home
by about 9 o'clock.
OKHehasverybusyDay
everysousuallywakes
upat7amandheGoes
runningeveryweek
rightafterwakingupI
reallyRespectThat
Thatwasasasurprisehe
staysFithestaysbuff
runseveryweekday
beforeWorkand
actuallysaidtimesa
weekbeforeWORKhealsoparticipatesinlikeEnglishlessonnotaproperlessonmorelikeaconversationTh ing
whereyoujusttalkto
someonewhospeaks
EnglishandThrough
conversationyou
learnthelanguage
Theydothatlikethree
timesaweekandthenhe
goestoworkataround
10amuntil9PMand
withinthose11hours
Whathedoesis
andenheattend
[Music]
and
AboutRunning
every day is probably good for your body,
but you never
find the time to do that.  I'm surprised
. It's very difficult.
[Music]
Yeah, let's move on to the next question.
Ejajin. I
want you to tell me about the birth and death that started Eka. I
also want you to tell me what the environment was like before Hol Live started.
Well, it's a life-or-death situation, but I had
experience working at a game company and an Internet company, so I thought, uh, I wonder if I could use that experience to
start a content company.  In the
future, I'm going to
start a business in VR and do things like develop games.  Eh,
before Hol Live started, were you doing any kind of game
development? I see. You
were making something like that VR table tennis game. What
kind of game is it? It's a table tennis game. Table tennis.
[Music] I
see. Next question.  This is connected to this,
but
how did Eno go from being a technology company to an idol management company
? Well, my company is still a technology
company, but also a talent company.  I
think it's a company that also manages Hololive, so I started Hololive after gaining experience managing
Tokiso-san and then Roboco-san.
I
see.StillConsidercompybeTECHCompany
asDo
Management and
laterJOINaswelland
startedmaningthose
talentsandafter
experiencefromthat
They
GENERATIONI'd
like to ask you a little more about what happened after that,
but I wonder
how that happened, so you
suddenly decided to include that idol.
Well, when I was making that VR game, I was
thinking, ``Why can't I use this VR
device to say something like Nemic?
'' And while I was thinking about it, something like that happened to me, Sora-
chan.  It's
like we've started testing the idea of ​​running a virtual talent.
[Music]
Idolsandsaidwhile
makingVGameshe
wantedtousedeviceto
sestThank you very much.Let's
move on to the next question.
What kind of image did you have before launching Hololive,
and has it
changed much since your initial vision?
Well,
when you first launched Hololive, it was like you
were coming from the real world or another world.  I had the impression that they were a group of broadcasters.Yes,
well, while we're still operating, we
performed our first overall broadcast at Hololive Summer,
and after that, we had a non-stop
story and performed live performances in uniform costumes.
As a result of my experiences there, I feel that my idol side has become more noticeable than my real life.Fromuniversoreven
THEREALWORLDlike
anyandthenCome
TogetherasaGroupso
forexampleWHOLE
Summertheyputout
theirfirstORIGINAL
SongFromlikeall
talentstogetherand
thenTherewasNONSTOP
whereforthefirst
timehadaconcert
wherelikeeveryone
wasingthesamekindof
[Music] I'm
sure that famous comment.  However, I
wanted to create an idol group like AKB. That's right. I
said it like I'm running the AKB group. I just said that.
I personally think that's pretty much the case.
Cross  I like Frontier and things like that,
so I know what you mean. I
knew I had a dream about that virtual idol, Al Talent, but I see.
Say
4islikethebiggest
IdolGroupthepopular
IDGroupJapanandhe
sayslikelikesFRfor
EXhe
alsoto
Sheryl
is a fan. Oh, I see, she's a Cheryl fan. Yeah, that's great.
saidmoreFcertain
IDsaidAF
ofOther than that Hololive, my
favorite is Sheryl
. Well, she might be one of my favorites.
Well, yes, she's pretty, she's good at singing, and she's very good.
Yeah, I think it's an idol-like presence.
Yeah, but from that first
image, many people have said that Yago-san's
image has changed to the point where he's probably crying,
but yeah, that's what I originally thought.  I think the
current state of Hol Live is quite
different from the image I had.I think it's a
more interesting group than I imagined.
Yes, that's right,
here with the
cat But I've
prepared another one, so I'm
going to theST, so please
take a look.  It was a
little bit like greeting him, but he was
smiling so much. Why is Yago always smiling so much? The
captain was smiling and saying, "I'm sure he's got a lot of heart,
but I'll do my best."
When I did the guts pose, Yago was also smiling and squealing with a big smile.It's
real!I
thought, ``The captain is real,'' Yago said.I was so surprised,
Yago yelled.
No, she doesn't do that at all. She's so kind. She's so
kind. She cries when something sad happens.
Yago cries like this on this trip. She's
very charming, and
even when something bad happens, she doesn't yell at me.  I do
n't know, but I don't know. I wonder if he's
yelling at his employees. But,
hey, the employees are also complaining. They're
praising Yago a lot. He
seems like a really
nice person. He seems like he's kind.  I
was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying, I was crying.  I
wonder if they won't stream it. I don't mind if it's as popular as Ego. Why don't we make it more popular on April Fool's Day?
Yago is still 2D. It's still 2D.
Hey, Yago was wearing a new costume today.  Yago
had a new outfit
[Music]
Yeah, that's right, Fu-chan had a new outfit today, and Chan and
Dakke-chan.
Ah, it looks like that today. Fu-
chan had a new Yago today. I think he was
taking some pictures.  I don't care if it's a photo shoot or
not, but today
when I was sitting on Corone-senpai's lap, Sago came over to say hello, and
Ko-senpai was pumping his knees, and the
captain
greeted him with a grin.  It
was so awkward. I was in a weird mood.
Oh, I see. I see. LetMOVback so ofhave 3D Now is the time to make my 3D debut. This might be my 3D debut. Maybe, maybe, that's it.
What's more, this is a new book.  It
's a new book about a certain piece of clothing.
Oh, where is it? The shirt is
new since 2013. Oh, the
unveiling of the new outfit. The unveiling of the wonderful 3D. The
new shirt. I'm already so excited
. Hey!
havethinkcouldand
alsoaboutifThisisa
newoutfitthathas
beforeButhesaysTHE
tshirtTHEshirt
underneathisSowe
haveSpecialreveals
todayhisnewoutfit
And
HisIthinkVery
SpecialtodaybythewayBy
the way,
all the talent said they had
seen Yago cry,
but I have
n't.  I wonder if you'll have to let me see it or
not.I wonder if I'll have to make myself cry.Maybe Yago-
san puts a lot of emotion into his work, so I think he'll
be able to show everyone crying.Nene is
like this right now.
SaidThatthinks
ThatEverybodyhas
seenHISCryingFACE
beforebutI
personallyhavenever
seenItmaybeIneedto
makehimCryOneDayand Isaidthat
perhapsis
emotionally invested intoLIFEandknowHIS CompanyHISBabyso Maybefeelslike
Bubbabu MayMay
B I would like to ask about one more thing,
but yes, Mr. Yago, I have an image of him being
very kind to those members, and to the entertainers,
but I don't
think I've ever seen anything but kindness to the employees.  Are you
sure
you're strict? Nema: Maybe you're strict when you have to be strict. I
see.
[Music]
AllasSweetandperson
Who
neverHIS
says
must ask Mr. Bunsha
that he's the best boss and kind.  I don't
think so. Well, I can say that it was a clip from Marin-senpai,
but let's move on to the next question.
THENEXTquestion
Well, what is the most important thing when hiring new talent? I
guess it's motivation, right? Yeah, that's it.
Mr. Holotalk has done it 20 times today,
so I
think it must be quite difficult to continue broadcasting activities,
and I think that if the person himself is not motivated, he
won't be able to continue, so
most of all.  Personally, I think motivation is the most
important thing.  Yes, there
was a debut. Yes, we
always meet before the debut.
BecauseWetalkedabouthimdoingalotofintervieweverydaybutthoseareforlike
newemployeesForThe
companynotlike
talentsandIaskedhim
ifheStilltakespart
inAUDITIONinthe
auditioningprocess
ifhechecksOUTifhe
doeslikethe
interviewsforNew
talentsaswellandhe
saysthatthesedaysNo
notanymoreButhe
makessuretoalways
likeBeforetheDEBUT
kindofintroduce
himselftotheTALENT
SothatTheyknowwhoYo is
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah no no no no no no no no but that
interview for the talent is left to someone else,
but at the beginning I guess
I was involved after all.  Yeah,
what kind of person were you looking at
? What kind of personality did you see? That
's a difficult question. It's
difficult, but I wonder
if it's a person who is meant for broadcasting.  I
think we were looking at whether we could continue for a long time.Yes,
Oksoas
[Music]
was
Focus
person.I see, for the
next question
[Music], there are
often original songs by the live members, or
songs that they sing together or that they like.  I do
n't have any songs that I sing along with.
Kanema: I'm behind the scenes, so I
want to make sure people don't know about it. Yeah, yeah. I do
n't know the lyrics to Shiny Smiley Story.  I do
listen to it once in a while,
but
in my private life I listen to things like Hololive,
anime songs, and idol songs.I do
n't know, but I listen to a lot of those things,
like the soundtracks of my favorite works.
There may be things like listening to things like
anime
soundtracks, I
see, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks, soundtracks.  Or metal, is
it an anime soundtrack?
Listening to EDM is biased.
EDM is good. I like it too.  I do
n't think I'll go,
Mr. Yago, but that's what happened once.I think he
'll
float.Ki and Kira both
went to that Japan's Irimu concert in that Japan,
but on the contrary, I think Kiara was floating.  Is
n't it Tarake?
No, on the contrary, is it easier to tell when you're wearing a mask
? It's difficult to be a famous person. TTOBE
FAM Yeah, bewithk
recognizable. Let
's move on to the next question. For Jin-eya,
Hololive talent.  What is the thing that you are most respected for?
Well, I guess it's the fact that you are
working hard towards your own goals, right? I've been
given a lot of lessons, and as a result,
my performance has been amazing, and I'm
really moved by the fact that I've really worked hard.  I
see.
[Applause]
comeandtheir
goalsgoingtodance
lonsandimproving
theirSkillseveryand
performComeOutthat
asimpressivehimMOV
After all, I do try to
watch a lot of concerts by those members.Well,
I basically watch all the concerts,
right?That commemorative broadcast.
Streaming is really important, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I see. Everyone is working really hard on those concerts, especially the recent holo
live concerts. The technology is
getting better and better.
[Music] Speaking
of concerts,
what are the highlights of Hololive Surface, which is scheduled to be held in March? I'm so
excited! This is so true. There are so many. I feel like there are a lot of
things that I can't say.
Yes, that's true. I'd
like to provide a live performance that even those who can't come to the venue can enjoy, so please look forward
to it.
No,
no, no, no, but by the time this hole talk
was broadcast, the appearance of that one had already been
announced, so I'll just say that and see. I'm
glad I said that. Well,
this was announced on Friday.
is
Future
RECONfridwasjust
announced will
beare
highlightsandPOINTS
worthyToeButhe
reallysaymuchatall
andalotofSecretif
youcometotheactual
Concertyoucanstill
enjoyityyouknowwhile
towatchITOnlineso
arepreparingtomake
itenjoyableFor
EveryonePleaseforto
andwanttock
[Music] This
is the first time that Ea of Ano Shikataka and ID has appeared, but the
Japanese members of Hololive like this participated.
But why did you decide to include us this time
? Well, right now, Hololive
has become fans from all over the world, so we're in a lot of
different countries.  I wanted to
put on a live show that the people of Japan could enjoy, so I
asked everyone to join me.
Thank you very much. I'm really
looking forward to it, so I'm very happy to be able to participate this time. I'm looking forward to it. I
can't say no.  There are a lot of things,
but everyone, please wait for the Third
Festival.Everyone waitfor
theNowaboutStill
Little
whileareexitfor I
think Wawa will be able to answer the next question in more detail.I
think there are people who don't know about Hololive yet, or Hololive, and Hololive.  Now,
please give me a brief explanation of what each project is.Hiro
Live Alternative and Follower Gama are
related projects, and Follower is a
meta that creates a virtual world that appears in Hololive Alternative.  It
's a Bath project, so I
'm thinking of creating a place where talents and fans can interact with each other. Yeah,
yeah, Hololive error. That's the Hololive
talent's broadcast.  It's a
horror content project that aims to show the other side of the game.Well
, there's also a game out now, so I
hope you'll give it a try.Also,
as for Hololive
Alternative.
Hololive Alternative, which I feel like hasn't been explained yet,
is like that Hololive talent Tagashi.
Is it like Tama-Other, which depicts a world that could be? Yeah, I see.
Yes Maybeguys
[Music]
virworldend
Earthout
[Music]  ]
oftalentsthatare
madeoutoftheVirtual
WORLDthatyouseein
WHOLE
Alternativesothe GOALHereis
toofferaplacewhere
theFans
andtalentstogether
allCanCome
thererecentlycame
OUTagamewhereHorror
GAMEactuallyand
theshow
[Music]
theirSID I
see, they're
working on a lot of projects, yes, yes, they're
busy, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, that you're busy.
Have you tried the full live error yourself?  I have
n't tried it directly yet, so I'd like to try it.What do you think
of the live streaming?
Or maybe
I don't like it, but maybe I'm not good at it.I'm a
little scared of it, so yes, I am
too.  Yes, I see. I
tried
said asked for
trying for
OUTlittle
[Music]
and it's going
to become a hora. I
think they've been able to do it, so
even though Dan Hololive has advanced to number 1 on EN and ID, there are no plans to expand to other countries.  Do you have any plans?
Well, first of all, I'd like to work hard on expanding into the en and ID areas. We've
also just started selling mags,
so I think we'd like to focus our efforts here.
Also, I think it would be great if more
people from overseas knew about Hollow Stars, a male talent, and if
possible, it would be great if we
could translate it for people in other countries as well.  I
think
it would be great to be able to turn it into a book.I think it would be great to be able to translate
content such as holograms and videos for various countries.
[Music]
andTheywantto
alsoLettheoverseas
fandomknowbeabmore
Aware
ofMaletal
HSareBetterwellas
wellandpossible
wantmakepossible
EXtranslatedmore
langues
thatyproperlyBy the way,
recently, especially with Chiara's broadcasts, it's
been very popular with Koreans as well, so I
'm looking forward to the possibility someday.Chiara I
just want to give you a hint.  I
guess it's
because of the secrets that made
people so happy. Thank you very much.  I often watch
what kind of technological developments are being made by companies and indie vtubers.Yes, I
do check the technological developments on a daily basis.Yes, there are quite a few people from overseas who
use VR chat.  Yes, I think there are a lot of people who stream.
Yes, I
can't gather people in real life, so I'm having fun and having fun using VR chat. I
think that's really amazing.
Thank you very much.It's all thanks to Amelia Wasso.I
think Amelia is really amazing.I'm
looking forward to the day when Melia will be behind the scenes.says
thatimpr
[Music]
WaTDooffstu
[  [Music]
vLIFE
Dosays that
stesimpressiveandes
AJIagree Yeah, I've
been watching Ano I, especially Kira, and overseas
vtubers are doing things like live 2D, and I
think it's amazing.
That's right, I
'm already working hard on my own 3D model. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's great.
[Music] I
see.
Makoto no development. Don't give up on the cover. I'm already
working hard. I'm already working hard on the 3D model.
Let's
go to the final question, Dodon and
Yabemeto. I want to eat Aki that matches with Dodon. I want to eat. I want to
collaborate. Yes, yes, no, no, no.
This is a heart, a heart, a
mutual thought. Teruko is
followed by Choco Sensei.
Hey, Choco Sensei, please. It's not Polka Castle. It's
too much, but I'm really
happy. And Nejipet, Nejipet, I see
. That's what I think about the festival, too. Yago and I.  It
's a friend of the soul, a friend of the soul, cat, but it's true that
Minecraft's thumbnail is the same as Polka-chan's,
and I know that we send each other things and replies.  The
correct answer was Lupolka.
Yes, and the next one was
Yago. This is definitely Polka-chan who considers Yago this much as a friend.
That face is certainly Yago-san's. It's amazing that she's not smiling like usual in the photo.
What do you want me to do with Niconico? What did I
do with this? I
think they've already made up their minds. They're all on the same page, so this and that is in my heart, and I think it's in my heart, too.
And then, I see.
[Music] That's
it.  I was wondering if you and Polka-senpai were
such good friends that you could say they were soul mates.At that
time, I was
asked questions in English almost every day, and I was asked to answer them.  I
have an image of something like this:
On Twitter, Polka Polka-senpai
offered Yago-san some English.I
think that was the case.
Hey, yeah, how do you get involved? I don't know, but I have the impression that I get invited to projects quite a lot.  I
have a project to call them
to Borde, so
I have an image of them appearing several times.
Yes, Mr. Tare, yes, I
'm rooting for you.
Anysayes
[Music]
Thank you very much
What do you think Hall live production will be like in 5 years?
For Yako-san, what is your
vision for Kava?  What
is that? Well, I think that in five years' time, Vtubers will be something that everyone around the world
takes for granted.
Yes, they are essential to everyone's lives.  I
want to be like that.I heard
someone say the same thing in an interview in someone's
Holtalk.I wonder who that person was.
But actually someone answered some M answered the same way as did ALI think was ORIGINdiffquestion someone answer the way Maybe guys know who the answer from him Was
thathewantsto
makeinto
thatthepeopleall
over the
worldliveany
[Music]
I'll probably see the answer later in chat
Perfect
Hmm, I wonder if
this
is right or not.My
next question is, from the outside looking in, I don't think most of you know about the hardships behind people and companies,
or the failures,
but only the successes.
Since I often see this, I would like to know
what kind of failures and hardships individuals and companies have faced and
how they have overcome them.Yes, that's
true.I'm an old man, so I'm just an
ordinary person.  I
feel like I'm the one who has a hard time compared to the
other people. Yes, yes, that's right. After all,
I focused on what I wanted to accomplish in life, regardless of what other people thought of me, and then I made the
same mistakes.
Personally, I think it's important to make sure that it doesn't happen again,
so I'm wondering
if you could tell me in a little more detail about the hardships you faced.Well,
this cover is also worth mentioning.  This
is my second company, and I
didn't suddenly do very well in my first company, so I ended up
running a company once and learning a lot of things
before taking on the challenge of this company again.
Yeah, well, that's quite true.
Managing a company is difficult in its own way, so even if you try
that one time
and it doesn't go that well, it's
okay to not give up and do what you want to do.
OK
[Music]
sayhas
peopleisalways
focusingonwhathe
wantstoaccomplishIn
hisownLIFEandhe
triesToNeverrepeat
themistakesagainand
everyimpr and
heto
andisSECONDComp
himselfsoItwasHIS
firstTrynotlikeit
surprisinglywent
wellonthefirstTry
andHereitisMiracle
CompanyNohedidlearn
althefirsttimehe
createdACompanyand
hedidsaythatleading
ACompanyisIndeed
pretty
TOUGHJ
] Well, what about that Unkuro?  I'm
sure the company also has this question, but did Mr. Yago
originally think that Hol Live would become this big?
This is quite a difficult question, isn't it?  After
all, I wanted to provide a service that people all over the world
could enjoy, uh, because of Japan's strong points.So, in
a
way, it's just as I
imagined, but
at that incredible pace.  I'm really happy that so many people know about me.asassay
[Music]
[Music] Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
but I've
had some hard times growing up,
and I've had a lot of hard work, too.  Well, I
think there are more and more things that you have to be careful about because it becomes popular and people see it.I see, that's what
EXpeople said.So that's the
next question.Yes, I see.
What has been your biggest accomplishment since creating Hololive? What do you
hope to accomplish in the future
? It's really hard to choose the No. 1 accomplishment.
That's what I
'm thinking of, and I hope to continue to work
with those talents and other creators outside the company to provide content
like this that everyone can enjoy.Yes.
I see
tohimhe
fromStill
continuouslyhethat
heto
Creatorsoutside
Wantstoateasmanyas
possibleandhave
everyoneWORLDenjoy
andofferthistothose
peopleYESYESYESso
thelastquestionis
alreadyhereguys
Sorryalreadytime
havetosaygoodbysoon
toButTheLast
questionistheone
thatwealwaysaskinThe
last question
is the one that we always
ask.
This is a difficult question, but I
think it comes down to my ability to express myself to do my best at work.That ability to express myself, yes, yes,
because everyone in the live production team is working hard, I feel like I should do my best, too.
I would like to work together with you to realize something like that that the fans can enjoy.Yeah
yeahsays
[music]
fortheworldtoenjoy
Yeahmakeforallof YeahSoweareHISis
that Wonderful
is I see today.  Mr. Yago, I
heard a lot of stories from you, and
thank you for all your answers.
Thank you very much, Mr. Yago.
Lastly, there is something I would like to tell you all.
Thank you very much for reading today, Mr. Yago.  Yes, I would
like to thank everyone who is watching today.I will continue to work with the talents to deliver something that everyone can enjoy, so please give me your support.Yes,
FINALmessageto
guysofallingmefor
forInterviewandone
Who
withandask
[Music]
AGAllUS
and Hforme
have today someone I respect so much, I
was really nervous, but thank you very much. I hope you will
continue to be wonderful to me. I hope you continue to be wonderful.
Please support us and our talents. Yes, we do.
[Music] I was
asking this question before this program, and I've
already received about 34,000 questions. It's
really amazing. It seems like everyone is really
interested.  Yeah, it was interesting to you
guys and forget about these Things but Yeah, it was interesting to you guys and
forget the HASH talk to Tweet out your impressions from Today I will go Through them and them and I would be very happy today. What are your impressions?  I'd
be happy if you could post screenshots on Twitter as well.
Please tweet using that hashtag, Holtalk.
So that's it, but at the end,
Chiara always greets me in that German,
so please say it with me.  I wonder if I can get it?
Yes, I want that line to be added later. Oh yeah, that line again. That
's what it means, but yeah, yeah, I've heard it before. I've
been studying German No.  Are you serious
? Can you tell me now? That's really interesting, but yeah, I
feel like I remember it, and German is quite difficult,
right? I'm
going to go there.
[Music]
I can't use my hands, but I can manage with my body.
Bye Bye Sen Cuba Thank you
Mashi
Tae Cold Hot Hot
Love Ludol
Hoho Ko Hokkol Ko Ah
Atta E Corde Corde Rice Rice Slice Rice Rice Rice
Rice Rice
Rice Nusu Slice
Rice Nudonununu Rice Rice Rice Rice Rice
Saizeria Saizelia Love Saizelia Saizelia Boze
[  [Music]
Asaizelia Saizelia Saizelia Saizeria
Saizeria Saizeria Saizelia It's
decided to be Gashi tter
Ivy Twitter Twitter Twitter Twitter Ihave instTTTwitter Twitter Twitter Twitter
Twitter
Twitter Twitter Twitter
Juice ah ap orange
Juice apple juice apple apuru apuru
apuru mountain climbing mountain climbing
ah ya ya mountain ah ba mountain
That's right so ah
mason ah ah
cry ah climbing maten no no no
no no double no climb mountain climb maten
primer mountain masoo mountain nun
mountain
fromthe mountain  Computer ah
concert ah PCPC's computer uh PC
computer PC ah console uh computer ah
PC computer computer computer PC
PC hey yeah kashikasakashin no no no
ha I'm alobe no aun ye
no paina
[music]
paina
abut soo
sweet mo sufu swee suee awa sweety
spicy
swift
like ah
spicy spicy
sous sweet sweet soo so spicy soo te
te I love milk tea neither is good te te te te chama te te ti ti ee
dreamy big year travel to the beach
paradigm beach beach beach ah big town
wow
vacation pibi ah  Oh, the famous master ah,
Vashonia Beach, ah, I want to sleep on the beach,
Spin-o-beach, Inel Beach, big city, Tokyo,
ah, beach paradise, big city, hum city,
city city, Uko Daito City,
metropolitan stay, I'm going to hang up
my clothes, ah, Naked, as expected, those clothes are coming,
ah.  I'm going naked with Casouk
Us Au Girat PK Au
Close WITH
Close Ukuku
-bra Cuscs Ah Kurokuzu Ah Sandekrismas Christmas
Christmas  Ah Children's Day Ah Labor Appreciation Day
It's Christmas
Christmas Oh Christmas New
Christmas Halloween
Christmas Oh Halloween Christmas
Fama
Oh Family Bart
Oh my goodness I love everything but these days it's 7-
Eleven Seven Lawson
Rosenthal
Lawson Family Mort Ah All My
Life No I  All of them are convenience stores.
Please choose one. We are
currently collaborating with each other. Family Mart Family
Masen Seven
Text Message Goodbye Text
Message I Want
Sing Present
[Music] Is
giving something also the same as receiving
Well then, I'll
give you a gift.
Present Giving Presentation
Walking? Uwa Station
Train?
Train Train Ah U Train on the Train Ah
Train Train Ah Train Walk Walk Ah
Walk A One
Station Ah Taxi Ah Train Ah Train Train Go Go Ah
Train Tare
Train Pink
Ah
Secret U White Ah
Un  Ah,
pangu black means black panties. I'll
leave it to your imagination. Oh, I'll take a
look right now.
Black, secret.
Pants black. I don't wear them right now.
No,
bye Bye Bye
Bye. [Music
]
MN
[Music]
[  Music]
YX
[Music]