[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
n
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
he
hi you Darlings this is hello live
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only narissa ravencraft hopefully I
don't sound weird or anything
uh good
morning I hate to
report
um so because this is really early for
me uh I know I label this as tea time
but this has turned into breakfast time
I'll tell you what I have before me I
made two pasture raised eggs I already
ate the whites uh but I've crushed up
the jelly yolk and put it on toast one
of the toasts have has half an avocado
on it then I have a shake made with a
keer kaer I don't know how it's
said
um fresh raspberries a fresh orange a
fresh banana fresh
blackberries uh and some frozen
strawberries did I say almond
milk cfir is that how it
said um then I have a bowl over here
that is meant to be my quote unquote
lunch uh which is rice and uh bulgogi
that I
made so sorry if you don't like eating
noises this might not be the stream for
you I know my toast isn't crunchy
anymore so yeah having a little bit of
everything o soggy it's not soggy it's
just
cold I don't like egg whites so I ate
them
first
mukbang stream yeah on
accident only 2K left it's actually
1.5 you guys are going
crazy why can I hear her chewing cuz I'm
eating
breakfast I'm
hungry
[Music]
oh we have a birthday onee spider happy
birthday to
you yeah I'm hungry uh I'll talk some
more once I finish
eating cuz um it's rude to talk with
your mouth full you
know
hopefully you guys have woken up too and
had breakfast or lunch
maybe the shake is
thick J on my
soul I can't stop thinking about it that
was so
funny
still in bed God I wish that were
me I want to tell you guys about my
plans for
today but I can't because I'm
[Music]
eating God I love
avocado
Fox thank you for the Supa Bosa thank
you for the
Supa does Monster count as breakfast
absolutely
not no I love
avocado I always forget I like
it
how do you
[Music]
forget you know when you just stop
buying
something and then you haven't had it in
so long that you're like do I like that
thing but yeah my body really really
likes avocado
so I like how it makes me
feel same with eggs I don't like eggs I
think I've talked about this
before egg yolk is
[Music]
okay but I ate eggs so much when I was a
kid like I cooked them every single day
every single
day dip eggs I would I would make eggs
basted medium I would dip toast in them
I ate that up okay I loved me a
runny
YK and then randomly one
day I look down and the something about
the egg whites disgusted me like it was
just gross I don't want to talk about it
cuz I'm eating eggs right
now yeah my egg
trauma yeah I like scrambled eggs
slightly better I think they're more
palatable
but I just like the yolk you
know give me a
yolk I'm now having the toast with just
egg on it I finished the avocado toast
with egg
YK
[Music]
I've been this breakfast is pretty easy
to make so I've been making
it in the mornings
recently how about omu rice I haven't
really had omu rice
before but I'm inclined to not really
like it CU I don't like eggs and I don't
like
ketchup
H you air fry your bacon right yeah but
I don't have bacon
today honestly I didn't like the brand I
bought last
time it way too
salty
so when I was at the story I neglected
to buy more
bacon f is Flavor I
agree Demetrius Bernette happy 30th
birthday I hope you have a great day
happy big big three three
have you had any black rye bread I've
had rye bread
before boiled eggs is my favorite
ooh in our class right now focus on your
class thank you for stopping by
though
I want to eat my rice while it's
hot but I hate eggs so I want to eat the
egg first so I'm done with it you
know any plans for
600k it'll be a little bit after because
she's not here right now and I think
we're going to hit it before she gets
back
but we're going to be bringing my mom on
stream if you don't like the egg whites
can I have them of course I already ate
them today but I'd be happy if you
wanted to take my egg
whites maybe a karaoke I don't know
about
that
how are they cooked my eggs uh I Bas I
do basted
medium I got them to the day
where half the yolk was
runny and half of it was like kind of
like
m a buttery
consistency I like to get it to that
consistency so I can spread it around
like
butter
M I don't think I've ever basted an egg
I mean you just get a cover for it while
it's cooking and then it'll it'll just
you know the steam will cook the top of
it it adds a nice little like film over
the egg
yolk makes it really
satisfying to di to dip into with
[Music]
toast what's that method called baseed
to
medium if you want your eggs like I like
my eggs you go to
Denny's American
Diner and you request your eggs based
medium so like French toast uh not
really
what kind of French toast are you
having okay let me shut this plate down
for the time
being I help over Denny's okay I just
haven't really been to an IHOP I'm sure
they're really
good Denise is a dangerous place oh why
cuz their food's
good I love making a shake but it's got
so many seeds in
it that
like I have to convince myself not to
chew
it okay time to mix up my meat and
rice such a good
combination beef and
rice
go to Denny
said see I
remember when I was a young theater kid
when I was but a young theater kid okay
um we would go have celebrations at
Denny's
okay so after
performance and all of our
makeup
we would
go
M thanks for the EU friendly stream no
problem wait I'll take a quick break
from eating in a sec one
moment so
I the reason I'm actually streaming
early today is not of my own
valtion at 3 my time I have my voice
lesson um
so I'm
busy I'm busy then so I was like okay
but usually that would be fine because
I'd be done before however then my
sister actually invited me out
today but it's at the end it's like at
the end of the
day but well like it goes till the end
of the day but we have to leave our
house pretty
early so I'm like
oh mouthful or a Radia a
Radia I'm going to a
party let's quick give a shout out sorry
my mouth is
full hello VOD gang and EU gang we don't
get to see you bros
often if you are VOD gang
and you've gotten this far in the
vaud please
leave uh is there an egg emoji is there
an egg emoji can we ask them to leave an
egg emoji in the in the in the comments
below is that a
thing yeah yeah
egg please please leave it an egg in in
the comment
section it's been 20 minutes yeah
and that's how I I know they're not
skipping to the
[Music]
end back to my Bogi and
rice I was going to uh toss some kimchi
on top too but I didn't have time I was
literally cooking cuz I like to cook and
clean as I go you know I don't like to
leave the kitchen a mess
so for example after I'd used the
blender I would clean the
blender after I'm done like microwaving
the meat because it's pre-cooked
I was putting I I had to put like the
the cover for like stuff in the
microwave back in the
microwave after I made my eggs I wash
the pan yada yada you know like the like
regular stuff it I think it's easier to
do it too it's nice to have a clean
space and not have
everywhere but so
I I um didn't I didn't really have a ton
of time a super ton of time to like do
everything you know what I
mean so I looked at the time and I was
like I got to click the start
button I wouldn't call it
OCD if uh the one thing I learned while
I was studying culinary
was it's way easier to work if the space
around you is completely
clean I actually learned that from my
dad because um not to expose father here
father does not clean as he goes he
doesn't clean after after he's done
cooking sometimes he leaves the stove
running and it makes it so when I go
into the
kitchen I find it very chaotic and
upsetting because I'm like I want to
cook something but there's a dirty pan
on the stove the stove is still on or
the oven is
on there's there's cooking scraps from
cut up like vegetables on the table
now I have to clean this if I want to
cook so I'm just not going to
cook I'm sure you guys know how it is
it's kind of the downside about living
with other
people yeah it drives me
crazy leaves the oven on it's an
accident it's not intentional but
yeah my dad is the same
mhm someone always usually catches it
pretty fast
but I think I mentioned my parents are
on vacation right
now we went into um we went into my
dad's office and he had left his heater
on they've been gone for a few days so
we're like
huh
what may have sometimes father is just a
little they're just slightly
forgetful vacation you say
yeah they're
celebrating their
[Music]
life electric oven or gas I don't
know I think gas cuz the strove is
G do you see the Flames
[Music]
yes
electric is safer I think so too but
alas do you use chopsticks
um I think I usually eat rice bowls with
a
spoon whenever I would go to Korean
restaurants I'd always have the really
big Korean spoons so I'm I'm pretty sure
that's
okay I'm allowed to eat with a spoon
don't call me weak excuse
me it's not the American way of of
eating Korean literally use use
spoons all the
time
I'm here to shovel rice and meat into my
mouth chop Chopsticks are bust I mean
for a lot of foods I feel like
Chopsticks work really really well
actually batsy thank you for the
sua and so I
agree chop sticks are actually the
superior cooking
tool they can do pretty much everything
that
like most people have multiple tools
for but
look everyone tells me I don't hold them
properly and I get yelled at because I
don't hold them properly so I have no
confidence eating with chopsticks so
unless it's unless it's something like
unless that's what they provide at the
restaurant right away
um
oh one sec I need to look at my calendar
[Music]
sorry sorry I didn't mean to cut off my
thought
um uh
unexpectedly my lesson's getting
moved cuz it's it's a
holiday oh that gives me one less thing
to stress about that's
good
okay to when uh Thursday more zatsu yeah
let me eat my
food
good I mate haven't had Jon yet Jon my
soul happy mattress sales day is that a
thing yeah now all I have to worry about
is getting dressed for a
[Music]
party
should I go buy a mattress you guys I
hate
mine I but also I don't want
to maybe this is the time that I try it
Helix Gabriel thank you for the
Supa I get hit by a bike every day I go
to leave for work bro are you
okay
well look I remember when I was talking
to you guys about
beds and I think you guys accidentally
encouraged me to make a really really
bad financial
decision
um
sorry who us
yeah
[Music]
so
I'm I just
signed I really
wanted
H cotton satin sheets which
unlike a lot of Satine or satin labeled
things is actually satin which feels
like Silk but made out of
cotton so I was looking all over but it
was hard to find one with like a good
thread count like they're all like 300
400 which isn't
bad but I was like you know if I'm going
to be spending if if I'm going to be
spending money on sheets you know I
should probably get something that's
really nice you
know
um yeah over 1K or nothing yeah exactly
um and so I was doing some
research because I have I have linen
pillowcases I want a silk
pillowcase but I got one and it didn't
hold up really well so I wanted to get
one that was like Better
Built you know and like could actually
go on the washing
machine cuz like actual actual silk
is really
bad uh to go in it'll fall apart uh over
time even if you're watching it on the
most gentle
setting so
I I can't find any cotton satin that is
good
okay I can't find any that looks
trustworthy enough to me and every time
I look up the reviews for these
like2 200 beted sets that come with two
pillow cases the top
sheet and the fitted sheet I was like
M I don't know that's a lot that's a lot
of money for something I'm not sure
about
so after looking carefully and doing
some research
I ended up
finding a linen place that has really
really really
good quality sheet like really good
okay so I'm
reading I'm reading everything and I'm
like oh okay I wonder how much these
will end up being I think it was like
500 $600 and I was like you know what
I'm having a bad day let's do it maybe
it'll make me feel
better plus the jailbirds told me I
spent like a third of my life sleeping
so I should treat
myself I immediately regretted the
purchase but it was too late and already
taken the money from my
card R yester thank you for the super um
so stop telling me to to to treat myself
please stop stop telling me to treat
myself and buy buy expensive things and
invest invest in okay uh it's I I it's a
bad idea because I I will take that very
literally but on the right side
though I think they'll be worth it and
then I won't have to buy any more sheets
right
but the retail therapy I
know I really hope they work for me
though
because the sheets I'm using now are
once when I first moved back home with
my
family I had like these polyester bed
sheets and you guys know how I feel
about
polyester so I
asked I asked my mom for my birthday I
told her I wanted cotton sheets
so she went to
Amazon and found some $30 cotton sheets
and bought them for
[Music]
me so
I'm I've been using those for a while
but
um it was $30 nothing you buy that is
$30 is built to last you know what I
mean 30 30 bucks is a good price but
like and for how long they've lasted
me they're good but they're not like
amaz you know what I mean you know what
I'm trying to
say I feel like cotton is best shortly
before it falls apart right it gets so
soft and nice and like it's at that
point where like I sleep in the same
spot every night so even though I only
use half of my bed cuz I've got a queen
siiz mattress
but half of it is delegated to
plushies and like my extra pillows that
I use for if I need more things to
cuddle with
um and then the other half is my half
where I have like a little nesting area
so basically I have a pillow on each
side of me a pillow between my legs and
a pillow under my head and then I'll
usually grab one of my plushies I have a
weighted plushy to put on my stomach so
like I'm like nested and I cover my face
when I sleep sleep with the with one of
the sheets
so it's it's my Nest
okay but because of that as you can
imagine when I'm sleeping I probably get
pretty sweaty you
know so I wash my sheets often of course
but because I wash them often and they
also get
a more
worn do you sleep on your side mhm it
depends I think I've gotten too used
[Music]
to I think I got too used to like being
on my phone when I'm on my side that the
moment I turn to my side I can't sleep
because my body calls for my cell
phone so I can't do
it
do you snore no but yeah so I like to
sleep on my
back it also gives me less back pain to
sleep on uh the real reason is I don't
want to show you guys cuz I'm actually
quite embarrassed about it I hurt my
shoulder One Time by sleeping on my side
that
now you know doing that move where you
put your shoulders up and roll them
backwards it's like a move you can do to
stretch your
shoulders um every time I do that my
shoulder will like make a cracking
sound and I went to the doctor and
they're like well does it hurt and I was
like not really but like something is
clearly wrong cuz this like I I'd never
had this be a problem
before and now suddenly it's a it's a
problem that exists and um they're like
well unless it hurts we can't help
you and I've had it for like years now
so it's really unfortunate
um shoulder cracking ASMR here I'll
crack it for
you wait I'm probably going to have to
mute the
music it's probably pretty quiet but I
don't know if you could hear that but
yeah so they basically told me unless it
hurts or unless it's killing you we're
not going to look at into
it yeah so it kind of
sucked and that it just does that every
single time I roll it back it it will
not fix
itself omnipotence thank you for the
pinky did don't treat yourself you
should Queen thank
you yeah I um I need to go to the doctor
and get it checked out again
sometime I think it's pretty normal no
trust me it's not normal my other
shoulder does not do
that ma'am that's not a crack that's a
fracture trust me it's a
crack
but I mean surgery is often eh wait you
guys are going too fast sorry was it
that gross that you guys are going that
fast I'm
sorry but yeah I try not to crack it too
much because if I get into habit
suddenly I I keep I keep getting the
urge you
know
yeah my 9 my my 10,000 years alive
finally caughten up with me it's over
for me but so that's one of the reasons
I try to sleep on my back now cuz again
that happened literally just from me
sleeping on my
side
so
yeah
[Music]
yeah but that's one of the reasons I
enjoy massages
so much in my um my shoulder blade area
I was actually really grateful cuz my
dad my dad likes to give massages so
before he left he he he like has okay so
my aunt is a was is I don't know one of
my aunts is a masseuse so my dad would
like when she'd come over to rub his
back but my dad is also one of those
kinds of guys who's like I can do
anything so for when she'd come over he
got this like big bed like what is it
the it's not a bed the massage table
like he got a massage table honestly I
feel like I should just for go a bed and
get a massage table cuz those things are
so comfortable like why am I
trying to buy a mattress when I can
buy one of those and somehow they're way
more comfortable than a bed could ever
be but that's beside the point so my
aunt would come over and like give us
massages for
free I miss her she was so good at it
cuz she was a pro I remember she
traveled actually she was on tour with
like a celebrity I think I don't
remember which one but like she was like
on tour as like the the on on tour
masseuse and I'm just like damn imagine
that's just your
job do you roll around in your bed uh
yes definitely my blankets are always
like they start all the way in the
corner of the bed but like by the time I
wake up half of the blanket is like
going off the bed tour for massages no
like a so when you're like an artist
okay um a lot of times they'll have like
a masseuse on with them so they can get
massages you know so like when they're
traveling and doing like touring around
the country you know what I you know
what I
mean how many pillows you have far too
many but yeah so my dad then also was
like I can give good massages too so my
dad gave me a shoulder massage before
before he left and I was like thank God
my shoulders were so much
[Music]
pain two pillows just right
well I have four I sleep
with and then I have two additional ones
on my
bed so I have the one under my head the
one on both sides of me and the ones on
the sides of me are more Temperpedic
esque so they're really
thick uh and then I have one that's made
for between my thighs so my knees don't
clack together when I'm sleeping cuz if
I feel my knees touching then I can't
sleep it's a weird thing I I almost want
to get a second one for like my ankles
cuz I feel the same I feel the same way
about my ankles to be
honest and then like but then it because
I sleep on my back mostly now that it
kind of makes a bit of an
issue that like I
like I need my again I learned this from
going to massages but whenever they have
you on their back your back they get
that like round pillow that they put
under your knees that shit's amazing
like I'm like yo I'm so
comfortable I don't understand
I don't understand why it's so
comfortable but yeah I need to I need to
go for that my my food is cold I can't
eat cold food you
guys I'm going to have to like heat it
up later I'll put it in the fridge I'll
heat it up
later got a body pillow could be used
for both your knees and ankles I maybe
when I make a body pillow
someday cuz the the sound the sad
reality is that most body pillows are
made out of
polyester and if possible if I ever make
one I really want to make it out of
cotton I'm going to I if I ever make
what I'm going to ask I'm going to ask
cover and be like can we please find
someone who can print it in Cotton I'm
begging you it's my
dream oh but yeah anyways my point is so
I bought sheets They're Not
Silk however they are pure
linen
so linen sheet time
[Music]
yay
yay I'm excited and
scared but it'll be
fine yeah I ended up I did get a silk
and linen pillowcase though
[Music]
yeah so yeah dying it with a lot of
detail and Clarity is really difficult
that's probably
true that's probably true but if I can
do it I want to try you know sieg thank
you very much for the
aaup just dropping by it's quite busy at
work good luck be nice to get some
encouragement to survive the work week
G every week is a new week to do your
best you've got this even if it's
difficult Jon my soul Jon your
soul you you've got
this are we telling
Mory
God it is so hard to not chew this fruit
smoothie LW model
please isn't there's something lwd about
a woman who's fully
clothed does anyone else feel me on that
can we just have a quick conversation
why is my arm up like that excuse me um
I'd like to think
I'm fully clothed if you think about it
excluding my head and neck the only
parts of my body that you can see is one
of my
thighs and my
shoulders
okay but I dare I say I have a really
kind of lwd
model what do you guys think yeah Le
something to the imagination you know
shoulders are lewd you you get like a
peak you get a peak of of the thigh
right but then I go to the side and it's
almost like you can see upskirt but you
can't so you have to imagine and think
about it you know it's lewd and then you
get the shoulders you can see the line
as if it's going to go to the armpit but
you can't see it and something about
that is very lewd and then with my chest
the Fabrics fit around it very nicely so
it's not too tight and you can still see
the movement but you can't see it you
need to use your
imagination so uh please do
that use your
[Music]
imagination sounds like lud copium don't
get me wrong one day I will beg cover to
let me have my boobs
out like hey Cobra Cobra
please please
let me let me let me open up my
shirt I need to show off my
cleavage sticking out your G for
[Music]
nler look
uh I actually I wanted I wanted to have
a open
chest but we thought it was maybe a bit
too too much maybe it was best to keep
these puppies covered until a later time
so this is what you've got deal with it
one day one day you'll get Nissa
cleavage I promise you just you wait
jail Birds one day one day we'll get
what we want shis no thank you for the
Supa as well as Rising Phoenix thank you
for the
Supa
we need to slowly work up and build up
our power level yeah
exactly we need to slowly get there it's
a process my horn is loot it is it's
like an open wound so if that's your
sort of thing that you're
into anyway
is what's the context someone said my
model is not lwd and I was like excuse
me just because I'm not showing anything
I mean think of it like a bunny outfit
you know like I'm going to be so
honest re reverse bunny outfits are so
lame I do not like reverse bunny outfits
I think they're just I I just don't see
the point you know what I mean like
they're not they they're like it's too
much it's like okay you're showing me
everything you're not leaving me
anything to think about you
know like I can see
everything it's just it's just not it's
just not what I like but however the
traditional bunny suit the reason it's
so sexy and the reason it'll stay sexy
and relevant as to where you don't
really ever see anyone drawing the
reverse bunny girl suit much
anymore is because some
about leaving something to the
imagination is really sexy it makes it
more fun it adds it adds the fun to it
and if you disagree that's fine if you
want your immediate gratification but
I'm not a girl who's going to
immediately
wait
anyway I don't like immediate
gratification I like the tights I like
the high heels the the you know the
slightly transparent or fishnet tights I
like I like the bodycon
bodysuit that is just so sexy you
know but yeah the the reverse one where
like all of the regular parts of the
body are covered and only the LW parts
are revealed I'm just like what's the
point what's the point just draw them
naked at that point like there's nothing
there's nothing exciting about it to me
that's just my opinion again if you
disagree that's
fine that's totally fine you do what
what you want but like for me I'm just
saying that's that's that's what I
like this is coming from someone who
also like think about
like those really really really sexy
bunny um
figurines those things are so hot and
they're always the regular bunny girl do
you see them making those super duper
expensive large siiz bunny girl models
of the reverse bunny girl outfit no cuz
why would you want to buy
that it takes all the fun away
especially when they're using like real
fabrics and stuff for the ties tights
excuse me
like I'm just
saying clearly one of them is is
longterm better than the other
but you're allowed your personal
preference Siege thank you for the
pinky you're allowed your personal
preference which is whatever you want
you know but personally
again you will you will never see me in
the reverse bunny girl unless you guys
draw it that's acceptable but you will
never see me putting myself in a reverse
bunny
girl the ones with texture yeah where
they use like actual nylon material
it's very
sexy bunny Rea win I love bunny
girl outfit I would be so happy I don't
think that'll ever happen but I would be
really
happy but yeah again I want to
clarify everyone is entitled to their
own opinion so if you disagree that's
fine we don't have to fight I know sound
like I'm being uh very aggressive but
it's also because I'm a streamer on a
stream so I am uh passionately stating
my opinion but yeah you do you if you if
you are super into your reverse bunny
girl and that's just your thing and
that's just your kick and that's what
gets you off seriously good good for you
I'm so glad you have that you so happy
for you we we do not Kink shame here if
that's that's what you like but I am
also just talking about my personal my
personal idea which is what I like which
is not that which doesn't mean that you
liking it is wrong or that it is
inherently bad just my opinion I just
feel I sorry for like overly stating
it kg and battle Ranger thank you for
the
[Music]
supas
it's just like how some
people might not like
strawberries I like strawberries they're
like one of my favorite fruits of all
time
but you know you might not like them and
that's
okay that's a thing Kink shaming is my
Kink
no what are other outfits you like
besides bunny girl oh
God I love made
outfits if you except like here's the
thing I don't like the sexy French made
outfit okay I really really
enjoy I really enjoy like the the
traditional like think like Miku asahina
type where it's like long puffed out
skirt the the front apron yeah like
Victorian it's very classy but at the
same time the the
idea of the skirt getting pulled up and
seeing some like leg oh my
God oh my God sorry for being such a
pervert but like I just thinking about
the glimpse of the leg beneath the long
skirt like I feel like a a Victorian man
who's like an ankle oh my God I'm not
going to survive the
night seeing an
ankle oh I'm going to need a moment to
calm down Madam you know like that's how
I
feel I'm an old Victorian
man that's that's who I
[Music]
am
anyway
but I also see the appeal in the in the
sexy French made style one when I was in
high school I think I bought one of
those and I was like yeah this is this
is actually really ugly because you know
it was cheap but like at the same time I
like I just love the idea of like having
a little feather
duster I need to I need to just buy a a
feather duster for Aesthetics cuz like
it makes me happy to have a I I don't
know why the idea of having a feather
duster and just feather dusting is just
so exciting to me I know that is the
dumbest thing I think I've ever said on
stream Butler's nice too female Butler I
do like women in
suits women in suits is also another a
really good thing women in suits
man but yeah I I I'll be your maid I'll
be your bunny girl what what other LW
costumes are there that I'm missing I
know there's so many
more but what are
they o oh o is so good nurse okay
wait nurse nurse I'm sorry nurse has to
be the sexy little short skirt like pink
dresses with like white white tights
white slightly translucent
tights oh my God race Queen Race Queen's
so
sexy let me sit on your car and like no
clothes like
please bike suit oh my God skin tight
full body bike suits chef's kiss I love
I love that you're going deep today I'm
sorry you guys are just like bringing up
stuff business attire that's office lady
we love O's
here o I love you
plug suits I love the plug suits from
Evangelion they're
so like it's again you can't see
anything the whole body is covered I
would wear a plug suit I would I would
happily be put in a a skin tight plug
suit please and thank
you
oh one sec
I have to Quick read
[Music]
something
um okay okay give me one sec actually
I'm done I think with my food I'm going
to go run it downstairs I'm going to
wrap the meat
into rice that I didn't finish for later
sundresses don't stop sundresses are a
weakness of mine don't just bring that
up to
me give me a sec I'm going to be right
back I'm going to go rinse I'm just
going to go clean my dishes I'll be back
I'll be back wait wait patiently for me
I'm going to go to the BRB
screen
[Music]
hi sorry just me getting back and
yapping
immediately hi what I was saying is um I
have a yakle yakle cuz I had one in the
fridge I have like a pack of it in the
fridge so I decided
wait sorry the fact that I just ran up
and down the stairs is catching up with
me it took me a minute because uh
because I ate the egg and because I had
a runny YK it got on the plate so I had
to actually like I couldn't just rinse
it because I let it sit for a while like
an
hour so I needed to actually go in and
scrub it and then later now that it's
scrubbed and looks completely clean I'll
wash it with soap later by putting it in
the dishwasher
[Music]
how was the egg it was an egg I mean
I'll I'll
admit I I wanted to try the pasture
raised eggs which my sister Aria looked
at me and she was like what the is
wrong with you because they're like they
were kind of expensive and I was like
well they're only like
$6 dishwasher not handwashing I mean I
handwash them and then I run them
through the dishwasher you
know I'm like that one guy from The
Simpsons who like washes the dishes with
his kids and then puts them in the
dishwasher you know what I
mean faster eggs are so much better
they're uh better they're worth it
honestly I think so too cuz I don't like
eggs very much so I'm only eating them
for the
nutrients so it's
like I'd rather pay $6 for 12
eggs than you know you have kids no
what but
yeah like chicken eggs yeah chicken eggs
what do you think have you tried devil
eggs oh I do like devil
eggs Rea kids
when I do not have the means to make a
child
I think I need to be married to do
something like
[Music]
that
alas you guys want me to get married and
have a child would you like that
content I think I've mentioned this
before but I had I had an idea where I
was like what if what if me and kiata
had a pregnancy not like a real one okay
but like we like have like a we over the
course of 9 months we we we have a baby
we we go over the course of a
pregnancy but like virtually you know
like vtuber vtuber
pregnancy it was like it was like one
night when I was really really
tired and I was like oh my God I could
like I could like have someone draw it
and they could like draw the ultrasound
and then like I could move around a
thing so it like shows the under the
under layer and I was like no ABS I was
like this is so weird why did I
think this was a good idea but I had to
tell I had to tell Kata cuz I was like
what the isn't this a kind of a
good idea like it's super dumb but isn't
this also like kind of a good idea and
she was like girl what the is wrong
with
you yeah don't let me cook
anyway I just felt like it would be fun
like it would be so
funny it would be so funny like imagine
just once a month you just get a baby
update except there is no baby it's like
it's just like a a weird little chimera
of like me and
kiata you know and then
like I just thought it would be
funny yeah anyway it's a terrible day to
have ears I'm I'm
sorry yeah anyway the Phoenix Raven
would look cool I know like think about
it like I just think I just look again
I'm not going to do it because I feel
like that would be way too
much effort and like I feel like it
would also be like just too
weird cuz obviously after nine months
for a a joke stream idea like there
would be no baby
so just imagine ultrasound streams
morning sickness streams birthing
[Laughter]
stream it's the worst idea ever I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry for sharing this
uh this uh idea I had with
you baby role playay after 9 months
right exactly ASMR baby
roleplay I I Fe you except you are the
baby you are the you are from the
perspective of the
baby what's wrong with you I don't
know a lot
apparently not the shower thoughts if
only it's like sleep deprivation
thoughts anyways this is my very
original idea please do not steal if
someone else steals this and it goes
viral I will be so
mad I'll be so mad that you guys told me
it's too
weird huh we're the baby yeah oh my God
wait
yeah the baby is
chat and then I raise you from baby hood
and you guys are only allowed to type in
gooo
Gaga the whole
stream
you can't say anything until you're at
least two years old during the baby
exclusive
streams because uh otherwise it's not
realistic I'm sorry this is so
awful anyway sorry about that
um again this is like a random idea I
had G PP thank you for the Supa
[Laughter]
exactly they like they like when I talk
about all this stuff but then I talk
about joke baby streams they're like
no no stop she already burned the food I
can't help it I just like these are like
this is one of the reasons I think kiata
is amazing you know like kiata
can think of all these really applicable
like amazing stream ideas like really
easily and I'm like whoo meanwhile My
Stream ideas are like pseudo fake
pregnancy
stream thank you for the Su poor Yago
drinking himself to sleep hey there's
nothing wrong with having a child the
the the creation of I I've look I've
watched my sister have many a children
okay pseudo fake I don't know what
pseudo means I'm
sorry pseudo pregnancy stream was
amazing
this isn't the issue are you sure but
look I I've seen my sister give give
birth enough that like I pseudo means
fake oh yeah then I used it correctly
then why
huh but yeah malfa has had like so many
kids crackpot thank you very thank you
for the super happy
birthday did your sister lay eggs
no fake is a double O
oops
anyway but yeah my sister has given
birth enough
times
that uh and she's crazy too she's one of
those like she likes to do like at home
births with like a midwife and stuff and
I'm like girl you're
crazy
girl are you sure about that are are you
you sure you don't want to like are are
are you
okay yeah crazier than me absolutely TMI
reset how excuse
me do none of you want children in the
future she likes to like it's a hobby it
is her
hobby saves a ton of money TVH I bet I
mean I wouldn't know but ew no ew ew no
kids for you I love kids I would like to
have kids someday so child
haters uh I don't
know in this economy the the actual
valid answer
actually I would want children a how
many how many daddy want to be wait
here's the real question are there any
fathers and or mothers in chat any of
you who have children
anyone who actually has a
kid nope yes someone
does I have three girls
congratulations one
daughter
nice pole pull it
okay let's let's let me try to remember
how to do a
poll do you have a
kid yes and
no okay
starple good luck
jailbirds no children would love to
start a family though I hope you can
achieve
that I need a knot that I know of no you
don't have a kid if you're not taking
care of
it do pets count I should have added an
ation for fur babies in this situation
no but I would like to clarify that I do
consider pets as
children as my sister considers her
her her cats her
children does bi boo count
no I am the 6% congratulations
congratulations all you successful happy
people
yeah no uh for this situation please if
you have fur babies I'm sorry I
accidentally excluded you from the
parenting board but please click no if
you only have for
babies anyways I'm so sorry I don't know
why we're having this weird conversation
still it's cuz it's early in the morning
and I'm really
tired Peter thank you for the Supa I
don't want kids in the future but I have
it
uh have a desire oh my God I'm not going
to finish reading that
actually I see I understand
W all right
uh anyway yeah it's it's early for me
look I know for some of you you're like
like it's late at night or like you're
into the day but like for me it's
early oh little
man my baby
come here let me hold
you
hello little
man he doesn't like how I'm holding him
I can tell he's miserable
hey hey come
here oh he's so so
cute yeah you sniffing my
microphone that's my son he's my son
actually I tell my sister constantly
that little man is my
cat hey you like being held you're not
screaming
anymore I won't let you leave our son my
son get your own
cat wait wait little man let me put you
down please don't dig your nails into my
leg he's so
[Music]
crazy anyway yeah weird conversations
aside I'm so sorry I don't know what has
gotten into
me it is
simply the morning for
me uh and when it is morning
suddenly something is wrong with
[Laughter]
me don't be sorry yeah I just I just
have no filter in the morning I'm I'm
just like thirsty for
water but my body doesn't know how to
inter like distinguish my thirsts you
know so then I'm like well now I'm just
thirsty for LW
art Evee thank you for the
Supa just some more uh thirsty
yeah normal behavior I agree anyway
moving on I have good
news I ordered some more accessories for
my permanent Renaissance Fair uh
estimate what the
my permanent Renaissance Fair
outfit
fit I wanted to buy one that was very
high
quality
so I I did
that permanent yeah I'm going to put it
on my body and never take it
off it's going to it's I'm going to be
core seted for
life um but yeah I I have I got one of
the like fancy linen skirts it's like
made of real
linen so I'm excited to wear it whenever
there's a Renaissance Festival that I
want to go
to imagine the smell oh you guys just
love sweaty smells huh is that like your
thing I didn't realize so many people
like the smell of
sweat what are your thoughts of night
gowns I love night
gowns I really love lingerie dresses
which despite having lingerie in the
name are not lingerie they're like a I
think Victorian
outfit
um and they're just like
great they're very like kind of
translucent they use a lot of
lace and they're very gorgeous I want
one but like a genuine one someday cuz
like I see I I went to the I think like
Nordstrom if you guys know what
Nordstrom is I'm sure you do and they
had
like they had they had a lingerie dress
top that just looked it looked like a
lingerie dress but it was just a shirt
top and I was like oh this is so pretty
and let me tell you this thing was
completely completely transparent like
it would need an undershirt no questions
asked the fabric was so thin you want to
know how much this thing costed
you want to know what the cost was yeah
$700 over $700 the person who guess 750
you're basically
correct 7 over
$700 for a
shirt I was like I looked at it and I
was absolutely not like maybe
maybe if it was a 100 and even then
still probably not I wouldn't have been
like yeah I should buy this is like 100
for like something that's see-through
like no
way I didn't even check the materials
but yeah for barely any material for
something that's translucent and it
sucks cuz like I think Nordstrom usually
does have pretty good quality stuff but
I just don't think they have any
business doing that for like a
translucent
shirt I just yeah I'll just I'll just
not wear clothes thank
you and keep in mind this is coming from
someone who like I
try to I try to actually buy like fairly
sustainable or stuff that I'll wear for
like a really long time at the very
least so I don't mind spending like a
little more on clothes but like not that
much for One Piece like maybe
for an outfit yeah then I'll be like oh
yeah that's great but like one slightly
translucent shirt no
way H yeah you're paying for the
experience what of going to the mall and
shopping in a Nordstrom Rack because
absolutely
not Nordstrom oh no Nordstrom Rack I'm
sorry yeah refresh the stream you guys
it's all good on my
side
Ellie so one of the reasons I I I had to
wake up and usually I like to shower at
night but uh I stayed up late but not
late enough for my hair to dry and I
knew I was going to go to bed before my
hair would be dry so I was like okay
I'll take a shower in the
morning so I had to wake up early with
enough time to take a shower and to do
my skin care routine
afterwards and then I had to make
breakfast and then I had to stream so
this morning was very stressful for
me what about wedding dresses I like
wedding
dresses I've been with both of my
sisters while they purchased
theirs which is fantastic for them I'm
so happy for
them but uh yeah I uh I've never I've
never gone looking alas
obviously it's really fun to go wedding
dress shopping with people and like see
them like find like the dress you know
and like just like fall in love I love
that for
them but
yeah yes there
money I think it's good to have a budget
for stuff like that
though does it happen like in reality TV
uh not necessarily but also kind of
stray J thank thank you for the
Supa but yeah I feel like
uh I like pretty dresses in general
though I just like beautiful
dresses how expensive are wedding
dresses I mean you can find ones that
are pretty affordable but obviously
whatever you get is going to be
reflected in like the
quality and usually you know because
it's a marriage people want something
really ornate and like really detailed
so it's just kind of usually going to
not always it doesn't have to be but
they're usually going to
be the in in the range of you
know 1,000 to I think
10,000 I
think yeah usually it's over a thousand
and this isn't to say that you can't go
online and find cheaper dresses
but they're just going to
look you get what you pay for you
know so if you're used to going to
weddings where most of the dresses are a
th and
up then chances
are when you find someone who or when
you try buying one online that you found
for $100
$200 it's probably going to
look like a wish wedding dress which is
isn't even to say
$1200 is like a small amount because I
still don't like spending that kind of
money on things willy-nilly
but
yeah yeah let's just skip the
wedding hey it's my dream to get married
someday you can't skip the
wedding that that's the fun of getting
married is having the the the ceremony
you know having having fun with your
friends getting to be the center of
attention and and you know have like a
beautiful dress and have all these
beautiful photographs to commemorate to
commemorate such a lovely joyous
occasion you can't skip the wedd if you
want to I mean that's your prerogative
go ahead skip the wedding
uh but
yeah in this
economy sometimes you have to save for
things that you want sometimes if if you
want
something it's going to cost you a a bit
of money and you're going to have to
you're going to have to you know spend
money on it even if it's a little bit
expensive how big of a wedding would you
like I don't think it needs to be too
big to be honest I feel like I prefer
all of of the weddings to I've been to
and I've been to quite a few I've been
to really really big wedding
with like 400 500 plus
guests uh and I've been to like smaller
weddings with like only maybe about
so
personally I think it
depends I think it depends I don't know
if I want 100 small well think of it
even if you only invite 50
people
if you give everyone a plus one and
everyone brings one you're probably
going to have about a 100
guests you know like 100 I would say I
don't think 100 is a large
wedding I've never been to a wedding
that didn't have that many people
because again like if you invite all
your
family if and then you invite your
friends you know and then you let your
parents invite some of their friends and
then you let everyone have a plus one
you'd be surprised how quickly how
quickly the list goes up you know you
might think oh I don't really know
anyone I don't really have that many but
once once you actually
start inviting people it gets to be much
worse cuz if you give people a plus one
Mo I'm going to be honest no one wants
to go to your wedding
alone they're probably like who do I
know there like if it was a high school
friend they might be like oh maybe maybe
this person from high school will be
there but it's not a
guarantee so people people are most
definitely going to bring a yeah and
then colleagues if you have anyone at
work you decide you want to invite you
know like trust me I know 100 might
sound like a lot of people but most of
these people you probably don't even
know the trick is to have no friends
mood you go for the food yeah weddings
got to have good food
but again so my point is I've been I've
been to smaller weddings and I've been
to like larger size ones I feel like I
prefer the smaller ones that are like a
100 people is I just feel like they're
more intimate you know like I I don't
like when I go to a
wedding and it's a ton of people that
like who even are these
people like and you know the bride and
groom feel that way too and they're just
like huh who's this person person at my
wedding who who are they even I don't
know like again for a plus one it
happens but I feel like when it gets too
big you get to the point where there's
just so many people you don't even
recognize guys we just went over why 100
is small it sounds like a big number but
it's not as big as you're thinking it
is stray J thank you for the Supa yeah
100 is small what are you guys going on
about
100 is not a large guys how many
weddings have you been
to but yeah so it's it's quite 120 1
okay well I understand why some of you
have no scope and some of you
understand but yeah I feel like yeah
yeah 100 is small guys I'm being so for
real most readings around here are 50 to
100 that's small sh no thank you for the
pinky wedding's overrated no guys look
if you're marrying the love of your life
you can't tell me that I think the the
most special moment for me at both of my
sister's weddings that I thought was
just a standout moment I know this is so
basic but seeing the bride walk down the
aisle and looking up and at her husband
to be and seeing him just ugly
sobbing because he's like oh my God that
beautiful woman is about to be my wife I
get to spend forever with her I'm so
happy that I can't help but
cry I feel like that moment is just so
special you
know so like I feel like why would you
skip the wedding like I don't know call
me a hopeless romantic if you want to
again if it's not for you then it's not
for you and that's fine but uh for me
that's something I'd really
like that's something I would I would
want save money for the honeymoon
instead no just spend a lot of money on
Bowl why just have fun I mean you can
literally have a really pretty wedding
in your backyard or you can like rent
someone's Farmhouse and have a really
pretty I mean look at let's look at
Twilight
okay let's look hey my cat's being
really loud in the
hallway come in here stop
screaming like it is better to spend
more money on something fun that you can
do together but the wedding is still a
important yeah stop being such
doomers but in Twilight they literally
just got married in their backyard
like and it was still gorgeous like you
can just have your wedding at your house
you don't have to rent a big venue or
you can just like rent somewhere that's
pretty affordable you don't have to do
anything
crazy you guys are blowing it out of
proportion like I'm not saying you
should go rent the most expensive hall
or like a castle to get married in
Twilight is not a good example yes it is
they had a wedding in their
backyard that is like the the the the
most cheap way you can have a wedding
you just rent a few things set it all up
in your backyard invite all your guests
there celebrate in your house is
perfect little
man he's staring staring at me like he's
going to eat
me come
here he's interested in my hair brush he
wants to he wants me to brush him with
my hair brush for my
head I'm holding it in my hand and
letting him rub his face against
it he's disagreeing with my take no he's
seeing me brush my hair and he's getting
jealous is what's actually happening
little man ASMR I try but every time I
bring him up to the mic suddenly he
shuts the
up like he wants to scream and act like
he's all tough then I put him next to
the mic and he's
like hey
what
what what can I do for
you he's like headbutting my leg
he loves headbutting
me I love you little
man oh my little baby boy I can't wait
to get my own cat
someday I love cats so much he's staring
at me I love you oh my
god hello little
man
this is your stream now will you say
hello
oh you guys can't see what he's doing to
me right now but he's being so
cute that's my son this is my
son my little
kitty he's reading your comments he's
seeing you all say hi little
man can we get a hi little man in chat
for the little man who's reading your
messages I love him I love my little man
my little kitty boy my little
son hi small thing hi buddy hey little
[Music]
man zly thank you for the
pinky I'm sorry guys I can't properly
read chat I'm petting my I'm petting
little
man hey you can't leave you cuddled with
me all cute now you're my
prisoner I rub your
tummy ah he's trying to kick me away
he's like I'm done with you P me
down
oh you're such a
baby I'm holding him like a
[Music]
baby
oh okay okay okay okay I'm putting you
down
okay you better not meow at me now that
I put you down NOP he's head butting my
leg
okay I love you too I love you too
baby a I love cats
he is a soon de he's like no you can't
cuddle me anymore and he's like oh you
put me
down time to rub my face against your
leg until you give me
attention even though I was just giving
him
attention oh he's so sweet sorry they're
not used to me streaming this earlier in
the
day so usually this is when me and
little man are spending time
together like it's usually when I'm
still in bed but I've like opened the
door for him so then like he'll come in
and like sit in bed with me so I think
he's probably like why are you on your
computer why aren't you cuddling with me
noisa the what I mean he's a cat C he'll
come and he'll cuddle with
me do your guys' cats not come cuddle
with
you yeah little little man is letting me
know that it's his cuddle
time routines are super important to CS
if they don't get fed right on time when
they think they are going to they start
screaming not a cat person so
no
okay then does your dog not try to
cuddle with
you every time I stopped petting him he
headbutts me
again oh
Kitty Kitty I just remember when my
nephew was here and that kitty kitty
[Music]
I'm so
sorry I'm so
sorry oh little
man I love cats I'm so sorry I'm getting
so
distracted you ever just like living
life and then your cat comes out of
nowhere and then suddenly nothing you
were doing
matters
comes the baby fever again shut
up shut
up
[Music]
yeah anyways this has been a weird
stream this has been a really weird
stream maybe I I'm I shouldn't stream in
the morning ever again is the vibe I've
gotten I think I feel like that's what
I've learned from this stream is that
me me streaming in the morning is a
mistake akake because I just suddenly
start yapping I just start yapping and
then I just can't
stop it is blurst this is why I love you
I'm glad somebody has to
right he's staring he's still reading
what you guys are
typing I thought this was a comfy
stream is it I'm sorry I did my
best
buy good sheets I already did I just got
an email that they shipped it's over for
me it's too late it's really too late
now yeah Fin and cat I love cats the
weirdness is why it's my charm
right it's my
charm my charm point is I'm weird but
the EU gang I know the EU gang always
gets the most
unhinged version of
me like the most unhinged version of
Nissa
ravencraft um just every time oh wow
guys we're only 1K subscribers away from
my mom wait let me open up yeah we're
like pretty much exactly 1K away from
mamisa once we hit the goal I I will um
I will be
uploading uh not uploading I'll be
putting out a thing on my Community page
on YouTube for questions for you guys to
ask her for when she gets back
so please prepare questions you have for
my mom I will be sorting through them
and picking so I know it might be funny
to put haha are you single haha will you
marry me but if you have a genuine
question you want me to ask please put
it there
I will I will be more likely to pick it
if it's a genuine question and not just
uh you
know I think little man wants to leave
one sec little man he's trying to
go
no
hey what are you doing why you staring
at my door like
that maybe he doesn't want
to nice weather today a
don't ask my mom if she's single she's
got a
husband does she do belly rubs for my
dog
yeah can we I mean you guys can ask
whatever you want just don't ask just
don't ask the the you know ask something
you actually are curious
about to on my
soul can you tell us her reaction when
you reach it um I already know what her
reaction
is I already know exactly what it's
going to
be um so
basically my mom is the kind of
person
who uh she she will feel as though this
is her personal
accomplishment
but at the same time she's worried did I
think I told you guys this already but
I'll repeat it because it's funny Virgo
Fox thank you for the supera she
literally she said I'm scared that only
five people are going to come to my
debut
stream I was like
Mom
five you think five people are going to
come only five and she like yeah there's
only going to be five people there no
one's going to want to see
me no one no one is going to want to see
me like Mom you're actually
insane yeah she's in for a surprise but
again I think I'm I'm probably not going
to let her I I'll have live chat on but
I'm not going to let her read live chat
just says most of you are amazing
obviously but sometimes some people come
in and say purposely mean things on
purpose because some people just like to
watch a world burn that's just how it is
so I'd rather not have those people have
my mom see it and then you know get
distracted by people being Rowdy so but
again want to clarify you guys are very
well behaved very very well
behaved but just going to take extra
precautions since it's my mommy's first
time you know
[Music]
sorry I'm so
sleepy now that my voice lesson is
cancelled I guess if I wanted to I could
just take a
nap but anyways uh she she's going to
have a really good time H we'll make
sure that we all have a good time
together but so with that in mind please
ask lots of really good
questions can I I ask for her blessing
she's a demon so I don't really know if
she can give you one of those that's
more of a question for
malfa how uh ask how Papa and Mama Raa
met and fell in love yeah see like stuff
like that would be a good question like
oh little
man just leave if you want to leave it's
fine
sorry can she stay the night to play
Mario Kart uh I don't know what the last
time my mom played Mario Kart was but
that means that what at some point we
can probably have her play maybe one of
the Mario games but I think the first
the first stream we have with her will
probably be more of a like chatting
style you guys ask her questions we ban
her type thing you know
ha can I ask her to curse me
yeah so feel
free
feel free
to uh who's the favorite Child oh my God
you guys should please if you guys put
that in and I see it I will ask her
that she's going to give the most 100%
mom answer but please I'm begging you I
I wonder if because we're on live stream
if she'll say it and that'll make me so
happy if she does say that I'm her
favorite cuz then it'll be eternalized
forever someone will clip it and then I
can show it to Aradia and malfus a
second and uh malfa and be like look
look I'm the
[Laughter]
favorite uh it's either going to be that
or she's going to say am malus the
second or she's going to say all of us
she loves equally and doesn't have
favorites we'll
see it'll be a surprise to the day
of can she tell us embarrassing Nissa
childhood stories
maybe
maybe I'll think about it I don't know
if I want to honor that
request favorite child the dog well the
actually the dog is my twin because we
share a
birthday so even though we weren't born
at the same time uh like even remotely
as far as I'm concerned she's my twin
cuz we're birthday
buddies 1K left uh 1K left to M Mara
let's
go guys subscribe right now for a chance
to help me hit 100 600k live I'm just
joking that's not going to happen
today maybe maybe tomorrow if I get
lucky but I feel like with the rate that
it's going at I'll probably hit it
before before stream
tomorrow cuz it's over it's over 24
hours away we're we're really
close really
close but oh wait there's something I
wanted to where did I save it did I save
it I did we're not quite there yet but
let me like I a fan made an our young
made an asset and I I want to I just
want to wear it even if it's not quite
time yet so like if you'll if you'll
humor me for a
second if you'll humor
me I I need to I need to put these on
cuz we're almost
there I'll wear them tomorrow
too
uh uh
uh okay okay okay slowly but surely I'll
get
there slowly but
surely sorry I'm currently
Frozen
okay where are
they oh there they
are he wait I need
to yeah
yeah yeah we're not there yet we're one
1K away from
600k 1K away from
600k thank you all for subscribing I'm
prematurely
celebrating as the for the
memes yeah it reminds me of bioo thank
you arel for these by the way let me
link them in chat arang made these
yesterday I'll actually I'll just
retweet them I'll make it easier if you
guys want to find them you can check
Twitter
woo not quite there yet but
almost let's go I'm so happy for you
you're almost there thank you Taki Kai I
love
you woo almost
there Wawa strikes again waa I'm
streaming I'm streaming in EU hours are
you proud of
me are you proud of
me I I'm I'm an EU streamer now just for
today I subscribed to W
finally I finally got takanashi kiata to
subscribe to me you guys it's I'm truly
[Applause]
winning
[Music]
I love
Teno she locked me in the usual room and
now
yeah that's
all
my oi Takashi
Ki good morning how many more to go um
we're about
away I don't know how to do a screen
counter I don't know how people I don't
know how people do
that otherwise I put one on for
fun uh and
kiaha yeah 800ish to
go wait is re's room canonically just
the usual room I
mean it is kind of a my cat what
shut up I let you
in is this Social account cuz I I just
usually look directly at the the YouTube
the YouTube thing oh my god I've had
Reverb on this whole
time ask am I don't know if am is even
awake if she's anything like me she's
still in bed as she should
be ah
[Music]
oh I got a
DM I don't know from
where
um okay what's the context of the poll
we were having a weird conversation
earlier I'm going to end
it yeah cuz the social
Blade the social counts whatever it is
it's not
correct because I have the one directly
through YouTube that shows me where I
am and according to YouTube it says I'm
at
599,000 social
counts it's missing a hundred of
those
so yeah lots of childless people here I
say is a childless
person mamaa on standby uh reminder that
my mother is not here right now whenever
she gets back from her vacay we'll be
debuting
her but in the meantime you guys are
going to going to have to deal with just
me just me for the time
being yeah kiata is not allowed to watch
today's VOD not like I think she would
but yeah don't leave kiata
alone leave kiaha
alone
[Music]
I have a six-year-old kid
lucky okay what don't don't worry Kiara
just it's okay go to bed you've done
good you've done
uh why is Kiara calling me wait one
sec wait you're you're muted is that
okay do you want me to unmute
you wait she can't hear me uh give me
one sec K wait yeah to wait for
me
hello okay uh do you want me to unmute
you do you want to be heard on stream
yes yes yes yes okay give me one sec uh
the Fugi Tech won't load it's okay hi
Takashi
kiaha uh excuse me I am
uh what
T I'm I'm the Yellow Ostrich
streamer
oh what was the
name uh Tanaka tanak
Tanaka oh my God
or hello Tanaka Tanaka Kia K yeah
Tanaka my my member stream is starting
in 10 minutes so I just wanted to stream
now
congratulations thank
you I'm like let's go I'm 750 away I
don't think I'll stream till I hit it
but I'm also not streaming for you are
streaming until you HTE it or
else oh it's so it's so exciting to like
hit it during a stream yeah but I didn't
advertise this as that so I don't think
I'll hit it during the stream you know
you will you will it won't take much
longer are you sure even I subscribe
even I subscribe I know that is true I
did get the the tanakha Kyra to
subscribe so perhaps Kia excuse me so
tanakha Kia sorry
Queen I hope you have a good member
stream thank you
well
I will I I I will await I I wish I could
stay until the end I want to I want you
to hit 600k now now I know me
to thank you my darling love how much
was it when you started uh I was about
uh 1,500
away5 so okay see you should have kind
of advertised it even
spontaneously go let's go almost 600k
and then you have it in like 5
minutes I see that's how it works huh
yeah yeah yeah it's it honestly it's
like magic it's crazy how it where where
do they come
from it's
really questionable oh I don't
know but I I did tweet I did tweet your
stream maybe that helps to a little bit
although everybody who subscribed to me
should already be subscribed to you
there except for my my dead Subs cuz
there's always dead dead Subs I can't do
anything about them except give them a
phoenix feather and hopefully revive
them but that's kind of a waste yeah
it's okay we all got dead Subs I get it
I get it yeah why did they die wow weak
weak
weak should have should have stayed an
active subscriber the hell or
unsubscribe don't do that they'll be
back when they remember how much they
love
you will they ever remember well I'm
sure nobody will ever forget how much
they love you
thank you I'll never forget how much I
love
you
I really even after what I said
yesterday yeah of course I don't
care what did you say about me today
that I can't watch the VA for um I was
talking about when I had the idea of
doing a pregnancy
stream um but like a fake one where like
we make a chimera of us and then over N9
months we go over the course yeah you
and me yeah except I'd carry the baby of
the the the fake the fake baby of course
oh that's chill yeah and then like we
can do like ultrasound streams and like
get someone else to role play as a
doctor you are weird how is that going
to work I don't understand really
concept it's not supposed to is it going
to take like what 10 months yeah 9mon
pregnancy streams and once a month you
do a check-in on the on the pregnancy
and then it ends in at the at the end of
the nine months with a birthing stream
where then we we
have I've birthed things on stream
before it's very exciting
yeah I'll suffer with you
exactly and then and then we have a
little a little Raven Phoenix
baby the the black phoenix you know
okay so no that's I'll have to think
about it that I it was a joke it was a
joke it was a joke
idea that's so weird it's like the
craziest laughing ever I
know I was telling them that I want you
if you're going to do this I would want
you to be like for real committed and
buy one of these like fake pregnancy
belly things huh yeah you have to wear
that for 9 month
IRL you're
crazy uh excuse me if you don't have
that kind of commitment and would like
to test that out how are we ever going
to have a child you're right you're
right you're so right okay show me your
commitment show me how much you love me
and want our
child okay I'll head I'll head to I I'll
go find a pregnancy belly sorry okay
okay oh my so weird it is feel free to
to uh work out the plan a little bit
more give it a bit more of structure she
actually wants to do it you guys look at
that I mean if it has more structure to
it possibly it could just be like a
weird reason to do a monthly
dadan the worst and best idea or you
could get a
prante uh low poly VR model oh my God
and we could meet in VR chat once per
month and we can have like a studio set
that's like a hospital oh my God and
then you spread your legs and we get a
doctor to look inside oh my God wait you
don't wait wait you don't wait no
there's no need to spread your legs huh
with the normal checkups we just spread
some lube on your belly right that's how
it works yeah yeah the the stuff the
stuff they put on your stomach for the
uh I don't think it's Lube you have a
you have a sister with many babies right
yes yes she could be at there at the
birthing as a what do you call the
ladies that help you the Midwife Midwife
yes she can be the Midwife cuz she has
experience she does you're right I'm
sure she would she would be excited to
help you with your first child yeah our
child Kiara our child our our our
virtual child that I didn't know about I
don't know how that happened I mean I
was just at your house
so just
yeah yeah okay so it's believable I
think you should start this you should
start the story with
um with a pregnancy test stream oh my
God yeah no exactly exactly all the all
the stages you need a beginning and you
need an ending mhm you're so right and
people called me crazy when I said I
just want a a VR chat wedding with my
cats why would they call you crazy for
that right what the hell I like that
idea what the heck thank you your just a
little bit crazier than mine I would say
mine is just weird well I was using it
to praise you cuz I was like I have
these batshit weird ideas that are like
really like not bad ideas but just like
very strange and then meanwhile you're
just like are able to effortlessly come
up with like the best ideas I've ever
heard and I'm like oh my God genius
takanashi k
unbelievable I think it's great if you
let your creative mind run freely you
should continue letting it do its thing
and just do weird and see what yeah
see what comes out like see whatever
sticks throw it at the wall see what
sticks M okay I appreciate pregnancy
idea is sticking cuz it's a long project
yeah it's a long project unless we do
like a Twilight pregnancy where I'm only
pregnant for two weeks and I'm rapidly
rapidly pregnant you're losing me
sis don't worry about it don't you have
a member stream to get to yeah I'm going
to go and watch a movie now but don't
give up I I think you should um maybe
put like a you don't have to have a life
counter what sometimes I used a life
counter before even if it's not exactly
accurate and then other times I would
just like keep on putting up screenshots
of the YouTube Studio
if you have a counter on the screen
people will be more motivated to click
that hit that subscribe button that's
true okay I'll consider it go go go have
fun with your movie
ction Time come
on she's gone goodbye my
queen she's so
cute I love
Takashi I love Takashi
kiata thank you for coming to that Ted
Talk uh very important information it
all comes back to Twilight that is that
is the the
situation everything comes back to
Twilight oh I got to turn
off okay here let me make sure I'm
pulling the right
thing here I just refreshed
it woo current subscriber
count
oh gambat cudai gbat Cuda
stop we love Wawa in this
household J on my soul I still can't get
over that that was so funny well wait
that was tanakha Kyra oh you're
right it was the ostrich
streamer it wasn't it wasn't actually it
wasn't actually my beloved takanashi
Kiara of course to to kiata kiata Senpai
is so busy she would never have time to
just come on one of my streams out of
nowhere you know that's just she's she's
such a queen she's so busy she has lots
of things going all the time
she she of course wouldn't have time to
to just come on little old My
Stream I just refreshed
it there we
go we can't escape Twilight Twilight is
just inescapable when you're in the same
room as
me wishing your success in getting to
600k thank you so many Twilight fans in
Hollow that's because Twilight is
objectively the funniest thing ever ever
created like I'm not going to lie to you
is it good not really but is it funny if
if you look at it from the lens of a
romantic not even a romantic comedy but
just like a comedy of a romcom where
everything goes wrong and everything is
just
blurs then that's that's
Twilight that is
Twilight I so
close oh little man he wants to leave
the
room Aradia look at our sub count I said
our but it's my sub count look we're
like 500 away from
600k how about that how about that do
you want to say hello real quick oh
hello hello everyone to tell them to
subscribe to my channel subscribe to the
channel let's get this over with why do
you excuse me okay you can leave goodbye
stop I can't give them too much content
of you or they'll like you more than
they like
me I refuse wow even with aadia and
tanak shakyra asking
you I can't believe
it can't believe it can't believe you've
done
this yeah let's go we're closing
in it's not the funniest thing it
absolutely is funny the I feel like the
amount of unintended comedy in Twilight
is just so
hilarious like it's so
hilarious so
fun it's it's a comedy it really really
is a
comedy Twilight watch along with Ms well
I I think I should tell you guys I
actually do already have a Twilight
watch along
planned I mentioned it already but
shiori yopi and me are going to be
watching the first two movies and then
fauna and Mum are going to be joining us
for eclipse and the last
two
[Laughter]
so yeah unless unless something goes
wrong but they all said they wanted to
join I already set the dates for all of
them it's going to be
great so wait to re-watch Twilight we'll
all watch it
together we you can watch it with
with your your your members here over at
hollowen and then EOP from Hollow
ID why is my chat so behind that you
guys are only just now saying hi to
Aradia wait a minute excuse me I'm going
to refresh the page in a second give me
uno
momento my chat my chat is really
behind it's really behind wherever you
guys are actually at in the
conversation so you're probably like why
are you still talking about stuff that
we
passed are you still talking about stuff
that we've already finished talking
about Nissa
ravencraft
[Music]
woo woo woo woo 500 left let's
go
wo egg laying stream I don't know about
all that that that seems like a I I
don't know about all
that I I I don't think that's I I don't
know guys stop saying hi to Ria she's
not
here she's not
here congrats a 500K wait
no we're only 500 away from
600k so close
yet so
far and our heart she's here I see hi K
kata's not here
anymore only 400k to a million I
know it's so
crazy that chat really is going
backwards through time what are you guys
doing what's happening are you guys
messing with me I'm really
lost I wonder what jailbird is going to
be my 600k
subscriber which one of
you congrats on your debut stream guys
it's been over six months what do you
[Music]
mean what do you
mean
why what are you you're making things
up you've only been here 6 months what I
feel like it I feel like it hasn't even
been that long you
know yukita thank you for the AA sua
congrats you can reach 600k Queen
narissa yes soon right now we're at 599
569 we're so
[Music]
close
yeah uh soon it'll be one year with
Advent since the Advent of Advent I know
I'm so silly haha so
original I spill water on my hand and I
have my shiny moment anytime I have any
anything on my hand where I look down on
it I go I'm so up I'm so
sorry that's my
humor who are all you people who are
subscribing someone
explain where are you coming
from who are
you 6 months time is flying so fast time
is flying
fast time is flying very
fast it was a summer's day in Winter and
the snow was raining fast a barefooted
boy with shoes on stood sitting in the
grass
little
man come in here and stop
screaming he can't
decide he can't decide where it is he
wants to
be I have to refresh what little man
he's head buding my
leg hello oh he's so
[Music]
sweet he tickling
me yeah my oshi's back little
man okay
delete add in out with the old and with
the
new yeah 400 to go let's
go I just need 400 people if you need
one reason to subscribe to me uh
I try my
hardest which maybe maybe isn't a very
good reason for some people but I sing
lots of
music I I love my family I have cats and
a dog whom I love and
adore you should you should consider
subscribing to me if you like that I
don't
know yeah if you won't sub for me sub
for my sisters if you won't sub for me
sub for my mother
you won't sub for me sub for my brother
and
father if you won't sub for me sub for
my sister's
[Laughter]
husbands May cat sing Bohemia R City
dude he just came in and he already
wants to
leave cats are so
crazy yeah if you if you won't sub for
me sub for Yago if you won't sub for me
sub for hollow
en don't mind me being
weird being a weird little
guy a little Karaoke If Only but the the
only thing is if I start doing karaoke
now then we have to private the stream
after
and this stream wasn't intended to be
privated this isn't to say that I
wouldn't mind it being privated because
all the weird conversations that we
had cuz damn did we have some weird
conversations
um do a hollow live cover I don't know
if I have any instrumentals on me right
now and I haven't updated the the app in
a
while got 400 more for
[Music]
mommy sing nursery rhymes a you're
right what ones are public
[Music]
domain sorry I didn't take a breath
before that or like I didn't take like
an act deep breath before that tonight
is
stream sub now or I can't
breathe if you if you don't subscribe
then I have to hold my breath until 600k
and then I will die so you have to you
have to it's a joke by the
way can you circular breathe I do not
know what the that
means my ears are bleeding bleeding why
are your ears
bleeding excuse
me
okay 300 to
[Laughter]
go
okay can you breathe manually of
course when I think about breathing I
start breathing
manually yeah hey new Subs talk in chat
who are
you galin thank you for the gifted
memberships
also spank
FP and hi thank you very much for the 10
gifted memberships to the
community I'm new yeah are you with your
Three Feathers I don't
know 300 to go quick summarize the whole
Twilight franchise uh okay wait you guys
just know someone requested this I'm not
doing this of my own free will okay so
Twilight is about a girl named Bella
Bella moves to Forks but she's
originally from I don't know she's from
a sunny place I think Florida I'm not
really sure uh she's actually in the
books albino partially even though her
hair is completely black and she has
dark or like brown and she has dark eyes
but Bella is super super pale because
she's slightly albino or something like
that I don't really remember so uh she
moves to this new school in forks and
she sees these really beautiful people
who uh are just too beautiful and for
some reason for some reason the she
becomes interested in the one everyone
is interested in because he's the only
single one of all these beautiful people
and he for some reason is interested in
her too because she's really
stinky she has a class with him where
they have to sit by each other and the
fan blows on him into her or on her into
him and he immediately recoils at how
stinky she is and she's like oh
my God I must stink so he leaves
class just a little bit early so he can
get away from her and then uh it turns
out we find out a little bit later after
this that he can actually read people's
thoughts but he can't read hers and her
blood because he's obviously a vampire
is really tasty smelling to him so he's
like
M that smells
tasty that smells good so he's not act
she's not actually stinky turns out she
actually smells really good but like in
a hungry sort of
way so in order to avoid uh killing her
he has to date her I don't make the
rules that that's Twilight the first
movie Bella almost dies because she
smells so so good um they kill
the person trying to kill Bella and then
we have one of the the main evil people
who's mad because the person they killed
who was trying to eat Bella was actually
uh her mate vampire and then the second
movie starts and Edward decides to leave
Bella because he realizes maybe vampires
and humans shouldn't be together because
my family has tried to eat has tried to
eat Bella
so uh he leaves without anything and
they actually steal everything from her
they don't tell you this in a movie they
installed a sound system in her car they
rip it out he goes into her room and
takes out every single picture and
everything he ever got her literally
leaving her with nothing so it seems
like just a me spoilers Guys these
movies have been up for 12
years what do you mean
spoilers and then and then you get the
best line ever
Bella Where Have You Been
Loca guys you should know this because
FAA and M watched this far into their
watch through so all of you should have
already watched this far into Twilight
what about spider monkey oh yeah
vampires are like super strong or
something I was planning to watch them
soon don't worry these are the first two
movies and they're five and I'm into the
first like 10 minutes of the first movie
so really it's not that it's not that
much and the first movie let's be honest
everyone knows how the first movie
goes the things that I'm missing are the
peak comedy of
Twilight that's what you're missing with
this
explanation what about the funny
part yeah it's a lot oh yeah they
sparkle in the
Sun Twilight is a 600k special no
someone just asked me to explain the
plot of
Twilight and people are now having
having the the G to say
spoilers for the first two
movies hi Ria she's not here please wake
up
jailbird jailbird she's not
here
almost time for
mother I need to update the screenshot
as you've noticed I'm updating it every
hundred every hundred
subscribers so give me one uno
momento um okay
200 where you get those cool glasses
they were made by
arang arong made
them arong made them and posted them on
the
Twitter so I
yeah
yeah we're really close yeah they're
connected to my hair I actually pinned
them
there
so woo they are clipped to my
bangs how are these supposed to go
around my ears you
know Storm King thank you for the AA
sua I don't lay eggs Rising Phoenix
thank you for the
Supa
W come on come on come on come
on
ah Aria my beloved stop she's not
here I don't I don't lay
eggs yukita thank you very much for the
AAA now that I listen to this I'm happy
that I skipped the whole Twilight era
book face thank you for the summary I I
only went over the first movie and like
part of the second movie you're going to
have to watch our watch along because
it'll be pure comedy please come when we
watch the Twilight movies
together does my mom like eggs no I mean
if she's in her Raven form the yeah but
I didn't come out of an egg I'm sorry to
inform
you Robo zombie thank you for the
Supa eggs please I haven't had breakfast
I'm
sorry hopefully you can eat some Eggies
soon wait did you hatch from an egg I
was
born because my mom my mom had us wait I
don't remember I feel like I've answered
this before and I don't remember what I
said I wasn't there I mean I was there
but I wasn't there don't worry about it
yeah in a way we all come from
eggs some people come from eggs like
chicken eggs and some people come from
other
eggs other eggs in the egg egg
thing
who
awkward nerissa Raven craftt
breathing the egg theory which came
first the chicken or the
egg trick question it was the dinosaur
boom hi hi hello hello
yeah we're really close I've been
updating it every hundred but I'm
already close to having to update it
again I'm like 15 away from
900 and then we'll only have 100
left crazy
valow you're so bowow
hok h h h h m m m m you can do it Ari
gelato goai
much ARA
thanks I love
you I love Advent I love
fuok mercenary VA thank you very much
for the
aaup thank you thank
[Music]
you okay
guys this is where those of you who have
secretly been waiting refusing to
subscribe because you want the chance to
be a big milestone
subscriber this is your
chance if all if all of you subscribe at
this singular
moment there's a high
chance that you
yeah 99 left let's
go inim my
show let's go let's go let's go
why wait earlier you some the better I
know I
agree
W let's
[Music]
go did on my
soul Jon my
soul
indeed that is that is where I am at
that is how I'm feeling guys Aria is not
here anymore stop saying hi to
her she's
cancelled she sent me a preminger and a
starian meme video this
morning you know how that feels that's
my that's my brand she can't start
sending my brand to
me
since it's the last one I'll update
it so close so
close so
close so close let's go let's go sorry
why am I turning into a cheerleader it's
not even my
branding
ah
I don't know how it goes perfectly
actually I would like to thank uh the
jailbirds for this uh for supporting me
every single day every time I stream
every time I don't stream for sharing my
videos for sharing my song
covers I would like to thank you guys I
couldn't have done any of this without
you uh it's it's only thanks to you guys
that I am anywhere so thank you guys so
much for supporting me
always I appre okay where's mom she's on
vacation you guys are going to have to
wait she'll she'll you'll see her soon
but not today
alas
guys guys uh there's a lot of things
happening right now I can't keep up with
it the chat's going really fast on my
side thank
you Mom get on the camera Mom where are
you they're asking for you melon P thank
you for the
aaup
vacation I know well her vacation has
been planned but she I don't think she
realized that this was going to happen
at this specific time you
know or else I don't think she would
have chosen to go on a vacation but it
it was already it was already
planned ah
600k thank you wow I can't believe we
hit it during
stream that's kind of crazy
[Music]
woo I'm so happy yeah now now we
continue to shoot for the stars with our
next goal being 700k but for now is the
time to
celebrate this was uh we did our
best let's
go
thank you guys for all the supas thank
you for all the
members thank you for all the gifts
thank you for all the sweet
messages let's
[Music]
go I'll continue to work hard for all of
your
support I'll continue to do my best oh
wait yeah
669k is actually our next
goal we got to get 600 69k chat that's
our next goal we have to work hard
towards it's it's it's what must be
done what about 666 I guess that works
for us
too Anthony Edwards thank you for the
aupa Yago will be crying I'm sorry Yago
Sama Yago
Sama I don't remember e thank you for
the AA supera that's my
Koshi thank
[Music]
you fua m tweeted about
it fua fua m
I can't believe everyone else is getting
to tweet about it before
me I want to focus on the live stream
I'll tweet about it
afterwards I love that song it's so cute
B time for me to finally come out as the
triplet to your guys's
pair KY papa is here
Papa thank you for the
pinky uh Papa
Papa Pap
[Laughter]
papa
papa not actual Papa my the papa who
made me move so
beautifully I'll make the Tweet
later I'm so
sorry I'm so
[Music]
sorry
W yeah freestyle rap I can't freestyle
rap oh
boom boom I don't know how to do that
uh the day today is a day 600k it's the
I it's February 19th uh
2024a and we have reached
600k let's go
jailbirds don't ask me to
Freestyle don't ask me yeah this is my
ninja way
600k yeah boom chab boom boom let's
go yeah don't don't edit that just don't
don't clip it either
actually pretend that didn't
happen
ah thank you guys for being here for
this moment I'm glad I kept
going thank you to kiata and Fu M for
advertising it so we could we could
reach it today while I was live
streaming despite the fact I didn't
expect
[Music]
to thank you guys for coming for this
weird breakfast eating stream that
turned into this uh
thank you let's take a
picture I got to make the glasses look
not
weird okay take a picture you guys
cheese I'm counting on you guys to take
a picture you guys can post it to my
live tag hash reive
cheese
don't forget vud gang if you were here
if you are VOD gang say hello to the vud
gang please don't forget to leave a
comment posting an egg
emote egg emoji and thank you for
watching thank you for coming and
enjoying this moment with
me what a what an amazing moment to
celebrate well as mentioned after I end
this stream I'm going to write up a post
for you guys to leave questions that you
have for
mamisa and uh once she returns from her
Voyage I will go ahead and I will select
some questions okay and then I will set
up her her stream and you guys can
finally uh meet my mother as you've been
begging and begging for you have voted
with your subscribe subscribing finger
and shown me that my mother is the one
that you want so I will give her to
you thank you
guys sorry I always say I should say
that so people know I'm doing it
intentionally to be
cute
Moonlight Kaiser thank you for the
pinky very squishy thank you for the Ana
sua now this was a blurst stream I
really don't know what
happened I I don't know what happened
here today but it happened so you know
I'm not I'm not going to complain about
that
[Music]
and this is this is what you came here
for right uh I really wish I could send
you guys
somewhere for a
raid uh but no one is alive now except
kiaha and the last I can't
really I can't do that because it's a
member's only Stream So alas I'm very
sorry I have nowhere I can send you
guys but thank you guys again so much
I'm so
[Music]
happy send to next upcoming stream okay
I think
Kyla is Kyla live right now I don't
think she's live right now but I
see I see one with bi boo that I think
is bioo and Kyla that's later today so
it's not happening yet
it's a keep talking and nobody explodes
with B boo Nino thank you very much for
the AA supera it doesn't start until
6:00 p.m. Ena should be in two hours uh
can I rate into
Ena can I rate into
Ena good thing I have you guys who know
everything um I don't see her stream on
here let me
let me go to her Twitter and see if she
has a waiting room up right now I'm sure
she does I might be able to steal it
steal it if she has
one and see if the link will work but
otherwise I'll send you guys to B Boo
for the time
being oh Ena yeah ena's raised I do
think they're turned off I don't have
them
alas we
tried you can't say we did not attempt
all right I'll send you to bio but her
stream doesn't start until later
tonight so please do uh it's broken raid
message
op our raid message is always
op all right thank you guys again so
much for joining me today thank you for
being here during this special moment uh
in jailbird history where I have reached
600k I love you guys so much seriously
so grateful for your support and I look
forward to seeing you guys all tomorrow
to play Chapter 2 of poppy play time
please look forward to it and we'll be
doing some more celebrations after my
mom gets back and probably between two
so thank you guys until next time by
[Music]
Darlings