[Music]
Mayonnaise is a drink.
By the way, the lining is made of air. Hello.
All volumes. Do you
always have frozen udon noodles? Front
completed 9Edy
[Music]
Make
Mayonnaise
is a drink.
By the way, I'm not made of air.  Hello!
[Music]
Yes, I'm experimenting with Hatchbug.
[Music] My
senior and I are
very skinny.
Now, let's go to Japan. Mr. Ken, who is currently visiting Japan, is here.
Please introduce yourself. I want you to wear a camera.
Ah, I have a camera today, so
that's my
real senpai.
[Music] I
've come to Japan, so I'll be heading home soon.
Today is the last O-collaboration.
[Music] I've
been selected.
Please.
50 kg of catchphrase
[music] I have
a lot of this left over.
I'm waiting for it.
[laughing]
[music]
And,
uh, thank you for this time.
It's
more than just one.
Ano Doro
Aaah
[Music]
Thank you,
thank you. You're
building a house with the feeling that you want everyone to come. Are you happy? It's
not special. It's special.
[Music] That's a
bad way to say it.
[Laughs]
But in this living room, like this.  This is my first time
with a camera on it.
Speaking of my beliefs, here it is to try your luck.Helen
Scratch 100 sheets at a time to try your luck.This is a
hot and thick yes.I have divided it into 10 sheets each.
This squirrel-chan is
cute.
Squirrel-chan from Indonesia.
Report to Squirrel-senpai.
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
etc.50,000 yen
3, 10,000 yen 4, 1000 yen, 5, etc.  200 yen It's
like you're guaranteed to win 200 yen once out of every 10 tickets. I
want to get the money back
.
[Music] I
'm trying my luck today.
[Music]  It's
20,000 yen per person. There are 100 tickets, so I
understand.
So if I win 2nd prize of 50,000 yen even once, I'm
sure I'll win 1 million yen. Why did you
choose squirrel when there were so many?
Kanatan
did a little research on this one.Squirrel-
chan This squirrel-chan is a little
rare, but there are quite a few 1 million yen prizes.  I
'd say it's a lot,
but there are 12 bottles, which I thought were a bit expensive compared to the other ones, but that's
okay.Although it may have seemed
expensive, do you bring a lot of them with you?
That's right.  That's right, we have the Uma. Well, it
seems that 2 million copies have been sold, but that's
300 of the 2 million, and
here's my
36,372, maybe, but there's also a 10,000 yen third prize.
There are 2,000 of them,
so I can't help it at all. [Music] [Applause] I believe in something amazing. I'm so confident.
It's my first time,
though.
[Music] I feel like I'm going to
win, I feel like I can go.
Hey everyone,
try to guess which of them is the most
accurate
?
Who will be the luckiest in the survey? Who
will be visited by the squirrel?
[Applause]
How many times does a senpai get angry like this
?
Isn't that typical of a senpai
? He said a lot of things to me, but I was
really scared when he said something to me about this boring senpai.
But, you know, I'm
becoming Pecola-senpai, but what hurts me is,
what did I want to do before I was like this? I'm
not lucky. I
was able to make it through 2022 with my pitiful character. I see.
You don't have either, but this year
is good.Oh, I drew that fortune-telling.I
didn't draw a fortune-telling fortune, but I didn't draw a fortune-telling fortune,
but I didn't draw one, but that Pokémon with a different color
came out with a probability of 451,
so it was certainly fast.  Well,
all of our luck went there that day.The
three of us went there today.We
went there and prayed.Here we were, praying that we would
win.
[Music]
What should I do? I'm going to carefully scrape them off one by one.
Oh wait, it's a squirrel. It
's a squirrel from the beginning. This is
fast.
[Music]
That's right. Don't
make me do my best.
Nakata
[Music]
Hey,
do I have to make a separate statement? I'm
counting only the hits, so it's
really like that. It's
shaking, it's
shaking.
2nd place may or may not be within reach.
Maybe, I guess. Emojis are for business use. It's quite like that. This has a lot of reach. It's not made. What is reach? I'm afraid of missing out. Hey, I thought about it. Now that's right. Well,
think about it and say, "This is reach."  Is it better to do it while thinking about it? It
's a situation where you have 2 reach and you only need one more to win. 200 yen has been 5 years, but it's been a long time since I thought about it.  It's too
late.
Believe me. Where did that thing go earlier? The
way I cut it earlier was probably better.
Thank you.
[Music]
[Applause]
Diagonally too. It's
Bingo No. 7, so
I'll have to win next time.
More of that.  I thought it would come out,
but if it was 10,000 yen,
I'd probably go. I'm a little
curious to see who will be the first to say something other than 200 yen.
What happened to the survey?  I'm
running the survey right now. When will I see the results?
Hmm, about 30 minutes
before I go in.
[Music]
By the way,
can I say this? I
want to do something before the broadcast, so I
wanted to do that.  That's what happened,
right?
[Music] I
saw it in 1000, and there's a certain movie that's being made in Japan right now.
The three of us went to see that movie.
What was it? Yes,
everyone please guess.
Sorry,
200 yen. 200 yen. It's the
first 10 pieces. Is there a
chance of 3 M10 pieces?
[Music]
Ok, thank you. It's
hard to see anime movies overseas, so that's
right.
Imported.  I wanted to see it while I was still in Japan, and
two of us had never seen it before, so
we all wanted to see it together.
Thank you so much for letting me know.  It
was great.
From the
beginning, I was immediately moved
by something. From the beginning, I
thought something sad in particular, but
somehow the introduction felt strange,
but it
shook my heart.  There's something like that. It was easy to
understand and quick. I got
it. How much is it? 200 yen.
Bowl10
[Music]
[Applause] That's
it. I'm on the 12th one. I wonder
if everyone has seen it. I want to see that movie.
I want to go see it because I like the insert song because everyone was watching it.I actually cried quite a bit
during the middle of it.It was so hard that I tried to hold back
but my tears were overflowing and it was
terrible.I thought I might be crying so much it was embarrassing, so I looked to
the side.  I was sitting next to her
with Tiara in the middle, and Talk
was sitting between them.When I
saw Tiara, I wiped my eyes and cried.
[Music]
What's wrong with that little mess?
Just when I thought that, Tiara
took out a tissue and wiped the tears from my eyes. But then I
heard a small sound. I
hate having that runny nose go back into my nose.
Everyone should do that a little bit. I'm
not crying.  I was
planning to go with a stance that said, ``That's right,'' but
halfway through, I couldn't hold back any longer, and when I
said that, I
saw someone next to my eyes
blowing my eyes a little.
Both of us.
Then I saw Tiara grab another tissue and
try to give it to the lever,
but her little finger was fine.
That's why she was going alone, but
even at the wrong place, she hit the tissue and it's
still an acorn.  I'm
used to going alone more than anywhere else, so I
don't want people to find out I'm crying alone,
even though it's people I don't know.  I've
lived my life in such a way that I can do anything about it even if I just get a little upset,
so I guess I've been trained to do that,
but I tried my best to hold back because everyone was feeling the same way.I'd
rather not cry than cry.
[Applause] That's
true.
[Music] I
saw that you were going out to everyone today, and you
were putting on make-up, but the
impression was reflected under your eyes.Cute
little bird,
is that what you mean
from the beginning?
Well, I've been
wearing this since the beginning.
[Music] I went
to the studio.
So, I
posted it on Twitter, but for
some reason there was bitter gourd juice lying around in the studio.
[Music]
[Laughs] I guess it
was at that time, but I was a little nervous.  Maybe it was
n't,
but I couldn't tell
anyone like that, but are you going to tell the other person that there's
something wrong with them, like there's some kind of glue between their teeth?
Even if you don't have a
reaction, the girl might just
tell you. It's a
lie. We're
good friends and we
're together. After all, I
understand how it feels to be embarrassed, so I'm the type of person who says things like that
.
[Music] I
thought maybe things would heal in a new way.  It
stayed like that until I got home, so I
fixed it.
I'm here too.
But, Chiara is like that. Why don't you
take the trouble to show me a photo of her with her make-up on?  You
showed me the clay today, but I
was surprised.
Actually, it's something
like a driver's license, a passport, etc. In
those places, everyone
showed their number cards.
Normally, in those places, everyone always
doesn't have a photo.  Isn't it?
Basically, everyone's
opinion is that it's ugly, but it's really
cute, isn't it? It's a
proper ID photo My Number card, and I
thought it was quite long.  I
put on my makeup properly. Even though I'm
exhibiting it today, it's
cute. It's cute. Yeah,
but I'd
like to see someone with the same makeup on. Yeah, I
wish I had done that. Now that I hear that, it
's time for the next one.
[Music]
But seriously, I've been
here almost every day,
all the time. It's
fun, but it's really hard.
[Music]
It's dark, it's dark, but it's about time.
Everyone is
telling me that I need a container.
But, you know, after
meeting so many people every day and talking to them so much,
even some of them are getting tired.
[Applause]
Meeting people can be tiring, so I do
n't really think they're going to talk about themselves.
During that time, I don't think I'm somewhere between a human being and a cheerful person,
but it's definitely fun, but you
do know that it does make you a little tired.You
had planned your schedule the day before.  I
talked to them a lot before this, and I
heard they talked to me a lot after they came,
so I'm going to do this on days when they're open,
but I don't really have any
plans to fill them in.  It wasn't
there, but then I
realized it was, and I
feel like it would be a waste if I didn't meet someone every day
.
But it was
really
fun and I got to meet all the different members.  I
felt like we had
become closer, we weren't close anymore, and I met a
lot of people for the first time, so I had a lot of fun and I was able to
make a lot of memories.Japanese
hospitality.It's
okay if you ask me about this, but this
trip to Japan was the best of all my stays.
What was delicious? What is the most
memorable thing? It
was delicious.
[Music]
Maybe it's that. I
think it's really good, or something that doesn't really work with Yakiniku
.
[Music]  I
ate so much that I really
enjoyed it.
[Music]
There are some events that left a lasting impression on me. The
location, though. Well, things like that happen in Japan already,
and this time I
didn't really come here with the intention of sightseeing.  I
guess
Enoshima is the only place I've been to. Seriously, I've already been to Enoshima. I've mentioned Enoshima many times, so I'm wondering if you
know enough about it to show me around.
Well,
let's imagine Enoshima as a place where there are a lot of couples like that. There
were quite a few groups of friends, and this one
was my group of friends. There's something like that that
makes a ring.
[Music] Hey, let
's go.  I've never heard of it before. I
think I'll be happy if I get married, but you said that. Well, I wanted to say something later.
In the last broadcast, this pinky was talking
about his mother.
I felt like I was in love with him, but he said that he was like
everyone else.
When I said that, everyone in the comment section was like, ``It's
finally too late?'' Yeah,
the dance was with that Hololith, and it's doing the same thing, and I
like that, of course I do, but I wonder what it's like, I
don't know how close it is.  There's such a
thing as emotional distance, isn't there? There's
a lot of things going on. I
really want to see Karator's eyes, like, do you really think that you'll be happy if you get married?
[Laughter]
[Music] I did
n't
say that. I wasn't told that. You
think you'll be happy if you marry me
? What do you think? I'm kind to my seniors,
even when I cook, and we
have such a wide-ranging relationship.
[Applause]
You're not home, so
let me do it. You're a shut-in, so
let me eat.
[Laughs]
[Music]
Well, I do
n't want to stop the cat, and I do
n't want to tie it down. So-and-so are you
playing today?  It's nice to be a girl.As
a girl, I feel like I might be a little
jealous.If I think about it
seriously, I
see.But
on the other hand, what do you think about Sayuri?
Can you cook, please?
You
seem to be
working hard there. You're working hard, aren't you?
Because work is my love, I'm now
my wife, working hard in the dormitory and
raising our children. If we
suddenly had a child, it would be my
job.  And
Tiara
will take care of the children in the family. It
might be a huge help.
When I get home, the food will already be cooked.
[Music]
[Music] I
'll go back to my small business for a moment, but everyone.  I
can't find anything other than acorns.
There's a song called Donguri Guri Donguri Ko.
Right now, there are 40 acorns.
[Music]
Collect them.
Collect them. They just want to eat them.
[Music] This is
so
incredible.  If
I had that, would I eat a hat? Would I
eat my own hat? It seems
unlikely, so
it's interesting. I'm
sure there are similar words in Japan, too.  I
wonder what it is. I'm thinking about it, but it's not good at all. I'm sorry. I don't know what it is. It's German, but it's similar in Japan. There's something about it. I heard it after standing on your head and eating spaghetti.
Or something like doing a full circle.  It's
not a proverb
like
that, it's a joke, it's a belly button, it's a belly button, it's a big box, that's right, it's a belly button, it's a big box, that's right.  It's
like if I won a million in the lottery, I'd make my belly button boil. No, I'd make my makeup boil. It's not when I burst out laughing. It's like channel or something that's too funny. Maybe I'll eat tea. What's that? Are you
eating spaghetti? It's
like eating a hat.  Yeah, I see. It's
really dirty,
but I remember poking the knob.
Yeah, 100 million yen If I can do this, I'll pay 100 million yen.That's true.I'll
say something impossible.That's what
Doraemon was asking for.
Maybe when the squirrel hits it, it's at an angle. Hey, I'm
sure it wasn't at an angle either. I've never seen it. I
'll go there. 1 million people will come. Wow.
Yes.  It's almost
time, but there's still a lot left It's
tough, isn't it?
[Music]
But 200 yen is a good win, and I won again. It's
gone in two minutes.
For example, if you turned into an acorn diagonally,
this one too.  It's like an acorn at an angle.
That's
unlikely. I don't think so.
So there's no way you'll hit two acorns. Seriously,
even if you hit two acorns, it'll cost you 400 yen.  I
wonder if it's a
difficult question, but it comes down to
how to count the double part in the middle.Anything
other than 200 yen.It'll work out
somehow.It
won't turn out to be an apple.By the way, that's what
Kane and I
actually bought together.  I wonder if
there are people like me who are running. Oh, please
. We didn't tell you if it was Maris or not, so
maybe you didn't know, but
there are people who won first or second place.  I
won't do it because I don't think it's a scratch weapon.I'm sorry I
didn't buy it, but I haven't
done it.I haven't done it at all.Maybe people don't believe me.I don't
like this kind of thing, but I don't usually do it.It's
okay, leave it to us.We're
doing it.  I'm a
former oblique who shouldn't give up.
[Music]
huh?
[Laughs]
OK
OK I
don't really use it for myself.  That's
right, me. Hmm, you
know what? I
use it for things like streaming, singing, and live performances, but I
don't tell myself I'll use it that way, so I've been
thinking a lot about 1 million yen. Eh, I
'll buy something good for myself.  It doesn't have a face or anything. I'm
thinking of prohibiting it from being used for activities
.
[Music] It's
not a
squirrel. It's actually a four-headed leaf. No, I'll
put out a squirrel after this.
Hey, ok.
1 million yen for myself.
[Music]
Well, Austria doesn't have that kind of ocean, but
there are a lot of really nice and beautiful lakes, and it's
surrounded by beautiful mountains, and it's a
really beautiful scenery, so first I'm
going to buy a house, a tiny little house.
[Laughter]
[Music] It
's not
even
close to a car. Well, it's cheap. If it wasn't a car, I'd understand
. You're
small. You do
n't have a driver's license
yet. Well, I see. Well, I guess we'll go on a
trip.
[Music] I
guess I'll travel the world. If I had a million, I'd make more. [Music] I think I'd make more money.
Cats and cats are a little expensive
. I
guess I
should buy some nicer furniture. I'm getting more and more realistic. Um,
then I...  I think I'll buy a bed. I
've heard good things about it, but it's
really nice to have proper eyes.
The face is
so fluffy and fluffy. There's a lot of things like that. Yeah, check,
check.  My
tiara is coming out now, so my
brother is
going to show it to me. I'm
sorry, but I thought it would be good to have a bed or something that would lead to a lifestyle or physical health. That would lead to activities, right?  From now on,
Rin, let's
go out and eat some delicious food. We've got a lot more
money.
[Laughs]
Still, we won't be streaming anymore, and we
won't even talk about going out to eat.
Isn't that the point?  Please
let me do that in the first place. Is
there anyone who has ever done it? It's 1
million yen. It's a
cheap, cheap lie 100%. Eh, the
sales in a day are probably more than that. That's
why it is possible.
[Music]
1 million yen is probably not possible.
[Music]  [Music]
[Music] I really wanted to
play Gochi Naru
[Music] There
was a TV program and I've only seen it twice,
at a rather upscale restaurant.  I
didn't know the price, I didn't know what it looked like, I just
looked at the menu, and
then I ordered. I came here with only the text of the menu written on it. It was about 1,000 yen. I thought they were really happy.
Congratulations
[Music]  It
's a game where the price is set, like 25,000 yen, and you order only the amount closest to that 25,000 yen.It's
like guessing the price.  It's
not like it's worth 10,000 yen to try this and eat that,
but it looks like it's going to be fun.The
contents of the distribution are already like ice cream, right?
But
in order to do that, I
have to lend money.
Besides, you have to order a lot of expensive items, so I
guess it's
just the right amount.It
's a show called Gochi Naru, so the
people who are away from the price setting are the ones who pay out of pocket.
That's why [Music] I don't like it, but it seems like it would cost a lot to rent it out privately.
[Music] We
might be able to do that with that one thing.
That's 1 million yen. I
get it.
Even people who know me know it.  Even for people who don't like it, I
hate having people see me naked, so I've
been going to Japan for quite a few years straight, but
that audio comes from a place where I've
never been,
but I like the idea of ​​hot springs.  I
really want to go there, but if I can, I'll rent it out for myself
[Music] I think we
can do it if we help the inns, right? There are some
small inns that
have hot springs in the rooms,
but they're
small, and they have audio and
beautiful scenery.  Hey,
[Music] When I
come to your room, I want to put it on the proper one, not the little one. Because I
want to go
in without thinking or worrying about anything.
-
[Music]
By the way, I've
been to that hot spring, but only twice in
my life. Well, I guess the
first time was in a public bath, but it was
n't that long ago.Actually, it's
been quite recently, or rather, it's been a little while.  About a year ago
,
I thought it's impossible that I've never been to Japan even though I've been to Japan for so long,
so I
decided to go there.I was
wondering if you knew of this big hot spring in Yokohama.  It
's in Yokohama.
If you don't know, there's a
famous
hot spring in Yokohama that's really big. I
can't read it on the beach. It's
called the Manyo Club. I went there naked with my tiara on
.  [Applause]
Wow, I guess I made that mistake. I
shouldn't have gone to a place with so many people. Wow. It
was embarrassing, I
was nervous, and I ended up getting burnt, so no matter
where I looked, I wasn't supposed to go there.  I do
n't know where to look when I see naked people, so I'm afraid they'll get angry if I look at them.
[Music] I'm
worried
[Music] I feel like there are
people from other countries in there, too
. It's
beautiful, isn't it?
[Applause]  ]
[Music]
Kae-chan really loved hot springs, and she
said so much because there
were so many of them
at that inn.  It's
nice to have an open-air bath that fits the balcony,
but I
guess I should have used some courage here. But I
only did it once.
When it wasn't crowded, it
was the least popular place in the inn.  I
went to a hot spring,
and the other two women left just as Uchi and Bora-chan went in,
so we
stayed together the entire time, so I
died. That's a good time.  I
'm used to Japan, but it seems like I
came here from the savannah.I
think it's
safer to reserve a bath for yourself.When you take a bath,
let's reserve a bath for yourself.It
might be better to reserve a bath for yourself, but I
wonder if we can do something about it.  I wonder
if it's possible to do something like a store or something,
but I'd
love to do a collaboration or something like that.
[Applause]
But I still think this
Even if I go with someone, it's still
embarrassing. Whether it's a
friend, an embarrassing friend, or a real best friend,
if they're my first and second best friends, I
might be able to go there just in time.
[Music]
Austria
There's a bath there, but
I...  But I'm going home today.
[Laughs] I
took a bath, and then went to the bath
event by myself, and then
went to the bath event, so I
kind of avoided the bath event.
If it was like taking separate baths, I wouldn't have done it at all.
When someone asked me to come in with them, I said no.
I think it's good that we're separated, right? There's a time when we
took a bath in a hot spring together.
Yes, we do. I see. There
's a
bath, a bath, a bath, a bath.  I
want to see his body.
Well, I can see it. It's weird in the future. I don't want to
look at it too much. That's why I
looked at puberty, and I
felt like I looked like a boy in middle school.  It's like
I didn't even try to put on a calm face, but that thing is gone. [Music] [Music] Eh, Marine-senpai, wait, you stopped when you were about to say hello to me, but what's wrong with you? We went in together, but I didn't.  I don't think so.
[Music]
But you know, I can already imagine it, so it's no big deal.
But that's not
the case. She
took my hand and put that thing
on her breasts,
so I already made the sauce.  I
can imagine it, but yeah, no, mom. First of all,
even if I miss it, I'm being watched. It's
different when I'm being watched. I've been found
out that I'm watching. It's
not a live show, but if someone
gives me the model of the car,
what should I do right away?
Or something like that.
[Applause]
Calm down. I
haven't really looked at it that much. I'm
not that interested. I don't
really want to see someone say something like 8 glasses of beer. It's
nothing special. I
'm a junior high school student.  If I
really have to watch it, I'll just
press that button on the photo and
watch it by myself.
I don't know what to do when I'm naked. There's so
much going on here.
So, is anyone else watching except Marin-senpai? I'll
come in with you.  It's like,
if it was a game, you'd just get stills, and
then illustrations would come out.But then you take a bath after taking a sheep bath.That's
amazing.  There
was talk about how embarrassed I was about Suzu and how true it was during the broadcast.
After it ended, I asked if it
was true
and asked if I would be able to
enter. It's an age-
restricted game and you
might not be able to see it in
other games.  But
even though we said we'd go in together, aren't Japanese baths
small? It
was ours, so Mel-chan
went in first, and
when Arai finished, her little finger went in, but
just for a moment.
When I'm naked,
at the same time, I'm
in the same room with my
little finger, and while I'm being used, my pinky finger comes up and we
use it together. After all, I've
seen it before, so I wonder
if I'm not longing for it, but I
can't go back.
[Music] I'm not
feeling well, am I?  My
mom came back and I was in a different world
right now.
[Music]
By the way,
at the movie theater, I loved that movie so much
that
when I finished watching it, I
went to the goods store.  I
thought I'd pick out some goodies and buy them.
[Music] They're
kind, so it's
okay
. They weren't expensive. I
thought they were making time for me, but
on the other hand, I heard about them, so everyone
came to meet me.  I want you to think of that item as me and
cherish it for the rest of your life.It's so
cute.If you
watch the movie, you'll
understand.I
bought a chair.Even if I
think of it as something special, it's a little strange.  It's
good
because it was in the movie
[Music] I do
n't want to give away spoilers, but that's what
Seishinkai's
movie was.
Well, there must have been a school there, right? I
wonder if it
was the enemy's child.The school comes up quite a bit.Maybe I've
seen your name, I've seen all the weather.I do
n't know which one, but it
was there too.  I'm
a little curious as to whether
or not they're connected, and I want to think that there's definitely some kind of connection,
right? It's definitely somewhere along the way.  It
might be a problem
with the battery.Everyone seems to be
going off.When I try to enter
something, it says something wrong, so I'll do it.Please
wait a
moment.Please wait.
[Music]
[Music]  It's
difficult because
even if I try to sing alone, it's difficult, but I love it, and I've already told Chara many times that I really listen to it.By
the way, I'm
going to say it on that topic today.  There's a
new one out, right? It's
been arranged.
[Music]
About three hours ago, I worked on the arrangement. A
new industrial BGM came out.  The
sound was good, and the
video was also good. It
's in 3D or something. I don't know.
Chane-chan and I
were running past. Let's
go back in a different direction.
There's a mentor that everyone wants to see.
[Music]  ]
Everyone,
please come back.
[Music]
Yes, it's a bit like that before
and after.
Let's hold hands so we don't disappear again.
[Music]
To Senpai
Sorry, I'm being patted in front of my house
[Music]
But I
can't play games
By the way, Sayuri also
has 10 left, but
hurry up, maybe 15. Eh,
while I'm talking, here are
10 left.
Well, there's a possibility, there's a possibility.
Let's take a look at this character. I wonder
if I'll help my senior, but is
n't it somewhere else
?
[Music]
But then, 10 pieces, 10 pieces that can be cut together at the end.
Nice, nice,
please buy it. Eh,
let's close the survey.
Ending point:
Sonya
.
Who is the best
? Tiara-senpai, 1st with 38%.
Kano, with 35%.
2 people 26%
Fortune-telling says that luck will turn around this year.
It's already
coming around.
It's coming around for us. We
still have 10 cards left.
Hey character, how
much time do we have left when we all do this
?
Delete all of this, too. It's
like he's not happy about it.
[Music]
Winner: He
asked me to postpone the summer.  I'm
not a patch group yet,
so what's that about Peko-
chan? Acorn was the only one who
was a genius.
Where did the numbers come from?
All of them were geniuses.
I don't have confidence, but I don't like it, but the clothes and hair are the last
thing to do.Well, I guess I
have to smile at the first one, or this is what I'm going to put out in the last 10 photos.At the
beginning of the stream, I
asked if I could make acorn rice.  The ending was amazing,
yes, it
was a shame.
[Music]
[Music] I was out of place,
Acorn Lion. I keep
adding up. I
wonder if I should count at the end. I wonder if I should count today
. [Music]  I've
seen so many of them that I've stopped believing in them.
[Music] It's an
acorn.
Why?
Seven,
seven, ah.
There's no squirrel reach left. If the acorn
hits, there
's no point in leaving it behind.
These 10  I'm pretty sure it's around 3 out of 5. Once I
get 2 Acorns, it's already
[Music]
Why are you saying this? I'm not
happy anymore.
That's the third acorn.
[Music] You
know that.
By the way, there was one that wasn't there this year.
[Music]
[Music] There's
only two more
[Applause]
Please
[Music]
[Music] I'll
do it one by one. So much
so that it
becomes a silver marinade. The
rubber gloves turn silver one by one.
Little by little, the bowl is filled with grapes, acorns,
leaves,
leaves, leaves, all right.  Is the
tiara damaged? There
may be only one squirrel left at the edge. There
's a chance to cut the stump. Let's
go.
[Music]
Let's do a Thai kick. Let's do some scratching.
Maybe we'll try that.
Everybody gets along well, and it's only once, so next time too.  Is
n't this a game of acorns? What do you
think? Well, let's
go. My
name
is 12.
[Music] I
never imagined this.
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter] There's a
glove on it.
[Music]
Yeah.
[Music] I
have this one too, but I'm sure there's
another one. I'm sure it'll
be number 10.  3 tickets should be a win,
so yes, it's there somewhere 295301
[Music] That's
a lot of tickets, I can't help it
[Music] There's a
minimum
guarantee of 30 tickets and you win 5,800 yen.
That means 6,800 yen.
Eh,
6,800 yen 30
x 200 is 6,000 yen, which is 5-200 yen.
[Music] That's a
shame.
[Applause]
This is a real acorn
deficit of 3,000 yen.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] That's
true,
please.
[Music]
[Music] You're
bringing your child. That's
right.
[Applause] This is
the last one.
Come on.
There's a possibility that leaf leaves can cost 1,000 yen.
[Music]
This isn't an acorn. It's definitely
not an acorn. The acorn is already blocked, so where should I look?
[Applause]
Lie
[Applause] [Music]
[Music]
[Music]  I
haven't really counted that.
[Music]
Acorn, I
wonder if I've missed it.
[Music]
Senpai also
got 7000 yen. Hey, one-two, as expected.Wow, the
camera is dead. It's not here.
[Music]
So this time, the 100-picture
competition is
Hi Senpai and Koyori, who won 1st place with 7,000 yen. 3
[Music] I
lost
[Music]
But, but, if you think about it, everyone  Is that so
?
[Music]
Everyone, 2023 is
From now on, I'm glad I didn't
have to spend 1 million yen. That means there
's still a long way to go.
[Music]
[Laughter]
What should I do to give it to everyone? Well then, it's a
big responsibility, I'll
lock you up and then I'll give you some
food.  This
is the last collaboration,
so I'm going to share some of my memories with my seniors.Memories
from today.Memories from Japan.Eh, it
seems like it reminds me of the club's club.Hmmm.  I
think we all have times like that, but before I came to Japan, my
motivation wasn't all that low,
but it was
n't all that high, either, and I was
playing a lot of clubs in Japan.  Being on the cutting edge and
being able to talk about things, I guess it's all about everyone,
watching people work, it's amazing, I'm so
moved by that, I'm moved by it, I'm
also inspired by what's
to come.
Thank you for making me think, let's do our best, let's try harder.
[Music]
Senpai,
Senpai, tonight is
amazing, it's
amazing, really.  I don't
think I would be able to do this even if I went overseas,
so I thought I'd like to emulate their amazing action, so
thank you for watching.
[Music]
We're going too. I want to go. I want to go.
[Music] In
the end, I wo
n't come.  I'm
here. Your
ability is truly amazing. I
want to do my best. First, I'll start with a passport.
Yes, I see. I have to get it
after I get it. There's nothing I can do about it, so
it's difficult.
Thank you. This time, I
tried to use that treasured kanji, so
please everyone at home.  Please tweet your thoughts at Takanakuya.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you again.
See you soon
[Music]