​​​ ​I hope I meet a dreamy guy!​ ​​
​​​ ​sutekina hito deaimasu yo~ ni!​ ​​
​​​ ​(hahahaha baby)​ ​​
​​​ ​(ahaaaa)​ ​​
​​​ ​(come on, Kobo-chan)​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna land a job by the end of this week​ ​​
​​​ ​konshuuchuu ni wa baito o kimetai​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY KOBO-CHAN)​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna land a guy by the end of next week​ ​​
​​​ ​rairaishuu ni wa kareshi o kimetai​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY WATAME)​ ​​
​​​ ​All these things to do, and I'm running outta time​ ​​
​​​ ​ma. souiu koccha de dotabata suru~ wa​ ​​
​​​ ​(ah~)​ ​​
​​​ ​(dotabata ah yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​Need some stockings or I'm gonna freeze​ ​​
​​​ ​pansuto hakanakya angai hieru​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY KIARA)​ ​​
​​​ ​But all these mixers are spending sprees​ ​​
​​​ ​goukon suru ni mo keihi ga kasamu​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY HOLOLIVE)​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on!​ ​​
​​ ​It should be simpler than that, listen to me​ ​​
​​​ ​ne! tanjun meikai datte itteru~ jan​ ​​
​​​ ​Listen to me​ ​​
​​​ ​...tte itteru~ jan​ ​​
​​​ ​(hoi)​ ​​
​​​ ​Dear Santa, I'm saying please​ ​​
​​​ ​Santa no ojisan onegai​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring me a heart-throb like in the movies​ ​​
​​​ ​eiga mitaku deawasete ne koibito​ ​​
​​​ ​(wow!!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna flirt to the max this weekend​ ​​
​​​ ​pittari shitai Kurisumasu​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna chill to the max this Christmas​ ​​
​​​ ​mattari shitai Kurisumasu​ ​​
​​​ ​All I'm thinking of is a boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​atama no naka hotondo kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​(mmmmfufu)​ ​​
​​​ ​(ahaaa~n)​ ​​
​​​ ​(yeah, hololive here we go!)​ ​​
​​​ ​My phone will stop working​ ​​
​​ ​'cause I can't pay the bills​ ​​
​​​ ​kongetsu pinchi ne denwa tomarisou​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY HOLOLIVE)​ ​​
​​​ ​Waking up early to doll up,​ ​​
​​ ​all the way to the frills​ ​​
​​​ ​meiku no tame nara hayaoki shichau​ ​​
​​​ ​(L-O-V-E LOVELY HOLOLIVE)​ ​​
​​​ ​And in the blink of an eye,​ ​​
​​ ​there goes my day off​ ​​
​​​ ​ma. a! cchuu kanji de kyuujitsu wa sugi~ru​ ​​
​​​ ​"Ah."​ ​​
​​​ ​"a"​ ​​
​​​ ​My friend's boyfriend, this is such bad luck​ ​​
​​​ ​tomodachi no kare wa naze ka​ ​​
​​​ ​Always brings along the lamest boys​ ​​
​​​ ​taishita otoko o tsuretekonai...​ ​​
​​​ ​Aw, this sucks​ ​​
​​​ ​a~n tsumannai!​ ​​
​​​ ​(wow!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna flirt to the max this weekend​ ​​
​​​ ​pittari shitai shuumatsu​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna surprise to the max this year-end​ ​​
​​​ ​dokkiri shitai nenmatsu​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna show off the perfect boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​jiman shitai sutekina kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​Petitmoni - Pittari Shitai X'mas!​ ​​
​​​ ​Instrumental: UndreamedPanic​ ​​
​​​ ​Mix/Master: Gojo Kai​ ​​
​​​ ​Illustrations: Resu (Full body), Mitsumine (Chibi)​ ​​
​​​ ​MV: Raina Illune​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Takanashi Kiara,​ ​​
​​ ​Kobo Kanaeru, Tsunomaki Watame​ ​​
​​​ ​Santa, are you even real?​ ​​
​​​ ​Santa wa hontouni iru no?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've believed in you since I was little!​ ​​
​​​ ​chiisai koro kara shinjiteru noni!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, Santa!​ ​​
​​​ ​mou Santa-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Santa!"​ ​​
​​​ ​"Santa-saa~n!!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna flirt to the max this Christmas​ ​​
​​​ ​pittari shitai Kurisumasu​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna chill to the max this Christmas​ ​​
​​​ ​mattari shitai Kurisumasu​ ​​
​​​ ​All I'm thinking of is a boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​atama no naka hotondo kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​(wowowow WOW)​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna flirt to the max this weekend​ ​​
​​​ ​pittari shitai shuumatsu​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna surprise to the max this year-end​ ​​
​​​ ​dokkiri shitai nenmatsu​ ​​
​​​ ​All I'm thinking of is a boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​atama no naka hotondo kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna show off the perfect boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​jiman shitai sutekina kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​Aw, I wanna show off my future boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​a~n jiman shitai mirai no kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​jiman shitai sutekina kareshi​ ​​
​​​ ​Boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend​ ​​
​​​ ​kareshi kareshi~ kareshi​ ​​