[Music]
n
hello
[Music]
yay y
yay
hi I'm
on why do you guys have clothes sleepy
I'm so sleep I got coins why not sleepy
wa yeah you get like 150 coins in the
beginning and one shirt costs 50 coins
it's so expensive I have Z
coins wait the 50 coins that's nothing
look at the other prices those are way
more crazy this is the cheapest shirt
yeah or you could get like a little fart
Emoji thing oh yeah so use fart Emoji
I'm gonna click okay well uh is it
everyone's first time playing the
game yeah yes going we introduce
ourselves no yes
[Applause]
okay
okay from
starting the player order Z okay start
okay we can we can introduce ourselves
while doing the volume check then okay
right
okay Mission I'm not a cat I'm P
hello hello
yeah sounds
good next one the one who says sounds
good
thanks for having
me did you just wake up oh no I'm just
sick she's sick she oh you're oh she
sounds a little bit like
money oh my God sounds like okay
and next uh uh my lovely this running
[Music]
bird which one uh w w w yeah why why did
you need to think so long about cuz
you're both are running I was
choosing okay
hi um I'm the kiaha I uh love ID girls
and I love am so this is like the best
party ever let's go let's
go oh my God so [\h__\h] loud
go let's
go next the one this yellow
bird La who's yellow yellow
bird um how to how to introduct
sh my soul there you go introduction da
okay good good day man my name is
k from H third generation D my
song that's what we've all been waiting
for have you had brecky yet brecky Brey
yes
Brey brecky okay okay brecky d okay next
uh Amy let's
go hello Amia Watson
[Music]
on we have a
detective we have a detective and we
have a secret agent very nice
I'm I'm barely a
secret do you
guys the misunderstanding of why am is
here oh oh oh should we should we talk
about
it
funny him wait can can we talk about it
yeah yeah yeah oh yeah so I I I reacted
with an emoji to the the invite of this
because I was like oh shoot that sounds
like a cool game so I put a little POG a
little cie POG reaction and uh yeah I
wasn't expect you to join but I'm here
and I'm happy to be here anyways we're
happy that you're here we're happy that
you're
here didn't sign up but she's still here
even though she didn't sign
up she didn't sign up for this it was
really funny more the merrier yeah it
was really funny cuz I was like uh react
if you want join and I was like I'm
imped so I was like let's
go
makes sense sense okay uh this
by re I'm Ru
[Music]
yay next last but not least our sweepy
sleepy
bird
bird oh did you hear just forget about
mea oh
[Music]
my that's how it is
okay how even I thought you did our
introduction I'm
sorry okay
go attention please thank you for your
[Laughter]
attention I miss
you okay now the real last but not
[Laughter]
[Music]
least hello it's Ana from Hol Live ID
second second she got
off wait um how do you change your color
can you change your I think you need to
already the perfect color mean Lobby
perfect yeah yeah yeah you look good
perfect you look good I mean yeah okay
yeah it looks it looks good okay yeah
good okay good go okay since we don't
have much time I'm thinking we can do a
um two maybe one uh one to
Classic one to two classic games try and
then we can try other stuff like um the
hide and seek or The Killing Spree one I
think o yeah there's many different
modes and stuff sounds gooda Sensei
yes is this um is this game like a
certain impostor game this call oh yeah
yeah something similar but
duck okay Goose du du wait which one
which one is the Imposter the duck or
the goose I think the
goose the goose is the crew
mate sorry uh I haven't very I think I
haven't play either two go and one duck
in the title I haven't
yeah I haven't played either I couldn't
up my alarm oops also this is also going
to be my
first sorry just in case I overslept
um yeah okay let's play I think it's
everyone's first time playing anyway so
let's play Let's
Play What go
wrong three two one
okay so we I haven't
played oh oh let's
go wait
what who am I lovers with Bud
very like they're not even going to tell
us who who who who the lover
is so okay somebody somebody else is a
lover but I don't know
who oh I shouldn't talk out loud cuz
it's like proximity chat
[Music]
raining
oh
hello oh if you click on the
test it kind of navigates you to the it
gives you
likey oh you're
[Music]
right let's see oh I can't go here I oh
this is so bad I don't know the
directions why does this why are you
following
me I don't know where to
go very
sus you you forgot about
me you forgot about
me I thought you were
H I thought you were
H you you you hate me that much okay no
I don't hate
you
no oh she
disappeared oh
hello let's
see dust oh oh it's supposed to be
inside
oh I'm so bad at directions I don't know
I haven't played the game okay I I
wanted my first time to be with everyone
so okay let's see the map I'm in West
Wing and then I see a bunch of people
there I think no not a bunch of people
that's task
right oh
chest something o Senpai doesn't have
but she oh
hello hello I'm cling hello are you sure
you're
cleaning yes
I'm very sus oh I guess she is
claiming I think she's a crew
mate I think she is a goose she's a
goose why else would she know that she
has to clean the
clock
[Music]
what what let's
go am I done
huh huh
[Music]
y
oh we were
L we were
L at okay we need the wait did no one
kill yet no one to kill I was just
trying to see what yeah okay okay it's
okay I think we can make the Tas
longer
[Music]
longer I was looking for dead bodies cuz
I was the vulture I'm supposed to eat
dead bodies but there were no no dead
body oh my God what the heck it's four
um we do have um it's four for SC
right
no two dust and then two two other
people on the duck
site wait was there four people I think
the rolls for the um the duck site is
only two so oh wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait yeah only two
only two
and
both
ah yeah I I was I was a vulture which is
not the duck wait who's the duck then
you're not a duck but a duck is a are
you guys supposed to help the Ducks
no means no the vulture is kind of doing
their own thing they just they don't
don't even have to do tasks but they
also don't kill they just eat corpses
and if they get to eat corpses they
they're just in for the they're just in
for the win
yeah just for yeah just I mean dodo as
well it's like Jester if they get folded
out they they win thought I thought yeah
I thought that was supposed to be like
know the um cuz when you're a duck you
get these like unlock this and that like
sabotage unlock blah blah blah do I
could but yeah I've been trying to work
that out but I didn't get
it I understand you have to kill someone
if you want to sabotage oh so it's like
oh knowled I will bring Senpai I was
searching for you we were
lovers you know you know what's crazy
the lovers Ro they didn't tell us who
the who the other partner is yeah yeah
yeah so we have to look by ourselves is
it okay if we just came out where's my
lover yeah my lover okay try one more
time um my task I I I set the task list
to be larger so I think it should be
fine can everyone okay let's go press
ready ready up please ready okay again
let's go
[Music]
game
again who is it this is not fair also if
like the other one dies then
I hi hi are you my
lover no you got
another
yeah so silent I'm
scared organized knives wait is there
anything I can
do
okay
cleaning done the thing is the the task
should be larger I don't know
what
yummy sorry sorry what hell hello no no
no we we were at the dinner table and we
didn't know that it means like
emergency okay my oh my God okay okay
skip skip
Sor wait we can't skip we have to
vot okay okay this is literally a skip
ad moment
okay oh now we
canip the Ducks are
flating the Ducks
fled what what does that mean what does
that mean I know what that mean everyone
is safe for now okay okay
okay also I'm not going to be looking at
hi hello hello I'm not going to be
looking at chat because I know you guys
will spoil me and I don't want spoilers
how do we
eat how do we eat the S wait wait wait
wait that's the dinner bell oh I'm so
sorry sorry I got whenever I see Bells
I'm just
like
amazing
oh okay huh how does this
work you scared
me
I cannot do this
task no
oh guys guys
guys I did see
ol you and Ollie went upstairs right I
went right and then I saw it upstairs m
upstairs the room beside it oh how dare
I was doing the dishes Ella was with me
this where wait report in this game can
you self report in this game yeah I
don't know I think wait I think so it's
it's
either both Ollie and
Kyla but it wasn't Kyla because she just
got into the
room how do I vote how do I how the hell
do we vote you just pressed the name I
think I just what what yeah I think I
press the
name how do I skip what oh my god oh w w
wo okay I think we don't know what we're
doing yeah say I
think I don't think it's
rainy I don't think it's rainy because
she she got footed twice might
be I think hi you super sus hello super
Super SU super sus I only trust
ring are you sure you only trust rainy
because I'm starting raining ooh hello a
lot of people here
it's but if you keep it's okay you can
just keep going with rainy so if if you
die I'll okay okay okay okay if I die
it's rain okay good
luck and you look sus too afan look very
s sure are you oh are you my
lover are you my lover are you my
lover are you my lover no way are you my
lover are you my
[Music]
we can't die don't we hate each other
today no no no no it's it's it's a it's
a very popular Trope from hate to
love oh my gosh enemies to
lovers enemies to lovers
stro we are friends to enemies to
lovers together okay okay okay hello
hello rain it rain it do you know that
we we became enemies to
lovers what we we went from enemies to
lovers you can kill anyone right sh why
are you guys always together why are you
screaming that I can kill anyone you can
kill anyone right just kill all of us is
so kill me kill me kill me kill Sheriff
can kill anyone right I think no I'm a
sheriff I I only I only kill
Ducks I think it's KY she keeps ssing
everyone then can I kill KY yeah just
kill me no no
no don't don't don't don't just kill me
no no no no no kill so everyone
witnessing yes going to be yeah and then
going to be responsible for my D my
lover will die no that's so dramatic
no what what do I
um no one trust me I said I trusted
you I said I said don't raining no one
trust me
before she selfreported
Senai was staying L the entire time wait
wa wa wa did you actually report or
because I was Canadian so like I self
report report it's Auto
report don't kill the Canadian don't
kill the
Canadian I literally said that I saw wa
and rainy together before that happened
and but no one
TR we didn't hear though I I don't
remember you saying it yeah
it me and are often
together who was who who was the who was
the who got the lover
roll oh yeah I no not me what the lover
R was was it
you no I'm I'm lover with you oh wow so
we got it
correct spicy sorry my alarm keeps
ringing on okay so turn it off girl I'm
trying turn this is a lot more faster
than TR I have anot I said an alarm
every
alarm I'll turn it off okay so are we
ready how about we switch it up with
different
rules
yeah let's see different rise and grind
Gamers I
think uh I think I think I think I we
can do assassin so basically it's uh you
can kill during meetings by correctly
guessing a role or die
trying your tasks are Die Trying yeah
kill during meetings Okay mhm okay let's
go let's go
okay let's go give me one
second one one more you scare me
woman I'm
ready
uh okay let's go save save
[Music]
save
oh
interesting
hello
W okay let me do
Tas oh
stuck how do it
are you my
lover I love
[Laughter]
you it counts it
counts
M be gone P rats be gone okay we killed
all the
rats now
what was that what did you say
h did did you just say something about
killing I said kill the
rats
is it kill the
rats why because I I got a task that is
whacking up see it's not
[Music]
Mead self reports us might be self
report no no can can can you explain
where was the body where was the
body uh the body is is in the laboratory
in the top right labatory wow
labatory well me me and Ella we were we
were in the kitchen I'm in the kitchen I
was trying to
find very far we were in The West Wing
yeah we were in the west suspicious I
think it was me don't skip it was me I
self-reported don't
skip oh it was you actually what it was
me that's very s that's very sad that's
so sad what if she's not that's very sad
what what if she's a doo bird oh she's
the doo isn't
she probably a
do
very wasn't me
I you guys believe her so easily I was
like oh how do I make myself like if I
want to be kicked out as a do I should
just make people think that I'm the
sussy one so I
just too S I skip I voted
Watson how many times did R Senai got
the duck and the
the two the duck it's the duck I'm
voting you next times
now whatever happens we're voting her
out
first okay let's ready I'm
ready
[Music]
again n n hi hi I'm in
love
just I'm just going to act
normally it'll be fine I'm just going to
act
normally
oh oh hello zaa yeah I have a compromise
are you it
yeah huh I'm a vulture I want to eat
bodies me too I want to see
bodies so are you it or
[Music]
not why are you not doing
tasks because I'm a vulture vulture have
fake task oh okay I'm just finding okay
let me find my
lover where is
it where is
it that's very
s
I think I'm supposed to is it sabotage I
think we need to fix the sabotage thing
yes yes sabotage
sabage did you guys got it yes I got it
I got it
fix does everybody have to do it I think
everybody has to do
it I did it I it already wait wait wait
I think
what wait I
think
okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay this is my own personal
office oh hi you're not doing anything I
see no I'm doing
that
stop following
[Music]
me no no it's for your safety if you die
I can just eat your body
no yum
yum
no so you're not doing tasks you're R
around am I'm being stuck I'm just sling
up my
last
hi hi oh I love this
task cleaning I love this task putting
the water in oh you're cleaning no I'm
putting the putting the water in oh yeah
you're putting the water and then it's
going to be going to be here
later
huh no two people
gone two people gone
where is it in the piano room I'm voting
no matter
what why it's re Senai re it's her why I
mean it's your
last
recent because she's always
it nah it's just my luck
previously are we voting I I vot I voted
he I
I'm no
no she
[Music]
isn't no no was no longer wanted that's
so
sad it's okay one body gone
hi oh hello
yeah are you Su
no are you sure you're not don't follow
me don't follow
me don't follow me not
you she's following me K is
following
no see I'm
innocent
I I never
trusta only died cuz she was a lover
with me I was killed and waya died with
me so romantic so
romantic no wait that's not true I
murdered you
K yeah yeah you did you did but Rea died
with me because you murdered
me yeah so you guys their lives are
somewhere else and I
died okay let's do something
really
stupid let's
go stupid stupid stupid something stupid
something stupid something Dum
something
what
about what
[Music]
about how about a detective
round I hope I'm what the detective do
detective you can investigate players to
see if they have killed that round maybe
it's too op maybe too op okay never mind
too op too op okay okay I can we we can
go with stalker basically you can track
one
player that's my turn
okay again you scare me
woman I'm ready by
the
[Music]
okay
byebye
no why it's so
difficult it's so
difficult
and
then
suspicious stop I was innocent last
time
Su wait a
minute isn't o Senai a technically a
core
do you
have the thing is I don't really like
um I don't really like
uh see I can't think I don't
think where do I want to go wo so many
people why do you want to follow you go
right I go I go left okay you go left I
go right what see you're the one who
follow
me
uhoh I would like to deduct a few things
okay okay deduct okay D I thinka might
be a stalker so she's not a duck what
okay I'm I'm the stalker Ollie and it's
kind of useless
oh oh call you're
useless useless no no I'm saying the
stalker roll is kind of useless cuz I
like I don't get much from it I feel
like does it like do do you win if you
successfully stalk someone what does it
do Ollie Ollie why are you blaming me
I'm fing you no
no I was trying to call you no I was
trying to like
nice
[Music]
deduction wait everyone is saf only
Senai might be the doo
okay only Senai could possibly be the
dodo she's acting so sus
hello she's probably the dodo this is
not the book you're looking for the art
of
deception
deduction
deduction oh Goose goose Goose
goose damn this match is giving me Goose
bums
hey
h
h you not a
stalker I I can go here she's a lover
[Music]
Goose oh my
God wait wait wait wait wait what wait
what see
is I was was cleaning a picture and
Raina ran past me and I heard her and
then I was ding with I was going in the
same direction Olie was going with me
and we both saw the body kind of at the
same time I was like what the what what
well one thing for sure it's not aelia
inp I was the whole
time you guys are
lovers where was everybody
where were you
huh I was at where were you you tell me
right nowson tell me where you
were I was with
ol yeah she was with me I was with olly
I was with ol no no before that I was
with
her what's
happening oh [\h__\h] no you guys messed up
you messed up big time the D guys messed
up no that is messed up that is messed
up Who's d
opinion with the fish can
[Music]
you yo you are so close you were so
close but you were telling the truth no
Ollie Ollie fny I knew you were the doo
you were so
SS
sorry wait what does doo do again um
needs to be voted out yeah
but ol got the people right though
the yeah she
said yeah but I still wanted to win so I
voted for
myself I see crazy that is so sad I
see and you didn't win I'm so
mad
it's okay so in kind of unnecessary mhm
okay the stalker
roll off useless um yeah this one
instead of so I'm exchanging the lover
duck to um Hitman duck and bodyguard
Goose so the bodygard gets a bonus for
protecting a
player but the Hitman gets a bonus for
killing them I don't know what the bonus
entails though how to the same yeah it's
like a discussion time I feel like the
discussion time is a little bit too
short for sure to be honest okay okay
let's yeah I agree discussion time that
was 30 seconds how about um how about uh
45 yeah okay what from 30 to 45 yeah and
the options are only 30 45
60 60 okay 60 okay let's go 60
[Music]
okay
okay I need to write this down
mhm let's go okay
so let's go instead of mimic I'm using
the detective so detective can
investigate players to see if they have
killed that
round okay okay we can try that one okay
let's go okay H bye-bye bye bye don't
kill
me I swear I swear every
single just don't get killed just don't
get
killed want to
no I knew it I shouldn't have gone alone
I shouldn't have gone
alone wow that's so
fast so fast I jinxed this
I is is is it like automatically
reporting no I report it it was at West
Wing It was at w went to West Wings can
you actually see the map oh you can
actually yeah you can see the map
oh well it wasn't wa to play doo thank
you why do you I was right there so I'm
to it was pretty last time the last time
I saw someone one mhm and The West Wing
is actually
Ru
no no
NOAA and then I
left from
hway you're from
hway is library and then why isai so
good it's a long way why so good
though good L I'm skipping I'm skipping
you're very
quiet kind that is true rain is Prett
quiet when she gets
imposter
is oh she's still she's still
she she's Canadian I actually don't I
don't remember what what do Canadian
people oh sorry Canadian people Canadian
goose do what does Canadian goose do
again uh I'm not supposed to do any
tasks so let's follow Amy around see if
she kills Hitman
right who are you going to kill huh who
are you going to killay for me you
murder
yo wait how do you deal with this
one okay
[Music]
she
like is like I mean it looks like it
looks like double kill double kill
double kill double kill double kill
double kill double kill is an option
what where's the lights do they know
each other like who the other goose who
the other duck is do they know oh no oh
no uhoh everyone's
here I think so they know okay that's
good I imagine if you have to
guess quack that's a whack
[Music]
qu I'm happy I'm is joining though I did
ask her again I was like are you sure
you can join and she's like yeah seems
fun
so
damn I can't play doo bird because every
time I every time I play dodo I get
killed
first they're innocent look look at her
you know rain 75 was like oh how do I do
this how do I press this how n n turns
out she was like busy trying to figure
out the controls of killing and sabotage
I knew
it get away get away no she's going to
kill
me to report that cuz I'm medium I can't
see it I see going
around around where wa
left wait yeah the whole don't no don't
stick it on
me I'm the medium I can see the de
bodies I was about to go back to the
dining room
to a
medium it shows me it shows me uh like a
countdown every once in a while I can
press shift and then I see how many
ghosts there are and for the longest
time it was just one from the last round
and now I just after my task refreshed
and I saw two so I was in the studio
doing the the base or something stream
connection and then that just around the
corner is a dining room where you can
report right so I don't know where the
body is but I went to the dining room to
report you going back and forth that was
with I no no I saw you going back and
forth as well so don't stick it on me
now you you two were together
and if I kill someone
no oh my
God no they going should be killed again
actually I they're going to put
how good did I just explain how the
medium Works
no you get the wrong person it's going
to be bad okay okay I'm not sure oh no
I'm hungry I swear me too I mean yeah
how how did why would you do that why
would
you somebody voted for
R wait she no we everyone is safe for
now okay not
W they're sticking it on me right I
swear they want to like kick me out they
they saw me and they were like oh looks
like someone who we can stick it on oh
no oh no how do you vote actually I'm
not really
sure like cuz I don't know have I been
voting because I tried to vote I wonder
too it doesn't really show so well oh
there's what are they yapping
about what did they yaen about Ella I I
I was like oh my hunt just selling me
it's straining my hun just selling me
it's staining and she did kill
[Applause]
me these ducks are too
clever
Wasing I don't have the heart to lay a
finger me
meing on me it was so it was so funny
seeing all said I ran away from
rain she was like don't kill me S you
didn't say
anything she we out a little bit too
late she was silent like me
and wait you dead I'm sorry
loesing okay uh I think
uh how about we try since it's been an
hour how but we Tred different different
uh mode yes yes yes sure okay we can
try okay what about this hoot and seek
hoot hoot and seek the owl must blend in
with NPC to complete task to win the
game spotters and snipers work together
to identify and kill the owl to win I
don't know how many owls there is though
that's so much
anxiety
what about Goan Goan might be like
better like hide and the tag oh the tag
go okay want to try
Goan yeah okay let's try Goan first can
to ruce the timer or choose to hide oh
okay okay there's a similar mode in um
in uh Among Us everybody runs really
fast can try the other
modes yeah I I think we can try the
goose hun first and then we try a
different one after this okay should be
a quick round let's
go let's
go who's the
killer who's the
killer
oh of course I'm always innocent zitas
zitas
zitas I is more me
time like you a little complic oh they
just
died this is really bad Chad I don't
think I should be around
here I should be doing task right should
I be doing task I think I
should don't
talk interesting it's
not budy
get
CH no not me not me not
me how do I do task no what
task but it says
task
with oh my God I knew it what she did
say what
nice very
nice what is in it very nice very nice
very nice you can still do
tasks okay okay let's do task let's do
task no no no
task I was doing my task who's left how
do I cut I was doing my task wait wait
we can still do the task yeah we can
still do the task we can still do the
Tas do we have to do the task TK like
hard I think so yes yes yes you have to
it's so difficult though no it's
so why is it always
woman oh my God keep getting the G hard
I don't know the task is too much the
task was too muchad the task is too much
the task was too much for this game yeah
okay also I spawned where still spawned
in the beginning so I
[Music]
was what are the odds of spawning with
the killer man we can't adjust the task
it's like set I know it wasn't time K so
the moment Ru immediately came to chase
us I was like oh no don't don't
come Z is like what what is
that me no I wasn't talking
about I thought it was I thought it was
Zeta but then Zeta
died why I did
nothing okay um there's this one called
Trick and
Treat so villagers complete tasks to
call meetings and then fold out the
monster to win so it's like we're wolf
right the monster wins when everyone's
been converted to a throut I don't know
what a throw is like vampire I guess
okay I I okay basically we do task call
meeting vote out the sus
one
okay let's
try ready ready
[Music]
ready so somebody has to be the
monster stop THS to protect yourself
okay okay stop THS to protect yourself
how how complete okay we have to
complete the task
shrubs shrubs shrubs let me let me wash
out the shrubs werewolf game yeah it's
like a werewolf
game
oh Kyla just passed
me oh interesting who is the
monster
what's a throw
hi I don't know I don't know
English me
either how to
English
no the thing is I don't know like if I
say something I'm going to jinx myself
so shouldn't say all is
slave damn just like buzle
then oh ooh meeting time it's oh my God
what the
f I don't know um I was at the studio
restraining Theos I've been
very I haven't seen anyone I haven't
seen anyone but wa wa but she was just
walking around I don't think I saw waa
or Ru anywhere either I'm going to
for
goodbye goodbye what bullied we have to
pull the not me though have an
intervention about
bullying I
know H oh oh so that was right I mean
technically we would win if we voted out
all the
people
huh why
why she's a thr
now okay okay okay okay okay
okay oh okay I see how it is okay
okay
no it was so hard to figure out I didn't
know what I was doing but I guess I
won thank you my little vampire babies
you're welcome mAh was the one who
converted all of them well not all of
them but most of them oh wow that was
weird wait so what can the
do kill the other villagers convert
people the vampires turn into like
zombies so they're kind of like yeah
like
zombies but even when I clicked like the
Turning thingy it didn't happen
immediately it takes a while I guess
until they turn into oh did it happen
immediately for for the others for the
ones for The fals Who converted other
normal people you know what I
mean I don't know let's play let's let's
play one
more
yeah whoever becomes the vampire good
luck just try pushing everything TR
killing
everyone turn
everyone honestly isn't ra isn't o sen
by technically a
zombie I should do me I should do
task
no okay no why it's I newer
again again
okay I I know I know I know 3 two 1 3
two
1 okay so what am I supposed to do as a
thrw do I just kill people I think I
just I think they just saw me they just
saw me I just two people
just
yo what the
[\h__\h] okay I don't think it's I don't
think it's an either yeah I don't think
it's R so it's either Ru or wa I vote wa
I had enough being
voted I understand yes vote
you I'm going to be a bully today inv V
Ru you going to reget
you were talking about spanking
something what that's that's my
job what
what they were spanking while at where I
wasn't
looking oh no I wanted that
one
[Music]
hello hello are you let's look together
mhm we're both
zombies always s
bias in her role you
know
[Music]
y
Survivor see you got to trust me I'm
always Hest I I don't know why it gave
me vampire
again I told
you why do you want to have spicy time I
tried to stop work for some
reason you knew what was going on then
what was it's because I need to fluff
the
pillow oh me too I had to do
that
sure for
blood one more please
okay please please please do do we still
want to do the previous one or new
one new new okay what about this taste
like
chicken social dedu Battle Royale
protect your team's chicken and kill
everyone else what do you mean social
deduction I don't
know I don't duck duck duck duck is this
like
P Battle Royale I think yeah I think
it's like it's like Battle Royale I
think you're supposed to protect
yourself one one man for their
own okay okay protect your chicken ready
up
[Music]
protect ready protect your chicken
protect the chicken the chicken chicken
chicken you're a chicken who's not ready
let's
see everyone's ready everyone's ready
start the game try again try again are
you ready I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready
are you ready wait
maybe here okay I'm ready up
again
ah maybe we need a minimum amount of
people to
start
maybe
maybe we okay we can try the um we can
try this one this one who and seek maybe
okay okay let's try whatever this
is let's go we have to take down L even
though she's not here
yeah I can't start either I wonder why
that's so
weird un ready and then ready maybe we
ready and ready already um yeah me
I just did it I'm ready I also did
um
weird let me try again sorry let me try
again no
problem maybe if the room is restarted
where case I think the only like you can
ready um if it's like classic my button
lit up when it was classic but other
molds I don't think I
can that's it
what do you guys want to
try again so draff is like the like
classic but like you can pick your rules
now okay okay oh that's so nice let's go
let's go let's
go okay let's
go okay so
let's oh you get a gcha is this
important oh you get AA
oh what
what is this oh it's like if you're the
first you get to choose
first okay you need to win a vulture why
would you choose vulture out of all
things I don't know
what I mean I'm I'm picking I'm
picking whatever this is wait but can we
see what the what the duck the goose the
duck also chooses then yeah I think we
can choose we can choose everything like
we can see
everyone's oh
but but I'm not a kill
G living the life of G does it show a
fake one maybe for the maybe it shows a
fake one it doesn't show people's names
or what player they are yeah it doesn't
show like it doesn't show I guess yeah I
guess technically we can just like guess
which one is which yeah who which one
wow a lot of people picking random I
didn't I was sheriff
sheriff damn it I wanted to be
Sheriff then K sherff no
[Music]
no um actually don't know it's just you
know agents what kind I I don't know I
didn't
think let's do
task
apparently you have tasks to do too
interesting isn't
it no oh
here someone
died this is horrible
[Music]
yeah you didn't kill somebody did you no
I
didn't
[Music]
no
hi
[Music]
hi oh I didn't even see a body so I
don't know why it
uh why is it so silent um where where
was the body where's the body I don't
know I didn't see it I think it's
selfreported
I'm the sheriff so I
can't you're
sh What role can self report wait so um
where were
you in I was in the hallway by the
laboratory by the sun okay I think Zeta
Zeta came from above from the hallway
and said hi was it you
Z yeah I think it was
Z the you heard the high
right two people
did West wi no way you came to the
kitchen there's only there's only I was
in The West
Wing I was in
the came you're under arrest no you said
hi to us well one thing for Ser it's not
Ona because I was with her the whole
time yeah I was with all the whole time
so wa wait wait tell me tell me tell
me
hold
to out of the IED
[Music]
myself public
opinion it was your
mistake what did I tell
[Music]
you should have not killed me I actually
don't remember saying
hi I gen don't remember saying
hi you should have not killed me Zeta I
am your
helper you're my
helper didn't you hear a hi didn't you
hear someone saying hi no but I did saw
Zeta I don't remember say oh you didn't
see Zeta I heard hi I mean I said hi to
everybody she was singing But weren't
you dead Ru I was dead Zeta killed me
yeah you were dead yeah I killed my
helper yeah it wasn't you then if you
were dead cuz it was right before the
body was found I heard a
high oh yeah we need that was fun though
Thea was fun yeah that was fun can we do
it again the yeah let's let's do it
let's do it again let's
go let go I wonder to I swear to God
someone said hi Chad you
heard I didn't hear a hi a damn I was so
close to killing she was in front of my
eyes
why would you pick
vulture that's so freaked up who picked
vulture you sick sick
being but does vulture do
again I like this one I
see then you're a party you win then
that's you Z no what's w z
a what
do detective nice what is guy
like Batman
Batman will never
[Music]
know oh
cute
who cares
like the imposters are going to kill me
but then if they know my role they won't
kill me because I'm I'm innocent I'm I'm
the
goose hello
hello hi hi you walking so slow oh um my
mouse
settings why am I oh I can walk faster
I've been walking so
slow hello
[Music]
hello
hello you're not a vulture this
time
no the got taken from me that's sad no
TI tippa
[Music]
CH
okay yeah I'm going to serve
dinner
okay okay how do I oh I go to the dining
room instead
of huh
H together oh
hello
hello H was together I saw you guys I
don't I don't want to
know
hello oh it's not this
way
now hold little together you have
a for me
for okay okay
okay it's
waiting where's
KY K was going to the Opera I think
she's doing task she must be doing task
are you doing task didn't want to hump
together on the
pillow
no
huh SAU too sa too Saucy it's like
down I don't
know
what do I
do tasking tasking tasking
[Music]
tasking this is
hopeless it is so
hopeless
oh no fire fire fire let's get
fire fire fire
fire I'm not yet fire fire let's get
fire
fire do we all have to do
it where how do you get there wait there
was a wait how do I how do I use the map
again this
one do I how do I click on the map
unlock how do I
hello okay it's
distinguished yeah she did oh hopefully
not
H where's
Ana okay eat food foodo food
foodo are you guys done with your task
not yet not yet have to do
bath test the chest the chest I
mean I'm glad none of us
died
[Music]
you are
not
hello hi
hi potato
salad turn on stuff stuff
matches bath bath bath bath bath
bathroom
no h
[Applause]
yeah what the [\h__\h] you were a
[Laughter]
vult she was following you just in case
you
died yeah I was hoping I was hoping
either of you guys will get
it
D it was hard cuz everyone was together
the whole
time yeah I I think having only one
imposter is hard it's so difficult so
diffe when people just to be like y
together need to be
too I'm not making it better
though I'm going to only accompany me of
you
yeah okay I actually you know what's
crazy I actually didn't know that party
was an imposter I thought party was just
like uh like the goose just like just
like a yeah just like a useless role I
was like it's it only says something
like you can give someone high pitch
sound during meetings I was like sounds
cool
what so you can get high pitch voice but
also kill yeah I mean we can also
kill so I guess it would be hard for
villagers to like discuss with each
other about
sound it was difficult basically my RO
is like if I'm not alone if I have like
at least I guess if I have at least two
people with me I can't get killed so
that's why I keep asking people to
accompany me
a for someone to get eaten H was
together the whole time it was so
difficult okay okay I think we could
possibly end it here maybe
yeah I want to play again
sometime yeah let's play again play
again sometimes yeah this is so fun
thank you for making the time to play
[Music]
together thank you for inviting
it was fun it was a lot of
fun thank
you okay so excited to see all of you in
Japan soon for
[Music]
FES
y then we can party yeah we can do party
for party hard Party
hard take care of everybody take care
everybody
[Music]
byebye
[Applause]
[Music]
bye