[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
one second
oh
[Music]
wow
what do i hear my voice is too loud
what what
hello
oh wow that might been really too loud
kick
don't you find it weird that's um i'm so
loud
don't you find it weird
don't don't you find it interesting
no you're used to hey i'm usually always
quiet you always complain i'm too quiet
starting off today i'm using a cloud
lifter
and it's amazing because like before i
was like speaking into the microphone i
was almost eating the microphone
and still you often told me i'm too
quiet or at least when i would collab
with someone
um yeah i i would always be overpowered
and the cloud lifter like i have a sure
sm7b
as a microphone that i recently bought
because everyone
in the beginning told me my microphone
is [\h__\h]
so i bought a good microphone okay
but then the microphone alone was not
good enough because it was apparently
too quiet
so now i finally bought the cloud lifter
expensive little thing it's it's pretty
small but it's pretty expensive
uh and now i don't have to eat the
microphone anymore like i'm
i'm at a comfortable space away from the
microphone
so like um my face also doesn't get
covered up by the microphone anymore
like like you hear me perfectly fine
right and i don't even have the gain to
the maximum
so that's awesome uh yeah
awesome thank you i'm loud or real
louder maybe even too loud because if i
go too loud
um i see it goes into the red red area
so maybe i should turn it down even i
don't know we'll probably scream a
little bit
in today's game and one more motion
one more even bigger news than the cloud
lifter even though i'm really happy
about the cloud lifter
i'm really happy about the cloud lifter
but starting from today
i finally am
in my new house again with my new
internet
yay for the people who don't know
i moved uh one month ago
or three weeks ago i moved three weeks
ago
but stupid internet provider decided to
say
[\h__\h] yourself to me and excuse moi
kiana language uh and they were like ah
we're gonna like it was already like uh
internet was gonna come late already
but they moved it even further to three
weeks
after my moving date so i would not have
internet
until three weeks later yeah
but finally today uh i can stream from
my own house again
again i never was able to stream from my
own house but yeah
finally oh my god so finally
i'm in in my uh my house
with with a cloud lifter and
everything's cool
so so so so
would they see
it's not necessarily a new mic but yeah
i mean the microphone is still pretty
new woohoo
i'm happy but i have to say i'm a bit um
a bit scared i don't feel very
comfortable in my house yet and uh
it feels so it feels too big
and there's ghosts there's ghosts in the
form
of mice
[Laughter]
there's my mouse ghosts and um
i'm also trying to uh do something
against those
a week ago um i had
to go my mouse ghostbusters come into my
house it's a really old house
really really old house you know
and i kept hearing them like running
around in the ceiling
it was like killing me i don't know i
find mice cute but when you have them
like in your house
i didn't see them but it only hurt them
the whole time and they were going crazy
so i had the ghostbusters come over
they're coming again tomorrow and then
they're coming again
another week later and hopefully my
house will be ghost
free uh soon
yeah it's a bit uh terrifying
but it makes a it makes it halloweenish
because it's
spooktober right so it's uh perfect
anyway let's play among us
here's my code come in rule number one
and don't watch the stream what wait how
the [\h__\h] did you
how what
what
huh
rule number one don't
don't watch the stream
rule number two be fair okay
don't vote me out for no reason
rule number three leave the room
after one round
or i will fire you
let's play fair okay i wanna i wanna
have fun today okay
uh okay i believe in you guys i know you
guys can follow rules if you want to in
in the in the moments where it's
important by the way what is that that
button can i kick out someone
okay okay i will kick you all uh
everyone remember these names or take a
screenshot if they don't leave next
round
let me know okay let me know
someone take a screenshot let me know if
they don't leave next
next round thank you okay
okay among us do do you guys want to
turn on bgm or do you think it's better
without bgm
what do you think
uh oh god i think i forgot to turn on
the slow mode
it's like bgm please no bgm oh my god
no bdm i guess no bgm is fine i like the
the thumb sounds i like them you hear
those right are they
too quiet don't don't don't don't maybe
they could be a bit louder
because we have no bdm so
let's go
ah this is the first time i'm having my
own server so i guess i'll just click
start
the game is quiet yeah there's no audio
like i mean i guess we let's turn a
little bit on
i mean it's just a space sound sounds
very spacey
okay oh by the way i i haven't even
stress tested the internet yet i also
didn't even do a speed test so i don't
know how fast the internet actually is
uh i'm sorry if it if it like i don't
know if the stream cuts out
at some point but we have to we're we're
testing it ah okay well i mean that's
something else
oh no i'm so sorry to everyone who
no i'm so sorry i'm so sorry to everyone
who joined oh well good luck
good luck joining again there you go
let's see how fast they join let's see
oh
is it the same people screenshot
you know the rules and so do
i
uh wait okay wait wait okay screenshot
everyone
you know you know we're kicking these
people out okay
if they don't uh leave next round
okay let's go starting in five four
three two one by the way i was never an
imposter before in the in the collab i
was never
impossible for and again i'm a crewmate
well well well well also i never played
in a different
uh loop
round than this oh okay let's do my
tasks
by the way what was the what was the key
for tasks and please
please don't kill me for no reason okay
just because you hate me oh wait where
do i go
also don't watch the stream okay
am i going the right way because
everyone went upwards
maybe maybe there's one here i know i
should probably oh they're so fast
well at least i don't have to take too
much care about this
play with the keyboard eh
i'm yeah i'm playing with the mouse it
makes it a bit slow
pink goes to pink
yellow goes to yellow red to red and
blue
to blue thank you for the super chat
don't kill me
as i've watched a bunch of uh pokas
manga streams she's been enjoying it
very much i see
and her english has been improving too
maybe my english will improve as well if
i play
a manga
yoshi download those loot files
downloading cali loops loops loots
loots again that's it
but those things are activated by the
imposter right
then they're doing a good job oh so
you guys are good at this game
you're like taking care of that so fast
man if i'm going to be an imposter it's
going to be chaotic
i hope you guys are not watching the
stream
uh one more one more one up here
one more beer this reminds me um
there was a game that i that i played
sometimes
when i had like actual friends that i
could actually meet in real life called
werewolf is it called the same thing in
english
it's like similar right um but like uh
what is this do happen
dead body okay who's dead
brussifa and askaray where to go
they're gonna have the newest question i
didn't have to say anything it was at
camps oh
hello reported those boys okay every
part of seeing those boys
uh no idea man
too busy streaming
wow yeah just discuss with yourselves i
can't really help but you guys know i'm
the good one
i was in the electric cali cali
jelly oh
who vouches for meadow
someone vouched for me
oh kiana safe oh
i saw it kiana and copy yeah we're
waiting for cali
thanks dude
[Laughter]
food came in what what do you mean you
don't have what
priority is my rifle i okay joke okay
[Laughter]
yeah i don't know blues blue sauce white
blue white blue doesn't even have a name
blue says has no name
[Laughter]
okay let's give him one more chance
okay okay okay eh my wife will vote it i
i say skip photo skip bullet i take it
away from from podcast
stream skip on the skip bottle
add some more what do you mean add some
more add some what
two common one long what
speak english with me
you mean more imposters
[Music]
i'm more tasked with how do i do can i
do that
during the game i don't think so
i'll do it next time uh when setting up
the game i guess
okay uh i'll have to do this one
yes
wait what what happens if i miss them
i'm not so good with these kind of games
that was bad
that was fast um
wait brown reported that
okay green walking away from body
aha
defend yourself my friend
speak speak [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
um
[Music]
doesn't sound like a real chicken sounds
like a fake chicken
fake chicken alert
us both great
actually i have no idea how many people
um
one more skateboarder one more
skateboarder
yes i'm not sure i have no idea until
someone can actually
like say something but keep the green
one
in in your eyes okay don't don't let
them out of your
eyes petra by the way petra
did you name yourself petra on purpose
because i love petra
yo blue what up
i can't add them now i think
i will later when game is
over two short one long and four
comments in
well didn't we all vote now okay
and no one was voted ouch
two impulse oh i didn't turn that out oh
god that my two impostors are still here
helper and once again
we play the shooting game
oh jessica thank god okay next
is um navigation i need a bodyguard my
friends someone bodyguard me
complete and they're complaining about
pasta i'm also done i guess
okay stay with me you seem like a
actually
yeah he doesn't kill me let's start with
blade
but let's explore you stay with me
though you still the key for me to not
die
blue dad blew that
tell me more tell me
more did you get really far
tell me more tell me more like does
he have a car
what ignore me
boomer quote
okay let's be serious okay i'm the one
who's probably the least serious
but okay
wait what did they write green walking
like okay okay i'll go
get baba queen
very um
i forgot sometimes i forget english
words that i definitely know
i definitely know what you put talking
about
um convincing wow there's german people
in my chat
nice one the short long and commons are
the tests
yeah i'll think on i know i can't i
can't do anything about it now
anyway read this part number mess up
like a double kill
what
confirm ejects make it more
investigative
me is done took a while
because i am stupid shooter
blade is safe by the way
he my body guide
one speed what speed is that you mean
like for a conversation
oh confirm it jacksonville if you want
to make it more okay
guys remember that when i do the
settings again please let me know
a move speed oh okay move speed okay
wait are you listening to the stream i
hope you're not listening to the stream
you better not be listening to the
stream
okay let's go
he wasn't in foster pasta pasta
spaghetti
i have no tests we all have no time okay
so wait
how many people left how many with
four here who where are the others
where are the others five are left
so wait one one person just ran away
huh
well that's pretty obvious now isn't it
is it pretty obvious that it's red
we got you my friend you left us all
there why would you oh
oh petra oh petra better i know it's you
i know i know oh that
well that's i mean that's obvious
[Laughter]
thanks petra though it was fun
having you here
you turned me down
you were straight yeah
for people who don't understand it's
about the fire and blam stream
bye bye
my bedroom
come on vote what
there is no no you isn't finding it
hey blade without buttons you need to
like keeps on
keeps on telling me what to do stop
telling me what to do
what movement speed 125 okay
imposter kill rate is too short okay if
i remember all that
kill cd2 what does that even mean 27.5
too short one long for common tests
right yeah but you better be watching
when you're not in the round
thank you you think i can remember
all of these things you'll think i can
remember that
now vote vote
okay he's faking
it's a she it's petra it's a girl
and i ate lasagna today
okay let's see if we can do some
everyone leave by the way
oh wow how oh there's already new people
aren't they all new
they don't look new to me no wait why is
it starting no wait no no no no no why
is it starting why is it starting
wait wait wait let me change things no
grandpa left again wait wait wait wait
wait leave game
how do i do it maybe i have to go in
where do i do the settings
okay let's go here it's new code sorry
friends
how do i do it i don't see the settings
how do i
chat confirm eject yes no
no so what away with that ah i mean that
text out that's the text okay okay
emergency meetings one or more
what does what does it even mean why is
it why can isn't it always when someone
reports
anyway emergency cooldown 15 seconds or
more
uh 20 seconds oops
okay discussion time 15 seconds it was
much more than that it was much more
than 15 seconds
ah that's the voting time i think the
voting time was a bit too long
90 seconds maybe maybe even 60 seconds
nah
60 or maybe 75
9 19 okay
player speed faster speed
sorry um cremate vision what is that
impossible they didn't say anything
about that so probably that's fine
visual
common tests okay two long tests one i
think and sure right no common text
maybe seven
what did they what was it short tasks
how many short tasks
wait uh oh my god visual off
visual tasks off okay
uh what was that anyway two one five
okay
gotcha is it fine now
seems fine
two or nine two and nine two one four
i'm sorry
four okay
okay don't watch stream
let's go what was that
what was that
what why am i censored
what a kicker kicker what is what is why
is that censored anyway
anyway let's go
my friends oh i think no one
no one old is in the grip now let's see
what could it be
in pasta
oh again the crewmates
oh
okay well we are faster okay let's go
down
i don't i should probably not be alone
but
but who dares to kill your boss
so early on who who dares it wouldn't be
fun
okay being a ghost is not so much fun
too
wait there's one more here the card one
card swipey swipe
what
yellow reported okay in storage
huh pink also saw it
oh they went um
i'm swiping cards
wasn't me i was alone but it wasn't me
wait so both both pink and yellow
saw zion dead maybe they're both
imposters
don't you think
i would agree with that
wait green pink red and me is clear
isn't that very suspicious
why this is because they were alone what
about me i was also alone
i was alone
no no
no no i'm just being honest
i am obsessed but it's not me
i am just uh oh my god
skip on it skip skip
skip skip order i hope no one voted no
popcorn popcorn how
you dare you dare to vote me out huh
you dare to try to vote me out
now it's okay we're trying to be a fair
oh there's a light needs to be fixed how
do i get there
quick is it here no
i i don't remember how to get there
quickly it's already fixed okay
now swipe some cards i'm so slow man
hello popcorn don't it's purple
it's purple it's purple
first try peculiar senpai first try
oh
don't kill me where do i go
um here
single swipe yeah i got the the swiping
skills
although i don't even own the credit
card which i always ask myself why
haven't i made a credit card until now i
like it could have been very useful in
many many times like there's so many
times where i can't buy something
because i don't have a credit card oh
pain pickle
purple keeps on following me but doesn't
kill me so he might be he might be
he might be safe he might be fine but
he's following me
he's following me don't kill me
i'll send the loots before you kill me
at least let me send the loots
let me set the loot first those are
precious materials that need to be
delivered and seen by the world
okay
[Music]
i'm a bit slow with my tasks
i'm coming wait where is it oh it's
there
is it there oh okay whatever
they'll take care of it okay so purple
saw cyan okay purple seems
safe now
i don't think purple is it anymore
um
[\h__\h] push it
hey hey hey hey hey why are you trying
to
i was you were following me the whole
time if it was me i would have killed
you what the [\h__\h] is that man
i should do a swear jar
huh
i just don't know where what
is
yeah cameras i don't know man
cameron's i don't understand those
no no no no no no no no no no no not me
yeah i don't know man skip about it
skip order
i don't know do you guys know nobody has
a real idea so
why those imparties are good you guys
must be playing like
actually now last round last round we
found it that we found them quite easily
why do we always start up here it's such
a long way to go anywhere let's go to
the left side
but i'm i'm happy that i'm at least not
being right away ejected or right away
killed so thank you guys for being fair
players
thank you guys
next reactor
oh fix lights still wait
someone else will do that right one two
three four
what's up what's up now what
that was not a body right what's up
huh
we need we need to vote what what why
why why why why why
so okay
but you were already in camps too oh
some oh he's watching the cameras
well who do you think it is huh
but
hey i have no idea because i'm like so i
always alone
i haven't seen anyone
[Music]
maybe green i think
he's not even talking
i don't know he's not not talking
he's just not talking
uh
green team saint says the white one
who's also suspicious
oh god
okay everyone seemed to agree it was
pink even pink themselves
[Music]
why did pink vote for himself
oh bye-bye they admitted it
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh well i'm just gonna continue doing my
job
because i'm a mom
don't kill me i mean i mean i guess you
can
if you if that's what you got
ah help me help me help me
panic panic panic panic
[Applause]
and claustrophobic bye-bye
this is the first time that i got stuck
somewhere actually didn't even happen
during the collab
okay one two three
six
no no
[Music]
wait who was just following me who was
just following me the whole time
who was that because that person might
be oh my gosh only three left
what what the [\h__\h]
probably it's too impossible me
eh boy i am just
slow with numbers you rude
not i was picking the numbers
right
help her win another how would that help
me
what why would that help me are you two
impostors
my actions
[Music]
what
but that did not let me win aren't you
trying to let me win
what blue in the end it was green and
blue left god damn it i should have
fought it for blue
god damn it ah gg i guess
okay did everyone leave and they seem
seems like new names 299k
hello hello
eh but i don't understand why did they
vote me out
did they legit think i was an imposter
did they but that would not have made me
win
i don't get it they
wait but green thought i was the
imposter i guess but
voting me out i don't understand
and i didn't even stop i really did you
saw it i didn't stall it all
i didn't stall though you saw it didn't
you
are they he tricked a blue tricked green
i didn't ignore the light i don't know i
just went to the the one that i
i could go to i don't know i don't know
where they all are
i understand someone has to explain this
game round to me afterwards
let's start i don't get it man
don't watch stream
you better not be watching the stream
ah goddammit got them
[Music]
also what's the button for opening i
think it's uh tap no what's the button
for
what's the button for the map
download some loots oh yeah it's on asia
the
server is on asia um
okay a tab but tab didn't work
it's not working for me m is also not
working
weird fast
quick wow so quick
speed speed speed speed
uh red was standing on body wow
well what were you doing with they died
right
uh-huh well right behind you then who
didn't
if you didn't do it then
who did it
yes i was in cafe
but actually seems legit red because
they say they died right where where
where they were where we left the back
um actually right is quite sus
pretty sauce yeah
pretty sus man
he's a fast killer i don't know if we
should let him
weep
[Laughter]
we were late
[Music]
what are you voting skateboarder i guess
skateboarder okay
okay i guess we can skip for you
bye bye blue faster blue
blue blue faster okay
but i gotta i don't want to get too
close to red now rant kind of
seems very serious if red kills me now
then i'm gonna
fire him straight away you're not even
getting your
uh this month's salary you're gonna be
straight
please someone stay with me someone
stayed with me
gonna be straight uh fired
salary oh yeah there isn't there is no
salary to begin with
at kfp your salary salary goes
straight to me
thank you very much for your earnings
well first strike high swine did you
think that
i could do it that well okay where do we
go wait and
what
what wait
i don't understand huh
ah okay okay okay
i don't understand
yeah he died did he report again
i don't understand though
who is dead now who's the phoenix now
this eh what do you mean it's my stream
dad oh
oh oh i don't know why that happened so
weird
i'm not even connected to anyone
not that
i thought my stream disconnected i was
shook for a moment
thanks for the super chat yep
okay i guess hey but wait is the blue
say why he
last vote i was back it's bug what
okay are they yeah it's eh what
i don't understand but okay skipper
it's a bug they didn't report okay let's
move on
okay skip baloo i got that from polygamy
by the way it sounds so cute she's also
like
uh like she's um
taking so many like uh english slang
words like
slang i guess it's internet internet
slang like she took elle mao
laughing my ass off and made it into
paul mao
like her name with lmao
and then skip is skip for you what else
did she do
what else did you make uh
i think there was at least one more
she's like really like picking up these
words we should teach her about the
words
we should teach her the good words
what's a good word
what's a good english word
i'm scared where do i go when do i go
i have two up there i barely go to the
left side because it takes me so long
to like open the map and go somewhere
one don't kill me don't kill me
don't kill me why this is looking at me
why this white and red
white and black is looking they're
they're trying to see how much time i
need for that chin
where do i go where is it
wait was it there i don't get it
sorry i'm a bit tall i was still bad at
this game apparently
oh yeah
why they white was
watching me
but i'm always doing something
i'm always doing something
i am just slow no
no no no no no no no
why no no i'm just slow watch my stream
hey why why you do this to me aren't you
the kfp man
don't you know me better
he wants me out so bad that he called an
emergency meeting just because i was
standing there for a little while
hello hello
what up blue what up blue
still not vote oh eh
blue he was bugged
it's okay blue you can do it can you
type
should i vote should i kick him out
maybe ah did he just vote or did it is
the time over
fighter blue he's being sabotaged oh
he's gone
what okay white is like watching me
don't i'm not it's not me it's you
oh where is that reactor meltdown where
is that i'm see i'm running there i'm
trying to get there i'm running there
i'm running there i'm i'm there i'm
there i'm there okay i'm having green
i'm helping green yes i'm touching you
see i'm i'm just i'm i'm just uh
i'm just a big big girl
why emergency meeting what's up man
hello
hello yeah okay okay what do you got to
say sorry guys
ah
maybe yeah
and what should we do should we kick him
out
okay sorry bro i'm gonna
vlog you out
but don't be sad
i love you
sorry it's just so that we move on with
the game you know
it seems to be a bit slow a slow round
damn the time goes by so fast too
things blew out of oh you're definitely
a taco
a taco friend
with those bad really bad puns
yeah is that ina
is that enoch oh yeah let's see
we have to um sorry blue
okay bye bye blue maybe he was the
imposter
maybe he was but he seemed like a good
guy
he seemed like a good guy but he was
bugged
it wasn't his fault okay let's go to
uh oh two
let's go green queen what's up
i'm scared i'm gonna be like they're
gonna think it's me again even though
i'm just
taking my time just give me some time
i'm slow
uh but i understand that i'm i i can be
suspicious because like
in the in the collab i was also the
suspicious one
like i mean i was suspicious because i
was slow and i was alone but no one
suspected me interestingly enough
now these guys are a bit smarter
by suspecting me but but again it's not
me believe me
huh oh
i'm coming where is it
i'm coming i'm gonna save the world i'm
gonna say it oh it's not here
save the spaceships
i just don't know my way i'm just gonna
follow the others
oh wait one's down there uh how do we
get there
purple sauce oh it's over well ran seems
fine
he did it
oh okay
sayan reported body was in navigation
in the policy ooh nice scene the pilot
is dead
yeah where the pilot is dead how are we
gonna move
damn damn good job
oh green is covering me thanks mate
thanks mate thank you
a good man a very good man
yeah i don't know let's see
who who is suspicious
[Music]
purple sauce oh
there's no way they could have killed
white why
why who did the oxygen again
where did the oxygen i think
hey
i don't even know how to kill i was
never the imposter i don't even know how
to do it
don't vote on seven hmm
skip photo
skip skip skip skip skip skip
okay seems that i was safer because i
honestly still have no idea but red
voted for black interesting
interesting
no one was ejected slow game indeed
well we're gonna get there soon what are
my tasks electrical
oh don't kill me oh he's coming to kill
me don't kill me
no okay i'm being protected i'm being
protected everything's cool
hey i'm doing more tasks i hope that
maybe in the next game i can finally be
the imposter to show you my skills
my wait it's not here uh
it's over there they definitely think
i'm suspicious if i move like that
[Music]
ah
how did red come from left red says
oh see i don't even notice these things
i don't even notice that and my tasks
are done okay stay safe kiara
stay safe maybe we'll find the body
let's find the body
nobody nobody
i left the game uh wasn't that the blue
one
okay bye bye you should be helping with
the taste though
wait red is dead
this is cooked what do you mean it's
cooked is it pasta
i am done with my tasks
now too but why do we even say that
anyone can say that
black cyan
doesn't matter if you don't want y
purple even the chat okay science says
my chance says so-so
i guess my chat says yep but he reported
sorry sorry
i i don't know i don't i have no idea
i've not i voted science
fine
[Music]
he voted for me didn't he oh no he voted
for himself interesting why don't i do
that
because because he likes me so much he
wouldn't vote for me
even even if it was me
bye bye okay tasks no tasks okay let's
stay with green
and purple we stay together okay let's
just stay together
never trust chad
wait where is it bottom left teach me
where it is
show me the way why is green staying up
there
why the [\h__\h] is green staying up there
but i
i think i did do it once with green
together oh
um excuse me green
wait that's a different green wait which
green was it god damn it
one question why did
green run away instead of going
to the emergency
isn't that a legit question
what
what uh not you
other queen i think
tell me
eh you were running
with us and then ran away while we
ran towards the emergency
get it i'm going to save wait was it
lime was it lime or was it normal green
white which green was it
it was lime okay it it was lime
maybe
it was you
last second i got you i got you lyin
i'm watching you i'm watching you
but one of the greens is in the room
right now it
or not anymore [\h__\h]
come sabotage wait where is that what
where where is that what all going there
so
victory how hey the greens are
the greens were fine what it was
tasquen what do you mean task friend
that's possible
but wasn't that often the case that all
tasks were done
ah just because i was done with the
tasks
doesn't mean that everyone else was done
with the test but even often i had uh
like
all people say oh i'm done with my tasks
i don't know anyway let's see who is in
the group now
uh i think they're all new again
oh my god what's what what but we're
still uh there should still be more
there's three people missing where are
you guys hello
hello eat
welcome welcome toilet paper guy
toilet paper roll and green skin
interesting egg not green
brown can't see colors
uh two more two more new room
says it's full ah
pause stream what do you mean okay okay
but
people can't seem to come in anymore
but we are missing too
ah
kiara should also not look at the chat
well hey but but
i don't i need your advice i
short game in front okay okay let's go
let's go
let's do a short game so fast one
imposters
your turn be quick oh god if it's me
it's not going to be quick
is it me is it me is it me no why
why why why why why
how is this even possible
i'm telling you i played this game many
times now
we had two hours practice with the girls
before before the
actual stream and then we streamed i'm
just going to ignore that thing down
there man if someone's going to do it
right
um is no one's going to do it um
okay there we go then during the stream
i also never got imposter
and then now i also don't get impostor
wait a second where am i going some
up there okay
yeah that's like it unfair
i wanna be the imposter by the way guys
let me tell you something wait isn't
this game i
i saw the release date was um uh
2018 but why is it being so popular now
oh what is this one and what ah i think
i know okay
because of streamers oh okay okay
okay i see but i want to tell you guys
um
uh self-report
simon electrical just came in
i'm also an electrical no
purple sauce white pepper
thank you yes i'm safe i'm always safe
thank you kiara for what
um
what okay so
i just came in that was pretty sucks for
me not gonna lie i just came in
i just went out and yelled died no rip
rip yellow bye bye yellow
eh we're on top of the road
yeah and the lights went out i didn't
even notice
i was just focused on my tasks
me
why was everyone in the same room though
very interesting good that i didn't die
is that doesn't mean that the yellow one
died in my room
bye bye so by the way what i wanted to
tell you so recently this game got super
popular right and everyone is talking
about it but
i didn't know about the game yet and um
someone was like sending me on
man several people were sending me like
references on twitter
and telling me like like i don't know
if they would show me like a picture of
these uh of these like crew mates and
imposters you know how they usually line
up together
do i even have a task no
and i was in there and it's like uh
it was something like there's an
imposter among us
and i didn't understand the game and i
didn't even
really realize that the game exists so i
thought it was like haters
saying that i don't belong in holy yes
because it was like the other girls i
think
and me and and somehow
i don't know i thought they were like
trying to say that i don't they want me
out of holo yen and i was like
what is this and i sent it to one of our
staff and i was like
are they trying to say i don't belong in
halloween
and he was like no no no this is just
some weird
game thing
[Laughter]
i knew the brown
brown toilet dude was
suspicious from the moment he
joined the server
[Laughter]
the boss is dead how could you they were
like oh let's do a quick game i just
i guess that's how they meant to kill
the boss
[Laughter]
i would never uh i saw you oh purple saw
it
purple was close if purple was around
there
oh he must have seen it because
otherwise how would he say it
like right away she's my favorite
picture
uh-huh really if i'm your favorite
youtuber
then what do i say at the end of my
streams
huh huh
sounds exciting
vote him out he killed me he killed the
bus
how can i run my business if i'm bad
how can i run my business i need to pay
my employees just kidding i'm gonna pay
you never gonna pay you
bye bye wow
well done well done well done
oh victory nice that wasn't that fast
okay i'm making a new room or is it full
now
oh it's full um they all seem new hey
you guys are actually following the
rules
like actually no one tried to stay in
the room
hey guys
i am not
turn off of uh the stream
okay good job welcome to the welcome to
the game
this uh might be oh no we'll let's do
until half past
nine let's do until half past nine so
maybe this is
maybe two more games stream up okay are
you
you promise you promise you promise
let's go i'm on mobile you can play this
game on mobile
oh 20k viewers hello hello
thank you for coming did someone leave
two people left again
yeah we're eight again oi
two people left that's a bit sad but
okay
and again i am not the imposter
we're in buck yeah maybe i should reopen
the room
yeah i don't know man start new game no
no
they made it like how much luck do you
have to have to get into
one of these rooms with me i i would
feel so sorry and so sad if they
like you know
if they would get kicked out without
getting to play with me i would feel so
so
sad and sorry but next time i'll next
next one
girl uh guys don't don't even try to
join because i'll make in your room for
the last round
just in case it's really blocked i don't
know yellow is following me
i don't think yellow has
yellow is a symph that's why he's
following me
okay what uh wait it's not
one two three four now it's ten
ah ah because they're showing us dead
because uh okay okay okay
because they left the the game okay but
who actually died
yeah too disconnected one died who
actually died
[Music]
um wait who reported right okay white
say something
it wasn't admin i didn't see anyone okay
um
is there any suspicions
am i being too fast with my suggestions
yellow was with me stimping
a good man a very good man
we didn't see anyone i only
saw a simple
a good simp a loyal simple
yeah he's he's called killer f fps that
okay skipping but he might be a killer
it's probably it's probably blue
probably it's blue
i don't know why i don't have any logic
behind that but it's probably blue
no one was ejected oh
well but he looks he looks like an
imposter
okay yellow stays with me let's go where
do we go ah let's go that way
come with me sam protect me
uh leave this is where they were like
watching me and we're like oh she's so
slow she must be an imposter
excuse me how was i supposed to do that
faster excuse me
oh navigation one task
oh oh that's more important right do we
go up or down
where do i go sam where do i go
how do i go there you should lead me the
way oh it's over okay
oh let's go admin
yellow was just doing his tasks casually
damn he's a good man
he's a good man i trust him with my life
and i have to go back
up there to do a task simply stamping
green is following me too now he's also
simple
what what who
brown reported the death of uh gr
who green i don't know storage
interesting very interesting i must say
mr brown
who did i say was suspicious before oh
killer
he's dead ah
i thought he was the imposter
interesting
bottom left er
lime yellow and
me seem like good good
sims unless green
lime just wants me to think that in
reality he's an impossible but he's
trying to gain my trust right now
me and the sim what about me boy what
about me
like yeah maybe maybe lime is um
[Music]
maybe he's just trying to gain my trust
and
yeah he joined us recently maybe he was
trying to kill me at some point
but he was just waiting for the right
moment
hmm why did it come from starts before
reactor but i don't know how long the
body was there
what do i do
that was a panic decision i'm sorry
white i'm sorry
should have been should have been lying
they're gonna
they're gonna try to kill me now i'm
sorry i'm sorry
okay let's go to the navigation
i'm not i'm sorry okay that was fast
which is right there at
eight five six eight five okay
sip keeps on following me keep some [\h__\h]
that was quick that was a quick reaction
what is this
there's still tasks that i haven't done
before interesting
oh i'm sorry right i'm sorry i'm sorry
right don't kill me don't kill me don't
kill me
i'm a good girl
uh yep
what we were we're stuck
we're stuck simp you and me don't leave
me alone with a symptom
that's kind of scary don't don't
quit
why the feet why the feet eh but why the
feet
i'm still alive wait i don't understand
what
outnumbered
no but does that mean that they both
at the same time just killed somebody
because otherwise if they just killed
one body
then we wouldn't have been outnumbered
yet
yeah double kill right
holy [\h__\h] they all just went into the
room and were like mess soccer time or
something holy [\h__\h]
new room sorry guys sorry sorry sorry
making new room sorry sorry sorry um
there we go let's see how fast they come
one two how how how
how how can you be so fast how is that
pain pickle
judas judas is that judas from from the
chat
damn okay two people still missing
can two people still join in
is the room bugged again i wonder
roomful they say
hmm
i guess okay
i'm sorry we can do this more often guys
we can do this more often i'm enjoying
it and i'm
still probably still this round i'm
still gonna not gonna be an imposter
um so there will be more times there
will be more chances
i heard any servers are sus
but maybe next time we can try the na
series thank you for the
for the super chat thank you thank you
scala chicken lives
oh pogo is very interesting
oh well last round
here we go are you ready
let's go let's go
let's go my friends can i be the pastor
the last round
i don't know how to do it me and egg
okay how do i do it how do i do it how
do i do it how do i do it
what if i just kill them like how do i
how do i do it how do i do it okay let's
let's act as if i'm doing
that fake time fake joint okay i'm like
just going in here
someone here now okay all right wait we
can sabotage right okay so i'm standing
uh
where the task should be here so oh no i
didn't no no i didn't want to do that
you didn't see that did you
sorry what hello
you didn't see anything if
your job and your family is important
to you you know what to do
okay huh
no no you did not walk in on kiana
murdering no no
no come on this is the first time this
is the first time on the
imposter i need to learn how this game
works okay give me some
give me one game where you can carry me
come on come on come on
come on green votes
[Music]
i was not rejected
don't run away don't run away
[Applause]
stop running
oh my egg is fun do this
oh i have a cool down goddammit wait you
guys wait here judas wait
judas did you just vote for me and wrote
me out
did you just vote me
i don't i don't know what you're talking
about i'm just protecting you
[Music]
let's butt
orangey sauce orange is not
don't you want to spend more time with
[Laughter]
me
sorry i'm sorry everyone this round is
not fair but
how i cannot help it it's my first round
as an imposter i want to learn how it
works i i can't even kill them properly
so
okay how to lie one-on-one
next time i'm gonna try to be a serious
imposter okay if i ever
if i
con confirmed
who is confirmed
what what do you mean
come on wait who i didn't see it
no i was not the imposter
oh i can still sabotage how do i do that
close close
does that even make sense does that
does that make any sense
what what
for safety
the last imposter
i don't know what you're talking about
guys
yeah you totally got the kiana vote
wrong there's
two impostors still among you
blue and i are considered safe we trust
is that it
you can't trust no one in this game only
me
you can only trust me trust me
bring me back to love
oh why are they making out stop making
out
sensitive
i know
well what is this meeting
egg has voted cool probably to skip yeah
well good luck egg i believe in you egg
i will fight for you
okay so i guess i should not close all
the doors because they'll they will just
call an emergency meeting if i close all
the doors
[Music]
but i want to click all the buttons
bye bye
let's take some time
okay what happens if i do that
did someone chat with me task boys oh
yeah oh yeah i don't have to do a test
that that's nice
to not have to do anything as a ghost
hello chicken
oh they they be running like little
chickens running over here
okay next one um oh no
oh we we can't do it right and i'll just
close a few rooms here
what exactly am i supposed to do besides
sabotaging to sabotage it
let's follow egg let's see if he's doing
a good job as
my second imposter oh he's just
following everyone trying to not look
suspicious very well very well oh
oh oh he will probably kill red now or
not
oh oh oh but did i just click that
i just it how did that happen
oh nice good job good job and he
disappeared
nice he's good he's good
that was that was clean he disappeared
before the other guy joined the uh the
room
good kill
[Laughter]
better than me only
a little bit
let's see if they can figure it out
i don't exit
anything
egg is having a hard time okay he lost
his impost
second imposter pretty quickly but
he's a good he's a good man okay he's
trying his best just
just help like help him out there a
little bit okay
someone rented from mad bay to
electrical no it's the other way around
my friend
it's the other way around
this is herself a pink
it could be it could be yourself in some
way
ah
you're gonna skip
[Music]
sick of zion yes stick with oh you mean
so that he doesn't kill anyone
god damn it i will help you egg
i will help you
i will help you i will help you we need
to win
let's see huh
let's see what they do
yes just act as if you're doing tasks
very well
let's close that for some reason i don't
know why
i want to do the oxygen what's going on
in here wait where did egg go
where did my egg go where did the egg go
ego is he up here oh yeah
let's close that one everyone's here now
i'm not no many ghosts but
i wanna do oxygen
there we go
death has come upon you good luck with
that
run egg run run run run run
oh egg why did you go back
egg what why why is no one going here
hello where did egg go
are you egg what are you doing
egg run what should i do for you how can
i help you
oh egg reported
oh
pink is running me down why is it
uh uh
was that a good move
is he trying to look like like he's
worried
that that they're gonna lose
wait are they suspecting are they
suspecting pink though
oh oh oh oh
egg egg egg you're a good man
holy [\h__\h] damn
damn son what is this gonna work is it
actually gonna work
this is fun
but he seems a little bit too excited he
seems a bit too too excited he got to
chill a little bit more
he needs a little bit more chill you
would have done those when
he really suspects pink
no don't escape no
no no no don't skip no
he almost got him i know you're lying he
said
no
yes
egg was alone why is blue covering for
egg
is blue the third imposter
okay reactor here we go have fun guys
have fun
i hope you're busy why is blue not
running there oh egg is
oh egg is trying to like
oh no
wait what did i win did i
wait wait who won i don't understand
this uh did i win or did they win
because it says defeat for me but it has
their image
i lost
and you were a good a good friend
thank you for trying your best
you did very well your acting skills are
impeccable you almost got the green dude
the judas dude to believe you good job
thank you for carrying me even though i
messed up and killed
someone in front of everyone else
it was fun it was fun respect
egg respect um
everyone except i have to say
white how why
would you come on give me a chance it
was my first imposter run you gotta give
me more
chances i i messed up
okay but but but i mean
give me a chance okay
oh man
but i did have fun i want to do this
again maybe even in this week again i i
was
not planning to play among us twice but
i want to do it again
very good job ah
i gotta i'm gonna make my schedule
uh after this stream and upload it on
twitter
thank you everyone for everyone who
joined today i think today i
am gonna not do the super chat reading
because there were not so many anyway
i'm just gonna combine it with tomorrow
if that's okay
but i i gotta practice how to be a good
imposter
ah it just it just stressed me out that
was my first time
uh
i want to practice so we got to do this
again
okay thank you everyone for joining
and um do i have anything to announce
nope but i hope you enjoyed the the loud
microphone
with the cloud lifter i hope you enjoyed
that and streaming from my new house
seemed to work as well seemed to work
well
and no internet issues except that one
disconnect but that doesn't i don't
think it has anything to do with the
internet uh with the
yeah with the internet thank you again
for the reception thank you thank you
thank you for the support guys
one more game no no no i gotta do the
schedule and
later i have a little uh call
with a certain senpai to plan a certain
collaboration project together with that
senpai because i was the chosen one
i'm the chosen one apparently
this this certain senpai asked me
if i want to try out a certain game with
her that
some of you have been requesting to ame
today i have seen
um and we played together and then we'll
figure out who to invite to the
collaboration
it's a it's it's a japanese senpai yes
yes
no no hints no hints
and also i have been preparing for my
talk show
i have commissioned many things such as
a nice background that is suitable for
talk show
and a logo and
original btm and
intro music i've been uh commissioning a
lot of things okay
um let's see the talk show will
start once i have everything all the
commissions done
i wanted to be really really good i
wanted to be good okay
i wanted to be prepared well so i'm
commissioning all kinds of stuff
i commissioned like some some jazzy
music you know with
with uh how do you call that instrument
that goes like
that's an elephant
no there will not be elephant noises
yeah saxophone saxophone
i wonder if they can do that trump
saxophone i wonder if that's possible i
want like some nice
jazzy music for my talk show
so i'm really looking forward to that
it's in preparation so stay tuned
thank you guys for coming i had been
lots of fun thank you for playing with
me
thank you for being there thank you for
following the rules thank you for
leaving the room every time i'm really
really
happy with you guys here you guys are
the best crowd ever
the best audience ever props to you
applause to you
club club clappity club
see you tomorrow i have a stream
tomorrow planned
uh yeah you will see
[Music]
bye-bye
amateur mistake
[Music]
us
i love you all
thank you for joining the membership
thank you
fun