[Music]
1 two say
oh so
[Music]
1 two say up
go
[Music]
1 two say
oh 1 2
[Music]
me
hello hello
hello sparking
now
English day
is episode
7 season 1 fin Al part one but not
really do not get fooled by the part one
in my stream title uh there is no part
two I am making fun of
anime
so so is the part two is live there's
only one part just say don't get fooled
by my stream title anyway
hello welcome to the finale is there
going to be a season two who knows
spawn also my ey my internet is being
like
slower today like I don't know so
hopefully it's okay because it's
like it's not blipping it's just
actually legit slower and I don't know
why maybe I got the curse from Kiara
that was happening to Kiara yesterday
but
hopefully okay it's it seems fine for
now it
seems
somewhat
D so
hopefully that
means yes is the last of seven days to
die we
are probably going to go up to 4 hours
again because the hoorde is on day 35 so
we have 5 hours 5 hours is yes on day
um I will go into
hell hello
hell good morning good
morning oh my God I'm so
e yes wake up wake up okay oh oh that
was
easy W
up that was easy have you guys spawned
can we spawn yeah oh I've spawned
already my stream started already oh
okay I'm going
in heck
ooh okay
oh Tas C
stretches I am I am stretching I I
literally woke up five minutes
ago good morning
sunshine the sun says hello
I see
[Music]
some what what I I I I I don't know I
don't know I was about to do p but good
one I don't know now I feel embarrassing
self-conscious so I don't I don't if I
can do this anymore you you canot ruin
the moment you can you canot Rin it it's
over I don't know where I am oh yeah I'm
home hello
hello
hello what's up it is the finale day
final day season one finale let's go
[Music]
finale are you
excited I'm sleeping I'm a little I'm a
little like oh man it's the last day do
you feel that
too yeah I do it's okay we make it count
I'm you for for for the finale it's
going to be good me too I got a poke a
stick so ready to poke some zombies I
wonder if this would how father
reaches where is
Pa I miss her where's where's
mother yeah mother she's not mothering
right
now what oh mother mother mother why why
my mother
just because well in this in this family
you are my mother am I yeah do I have to
be I like how this this to die wasn't
meant to be role play but somehow we
kind of turned it into a little bit of a
roleplay
thing yeah
[Music]
naturally we just fall into our Rose
maybe because we're destined for them no
I don't want want to be destined for
mommy no one said Mommy we just said
every day since for the last three years
the voices have been in my head they
won't leave no no this is different this
is different he you mother mothering
this is this is different cuz I have
like three so you're just part of
it oh I
see people where are you um I am heading
home but looting houses on the way
M if you don't want to be mother some
Stu what are you going to be fauna what
I want to be me I want to be
FAA so
inspirational you know what you know
what I'll call
you thank you thank you
wel we'll make it the thing don't
[Laughter]
worry I have paint brushed what do I do
with that can I paint
something paint the house very important
before the finale yeah that's priority
mhm yeah call her call her one punch
fa oh my God I can make the walls wooden
we can make this like a cottage Co house
guys oh my God C let's do it it's like
it's like a oo rotic Chic oh my
God hello can you hear me hello hello
yes we can hear you yes that's good at
least at least you can hear
me game kicked me
out oh no oh no
rud come back come I thought I thought I
was going to have the internet curs cuz
my internet's been a little funny so I
was like scared
it really they don't want us to play
right they're afraid of us honestly they
probably heard that it's the last day so
they're
like make it long I make it long kick
them all out I have a question are we
going to protect these house or they
hold out for the raid the old house okay
yeah the one with all the spikes we we
dug we dog or g dog some some Moes in
there you should check it
it looks very
intense yeah oo I'm ready where are you
I am nearby because I'm getting I'm
getting
Stones oh okay okay wanted to show you
this new interior design oh I'm
[Laughter]
coming my leg is broken oh no has it
always not
been every single time
I think
splints the house I but it need to okay
more time 21 minutes easy it's kind of
like I mean I have Hur you know when
people like dislocate their shoulder or
something then they more prone to
another injury maybe that's what it's
like with you at this
point your leg sees a pebble and it's
like I'm here s MC Meen hello look
look oh my God this is actually is so
cozy right is it the paint yeah it's
like wooden wooden paint it paints
everything fake wood this is so
pretty good job I was an interior
designer before before the zombie
apocalypse happened
really yeah sucks so even though I can't
live my dream job anymore you know what
I put it into the world whenever I can
wait what did you paint let me
[Music]
see this yeah oh cozy was was there a
difference all the walls were like like
this before where the candle
is oh where I'm standing where I'm
standing turn around turn around turn
around like this oh another wooden oh
cozy
I love it she totally noticed
yep maybe want the be the type of person
to lie when you go up to her and go like
do you notice a difference do you do you
see what I did it's you did great
s it's actually veryy you can see the
concrete over there and see the
difference
people okay sorry I got distracted do we
do we do we do you guys want to do
something do we or should we we wait for
the others actually I guess so yeah wait
for C I am I am home by the way kiaha
welcome home welcome home I have
something for you that I think you will
be better at using at the final
raid oh thank you hello 15
H how did everything go yesterday it
went good oh it was
funny it was funny it was funny was
quite funny funny
may have been more dangerous than the
zombies
really please what was more dangerous
than the zombies sorry the the defenses
we set up around the house was more
dangerous than the actual zombies oh
jeez was it around this house no old
house still it's it's holding up wow
that's crazy I saw that you guys have a
Dugout around this house though oh
that's giggy can't stop herself the goer
yeah did that
stoping use the
all this the good use I guess does
anybody has any extra clay by any chance
oh we have a ton in this chest over here
follow me follow me I'm following you
wait that's the okay okay this
chest thank you so much hey ladies did
we find any shotgun parts by chance yes
there is the parts weapons Parts chest
in the new house thank
you weapons Parts chest there we go we
also have a couple mini bikes by now and
the forge has
grown and yeah by now the zombies that
show up are a little bit more dangerous
we have crazy direwolves showing up when
you see one of those it's so over it's
not over you just got to jump wolves you
just got a JK
just a big Bole do the
trick right so I want to try to improve
especially the armor from the girls who
have the most shitty armor right now oh
and I won't have like enough armor kits
probably to get everybody like the most
amazing armor
but some parts at least yeah um I'm
assuming L CeCe your armor is probably
pretty bad and Callie's maybe too yeah
how much level is it yeah I think so I
think mine's might be better than Ras
but it's still not the best okay my
armor is weakened though I have a few
hand me downs at least uh there are for
example there's level free preacher
gloves which already give you 30% Undead
damage oh there's also so many armor in
the armor chest yeah there's there's
where the hand me downs are as well just
so somebody take the level threee gloves
and the Commando boots can we can we
get this this uh sorry boxes anything
right oh yes okay take take take mhm
okay I'm going to have a ton of bandages
that's good we're going to like at least
30 did did you collect all that aloe I'm
collecting it right now nice nice so did
farming work yes well sort of maybe not
it's easier to just go out into the wild
and punch plants oh okay through that
through
that yes I'm here I can find some
leather and duct
tape
you I died again she blow but usually
it's like two times and then it doesn't
happen anymore
so hope
so is duct tape still like our diff most
difficult thing to get like a high value
commodity yeah duct tape and uh Forge
steel but yesterday at the end of the
stream we were able to get The Crucible
to forge Forge
steel okay we can also make
glue like C GL as well we should have a
good bit of
water things are getting better GL
little by little but still we still need
all of those basic materials anyway yeah
I get it now let me see so just do some
quests and and raid some houses and then
you'll be able to collect plenty I think
ammo as well ammo very important I think
cuz you run out of those ammo so quickly
I I can craft ammo if anybody needs it I
can craft we have some materials to
craft right now too as well M nice also
please let me into your
team oh yeah send me team request please
your
[Music]
party I think one of the most uh
important things for me right now is
sewing
kids you can't craft those right there's
no way to craft them no crafting but the
sometimes the shops sell them too so
I'll keep my eyes peeled if you keep
your eyes peeled for uh shotgun shotgun
parts how many more do you need I
three go to the Traders the Traders
should be selling some Bob wasn't
selling anything today well go check
check Jane and wrecked because they sell
different things I think I saw shotgun
parts but I need to save my money for my
handgun Parts
understandable
understandable Okie doie KS also I think
we'll need repair kits yeah repair
kits
import okie
dokie sounds good and at the old house
have water yeah we have lots of water
now oh
nice I'm also cooking some purified like
the good water I'm cooking that right
now oh yes the legendary good water
didn't you one hobo
stew I love me some hobo stew not lie
stew
now
oh also there's apparently another Traer
in the snow have you guys found him yet
uh I just got the class for him so I
know where he is okay let me know if
he's if he's still the shotgun parts uh
sorry K where did you put the hand meons
is it just
in uh wait they should be in the armor
chest
there should be preach gloves like on
the right side unless somebody else
already took it I don't if I took it
already uh I took some
gloves okay the Commando boots are good
too Commando
boots where did the nerd hat
go ah okay now I have a nerd hat for you
oh might have to repair it soon
but thank you me
yeah I'll be making more armor don't
worry okay I picked I took the commander
boots thank you Ki are we bringing stuff
for you thank all right here's some
sewing
kits where do where do you want me to
put them H the forage you have SE kits
let's go the forge okay
okay F
five
yo nice thanks for the party in I'm just
going to go up to the trader the new one
anyway uh right now so that way I can
see what he
sells okie dokie okay maybe he sells
seashells yeah buy the seashore by the
seashore you guys are so
silly I knew immediately where y'all
were going with
that I need duct
tape okay I I think I can I have some
glue as well if you need
oh glue and clo here's some
glue glue I know glue would be so
important right I'm cooking I'm cooking
glue right now okay the water you can
grab it when it's done there's five
that's cooking
yippe yippe she's cooking all
right is it okay if it blueberry pie wow
yeah super yummy blueberry pie in the
apocalypse is pretty
impressive chefs can do anything that is
very impressive my hammer is called
gimly and I stand by a forge making
armor okay maybe not I am
gim new shotgun is going to be so good
we can get
it I think there's books and
char No I just
you
vertical the
floor fell into
the I'm going up north to unlock that
other traitor traitor not
traitor he's a traitor kill him
backstab if somebody has more armor
parts I also need those for more armor
crafting kits to make more armor I put a
bunch in there in the chest but maybe
you've used them already they are very
necessary if you put them in like two
days ago then I definitely used them
yeah
probably okay I got a couple for now I'd
love to get a fancy new armor for myself
at some
point bring um I want to look real fancy
even though this I can make your stuff I
just need more
materials right so maybe we all do a few
quests today and then we can gather some
materials yeah sounds good to me good to
me I want to go tror we got to go to the
library too yes oh yeah there's a
library I forgot Library it's kind of
broken
this what was I doing where reading is
so vital I know we're all bunch of
readers you think she's closed she might
be closed we very we're very literate
and very educated impressive I love
reading I mean honestly if you are in a
zombie apocalypse and you're doing okay
survival wise there is nothing really to
do other than learn Mak sense just
power I mean probably there not going to
be any smartph around what are you going
to do yeah SP
time nothing
yeah well originally we said we had like
a streamer home right yeah the one with
the computer so even if we can't stream
because we don't have electricity we
could act as if it we do well we can we
can actually make electricity talk to
ourselves we can yes we can we there's
solar panels stuff how do we connect to
the internet I don't know I don't want
to stream by myself no it's okay you'll
you'll we'll sit around the PC and we'll
be your audience oh okay yeah we all for
each other it's like a little you know
each pretty good yeah it's like a l
party but everyone else shuts up and one
person talks I like it sounds good to me
I'm
in
um tell me when you guys are going to do
quests I I want go do one oh oh yeah I
also have one treasure map that I
haven't done yet and it's good to do cuz
it gave me like five k and a bunch of
weapon parts so we should probably go
dig up that one too ooh
5K that's big money yeah okay well I'm
going to head towards the fauna Quest
actually cuz there are two quests over
there people area start questing I guess
we can yeah we can might be a good idea
when's the next
raid day 35 4 and 1 half hours
okay yeah a while 1 p.m. day F 5 I need
more iron I need everything I need to
wrench cars what time the Traders
Clos pretty sure 9 oh 10 I think it was
10 minutes before 10 p.m. hurry hurry
hurry R you got four
seconds okay so are we heading to PHA
gear three Quest I I just head there
okay I'm going M
oats um there's bices outdo by the way
and mini
bikes okay will probably join
my we Kelly do you know I think that's
yours Kelly it's oops is are you there
already can I just follow your oh yeah
just come to where I am okay okay pray I
don't die how did you get there Kelly
bike
you bicycle or bike uh a bike okay good
good you're using your bike it's so fast
yay oh tra got a
bike I'm sure it'll be fine any scary
zombies come I'll stand on top of this
truck easy
bottle I sell certainty oh
go I is right
behind oh the new trator has six shotgun
bro it always finds the one that have
the ones that have the shotgun parts but
he's going to close like any second and
kick me out yeah buy pray somebody has
them
tomorrow that's an ambulance but still a
good idea yeah ambulance truck same
vehicle really what do you think to
do is on my head right now she's on my
head oh oh not oh now I thought you
meant IRL no she is
what do you mean totally this is IRL
what are you talking about cute how are
you balancing her like that does she
like put her how manys do you need she's
good at balance I need four no three
wait hold up uh three oh I have them you
got them three shotgun parts for your
boy thank you I owe you what what do I
owe you give me handgun parts or money
okay I'll give you the money from this
Quest
that would have paid for the shotgun
parts you know we're going to have to
put it on credit cuz I just bought for
steel okay I'm I'm coming to the quest
too by the way so okay yeah I'm almost
you some of my cut some of my cut I
think I am
hearing the world has opened up since we
have gotten bip
pedal driving the bike do be fast yes
yes yes you think we can get a car today
that be
f i wonder let's see how far we are from
that we should you guys should do lots
of quests so you can get this new Trader
where I'm at and maybe he'll give us a
car yeah I bet he gives a car oh
oo you think he a whole car cuz I I
literally just got motorcycle parts he
gave me motorcycle parts so maybe the
next step is car parts yeah car parts
but not a car
I need to learn how to make make a car
in the oh you can I you I think when I
went to the forge I I got the I make the
four thingy so you can't make it you
need to get the magazines first I'm at
47 out of
70 with 70 I can make the car oh so I
need 23 more
magazines okay we'll look we'll look out
for it
yeah Library oh can you guys bring me
some food because I forgot about it and
I have I'm coming to the
quest you she probably be here quick if
she's using the bike yeah I'm Ying I'm
gas
gas let me know when you're
ready
okay trying to craft
oh some Banda down here a quick raid of
a rando house yeah go go loot some stuff
while you're waiting that that good
stuff a rando house you can actually
loot the house that you're raiding
because it's going to reset when you
start the quest anyway so oh really
yes clever and then we know the layout
right away
yeah it's pretty cool de wow what a
gentleman I'm
scared feel like that's somebody I went
to school with the Rando photos are very
frightening it's right oh no alarm no
alarm up wake up this is not my wake up
time dream no it's okay I was happy to
wake up early
today I surprised I woke up without any
alarm I
[Music]
think I'm I'm ranching a car nearby let
me know when you're done okay I'm just
going to try to get some food cooking so
we have some when we come back good
mother she's mothering what what level
is your
wrench sorry what what level is your
wrench cuz I found a level 4
one oh mine is level free if you want to
take my level four wrench I can give it
to you oh maybe it'll be better I can
give you my level three wrench okay if
you want to switch then you can wrench
cards too or do you have your own
no I just have the level four that I
found oh okay I'll take it
gladly oh challenge
complete ah by the way the girls who
weren't online yesterday have any of you
um in your
achievements have you seen there's a
second window of achievements and if yes
have you completed the 50 50
cops 50 cops oh you completed that by
any
chance why what does that give you it
gives you good stuff actually it gives
you like water filters and crucibles and
like useful stuff and solar panels
potentially maybe all of them all of the
Zombie Slayer ones give you maybe good
stuff maybe not
sure we haven't tested it yet properly I
can see where you are thank
you that's a lot of zombies uhoh any
help as we work ohoh you will reach the
50 cop zombies today at the final raid
for sure yeah for sure M that's awesome
wow and then we'll have to do season 2 I
asked about it and they seemed receptive
oh is do they at least know how we can
keep the characters and stuff um when I
mentioned it to them they seemed to
think it was possible okay yay let me ly
yeah the to let's
go okay I think I'm ready okay
[Music]
probably by lots of food cooking y
okay
okay bike is over
here cuz I feel like yeah we can go
further M oh yeah the work
big we haven't even set up turrets and
uh electricity yeah
that's like the next step yeah what
about theop pretty far
off yeah that's pretty far away but
turrets would be so
nice oh you're RA in the same house as
me no I just ran away from someone and I
ran towards you cuz I was like who can
protect me not me I'm cracking open a
safe I forgot to take off my mod off of
the wrench if you can take it off and
give thank thank you you quiet down
sir why won't you shut up close the door
for
now quick ranching session
on
fuel
always got a it's not just a fuel it
also gives me iron and I I'm actually
out of iron I think so okay I'm here by
the way
okay yay we're coming we're
coming wow my inventory is already full
what I
have
a you'll get rid of them
yeah but maybe we can try to save most
of them for the raid I know I feel like
I I don't even have enough I have like
20 right now but I feel like that's not
even
[Music]
enough Hammer Parts by the way Kar if
you're trying to make make a big
Sledgehammer H Sledgehammer Parts yeah
oh uh yeah oh wait I think I already
have enough but might more I'm not sure
not
sure dang I blew him away God I can't
wait to see the next
shotgun may I grab those parts from you
biu I'll I'll un over you if you want
have some
money mission put it on my tab
please how much can I buy off your
current shotgun off of you when you get
your new shotgun sure empty absolutely
you
can or handgun Parts if anyone finds any
handgun parts please give people handgun
parts I'll keep it in M that's
terrible where where are where are they
are the new
te okay we have
arrived oh one second before we start
the quest can you kill me because I'm
about to die I don't want to
die no
hesitation no hesitation the back watch
the sunset n forget all watch out watch
out rest in peace I'll miss
you Gone Too
Soon they left this world too soon who's
going to give the chatini their jet
packs no one
[Laughter]
no I'm
coming there's two class we can do here
there's one for R and one for fa yeah
that's why I came here cuz there's a lot
popping
off all right time to blast them I am
ready ready I'm hyp I'm ready for
blasting make sure to check everywhere
sewing kids could be everywhere slash
the curtains the curtain
have cloth we e that embrace your inner
loot Goblin or your outer loot Goblin oh
I am very much an outer loot
Goblin it's very obvious also I put a
bunch of food and Medicine in Kiara's
trunk you need
anything
yeah your spacious trunk Bountiful trunk
I'm people oh yes yes yes yeah yeah my
uh am I standing on R's head like Tut on
my head and it's me standing on R's head
and Tut on my
head whose mission is this R oh R you
got to start the mission oh okay sorry
it's okay yipp
yipp yippe
by the way come out come out wherever
you are no I
was just got
it they an upstairs I was this is my
natural
posture you just you're just always
ready can somebody loan me some money I
want to buy some beer anybody got any
beer
money money I always have money know if
I can sign off I bother you for 300
coins
oh yeah for some
beer yes here I am I am here I give
you here go oh no thank you doesn't go
any lower I'm trying to look for stairs
down but stairs be for you here oh you
bought it for me thank
you so
benevolent take a while oh do we have to
go up oh yeah there is an
upstairs oh we're retrieving supplies in
this chest I didn't realize yeah I'll
come back to
this you get up there I
[Music]
wonder that doesn't seem
good great now I can see where you
are I prefer not to hit my friends oh
are you on fire uhoh uh-oh oh I'm going
to die I'm going to die I
[Applause]
died come on man what's going
on oh no dang was the damage that bad or
was it the fire I think you were on fire
oh gosh okay no more
fire no more fire take some take some
bandaids out of the trunk some bandaids
yeah I have some Band-Aids put a
Band-Aid on it make
plenty now son of a gun oh oh is that my
I'll get the next
mission being H it's okay we got a lot
of missions this time oh when we've got
supplies if anyone forgot fine look for
your Satchel like I forgot uhoh yeah you
got to it's a it's a Fetch and
clear help anyway on the floor
I'm blind I can't I can't even see the
oh there it is okay there's a lot of
screaming going
on
here big scream oh there it is I found
mine yay okay I found mine too nice good
job nice oh no don't please
fire no more lighting the fire she's on
fire fire fire they're on
fire fire who
wanted to be on fire I found one no you
the area it's not clear yet have you
guys seen the basement yet I think
there's a
basement can we use this chain to climb
down or am I going to
die uh
99% tring to try it out
oh where is my
SAT I'm not ready I hear zombies
upstairs oh upstairs be
basement give it a
Bo oh this is easy to break oh I found a
oh
there we
go maybe it's outside they're Birds
they're Birds oh oh just
boards oh behind oh coming up not mine
let's
see you have to
fire be careful to the fire I should use
my AR yeah know the fire is no joke okay
we cleared it
nice I I didn't find my supplies yet got
to be in there somewhere oh B there's a
safe where I am oh where are you ouch
I'm on fire on the second floor okay the
office second
FL uhuh oh yeah F have you read have
have you read this one yet you should
read this
one oh I have not in the perimeter thank
you never encumbered at night yeah I I
read it already it's so good I'm on fire
why
crazy God where's oh there's the sa
okay found it love doing Missions at
night Missions at night are best
food I got I have food yeah
of dangers where are you I am in the
basement what color are
you could use more brownand I'm Brown
she's at the floor floor level I also
need food please I will stick
with get the yummy on and water if you
have water I have thank you so
much thank you there's also there's
better water in the
car car car
wait come back come back oh take some
food ah thank you I really need
it thank you so
caring oh my God why is it
so lagy in here there's
water here I have this for you this for
you I have this for
you I have I will not fail this time no
more fire thank you thank you wow thank
you
woohoo yes for
you thank you who's learning electrical
traps I'm learning it yeah I the only
one doing nerd
stuff I am doing nerd stuff oh I can
make an electric
fence that'll be helpful against the
raid that' be very helpful what if dire
wolves come during the raid oh that's
fine are you oh there were there were
two there were two that came during the
r yesterday and I killed them just fine
easy okay so they're killable
yeah all right where's the next one uh
Fest one is
nearby let's go to
it I need to do I need to finish the
quest so I can pay bio
back I got a debt to bio right
now I ow money I don't like going people
money don't wiiz on the electric fence
don't tell the zombies that I want them
to pee on the electric fence ranching oh
there's a tire how do you say this this
resident's name
Rara which one it is PTI
see let me check is everybody
here no one sec I'm on my way okay I
think I think it went
away I'm here everybody
nearby
neighbor
woohoo
okay yes ready
P oh
wow there's a lot of stuff going on
there's a lot watch out by the way
what what what what
what easy oh sorry oh there's a bird
Vulture I can't me did you hit me twice
no only once only once time had you have
been the zombie oh it's that thing
there he's dead oh my God
take care of your health you
need yes please can I have one there you
go thank
you thank
you every should some bandid there's
some in the car band yeah bandages help
you help you stay
safe don't whack the zombies with this
don't whack them with
it don't whack them with it because then
the light on fire then the light you on
fire it really that never happened to me
before oh it'll happen really oh oh
yeah oh God there's this green one
there's a sh there's a
Hulk sorry not a lot
of it's sweet that your head still first
is that how you see us too is it is it
how you see at me
too oh
boy I mean Shrek is actually nice yeah I
like Shrek me heal I love Shrek he's
cool he's
chill W wble wob wobble nice belly
physics is it super laggy for you too or
it just no no no no no no no no no no
wonder oh wow he just will not
die it's all right he's rag doin now oh
wait no he's still alive he's dead no
still alive
oh you better to come to where I
am yes did you see this
picture oh my gosh they're huging that's
pretty
ad those cats are okay apocalypse you
think they got away wish we could might
have been the best one we probably found
the best one yesterday but this might
top it think the kitty cats got away
safely don't make me think about it
Callie I'm asking you think they got
away they got f
I'm sure they Liv best
strong they're not strong they're good
at running away
though oh oh hello guys oh find
something good in there I
help no oh yike oh that's a big one hold
up oh man is he dead
nope I like the glow in the dark one
Fist and bat combin
Powers go think did we clear it seems
like yes we did complete ladies we to
the
TR yeah he should be open now I still
want to like just make sure to
thoroughly loot the house for Stuff
there's still um destroying the bed
there's no quests around here destroy
the everything let's
go this is
good oh even the bathroom
curtain no suing kids
though
why don't forget the library yeah is the
library
close no no
area oh okay we a quick Trader run get
some money to give to bio there should
be more I never forget need G for the
for the redirect that was very
sweet
welcome you guys ready for some last day
Raiden
y I was looking forward to this I hope
we get 10 dire wolves today oh boy
better yet 18 18 dire woles csing
Clementine house the big ones we saw
that one time where we died like 20
times oh the snow possibly yeah yeah
yeah okay well we hopefully we won't get
those yeah it'll be fine okay I have
stuff I for you guys make my
shotgun okay uh you likely to get bears
oh here you
go and here you go I got armor crafting
kids too oh thank you oh and here you
go yo oh so much
ammo yes anything
else I can't wait use my armor piercing
Me I'm
Scared okay come over here we'll save
you come to front of house I'm in the
tree in now I want the hobo stew but
where where someone else can make me a
hobo stew you need a hobo stew hob stew
I would love a hobo stew I've got some
hobo stews if you have a hobo stew
what's what's with your specific
interest in Hobo skin she just really
likes them I just think it's
yummy it's hobos stew man you know what
it's made of hobos right you really like
telling people
that what don't worry Little Missy I
know what I'm getting into okay
okay okay I got a bunch of cloth yay
that's good we need that successfully
clo de cloth this
building ohie we can probably make it
but I also want to give some gift duct
tape too oh yes and then this should be
I think I owe be about this much is
oh hold on okay I have not a single spot
in my inventory left let's go to the
Traer this way my
bike wait do we have another Quest here
oh did row just pick it up I see oh I I
I see
one ooh hey I'm definitely down to down
to
help okay I didn't see like my inventory
is such a
mess welcome to Trad tell I get oh I
just need one more shotgun part now if I
want to get this you owe me
1,350 amazing okay 1,350 no problem I
almost have that much here I'll give you
what I have right now I have 913 bucks
so I'll drop it on the ground for
you Duke's Casino token they're using
Casino tokens as money that's silly
Finly yeah do you think Duke is like the
final boss we ever me
him I was saying that I think the
tra here you go as a freebie present o a
freebie oh Nice Shot 95 shotgun shells
now I have
491 cool it might not even be enough C
it might not even be
enough the shotgun fires so
slow yeah please please take
these yes uh what is A9
mm what's that for so much my 9
meter oh I don't know oh no payment need
a is
that I give it to you that goes through
like armor and stuff I don't know I
think it's just stronger version yeah
but what's 9 mm what's that for B uses
it oh pistol okay excuse me bird waa
take
these thank
you and then you make me some of my own
[Music]
weapon take care of you be sure to tell
your friends yes should I take these and
then you make me some um ammo for my
weapon what what ammo do you
need I have an IR and I have a shotgun
oh the whole crew is here at Trader J I
just gave Callie some shotgun ammo so
you can split with Callie
maybe some more ammo here I have too
much welcome but yeah please take it
away from me Cece please she's oh I she
G stuff motorcycle parts okay I put I
take these thank you
and I
put I put
yours here oh thank you oh so four $400
does right
now get some money
St yes for
you for me
than
thoseo will forever for you that's a
very loud and pretty can opener you've
got there are you talking about
CeCe Callie she is very pretty Callie
take these yeah sure oh thanks thanks
Callie thanks and she probably can open
a ton of Cans really well yeah anybody
needs a a repair kit I'm good I'm good
but we will my we will need them yeah I
get in the future okay I'll keep it I'll
keep
it the gun but that's too oh
go I to repay you back here very
effective nobody cares thank
you I appreciate that you don't need to
pay me back though I want to be
nice bandaids are for
everybody what is thank you for looking
after us Fara this
yeah yeah that's for you for me yeah
this one I'm here I'm here oh behind you
oh
yeah oh thank you T I love te how did
you know right how did she know P my
nose yeah I have for
you this well hello can you is anybody
else learning armor crafting uh I've
started also learning it I think armor
crafting is something generally
everybody kind of wants to learn I'm
maxed out on it so everybody can need it
anymore do we need to make forg steel
Kiara at The Crucible how what do we
need to make it uh it's just iron uh as
well just same as for forged Iron same
as for forged steel more of it
yes take these oh thank
you that's why I keep on wrenching cars
and stuff because they also give iron
and anything in houses that looks like
it's made out of iron or steel also
wrench that so that you get more more
more nice never get
enough cool I got to make 3 Forge steel
if I want level two pump shotgun so yeah
we've been trying to make as much as we
can but it quickly Runs Out out so what
why did you drop that to I don't
know
CL ke I have some mods you might be able
to use for your Club if you don't
already have
them oh definitely thank you so much I
will take those oh metal spikes metal
chain metal chain I definitely feel like
I can use on the I think I can can use
it on the bat it might be a club only
thing though I don't know maybe not how
do you
actually ah you have to choose spikes or
or um chain it would seem but thank you
though I feel like maybe if we can make
bats for everyone I'd love to make bats
for everybody or clubs for everybody oh
that' be nice
yeah oh bats and clubs are different
yeah they're dead to me they're the same
thing my brain is a don't have to think
too much about it you just use your
fists
yeah yeah J I want to learn how to do
how to make drones but I haven't you
need
electricity or something or electrical
the electrical skill I think maybe Oh I
thought we going into robotics robots
I've been trying to do robotics but you
for the Drone you need 76 and I've
only like and G Stu yeah do you want a
chain Club are you goodar but I'll give
it to you here I'm learning Ranger and
hunting if anybody has magazine I think
there are some at home in the book oh
wait I already yeah Cron's not in VC
today guys we have all kinds of do hicke
for okay just she's chilling though
she's here so are we staking it out for
the final day more guts and you Mach
that I'm going to be back in one minute
I'll be okay
okay maybe we can invite crony to the
team I do worry I hope that she maybe
she'll maybe she can like try and get
some of the
EXP from our battles she can come along
with us who's who's uh oh we might have
to split down cuz we're six already oh
we're we six seven yeah in total we were
we're seven with crony yeah we need to
split too much I guess oh I tried to
invite her but I think six
is oh wait she's doing never mind never
mind okay that's crazy let's do
it nice we take another
Quest I'm like that hot Final Fantasy
mechanic girl m
she's yeah that that one from from 15
Cindy or whatever her name
was Cindy Cindy
Cindy where are we going F are we going
home or um I don't know I thought we
were doing more quests yeah I do more I
would mind my inventory is still
completely full let me you want to drop
it off at the other house I no cuz I
guess there's no point yeah there's a
pretty close Quest over here
storage so are we splitting or are we
going all together no we're going all
together
okay going into the deserted
land I'm just going to put I got to
check the other Traders today
too see if they have any shotgun
parts I'm back so uh what is it the the
bottom one has shotgun parts
uh no Bob Bob has shotgun parts
and I think snowy guys's inventory reset
so you're going to have to check him
again but Bob definitely has okay I will
go find Bob uh towards which Quest are
we going back to the L Quest or a Bob I
found one uh there's there's a bunch of
quests near Bob if you want to come by
Bob okay Bob and around Bob's area
there's quest for cie Kiara bio fa yeah
there's a lot oh that's a lot W oh yeah
I do have a quest there huh okay maybe
the closest one first the one where cie
and waa have a quest
yeah tier to
clear we can do that one really quick
and then we'll go south to traon going
to run there oh gosh can anyone pick up
cron on the back of their bike perhaps
uh I need to make more seed mods and
more bikes uh where is she maybe I can
pick her up she's
like oh she doesn't even have a bicycle
I can give her my bike is she running oh
no I have I have a seat I have a bike
too I have a seat so I can go pick her
up okay I'll give her my
bike people will pick you
up oh E I thought B was picking up oh
yeah after B picks her up we beat I will
for are we doing right
now we're
doing oh mine
okay calling yeah wait I went the wrong
way you need to be my GPS wait I thought
we were going to Bob I didn't realize
going to this one oh did you guys go
south no no we're not going to that one
I want to go following you it's over oh
well we were going towards Bob but
everyone else is going did the other
Quest I see them in the distance wait
where are we going where do I go who do
I follow the so the where is right now
wait not for Bio I think wait are we
going to the one North or to the one
towards Bob which one are we going to
where you are right now people stop stop
stop I thought we're going north
where where is is that not where the
quest are I
understand okay we're I guess we're
going to T's first and then and then Bob
and then toward okay on point
today communication
issues it
happens in
time imagine if we were walkie talkies
over over wait this reminds me of
something over no here we go again hold
I'm not going the right way am I I know
I can't tell okay that way that
way what's your favorite T show
over TV show I
think I hate picking but I like the
walking dead because that is very catic
very topical very nice over I haven't
watched it yet
over you should watch it at least like
the first couple episodes are pretty
good over we'll do over oops I'm sorry I
got off the bike I pushed the wrong use
it oh was doing stunts you like
dangerous thing
yeah moving
dangerously okay here we go
party all right I'm
here yay Cron's learning the wonders of
the
bike uh I can exit the group so crony
can get some expi no everybody's in the
seven apparently 1 2 3 four 5 I can't
count wait how is that possible I don't
know it's crazy
wait okay so when you guys ready I start
the quest ready seven people oh I
thought six was the mix
I what I thought the following party
members are out of range B can you come
closer okay I'm still R some
things I'll be there in one
[Music]
second oh oh
God she hates
mailboxes when they're empty I hate them
she has a personal Vendetta against them
why is there nothing
inside but IRL I'm scared when there's I
I I I avoid my mailbox actually way too
much and then my letters anxiety like
opening the
letter there's no reason for me to be
worried about it I can just pay it but I
just avoid it anyway I don't want to see
like
bills yeah same really shouldn't but
can't be help still scare me oh boy can
you not do that
sir zombies are getting a bit
tougher oh the the freaking Hulk is here
get him fa get him you can't let another
dream person beat
you oh that's a strong
guy oh he's reaching into my
guts oh
hello oh I'm going to take care of this
behind you oh God I'm just
looting kind of expected
that really really need a light
source what's this damage oh
oh that was
unexpected why does it take time God
we're coming in full force with
the people I found a safe can you
lockpick it okay
go uh uh can you find me on the map it's
yeah second floor in a closet second
floor I'm on the second
floor find me I'm
looking oh what are those W
oh uh yeah might have to go the other
way
let me know if we find any shotgun parts
oh we got to crouch to get down
here okay well that hurt me anyway okay
I'm here do we
need yeah in in here in
here okay good luck thank you oh
dear oh
wow protect the
safe dang it is fire fire fire oh dear
oh oh dear oh my God I hear so much
violence behind me are you okay uh yeah
I'm okay they're they're they're they're
going to die soon it's going to be quiet
soon so you can focus on the on
lockpicking I got it did you open it
yeah there wasn't very much in it El man
cuz they're scar
money scared of money is always nice
dang
it oh oh we did it oh ready nice nice
easy I
think there will be harder quests which
might be good
yeah hard is always good wait big
hitters who's who's uh big hitters Mory
okay I'm going to go through okay one
sec
guys okay thank you
nice oh yeah many many close by quests
thankfully wait I didn't me to pick my
thingy up there I wonder if we can
scavenge these oh she she come here
behind
you uh take
this some
[Music]
thanks that was really scary are you
good I'm okay oh why is she in
here scrap it I think I can though thank
you so much was this one where we had to
like pick up something
or no this was just a clear nothing
we're good just a clear I love clears
cuz they're so easy yeah not easy but
confused you simple straight forward M
okay I got a lot of cloth nice yeah I
got some too cloth for the cloth God for
the duct tape
gods and sewing though I need sewing K
we'll find some maybe at the next house
MMO yes want a you want bombs yes yes
thank
you take this too oh thank you and um
take take this
too oh thank
you not cuz I my pockets are full
obviously she's so selfless
okay well done what is the next
Quest my nails in this game are kind of
on
girl you know they're
[Music]
painted oh did you I never even tried
out the new horn
on hold up wait does Pony still need a
ride no she has a bicycle now does
anybody need does anybody have an extra
seat oh Ro uh come come here sit on me I
come hold on
uh get
on okay
here uh oh is it full
y oh nice it's 100%
fuel yeah I filled it up okay so we're
going south to Bob now right around to
the got what I need kiaha you don't have
a hat on let's go baby I gave my nerd
hat yes hold on to
me my other armor is strong enough to
handle being hatless wear my preacher
hat if you
want does it smell like I pressed the
wrong button o
f
get okay let's go
all right it's not the drinking hat is
it it is the drinking hat oh I'm thirsty
as
hell we have water if you need to borrow
it first in a different
[Music]
sense are you going to the Traer right
now oh I think we're going to the the
the the two quests that are on the way
to
Bob yeah okay but we could do St
okay I turned in my my quest by accident
that's fine
though it's fine I like to knock out a
bunch of them at one time if I can
but I like I like you know hoarding
completed Quest and then getting them
complet at once and you just
get feels nice I can't wait to see all
the little
packages outside and so much
stuff Amazon delivery
oh this was at the Poppin pills going to
be
fun isn't this where we dug ourselves a
big hole
before oh
yeah yeah that
traa it never ended thank you
for I probably should have got it was
nice hello
hello g g
what's going on did you can you join the
party I gave you an invite is it
possible um my
G yes yay wow no
limit I think the difference is that the
UI just it just I don't know you guys'
colors are kind of like I don't know
hard to see but that's
it okay I'm satisfied with with one car
oh this is a Mor Quest nice so I got to
be able to start this
one wait almost there okay wait do I
have the same Quest there cuz oh oh yeah
is it
ably yeah you both have the same
class nice oh yeah will we be making our
old house very strong is that the goal
yes yes okay it's already strong I will
head on over and keep digging
okay are you okay to not be in the
mission is that okay it's okay I love
digging sounds good oh cron is going to
get a lot of money too I hope from
this what a welcome see
him get him FAA get
him you can pay Oh I thought there was
somebody sitting in here be careful K
behind you
okay they should let us use shopping
carts as like motorbikes then we just
each
other oh sewing
kids
Yik where'd you find the sewing kit uh
in the on top of a shelf I'm
looting looting everything maybe go I've
shot a single zombie oh another s kid oh
I found shotgun parts oh you
did I need those thank you Kiara oh
don't thank me I'm just finding things
well thank you for telling me you had
them no problem give them to me right
all sharing and caring of course for
free
oh wait there's supplies oh yeah yeah
yeah I found steroid
CR it's nice those are nice you can
carry anything that you want for a while
Mega Crush yeah pump yourself
up I'm getting very
heavy cases I can get it yes don't worry
okay is going to throw out some oh we
have to find supplies yeah yeah I forgot
there so much loot in here though I
know so worth
it I need to find my
watch
yeah so
beautiful yes
is that also Kima yeah they're
communicating
wow I feel like you actually know how to
play it no no
no I
doing me
too I have for you a few things you do
behind you thank you oh y big hitters my
favorite bag wait do you like shotguns
need to go down yeah I have a shotgun
user there's that cuber I wonder if I've
read this before Oh Oh It's one of
these thank
you have your girls already found a way
down where show me base skills
shut oh they're down I need to go
up oh yeah mine's down
uhoh hello lad watch
outo oh you shot all no you didn't
there's another one there's another one
out they get in there oh this way yeah I
opened up the
door classic what's down here
oh
St my stuff is still downstairs maybe
mine is upstairs but where is upstairs
roof how do I get to the roof
wow crony found a meth
lab that's crazy wow good job where's Mr
White where is he
Jesse we have to C oh what does this Le
to some secret boar again or so no
really I want to fight a boar just a
weird
lab oh my Satchel is
here I can't get it
need more food what
F huh I have have you read bar brawling
five no that's what I need that's what I
need the most yes I have for you yes I'm
on the roof I need the last one I need I
can block bab hold up on the last day
you become the strongest Fister oh my
goodness oh thank you I need see if that
helps hold up there's some folks
upstairs oh it works thank you you're
welcome can't believe I need
opies
opies yeah my my Satchel is an unable
space I put myself in a bad
situation ouch it kind of hurts upstairs
I
might
no I thought you were so Invincible I
believe in you you can get frutus you
got
this yay oh fin take it take it here you
go thank you I'm so excited thank you so
[Music]
much oh my
goodness
uh well the area isn't clear yet no oh I
wonder I get Point recovery every does
anybody have lock PS by the
way did you find another save yeah
there's no there's a reinforc chest here
so we can just Bon it I
suppose very very over incumbered can I
give you some of the like stuff like the
sewing kits and stuff uh yeah the sewing
kit yeah I I have no space in my
inventory but the sewing kit already
takes up a space so I can take yeah okay
okay I'm trying to run up after you but
I'm very slow
I'll come to you I'll try I think you're
there hello okay so what you got here
glue do you have a glue stack oh
noan or
iron iron yeah iron I can take iron iron
iron maybe on the roof I bet the zombies
are on the roof there's only one I got
it you got it okay we done I do have a
glue stack oh you do okay here you go
cloth do you have a Glo you made it I no
I
my K has the same Quest here so we can
read that one I can't take okay okay
I'll yeah wait this one we need it away
take a fish
thank you I'm almost
Max I can't get out of here who did
this bab bonga this is how nerds do
things using our our brain
muscles if something's not opening just
hit it over and over again yeah that's
called using your
noodle there go strongest nerds you've
ever seen
wait that's what's called using your
noodle yeah your brain oh yeah using
your noodle my brain
noodles oh got a
repair oops I'm out of commission I
don't have any stone I can hit with my
bag though oh I have stone wait do I
have a lot of stones I have one stone I
wonder if that be enough like 500 oh
dangin
thanks father okay nice it's repaired oh
what is
that where is everybody on what floor
are you shots I have a quest liit oh
yeah I'm also at my quest limit didn't
know that was a thing
oh oh I don't know if I've reached mine
yet oh this is for you by the way B
Knife Guy oh thank you I needed I think
I can make machete now maybe oh nice
o we can go does anybody have there are
antibiotics or honey I have
honey also have honey in the bike I
think yeah there's honey some of the
Traders also sell higher level
antibiotics the bike oh I have oh no I
have vitamins never
mind I only have po 9% infection
so that's pretty low until it gets worse
right
yeah should be fine just a little
zombism as a treat yeah teeny tiny bit
will do you
that this lock hair looks
funny I'm trapped
inside yeah I love fauna's armor
she looks so scary like a Golem that
punches
people for
sure I'm finally out I've been I feel
like I've been stuck in this building
for just couldn't find my way out ready
to go back
in oh no oh we're going back in again
okay
um I'm dropping some things on the floor
please take when it applies to you
dropping big hitters on the floor
dropping cooking magazines on the floor
my arm is
broken what was it the parts still a
yeah dropping shotgun parts on the floor
I learned to make fish tacos o want
tacos for you can make fish tacos Tac
Tuesday it's Taco Tuesday oh
I'm
dropping wait it's literally Tuesday
yeah maybe not where' you get the fish I
don't I don't know yeah I haven't seen I
haven't seen fish at
all you find canned
salmon hey who needs shotgun parts I do
thank you okay welcome now where's Big
hitters somebody oh nice
okay oh just kidding it's not so we
going back to the TR and then we go oh I
think we're doing this one more time
right oh okay okay oh
okay I have a quest liit what does it
mean probably can't do this question can
guess I have a quest limit too can we
still do the quest of limit voices in
head let me try three two one uh the
following party members are of range oh
that's
fine okay we apparently we still can do
the class if there's a limit yes it says
not available until uh 20 minutes later
28 G minutes not too bad usually it's
minutes mhm so is that 20 seconds no
okay so the class limit is basically you
won't get progress for the like the next
Trader unlock but you still get the
class oh that's from Kiara that's from
crony wait Kiara sorry this is from
crony I stole it cuz it was on the
ground and I got
scared sor two Springs and 34 steel take
this this this glue duct tape did you
want arrows W I think you're using bow
right yeah yeah I'm using the B oh thank
you so much that's very helpful let me
know if you guys find Springs by the way
I need Springs Springs I think we have I
have Springs how many
you how many two here two yeah thank you
oh thank you everyone's so beautiful in
this game thank you thank you for the
two
Springs now all I need is 3 Forge steel
so we're just going to have to make it
at the 4 oh we can start the quest now
okay yeah let's run it one more time
with full inventories yeah this Quest
feels kind of wasteful if we have full
inventories and we can't take everything
I can take some more things you can
remember you have a mini bike mini bike
has a lot of storage yeah I know it's
already oh full I think
[Music]
find more Stone in the head's very
strong all I found steel Club
cards oo I might need those actually but
I don't think I'll get the club that
high level this this go
around I found handgun Parts people oh
yay thank you this is a great place
yeah this has everything it's like it's
oh it's a store right
he's it's like a store oh this time we
have to find supplies did we have find
supplies before I don't even remember oh
I think so oh
okay shortterm
memory blue Scavenging for
now oh this is so good yeah there's a
bunch of glue here
by the way a good idea will be like give
the same um items to one person because
there's but that needs us to be
organized and look if you want to can
handle the stones no sorry uh the the
clo
fragment okay and uh stone wood and
everything I'll drop them oh actually
put most of them in my car in my gun
parts nice
oh speci we can organize better when we
do question so we can optimize the space
yeah food you're starving I'm St a time
like this yummy in this
economy no way exactly in this
economy that's why I am
starving yeah
grab some more clay
and
lag seems useful right
now I also am a bit hungry not going to
lie OB sounding good right now I wonder
if there's still food in the in the bike
I have one hobo sto left oh there is
there is for sure I saw that's the end
of the quest we just had to retrieve the
supplies mhm oh okay I fell into the
hole oh
yes can you uh get out okay yeah K came
and is helping me what a legend okay I
got this I I totally came for you yeah I
know you were you had like 0.2 seconds
um Reaction Time iMed there there's a
locker that need boning I appreciate it
in the
roof oh I have one lockpick uh let me
see if I
can you could just Bonk it though oh I
could use a lock
pick what kind of things do you have in
your
inventory uh I have polymer
cement uh Rotting Flesh um um Nails lead
rten
iron uh cloth fragment
brass clay I know how to get to be oh
hey behind you behind
you
oh oh
okay there was a reason why I asked you
those questions thank you I thought you
were in front of me for some reason okay
okay
whoa your gun is
[Music]
loud but so functional a B
personality yes I don't see the Satchel
icon on my map I think if you're at your
quest limit there is none oh okay got oh
I was at my quest limit I have it oh hit
him no no wait use I'm going to
die no I'll protect you I made a
mistake dang
it I made a mistake now I have to go I
thought all the zombies were
gone it's okay we're we're learn we live
and we learn and we die and we learn I'm
lost holding bag trying to fight for my
life I'm just going to climb to bi Boo
from the
outside more trouble than it's worth
down the
hole Yeah I'm glitched I can't see what
like the distance from
my
supplies I feel like it's due to the
quest limit but I don't know let me let
me
Focus down no on this
level
see
okay the run back is
crazy did anybody have their statel
before on the the main the the the basic
the zero level if yes where was it CU I
think they in the garbage
shoot
oh oh mine was in the basement last time
maybe we'll check if it
was we still have to find it without the
GPS yeah drink machines oh gosh all
right I'm going to go on the
roof I should just follow why do I never
for
Minecraft just
following that way that way classic
there's an awning but of course there
is are you kidding I don't know where
mine is either oh there's one here
anyone if maybe it's here
K one right there no not
mine okay don't know where mine is
either but it is on this level hey
bab I got a lockpick for you oh okay I'm
coming back
upstairs where's the roof I'm lost the
roof is iuse Minecraft oh the roof the
roof is on the main the main hall you
just have to jump on the you just have
to jump on the
like a I got to depit my stuff in the
meantime the what does exclamation point
crossed out mean it means you reach your
daily limit but that's okay you can
still get the rewards that's that's what
that means really it just doesn't
progress the uh apparently tier up
Trader thing I'm oh I think according to
the voices my head but maybe I got one
guy you never know all right here's one
lockpick right
now feeding you wrong information it's
me what did I just
destroy I can't find it it's
over oh the loog pick is broken okay
time to smack it all right well at the
end of the day it always goes back to
bonking well it's definitely time to
drop off some things at home yeah are
going to close after all I they're
closed oh yeah then maybe oh yeah
they're totally closed now
should we just leave without finding the
I think this is impossible without like
the radar it feels
impossible could be everywhere um I
found one where I am right now if you
want to check that one there's one in
the garbage shoot that I found there's
one in the behind the next to the
hole always goes back to Bonk Bonk in
that right
chat
loveing punching can solve anything oh
yeah do I have any stone kie me oh did
your did your just break no I don't
there was some down in the shelves but I
didn't take it okay have fun
bonking I don't know if it's worth it I
the supplies I don't know if it I'll do
my best it's fine I think it's worth it
there there's quite a bit of stuff in
those chests who yeah
wa my game laggy
oh there's a satchel over here where is
over here I am uh in the corner of the
pharmacy
room oh God there's
stuff oh my God I'm going insane
I I see it but I can't you can't touch
it are you in the garbage
shoot no it's like
like I tried from every
angle just can't get to it it's it's
elusive hates me can you break some
walls with your
axxe uh that would take like 30 minutes
I
think 5,000 Health oh it's night time
now I can carry stuff again oh yeah
night time long encumbered I love night
time yeah no longer encumbered at night
time it's so
[Music]
good what it's a it's a perk from a book
you have to learn it but it's so
nice wait which what perk again it's one
of the
nightstalker magazines it lets you not
be encumbered when at night time yeah oh
nice wait how do I even get
out oh okay this is this this is mine uh
B did you check the one at the hole the
hole where's the hole Yeah okay come
with
me I was just where you
were I
sure strength me shotguns for range oh
Str one eternity later actually don't
come with me I have no idea where the
whole one
sec uh you know the hole on the floor
the that that leads us downstairs yeah
f are you also still in there what over
here I'm on the roof still looking for
the I don't know if I'm going to find it
though do you not even know if it's up
or down but I think it would be here and
it's not showing you the meters either
no yeah it doesn't show it for me
either did you check in the underground
cuz mine was previously hidden quite
well in the underground oh
like on a shelf on top of one it's okay
I don't need to finish the quest yeah
it's okay I feel like it's going to take
too long we could just go home okay if
it's if it's here though how do you get
off the dang
roof um well we got to get up here
ladder
jump I found I found nine sewing kits
for you
Kiara oh wow magum so lucrative oh
Magnum I'm glad I opened it up and
Magnum rounds for beo
yay I'm very cucum though okay I'm going
to make you a letter
Sears
go once we get home can you guys anybody
who has glue and Claw fragments and
sewing kits and duct tape and arm parts
all of those into the forge chest please
and I'll get cooking thank you you're
welcome there was one
here oh nope thank you it's okay we can
just go
home here's your Magnum round
here oh I'll see at the house I'll give
him to you there yeah I'm going to go
there too
now time to bring all
this okay okay oh people my GPS
GPS put I'll go the right way for sure I
can make it I have
remember I'll meet you
outside GG's working hard on refor the
old
base I'm making a moat and a zombie just
came down here but there's no spikes
down here
yet make sure to only make one row of
spikes down there so we can pick up the
loot yep cuz otherwise loot spawn one
time okay you go oh this one thank you
yay get him
entrenches yeah dire wolves can jump
though and there are jumpy ones so we
got to prepare for them
too this is the right
way if I go to the
right I hope I can meet the snow Trader
today
uh I wonder how many Traders there are
maybe like let me let me put a marker
there and then maybe I can share the
Waypoint with you that would be cool if
possible okay how do I share a wayo you
might not be able to it might be
impossible is
somebody who has been investing in
shotgun crafting
Mo yeah can you make one for crony cuz
she been she has been investing a little
bit into strength and she wants a range
weapon doesn't have to be the best
shotgun just anyone you know I can make
one similar to the one I'm using right
now okay it's still pretty
good
awesome so many shotgun
users oh Faun figured it out yesterday
you can share W points is that so yeah I
put a way point down I don't know how to
share it but I put the way point down
for the snow Trader guy let me see if I
can find
it hello to share way points you go to
your map and you click on the Waypoint
and then you click on the the icon
that's a bunch of people standing next
to each other which says share
Waypoint oh smart fauno with the strats
thanks comes back shares knowledge do
okay I think I shared it doesn't
elaborate I mean want to Shared marker
books with you oh
don't oh we're in the tunnels yeah I
know it's our garage I parked it in the
garage oh good nice won't get bird poop
on
it yeah that's never
fun hard to clean off the
windshield
okay what a lovely home we've made
here I love my home
it's a solid home it's
homey
yeah oh God I'm in the tunnels
too
hey welcome to the tunnel the heck no
thank
you dump my loot cozy in here I got some
things you will like but I got to make
more forg Steel
steel Club parts that's big I'm going to
need those later I'll put them in
here just need three more handgun parts
and I can make an
[Music]
SMG I'm take uh some of this forged
steel if you guys don't mind may I take
30 forged
steel okay thank you I'll make it up to
you guys I'll keep cooking more Steel
hold on math is hard for
me there we
go I can think it guys 10 hobos play
10 oh what what what what do you think
they made what do you think they what
are the nutritional facts of that hobo
St can you I'm I'm very particular about
my diet could you like tell me exactly
is it ethically it's very nutritionally
balanced okay yes no
questions only answers thank
you
[Music]
okay what's this Advanced mled
connector yay I'm home yay
[Music]
spring oh G did you see the wonderful
interior
design vaguely did you do something new
to
it
yeah I guess I didn't look hard enough
what did you
add so manys it has we have wooden
wooden walls now very pretty why would
you do that cuz I want it to be Cottage
core Dad don't laugh at me Cottage
boore we are out here working the entire
day we come home cold for man yeah I'm
working very hard too in the mines where
where where I don't see it I don't I
don't see anything we're not staying at
that home oh I have to be so far away
from my family to even here okay okay um
I'm back we never see
noways make her such a better one if I
have a few more shotgun
parts you were here then how could you
say it's attack M messed up sorry I just
like feeling like I'm there because I
miss
everyone a a that's sweet we miss you
too you should come into this hole with
me I'm good yeah it's okay don't worry
I'll pass on that one really interested
in that
oh there's arrows in my chest if you
want some oh thank you I got it did
everybody drop off their glue and stuff
and cloth and will I should I put it in
the next to the forge Kiara Forge chest
yeah okay thank you have wood oh never
mind I yeah I've always got wood I
do never mind morning and night why is
all
laggy
submit I will drop off what I
have the garage I got four glue that's
got to be worth
something glue that is worth something
yeah all right I'm going to try and find
aine gun parts I don't know if you use
that if someone uses
that uh I do I don't know if I still
need some but yeah oh actually I might
need it okay I'll bring it to you might
actually okay my crafting table that
could be helpful machine gun here behind
you
[Music]
um if you if you get a new weapon can I
have your hand me down yeah okay nice oh
okay if you're going to take kar's hand
me down then I'll give my hand me down
to crony yeah that's she does okay yes
I'm fine with either cool where's the
croner just want to shoot anyone need
steel Club Parts steel uh I'm going to
need them I think so probably put them
in the box I'll put them in the
box which
box to
say yo okay I'm going to start cooking
soon I'm already cooking constantly why
is the door locked yeah what is the door
locked
crap crap crap crap more
more I feel like even this would not be
mod that's crazy oh someone's making a
rifle here what is
this somebody cooking a gun a
rifle yummy what what kind of rifle is
that it's a shotgun it's a pump action
shotguns
oh
[Music]
enemies okay screamer in the house oh
that's no good I want to shoot her but I
don't want to shoot you girls good job
how'd she get in here what was that I
may have left the door
open okay we're welcoming visitors
generally uh when is the for coming day
35 5 10 p.m. 3510 p.m. okay a lot of
time then the lights really turned off
all right uh cron here's some
ammo hold
up take on I can make
more the other
one get you
more that should help I have plenty
I know why I separated it like that that
was
weird that we have
[Music]
twoes all right new gun needs about four
minutes to
cook so excited is that the best one you
can make or so no uh there's one level
higher I
believe where is the food chest I have
three points there any where it say it's
in the
middle the
fire I think by the Yeah the
fire oh natural healing might be good
but Olympic champion I don't think I
want this club after
all is a
club uh where did it go uhoh
where the heck did it go I just need one
more point to be an Olympic champion
anyone still have armor crafting
parts let's see not on me
[Music]
currently maybe we can search the
Traders tomorrow see if we can find some
yeah wa she should you wear I'll still
look for more shotgun part see if I can
make the twins a strong shotgun
too so I'll look around
tomorrow oh actually it's about to be
the next day
[Music]
convenient what level are your feet and
hands probably not so good yeah I think
yeah I want them to run around with a
shotgun it could be
hilarious I am worried about getting
shot by those
to armor for oh
okay
four these should go else these Springs
need to be in here your sandals let them
cook let
cook just a bit
longer also I also have primitive armor
by the way my my Ranger stuff died it's
gone it's done
for okay um wonder if I can repair here
make better stuff do I really get armor
parts from these things too CH can but
what do I I think I need a kit repair
kit a ranger
outfit what I need what I need level one
is really unnecessary I'm just going to
get rid of
these yeah the rate is day 35
yes I wonder if the pig
respawned you want to go fight him I'm
going to go fight him
cool go punch him fist him fist him real
good I will
yeah leave it the corner to fist the pig
I really have enough meat though what we
need is I'll get grass from that stuff
yeah I eat food so I'm going to take
some of we need a diet yeah I don't know
how to get
seeds
SE there's so many zombies at our old
house I'm equipped to to protect myself
into the
boat into the boat take some of this
rations oo fall fall into the
moat yeah shouldn't they be hitting
those spikes though we have a lot of
broken spikes have't haven't repaired
yet I see
scrap scrap that's right I can make
cornbread
too scrap scrap scrap
it I'm scrapping the whole armor chest
pretty much because all of those armor
parts are low level and they and they
give me armor parts back when I scrap
them oh ni yeah I think that's a better
use for now no Pig no Pig maybe he got
stick of your [\h__\h]
Pig he's done with you yeah I guess so
he's had it guess will just give me
grass wonder if we can make stronger
tools as
well my pump shotguns
done
yippe have fun with it I'm
excited oh three mods I can load three
mods in do it
nice see what we
got some more worth repairing recommend
it but not these
right it's good to clean up I think and
then I'll just make everyone The Meta
combination that I
have cuz they probably don't know what
they want either long barel
use asky ni it's
okay I think that's
it
okay need to read
this okay let's
start tell me please what up the what
armor parts you have currently I mean
what what's your armor on what level my
armor is pretty random right now I have
an Assassin outfit level three mhm I
have preacher gloves level three and I
have Commando boots level three
mhm and the nerd goggles level two l two
okay maybe a hat for you is most
important right now I
think if I could get uh something like a
ranger your outfit would be nice if you
you want Ranger outfit okay I think I
think it's better for me I'm not sure
because I used the bow but I don't know
I'm not an expert hey Kiara make me
something cool too please I'll pay you
back I just need more Alo Parts we'll
see how far we get with this wello you
can you can take care of my first
because I am more like a support no no
no no no you you need armor more than I
do trust me and that's not that I'm not
trying to be mean Callie what uh then
tell me what are what are your pun
what's what's your stuff right now what
level uh I'm I'm using primitive because
the Ranger stuff that I had broke oh
no there's a lot of armor in the armor
thing oh
yeah no I took it all and I scrapped it
oh because it's all useless it was all
like level one oh okay and they give me
armor parts which I can make to make
more armor crafting kits uh call is
there
too those are easy to make some tank
Ranger fine too I think ranger set yeah
are you sure I wonder what would be good
for shotgun what do you guys
think H I'll let you
know okay I'll let you know
biker biker that'd be pretty cool oh I
have I put a biker armor in the armor
chest oo
so if you want a biker outfit there's
one in there heck yeah I mean I fit the
bill I've got a spiked bat and a shotgun
it's just level one i' better make you a
better biker outfit and scrap this one
yeah I want to be a biker Bad to the
Bone yeah Bad to the Bone thank you K is
pretty good I'll be
waiting okay I'm just I don't think I
can make it a max level one but maybe
four or five level is good that's
perfectly fine sick
wheelie sure am a
biker can't wait to make a
motorcycle but you oh mini bike is mini
bike not good enough for you no I just
I'm excited about you know motorcycle
possibilities too yeah I can already
make one but I feel like it's kind of a
waste of my resources right now
understandable we need more resources
maybe in season 2 everybody will
become a real biker game
cation
y yay go okay let's start with cie's
setup uh I'm getting food just in case
we need extra food you never have enough
food we have le keep up the good
work uhoh
the tricks I can't make stuff my the
wheelies Ranger outfits or handguns and
rifles AKA Sheriff type handguns and
rifles am
mind um
clever what's best source of
lever BS and stuff
pigs I wonder oh I could probably SC the
pigs the little ones might have
respawned maybe scrapping couches too
so CES so far leather couches give
leather the Harrison nearby have fancy
leather
couches you can scrap yeah our neighbors
are not using their couch anymore yeah
uh K how many
um um vehicle Adventures do you
need uh another 23 23 that's all you buy
I'll buy this one no not yeah everyone
counts every single one she really wants
to kill those BS oh armor armor parts we
need that right then I'll buy that arm
part is he selling leather too three uh
leather let me check
you know I I'm going to Detroit there as
well let see what I can
find I need two more handgun any leather
I see blue and sewing kit do you want me
to buy that too yeah yeah the more
marer I can go to don't be happy in my
backpack okay let me get them oh Springs
did you need Springs SM oh Springs are
always good we have a lot of home though
we have a ton of Springs oh we have a
ton okay and shotgun parts did you need
that still
what was that shotgun parts yeah I was
about to buy I'm right behind you oh oh
you take it then was going to grab them
oh let me just buy this and then put
them somewhere you can never get them I
still owe Vio 400 bucks or handun parts
I the old house has Le got
you a g you're at the old house right
now yeah can you check if there's any
leather
anywhere okay thank
[Music]
you
oh I already know how to I already have
a metal
chain put somewhere
though
ooh that was a big boom
outside
ow let walk into them shouldn't have
brought so much
there's a can of salmon in here for the
fish tacos fish tacos fish
tacos
nice I love tacos there is one
leather oh wow let's take
it Crucible is so expensive oh my gosh
all right got it though we already got
it y' zombies is mini horde by the way
outside mini
H
oh how much maybe not that
much mini mini H outside the
house might need some
help H I'm fine for now I'm very far
away I got to go meet Trader Hugh now I
think we all should be able to do that
Quest if I'm able to do it
just on your own
time they're breaking our doors though
oh I'm coming oh oh that's
bad our poor
[Music]
door how much money do you
have uh
1,500 can you um buy the vle
magazine we're so close to getting a car
I have one vehicle magazine what if
people goes to a bank and lock pick you
can get 10 to
15K oh I need I need long pixel cuz I'm
like totally out of them okay I'll see
if some Traders are selling them you're
welcome I've never seen an ATM in this
game before why are we whispering
sometimes in the grocery stores I
think I
think I've seen
some that's rob a
bank I still have 10,000 on
me oh that's a lot of money money right
now no need
any okay I think H is
over okay pal successfully defended
wow when we all go
away thank
you are we going to raid this shamway
building maybe that's the final mission
that we
do the shamway factory yeah it's really
high level huh yeah looks impossible
which is why it would be a perfect final
mission for a season probably lots of
food in there oh yeah all the yum yums
I mean we can try if you want to we have
to know what it's made out of we just
feel like they're just churning zombies
through a wood chipper in
there I hope not I got to know the
answer to the
mystery I need to go to the second Traer
oh my gosh so far
away yeah they do be spread far apart
you mean Trader Jen yeah oh come with me
I I can pick you up on my bike oh okay
uh you're still at direct I'll come over
to
you yes I'm
the you get a taste of this mini
bike wait am I going the right way no
probably not am
I does it matter how come I still don't
know the directions
so okay it's difficult I always use the
checkpoints because I get lost all the
times do we
have Jen also has shotgun part a little
bit oh she does heck yeah yeah I'm go
pick those up I need some money though
I'll grab them to thank you for letting
me know I'll go grab I can buy them I
have I have quite a bit of money really
now I owe now I owe you money and bi boo
money there you are yeah get off on baby
let's go give me a
ride you beautiful lady oh I'll hit the
house first oh can you get on I'm
trying it says repair or
honk oh okay unlock it for you then
to there you go now you can get in I
think are are are we using cloth as fuel
on purpose are we who someone someone
put cloth in the fuel so I'm taking it
out our precious
resource burn that save the
club it's okay cloth isn't my most
needed resource right now
but before you know it we will run out
of
it oh Jen just said thank you so much so
kindly we should protect her so nice she
is nice Honestly though I I the Traders
have so much space like such a
big base it's
insane should give us that base we
should take it over actually yeah it and
we should like yeah yeah I mean we're
like there's so many of us there just
one Traer in each of those we can you
think any to do that
before yeah yeah are they
Invincible yeah yes they are you cannot
kill they should be it would be really
fun like if they allowed that but it's
really really difficult what if she has
like insane what if you kill all the
Traders and it's
over yeah what if you kill one Trader
and then the other Traders are like I I
won't sell to you anym and then you have
to do a long line of quests to explain
there was a mistake and that you were
overtaken by grief was it a mistake
though was it but they don't have to
know that they don't have to
know no it was not
see of course not we shouldn't kill Jen
though we should kill the guy with the
ma with the car parts then we can have a
car wonder how how we can make lock
picks I wonder if there's a way wait
there probably is a
way cuz then we can if somebody could
make a ton then be go rob a bank and it
would be
sick I'm I'm uh I'm trying to put more
skill points into the loot
stuff so every time I get like a per
percentage
more oh you can do
it I see this
shle your Uber is doing her best I see
you give me good rating I give I give
you the best the best rate I would hope
so
ah yeah you have to have the see you
rate rate me on your phone before you
leave the car
five okay okay now I now I feel treated
though so I'm not going to do that
anymore well then I
shall I shall crash you into this
mountain ah my bike is too
good don't do
it I hope you feel SI
you I will lock people I am aimless what
are you doing hello I'm going to the
Traders oh okay thank you for the ride
though very kind of you you're
welcome one star still good man I heard
that hello beautiful
lady glue
be might be
[Music]
useful B what what why did you want coal
oh I wanted to make some good water but
I found it but uh don't don't use you
more coal don't use coal or cloth for
fuel by the way cuz I found them in
there do you have a good use for coal um
I think generally coal is for the good
water that I was making in bulk and I
think you make you can help me make
bullets I think it's one of the
components for bullets like gunpowder or
something like that I'm not sure okay
yeah it's gunpowder I'm making a St but
yeah don't use it as
fuel
mhm got you understood
what do we have anything
good
perhaps uh Lea no of course not a weapon
right no glue no wow have you got
anything for me
lady no NOP no no no I got nothing
much we only have two lock picks so far
yeah I don't know how to craft them I
want robber
Bank me too know wouldn't that be cool
yeah if only it were that
simple where's my other Quest supposed
to go
to I
guess what have I not seen Bob yet
thought I did you have seen
Bob the only one you haven't met is
hug hug H look well that was nice
job is there a place you want to go to
next otherwise I'm going to Bob yeah I
come to you okay okay I'm putting two
vehicle adventures and a shotgun Messiah
into the heck yeah books box I will be
taking the shotgun
one and then shotgun parts as
well let's go does anybody I put them
before you on the floor thank you what
what are you going to do next somebody
else read them well I'm very I'm feeling
a little bit aimless right now I just
went and thought I got a bunch of seing
kid and glue but you want to try to
gather leather okay killing animals
animals I guess and then you need to use
like I think the bone knife do you have
a bone knife no but I saw some in the
chest okay I think that's you have to
use it and then you got to maybe
Le couches and stuff but I think just
going for Animals is faster okay better
okay I can do I realized I have
absolutely no lever and without lever I
can't make good armor let me see crony
do you want to go there is a lot cooking
okay I'll I'll do that thank you that
will be
helpful perfect yeah animals faster
right they do give quite a bit maybe try
close by to our new house there's the
the bores
and bores and corn place oh right yeah
there's a lot of boes in there what was
that again K there's 77 leather in this
crate oh okay but that's still probably
not quite enough a bit more would be
good F can you mark where the the your
favorite places the the bors the bors
it's literally just north of the new
house you'll see it has big farm okay I
see it if you scrap office chairs also
you can get
leather okay okay sorry Kiara but your
office chair has got to go oh no good
very good
chair of and then I'm
putting armor I'm going to the new Traer
oh cool the
arm I want to meet him
too I'm putting armor pots into the
armor chest okay thank seven and glue
and okay okay
noce too bad you can't make leather from
zombies why would we be able to make
that
huh Le well they have they have skin
yeah yeah that's not a bad idea so you
can make leather out of humans probably
human
leather that is
true huh it's technically a thing huh
cool
soill Ross going turn on the
radio driving through the the radio
show no I fell into the
hole are you back in the tunnel
CE no I'm I I'm where people fell
earlier the
moat the mo he's going to get a lot of
lawsuits from all the holes she's
digging where we're dying falling into
holes put any spikes in that one so it's
okay it's not so bad
[Music]
yeah could be worse yes could be spikes
in make sure that you
SW still there do bears have leather do
you think I think so
yeah just got to use the bone knife oh
my gosh this place is dangerous there
Bob
where talk to
me what's wrong with you is there
lag yeah I think
so oh yeah oh
God go oh my God I just melted into the
floor as everyone does when there's a
bit of
lag
interesting I got so much glue for
you really yeah duct tape I've got parts
tools and
wheels my
transmission
nothing should I got motorcycle parts
bundle
yeah why
not oh people you're here hello what's
up how are you doing ah he gave me
[Music]
that is a bear I'm
shopping a bear I already had these
bear God bears are so scary well if
scary why hug
shap no that's it's just not true if
evil why
friendship why did they ever make teddy
bears bears have always been frightening
ter terrifying
creatures of Destruction they always
been so cute looking and you want to H
make a cat
plusy you hug them aren't you very
durable you can hug them is this a baby
bear or
[Music]
something cuz I
think oh did you did you punch the bear
once he di you killed the baby bear
try that's messed
up cool oh these must be small bearss
right I know a
child you killed a child child two child
Bears whoa you killed two child
bears kill more kill more isn't there a
bigger bear oh you're killing their
family there's no way that's the same
bear I fought
before oh he's got the B not respawn
there's no Boris here guys yeah maybe
they
don't I is there something specific you
want to do cuz I'm probably going to
just go back
home I'm sorry puppy dog wait k Ki and
ra do you want to do this Quest my quest
nearby since we're
Clos okay it's uh South South East
Southwest of yeah yeah
yeah I can't afford anything but I'm
looking
yeah this Trader has great Stu I am Uber
right now yeah you
are you change your opinion quickly
about
me never
[Music]
Chang to you B I saw you going
down come back up United shotgun
[Laughter]
part try harder did you trying to steal
her from me what's going on huh why does
no one like
digging creepy it's really filling you
have KY while you're at it maybe make
some like Towers like platforms for
shooting in every
[Music]
direction you think I can do it um I
think this is it the place uh yeah it's
around this way
[Music]
okay I feel feel bad every time for
killing the animals
yeah wow I can it's okay they they had a
really bad life they didn't like their
mom bear they were like she never lets
me play my video games so B killed the
mom bear
yesterday that's mess up do you guys
have an idea there might be a different
Farm does anyone know have one on that
map you go by what if I just lead them
all out there's spars in the tundra you
can
find oh okay is this the
prison planning to die huh
well just give it a shot right
yay so satisfying every time where could
there be leather oh this is also a s
Quest by the way oh okay okay keep my
eyes open and peeled we'll do it the
coward's way
oh oh that's a lot of hissing oh
hello M I'm already so full again what's
going on oh weapon shops are
good
really all of these shops dang this
really this is going of aw wow I can
make my SMG now yay this gun's really
good okay we're going to the tundra and
going to try to kill some
beers do they give that have you tried
yeah they do okay okay I don't know how
much they give I have 29 right now that
doesn't seem that
much I feel like sofas might give more
leather than b killing a what if we find
what if we find like an office building
m
yeah Leather So tons ofes in the shotgun
range yeah we we looking for leather for
K
cow nice I'm the only one in here so
it's fine to be a
coward oh no is it a kitty I can't fight
the
kitty is it a big cat oh let's go
H where's the rest of the place I am
alone so where's the rest of the place
it's okay for cowardice maybe somewhere
downstairs again where is the rest of
the
bag is it over here got
rules oh yeah there's some people
here we killed a bunny success I hope a
bunny has leather I'm not
sure watch out behind you
[Music]
easy
easy more
trash I need to find my my bag yeah me
too distance just casually solo leveling
don't worry about me oh this place is
way bigger than oh there's a lot watch
out there's the rest of the place oh you
over there
some head
shot these
I reload reload oh he woke up
again
o yay yay
it feels like the W
baby door combat's my favorite comat oh
my God oh my God be
[Music]
careful at least there's no vomit
zombies God how many lives do these have
yeah it's very strong they keep on
getting back up again
Phoenix like
qualities in
here
I what hello it will not die
no not
nice nice
nice let's go
maybe yeah this place is Big I'll L
[Music]
end oh military chest ooh o hunting
knife that's maybe a better KN parts
interesting hey was someone making a
machete oh I already made one you made
one okay so you don't well I'll still
keep the parts just in case you want to
upgrade fuy
do that was frightening I can't believe
I got out of that
oh oh I think I found a better wrench
for
you for me yeah it's a ratchet I think
it's like the
next higher tier wo
oh I'll be careful C over there what
what what's going on Callie there's a
bear trying to this the biggest bear
I've seen in my life trying to enter the
shotgun range and he can't get through
the
door stay safe KY I can kill him kill it
get it yeah there's a lot of Le right
there that's probably the grandpa of the
Bears that oh you already did probably
the grandpa of the Bears has been
killing when the entire family has been
wiped
out this gun is insane let me see if I
can make one of these for foko that that
helped him a lot behind you behind
you n what weapons are foko using
shotguns I believe oh okay
slave I'm I'm beding he wasn't a part of
the mission though he just heard the
commotion OU OU OU out maybe all the
enemies are dead now no they're
still a
guy I got a okay now it's all it's y now
we need to find
our Satchel did you guys find me yet
fine I haven't got my Satchel yet oh
Kiara here take this it might be it's
probably
better I also have something for you I
think how about getting all the leather
for Kiara this oh thank
you cuz it says 9 mm I'm guessing that's
good for you herey take this
tool
oh oh ratchet I'm coming back does it
work the same way
H must be a place I haven't
got I have too much stuff so I wasn't I
wasn't going to be questing anyway but
yeah I'll be driving back a robotic I
found a shotgun choke mod I don't know
if you need oh that yeah maybe if you
could grab that for me I'll definitely
take a look at it okay oh I I literally
found a turret I think this is a turret
oh nice a whole turret it's a melee
turret it's a punting Ro
wow wow tier four class
nice oh yeah I'm on a quest right now
yeah I found a turret
nice I might need some help
here what do you need help with there's
still a important looking
chest that's makes it easier cracked
open oh oh my God sorry
smashed your
skull any dudes up here oh
you oh yeah almost missed B that's
really bad
yeah
Bo there's got to be something
good got to be something good what maybe
a whole
helicopter or a whole
car how's the orange mold doing is she
having a good time digging orange mole
how are you
doing oh uh ra here is I'm I'm knocking
down trees now than where's G orange
orange I have some stuff for you
yay if you could bring a delivery of
food food and repair
kit blushing batting my
eyelashes yeah I'm walking very slowly
to
you I see you does that hurt
sometimes can you take this deep um nice
take
this thank
you oh my God we're digging um take this
ooh
wait what else do you want repair kid
take
this thank you why don't you take this
too I want to open oh my God a blueberry
P ooh some
chili um take these nice thank
[Music]
you is there anything else you want do
you want some
testosterone yeah yeah yeah some
testosterone testosterone extract
from
bears what did you do there this maybe
the poor Bears o thank
you do you want to look at my what I've
done so far yeah give me the Tor here
okay so bad I have laid Spikes all
outside and I'm planning to make them
three tall but they're all around now
uh-huh so don't fall in there's a dog
yeah don't fall in all right I'm going
to die and then what I've been working
on for the past hour is is I finally
made the mode on the back side and it's
too wide and very deep uh do you see it
I'm hold on I'm going to come over I'm
really
slow oh I'll just take my bike over okay
okay okay I took the rest barely let's
go I need to find my do you see it down
there oh
yeah it goes all the way around wow and
then there's a little entrance you can
walk into the house here but you'll
probably die to the other spikes I'll
get rid of them actually these are
useless where is the exit you have been
busy this is impressive really hard
thank you and now new problem I I'll be
digging much better that's freaking
thank you thank you me
too that was awesome good loot doll
Harden chest what I want more wood now
this item need repair ah hey uh would
anyone with a lockpick love to come get
a ton of really amazing loot at the shot
you are going to need to smack it that's
what we did I you can't wait at the
shotgun Messiah
what shun Messiah yeah no we we we just
did did a tier four class and we had to
smack that chest so you're going to have
to smack that chest okay are lockpicks
not allowed oh it's allowed but we don't
have any I I can find my S have you
found yours uh I'll you haven't found
did you check your
radar some antibiotic there should be a
there should be a satchel
icon oh my god there a mannequin my arm
and if there's arrow down or up then
that means you have to go up or
down we're going to be here a while I
can see the Rader that you're talking
about uh do you have a bag icon anywhere
like if you look around there's bag oh
yeah I see now yeah go close to it yeah
yeah yeah okay okay okay let me just go
and on the top right of your screen
there should be a meter thing going up
and down depending on if you're getting
closer or further away all right I see
it no
okay oh it was so close when I was
like yeah I couldn't see it it was sorry
it was so small I
mean yeah I know if this chest is going
to be worth it guys people do you know
the exit
uh yeah I can't find it is there usually
good stuff in there maybe that way yeah
this
way brute for it should be here oh I
found it
yay oh
oh do you guys need back shot or can I I
don't think anybody's using that
ammo okay leave there I'm going to go to
the tra room and then go
home yeah I'm waiting for you l I'm
coming for the
assets can't take the stuff at least I
got the lever
I've got a bunch of stuff I'm going to
drop off at home hey Kiara are you able
to make lockpicks by chance
uh not better than anybody else I think
ah yeah I have I don't have it unlocked
so I cannot make them sadly lock pick
uh oh it is at the
workbench actually I feel like I've seen
it some lockpicks in our chest too
there's like two I
think are you good L I am looking for a
way to go out I can't you have to go
through the the weapon shop uh cuz we
went or jump the F oh I found it I found
it yeah 25% we're practically halfway
there 25% is not halfway there there we
go oh I'm finally out a bear shows up S
into the bike oh back back back back oh
there you are let's go home about to
the quest let's go yeah hello
Bob welcome got the Duke well now you
can Str sit almost end of day
32 we're getting closer ladies we are
I'll just turn to my quest tomorrow
should be fine you need some money well
that's better than a sharp I might have
a hand me down if you
[Music]
still what
happened I just fell into a canyon with
my bike she could fly in this game she's
so used to it he could not I was going
to say uh if you're still interested in
using machine guns I have a hand me
down I think he's trying to break in
here yes oh sorry I yeah yes please I am
currently looking for leather and I will
maybe you can put it are you at the
house see where you are uh no not right
now but you'll get it by the time the ra
happens for sure okay okay nice thank
you I just found a thingy so I read it
so that's really
nice my hammer got
[Music]
faster how do you heal
concussion uh painkillers oh okay yeah
which is not how it works in real
life okay I guess just put that on there
I'm sure it'll
work yeah know this gun is super
op very
exciting might go for the money seems
like you found something cool
Mar h I want to make one for other
people
hello yeah take I can buy a cash
register oh what you can buy a
[Laughter]
don't maybe I can own a little shop I
have the trade routes Quest yippe
yay but not today I think today Q has
unlimited shotgun parts I wonder if he
has other Unlimited uh parts for weapons
and such you has unlimited shotgun parts
wow that's
op unlimited
baby so I can make more of these really
powerful
guns 56 and hand them off to to some of
the others
bye
H how's your Thro are you okay I'm doing
my best
don't don't force your voice toor you
can dig all the way over here connect it
do you see it yeah yeah yeah yeah let's
go on the other side and then we can
meet G scared it's okay down please
don't reset the chest down if I use my
bath I will dig and meet you
guys
okay my back could do it yeah are we
still defending at the old house yeah it
won okay yeah it's still staying strong
think about my
home actually I would like I would like
to make a vault can we maybe go to the
new
house wait what what's the tunnel for
the new house
for it's the garage ah it's like a
secret secret lb you put your car in
there of the the bat's doing it faster
classic not the spikes Hur oh
no and the spikes are a little
dangerous
yeah we're already halfway
dead oh no we just hit this like
[Music]
once maybe in time to
hit oh my God
what am I going the right way
now crony and I have been hitting a
hardened chest for five
minutes me too I'm hting it with
my this better be worth it it'll be so
worth it F1 no tier four quests are fun
yeah of these locations are
[Music]
good we don't have much
food that's dangerous too everywhere's
dangerous am I st Escape do I'll take
you out don't wor treasure map and five
lock this was definitely worth
it
[Music]
y thank
you you can also I'm trying okay come
here oh did you see these spikes over
here oh you're still in the hole oh
yeah it's working as
intended there you are okay
and then wow do you see all the spikes
outside yeah it was
impressive these spikes I'm trying to
make them three tall so if you can put
these spikes and then make them like
this three tall all the way around
here's all the spikes I have on me I
have to restart my game okay
okay
wa Mommy
let's go in the house and grab some food
first though before we
[Music]
dieing if anyone
has Springs I just need a few more to
craft my SMG are we Adam Springs I
thought we had quite a few quite a
lot did you check in all the typical
chest
uh I'm looking right now it's not in the
Forge
one I think there might be in the other
like random looking
chests I I I saw like 50 or so I know
someone else was using Springs too
though so they might have used it yeah
oh oh never mind it's in the vehicle
test I found it yay
SMG there is a safe here oh my gosh it
takes 30 minutes to make an
SMG well we have time we have time we
have
time 30 minutes 30 minutes run for my
team I've broken my
lockpick oh shoot let's do that oneing
back take your time I'm trying to find
something to drink I think I can get
from the bending oh I have I have uh
Waters with me oh thank you I'll get
some your full AO I'm almost back
someone else can use this baseball
bat is a
good be way better really
okay people can you uh make ammo I feel
like the time is getting closer and may
you need ammo of all kinds I will start
to work on
ammo need everything
[Music]
who's this Quest
maybe
not how do we get it we can't quite make
it stuck Pap
here you can take these building blocks
and you can stack them on each other and
you can pick them up too again where's
my bike building there is a lot of
Shoto in the ammo to put them on top I'm
pretty sure okay thank you my thank you
for help me I don't know I don't think
did this
a check around the corner I'm very I
can't even run anymore Dude Where's My
Car hey you guys took the same Mission I
just did I think he took my bike not too
close no I haven't took your bite I
can't oh he took it he took it oh he
took your B no
oh yeah bio just took it what took what
uh the same Quest that I just did that I
just
soloed yeah oh behind by the way finding
a moment to mention that I soloed that
Quest this is hard
sick I found we found Silver Nugget we
actually found this was actually worth
it it took 10 minutes but I almost died
though I found some we found some armor
parts if anybody wants to go with me to
dig up treasure the treasure might have
money and uh yeah I will dig with you
yay GG want to dig
GG okay we can bring full m too yeah
okay nice I'll come dig too I like to
dig can you pick us up yeah I'll pick
you up I mean I might buy the
house okay don't worry about it did kill
a massive evil bear hand them was
awesome
give me some water ah yeah of course
he's not night though right there you go
water we
can we can just like walk around I don't
know in the meantime and loot something
around what level is your shotgun
Callie um the one I have now two okay
okay is it double barrel no it's a it's
a pump action the helmet you can give
that one to someone though yeah I put I
put another double barrel shotgun in the
chest so someone can use that
cool there are lots of dire wolves just
running around in the snow by the way so
just be careful oh my
God specifically at night I
think maybe it's okay
though
you're I need to put some more on that
corner one go
down right there yeah that's probably a
good stuff for
it I'm ready B boo whenever you are okay
con's using a shotgun right in the
corner there yeah cor is yeah all uh we
can
reach there is a really good shotgun in
in the corner time to it one
yeah that's a big
Bo we Whispering it's not like the
zombies can hear okay F you want to come
the zomes not here no they don't have
ear
holes just have to make some ear holes
then yeah with my shotgun I'll gladly
oblig
absolutely right this
way let's continue going around the
[Music]
way the house is the most important
attack
s there
[Music]
Troublesome also I got a bunch of
leather I'm going to put in the thing
what do you try to make with the leather
Kiara
ni I think they moved to Quest or
something oh
yeah just need to drop some things off
real quick
we'll be
fine we'll be fine my eyes haven't
adjusted that's looking good
though zombies are pretty brave for a
place like that though know
oh yeah oh do you want to do this tier
four clear quest to
people yes let's let's do that real fast
I'll I'll do just really quick you guys
close out uh Let's do let's do the
treasure first so that way we'll give
Callie some time to come over
yeah okay sounds good I'll make my way
over there in a sec we dig your treasure
[Music]
y oh oh B oh you want to get
it
um I'm sorry
piggy what you do to the pig drive by
drive
by oh no Are we almost there we're
almost there okay I thought we got stuck
in the in the spikes ourselves okay wow
it's okay so stand stand right
here mhm and
then this is the perimeter oh no
yeah we in G G can you come here where
are you look where we are on the
map I don't know if I'll make it you you
might make it this might take us a while
digging for an hour what are you digging
for treasure
wait can you hand me the map oh I can't
uh I can't you you use the map started
yeah it's already okay cuz I have a I
have a mod I think that makes treasure
smaller oh I think I have a treasure mod
too do you have it too it's that wide
even with the yeah I have I have the
treasure Hunters
mod um D if you go to the new house
there are mini bikes there that you can
use to drive to us I thought
so not the right gu the mini bikes yeah
if you if you go to if you walk to the
new house there are mini there's a mini
bike at the new house which you can use
to drive to here can I dual moded is it
dual moded um I I don't know I don't
remember feel like I shouldn't I don't
want to leave the puppies at the house
alone with all these spikes there's
there's also there's also multiple bikes
so you guys can both take bicycles if
you
prefer okay there's a lot of bikes at
the new
house as long as it's spiky regulars
here are some more spikes I'll get a
bike for
us use 100 I need to turn is that's true
that doesn't make sense don't
need those here
do you think it's better to dig down
maybe I don't know maybe maybe we can
get
lucky wait that's Stone that's Stone
accident I shouldn't take that much
that's not fair Corners are kind of
funny huh maybe I'll start from directly
middle make a
present is better than
yeah we should have brought some juice
to
drink make oh oh digging from the middle
actually helped okay that's good wait
does it I think cuz it doesn't work
middle of the
radius uh do we need do we need bones
for anything
Mountain yes like okay we probably have
a lot but they are useful they are super
useful
ow I know where to run I'm trapped it's
okay I got it I got it you got it yeah
what
I don't
know maybe too far reg R
iron D I could have sworn we had regular
iron
[Music]
I'll cook get why does have to make S
scary
sounds please don't give me the PO
always scary at night
time I have tea if you get the poo poos
thank you I'm
gambling we know where it's oh I found
an ATM what did she say we can do with
an ATM h
ATM yeah didn't Kara say something about
an
ATM I don't know the bank or an ATM I
think you Lo pick it steal the
[Music]
money let me see a little break from
this
bik have food yeah where's the iron yeah
where's iron make for IR I think we
should eat
to I have this oh it just look like a
big
metal it's it the circle is getting
smaller so we're doing something
okay let me see what armor they
got scavenger outfit this I'm halfway to
the house
ni only halfway to the
house are you walking yeah I'm on foot
oh
no let's see let's see who's first they
getting to the house are we Finding the
Treasure
yeah extra one there yeah oh it's
different armor oh maybe my hat's in
trouble no that's fine they were really
cooking with this treasure digging mini
game yeah really they really made
something
here hold on my shoes digging in general
is like the the worst what do you
mean what no no what what do you think
about digging huh it's great and what
about earlier when you said you I feel
like that was uh I was just saying I was
just saying no one likes digging with me
I just don't know why oh you took it
personally yeah it was
personal
good what's wrong with digging it's yeah
it's look they like digging too di is
tiring though G is not tiring digging
is down down with the
digging what's wrong with digging it
said we're getting Clos yet hold let me
check the perimeter are we we're still
nothing wrong with digging you should
come and join us we're still in the
center we're still in the
center iron than I
thought I think we're getting close to
the end [\h__\h] maybe
maybe let's
see there's not going to be zombies that
can go through the cracks of the for
these we need steel
though pretty good H can you guys still
hear
me yes okay my power flickered and my
screens turned off
oh I
think don't get her M we're still
thirsty and hungry we're
thirsty hey guys how do you make Forge
steel it's not iron is it wait hold on F
I'm
broken are you broken stop digging no
you can keep digging I'm just
broken I see we need iron we really
don't have iron
huh Rara may I take your
iron think she's in the other call
[Laughter]
oh yeah I'm going deep right now I don't
know where I'm going going you can mine
it yeah with my great Stone
axe why is there like a fog around them
there I don't know was it always
there maybe it's because it's they
young I don't want to go to the tunnels
maybe they're
poison
okay where the rocks at
got to rock somewhere just like a grand
pirate hunting treasure Adventure yeah
I'm so immersed right now do you do you
did you you still haven't seen the
chest no hold let me let me let me check
where you are for a
second
um oh watch out ow
I'm here and all these bikes are locked
no there's one bicycle that's unlocked
how will I how will I bring through a
moco
here all
right I will help you guys dig and then
I
will M the bike so they aren't so stuck
in that one the house we got some iron
let's make some St I want to make new
house the away no no we're still using
that house but a lot of people are at
the new house for crafting and stuff I
see but it's not that far away righty
this is going to be the B that's not
super far away it's
not Crucible use Crucible [\h__\h] than a
Donkey Kong level steel can't for it why
in the movies there's always just an x
on the ground and right there is it cuz
I'm not you have to put the iron into
the smelter okay I got oh okay you right
on the border
[Music]
now so where is
theas please make the
steel
morning thought okay we out this place
here quick
where's if if you see Rock that's too
that's too low okay yeah sometimes
there's like tunnels of
dirt who's Judy
Witch good JY witch um oh yeah I
remember seeing
that driving by her house oh it's got to
melt first
gotcha oh okay I understand how it works
now okay we don't want to be it'ser oh
gig's almost
here there's a gigantic Mountain
separating us I'm climbing it like a
goat Traders have a bunch of iron
so
oh we's kind of weak
huh it's going to repair
it has to be
close okay it's a little close little
scary was this view
SMG I'm not going to touch it wait is it
done already no it's 6 minutes left oh
it said we're getting close again
fa where this way this
way hold we how are I supposed to get
out of here I think so we'll figure it
out I'm more excited to think of the
zombies that could get through this
what kind of talented zombies are there
out there maybe where are you guys nope
I see the
hole I'll It
Up Stand Back Kitt check out my iron
shovel I want to iron shovel my iron
shov leveling up just watch me through
all of this you're on the border wait
wait one shot this pick a different
direction there you go
wow you're so
good yeah yeah I
know wow oh my God wait wait border
again pick up go in this way Direction
This Way okay okay okay in on this way
Direction wow so fast yeah I I think in
in one more I can upgrade my shovel and
I can kill these blocks in one hit we
not being impressive yeah it would
really impressive mhm everyone would
want me they' be like ooh you can dig a
dirt block in one hit blushing oh wait
okay this way
Direction
ow did you get
hit in case what is weak what if it's
above us think I wonder
I know I worried about that
too don't worry I'll dig
up I was going to repair my
bike there oh I found
it oh and now now we have to smack it
open woohoo oh boy not my
bike still hungry we're still thirsty
classic
ow did you get
smack well somebody's bike got repair
here congratulations to
them does anyone know how to make a bath
B baton Bon I don't but I have a there's
there's baton Parts in the in the chest
in the B P at
home yeah I can make one oh I can make a
normal one too I'm looking for my
friends so I I made this thing a while
ago it's called Uh yay it better be
worth it repulsa mod so I'm looking for
a
St Bon St baton I'm pretty sure I saw
something like that in one there was
really no money in this last time there
was
5K do you want my 10,000 you can pretend
like it was a no I got there was a there
was a lot of ammo in here though so
that's
good nice there's my
bike let's see how I oh old cash is
Apparently one to one you sell old cash
for the coin yeah I didn't know that but
okay never mind it's okay there's money
in
here don't C dot dot dot me Chad I
know I got someone's bike got a nice
repair I got ammo
and weapon parts
okay should we go do the four clear okay
let's do it I'm coming I'm coming I'm
almost
there okay if you come do this tier four
I'll give you these shotgun parts o
really I love shotgun parts I'm making
shotguns for
everybody just I need steel I can't help
but but see the C is is pretty far from
SN I see I'm on my bike you don't
understand I feel as though you're
moving in the opposite direction wait
what you're not in a snow area no no
what oh all right go do your quest I
thought you guys were I thought you guys
were doing the quest that I soloed I saw
it said B boo wait D wait come back do
you want to do the quest with us
okay I was going to return to my hole
but we here just we're forcing you to
get out of the house family activity
before let me actually get some rocks
first hello
H I'm back um I've heard we run out of
steel
again and iron again right now but it's
because I'm trying to make a a shotgun
for oh yeah I used a bunch of Steel to
make a my SMG that's currently cooking
mhm the thing is I need that for good
armor too and now I want a gigg
yeah are you finished with what you're
doing no I'm still still
digging ladies I did you know that uh
when you find an iron or stone on the
Overworld oh yeah there's like a deposit
underneath yeah there's like a whole
iron vein underneath apparently usually
yeah I've got some it get you like 15K
of iron do you want me to get you some
iron yes please Weaver thank you Angel
Weaver my wife punched me I fle
again can't tell
theart my
life take this the beber time stop beber
time don't don't die you can keep some
Band-Aids
I don't want you to die okay okay you're
just what's everyone up to what are you
doing let me in you let me in we're
doing a quest
fast a quick Quest crony and I found you
now now stay seated 20 leather oh okay
okay that's good that's good
now so people looking for leather thank
you I put them next to also there's like
nine weapon parts now in the weapon box
no parts armor parts part
thank you're supposed to open at 4:00
a.m. open up you oh my God is it cuz
there a zombie out there's a zombie
outside but I'm scared I don't want to
go in here without you oh where are you
sorry I was just having a
toilet maybe we should EXT I am the
strongest in the game
I can finally put my stuff
there yay all right Lads I am now
Olympic champion level strength let's go
one
more in the corner down only a th make
it
taller who over oh on fire
burning yeah that looks
right maybe here what this is so
edgy oh do these valves not do anything
oh it doesn't turn it
off just for looks oh dear is that the
only one in
here you got iron Maxim
[Music]
security a for usually they don't
sell uh he might be selling forged iron
and forged
steel oh yeah he's got 7 Forge
steel maybe I should just spend my money
expensive it's apparently quite a
waste it's inside I don't know what it
is I can't get any closer huh the back
door back door oh oh okay okay try
reinforcing on that side I already did
maybe is like a dog like oh F this way
he's like you're going to do that Quest
alone okay
no bio still definitely has
this you have a quest that's at the Shak
of Messiah I didn't no yeah can you
wrench this what is this I think you can
wrench
that I think we my
gosh a bad dat please thank
you that's green
green I got over zealous with the
puning have a
question how do you improve the level of
a
weapon the level you have to craft a
higher level of the weapon you don't
upgrade the weapon you craft it oh okay
right in here if you jump oh my head is
so dazed from that
PL I see they're on the ground
do you need a med kit I okay first aid
kit I'm so
sorry I'll just lead them out here
wait do we go through the water room
this is what I don't know oh I think we
do oh all right uh can where where's the
weapon the weapon oh
oh how are you going to get
back uh maybe it's not an
idea like people there're zombies oh yes
yes zombies right here right
here is anyone doing a planning on doing
a quest I can't for a quest I have
nothing to do I think we're finished
reinforcing everything now okay we can
split let's go to VC to if you want to
do quests okay I don't I don't have any
quests but I can join a
quest okay okay I'll put this stuff back
in here okay I'm I be wait I'm dropping
you the weapon here okay thank you you
can drop it in the chest it's funny
though okay okay
[Music]
enjoy Also there's no new vehicle thingy
I think in the box and some other stuff
okay
thank you okay I'll be right back one
minute and then we can
go to
to I can supply to to bat if somebody
wants
one did you uh carry anything
interesting that I might need uh you can
check everything like pretty much
everything on my chest you can take
it oh should we the quest
should we try and search for
items quest for someone Quest okay owie
okay good stuff I can come back and hand
you a bike once I get out of
here I do we need up bik I don't think
my a is very inconsistent it'll be so
fast bikes are probably r
no let's redeem those
[Music]
let's make that there's a lot of zombies
in here
yeah this gun makes quests very possible
by the
way I wow you took a shot to the head no
problem that crazy over there you punch
me again oh no you didn't did I punch
you you you I die I might die hold
on was that's rude call your help the
other one assassin thank you we're
hungry
don't are very good A lot of
them for Plan
B I'm so oh no no I don't think it was
you I think it was a
zombie you're okay it is like a 50 50%
chance it was
you yeah this way boys now we're not
hungry but we're thirsty they're already
on fire they don't care it must be
really to begin
with Kelly for the bike outfit did you
want a full set or did you only need
specific Parts
um full set would be awesome but if you
could only make one I'd say the main
armor body armor you can you can climb
this rope over here and there's like a
next
area there is a I can't find is gigantic
yeah yeah maybe go back to where we're
put does the biker set need a lot of
leather Kiara cuz I'll bring a bunch
more leather if you want it does but oh
yeah I mean more is probably going to
help okay I'll pay you back how do how
do you climb it I'm not very good at
rope
climbing p w what was it
um can you not jump high enough maybe
not I never invested in parkour
I a sh Wait I can't make a Blog here
here don't
worry how do I put it on the ground
never be a parkour Pro no don't say that
you can trade it's a lot actually I'm
going to parkour
[Music]
prison can you make
[Laughter]
yay climb the
rope
w there we go you can do it
yay you
did Chunky climb
the why is the music so terrible you
guys have any Spears book please let let
me know what food food for spear
oh
Spears maybe up
here Mak can help by making cloth right
right at Le the
fragments do you have duct tape do need
lagging I think I gave it to
KI what do you need it for crony asked
for it in chat oh was oh there we are
wonder what she's
making uhoh uhoh I'm scared to fight
with the
lag I don't want to punch my friends to
death oh wait I already have a
couple
flow wow we're still not done I guess
not are you guys still digging oh you're
not digging no that that ship is sailed
back to the house so many oh they came
in through the walls help I'm
scared let me stand in the doorway and
protect you oh thank you you're so
strong
underground I know exactly what those
fist feel
like h
bye-bye that's so many oh my
God
yay oh now we're done yay there's a pig
outside you got outside already yeah you
go on the ladder and it sends you right
outside so you don't have to go through
that
again
oh I'm over here Lads I might die so
many
zombies What if I
I want to check loot
any I don't know
[Music]
maybe die Pig someone can just wear this
I guess maybe
not
but wait do you learn handy land G&G
yeah I've been learning all
the what about armor wait bi boo was
learning armor
yeah oh no you guys left to early
there's a loot
room come back H I might need some help
yes
okay that means there's a loot right or
is there just a chest we need no there's
a lot of Loot and I do not have a lot of
room something to loot the cars uh you
mentioned something ah oh
yes yes yes also by the way you're
constantly crouching press
Ctrl she did walking everywhere slowly
cuz you're
[Laughter]
crouching did
you go yeah down here down here there we
go okay there you go wow a lot of stuff
yeah thank you I got loot stuff
have fun thank you oh yeah do you want
to come I'm I'm thinking about going to
an area to to
scavenge okay when cars aren't
completely together when cars look
complete they will also give gas so
those are nicer to rench L okay that's
cool I follow you I'm waiting for crony
but then I already have one of these
what should we make hold on to it anyway
what were we making
all right and now it's time for
the to smack it
7,000 working very
hard going fast yeah
yeah who's here I thought we cleared the
place out
ooh legendary I found a bunch of good
stuff what dock work of it you
are just make a Max of
these where do we normally put bullet
casings they
mining okay go ahead
yay there's another treasure map I know
how much you
like stop they're probably sick of the
the treasure want to do another treasure
map oh thank you hold it thank you
getting sick of the Treasure by now huh
but the treasure was it giv us a lot of
ammo and weapon parts though so it was
worth it
mhm be sure to take your steroids and
your vitamins do you have more space FAA
yes okay you can take the treasure map
on the yeah you you can look at the
treasure map
now oh who is doing like Tech and turret
stuff cuz I have a you can craft robotic
here take this you
chill thank you oh and you know what
I'll give this turret to
you
oh hold it thank
you oh I think this mine for you maybe
oh
really I think I think it breaks blocks
or something I think you're sitting on
something sir or
doors oh that's his
guts IR
oh it can punch zombies too we should
set it up like outside the yeah yeah
when the when the cord happens you how
to punch
zombies the auto Fister yeah oh did you
did you have did you have any more tea I
have this
stomach was that
surprise oh there's two of them there's
two we did
it did you hear that sound it was like
yeah it was a plane it's a it's a supply
drop uh uh Kelly do you remember where
that one sham food thingy was yeah the
Sham Factory the Sham Wow Factory yeah
what is it on the map oh do you remember
where it was it's in the desert I
believe it's between the desert and the
desolate area yeah I could probably find
out where it is yeah we can go home
first home is on the
way damn I'm in so loveling out here
pretty
intensely I should meet up with the rest
of the
group can we go talk to W okay yeah the
way W okay guy sucks yeah we have a
quest money
yeah ah money money he owes us
money yeah he owes you B big
time especially for all the mean
insults yeah I hope I hope I have enough
gas to make it to
wreck we can always wrench some cars on
the
way oh I should make is not that
bad Hugh is my best friend
now I love snow areas though
could be nice these are kind of bad okay
we're
[Music]
here
yay I'm so
slow it's not
nighttime I
know so many things in these
Pockets water filter that's nice do
already have a water filter yes but we
can always need more okay it's a little
expensive but I'll keep saving up for
it how do I get rid of weakened armor uh
you have to repair it I need water I
have my house with weapon repair kits
yeah oh is
it cuz I'm
trying oh you have to unip it first I
think oh I'm silly
okay make a run to the
house I don't know if this works with my
thing no refund Deal's done now you know
the drill [\h__\h]
on your way out oh sell the cash and
gold a I should sell the gold does work
I don't know if golden n
better me do that real quick
maybe St is
better okay I repaired it thing are you
dropping the things for me oopsie oh
I've just dropped off a bunch of random
stuff I found I found some
steel is oh is there Iron among it
too no I think I left the iron at the
old house we definitely need that is
there a lot I was tired of it maybe a
thousand okay that's good that's good
are you walking cuz you can't Sprint I'm
I'm this is my sprinting
speed I'm full I'm very full maybe I'll
go pick it up l
oh I'll head back and see uh-huh Callie
did you find it get randomly check find
what hold I need to buy gas real fast no
I haven't gone there yet it's fine I'll
just look around in the yeah I'm still
in the snow area I'm heading back to the
house though okay okay no
worries unless you want to yeah okay I
can wait for
you you want to come with us then yeah I
want to go with you okay going to raid
the the Sham Factory I'm going to ride
my bike home this is so close I will see
you
there heck yeah also I have a treasure
map if anyone wants to look for Treasure
later yeah of course of course we were
just waiting for colie okay of course of
course I was come back home then
counting you
in even more like of course of course
how will I do without my
cat I need her to drive she's a big
car what crazy
[Music]
cat guys you know what I realized the
other day what you know is a pink she's
pink and she's called
panta she's a pink she's like the she's
like the pink pan is this something the
first is this something you just
realized just now what wait
what realiz every once in a while
remember didn't know that's why iing it
what are you saying you never thought
about it it's a joke right
realize it's just what I thought a very
sarcastic I
hope why the gaslighting on
we're just trying to have a good time
and you're trying to Gaslight us me
don't take everything personally I'm
taking it personally good I'm going to
HR about this
good imagine today we have a meeting
because I was gaset by them about Pink
Panther was
gaset wait
what can't believe you would do that to
her
that's why you said that I'm a furry a
lot yes she's a furry did you get your
new gun I did
SMG let's go 30 minute craft yeah it
took 30 minut minutes CRA the old 30
minute
craft my save five minutes craft my
favorite not the 5 minute crabs I not 5
minute ladies
I have the first motor bike on the
server and it's
huge I want to see show show gas this
better be like the fastest thing ever I
have no gas in it right
now I have a lot of G for you K it's
crazy bone structure painted a SE in the
bag
yeah so cool with the this this is like
T coated with
the oh yeah the biker build really suits
this oh head is though the animal head
is like eating the light in the front
yeah that's
cool I'll have to fill it up with some
gas and we'll see how fast have 300 gas
can yay I want to have thank you
see we can only two no rush but let us
know when you're ready um Kelly all
right I'm just I'm just cooking some
steel real quick and then I'm on my way
oh I'll do class with you guys too now
that I'm done oh we're going to the Sham
Factory oh I want to go to sh Factory
okay let's go you guys want to come yeah
let's go oh yeah let's just wait for
call for seconds yep I'm just putting
away some ammo I've got a ton of
different ammo I need to organize stop
at home for us to anyway yeah I think
we're low
on uhoh I think quite a few raw meats oh
it's more that we don't have any
ingredients to make a good food oh I
found some potatoes that's about to
change at the S at the Sham at the Sham
Factory that we're about to raid which
is why I need to open come here for a
second yeah take that that mind I don't
know where the potato was thank you okay
we can just keep them in here it's just
easier to
just
motorcycle parts where I put them that
doesn't seem
right where are my shotgun no one else
is making shotguns I don't think right
no I don't think so no you are a
provider okay they're in here I see
they're in the weapon parts box
okay it's was about to be real sad
we're fine we're fine are you putting
gas yeah I put everything inside here oh
thank
you yeah oh I want to see the speed
now
yes this one doesn't have
a to cook some meat is it hard to make
us an extra seat for the mini bike c
yeah if you give me more cloth fragments
I can make one how many do you need
Maybe 100 would be nice 100 100 what
what do you need to make the
motorcycle you
crap I would need a bunch of f i ches I
have the handle bars and two
wheels yeah um I'm coming you probably
are missing the motorcycle chassis if
you look it up and you can see what that
needs
let's go all right are you ready I'm
ready to go to the
warehouse Factory people ready yeah K
was your the pink one I'm almost ready
sorry was yours the pink one your old
one my old bicycle or yeah um mini bike
mini bike no cron is using the old Mini
Bike now it doesn't have the the seat
anymore cuz I put it on my motorbike oh
that's why okay okay no worries is it
okay if we go to the factory with you
guys yeah okay we're just riding over to
where you all are right now
so that's fast I'm going to go hit that
Riv
real drink so fast so I can probably to
stop up in a pool or something I drop it
is it really that quick yeah and it it
gets curves really
sharply I can drift I can literally
drift oh drift it that's pretty cool
oh my gosh oh is
cooking oh yeah I'm
hungry everyone's yeah the problem is we
have like no potatoes I have I have two
potatoes here you go I I don't make one
here's two potatoes a little bit more
water I think the Sham if we go to the
Sham Factory I assume there's going to
be a lot of food there so maybe this is
a good
opportunity for you oh is that from me f
for
you thank you you're welcome thank you
welcome my off I wonder I made
some chest pieces I don't know who to
give them
to are we out of rotten flesh there's no
way right really there is way
uh what's on your
chest I mean I mean no no I mean your
chest your armor uh what did you wear
for the top again so I am I have an
Assassin outfit which is not really
useful what level three kind of okay uh
switch with this and give me the
Assassin one oh thank you I keep you
mine now
mm there you go let's
bye does anybody have any rotten
flesh I
don't it's very important here here here
I have six here you
go put some into those like white boxes
let me
see I have aair one foron
[Music]
or did I make my nerd hat
oh it
wasir bik's heavy okay um don't mean to
rush I'm just um just checking is
everyone ready or I'm
to pretty much
ready okay
I my after
everybody's Mo are on their way they're
just on their bik
okay okay time it's fine I just need
some are you good what are you doing
just trying to find their way to the
house the way to the house oh yeah I see
them North oh I'm digging don't worry
about me are you good yeah do not worry
about me we're heading over there right
now I'm going to pick up the iron gigy
I'm coming over with my motorbike okay I
have 2,000 on me right now oh let's go
uh F do you need help do you want me to
pick you up
or we just we got a little bit lost on
our bike so it's understandable it
happens
always we'll just follow after you
guys may I can oh I have so many
explosives for this hoorde so ready okay
very exciting I got
them I'm a crafting
bundle I put it here in the
middle oh my God chest you mean a forest
in the middle here the the the chest the
boxes in the middle I don't know what to
put I'm a crafting kit you mean or what
did you get I don't know it's never seen
this before it's like I'm a crafting ble
is a red box a bundle ah
bundle ready oops oh man I did a
mess this is going to be the sickest
raid ever yeah yeah I'm so ready we're
going to fight so much
food yeah I just need a little bit more
food this out so awesome the biker
outfit's so cool thank you with the nerd
goggles though the D position is a
little it's the more Gap the more Gap
Callie yeah we love the Gap there's
something wrong with this guy uh Bon do
you need sham for the Sham food right
with this guy you can eat the Sham okay
I'm going to eat the
Sham the sandwiches give you a tummy
that was so fast some of them do the the
sandwiches give you a poo
poo
wao free spikes rolls nice I have 4,000
iron wow wow that's a lot of
iron where is it um I'm in the hole
here let me get
[Music]
it ride let's make it
out I did a a flip too where are we
going here press all my iron oh there
you are I fell into the hole Okay jump
to the left thank you so much okay okay
let me see if I find something you can
take this bike if you want or do you
have your own oh I can come with you
oh no I already have I don't have a seat
if you have a bike you have can use your
own bike oh okay never
[Music]
mind okay I was just
lazy me too okay let's
go it's not even that bad lead the way
someone wait where where are we going
you said you know
where I kind of know where it is one
moment let me Mark it this is a biker
gang
yeah I got another thousand Iron where
from how are you producing these so fast
I found it in my
M it's so good I know that it's around
this area
so inside the house right now
everybody
almost we really are the nerd
biker oh are we going this way wait does
this mean that I'm the queen of the nerd
[Music]
mot always 500 kilm ahead of you we ride
as a model gang model we ride as a gang
we ride we
ride
ride what we have to ra again sorry
35m
okay we got time
time friends it's
okay behind oh I'm just following Callie
she seems like she knows where she's
going on the
[Music]
highway a danger
zone all right so it's not the church is
such a scary
place but I think it's here cuz that's
where the town is it was right to
through the Sham Factory okay update
it's actually 4,000
iron what wow found a lot of all right
good that I have two forges I'll be
cooking a lot of iron now thank you
problem pretty wait gy do you want to
see my motorbike I want to see it you
can even get on and be the first to test
it oh my God so cool wraps my arms
around found
you let me lock oh sorry for safety you
know yeah I can't let zombies get on oh
so
cool it's so fast look I can drift it's
awesome you're our gang leader our biker
gang leader with our cool hat I am yeah
I know exactly where I'm going my you do
are you sure
hold on okay get
off okay actually no damage is being
taking it I found it it's not here it's
not here this way follow me get me out
of here get me out of here I'm try I'm
trying I'm try I'm try it's fine it's
fine it's fine I can do it all right
ladies it's h this way I found the right
way okay you found it this what happen
I'm diving into the spike I'm not taking
any damage interestingly
enough taking damage uh
no that's good that's good that's good
that's good thank you out
[Music]
of it might have uh given the Trap some
damage it seems I can borrow some she
went to she this way okay show this way
follow me through the mountains ladies
through the mountain I trust you
oh yes we really are a
b so we ride into the sunset the air
brushing through my shin I want to
be gas forever somehow it get to the
might be like a children's movie maybe
I'll find is this all like social
structure depending on who has as a
motorcycle motorbike or
bicycle mean yes this is why I'm the
motorbike Queen she is the
queen okay wait FAA FAA what does that
make you since you you back
seating I'm I'm the sigma I'm not oh
she's the sigma yeah let's go yeah she's
on a little bit of a different level cuz
she got she got back seat rights to my
motor B
too found it ladies I'm going to need
some borrow some gasoline by the way
before we get out of here bicycles
really are the best huh we don't even
need gasoline yep just our legs all
right shamway Factory ladies oh this is
the fact here it is before it gets too
dark but it will become night so the
zombies will become stronger so this
will be a great challenge for us it's
okay you can die over and over again
since it's not a yeah
Quest be fine we can take him but who
wants to
die
nobody you want to die I can help you I
can help you with that yeah we can help
with that if you really want to you guys
are so helpful but you know sometimes
you have to do things on your own I
don't want to get carried in my own
death okay I kill you without asking
them okay let's go in
ladies who
me oh
[Music]
god wow this is a good
weapon I'm excited okay office chair
guys we need the leather destroy the
chairs
Lea oh boy oh he's going chairs with
the hammer everybody else will get oh
gosh I picked up the
chair destroy the chair the sofa's too I
ouch
okay it's
a give Leever if the lever so close
otherwise they just give cloth which is
nice too nice I oh oh oh get him get him
get him get
him
yeah how do I
shoot I'm so
sorry you're allowed to shoot me cuz I
cuz I stabbed you too many times
a
there you see the body just in case
there okay is crazy no but here's my
number so call me
maybe maybe I will okay maybe yeah let's
break
things there's a hole that goes
underground too oh boy hello yes you
really shocked me you gave me a fright
sir
oh he's still there's a lot of boxes
everywhere here huh that's a lot of
zomes in
front Okay help help green ones too oh
boy I've
suffered watch
out I have
bandaids everybody come get some
Band-Aids before you
die
Lady w
what you drop I want to see I just took
a peek big hitters I'm going to go ahead
and use that what is this I'd like
everybody come get bandaids a bandaids
we can bandaids that's it doesn't matter
we have band one thank
you everybody needs band for their
o which
me get him get him get him
yeah oh my God nice J
fire
fire is the shotgun stronger than the
bat I think so
am
anymore amazing the everybody's walking
forward that was awesome good job
everybody ohe good job everyone
so good I guess we can clean the place
out like after we kind of kill
everything yeah yeah
yeah looting along the way is not a bad
idea okay let's stick
together not much more this
way I do be a little hungry I was saving
this for the raid but I'll use it now
[Music]
oh it's up here up here okay let's go up
yeah let's go up the way I
see we can't hear you with anyone
shooting yeah it's any
game fire
people hello
boys like
pictures hello oh a bed roll was up here
what the a bed roll
here NP
time I'm burning the ground is
falling yeah that's not that is not
great it does not Inspire confidence
what's in here aair that SC them SC them
SC
them those look like they're going to
break not this
yeah huahua if you needed I have 6,000
more iron oh my
gosh get closer
[Music]
to oh let we turn off that fire though
yeah I saw
some them
[Music]
off okay
where where are we
supposed more iron you can't turn it off
you can't I have 7,000 more you need it
okay I'll pick it up later okay do you
need G do you need any armor by the way
no I'm
good okay oh yikes are you
good oh I'm
great oh you're fine is saving me right
now
gy I'll give you so much more this hole
has so much iron in here I have 8,000
now don't
worry I want more creepy I don't want to
shoot you okay I'm just going to
owo is there anything you would still
like to have in terms of armor to uh uh
let's
see I think I'm fine with my
[Music]
I
he oh when you come can you bring repair
kits though how many
[Music]
maybe I think I'm going to thank you
this way bye
Bo
okay does anybody have
on me
or not on me but maybe at home I
think yikes oh oh okay there's a big
dude how did he get up
there okay I got him up the
stairs I should be a way up somewhere I
thought I would have enough turns out I
won't remember to scrap chairs ladies
for leather yeah as much as you can okay
Nice Shot thanks anything
[Music]
else this is a new area
oh hello is he dead he's dead he's
dead he's super
dead where's the big chest in this place
is what I want to know there's got to be
one yeah there's got to be
one this place is huge though I will
[Music]
say oh hello Bo uh-oh there's one
there's one
thank
you Callie why wait
what to the light I'm to the light come
on my friendly fire was such a bad
idea sorry see everybody sorry about
that it was a little hard to see it's
okay it was
dark hope it doesn't spawn you too far
away let's take let's mess up the
CH all right yeah don't pick it up
yeah
yeah how I just got to find where that
was that's probably beo is somebody did
somebody die I think it's it might
[Music]
be I need that I found
it this is full of good stuff that we
need to scrap or not gather rather
there's another CH let's get that
one yeah yeah I'm back welcome
back go to the
[Music]
ground armored up I'm going to use that
really quick cuz I do okay where did you
guys go I I we're still in the building
oh I'm not in the party anymore can you
invite me again oh yeah uh I just did
party leader everybody fall through the
floor is now okay is that a zombie or is
that a thank
yeah these doors are locked we might
need to break them no there's there's
another way there's another
area did you go downstairs or are you
still on the same
level it's a shame tomorrow's the last
day I know today I have 17,000 iron now
how are we going to smelt it all yeah I
know what a
shame where are you did you go out down
ah oh oh There stairs that's not way I
found you yeah that looks
like uh there's a b way there's a
staircase on the side of the guys I'm on
the other side of this wall hello saw
behind the bars hello
hello okay it's okay I see you B yeah
show me the B way you have to go outside
first some outside
parkouring
gotcha got to exit through the window
okay I see and then up
here
okay cool nice find
B
find
zomo ooh this looks super creepy Up on
the Roof
[Music]
uh oh there's a lot of Mines here watch
out no maybe we can lead the zombies on
them time to shoot time to shoot where
are you guys we can lead in the Min on
the roof get the if you come over here
we can lead them past the
mind good
Miss
for got
[Music]
traps
no it's not now now is not the time for
a ping pong at the
door ping pong ping
pongy
thing get
home tou stuff
I I think if I step on the mine I won't
activate get hungry let's have some
water M oh okay I'm
good there's some angry sound dang is
there no treasure oh maybe there is
there there's another way oh down here o
let's follow everybody
m not to
let's open the mines this place is crazy
it's like a maze it is yeah
oh
uh-oh you rning uhoh uhoh uhoh shoot
shoot don't know how we're going to park
for on here though
okay I should eat something my
maybe now are you crouching Again by the
way yeah yeah yeah I know I'm just like
TR to see no I'm not I was not crouching
now she
you I think that is a b back because
everyone is telling me that I'm
crouching I don't
no weird why would keep lying to
us am I lagging right now yeah the the
the server's kind of laggy right now
with all the of Zombies watch out watch
out oh gosh it yeah they like flying and
floating for
me
nice I'm going to go home and craft
stuff okay
[Applause]
okay I think everybody else is
downstairs now okay we're going to
follow K up by that okay just be careful
because it's a very very far drop to be
I wonder how we get in here
slow as slow as you can oh behind you
behind you behind
you if anyone passes by me cuz they're
on the way can they take all this iron
off me well there's a pack of wolves
outside I'm going to run your iron does
anybody have a repair key there's a bear
to Bear you with us though there's a
bear
okay I'm going to try breaking this open
with a stick of dynamite okay okay stay
behind M stay behind do your best I got
the
zombies oh you have to activate it and
then throw it there you go there you go
there you
go a little
hurt somebody somebody here did work
good job yeah that's crazy
wait have we already been here I think
we've been here before Oh hey appr
though good
job does anybody have a repair kit by
any chance I have one where are you I am
right there I also have one thank
you thank you so much I need to repair
my Spar spear spear that's tons of
leather are you girls uh coming back
sometime soon or soon I think we almost
there's a bunch of stuff here here where
I am oh oh oh oh
oh oh there is a green
guy cuz i' love to I'm going to die more
it's over
no how do you get over there I get it
now he's in my
sights I'm coming I have a wonderful
gift for you
is it IR or yeah it's all Iron don't
expect anything
else got a stump
bike my bike can fly oh there is some
stuff can fly oh nice a bun of
stuff look might as well take everything
want a safe too take
everything I don't have loog Pickel I
don't know if it gave us anything oh
shoot I should have given this lockpick
to bi
boo monster monster well I guess we're
break trees yeah oh this is an easy one
to Break can I plant those are you
planting on getting rid of those trees
this is an easy one the trees are the
tanks
no it's going to be hard to see and
shoot the enemies for all that all those
leaves oops I'm here by the way yeah
okay let's work together second out of
myle okay I'm not getting close to that
right
now oh yeah you want to get hit are you
ready yeah I'm I'm ready bring it on
when to get smacked that's wow that's a
lot of it's
20,000,000 oh we're still hungry for you
thank you you're so
crazy back to my hole missing something
because this feels a little bit
underwhelming for how big
is I hope there's some good stuff in the
safe like
money
probably ow someone hit
me I have not moved my my hand I wonder
if there was iron uh lever you don't
have any lever do you g no I've not seen
an animal in
ages sorry
sorry except maybe for some moles or
what shows up down there little earthw
worms and another little mole rats are
down here too is that what you have been
feeding on as
well I eat
them let's crack it open sorry I opened
it um it's there's nothing there's big
hitters which I'm going to read because
I am the club oh steel Club quality one
y and then iron arrows I will take those
just in case someone wants those that
was all that was in there it was not
very
exciting disappointing where' go what
happened to
her search the garbage angry
sound a steel Club
ladies wa wait here here where'd she go
one inside here there's an area we
haven't been
take is is it back
there we're not going to let them in
right nah it's I'll give it to her later
oh there's a dog enemies still there's a
angry angry dog outside everybody's
angry oh yikes excuse me oh you I go
upst sir can you wait just a
moment thank you there's still quite
some enemies here so I wonder if we
didn't go this way people this way
yeah this where we this way oh they come
in from outside I guess oh maybe they
Spawn from the outside so it's night
time
prob I like this flickering
one let's
up you back up
[Music]
cron okay I deserve to get shot it's
F the to dirty today I deserve
it y yo yo yo it's going to die let's
run away let's run
away stay in the brightness of the
fire
uhoh um that's no good
blind I doing I need to
to is the server really laggy for
anybody I'm very slowly it's a little
strange okay so I'm not
sure uhoh oh God there's like an
exploding guy like a red green guy it's
over
for where
is z here our
nice I want to find the dog did
everybody go you want to find the dog I
want to find the dog and kill it yes it
gives good loot I want to find the dog
my are you talking about the DI yeah
dire I see
okay oh wait that was it we can eat food
do we have food that was it I'm walking
super
slow that must have been it oh boy
somebody have you guys been collecting
some leather on the way for oh yeah I've
been scrapping all kinds of
chairs does it help with our
light get away get away get
away good J
hello okay maybe don't shoot the ground
no Panic shooting no Panic shooting
somebody looks a CE behind you behind
you
CE oh there's a lot of
them
take me
XP just trying to see if there's
something here since there's a block
where the Sham sandwich is at he's
running
he looks like everybody else oh I'm
so I'm CR we need to hold the torch up
I'm still kind of
slow
maybe to go
down I think it's morning now so we
should be
okay okay okay we're
chilling where was the Sham I was
promised there was like no food here
yeah this was
insanely misdirecting I feel like we
should have just done a
quest yeah it's okay you live and you
learn
yeah
Le you you're home I am home I have a
present for you you
do no special
alcohol thank you there's a lot of stuff
we didn't pick up here though help her
punch stop giving
alcohol go but it will save us it will
will it save our family it will help put
our family back together not mentally
but it will save us
physically yeah our interpersonal
relationship my all that matters is that
we stay
alive I'm happy to do more snow quests
with anybody who wants to do the snow
quests they're a little bit harder but
they're fun
any way we can
help a bunch of cloth scraps you guys
are doing great I actually I want to
make you a thing really quick though to
make it even
better you guys will be even more
helpful once I make you my special
present I'm going bandages oh we can
make
bandages yeah do medical stuff so uh
fauna is just getting meat not good is
on the roof they say uh we really need
more than just
take apparently the loot is on the roof
yeah
I'm will take care of it we need like
potatoes rotten meat rotten meat okay
rotten meat potatoes and mushrooms
mostly and eggs eggs are good too eggs
oh yeah very very good I wonder what we
can find that maybe just houses no eggs
are like in the nest on the way oh right
yeah hello
lady okay let's go on I want
amazing could use one of
these oh yeah there is a cave of
mushrooms oh
yeah I think we might need potatoes more
than mushrooms for now where do you
think we can find potatoes I don't know
is there a potato cave
I mean they are in the ground I do need
antibiotics she has
them go over here I am hungry I'm
starving I'm going to die I have three
rotten
flesh I'm also hungry I want to go home
together with everyone I don't want to
go on our own I'm
scared should we leave the factory
now
yeah okay
what's
that where's the food at lady where's
the food
need good good good good
good that's Prett good trust her she's a
doctor
okay okay I think I'm going to go try
and Scavenging bless you
people panicking means it's pretty
bad okay hold up let me go back
[Music]
home does anyone else want to try
targeting houses in order to find food I
found the room with the Looper the
problem is the room is also full of
zombies wait in the in the sh Factory
yep oh okay okay we go back no it's okay
I think I can do it you can take them
yeah we also need more claw claw for
[Music]
bandages or maybe
not okay hold on okay well by the time I
get there the situation may have
resolved itself but
okay we're coming where are you people I
I I'm at the roof okay the roof how did
you get there
coming maybe like
back we have done four 180s Mory yes cuz
I can't decide where to go
out where no I I think it's I think it's
fine I think I got it
you got it yeah the last 180 I'm
doing I can get home I'm pretty sure I
can % gas should be fine don't make me
turn this bike around that's
possible ladies we have 40 IRL minutes
left until the raid until zombie
night boy I'm fine I cleared the room
it's good oh you good yeah guys I will
finish my weapons in time I'm sure so we
going to the old house correct yes I
just need six more forged steel and then
I can make it for
them come on we got plenty of those
now is anybody coming home with L soon I
am anybody got cloth cloth
pieces I'm going to
I can try to go get some I'm going to
the own home and see if I
can many possible don't have lot going
to like small houses and we'll try
finding cloth as well we have
cloth the cloth fragments can be made
into cloth I think so yes cloth
fragments is what we need we got a few
hundred that's good
okay maybe I can make steel
Club did I
okay the world a bit bright enough I
mean that's enough if I was using it
alone
alas I also have I guess having more
iron is inconsequential Gigi did get
like 177,000 yeah we have we have plenty
of that now it just takes never ask for
iron ever again you w me to
ask got it I have so much for you oh
happy I'm honored I'm going to make it
so you're all relying on me for iron and
then you'll never know what it's like
without iron and then I like drip it
slower slower yeah until you you like
desperately need me and you're begging
we already need you we're already
obsessed with you I guess I'll never
stop collecting iron
there the
weather not a ton but it is a decent
amount hopefully it'll help you and some
glue as
well I actually need to make duct
tap with this gun I need
duct um can you put them in the medicine
box medicine box okay thank
[Music]
you cool
and it's kind of mess oh the cooked food
and medicine one is good okay this will
be worth it I promise can I
not I have some more I
put what else do we
have whatever
the
medicine we have two leather where
should we put the
Lea I think Kiara wanted the
leather Sorry by probably for chest
[Music]
yes this one's making iron I think this
one's making
steel storage
oh the fire chat yeah yeah okay I just
see 20 I want to make them
maybe
40 okay it should be the chest in the
kitchen nice okay thank you big somebody
was was somebody making a yucka smoothie
yeah and also duct
tape I was making in a smoothie oh okay
I'll give you the Smoothie oh you can
put it it's not for me necessarily it's
for anybody you can put it in your food
chest or you can drink
it oh there's so much cloth fragments
okay there's a couple glues oh
no where am I going yeah that's the
one okay time is it 7:30 oh plenty of
time to go check for steel I'm sure
we're forging Steel all right we're
forging
steel yeah I need some forg
[Music]
steel
antibiotics I'm making some yum yums oh
I need to oh I need to eat these I'm
going to
die wow my favorite hobo stew thank you
for cooking this hobo
stew I thought it was a sculpture but
not a sculpture
oh did
not I thought it was a dog
scul I wonder be taking
these a chest for
explosives I thought it was a
robot I'm going to find
flowers
the do we have any
food I'm going to have it
make
feel
okay a
stamina thank you we're hungry we can't
get that far
just for now so if everybody can eat the
grilled meat before the raid and then
save the good food for the raid I think
that would be ideal
okay eat the grilled meat first you're
going to have to eat a lot of it
but I'm going to stop this I think it's
good to
sa oh there's a couple here I'm not sure
how long feel like an hour 30 because
this stays an hour and then is it that
long till the rain is it really it might
be is it on the 35th we should be able
to
actually yeah realiz is kind of quite
far oh oh 1 hour 30
minutes hour and
30 well we still have a lot of time
maybe I'll go for some extra
Quest could have played longer yesterday
that's that's what I'm saying yeah we
should
have but it's hard to do MTH that's good
though we
got we making what are these Sor what
you
making sorry call were you making bullet
casing yep I'm making them
for do you to do
byebye uh oh maybe not
yeah cuz I got to make
steel and I was wondering if I could use
this to make steel if possible and then
maybe we could make bullet casings over
here how much Ste you need I have like
100 in my pocket oh my god wow that's
crazy well to make the gun I wanted to
make it's like
40 okay yeah wait let me make oh but
they're off for the day huh they're
offline
oh oh they just left what I didn't even
realize yeah what they left yeah
they got oh here let me maybe I'll give
it to I'll give the I'll give the gun to
C let me invite you back to the party W
I think there's room now there you go oh
yes please I might go since we still
have so much time if somebody's still
doing Quest so I might yeah let's do
Quest want to do quest
Quest okay I do I I was making some
armor so I got some stuff to give to the
weakest
links yeah that is and I did make some
repair kits oh did you I have nine now
that yeah we can use I think we'll need
a bunch yeah steel Club how do we make
steel
Club need a workbench for this one this
one actually can be made pretty
quickly let me know whenever you guys
are on your way to a new Quest okay okay
what do we
need potatoes
potatoes where do we meet guys which
Quest We gonna
do making some
weapons
oh not sure which one yet I like the
snowy Quest though I think they're good
I want to go there too I've I don't
think I've been there before I still
need to open up the trader route to the
do you have to open the trade route or
can you just talk to the no you can just
talk to him
okay but I still want to open it up sure
that's fine yeah might be good might be
a good
idea
actually I got an auto
turret oh nice really I got two auto
turret I got two SMG Auto turrets o
where we can set these the
finale I spent like 10 minutes opening a
chest it was so worth it oh yeah that
sounds like it was worth it auto turrets
yeah auto turret to auto wrench I need a
wrench heck yeah I'm coming to the house
then and
then maybe I'll make some 9 mm girls who
are using 9mm ammo is it only bble it's
only bble but I could use a lot more
I'll I'll uh put some into the queue for
you thank you cuz I'm also making ammo
for
myself guess I could make some shotgun
shells too shotgun shotgun ammo o you I
don't know if you're able to but I would
need a steel
arrows um I have iron
arrows I haven't looked into arrows yeah
um some armor to take a bit too much
baby I already making armor and
stuff maybe I'll wear the Nomad head
here I doing
wait
ammo no I won't G powder take it back it
looks cool but I look cooler
oh and I have a treasure map I probably
want to look into can I don't know if
it's any if it'll be any good though hey
Vio did you want Molotov yes please okay
a how much cloth do you
need um a lot but I think I'm I might be
okay in the chest in the
kitchen which chest in the one in the
kitchen by the forge if you want to take
it CeCe were you using
batons I wanted to get a a I have a stun
baton level five oh yes I can give it to
you yeah because I have like a mod
extension thingy for it yay yeah it's
it's really good I think you should have
it thank you
okay I'm coming home to store some Loot
and then we can
do I'm ready anytime I'm going home to
three maps are based on where you look
at
it oh if you read it in a higher level
you get better loot okay maybe I'll look
at the treasure map when we're in the
snow
[Music]
area thank you very B thank you very
much for the redirect that was nice I'm
sorry I couldn't make you guys the
shotgun I wanted to make
you but that's okay just it's it's in
it's in your heart I deliver it to your
heart we're ready for quest I'm was at
game stage
190 oh yeah I did should we be worried
about that I murdered a bunch of things
God maybe worried about that I don't
know
hey crony's at 94 though so that's kind
of it also depends on where you are
because I am still at the factory so I
see
a I see she's in the Wasteland I'm
making a few more repair kits just like
maybe oh yeah repair kit I need repair
kits repair kits are always
good where the area head to the Rally
Point should I head to the rally
point we should wait for everybody what
is that what am I
doing um I just see it on my screen it's
1.6 k no that's a that's a tier one
Quest that's a tier one class I don't
think we should do tier one not do that
yeah how many people are using shotguns
in here quite a few crony
okay I'm in need of a little
fuel just a little fuel we'll find some
fuel
surely CE K you're right CeCe I'm right
by you uh let me drop off this weapon
for you oh oh oh watch out bird bird
uhoh it's always the freaking Birds okay
take uh I can't learn that yet you leave
a little
nice thank you yeah do you happen to
have a repair kit I can buy off of you
you can just have one taking some
Provisions what hat are you wearing I'm
wearing the nerd hat still Level uh four
I believe do you want a higher level
nerd hat or would you like some
different hat sewing kit yeah um sure I
could use a higher level nerd hat
hat cool turret you prefer nerd hat over
anything else do
you
um well that's the EXP one
right oh yeah yeah yeah I would prefer
the
EXP okay I'll make you the max level
one using up one legendary
part wait do we still an hour and a half
we do and we've been going for 4 and a
half hours we we timed it I thought I
thought one day is 1 hour but I guess
not is it longer than that I think it's
longer than that I could keep playing
yeah me too me too I'm fine still yeah
me too but I'm definitely staying until
the hord though yeah we've we prepare
too hard for to not have a hoorde at the
end yeah definitely
hope we get a season two we're working
on it it seems
possible so I would love that let's do
it I really want
to can I have a better hat if possible
mine is level two do you want the EXP
hat or a different one is fine okay just
a bit stronger maybe yeah no problem
thank you I'll make you're level five
whoa I think oh I'm going
the I kind of want to get some mod from
my
spear feel like this is still not enough
bandages
I have five on my hand personally right
now so I'll just use those I think I'll
be fine with
five for the raid
yeah I I'll forget using them anyway
literally yesterday I only used
one bu I just forgot about
them I'll be back very
quickly okay where are we going to do
Quest
how about the snow area I will keep
recommending the snow area we can do we
can go to the snow area since it's
higher
tier um I have one up there tier four
clear that one's fun beu it's fun one
it's a big shooty
one shy
spy I'm trying to make ammo for everyone
right now thank you thank you thank you
thank you I've got lots but I'm going to
I'm going to use all of
it this shotgun is amazing that's what I
need to
pick here here you
go oh wow okay then I I'll just focus on
shotgun sh and 9 mm yeah if I could have
a lot of 9 mm up here I'm sure he has
fuel
[Music]
oh also there is about 200 shotgun
bullets in the weapon ammo for right now
oh let's go awesome I'll split that with
Co I I'll probably give it
that it's poo don't
mind tell me about poo do not worry
about poo tell me about popo popo is the
little green bird flying next to me I'll
send you a photo of
[Applause]
him I didn't expect him to sound like
that yeah he's really good at
bar he's so talented should we find a
phot of
him yeah I want to see I want to see
popo too okay what is Popo's
personality um silent until the Barking
starts and then not silent yeah they're
Not So Silent wait remind me please of
the levels of each of your
armor
l oh she's you muted L yeah she said
she's going to be right back a while ago
okay she's looking at me in
game messed up I have telepathically
sent you a photo of popo into your TMS
let me see ooh let me see Popo oh my
good look at
po
cute so
[Music]
rattie where's my am does popo like
being called a
rat I call Popo ugly so much I'm like
come here ugly I little ugly one and
then Po's like
hold on I gotta
sign hold up oh here's even more for you
seven I love paying my taxes do you have
any more gunpowder or nitrate uh uh I
have bullet
casing I don't need those necessarily
but
yeah later
done
now let see which Quest is that I don't
want to do with the tier one clear can I
ignore
it yeah should have made more 9 mm maybe
where's the quest I
took we're wasting
gas oh sorry guys I'm back I welcome
back
welcome welcome back my hat nerd hat oh
thank you yeah but tell me the rest uh I
have the armor is level four and the
gloves are level three and the boots are
level three m i
see take
these thank you you're welcome and and
the the ones you have
now can you just drop them on the floor
the old ones of course of course I
didn't even see the bir a
sec aren
those ah those are the old ones okay
yeah those are the old ones good should
I see oh wait is this supposed to be on
the forge at all
times yeah oh well I think uh if there's
nothing cooking is anything cooking cute
uh let me let me
check that's a cute that's a cute little
bird you got
there cute bir got there very cute
birdie I'm jealous of your cute birdie
is it making stuff I know so fluffy it's
uh it's it's like smelting the iron
pretty sure is it not for
iron uh then that has to be done
manually like first you put in the the
raw iron
and it loads up the forge of the iron
and then anytime you can cook the forge
stuff once the iron is like loading up
there's like a count on the right side
how much iron How much brass Etc is
inside oh here's here's two workstation
book oh thank
you haven't seen one of those in a
while 38 out of
75 uh yeah girls let me know when we do
quests okay I'm just organizing my
inventory right now first
[Music]
okay it took him a
second was using the bathroom huh
oops more chairs to turn into a
leather there's a lot of them
wait does the does the fire not just
like if it's burning does it save the
time and then or is it just like wasting
fuel if nothing is cooking in it or is
it converting it
into oh it is wasting but the forge is
not wasting if it's just
running ah I see
oh oh he wants to come
in there's a steel club and a pump
shotgun in the output of the shotguns
for crony uh the steel club's for me
though you
good oh these look like I could scrap
them
[Music]
who's screaming calm
down chill it's not that big of a deal
why you said eat the meat like the basic
meat yeah eat the grilled meat okay
before the ra to eat like a whole stack
I am I'm working on it I'm eating a
whole stack right
now the red tea oh no money it's hard if
we had more eggs we could make better
food if we had more
potatoes farming is so hard cuz you have
to spend five potatoes to get two seeds
it's not
efficient yeah or to get one seed five
potatoes to get one seed and then you
get seven potatoes back so you only get
net two potatoes and it takes forever to
grow yeah that's not
efficient is the farmer armor expensive
to cra C
kiaha uh farmer
outfit the whole outfit hello and maybe
just a chest I have a hat
already uh depends on what level you
want it on cuz I will be running out of
leather if I make this not again not
again not again not again not the bear
the bear the bear brings
leather maybe just level one is okay
I'll make you at least level
three okay do you need help you're
breathing very
heavily but I need that think you went
away I I'm ready for quest now by the
way H I am a finishing a solo Quest and
then I'm I'm ready to go
okay I don't know I have to wait the
boots are better farmer boots okay well
they also are most important they need
to say
materials
take welcome back welcome
back I don't want to do
that let's make level four think I can
take
him okay we'll see maybe we'll get more
leather that is a bear on our
way I got
your uh farmer boots thank you he can't
get in here right is he dead I'll try to
get us better seed this there you go I
do love cheese I don't know how much
time we have to grow stuff I love cheese
that leather though we need not much
time I should be able to grow a few
potatoes at
least mushrooms though a few
mushrooms he's a big
boy uh I'm putting 61 of Ky wobble
bullets in the Forge chest I feel B bad
oh I found the bun you give me so much
ammo yeah I I just found
them ah did you I think you you found
the the 20 bullets that I put into the
ammo
chesto oh hello did you did I I think I
did they're gone now oh yeah I took them
I took them yeah yeah yeah call there is
a bunch of shotgun ammo in the new house
so make sure you but found a bunch of
those too I found everything except my
own people I have another unrelated
present take oh thank you that will be
very if you need more let me
know why am I using the
lock
yeah and
and this will surely help I think I have
one more right oh thank you just one it
will help it will kill one zombie yes
the one head shot will make the
difference ZZ do you want to make metal
spikes yeah how I I have a I have a mod
smash for metal spikes I want to make
metal spikes yeah
okay I run back to all house is that I'm
at the new house
oh back to the to the new house I can
drop it off for you I'll come by
okay well oh
well oh I'm
hungry I Got No
Seeds there's there's almost 400 uh
shotgun ammo in the shotgun or in the
ammo chest yeah
oh hello farming is a
scam
but there must be another way
around
yeah
o uh why do I have these
ah what's in here
that looks
good oh he waved at
me oh
shoot
doggy I'll just you're my favorite
customer I want
[Music]
separate let's
see Oho
chill this isn't about
you is there a good way to get
[Music]
eggs chicken there's got to be a way to
raise chickens or something like that
right it's too late to raise
chickens
yeah should totally be possible
Right wasn't sure
is VI L too calm to make
this but only on level two will it be
better take that I wish I could take the
photos wor I'm coming on your direction
cross me you'll meet the I'm also going
to head in that direction oh okay me too
wait Wait f I'll I'll I'll carry you
give me a ride of course I will thank
you uh just give me I'm used to this one
more moment okay do we have some wood in
this house yeah be wood in one of the
middle chests you can also check my own
chest I should have
use your
gunpowder you have gunpowder in your
chest Cey can I use it yeah for making
ammo for everybody okay yeah nice you
got some good stuff wood in L
chest maybe not or maybe I
dep there's 84 wood in the top middle
chest top middle chest ah thank you I am
blind as always me too okay d coming to
drop by a present for you y please make
are you eating
something no
yes hry scamer I just order for to I was
hungry barrrel at dinner
time oh means lunch time it's lunchtime
no never mind I read it wrong it's the
mods for clubs you don't actually make
metal spikes I'm illiterate
no metal spikes
no that's really bad oh there was more
wood
too hello I mean if we can put it on a
club we can put it on the
ground loud loud very loud oh very loud
in new house very loud yeah
defending I'm punching our house
defent a beautiful
house
yeah did he fall through the ja
radio
okay really know why you did
that zombie still at the
house
um she's dealing with it she will handle
it okay 100 bioo ammo thank you who is
vomiting at my back door oh oh sorry I
got him useful battle music stops okay I
think I think I think I can uh in 55
seconds I can go
okay can we take this guy with us when
it's time oh there's still dudes this
guy but a melee turret yes we should I
did it though so that's oh yeah let's do
that just you know they keep
coming maybe I left the door
open
oh this is going to be
rough okay okay I'm all over the place
I'm like everywhere oh nice
lucky
hello Forge head two Treasure Chest
about already have one of these
right do you need any more forged ahead
you yes yes you do many many many gotcha
I figured as much I wasn't
sure okay good to know good to
know mission complete oh oh hey what's
going
on I'm helping I should I should just
stop I need to stop I need to stop
crafting thankfully the mission is
complete so we can get out of here I'm
heading toward the snowy area okay I
don't think anymore I think now I need
to claw my way out of here bring we have
the sealed shipping crates
too oh and this okay we found a
bunch
of
clo can you bring me should I bring you
the the the should I bring the pump
shotgun at the steel club with me sure
if you're coming to the snowy area yeah
I'm coming there will CR be there I
wonder thanks oh if you're using Club do
you have the mod for
spikes metal spikes mod I do have one oh
okay well I have I have a schematic for
it so you can make more I'll give it to
oh yeah that's cool I'll take
that since it's not placing
spikes yeah okay I got a bunch of cloth
if you're still available to make the
seat oh right now mhm I am quite far
away so I don't know if you have some
then uh
yeah I
think we can exchange the cloth I have
enough to make it right now and you can
give me the one
you uh gathered um okay we are coming
home but let me see how far we are the
zombies were doing not too far um but
you can also just see what it's up to
you uh depends on if I have enough
leather
honestly I might be missing one leather
oh okay N I might need you to come over
unless I find leather here
okay on the
wall leather
Lea W but course not our most needed
resource now is lettera and potatoes I
guess okay potato
potatoes for coming to help me
why you end it up there drop from the
ceiling other
office I see there it is oh there you go
I hello to right now traveling with two
bicycles yeah
oh okay so much good stuff in
here do you have room in your inventory
by chance
yeah I have space there's a pump shotgun
too oh my gosh this will be great to arm
people see if you can carry some of this
stuff I I can carry everything I just
got here too so if you need any hands I
have hands awesome yeah I'm very
cucumber at the moment so I like
cucumbers really no what I
cuy yeah cucumbers are kind of I had a
funny story I was at a grocery store and
I was buying chili oil and this like man
who looked like like a like a wild like
Lumberjack kind of man that kind of man
came up to me and was like did you see
the tick tock cucumbers oh sometimes you
got to eat an entire
cucumber yeah it's a
nationwide thing everybody wants to eat
cucumbers cuz of that specific guy which
sucks because there was already a
cucumber shortage so I'm mad at him for
exposing how good cucumbers
are I was not expecting this like
Lumberjack Mountain Man to be on the Tik
Tok cucumber
[Music]
meta go get the direwolf he's over
there
cuum gate over there okay I see my
favorite is the one where there like
this guy when he's just in in a in a
like a lake or something and he goes
salad in the water I think he dropped I
just want to see what the loot is I just
want to look at it oh he
dropped
oh oh shoot oh I'm sorry I'm I'm I'm
waiting for the lever delivery to a want
biker gloves I sure do want biker gloves
okay hold on well let's clear this out
first yeah delivery
from uh Cey crony again okay
then they can go around faster cuz I
think yeah they're also the quest
maybe don't worry we'll we'll catch up
super fast with our bike and then we'll
wait so for the ones who are still
behind so catching up doesn't mean
anything yeah I feel like I should go
look for stuff right now I'm not doing
anything I'll just go on my bike and
then and then if you find me on the way
you can pick me up okay easy
what is in
there red
shotgun M how much 7.6 those rounds
people ammo do you have I currently have
uhoh
outside God the lag really strong okay
150 okay uh
car thank you when I see you I will
maybe until the raid maybe focus on
close com
so that we don't waste too much ammo on
the quest okay we'll do
uh-oh excuse me do you have any mods on
your
gun right now
no I don't I haven't found any gun mods
actually there's a lot in a chest that
my I have I have all of the
recipes nice are there
actual oh yeah actually you can probably
take these should work for you I'll take
the ones that should work no don't go
through the wall sorry I don't want to
kill you I'm Sor sorry I'm so
[Music]
sorry take this here you go what
oh shotgun shells sorry about that no
worries you guys ready for question yeah
I'm ready
any Le for
you and then that was fast yeah okay can
you me okay 12
leather 236 Clock Two sewing kids you
want to be you want to be hit yeah
machine gun parts your
head oh oh armor up actually you can use
if you want it's okay I'm on steroids
for 19 put rotting Flash and food stuff
into your food
area Okay in 1 minute your seat mod will
be finished
yay ah wait wait come over to the middle
uh I I chose some mods for you for your
gun for your rifle thank you and then
here's some ammo but don't spend too
much before the raid okay thank you and
I can upgrade my shotgun but I wonder
what materials I need let's defend our
stuff okay there she is thank you got it
uh 60 forged steel that's a lot of Ste
schematic C oh thank you hold on just a
sec drinking some
water oh
lingesh that's
good I have some ammo for you kahua I'm
just going to put everything in this
[Music]
chest the shotgun was for crony right
Kelly
yep it's my gift to her and this the
steel Club is for you yes
oo
okay giving I'm giving her the the
shotgun right now and some other
stuff okay angry outside oh gosh they're
coming
in
oh good job FAA all right um we got it
all I think we're ready to go fun do you
want to head toward tier four beo in the
snow sure I'll I'll go snow I'm going to
stop all wait tra is already closed it's
so
noisy we can do did you take any quests
you took the Shaka Messiah Quest right
yeah no that's the that's the tier four
clear beoo next to the trader one yeah
you want to do that
singlehandedly or double-handed
destroying our house
no uhoh not our beautiful house not our
home on earth oh the turret is
working
zomes needs to work a little bit
better not good enough no
grny no he's com
for use the gun the side where are you
guys
again inside the building a look at this
oh my God it's electrified wait it's
crack a book the book store it's it's
just stunned is why walking on all fours
weirdo ah I'm
dying she broke the house oh no does
someone have words to fix
that I'm sorry no just the two blocks
are gone no worries that's fine someone
who died
me we had two dead ah
casualties oh so many dead bodies oh my
God dead bodies everywhere dead bodies
[Music]
everywhere
see
man um but at least your seed mod is
finished W woohoo wait see see I'm going
to put it down here on the floor if you
pick up your your bik then you can put
it on there in the modify window
okay uh it
was this one no that one's
lock oh wait uh you want to put it on a
mini bike right oh yeah do we have a
leftover any right now I think we had
one
it's
here yeah let see oh yeah M mine
probably my old one yeah yeah I'm back
for sorry that's so locked by music no
actually no it's not who who last used
this one uh crony right oh
yeah
[Music]
crony you got to unlock
it so we can put the seat mod on
yeah how's it going Gigi are you I'm
checking out the farm I'm looking for
eggs now EG thank
you I also have um 100 cloth if you
would like a 100 cloth I kind of need
Aloe now okay it's in the desert go to
the desert start
punching in the desert
where is she oh there ah do we happen to
have repair kits oh wait we have two
extra
B ouch ouch ouch
ouch hello hello just parking my bike
across the street near this mountain are
you guys near oh you guys left me hello
no no no come here come here come here
you come here you come here I'm coming
Callie while we wait let us loot the
place oh yeah you just want to loot it
while we wait well it's going to reset
anyway so you might as well Lo the place
okay but I think um it's over for
me why would I find repair do we have
any or is it
over it's not over till it's over I can
pick you up if you want kids no no no uh
uh uh CeCe yeah it's the other mini bike
I don't know who locked the other bike
but uh there's one mini bike that's
locked by me I'll unlock this one okay
or
wait lock no it's unlocked it's unlocked
yeah if you pick it up then you can put
the seat mod on so pick it up take and
then
I
modify
okay yay now fauna did you ride off
without me I did you can you can pick me
up though okay are you on a bicycle or
what yeah I'm on a
bike uh where's the real go here where
biu is okay yeah where biu is where the
quest is I'll wait for everybody to get
here yeah doing some light looting
beforehand curio infect oh I should have
oh thank you we did it thank you I'll
catch
up bike Queen
uh how often do we need
oil uh every now and then but you can
get it from like in uh cars that are
still
intact um when you wrench
them who's making these noises yeah I I
hear scary sounds out here too oh I
meant bicycle bike noises oh that's we
spamming the honk no call I have level
five biker gloves come here
wow even better gloves thank you what
should we do with the old ones probably
probably give it to someone else yeah
you can yeah good
find uh see it is worth it to loot
before you do the quest true yeah extra
get extra goodies mhm are you girl
waiting for me it's
me I lost my
backpack it shouldn't show up on your
map
yeah yeah yeah yeah I just
respond oh yeah oh yall aren't too
far this Quest is going to be super easy
with all of us here for sure do we have
anything for infections with us uh uh no
usually Traders have those I only have
vitamins I too am very infected oh are
you 4.4 yeah do you have honey with you
some but I don't have any with me but
I'll find a tree stump on the
way he's guys when is the raid again uh
uh 10m in game day
22:00 on this day yes this day 22:00 oh
oh the new just we just passed midnight
so yeah I think is B hour in real
life yeah yeah okay I think I'm going to
go on a quick like five 10 minute break
I will be back and our house just going
to get some and
starving
okay see you in a bit a have a good
[Music]
break oh there's
fauna I'm here
fa uh think it's going four of us fa
what gloves do you have I'm coming I'm
coming I have you're coming I'm coming
Raider five gloves
she's probably fine biker gloves give
melee damage bonus they do I think my
Raider set is good for me I also give
melee bonus okay
good um if anybody has um magazines
for treasure hunter let me know treasure
H okay oh yeah there's such thing as
Treasure Hunter magazine wait everybody
needs to take Band-Aids ra oh thank you
everybody stay bandaged up take these
thanks I'll take my bandaid let's
freaking go B
boo take these thank
you only I had a
GPS follow the Road North wait oh you're
going that way no no well I I wanted to
go north but I can't find a road that
scores nor it's a bit of a windy
road actual Road uh you could have just
taken the road from the same Road North
all the way was there a road there's
just m one from our house oh no yeah
yeah there's like an intersection and
then you go up I'll find the snowy area
yeah I'll go there
now we'll probably anyone need
food I never turn down a meal fauna okay
here's some food thank you how about
water
thank you going for the mountain guys
Water bottled water I need I need water
o pure mineral
water what B's got all the good thank
you IU do you need water I have water
okay dang it I feel like we've finally
really gotten into the groove of the
game and now we're going to stop playing
D it we're so efficient
now I got so good yeah yeah definitely
the first few days were pretty rough
yeah it was hectic but once you learn
the
stuff what season two is for day one
heat up does anybody use axes look at
how big this map is just for chopping
wood oh okay uh here's a level four axe
for chopping
wood stone or steel or
iron iron H I only have a stone still oh
maybe like this m yeah maybe giggy has
yeah giggy what's your uh axe
like um I have a level five iron fire
axe oh okay mine's Lev four so that
yours is bad okay is everybody here or
I'm coming we will wait just got my
steel Club too yeah no more baseball
bats still Club time so beautiful here I
know it's my favorite area snow
area no that's not
is run any dire wolv no not yet Are
there many here di wolves are easy now
though are they yeah they they really
are they really are they're not mind if
I just never mind he's not
open a traitor oh he open tomorrow
probably by the time we finish this to
be
honest this will be a quick one am here
oh hold on I found I found some more
loot boxes in in the place that we're
about to Quest let me just open them
real fast thank you
uh oh you ran off okay get my mods
off okay I'm coming back me mod my club
real quick brand new club
I know I don't need to drag them but
just let me drag
them where did I bring this wa wa do you
have
Band-Aids yeah
five
water you think it's strong water I'm
fine right now why don't you take one a
bite of food would be nice okay how some
food
thanks yippee I wonder if it's strong
okay are we
ready to give them to CR
for okay I am starting
woo um I don't like this lagging my
microphone right off the B oh yeah big
lag oh hello he's really having a bad
time with the clubs
nobody likes to have a bad time at the
club I always have a bad time at the
club same that's why clubs
anymore that sounds like I ever went to
clubs but I really
didn't I know what I like and I know
what I don't
like the uncomfortable
spes
greed y' Raider outfit level five are
you for real oh we just crafted that
braah for
free this is making me mad this
place oh there's stuff happening over
there yep lots lots of stuff happening
yeah I as I yeah we can give them to
someone else
oh heck yeah hey they sprayed my knee
these jerks whatch do you kisses
[Music]
again it's just too fun to use the club
I I know the shotgun is better but
you're saving
bullets who's doing that to me thank you
I'm bleeding ah okay hold up not
anymore fauna's bandage makes it
better yeah thank you
haven't touched a single enemy
yet yeah I'm sure more will come out in
fact there's some up here or around here
some
workers just taking their time
oh hello don't run past
me something K what level of cooking are
you by the way should you be maxed by
now no I wish I'm all
I'm only 47 explosive
magazine take
these what are exposive magazine surely
I will get an electric shock if I try to
rench this right
chat
possibility
tra there's a high
probability no they're scaling all the
all the freaking walls
wow but that's
10,000 not worth my
time how' you get out there we have oh
parkour oh
no
whoa using these blocks for good wow
Minecraft actually they don't have much
HP on these Gates there's a there's a
hole on the ceiling on the roof right
here with stuck oh that's the the chest
that I hammered out for a long long time
oh
oh there's a lot of dud oh
hello uhoh that's bad lag H
[Music]
doggy sorry dog go away dog
byebye dog we did it nice we did it now
we that big locked wait let me let me
lockpick it
oops how difficult is it to kill a bear
um you got
this yeah you're probably fine that's
totally going to do the
trick wow really oops
okay oh there's more stuff back here too
wow good uh here's bullets for kihala
bullets for cie thank you also there's a
safe back here level five nerd
outfit
wow I partially unlocked it I think B
will do a better job though which one
wait back here where I am I'm a little
far in but there's dropping ah there she
goes oh I was muted I said does anybody
have some the nerd outfit or I can use
it thank you you can have it okay use it
thank you thank you that's so
cute right didn't even need to make it
where is she yeah B will probably do
better your shorts your boxy
shorts cute oh that is
cute is it Ultra sty I would
definitely go around like
that
100% it's going to be cold in the snowy
area for you no problem was cracking it
open oh uh what's in it do you do you
use iron Knuckles
F no oh okay I'll give them to you
anyway anyone else who needs a uh ra
here's some
arrows do you want to help me wrench the
safe okay I can rench too wait do you
guys have Salvage ability wait it's
already
open yeah the material okay oh it does
give you
stuff although I'm really I don't have
iron problems anymore chat I don't our
iron problem Days Are Over yeah thanks
to
Gigi never need iron again I have ammo
for youo I
have
[Music]
too thank
you Callie I have a book for you oh is
it a shotgun Messiah book
it's shoter shotgun weekly a shotgun
weekly let's go you might want to learn
this schematic this might be useful for
drones
later uh here you
go thank you thank you don't forget your
ammo B
Boo there's some 9 mm so nerdy oh thank
you oh thank you what does it say
yield armor crafting
also and then here's explosive explosive
weekly oh
here oh thank
you of baseball bats I can't kill this
[Music]
bear figure it out fight
harder fight
[Music]
harder I shot it with so many arrows oh
no you did what you could
yeah ranching the cars makes more
sense need the
gas are we going to a different quest uh
the trader just opened so I'm just going
to take my stuff TR okay good to the
tr get on I'm Bing I'm already Traer I'm
already why would you do that I want to
flex my B my my motor to you turn I do
want to ride on your bike where's this
entrance to this guy was it here the
doors won't open for you is the thing
what yeah it's messed up what why what
how dare he not open his doors oh
because you you don't have the class
[Music]
yet oh I I'm coming in
anyway are you breaking down the door oh
I open it not too
shabby oh is that easy see how you
handle the next one of
course oh
yikes
okay can I put this on my Knuckles
buy he's so cool wow he's seen some [\h__\h]
Let Me Shine my little flashlight
at hello let me talk to you hope to see
you soon and you got infestation Quest
prove it a cigar that's
it oh I need these but oh I need Pockets
I need antibiotics do we have antibi we
don't have antibiotics do we uh I can
probably buy these from Trader Jen I
don't know oh he's not selling
antibiotics
huh I'm also
infected yeah
okay was bunker
Buster against
Stone B have you read Pistol Pete Volume
let me
T I'm going to heal myself yes I'm
done
okay maybe these um could be
good how do you when you have different
kinds of ammo how do you choose which
one you're using or does it is there no
way I don't know I don't know how to
make it use my piercing
ammo hold r
to when ah holding it you can choose
what you're reloading I guess okay I see
okay can I Ste
his steal I
can I'm looting his stuff you're looting
it he doesn't care I know he has a sign
that says you loot I shoot but he
doesn't seem to enforce
it I don't know I I think he might
there's am over here ky dropping just a
little bit of ammo for you thank
you oh yeah we can loot his stuff yeah
there's a lot of ammo around you guys
should loot his stuff oh drop this wait
Kelly here yeah oh two times shotgun
shells behind you thank
you here here I sir
very
helpful I'm lost yeah this Co
lit nice I can't believe he's just
letting us loot
him nice I guess he's afraid apprciate
it oh can I use this Forge no I guess
not he thinks we're super scary
destroyed Forge has a forge head pick it
up what a man he's got a couple forg a
heads I have a forg a head for you too
the cement mixer also had
a welcome back hey welcome back
enjoy youve
consumed I wonder the other Traders have
the that kind of stuff I think I put it
away oh yes everything I need all of
them should have destroyed benches and
stuff I guess so I never tried touching
them I thought they would like get angry
at me
what's the worst they could
do oh yeah guys does this work on non-
machine guns too it's it's a schematic
again I need 70 steel and maybe a couple
more shotgun parts I bet we be good
steel is at home plenty yeah I know we
got steel plenty of Steel that's good
for shotgun parts I think we also have
enough shotgun parts I'm not going to
spend all my money here you kidding me
help you might have something yummy
flatter the brains of a zed head just
fills my heart with joy
H
cucumber does he so cucumber I think his
stuff is good it's better than the other
Traders he's cool this guy is cool who
dropped that do you guys remember when
we would get Dent
Terry sometimes
sometimes you got to eat the sandwiches
yeah sometimes so
hungry okay a cream I don't know about
all that I just don't know all right I'm
running back to the house unless did you
guys take a quest I took a quest you're
running back to the house I did take a
quest I got the
quest took one
to there's quest to the West Bas and
kiah is to the West yes to the West
shall we take those real quick sure we
can do those proba do it real quick yeah
F's first cuz it's on the way and then
Kiara's okay oh fa where are you I'm
coming gig are you still at the old
house yeah I'm not going to eat the sh
are you kidding me okay I you can look
at my work I'm very excited to see the
viewers work that's the sole reason I'm
coming don't worry yeah
getting picked up by a hot lady with a
hot motorcycle yeah oh I like that
horn I don't even know how to activate
it how do you h x x
x yay
ah you got to go
h i I don't have my hands on your waist
anymore though
in
the chilling can anybody give me a ride
oh yeah I can give you a
ride and I'm encumbered I'm outside
here I I to unlock it one
second oh it's the wrong way actually
why did I follow B
boo West
West you got to go oh this is nice this
is luxurious mhm we're really fast now
yeah you are the queen of the biker gang
I am I provide all the bikes I'm jealous
I got to get a
motorcycle uh season two everybody will
be next step is everyone motorcycling CL
who hey I'm driving
here I think lag must have happened
again yeah I didn't see anything through
the Mountain St Mo going Evil Six I
think we're going to the church up the
hill yeah there's a path there's a
path there oh there's a bear kill it
kill it a bear go go
go
oh no we miss
wow why got to level up from that
leaching exp
yeah oh
wow lot of stuff okay if only he was
here we could reew our triple take this
no oh that's mine I have to go to the
church why do people renew their vows
was one time not enough like do you not
believe each other than you I got the
they want to have
party again yeah just have a part
sometimes you just need a party for no
reason sometimes I wake up and I'm like
good job me party party time yeah butra
myself because I just want you to look
at how in love we
are oh so you're just trying to show off
yes what happens when you don't have
time for a party anymore and then you
haven't reup them 40 years it doesn't
matter anymore we're still in love it's
okay we'll do it when we die
okay you say
so the exclamation mark is over here
okay where I hate those
churches there's always wacky [\h__\h] going
on
here
wait where you guys
going oh we're following I just chch
church Cathedral why is she biking over
there what about me guys where you guys
headed
I don't know where do a quest where you
[Laughter]
going wait R yeah R is
here wait here here okay where I'll take
the wheel wait oh oh yes he's here
here I was looking
is everyone here
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah ooh wow
ooh oh boy watch out there's a hole okay
there's a
hole check it out
holy
oh you like it you know what I do yeah
it's really cool go all the way around
it's it's it's great thank you big mold
wa what the heck wa good job good job G
work really hard on this I can't be
sarcastic or insulting you're you're
impressed genuinely actually ironically
good genuinely impressed by
this I love your we more I felt it's
over yeah you it's kind of over shot
gun's very op it don't fall in the
trenches when you're in the battlefield
cuz you will not be able to get your
stuff
back oh yeah during the hoard be careful
cuz we definitely won't be able
to I'm in the dang catacombs oh wow
found the catacombs the
catacombs no cats though a man
the point
welc get to my
crib thank you oh actually that's
supposed to be a good thing oh drop loot
paa said you stay down you hear that
sir listen to her oh down here's the
catacombs a lot of I hear a lot of
noises I hear a lot of noises but I
don't see yeah figures zombies it's okay
here how do I take off uh a weapon mod
that I put on my weapon uh you unclip
your weapon and then hit modify and then
you drag
it oh it's not letting me it's like it's
locked
something okay
unequip I think I'm going in
circles kind of oh there's bookshelves
around
too if you don't mind I don't really
know how I would to say about that cuz
you know I am okay oh I fell into a hole
do not fall into a
hole no I haven't maybe avoid any of
that I have remember which way I went
yeah she's fine she's
living open up
FBI is here what are you hiding
oh maybe
nothing oh it's a book I can't where are
you where did
you oh oh do you see okay come to the
when you're facing the house all right
Fallen where you're at right now fallen
I am so lost
my I
was they never going to come here G why
would you go this I was thinking this
this the most impressive thing you've
ever done I think
yes me I'm going to leave again tring to
M I got to go this
way uhoh that girl
is that seems
bad how do you get out of here whoa
oh W okay I opened up a big congregation
is here oh no did I punch you kiaha oh
maybe it's okay do you have
Band-Aids yeah oh my God this is a
lot you found something nice to oh lag
lag lag lag lag lag probably get out of
the way before I get
myself Hammer
Time Hammer Time another one
[Music]
we just Disturbed a big zombie
party yeah was it a wedding oh behind
you what a beautiful wedding open
there's some other stuff you can look at
though I just took uh what did I
take it luten forgets immediately what
she took is more interesting for someone
else I'm full where the zomos at
zos I'm very F there's a still a cooking
magazine up here I have no space for
it oh I'll read
cooking still got to make us more
delicious food wait I picked it up out
the out the one slot but that one I
don't know maybe if you can pick that
stuff up too Pi it
up I still have two magazines for you o
oh I'm actually done with the
fist
nice don't really I don't really
personally aspire to be a a Fister so
maybe Gigi should be reading made it in
there
yeah it's her Destiny shut up where did
you die shut up J how did you die shut
up somebody behind this wall it's sounds
like it oh yeah
course waa who was here before where's
your loot should I do I need to break
any of these spikes for your loot no I
got it are you I'm at the top of the
church oh
Jesus on the ro oh there's birds at the
top of the church ah that'll do it have
F oh here
oh this is
cool how does one climb higher that bird
was the last
one okay wait where is where is the big
area with loot cuz there's always got to
be a big area with loot so we got to
find
that maybe up there on the roof you
think May how do you get up there ladder
ladder on the wait I think I see
something suspicious that might happen I
mean surely there's a better paff but I
just don't have
eyeballs oh gosh I feel like I'm going
to fall off the roof it's slippery no
careful it did feel
slippery I found the
loot oh where was it it's it's in the
it's in the tower at the tippy top I
knew it I'm going to need help though
cuz I'm almost out of space okay uh
let's see not sure how to get there I'm
bird forcing my way in right now with my
hammer through it's very scary up here
it's okay there's nobody's left but it's
so
slippery I'm the jump King what oh
this how did you get there people I'm I
can't find the right way hard I'm on the
roof though uh here here let me
let me uh no I'm not no I'm not I'm
dying without ding my hardcore broke my
my tire leg oh did you miss the jump I
saw
that you didn't see
anything from there I guess oh they just
going to have to be encumbered
B I see
now
yeah I'm
coming oh
I'm here welcome to the
[Music]
stash what's in it lots of stuff that I
have no room
for actually I don't have much room
either but the mega
curtain Mega curtain it spans two
stories all the clove oh I have four
available points what the heck uh who's
learning wiring electrical I'm learning
sort
[Music]
of and electrical trap crafting yeah
that too sort of I found another Millie
robot turret level four we have a friend
oh we're going to be so decked out for
defenses for this
hord nice yeah should we start preparing
about now
okay I guess that's it people right yeah
I took some things did you did you take
the stuff out of all the boxes yes you
did okay cool we're good pretty empty
mhm uh how to I guess we here
again oh lockpicking I probably
[Music]
should oh
robbing some Graves
again like that I found another shipping
crate that I have no space
[Music]
for yeah I got to
eat then I'll probably head back to the
house well we there was one more Mission
wasn't there h i don't have room for the
at next Miss oh yeah going home might be
the best idea
then I too am cucumber for the
max the traitor's on the way so did yeah
yeah I think they're mad at me for some
reason I'm not sure why they're mad at
you but why H why are these zombies so
angry at me after I robbed the grave
Wonder we're taking a shortcut we're
taking a
shortcut does that damage your bike by
chance yes but damages
me I got some exp so mad
bro chill I like shortcuts and I like
flying too no
problem 50% carrying
capacity huh oh you woke up
again didn't expect them pretty
resilient
there's so many grapes for you choose
one okay where is my it's so
loud are you still fighting
FAA no I'm headed
home how how with what how on my on my
my little bike why why why why why why
why why why why why why why why I got I
got to get I got to get home every
minute counts to do yeah I'll I'll catch
up to you
now I'll make you regret that you took
your mini bike or
bicycle I built this to impress you why
I am impressed I'm very impressed but
you don't like it do you not like
motorcycles environment
a so
cool this is like
this like a married man in the middle of
Crisis getting himself a motorcycle
while his wife wants a
minivan why didn't you get a minivan for
our
family I don't know like them like can I
not just make one of my dreams come true
for once
you can you can you're free to ride your
motorcycle well I thought you would be
happy about it and appreciate it I do
and that we would share en into the
desert to get a bunch of aloe really
fast wait my
turn we can do that let's see uh let me
sell all
this okay we have plenty of these do you
want to ride
home please okay hey I'm so
heavy me too oh oh sorry sorry do we
need robotics Parts I don't think we do
do we
[Music]
let's I don't think so I'm going to hold
I'm going to hold on to them just in
case though because I'm going to be so
mad later on if it turns out tax driver
I'll leave you a good review please Uber
good review thank
you here
sh can I have a discount
[Music]
Let It Go I don't think there's really
anything that I need go here I feel like
my timer's wrong
again oh no can someone
make eight metal fences and railings
they seem to be pretty cheap but they
need a forge and I'm at the old house I
can probably make some wait why just
eight thank
you uh because I'm making like a small
Tower and I don't want us to fall down
so trying to make around iy Tower yeah
Tower
nice that would be very
useful how did I break my leg and how
you broke your leg a little boo I have a
splint I also need honey again that's a
comfy ride yeah isn't it look I have a
you have a drink to the side so if you
get thirsty you can drink yeah
exactly I'm eating right now yeah the
the Uber come it's like the high the
high effort Uber with like you can play
games in the back and with music and
stuff yeah with snacks you need any
Advil
[Music]
I any
mirax what does that one
do I don't know I never tried it wait
isn't that a LAX is LAX oh yeah good
thinking Vio
yeah that is what that would
be I'm getting really hungry
too well you know who's also getting
hungry the
zombies no I mean IRL the zombies are
getting getting hungry banana today no
no banana
banana you just have like 20 minutes I
think to get a snack IRL
oh I'll myself eat my Pringles
Pringles I want eat sounds good
yeah do you think this is High Enough
full snipy tower pretty good yeah looks
good yeah please please honey honey
honey honey honey honey yeah honey
gotcha it's real honey
[Music]
gotcha
good actually
meat I'm out of
meat okay the IRL hunger and the in-game
hunger
are
unbearable I'm pretty hungry too I have
not eaten today not at all today or no
well typically I don't eat 12 but it is
like almost 2:00
p.m. it's like 10 p.m. for me oh you
haven't eaten all day oh no all day it's
normal no no it's normal it's normal
just kidding it's
normal huh huh no that's just my normal
routine we make some rice dang it well
then again if you go to sleep you you
won't really need that energy
so just playing games I don't really
need the energy I'll need the carbs
until
later yeah we're just playing games
games doesn't take that much energy yeah
just some mental energy I guess just
checking out some things Gamer's eating
schedule thanks for all the amazing work
on it I'm so glad I have things to say
but I'm waiting till the
end but I've been having a great spee
speech speech spee spe speech spech
spech spech it's before
SP before the raid oh yeah let's do like
a motivational a motivational like thing
where you go down the line on your horse
and we like you die not this
day yeah it is not this day it is not
what say you you know all that stuff I
Brothers
Brothers yes that's right for the
emperor for froto in the ring yeah yeah
that too middle yeah what
youah huz huzzah I don't
think
here you have enough steel for me to
make my gun oh I need to make sure I can
make my gun in time let me get that
steel I just put a 100 Steel in the
chest oh heck yeah thank
you o
crunchy oo w
I a walnut ricotta salad yesterday oh
that sounds really good it was
yum was definitely yum the ladies
enjoyed
it can you take the shotgun shells out
of the chest no I haven't taken them yet
you should take them I will a little bit
more all right we make a the shotgun
really quick cuz it's going to take
time ce's shooting at me she's killing
me
party what did you do to make her mad is
the question she does like it exactly
thank you she was flashing at crony she
no I wasn't ran away and then she kept
running after her I wasn't I was showing
her my bald
head here
yeah it's very
cannot carry you
far the
ammo shotgun sh I'll you I'm screamers I
hear I got no time for
you oh she's in the
pit help oh yikes I got you
where's everyone oh I'm
coming I don't got oh the turret's doing
work so
cool dang it when they raged allll it
doesn't mean they're dead I got to
remember that yeah that's not
work this to is birth RP what are you
talking about nothing what is no I want
to know I know I sound incredulous but I
just want to know what does that mean
I don't I don't
know I why say it GG I I don't know
say I say it I don't d d they told me to
say
it of my own will GG is always sing to
Max say it say what this this Che is
birth role
[Music]
play what on your head now sorry
okay wish I knew what it
me this needs to be another chest um
bber do you need grenades yes please
okay I'm going give you some grenades G
are you the only one using arrows I
think ra is too I am using arrows I have
exploding arrows but thank you oh oh
oh going to put a picture
on yes take these exploding arrows but I
need to explain to you how to knowingly
use specific
armor if you are on your bow I guess you
press R you hold R and then you choose
the ammo you're shooting with now make
sure when you're using the exploding
arrow that there's not any funel or so
around it could explode in the vicinity
take this beer I have beer for you
boom boom boom boom
yeah I'm excited yay every time on in
the street I hear you fa do you want
rotten flesh in the ingredients chest or
elsewhere yes in the ingredients chest I
the shotgun mod for you you do what kind
of shotgun mod I'll take itun choke mod
oh that's a good one you can go ahead
and put it in the mod chest I think
that that will be nice
thank
you some story still fighting out there
huh are they I still hear sounds do I
need to go help how to use armor
piercing I wonder I guess nobody what
are they talking maybe a tree or
something oh the turret oh yeah I think
they're quiet now can't find them
anymore tur's doing work
good baseball bats
oh are they in the huh maybe
inside or in
the no huh not in the mod could they be
on the
roof could they be why why would they
choose to be on they might be deep they
D or maybe CU they're
oh I found
it it was in the
M oh okay be
right
finally armed and
ready okay I made a lot more
gunpowder who's worried about their ammo
not being enough I think I have enough
give me like a thousand
I call you think you got enough ammo yep
I have plenty I have like over 500
rounds for a shotgun is just a lot sure
if that's enough you don't think
so depend are you going to Mele
too well M melee I'm just going to do my
you know Club just
ammo and in terms of uh armor do we have
any with a chest piece below
four probably not at this point right I
don't think so I made it for nothing
where's my mini but oh I have a forged
ahead for you I'm putting all the boxes
all the books in the Box the tech ones
too can use
this
where's should I made my bow pink it's
so pretty yeah
yay nice sir
I've already read the shotgun
Messiah I'll read a couple of these
um Team
workor good idea fly Decked
Out G G look I got an electrifying
stick it's why are you trying to hit me
with it I'm I'm I'm 5 m away from you oh
sure me is right next to me ladies
ladies I just wanted to show her my
stick I don't understand she's hitting
me with her stick I'm
not okay I'm going I'm going to the
whole house okay I'm going to head there
soon
too me
too see my house please bring fence
thank you I need
this but I can get in myself no we got
plenty at the house welcome back I got
it thank you can you bring us food okay
I bring food
thank what did you want for uh steel
iron uh it's called let me see see it's
called metal fences and railing it needs
iron and
Clay
uhhuh how
many 10 10 10
okay
course um I'm going to try to get some
more aloe can I borrow somebody's
car oh is in like wait you can use our
bike where is
it somewhere outdoors in front oh is
this it yes the cool one thank you I
will be right back so close you will
definitely be right back with that speed
yeah K would you also be able to uh give
me any armor if possible that's fine
need the truck because I we have I have
time for this I don't have time for this
do I you might not yeah it's already six
we probably should go yeah I didn't real
what are the what are the levels on
yours CC I don't have that much time
anymore but let me let me know
uh the levels on my hopefully we have
enough band don't forget to break oh I'm
going to I'm going to grab the Bandaids
and healing items from the the new house
soov and
shoes that would be nice I'll give you a
better uh chest I have one nice
um oh I wonder if I can make it
so oh these are mods I don't need
them we're looking
organized o oh that storm is starting
storm
some here it's almost time ahie
[Music]
this will be easy bring in everything
I've
got yeah everybody bring your
aame level four when I have a level for
example in my skills right and then it
says like level one level too and then
the third one even though I have skill
points it's like a lock how do I you
have to uh level up your main stat so
whatever attribute it is level up the
attribute stat and it should be unlocked
as it levels up okay need a better level
so for this one okay I cannot make more
than that I I don't have time no problem
I think we're
good so for this
one and how do I know what though uh so
it should it's the stat on the very top
of the page so the same page that you're
looking at to say a tribute whatever oh
okay to level that
Classic Home back to the original house
the first one
we it all comes from
Circle yeah the house that we built
together the first one we found together
I want to set up like three different
turrets hopefully that'll be good too
yeah for
sure no doubs we're going to do
it no don't break a
leg no don't break a
leg I found a
chicken is there food at the old house I
suppose yeah no did somebody pick up all
the food and take it to the old house I
think somebody else got some too was
empty bringing all the the health items
but I I didn't bring fluid oh maybe I
have all of it we don't have that much
hopefully it's
enough I'm share with each other I got
me for
days I
have what did I put them in did I make
them oh God oh God oh God oh
God come to me I put the food in the
food box in the old house okay
thank you very
much
who here we
go very soon you better get over here
I'm almost there oh this
scary you'll be fine SN the
chicken you're heartless where should we
put our bikes I I put where do you think
your food I put the bike inside the
house if you can drive it into the house
I would suggest doing that okay we'll do
what abrasion is that what I have right
now oh you need a
Band-Aid oh yeah okay that helped I
think oh my God it's so well
fortified I wish there was a way to to
shoot from okay in the in the food box
I'm also going to put some healing oh my
God oh my God oh my God did you fall oh
my God
she fell she's dead it's over y get out
of
here know how okay guys don't be very
careful my
backpack get out I thought that I could
drive my bike
and I'll get out get out that's why I
said be very
careful oh that was the one thing to not
do stay on the
bike I wanted to ride the bike into the
house but I should have just picked it
up dang
it oh God oh God well atast know a hard
time get in the house I was just testing
it out yeah test I'm here what weap are
you using again I'm using a bow you want
to come with me on my tower on my snipy
tower yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
come here come here all right
oh okay your backpack should be free are
you sure the spikes kind of look a
little that's a nice
[Music]
place eventually I'll go into the field
and fire
everyone okay wait who's that oh people
right behind you is a dead chicken if
you want to H oh scavenge the dead
chicken Jesus oh
[Laughter]
Jesus I'm going to die we have
more over there I I put the healing in
the ingredients test okay yeah how do I
pick this up oh man
Callie can you fall again we can we can
pick up the it's fine fine the backp for
her I know it's hard it's fine all her
Loops in there it's okay oh it's right
it's on the top this time
it didn't fall to the where's the
ingredients chest that was the plan wait
you don't mean at the new house do you
no no no in the in the in the old house
where know it's going to be very good
the fortification wait did you take the
ones out of the healing chest yes okay
there's my bag oh are you in the old
house or new house old house okay uh
it it's in the food chest going my bike
wait we had way more didn't
we uh is that all we
have oh I have some in my inventory I
can put some more in a thank
you st I have
like we did I thought
so that's all that's all I
found okay well that's that's fine
I am so ready maybe I gave a lot out
maybe let's see hair
kit is crony here not in the be see can
you leave real quick I want to build
rail
Lings that thank
I had the better shotgun did you make an
even better one no it's just a level two
pump action instead of the one that she
has yippe sis crony I'll go find her my
hero she up there she might be up there
oh nice
fat trying but I kind here in the hole
it's kind of
annoying oops she was behind
can I pick up stuff that I've built or
do I have to destroy
it honestly don't know I think you have
to pick it up um but it might it might
be effective who claimed this land maybe
the the person who claimed the land can
pick it up only
maybe oh who claimed the land I don't
know who claimed the
land who claimed this land whose land is
this whose land are we on
the land oh
we Kelly is this your land I mean kind
of can you come and pick this up for me
pick what up I don't know the middle
ofwhere a fence I didn't put a fence
down no I put it down but apparently you
might have to pick it up oh okay hold up
I'm coming I can break it stop stop
don't
break I think she got it okay we've got
lots of food and Buffs in the food chest
make sure you have food and water and
heels and everything I think we're
good no okay let's break
it be able to take us can I break it
yeah you can break it now I jumped too
high why you sto
me cuz I wanted Celly to pick it up but
I don't know if you care me do we have
pal like this in the back too yeah
because you claimed the land so we see
that you have to
like I'm going to get down a bit
more more of a lower shooter
dang this is well fortified
yeah really are just kind of broken
honestly we can't survive to any
hord the the spikes is just there's so
many if we had one more week we could
have iron
spikes yeah yeah we could make sure to
eat four bites in the in the chest those
will give you damage reduction how long
does that go on 6 minutes oh okay oh
it's in a chest okay
I will yell before I throw my fire
F okay nice
okay right here we go you can try to
drink recog too it will increase your
range damage but I don't know if it
makes you
drunk oh is it starting let's go
starting let's
go let's freaking go do your best
they're coming from from the back the
back hill back hill back hill are
okay I put a trench back there too
there's a
trench oh well oh boy oh it's so
dark Goa Goa something hurts you you are
so like uh you're blending in with with
the darkness it's hard to see hard to
see the green as well
wait why does this make me drunk oh my
gosh I thought I was immune to this no
the
alcoholism just not beer well that's
fine I can deal with this it's the first
time I'm
using oh gosh oh that's okay that's F I
must watch
out there's a lot of cop zombies
spawning huh
not surprise what are you arresting us
for what did we do what do we do oh
yeah you guys are totally not Haring a
criminal oh someone got inside what uhoh
that's not good I definitely closed the
door not inside inside yeah close the
front door if you
can you should be closed thought I mean
someone got inside I I'm looking
fortification
maybe oh great maybe should have checked
that first it's fine
so
far why are they all coming from
there he's going to blow blow oh God W
wa
firor uhoh come do you have a repair kit
I'm going to fix my spikes I have repair
kits too if you need
some I'm double
yeah it definitely gets kind of laggy at
about this point seems like I can't
repair my assault that's weird
okay wait how are you trying to do it I
click on it and the repair thing is
grayed out for some reason do you have
aair I have six leg okay I'll go out on
the field with
my all right I'm going to throw fire
watch out I'm throwing fire
run run
okay are they still coming from the
south going to blow watch
out I forgot bring
[Music]
my the rest of
the see hold on can you can you give me
back I'm I'm outside right now but
okay zombies are on the back uh oh in
the house oh
God we can take them I'm taking a med
break can't
see oh oh is that setting our spikes on
fire uh it might be but it it is also
helping Kill the Zombies
true
that yeah it is I need just one yo that
range on his bomb is
crazy oh is this not what I
[Music]
need don't hold the line codyy hold the
line what is that what even is
that what is
that oh not this one this one
I don't want to use that one fire where
are they I can't see of the
back it's so hard to see we should light
up the area
yeah you think they're changing where
they're coming from they all want to
come from that side today I don't know
why they're switching it
up like they
know nice does it kill them when they F
oh they're coming from the front now by
the way you want to come from the front
really really they're testing all our
defense see how it
is this is much of a long range weapon I
will say is fa there I don't want to
yeah that's I am there okay always there
everywhere oh that's
cool like naked
she died I think oh no I'm going to
throw again for a run possible where am
I oh
hello protecting my front porch they
keep slipping into them
oh keep running keep
[Music]
running it's good when you're Mass these
hordes you can just shoot it right in
the middle of it like a hurting
dog running oh no that's I'm
sorry okay you didn't hit me it's fine
keep running it's hard to tell it's
really hard to tell keep running we need
to dye our armors just so that we can
tell each other apart that would be a
good idea actually
ouch okay oh boy spray pray spray spray
oh gosh they're on fire yeah yeah I'm
throwing a lot of Fire
fire fire am I right ladies the
fire which
one oh that's good that's good that's
good that's good
uhoh my arm is
[Music]
broken counts for
my it is getting very lag to be broken
yeah it's so lagging it's really lagging
hard fire
hoping it's hitting something in real
time oh
God God is it the
fire I can't handle nothing's moving
nothing's moving we might we might die
cuz oh wait wait wait wait wait so we
it's coming back it's coming back it's
coming back at least it's not just me
all right I'm going to I'm going to
pause on the fire throwing now
oh God what's
happening I can't sh oh please no fire
ah because
my makes sense
um oh God train the leg oh no I'm
blaming
the good ridiculous it's
you that was ridiculous okay is a cast
better than a splint definitely oh as
far as I fine h no freaking way I wonder
if this is any
better right now the lag is okay oh no
that's sorry I'm touching it
everybody
okay this is a bad bad place to spawn oh
turrets help
me oh dang oh my
gosh where are you s
are you dying out there uh I was dying
but I'm back inside now I'm just going
to get some heal oh gosh oh no I'm
strugling lag lag lag lag lag lag I'm
really drunk right now so don't walk in
front of me cuz I'll almost certainly
hit you by accident the game is not
responding I'm just drinking and
punching oh no Cy did you get kicked out
of the game I I got dced yet no I to all
of us I have a feeling no yeah let me
see
um oh man that was
intense This Is How They really beat us
so crazy up knew it would be the only
way to beat us yeah ex hope you get back
in cie yeah my I'm doing my best I join
the party again when you here oh yeah
let me uh
okay let me know when you're back in
wave
over doing great G thank you
shiori get him get him get
get fun when the next enemy come comes
please look when I when I Boop them with
a with the thing they fly away I've seen
it I've seen it it's amazing it looks so
silly is somebody out there right now oh
they're coming from the side
oh okay would be good to loot in between
but not enough time oh I guess so yeah
they
might I think it will
despawn
honey for the first raid it wasn't too
bad
wait I can Loot and shoot I don't mind
me too lagging from too [\h__\h] oh there's
a cop inside no in the house it's okay
it's okay SP that no pain he already
fell into the ow into the fit pit he
fits into the pits that's
proba how did he get in there I
wonder
okay good it is definitely struggling to
load but that's okay oh no
it's like wow there's a lot going on
right now in the server there's quite a
bit going on right now being held
together by gum duct tape and duct tape
maybe there's a way to strength from the
server somehow for season he's
[Music]
jumping you got to jump first okay there
are definitely enemies that can uh Jump
free blocks
high I'm so good right now
how drunk are you how many fingers am I
holding yeah how many beers have you had
tonight bird bird bird bird bir dead God
oh another bird ow what's that oh my God
it's back on my
porch help is that a
bird fell the holeo wait oh that was
Cece I'm so sorry I thought you were
zom my cat the hat
let it handled over there I have night
vision so everything is in black and
white so I can't tell who's wearing
what oh that sounds so
terrible head
off okay oh my god oh wo wo W welcome
back Li welcome back I'm so sorry
welcome back it's okay okay yeah come
from the side let's get him bird bird
bird bird got
it they run so coming up the
hill without lag I feel like I would
shoot a little bit
better so the flame is not
completely it's okay we're doing good
we're hanging in there we
are nice oh my God go so funny ow oh
yeah got to back
up thank you guys might be
concussed def only good to have lots you
killed
yourself I died don't kill yourself yeah
maybe don't do that I wonder if there's
like sexy Hoppers like in Minecraft that
can collect the loot
yeah right a Zombie
Farm oh there's definitely like
something like a farm that you can build
but I don't know about if there's
Hoppers Chad are there
hoppers need Hopper mod for the game get
smar about the for
XP oh yeah let me let me re invite
Callie I think that wave is over Callie
get in the party thank you is it over
the wave is over have
honey or
antibiotics yeah now are we oh the music
stopped the music stopped but it stopped
yesterday too oh wait no it's still
going it's still going it's still
going which side is it this time loot
loot while you can I did not see any
antibiotics in the
chest
already one in my chest next to the
laundry have yeah take it take
it oh the music stopped wait which chest
my chest is next to the laundry there
there's the
laundry H yeah in the basement floor ah
that real laundry it's over oh it's over
it's over think it's over the music
stopped yeah
zombies that was we so strong we're so
good we are strong they need to spr them
out a little bit
more they always end early and we're
getting like no freaking loot I have so
much stuff
left
H I wish we could get the
lo I got some lot of loot but it's next
to the spikes right
there if I want to go oh right yeah that
makes sense I can I can tried to jump
okay I
jumped I like giant CR someone someone
we did it
[Music]
I we did
it it was fine we're so
good good job the way our Fort is
fortified by now is kind of crazy we're
this we got really really really fixated
on how to how to fortify this
place they could barely touch us
yeah can't touch this
Yay song that plays at the
[Music]
credits do you tell us some words yeah
words this Victory hold let me blow my
nose
[Music]
it's okay well well well well well well
well well well well well well well
well deep Victory my my soldiers my
soldiers yes um soldja
boy soldja boy tell
them hey um thanks for playing want to
go up there yeah
position talking down above
everybody uh I just asked for the server
to be made and tried to figure out dates
so I don't really I also asked for art
to be made that's all that I really did
but to be honest people people joining
in you guys made me very happy joining
in the server you know I wanted to do
something more casual
G um I wanted to do something more more
like casual just play a game with each
other kind of thing instead of like
something that was like super hardcore
RP or like a hardcore server seven days
in a row was pretty rough though I think
next time we'll maybe space it out a
little bit seven days we die seven days
yeah but it was it was a great time and
I am very very grateful that you guys um
made time to be here CeCe are you good
CeCe I think you're dying Cece
Cece I just I just did all like just had
such a nice time
Dr going crazy no I tried to get some
loot sorry that's okay understandable um
but yeah I'm very happy because um even
with you guys I feel like um why I say
even why am I saying even with you guys
no you guys how do I say I feel like we
all got a lot closer and
[Music]
I'm get I don't know how to get close to
to people very easily without doing
things like playing games and stuff like
that so gam play people together I feel
like yeah it was just fun play a game
together you
know we do yeah let's do it again thank
you for
organizing thank
you wait can we somehow take a group
picture maybe if we're on our bikes we
could yeah yeah oh yeah let me get my
motorcycle
yeah Kiara's got the cool motorcycle oh
no she worked hard for that motor oh
fa I want to
die no my sweet get out of my spy trap I
don't know how to it's not
for okay excuse me I'm scared I'm so
scared right now excuse me all right
I'll go and get my stuck wait wait wait
wait wait
thank you thank you you made it you made
it
so okay I made it
yay all right let's line up our bikes
yeah maybe with the house in the back
yeah yeah that's a cute idea let's do
that can I have my SP
my you have your
what are you sure get on get on the
other
bike I think this might be the wrong
bike that oh no this one's mine oh it it
it has my storage in it yeah it's mine
never mind you're
right does anyone have space on their
bike I do you can get on if you'd like
can you unlock oh okay oh wait it is
unlocked it was the other
one okay I feel like I'm in
and I got the cash Shop Mount that is
like super
expensive how about we I think we're at
the wrong angle guys I think if we want
to get the spikes we got to do like here
get in front of it and then back into it
so like right here and then back it up
just don't back into the SP down the
hill just do not back into the spikes
it's very
important I'm scared okay it's not the
only one without a right now and a bike
partner should have brought one I think
there's one at home oh wait I have I
have a bike here can have my bike I got
a bike oh you got to B
okay I think I can get a good shot like
this the sun rising the oh
God watch out for the
[Music]
spikes I can't
manuver wait wait I I really can't I
don't know how to get into position H
okay you got to back it up
back it up back it up really bad at
that I'll do a big turn or like oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah I wish I could
make the names go
away there's a way to do that don't
erase our
names they just kind of overlapping we
all the same the turret is kind of in
the way you all look the same never
mind oh
oh this is really
difficult GS gamer
skills I have an idea why don't you pick
it up and position again and then you
jump right you're so right best so smart
Okay easy easy
here uh perfect y oh wait it's locked
again it's locked again ah okay unlock
okay there we go y oh we look so cool in
my picture
oh to ride seven seven rides seven
days R seven days to
ride you that we are exactly seven right
now Riders to ride wait but is eight
right yeah we're eight
it was almost perfect wa girls follow me
in one line let's ride into the
sun
together bad to the boat plays in the
background or can't touch this or
something
[Music]
[Applause]
playing again
somewhere
the they all rode off into the sunset
the
end yipp well technically this is
sunrise
W the biker gang is so cool
y oh don't die don't die
I guess that's it yeah it's not
it bike bye everybody uh I will I will
be reading some I will be reading super
chats in the like so I will continue for
a little bit oh yeah let's see let's see
catch you later
everybody thanks for playing thank you
thank you girls it was a pleasure
a lot of fun I enoyed being your
armor you did a great job I'm looking
forward to my motorcycle next next
season yeah next
season yes a little bit different times
maybe yes different probably different
time all right bye
everybody you
later
peace this is probably I should have
done oh I probably should press this by
but it doesn't matter Bye
[Music]
by
wow that
[Music]
was seven days to die I'm already logged
off can you not hear the menu music
that fun that was
great what an
adventure nice Adventure almost 1K yeah
almost
1K that was really fun I'm so glad I was
able to make my my
SMG um
and the SMG did a lot of work the the
boom boom explosives did a lot of
[Music]
work that was great I loveed that it was
so fun you took the treasure yeah the
treasure room by myself I didn't die I
totally thought I was going to die in
that in that one treasure room where I
was there for like 10 minutes boning
that Treasure Chest I was like oh
man it's uh it's the Cod training was
the C Cod
[Music]
training c training in clutch jumping
jumping is op
ah okay in this episode of how long you
can stall bble until bble has to go I do
have homework
today what is next game tomorrow we're
playing Space
Marines uh tomorrow playing Space Marine
Warhammer so we're going to we're going
to play that Brothers we're back
Brothers I've been itting to play so
bad no schedule this week yes schedule
um tomorrow Space Marines and
then Thursday is two collabs one with
kiaha gig Shori and then after is
Avent uh and then Friday is Gigi's
birthday collab and then Saturday I kind
of want to play
more more
TCG I want play with TCG I haven't
gotten the ghost we'll see that we'll
see and then Sunday we'll
play
um I think Silent Hill too if the perms
go through Silent Hill too if not then
another spooky game but spooky game
spooky spooky spooky
game
um I don't know
if like I said before if you want me to
play some spooky games then I have to
pause on some of the ongoing games that
I'm doing right
now um if you want if you want me to do
spooky game I'm just saying
[Music]
it's
October and then Monday Monday is
Kyla panor Kyla yeah panor Kyla is
Monday um gr oh I dropped my mouth oh
come back come back Mouse come back come
back why did you
fall okay there we go
okay reading supers now and then we can
till and talk why did someone send me a
Super Chat just saying Tik Tok bad what
is the context
of why is that the first Super chatter
yet uh PE s thank you for the super
watch Rock Tik Tok bad okay
but I'm still going to watch Tik Tok
videos before I go to
[Music]
sleep oh they're from YouTube shorts if
you if you watch YouTube shorts you are
just getting Tik tock content a week
late so if you are an enjoyer of Tik Tok
shorts is just as bad or not Tik Tok
YouTube shorts if you are an enjoyer of
YouTube
shorts you are enjoyer of Tik Tok videos
just
late and I am not wrong with this I
absolutely not wrong with this it Tik
Tok shorts is re-uploads
of Tik Tok
a lot of it is so just
saying just saying that's why you guys
are late on the
trends hey I have a brain Rod side but I
also have
a book reader how how many of you
actually read books
huh
anyway yay thank you for the super rock
rock good luck on the final day B this
has been a fun and chill series with the
occasional screams to to tune into I
loved all your interactions with the
other e members throughout yeah I like
this it was just casual you
know just us playing game together it's
it was so chill and nice this is my
ideal of just sitting in a voice chat
just playing game and chilling and just
doing
stuff it's nice
CeCe boy thank you for super rock rock
hey Babs it's my birthday today I want
to thank you for your hard work bring us
laugh and joy um and help me through
rough times over the year can I request
a cute happy birthday and Tha uh I'll
give you my best Tai a and
um happy
birthday to you happy
birthday
to you happy birthday happy
Happ happy birthday to you and a one
good uh happy happy one good happy one
good one good Med to oh no way that's
Japanese uh one good uh uh
um me cl one good what's suan oh yeah
suan suan one good okay there we go
happy
birthday
om I hope that was good for you
[Music]
yeah St thank you for the super rock
rock I can I I can do sort of atie
accent people
B
put
myang put
[Music]
I have I still have a slight thae accent
when I speak Thai it's not it when I
speak thae it is not it is not Western
tie okay at least I'm using a bit of a
at least I'm using the the the vocal the
vocal thingies Ty people would know Ty
people would know
can I speak English with a tie accent
uh
hello
everyone uh my
name is
bio h
a little
bit
uh give me a
sentence I'm just imitating
Momi a send
sentence uh a sentence
uh sticking out your Gat for
naris your
so B bow you're
so
beack I just
want to be
youry Jo oh that was a little Japanese
at the
end okay there we
go happy birthday I'm in thank you for
the super rock
rock ah C thank you for super rock rock
wait it's been 7 Days in zombie
apocalypse really enjoyed the relaxing
exploration intense fight with the horde
and of course the fun youall are having
have fun in the finale Y super fun I'm
ready to go back to bble gaming though I
miss bble
gaming so many clouds that I'm looking
over like H was behaving I you could see
me like flicker you guys be like are are
they okay are they are they fine am I
leaving them alone for too long huh huh
maybe I said uh uh are you guys
good are you guys behaving over
there
uh C thank you for the super rock rock
mark thank you for the super rock rock
hey people I love your content my
birthday's coming up soon can I get an
emo Birthday song you have to ask you
have to ask for Emil Birthday song I
suppose I guess I could give it to you
since you just you asked so hard happy
birthday to you whatever this is so much
effort for me happy
birthday to you it's not like I care
that it's your birthday or anything soon
happy birthday dear Pebble eat something
good or enjoy your
day happy
birthday to you it's not like I want you
to be happy or
anything
H thank you rock rock you're welcome
rock rock are you excited for Sonic's X
Shadow gener ations # the ultimate life
the ultimate life form yes I am excited
for it I haven't seen the shadow shorts
yet no spoilers on the shadow shorts
but I need to watch
those
um R Panda thank you for the super rock
rock hi hi bble it was neat to see how
you and the other girls naturally took
on roles supporting one another base
defense making things Supply runs would
you do anything different if season 2
comes no I must kill I am built for
killing I that is all that I'm good for
is killing so I will kill
yeah violence
killing saving my
friends accidentally kill my friends
violence
yes hey I contributed quite a bit to our
survival I really like the
thing I mean someone's got to take the
role of
killing great great
asset you had 19 Friendly Fire yes but a
lot like at least half of them are
people wanting to die especially in the
beginning like I accumulated a lot of
those player kills by people wanting to
die and I asked people to kill me
too no
hesitation but hey there was friendly
fire all over the place though B killed
me Callie killed me I think car killed
me once and ask the friendly fire wasn't
just me though it wasn't just me it was
all over the place can't help it
sometimes people just walk in front of
you anyway
obviously obviously though I would be
more careful if there were consequences
to dying
but there was absolutely no consequence
to die not even an exp
exp what is it exp de there was
absolutely no
consequence except for failing Quest
but I tried really hard not to kill
anybody while
[Music]
questing uh MN thank you for the super
rock rock FPS training off trading
paying off big
yeah I think
it's it's funny the the the FPS skills
are transferring over through games It
transcends games the the FPS skills are
are
helping wherever I
play it's
nice h s t thank you for the super rock
rock I can see you organizing a big
event like this someday it's simply in
your nature to be involved in everything
and help everyone as much as you can
definitely not false advertising when
you say you're down for
everything yeah I can see myself
organizing like a big gaming thing uh
probably not for a while though cuz I
could definitely use a break um and I
feel like we all could use a
break in in uh
and collab stuff for a
bit um bir thank you for the super rock
rock I am always down for everything I
should just I always feel like I have to
give a warning like hey heads up I might
not do every day hey heads up I might
not stream everything hey heads up uh
just so you know I might need a break
hey heads up but
then I will I will continue to give out
the warning though because I don't want
expectations don't expect anything from
me just be pleasantly surprised
don't burn out I
won't or it would take a lot for me to
burn out
because this is what I like to do so
like
uh I'm having I'm having too much fun
gaming and yeah and
stuff I honestly honestly thought I
might like like get burnt out of like
collabs a little bit um from this but I
didn't probably because it wasn't
RP so like it was very casual just
hanging out with friends sort of thing
so I was like oh this is
fine this is this is fun so
yeah it ended up being a little RP but
not like High effort
RP you know Ian REO was high effort like
got to think about the lore in the story
RP and I took the role of like a bad guy
so that made it more High effort too and
then GTA was very like lots of rules to
follow cuz you're a cop and stuff and
you have a role you got to
play but but this is just kind of like
ha T we're we're dis functional family
oh and DJ was also definitely about the
language barrier that that made me
nervous but again I would
not I I would not trade DTA for anything
because that was so fun and I stepped so
much out of my show and I got to
interact with so many DP members and it
was just so so worth it and so many
memories and yeah so I am proud of the
effort
that I put into
GTA it was a lot it was definitely a lot
streaming yet but it was it was
uh worth wor
it but yeah you guys know me if anybody
ask me hey you want to do this I'm like
okay sure yeah I'll take
part yes of
course fomo I don't think it's a fomo
thing I think it's more of a o
opportunity for
fun with people I like count me and sort
of
thing but the for this one this one it
was definitely a uh was this one was
definitely a I felt responsibility to
keep up
with um the progression I guess this
this one this one was definitely I like
I felt I felt like the responsibility of
keeping up cuz if you don't play every
day you fall behind a little little bit
progression wise
yeah I feel like I feel like maybe if we
do a season
2 um we should do it where it's not s
days in a row and maybe like a couple of
days and then the next week a couple of
days and the next week a couple of days
so that way people are more inclined
to like play a couple days in a row and
then pause and stuff because that way
some people like people who can't do
like all seven days will't fall behind
as much or something like
that cuz I think it would be better if
everybody is
like on the same pain maybe like
progression wise
[Music]
what do you think of the super rock rock
has been such a blast seeing both the 7
days to die and 7 days to St Beil series
yes how long can you stall me today how
long well demon thank you for the super
rock rock thank you for the fun seven
days what are some of your favorite
moments people I liked when you took on
15 glowing Zombies by yourself was a
truly gamer moment I like that too that
was one of my favorite moments
too just soing
soing our entire
room full the zombies when I locked in
yeah that was
crazy crazy the raids were
definitely some of my favorite parts as
well and just you know just chilling
with
everybody uh captin thank you for the
super rock rock D4 thank you for the
super rock rock DG and congrats on
finishing season 1 of seven days to die
remember there's not a part two of The
Stream I'm just I just did that for for
T anime funny
I kind of expected you to go on a
rampage at end like the whole party rock
rock
nah they're my friends I'm not that
ruthless
okay I know when it's okay to mess with
them but I also know
not not too much you can mess with you
can mess with people but you can't mess
with people too much you know you can be
a mess but you can be to be a controlled
Menace so it doesn't it doesn't hurt
anybody else's
fun um and how how could I get in there
and destroy and kill everybody we had
our biker gang moment if I killed
everybody we were having our biker gang
moment that would that would it wouldn't
we wouldn't be us
together
togetherness
okay we were we were having a
mood Ro thank you for the super rock
box when you we when you when you we
when you we did I say that when you when
we when when you you when you when you
you
when when
you congrats on the finale thank thank
you can you explain parkour civilization
again I missed it uh go back on the
vlage just don't go for the beef and
work your way to becoming a
parkour Pro
yeah
um H think for super rock rock that was
fun Su look forward to Spook games yeah
have you watched the second one no I
haven't watch second one
[Music]
s thank you for the super rock rock
thank you joining seven days to die in
event every day always happy to see you
and your buddies have fun together next
big event H live Minecraft Parkour
Kingdom definitely has
toai you're you joke about this but what
if it actually
happened parkour civilization
play uh comrads hammer thank you for the
super rock
rock uh who would start off as a pro
though I don't know
me why are you asking have you seen my
performance in Hollow up at last year's
hollow life sports festival where I got
the fastest time in Hollow up and won
for the red team and then at the end of
the whole thing the red team actually
won do you remember that we got a gold
medal do you remember that do you
remember that
huh it's a kind of Parkour cuz it's a
kind of platforming is like you you you
press a button to jump okay it's still
technically it's you use a weapon to
jump but you're still pressing it's
Trident
parkour yeah it's aiming and jumping
it's still technically
parkour
uh comad Hammer thank you for the super
rock rock jel thank you for the super
rock rock thank you for the seven fun
days The Rock in moment was really
impressive can't wait to see season 2
when it happens good luck with your
homework later thank thank
you uh I thank you for the super rock
rock can we get a tie accent be later
before we go uh be booo
later be bo lar I'll say that at the end
be b b
lar
hi I'm not going yet I unless you want
me to unless unless you want me to
[Music]
go uh you right thank you for the a
super is it going to work today
yes it is also is
[Music]
this both both work okay
cool
um be able please play Dead Space over
Silent Hill for spooky games I guarantee
you will enjoy so much more lots of
violence
but weren you guys the one who suggested
Silent Hill
why not B why not play
B why not why not
[Music]
B well I mean I'll give I'll give I'll
give both the shot
yeah I could play I could play one one
week one for spooky games there's no
guarantee that I'm going to finish them
anyway so like maybe I'll play Silent
Hill this week and then dead space next
week just uh just to try them out cuz
they're spooky gam so I'm not like
aiming to finish them I'm aiming to
experience a spooky game
hey there we go it depends on the story
for example our e story was good so I
finished
it but when I played two I already
played seven and eight and four so I
knew I knew the story was going to be
good and
anyway so that's why I was like I'm
probably going to finish R2 but I don't
know anything about dead space or Silent
Hill so there's no guarantee that I'm
going to finish those just spooky games
to experience spooky
games son Hill to has a great story o I
like good story
uh D4 thank you for Silver Rock
Box yeah so my answer is I will play
both uh def thank you for super Rock Ro
just realize this was baby mode compared
to zomo you lose all your levels when
you you respawn in random place and you
have to fight your Zombie f former self
to get your loot back
well I don't mind the baby mode though
because I feel like it' be a lot
stressful
for a lot of other members if that is if
it was that
ruthless yeah this is this is just you
know casual gaming together so it
doesn't need to be be super hard for
less
stress some these St has hardcore more
too
oh zomboid is Hardcore yeah I don't know
anything about zomboid
but rainy ninja thinkk you for super
rock rock make sure to get some rest and
eat after stream good job with killing
the zombies There's a haad thank thank
you
[Music]
I don't want to do my homework can we
stall more can you can you give me stuff
to talk about so I can stall and I don't
have to do I don't I'm working if I'm
streaming I'm working I don't want to do
it I want to do it yeah can we can we
talk about stuff and St stall you stall
me did you want to stall me anyway
[Music]
I always did king hearts Lord we need a
couple with new things to talk
about did you get to watch any 40K L
that's part of my homework I have to
watch 40K videos tonight cuz I'm going
to play tomorrow that's part of my
homework
they you H
like fire ammo 3
house there person
named by left spoiler spoiler spoilers
spoilers spoilers spoilers there's a
there's a goddess named Saros spoiler
spoilers spoilers spoilers and there's
someone named Nemesis spoilers spoilers
spoilers spoilers
oh uh
red dragon thank you for the super rock
rock any chance that all of Hall Ian
will get to play GTA online not as RP as
standard gameplay with the various
missions that default GTA online has
perhaps if enough people are
interested but like I said I think we
all need a little bit of a break from
lots of collab events for
now at least for a little bit at least I
feel like I need a little bit of a
break uh randomiz thank
you
for the super Rock block us Pebbles were
done for the bble would you make a two
block jump to reach B would you would
you make two two block jump even if uh
you might go to B jail Pebble
jail even if you go to Pebble
jail yes wow how dedicated thank you
very
much uh Mason thank you for the super
rock rock AKB thank you for the super
rock rock they a nice job fighting hard
against the zombies speaking of zombies
has there been progress in fighting a
day for COD zombies collab or is it
stuck in purgatory also this is an
orange Super Chat stop gaslighting me
it's yellow um well everything was on
pause cuz 7 days to
die and it is spooky month right now
so um we will decide after again I guess
need again
okay
better
uh star Creator y she you thank for the
suers rock
rock
um so thank you for super rock rock I
started watching some 40K lore to now
I'm in love with Orcs wow I don't know
what that
means but wow sure
wow face Orcs yeah you were you guys
were telling me something about space
Orcs but don't know about that
yet but sure
wow um yay thank you for the super rock
rock hey Japan congrats I'm finally
moving to BBU huh I hope BBU is being
nice to you and you'll get to enjoy
going around beu soon congrats again
Japan
huh
huh Pebble use confusion is very
effective I'm not even just Jaan
Jaan you I'm not even there yet
Japan is not in beable
yet huh I confused no I'm not there
[Music]
yet uh Peter thank you for the super
rock rock when you read this I will be
asleep you and the pebble send me happy
dreams quick send them nightmares quick
quick quick quick let's let's prank them
and send them nightmares yeah quick
quick let's let's uh let's
uh I'm just kidding I hope you have good
dreams Pebble I hope I get some be head
passs and Jetpack no you will not get a
head pack even head pack head pack jet
pack yep J Pack I de pack not even in
your
dreams I swear my the more I talk the
more my language
regresses H by the way
well you know you know what it is is I'm
getting too comfortable so I'm not
thinking about what I'm saying or being
careful with how I talk like if you
compare debut me to Me Now debut me was
very careful with how I talked and I was
very self-conscious with how I talked
and like I was shy so I talked I feel
like but now I'm like I'm okay with
going I'm less mindful I don't
care I'm less I'm less mindful with what
I
say I I just Yap and say whatever I
don't care anymore I'm not mindful so
now I have regressed in my way of
speaking cuz I feel like d bble was way
more
like make sure you speak properly makes
sure uh very self-conscious yes but now
I'm not self-conscious now I don't care
now I'm
[Music]
like we should do yeah we should do a
watch long of my
debut maybe is it too late to do it I
mean I have when's a special occasion to
re-watch my debut next anniversary or
something I don't
know I feel like rewatching the debut is
like a special thing you
know
so prepare to cringe nah I won't cringe
cuz I had a great
debut my debut was great I don't know
what you guys talking about I don't
think I would CR
that it it went very it went very smooth
I remember it went very well
[Music]
um but thank you for super rock rock as
much as I want to stall people I'm
currently fighting a hord of beeping
deadlines we can't escape our homework B
yes we can if we just keep talking if we
just just keep talking we can we can uh
cuz I'm at least for me I'm working
right now you can't say anything cuz I'm
working
I'm I'm working right now because
because technically I I am streaming and
that is part of part of working
she's a think for super rock
rock yeah you think for super rock rock
I I gu sne again
again
no my nose is itchy
wait no
wait
no
Sni Daniel Victoria thank you for super
rock rock thank you for the amazing
memories during this collab see you take
on all those zombies on your own is
awesome makes you want to pick up gaming
yeah become a
gamer game
play games games are pretty great I
think I'd rather watch or watching
someone play games is rather great
too sometimes sometimes I like shock
myself awake though like at night I'm
asleep and
then people just watch me play
games I just play a game and people
watch and they like
that how does that make
sense OMG
um that's
wild how is that surprising well it's
not surprising because I enjoy watching
other people play games too so it's not
really that surprising
but but I I guess the surprising thing
is like no matter what game I
play someone will be around to watch I
guess or or I could be I could be just
sitting here and chat chatting and
someone will be here to watch and that's
that's kind of wild I yes
to but yeah I remember I remember
watching hakos B play play like lies of
PE and I'm like yeah this is what it's
like this is what it's like to enjoy
someone playing a Souls game I see the I
see the
appeal I see the appeal this is good
this is good I like this and then and
then because because I was watching I
was like oh this is how you must feel
when someone's so close to being boss
you can't tear your eyes away you can't
tear your face away from the screen you
have to make sure she beats the boss
she's going to beat it
I rnle thank you for super rock rock
hello be you cute I know you currently
have games up toet can I recommend you
another world called hidden
folks hidden
folks oh it's like a scavenger o I like
Scavenger Hunt games last night I was
having so much fun uh playing the if you
saw rip your notifications if you have
me on notifications but I I
like the play I went off on Twitter play
cuz there's there's a person who draws
bble every day um with in a different
spot and then um in a different place
around the world and then and then uh
uh and then they hide a cover logo in
every single one of the every single one
of the how do you inine the icon quickly
I'm pretty
fast you want to do some now you want to
do some
[Music]
now hold on let me finish reading Super
Chat first
um uh where we what are we also going to
watch L with Pokemon I want
to I want to
mom membership spooky watch long
maybe I want movies do you guys want to
even watch though I don't even know what
horror movies there are because I don't
I'm not really into horror movies so
like
yeah I don't I don't want scary
movie The Cabin in the Woods
scary movie what's a scary movie is this
called scary
movie scary movie is
[Music]
funny having the woods is
fun it's comedy
oh papa it's a parody
of The Conjuring
alien I've never seen any of the Alien
movies The Ring oh I've never seen the
ring
either
well let the conjuring is really
good well lots of choices maybe I'll ask
or
[Music]
maybe
okay
members
Community
uh hey if we did a hard movie want so
long what would you want to watch uh a
not a horror movie a spooky spooky movie
spooky
um please
like please
like
uh
suggestions with lots of likes will be
consider considered
okay boom done posted
did I spell considered
wrong yes I
did whatever it doesn't
matter
uh I type too fast
[Music]
what up thank you for the super rock
rock I almost don't want to keep you
from your 40K homework but I just want
to say that I only saw I want to be your
skiy plus dress to impress videos on
YouTube shorts what is the latest on Tik
Tok Trends see dress to and press videos
were
so got popular like months ago last
month okay just videos got got popular
like last month a couple months ago is
that's why everybody wanted to play them
see you're late you're
late what is popular on Tik Tok right
now hold on what twiends are you guys
messing missing out on
[Music]
oh you guys are missing out on Cherry
Blossom ice tea cherry blossom ice tea
cherry blossom ice cherry blossom IC tea
Terry Blossom ice you're missing out on
that
uh what else what else is
there and well obviously it's
parkour um oh you know what I've been
learning how to play chess because
there's a Tik Tok channel that turns
gambits teaching gambits into like
really hardcore electronic music so I've
been learning chess gambits because
because they they teach you with song so
like yeah
it's really amazing it's really amazing
yeah they
it's like I got the the Stafford Gambit
down because of because of because
of because of this song that they' made
anyway now I want to play
chess um
what else what what else has been
trendy do you guys know any
Trends
uh I've been getting a lot of
cyberpunk edge
Runners edits on Tik talk lately
oh oh the Poke oh not the Naruto girl oh
yeah the narut
girl wait the Naruto girl dance
[Music]
Trend he not a girl yeah he not the
girl okay there's this culture of Tik
Tok in Tik Tok Liv where you send like
for example supers and based on the
super based on the category of super
they'll they they'll do a dance
so it's kind of like it's similar to NPC
stream but like the next level where
every time you send a Super Chat they'll
do a dance and it's just that over and
over and over and over again and you
just and then every different Super Chat
is a different girl dancing to a
different song but only a section of a
song and and then and then and they're
and they're in Cosplay and right now the
Naruto cosplay girls are very very
popular and then and heata is like the
most popular one and then she goes and
then
[Music]
and then she gets mad and then she gets
mad because because she dances so much
and then she gets tired so she like
collapses on streams or like she gets
very sassy and then she gives you the
middle finger because she's mad at you
and if like like if you can send another
Super Chat while the girl is dancing
already so it replaces the current song
so you can cut them off so if the girl
is dancing you send a Super Chat and it
cuts them off and then they get mad at
you for cutting them off of their dance
they're like huh well which one is it do
you want to stop dancing or do you want
to keep
dancing
huh anyway that's that's that's really
popular right
now make up your
mind um
I'm
looking I started getting H life Clips
on Tik Tok again and I don't want H life
Clips on Tik Tok because YouTube YouTube
is for Hall life stuff Tik Tok is for
when I don't want to think about like
Hall life stuff I need to keep it
separate Tik Tok is is for like
everything else because my entire
YouTube feed is just full H life stuff
but now I'm getting like my own stuff
like I'm I'm getting I'm probably going
to get like a bble clip from this
stream on Tik
Tok later and then I'm going to be
like oh yeah the the Y no that's that's
what happened I started getting like
bble Clips when when the Press n thing
was happening so I kept seeing bble
wiggle on Tik Tok and
like I can't escape
myself
uh but there's this really good people
at on Tik Tok I really like it thank you
for doing a b edit anyway that's what we
doing uh are you fan PE thank you for
the super Rock
v
um buddy thank you for the super rock
rock stalling be escape from work I'm in
[Music]
yeah it's almost midnight man
uh Ro a thank you for super rock rock
congrats on fting 7 Days to Die can't
think of much to tell you but is there
any lore for any game series that you
would want to know more about
discounting for DK obviously milk
[Music]
oh I can tell you Pokemon lore once
there was an egg and the Egg hatched and
it was orus and then and then orus
created a DI Dialga and Pia who had the
rulers of space in time and
then no I'm saying official L I'm saying
official that's official law that's
official I'm not
[Music]
saying I was I was saying the official
stuff that's official
anyway
um
stop I'm going to start talking about it
stop I'm I'm a good be
stop it
don't no I'm not looking I'm not looking
I'm
not I'm not
[Music]
looking I'm strong I have
willpower I'm
strong I'm strong
I'm
sry um CES thank you for the super rock
rock
uh it's been a while since you read
Morse code right yes it's been a while
so this might take me uh a while to
translate it um bble do your homework oh
I translated it oh wow I must be that
good wow it was still in my mind uh sure
I'll do my homework
um AK be thank you for the super rock
rock hey B I'm here to S you no need to
rush the stream and if you pause your
speech after every word we we can stay
here longer and can you say Peter Piper
picked the pack of pickle peppers fast
Peter Piper picked the PE
ofet Peter peer Peter Piper pick the P
of pickle peppers Peter Piper pick the
pack of PE pepper pick
peanut paper PE peut Peter Piper pck the
PE PE peers Peter Piper pck the PE
peers Peter Piper pck the PE pickle
peppers
Piper Peter Piper pck the PE Peter Piper
picked a pack of pickle peppers Peter
Piper picked a pack of pickle peppers
there there that wasn't bad I Did
[Music]
It Sick
bit
um AR thank you for rock rock H
something stall conrat Japan be for our
orange SC no that's not Orange it's
yellow
wait I haven't done today's one yet
let's do today's
one hold on let's do today's
one all um um it's easier on the phone
cuz I can't I I can't zoom I can't zoom
too
well but like
this it's easier on the phone hold
on cuz now I have to like lean in
do you see it hold on I'm going to look
at it inside my
phone you know where it is hold on hold
on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold
on I got to look at it on my phone okay
there we go
[Music]
oh I see it oh I see it it's left side I
found it okay yeah
yeah is this is right here it's right
here it's on the corner I found it left
left side what is that left
[Music]
left left
side left
side rock left side rock okay done
reply I ended on 50 uh what where where
did I end
[Music]
on yes I'm stalling
I just stole manyi last
night okay next one oh wait I found
it that was easy oh I I found it I found
it I'll give you a
minute do you see I found
it I found
it okay it
is right here I'll put it on the corner
see it was on the top of the house the
house house decoration window red red
red stripe
building decoration red stripe building
decoration see right there I'm putting
it on the corner at the very bottom
now that was pretty
easy we were looking for the hall live
logo the hall live logo okay hold on I
got to tweet this on um red stripe
[Music]
window red stripe window red stripe top
window
building
decoration
ahead wait okay
oh I found
it that this one's kind of easy too I
see I found it I found
it this one's
easy did you find it did you find
it did you find
it right
there you need more time I'll give you
more
time uh top
of uh right side
Temple let me think okay I'll give you
more
time uh
oh I found
it did you find it I found
it did you find it
yet it's on a thing it's on a thing
you you found the
thing okay it
is right
here
uh
top top right
tapestry pattern
boom
NE this
one okay this what I'm going to need my
phone for hold on I need to phone this
one
hold let me get there on my
fault wait I haven't started
yet I haven't started yet hold on don't
start without me
okay I got it up
uh okay I'm starting
[Music]
now h
I don't I don't see it right
away this one's
hard
unless unless it's my chest Jam triangle
but is that really the logo or just my
chest gem in a shape of a triangle
no okay
uh we're trying to find the hidden cover
logo but I don't ah
Pebble no the pebble Pebble the pebble
reflection doesn't look like the cover
logo at
all the pebble
jum I don't I
don't think
so because this the the test gem kind of
looks like a triangle
too
but uh
[Music]
uh one of the windows may
be triangle window where
I don't see a triangle
window it's the chest Y is it the chest
down I mean it could be the chest
y I think I mean I can kind of see the
can someone look at the spoiler isn't it
who doesn't
mind is someone look at the spoilers in
the comments is it is it the chest Jem
is it is it the chest Jem is it is it
the is it the chest
Jem it is a chest Jam okay thank you
thank you thank you okay okay that was a
hard test J
cuz the line is barely
there
[Music]
tricky uh do I need my phone for this
let me just look really fast
okay I need my phone for this
one oh wait no I don't need my phone for
this I see it I see it I see it I see it
I see it it's right there it's it's in
the middle it's the it's it's right
there that's easy okay yeah yeah it's at
the um base of base of pillar under Arch
left base of pillar under Arch
left
done okay I should go I should go I'm
stall this this is fun though but
I should
go one more no then we're GNA keep going
and going hold on let me check supers
one more
time but you can follow along with me uh
when when you see me do it tonight but I
got to finish my homework first before
before I before
I before I
yeah before I before I start playing
games
um okay we're good bye-bye I'm going to
go eat dinner and then do my homework
cuz I got homework to do and then if you
see
me have 5,000 notifications on for you
um
sorry sorry for the 5,000 notifications
anyway see you next time by people
later see you tomorrow for Space Marines
tomorrow I'm playing Space Marines okay
yay I'll some days die people later
bye-bye
we oh yeah watching the videos is part
of my homework we got to make sure I
watch this okay byebye
[Music]