[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
character what's up
what are you guys saying are there
problems with the Stream
again
hello good evening
oh [\h__\h] I messed it up
wait
weird jumps
really
is it because of me because of me
um
the Cali finally end her stream
God
Kawaii pimori
I just I was like waiting for her to end
her stream not because of me wanting to
end my stream
other reasons
for sure
[Music]
ah on it
all right
oh that works oh
sh I think
sorry I know I [\h__\h] moved it again
the sweater someone made a Christmas
sweater for the champions
they're not shrimpkins but
you know what I mean
okay okay I'm I'm ready to
show myself again
hi hello
um we could just stream like this
no no no look they look so cozy
[Laughter]
sweater is so big damn
needs to be baked to fit in order to fit
two of them you know my dishwasher never
gets glasses clean it's so weird even if
they're like they're like dirtier when
they come out of the dishwasher and no
it's not because of the dishwasher being
dirty I cleaned it too
oh that's so weird oh well I mean it
seems to be
dirt that's kind of not really
mixing with the water so whatever
um
[Music]
yeah I cleaned them
the whatever filter or whatever a while
ago when it was doing this
it didn't help but maybe it's missing
salt or again or maybe I don't know
whatever doesn't matter
are you feeling better uh
are you asking me because
yesterday was my day off was yesterday
my day off did I have a day off
yesterday
did I
I guess probably right
I feel like a day off because I had to
record
um two songs
and then uh in the next two days I have
to record
um two more songs I think mm-hmm
it's not I'm not making an album
it's just other things that are all
separate uh for separate things
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and then it's not it's not what you
think
um
it's not you origin
yeah but uh many things to do right now
this is kind of like the I feel like
this has to do with it being close to
Christmas
or an end of the year
because like there's also like some
sponsorship stuff going on and some of
these things are for sponsorships as
well and uh yeah I guess like
it's like sponsors just at the end of
the year they wanna
you know get their game out there and
uh
do stuff
oh yeah that tweet by the way did you
see my sponsorship tweet for that
a gacha game that fauna played
I know that came out of nowhere
and it was only a tweet I'm not doing a
stream on it but it's basically just a
sponsorship tweet and I was like why the
hell not it's just a tweet I don't even
have to really do anything so
forgive me guys
I know it was like what
oh yeah I saw I saw a video got
copyright struck and that's interesting
as well isn't it
um
but yeah
gotta get the bag gonna get the money
bag
the Christmas money and the Christmas
bonus you know
it's like a Christmas bonus all the
sponsorships and stuff
yeah yeah
you're in the bread earn the bread yeah
also the the counter side stuff has been
really cool too
um
have you been watching it you know what
they've been showing us with the
different beautiful artworks and that
are animated into life today and so on
it's so cool and like my fighting
animation so I was like what the [\h__\h]
when they
um showed me like a fighting animation
and I'm like you can do that with live
city what
it's like
the fighting animation is like I go like
swoosh swoosh swoosh and turn and this
and that and stab holy moly you can do
all of that with like
one piece of art and life to see they're
like Gods what they've I've seen so many
things they've been creating so many
assets what they do with left to do is
those like next level [\h__\h]
you can just say whatever don't need 3D
just use just use life today
no
counter Countryside Countryside so
please check counterside out because
actually we're also gonna do maybe some
of us one of us who knows
possibly me
to um a stream on it as well
uh soon next week or so maybe maybe if
if we can squeeze it in hasn't been
confirmed but might be
hey
oh yeah yeah yeah good luck with Yuna
it's apparently the character who's
um you know behind my character because
you have to give my body a soul because
otherwise my body will be so less
you got her well she's apparently really
strong so you know you'll have a lot of
reason to put me in the team and fight
with me I won't be in the way I won't be
a bother
um
counter-sized to sponsorship foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I see I see every character game has a
Pity pool huh I know that kind of from
other other gacha games
um I'm sorry I got to get it's just like
that with gotcha games you know normally
in these characters you you have to
invest often some sort if you want a
specific one you will probably end up
having to invest some some amount of
your own money
it's just no way around it usually
most of the time
yeah it will be like that with gacha
games
ah yeah and anyway uh
[Music]
uh
uh we're gonna play this game for the
first time in a while again but ah oh
primary
finally reply to my DM yes
[Music]
us so
I've been struggling with you know
campaign the last campaign I did as far
as I remember the Barbara Russell one I
did not finish it because I couldn't
stress me the [\h__\h] out and Skirmish
people have been telling me to practice
with Skirmish instead
but I don't know then then someone else
said um maybe Baba Rosa isn't for me yet
I should finish this one
and maybe that's right because like I
was so confused because you know this
one's red so I thought all the easy ones
are red and the other one is this one so
I thought oh oh let's go to this one
then
I already played the William bonus one
but honestly at this point I should
maybe even play it again because I
forgot everything it's been too long I
don't remember the the keyboard things
anymore I don't know how to select a
group
of the same type or or I don't know how
to select all my fighting units anymore
you guys have to tell me these Basics
again please
um
audio check
uh
so
would you say that the fourth one here
would still be easier than doing the
babarasa first one
I should not leave
cool music
yes
there's no easy
oh there's no easy
why is there no easy
[Laughter]
oh wow almost fat bird why is there
nothing below standard
okay well then what happened here again
February 19th oh
this morning I walked to visions of fire
and steel these Nightmares come more
often now that I've seen my beloved
flowers eaten Away by years of war I
wandered through Camp ignoring the new
snowfall but observical wounds and
weariness of every Soldier under my
command
observing the desperation in their eyes
it was then when I first saw the girl
she told us that her name was Joan
she told us she was better Pleasant and
remember what we did there
whoa but how many swells with new
recruits
according times lens will feel tea only
to that particular Lord now
we fired
of all of us
there is no distinction
oh the door himself has arrived in not
Leon never have I seen such a
celebration
thus needs a king so we must escape
and if they never marry yet
commands that we must liberate all three
cities before the coronation and we
eagerly seek to fight not that [\h__\h]
mattered in the mid Medieval ages are
you serious
40 year old dudes Kings would marry or
not even married but just to have
funeral relations with 13 year olds
whatever dude
anyway I can't imagine that maybe it was
a uh him already being like promised to
someone else B him wanting someone
that is not like her more like a normal
woman because who doesn't fight like
Wars because it would kind of undermine
his himself uh against his uh to his to
his folks you know
or c
he needs someone who is not a peasant
who has a connections to a royal family
or so
yes I know these things because I am a
nerd when it comes to
middle age history
anyway
um so John must survive travel West to
help reinforce the French Camp be wary
of opposition along the way
what that's it what we travel West and
that's it we don't what
the France can now advance to the
Imperial age but they still cannot
produce gunpowder weapons their
population limit is 125 gaining control
over the river may be a good strategy
but do not squander your resources
needlessly on ships
okay
shalom's is the clothes
is the closest and most vulnerable of
the three English occupied towns making
an example of them early
sounds it sounds like just taking them
down could help even the odds for you in
the long run oh
where's remember your objectives it is
not necessary to level the cities only
to force the English to withdraw
oh huh so in the west is where the
English are and where where okay the
objective sounds like we're not doing
much
one of all shallows to slow enemy
attacks
of what looked like what what on on my
whole path
or what ah it updates once I travel okay
okay
your Scott's report I'm your friends
traveling to a French camp in the West
yeah
left okay
but the road there is defended by
English guards
Joan of Arc will need to reach the camp
before she can live over her twice
shaloms and most importantly Rings If
the French are to Crown the the the
phone shalon's choice and Rhymes are the
three towns occupied by the English uh
and they are across the river and are
well defended
yeah so am I supposed to set up camp
here first and and and and build a
bigger Army
just stay here for now or what
the English channels will feel
Knights and scorpions and even warships
are threatened their town is unprotected
and can be easily reached by crossing
the shallows okay so shalom's first
make walls where the water shows the
enemies can't walk across but not now
right later
right
huh
this is the worst one in Jones campaign
oh no
okay
um Torrance is slightly better defended
with walls than a castle protecting the
river crossing to the east
neat owner right we're outside however
they are now prepared for an attack from
the flank
um they will train Pikeman and knights
to fight the French but will also build
warships if they feel that they are
about to lose the control of the river
but if they're East and we're already
East now should we go to them first
lames is a one city protected by castles
and Towers the English Garrison there
will there will include longbowmen light
Cavalry and I don't remember
it counters these so you guys gotta tell
me
a true challenge for the French luckily
it will be quite some time before they
feel confident enough to launch an
attack okay so their last obviously and
that was the most important one anyway
you need to go to the camp first okay so
the West one okay
okay so uh first of all one question
what's the like
um
or cheat keyboard whatever or what's how
do I
um
like let's say they're all spread apart
how do I select all of my troops
what was the way of doing that please
oh
Mouse drag what you mean this that's not
what I mean what if they're like all
over and I don't I don't want to select
the villagers in between
digital number to add oh okay I guess I
always had to do it with control group
Ctrl
one
[Music]
how do I get back to them oh there we go
now it worked
huh
okay
let's go
slowly but surely
follow
me the mouse the mouse you're following
the mouse you're being controlled by a
weird iron Mouse
you kill him he's just a scout
not worth it
come on come on everybody
[Music]
what
I just Scouts they're just Scouts we're
wasting our time if we try to kill them
but a big mistake oh what what what
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Joe Divac is attacking our camp
do not let her cross the river
okay
what am I supposed to attack them
I mean we're already killed four we kind
of baited them this was on purpose I
baited them
[Music]
cam
not gonna micromanage
[Music]
so useless anyway but I keep this in a
burning State I thought it was more
behind us like a city or so well okay no
problem
however
they did Target him first those suckers
he was a holy man
it was a man of faith
yo how dare you
you're disrespecting God in the church
yes but okay so this is where my Camp
will be this is my Town Center okay
not enough food okay well uh uh or do I
not have any Villages out here okay I
need I need a normal villager
okay I'll still I'll steal you
bust yourself and not only are you only
want only one piece
Cafe ah here you are
um
okay you stuck now we already have one
here do we have someone doing wood oh we
have some people doing good
and you can work there okay you can you
guys also work on the berries
make game audio too loud right sorry for
sure
I turn and turned it down a little bit I
was probably still too loud I don't know
yeah Stone Stones okay
can she bring those stones to that camp
so I have to I don't remember [\h__\h] guys
so you have to tell me everything again
at least the basic things are already
built here that's nice
should I tell them to Just Right chill
oh yeah
how do I do that again guard or
no attack stance maybe
maybe defensive stance
well I'm also trying to see what slash
that is too loud more The Sounds oh yeah
the sounds the alerts I know they're
loud can I turn just the alerts down
voice sound sounds if your music is that
then sound is
just the alerts right
hopefully okay
by the way I did change one thing here
what was it
ah this one select only idle villagers
for double click that didn't really
matter just just so you know if you're
trying to tell me how to do something
this was one thing that's not default
okay ah
uh build a church to get back my monk
okay okay okay okay can I already build
a church is that a military building
right
ah oh yes
yes leave the scouts alone
you're wasting your time oh oh
you almost got him see what you wasted
your time
uh Monastery Right monastery Monastery
is church this one
okay here we go
uh do I have a scout this is a scout
right it should be how do you just
where should I where should I let him
Scout here I'll Stand and one thing I
know now that I don't think I knew
before is that if you right click on the
map
into the black whatever he will go there
I did not know it works for the mini map
very villagers are wasting time walking
yeah how do I fix that
I mean those are really far I know that
and I need to make more we have a big
Max
oh holy oh holy oh Holiness should we
make maybe two
oh yeah yeah and I want to wait for
um this I want to upgrade this because
you are gonna you know what you're also
gonna bury
bury the berries collect berries next to
the mill oh yeah okay
[Music]
you are being attacked by three salons
this is so annoying when stuff like that
happens I think you died
oh he might have died
Scouts is running around most of the
time he's fine he will not get attacked
but hey at least we have a look into
this now thanks Scout for yeah losing a
life for that purpose
nice
f
[Laughter]
a the famous French word
what does it mean is it really French
also I don't know what to do see I don't
know what to do I don't know what to do
here you want helps here okay and
um one more helps here and one more
helps
okay let me make one more and then with
that one more we need to start building
stuff like stables and [\h__\h] right and
the military thing whatever
so stressy stress stressful very
stressful
oh
thanks so much okay this is the maximum
okay you built Cafe uh you build
Barracks
um
move the monks to your military
oh yeah you can even heal them if you go
there slow dudes I want to upgrade the
thing that makes them walk faster
eventually eventually
ah this one
yes very necessary for my patients I
cannot stay or be patient
let's make more I'll say they're healing
beautiful heal faster
stronger put more skill points into your
intelligence
don't you dare walk in here
you little [\h__\h]
how the [\h__\h] did you survive
don't let them go he will tell the enemy
wait let's not let the enemy know okay
next up uh archery
is
[Music]
Korean what what's happening
no no ignore the scouts ignore the
scouts
do you guys go after the scouts or do
you ignore them I feel like you should
ignore them
archery Towers oh yeah you mean the the
watchtowers
um
don't chase them very far unless you set
them on oh okay okay they don't chase
them very far okay what are these one of
these small camps they're cute
you feel that good job and now let's
build oh I can't build [\h__\h] what am I
missing what okay you help what
and now we start
um what do we want the most
what kind of dudes do we want the most
or just everything
I mean they did mention certain units
in the beginning
why
really
nights
nights nights oh but nights are not here
right nights are uh in the castle I
can't do it unless I have a castle right
traveling in archers some
I can't really arches okay
let's turn the stable those are not nice
you mean after I upgrade to Imperial age
like Ah that's not a stable oh [\h__\h] huh
okay I'll make a stable next
uh uh do we not have an idol one all
right okay kill it kill him my
permission
uh here I need a Cavalry Archer it's
used leave it I was too fast stupid
Scout
more than one station
I make more than one stable
good friend where is Cafe
so far it's okay if they give me some
time and don't stress me out oh I can't
build a staple yet and we need more wood
work faster
faster faster faster
faster faster faster faster oh these
things work as houses huh
[Music]
okay you can can you build one more I
mean I will also use up some wood but
I'm I'm happy with that that's the show
one more please
okay yeah oh yeah also
here
here okay we just meet in the middle all
right so I know where you guys are at
all times
like that that's
we're gonna Feast on your dead body
I'm capped now yeah okay okay
[Music]
um
we'll make a house
oh those look like actual houses how
nice this one will be behind the church
another one
so far so far I'm still enjoying it but
soon the stress will follow and I will
freak the [\h__\h] out who should we go to
first then by the way
I think something made me think that I
should go to Detroit's first and it's
actually in that order up here anyway
the toys were what color again where's
this uh
where is this thing
try slightly better defended but however
they are now prepared for an attack from
the flank flank is like from the side
but which side
well how do you know when she's front
and which is side they probably have a
main gate right go for the closest what
wait what what color is Troy's orange
orange
but the closest is I guess kind of
shalons will fight nights I will Fields
Knights and scorpions and even warships
have threatened their town is
unprotected and can be easily reached
okay shelons I guess they're closest I
know where they are now
um
yes yes yes
uh but then orange
is my color how dare you steal it
make an example of the show yeah okay
true and the example should be the first
one yeah
um so what what do we they feel Knights
and scorpions what's what's the best uh
stuff to bring there then
tell me please
AOE gods
they know where you are too well well
they have yet to make use of it
that knowledge
Pike versus Kafka versus Siege
that that's not what's written here
though
hikes
my own Knights and Pikes but should I
bring a scorpion or so as well
bikes for nights and Calgary for
artillery okay Pikes Pikes and Cavalry
Pikes and Calvary Pikes and Calvary and
maybe some nights
um hi oh
okay we're upgrading to Pike man
[Music]
um uh currently
I can't say it but I still need to get
one person to build me
[Music]
um
something else right what were we
building uh
the thing
here I'll just make another oh okay here
he is
uh uh a stable stable stable stable
stable
foreign
okay if you have enough night strategy
it doesn't matter I hope so I hope so I
hope so I really do
should I make a new Scout and let him
run around
Scout was from the stable too though
right so I have to wait for that anyway
anything we can upgrade here this one
let's upgrade that
oh kill him kill him kill him
all you have to think about how long it
takes for your arrow to go to the Target
words even I know that
aim to go the [\h__\h]
so much
use your stupid brain oh oh no it's nice
yo
you dudes
oh wait so now I have this problem these
dudes were here before I think and they
just they were just chilling there leave
it they have to join the team
okay stable is built
now we make
night night well only two we need way
more poof okay okay you guys uh one of
you make make of the field because field
is closed and that's good
yeah we may make one more and we add you
to oh the berries are the berries gone
if we use up the berries up there then
maybe we can use the berries down here
I think we're done now I'm doing pretty
well I I did a warm-up before the stream
because I was freaking out and I think
that's showing oh wait wrong wrong dude
um
work on that
warming up warming up okay here
help
oh yeah build house
no not all of you
so your house there we go there we go
there we go oh she's okay she's chilling
here what can you do
what do we need more food right now to
be honest
money what do you mean challenge you're
coming for me
so
with all of you
yeah bye
okay yeah no go away lady
it's just him
let's
go let's go to what are you doing with
your horse why is it turning and
twisting like that this is like it needs
um
what's the the word for oh no
this will be exercised
go faster
why are you so slow
[\h__\h] scorpions do it do it do it do
it do it do it kill the Scorpions
but you were one second too late
okay
that's uh
I mean we can take him down to oh no no
wrong thing oh well okay
yeah okay I should just leave the monk
out but he has to follow too kind of
cool new tower oh can he just repair
that one no
lost yourself
oh nice nice okay Scout will not survive
um
more night though many nights so that's
a [\h__\h] ton of nights that's what we want
and maybe some Pike
so far so good so far so good control
group one here fixed
but
where's the monk there is the Monk
s Xerox
monk I make you control group too
did I do that sorry
okay okay
you just chill chill there please so
you're a little bit at a distance
am I forgetting something
separate the crossbows also how do I how
do you like if they're in a group like
this now how do I separate them
can I when I find one crossbow can I oh
there we go then okay good why why also
the crossbows well why would I want to
separate them
uh oh my God I'm stressed
they're all so slow and they'll have to
funnel eventually
events
okay
control group
oh
okay keeps on growling I'm trying to run
okay
should I do I need more still
um probably speed what should we upgrade
maybe something here
research Squires infantry speed and
trying to do more damage versus
buildings
[Music]
to keep my monk alive
I probably want to make one more monk
even didn't I have two already anyway
here it only shows one I thought I made
two
you're feeling distress uh what can we
make what can we make
[Music]
um
gold
[Music]
um
but it's focused we have to go take them
now do we have enough enough people what
do you think
I'm just gonna send a couple of them
ahead
it's time you will not take down my
tower
where are my resources my resources
I'm running out of them
okay can we go
you think we can go
get more villagers
fill an extra Townsend to wear
just like like from here or so
save and try save
okay here we go
this one this these two were me
practicing
was that bread group
um
where are the other ones
why are the other ones gone where where
are my other groups what about three and
two
it was weird
did I cancel it out by refreshing the
first group
confused
uh
that sounds like a troll shitty
you little [\h__\h]
um
it collapsed back into one when you put
them on what why we do that
it almost right what the hell
monk Chan uh
[Music]
five yeah okay okay John can stay
because she's good
okay okay I don't know if I'm ready
I mean I need some Stones I need some
Siege stuff though
uh let's make a staple thingy for Siege
stuff
Workshop
that's 125 population no hurry really
by the way 125 population I get an
upgrade then or what
[Music]
okay
okay monks updated I think oh yeah Oh
Yeah lyrics
guys no no
come on come back come back come back
come back
don't forget not to let them take the
bulk of the damage support them with
troops ah you mean the The Siege weapons
mm-hmm
oh no it's nice takedown
hey
okay
I will make
[Music]
um
I'll make another meal
what if I run out of these resources
should I make like a Trade Center or
something like that I can build a castle
[Music]
um
Castle go here
nice pillage the other villagers
what these idiots what are they doing
what
I said aggressive they won't follow so
far
the hell
idiots
I'm just vibing I'm good for you
I'm not vibing I'm scared
let's make some more nights
um
upgrade
you up okay what kind of stage do we
want everything
but what do we want the most
okay yeah
[Music]
Rambo Rumble
I need to build more houses I'm on it
I'm on it I'm on it I'm building more
houses
so what's your song
mango nail as well
what is the difference in them
what does one do better than the other
let them go here
oh I'm hanging out those like friendly
fire damage
I'm just dry feeling this oh let me
check something
ah
a
video has been delivered I have to
I have to quickly uh
uh uh do some Advent calendar things one
one second
um
[Music]
okay done
uh
okay
I'm back
you didn't even notice that I was gone I
was actually still here multitasking
hmm
Libre away
[Music]
so now it's free there you go
oh
it's almost 7 Villages yo
is this still here
oh okay
[Music]
I heard X-Men are good should we get
some throwing axmen to join our team
yeah
okay let's make a couple of them and I
hear shots again
[Music]
he's too close to the Watchtower can't
shoot him anymore right
oh what are you little suckers doing
here huh
all right I'll send reinforcements
because there's actually a couple of
them coming
oh oh no the Pike's been already
oh no
oh no okay
[Music]
bye
okay we're good we won we won we won the
battle but the battle is not yet over I
need more nights now
make up for the lawns
oh yeah University that was also a thing
I forgot about that hi
[Music]
customers need to give everyone
something to do
you get something interesting and you'll
get a job and you can jump so what about
this song
Monastery university did I really built
this oh
yeah
oh yes yes shoot them in a good spot
attack
oh
[Music]
yeah
leave it
all right all right all right yeah bye
yeah bye why is everyone just standing
somewhere right
oh yeah
oh yeah oh you know what you can stay
here okay
counter attack now should I should I
should I
hmm
oh time for some walls I have enough
villagers to make a wall but
so maybe
he uh where does it even
maybe because here's the river so as
long as I build a gate here and then a
wall around here
then they cannot come from the river
right
I hope at least not from that side for
now
so let's make
I learned how to change the direction
here
you're doing it right okay and then
uh should we just do Palisade Waldo I
don't know
it's faster and cheaper
University build
are you doing that and uh we need a
Stone mile
nothing this this is better than nothing
so like this okay
oh God Palestine wall and you make the
rest of that
okay so maybe that is some
useless but I don't know Cafe
we are almost completely rid of the
materials so I feel like we should save
on Stone you know
and I don't know about building a wall
here but
nice
[Music]
um
okay leave it
please heal heal the little villager
so she may not die
use mining stone okay
um
what else am I lacking
almost at least you know if it looks
like we only have one patch left even
that one patch will video stay for a
while
right [\h__\h] are you doing there
[Music]
next stage
we're lacking gold and food
but I didn't say body Glam or
early University I just did
that oh where did where is it this thing
it's minimum range oh yeah yeah
um
this one
great to car towel what the Watchtower
will become guard Tower missiles more
accurate
but this all takes a lot of materials
filling hit points
I don't take this
I'll take this oh my gold oh my gold
I can't do this much longer I feel like
do I need more Rams this maybe one more
each
okay
Mineo
Bowie
pasta sauce
hey
one more Farm
everyone must be used
effectively
how about another Watchtower now
okay and
another one
for good measure I don't know
pasty soap
need ballistics to hit Knights
ballistics what what is ballistics did
aren't these things ballistics
Oh you mean a thing here to learn ah
ballistics
[Laughter]
oh I think I understand
it was because I was too close oh yeah
we're back
don't open the gates
together you come back living
knock knock knock knocking monkey store
[Music]
yes it should be properly closed now
where did you come from
out
yeah
my walls okay thank God
[Music]
all right I think
my hell fresh
why not try to deliver it to me directly
I'm not normally always works
set the manganules to non-attack
um
well I mean I feel like going now anyway
let's save again
do you think I'm ready
because all
Scout your side of the river
good idea because I'm running out of
materials I'm more than ready okay that
is a relieving thing to hear
I want to be more than ready and I want
to do Overkill but indeed before I go
I will have a
scout scout some stuff
okay
soap maybe it shouldn't be there oops
[Music]
forgot about those buildings
materials don't go limp I ran out of
wood
okay
well I have a lot of idol villagers so
we
um
[Music]
Scouts Scouts Scout where did the skull
cause it's a scout okay
find me something useful
foreign
[Music]
okay
I can't do two things at a time by the
way I cannot
oh there's some Stone
ah Again by a tower interesting
okay
uh take down Tower
maybe without John
it's happening three shaloms where are
the shalons
oh what are these kids doing here leave
it
okay
yeah this one
ah I chose all of them okay yeah oh yeah
leave it
I'm so so useless how's this going is
this a good way to fight a tower yeah
yeah yeah yeah
it says wait maybe my ramp should go oh
that's the realization
Cafe oh yeah maybe my rounds should go
yeah
bonjour
so friendly always always a nice
greeting is one enough
oh something's happening up there
I love that word probably not uh
what the [\h__\h] oh they're attacking no
[Music]
oil
the stress
wait
okay prepare
how's this going
slow slow but it works
great
[Music]
everybody
since that one is pretty much done for
but do I need a camp here for the
materials
probably right so a mining camp here
ideally
busty soap that will work right
you little fits
okay you're done here go away from the
gate
relax
oh God
hmm
uh okay and then also a stone Camp
um down here later right
um
like a mining camp
I don't want to do it just yet yeah it's
dangerous now oh well
slow anyway
okay and
gabber here
Thomas
she's gonna be fine should I build a
watchtower at my own Watchtower there
huh okay like before you continue okay
actually I'm gonna send you someone to
help you
um
uh my own Watchtower because otherwise
they're kind of like alone here right
[Music]
oh this is working
so
can I not convert a watchtower into my
own
what how God that's a joke right
they're gonna attack me with missiles at
any moment that's a joke right please
tell me that's a joke please tell me
that's a joke please tell me that's a
joke I mean there's some people here but
okay
[Music]
Mineo okay yeah
sometimes it would always lead me to
where okay they are when I click on that
video okay
push okay
all right all right all right all right
and all nights
Ctrl one
all these ones
Ctrl two
oh
goofy all of whatever that is Ctrl free
leave it all of
I have too many different things you
know
this is a problem okay yeah you're an
Archer right you're a crossbow man okay
all archers how many do I have
only one
oh yeah
oh yeah you join
then I have more people where are the
all those Fighters
Cafe
boy
it's just
okay yeah
okay oil they died
[Music]
I was ready to go but no I'm not
oh good morning X-Men a couple of them
are here
did I make a group for them
let's give them six
oh here's some more of them okay
December Nights
okay these are gonna be seven
okay
oh
it's safer to go up and I'm pretty
annoyed what what I understand what are
you talking about
uh we're gonna
okay we're gonna go now we're gonna keep
one monk here
whatever whatever I'm just gonna go now
let's go let's go let's go let's go
you're free let's go let's go let's go
all right let's go let's go let's go
yeah maybe we should keep some here
though to protect
and always keep recreating if we uh lose
some dudes
right I always always keep doing that
[Music]
okay okay
foreign
[Music]
one more time safe
oh yes leave it
yeah bye
[Music]
weekend progress after we um multiply my
golden resources we're trying to cross
the river yes
go faster um
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go
[Applause]
okay okay destroy [\h__\h] destruction
[Music]
Loki
oh my oh my God my HP
[Music]
your face
who said that
book
okay yeah
Rams to the town center
uh
[Music]
yeah
I am
ah can I ignore this [\h__\h]
hi throwing ax man oh they're gonna keep
on creating aren't they
can take this I can't take this
mm-hmm
go to town center Town Center almost
down
oh Alto Center
right
that's all yes
are they gonna give up if the Town
Center is dead
[Music]
yeah
can I get them to join my team
John John John John John
where's John John
okay
can I go back now will they actually
like if I just leave it like this will
they rebuild everything and start a new
Army
they will Ryan
um
hey there were allies now
oh they're done you're done
okay I'm a bit relieved now so oh yeah
oh yeah we got the check mark here ah
Ah that's good I think we lost a lot of
um right our people but uh yeah okay and
we got the only return
foreign
let's go let's go let's go
Knights pikes
uh for that for now that's it oh God uh
can I send if they're if they're allies
why don't they give me their gold now
what if I sent like a few villagers
right here and gather here
that's fine right
or the Trade Center
I have a lot of food I can trade food uh
for you know but I don't I kind of don't
know how the Trade Center works I need a
card first right
card and then I can buy right
I can mine it too all right I'll send
some people to mine it then okay first
of all
um build and do I have do I have some
before I go to the next place I need
some time
build a mining camp bestie soap right
there
what's the shortcut for this
click on the market did I find their
mortgage
there it is
uh
with the cards
I really don't understand this
where is my oh it's not done yet okay
set
Gathering ah yeah bye okay
good idea good idea good idea good idea
no need for cards you think well at
least one I guess you also learn how
this works so my card I right click on
on here what
but then how does it know what I want to
trade
going it's
how does it know what I want to trade
Market is defended by our Tower oh
oh green yellow oh
oh
cart just gives me gold
automatically gold
oh
go to Imperial before attacking yellow
okay but I still need a [\h__\h] ton of gold
before that
so
the cart may die that's okay
if that happens that's okay
[Music]
mmm
oh they cost gold the X-Men goes gold
one of you must fix this
um
okay
how's the car doing card doing good so
far
nice
[Music]
oh
the greens just go into the yellow area
is that okay oh
[Applause]
it was it was worth for a try it was
worth a try I wasn't worth a try
okay yeah
so close
oh well I'm good with not using it for
now if we can get all the all the gold
here
is that gonna work out
and they're coming they're coming
what do you mean I'm being attacked
which where am I being attacked
but James is yellow right do they mean
when they say I'm being attacked today I
also mean my Ally
I don't see where I'm being at ah here
oh they came with a ram
oh yes and the monks
how do I heal a ram do I need a villager
for that
initial shits or maybe not good is it a
good idea stop
[Music]
foreign
I'm a beginner okay please guys
this is just danger danger danger zone
[Music]
it's a dangerous place to be
okay
um
villager of Paris okay uh who's okay
you're not busy you're prepared hey
Libby
actually not you help me Neo
mineral yes minerals
the ones that they talked about as
flanking is it the yellow ones
let me see
uh
yellow
[Music]
ah yellow is ah yellows are Flames that
I want to do last okay now my next is
orange where's Orange I only see red
here
English cards I didn't see orange yet
that's weird
oh
my golden mind is being attacked
what no no no no no
it's fine
are they Orange
they're Orange
goodbye the Watchtower uh
foreign
help
last thanks for telling me how the [\h__\h]
did you see them
Revenge
[Music]
we should station one of them here
okay
it's being taken care of but oh
okay you stay and continue here we still
have gold there
I think we can stop the Gathering up
there now
we lost some people here I think
the next villager that comes out a
little repair
hi
that Watch Tower and then continue to
work okay
[Music]
um
oh yeah yeah yeah
I can sell no right okay okay okay
[Music]
sell sell sell sell the gold it sell the
little meat
to do it best I just want the upgrade
okay here we go
finally
okay okay we're upgrading to Imperial
and then
um we fix our our
ugh we fixed our army and then we go to
Orange wherever the [\h__\h] orange is I
don't know where orange is if I didn't
see orange
but I already discovered the whole map
but not really
where's my Scout do I still have my
Scout somewhere
I can't find it is there a shortcut to
find the scouts
there's more Barracks to build more
Pac-Man at the same time
um
do I need the pikemen
I wasn't explored by me no more shortcut
now what the hell
no
I mean I'm guessing oranges like over
here because I wasn't there before
probably
okay
do I really need another barracks
yes they are there
smart
uh unfortunately oh wait I forgot I
should um upgrade uh I had like a didn't
I built or did I not build it yet
because I didn't build on an iron thingy
I don't oh I forgot about it
the blacksmith that's what I mean I
forgot about it right I don't see it
anywhere bestie so
I just I'll just do it all
foreign
[Music]
here again
yeah no
well I don't see it
I don't see it so it's not happening if
I don't see it it's not happening
good good progress really I mean at
least we have this one down
oh I guess I really don't even says here
just destroyed the Town Center
specifically okay okay okay
oh my trips already took care okay so
fast I
wait you know let's go calorie Archer
oh there you go here Scout that I mean
is it really necessary
when we just
when we already kind of know where it is
but okay bye bye meet you on the flip
side okay
mmm helped with gold maybe I don't know
and what else I have upgrades
iron casting chain armor chain armor
we become stronger day by day and they
totally expect it because they know
I'm not a computer I'm a human with a
chat helping me telling me what to do
hmm
it's really select all of them
[Music]
perfect
oh yeah does this really does double
click really select all them because
somehow I feel like it doesn't you're
free maybe it does
[Music]
hey
boy
just making some teams now with that
[Music]
stand right long swordsman
okay
good friends now
oh you're free did I make one out of you
you're afraid Pac-Man Pokemon
they're Pokemon let them go
did I make a grip out of you
are you friends
accepted
six okay
am I ready to go probably not I need
more I need more I need more power
here
should we do Cavalier
oh pal there's paladins that's so cool
you're good okay
maybe do some Monk upgrades too
long or generation conversation versus
resistance conversion conversion
one of my wolves is attacking the enemy
that's funny okay yeah oh yeah
leave it
oh
say thanks Wolfie Chan
he's chilling there right body like
can we kill him can we use him as food
no perfect okay first off let's not do
it he's nice he's nice he helped me
oh wait that needs so much gold wow only
one monk in group must rest after
conversion
monk conversion range
how do you Converse
does it happen automatically
I'll just do this for now
it's so stressful don't upgrade them
don't worry oh okay okay then that's the
only thing I'll do then okay
no no no no
right click with monk I thought that was
healing
oh I guess it was an enemy then okay but
you have to do it yourself huh
um
okay
don't bother with it yeah if I have to
do it myself then I don't want to do it
that's too much for my brain to handle
okay okay
[Music]
what no
Torah
okay
all good where's my scalp by the way oh
he must have died right
people here died too
[Music]
are my allies out allies with the Enemy
yo what the [\h__\h] okay it's okay right
now I still have some gold here if I
really need more golds
so in the moment I can still trade as
well
green is neutral
what the map of the forest is almost
gone
uh oh we have some
good looking stuff here Elite skirmisher
crossbow man oh yeah I'm never I'm
barely making any of these let's make
some calorie archers
oh my God looking not good
foreign
[Music]
no no I don't want to do that okay okay
oh yeah
right
I think
I've been I'm gonna go now
can I go
which how do we go there probably
through the
English
stuff down there and then over the river
do you see my mouse here
what's trebuchet what's that they keep
on saying that what is
flying from Stephanie okay okay okay
from Castle
ah
foreign
leave it okay we go that way then let's
gather every piece of troop I have over
there
[Music]
leave some for protection though
oh
I don't know
okay you know what you'll stay here for
protection
maybe you stay here too oh he can't
leave he can't leave he's stuck
yeah bye
never mind don't don't go then how many
should I take because uh gold is not
looking good again
you are
good job Castle Sean
who are you a cavalier
any army people that I'm missing you're
fake
oh yeah okay yes leave it
right oh yeah yeah okay
I don't see any more
you're staying here
it's just one but better than nothing
[Music]
and always keep on creating more need
more houses I
saw this now okay
you know
um
oh oh they're down here what the [\h__\h]
okay oh I didn't notice that
you still
little Rams oh yeah no
Cafe I don't know about that okay okay
why does no one protect her
checked
well really really how dare you
that's quite so good still damn
right leave it detection Squad
you're being attacked by two
cool oh here oh oh oh oh oh yeah oh
that's not just two that's a couple
well I'm on my way to kill you guys
right now anyway
is this enough
yeah the mom killed her but she has a
lot of HP anyway that wouldn't have
really mattered I think
oh oh it's turned playing there
ah
okay
more than enough okay okay okay okay
let's go
oh no no no not the villagers Cafe
no okay
okay
what are my monks doing
ignore ignore the tents they don't
matter we're going to war I should
probably say wave
War
Chihuahuas more cry
[Music]
I'm not making use of these things I I
just wanna I just want us to work uh
move as a group so
oh that hurts oh that hurts
oh the body runs
yeah oh yeah oh no I'm taking down my
own people
stupid
that's so smart not so smart okay
oh right oh
[Music]
man I got something I got some back up
here
we could be good
[Music]
okay
flank them flank them blank them
is that big thing
assistant
oh no idea what that is
oh there is the gate already is this
Orange
open it up
all right open it up open open oh it's
already they open it for us but never
mind no no no no you like I don't know
you do something else before going there
we let them go back down
[Music]
is that one of theirs
oh God oh God oh God
oh yeah
wait Town Center focus on Town Center if
you can go through
oh my God oh my God oh my God goodbye
don't send them first no why not
back up I don't know if there would be
too late but
should I destroy the castle first or hmm
[Music]
okay I mean it's happening
it's happening
is this thing shooting it is whoa
[Music]
oh that does a lot of damage
okay
[Music]
really bad
oh
[Music]
okay
do I still have to take down the castle
oh no it's dead
it always looks like I have so many
casualties but it was okay it was okay
we did it oh
they surrendered they've seen the light
ah okay we go back let's pause hi guys
go back
or should we go straight up to the
yellow ones we're not ready for them now
are we we need to rebuild
um it's gonna take a while maybe I don't
know
[Music]
I could march on
Scout yellow first
if I just walk in and quickly destroy
the Town Center we might be fine but
Village really go that's will it really
go that smoothly
I could group them there the ones were
already there yeah we would save some
time I guess okay but let's stay like on
the somewhat safer side over here how
about that
what do you think
damn look at that look at what I did
the aftermath
do we have a monk left over
okay yeah oh we do
heal them
friends no
it's like a dog that I can't control
[Music]
let's go unexpected
oh I don't have to look I don't know to
go there okay
okay hi guys by the way what do we do
with you
um
there's still some work to do here but
not really uh how about can we go back
here
one of them
oh it's summer gold here why not
let's make uh some more X-Men
how are you guys
we're about to stay and one voluntary
would be nice to fix my
Artisan uh Siege weapons here wait one
or even two
oh oh
it's not worth it
it's not worth it guys
oh no
so stupid
I'm being attacked by four rings where
oh here oh look what they brought oh
no no no no no no no no no no attack
back
nice
good that I had those here
oh yeah bye
yeah bye
this will hurt my own Mandel your face
go take them down
take them down at least they're focused
on the gate okay we took down that he's
now focusing on my X-Men who will win
this fight oh oh
mama mama mama mama
it's still shooting
finally
wait okay
different ah for taking down one of
those things
hmm
uh are there the villagers here now or
what
okay you know what I'll use you guys
I think they did it I don't know where
those villagers are but I think they did
it
those look pretty repaired to me
all right
Mineo you go here whatever
uh
maybe some more upgrades here
[Music]
um
I'm so stressed I'm so stressed out
let's see what you guys are saying uh
they're still guide and cute what
huh
looks done to me ah this dude
what's he doing ah just
see regrouping
ripping
okay okay
it still looks like I'm missing I have a
lot of Siege weapons but I'm missing a
lot of like fighting Power
oh
I'm getting really nervous here
upgrade cavalry
to Paladin
oh thank God I have so many so much wood
and so much
food
at least that's one thing I did well
okay
Paladin
super strong so are there all paladins
now after that upgrade all those nights
foreign
[Music]
I'm pretty happy but uh
um
you can always send one more over here I
guess
good job Kayla thank you
um
check for upgrades in your buildings
upgrades in which buildings
maybe University
fortified wall would that upgrade the
walls I have right now
chemistry missile plus one missile
attack
hmm
blacksmith upgrades oh okay
attack range for arches yeah that sounds
good
and lever armor for Archer I don't
really have archers
does it also count for archers on horses
I hear you are
make yourself useful
Kelly armor would be better Kelly armor
is more important Cavalry armor
where's that I
want to do
oh did I do the gather point
Cavalry cavalry
armor the top one from this one the ah
okay but it says plate barting armor
that's why I didn't understand I hear a
calorie okay
okay okay okay
should I do these upgrades too
yeah I could do an elite skirmisher or
wait
hmm
nah
did the guys help at all I mean
not much but maybe for some small things
like you know things like keep like the
tip to keep everyone busy at all times
and keep on recreating villagers and and
army constantly
um even these small things are things I
forgot since the last time I played is
like over a month or two ago
oh
I have no arches of skirmishes so true
so true
[Laughter]
[Music]
how many do I need because their their
thing is pretty big town center do I see
the Town Center
which one's the Town Center
that's uh that's something else
oh is that the Town Center
yeah
my Center
it's all the way over there
oh wait that's Orange
almost looks like yellow here
I steep inside okay maybe probably like
like here
somewhere around here so we have to
advance pretty far
um
I'm worried about that
I haven't scouted yet but it's probably
over there
right
or or yeah in the middle of a Farms if
the AI is so smart too
well okay don't need to scout it
my trebuchets
can pave the way well how about we make
the treble Shades into eight
yeah
right
nice
there we go oh we went we went down to
six nights here but now we have 15 again
um okay
let me see what we have
um
I don't know
I don't
understand I don't want them to reset my
Mac my Macross
oh well
look at those paladins paladins oh yeah
they look they look fierce
looks strong
[Music]
let's make a few more
and bring them here
where is this Overkill it can't be
Overkill this is the big last fight
make some more Pike man
sent them here you're free you guys go
here too we need everyone everyone this
is the last big fight I don't care if
they attack my quarters while I'm
attacking them
um
big finale
[Music]
you can upgrade the Pikes too you mean
this hell bear deer we need I would I
would need a bit more gold but yeah why
not
how birdier
okay
yeah
the best chance to have an army of
hundred bucks
aren't like paladins fighting monks to
me they are because of World of Warcraft
since they can heal
don't be so stupid don't don't just
don't be so stupid Oh Oh No
She Stacks man
collateral damage
you wanna like fix something how about
you fix this thing while you're here
okay
are you still joining
I think I want to go
to Captain
I will do whatever that is is it if it
makes it stronger than
I'm happy
oh
[Music]
about that
um
don't worry about them
you can go should we go should we go
send one Paladin one pet you think one
Paladin will do it really that would
really impress me
artisan
uh
here I come
oh that's the orange still okay we're
passing through
it will take a while
the others can surely catch up in the
meantime how's this going
no way
what look at the damage holy [\h__\h] okay
you pounding of one Paladin is enough to
protect my city I see I understand
everything now
goodbye
okay it's quite impressive
oh yeah
oh oh I told him to come with us
can he go inside and fix it while he's
inside or does the RAM have to stop
while that's happening
yeah everything's going smooth so far
he was that villager to build Barracks
there
we mean like around here
interesting interesting interesting
where is he now
what are you doing
ah there he is okay okay good idea
um
right
except okay yeah I'm just gonna [\h__\h] my
shortcuts
we just do it like this
supposed to walk slow when they're going
to a war like this
it's a whole system it's normal it's
normal
okay should we go for here or maybe
through here
because I feel like if we go through
here the castle will have an easy game
at attacking us as well
so I would say this one what do you
think
where are my things
oh wait if I send my Rams there won't
they be attacked by The Friendly Fire of
my thingies here
there might be more than one Castle oh
but I don't see one here
will they notice that they're being
attacked
that was a mess what the [\h__\h] how can
you miss
you're you're stationary is that the
right word
it's gonna chill
you don't I don't know this thing no
no no where are you going
okay okay what the [\h__\h] we're already
ah you died for being an idiot
right
all right here we go
I guess yeah
[Music]
all right let's go let's go it's
probably
I don't care about the casualties it's
casualties happen
uh once we see it I will there we go
wait is that it looks so beautiful did
they Advance oh what's that it's dead oh
they're way more advanced than me but
that's that's it right that's the Town
Center
yeah okay
yeah
Cafe
round body round body around please
don't all die ah you guys be like a
little bit slower maybe like I'm wormy
oh God oh maybe not
all the towers
uh
right
what voice broadcast
[Music]
worst case they will be the last one
standing but
oh
yeah don't waste Joan by the way
where's Joan out there okay John
oh no ah the one with the little health
is subscribers okay I forgot
you know one you go you go back you go
back you go all the way back flims has
been liberated
now is a coronation of the fact can
proceed
[Music]
back what are you waiting for
Hallelujah that took me two hours damn
oh my God I am
I which sounds pretty good really
uh I hope it's just not too bad
hours
as some even now to kiss her horses yes
and a thousand Flags danced in the
breeze
Palace
the door fan knelt before the Archbishop
and Rose as king of fall
history anthems and sermons filled the
great Chateau
interspersed among perfume dukes and
ladies were tattered soldiers from our
army
yeah I'm sorry about that
was that the king's side as was her
bedraggled battle standard was that mean
despite the celebration I know in my in
much that this war is far from over
really well this is not the end of the
Zone grandfather died
the last one no Joan gives us hope hmm
but I do not know if hope is enough to
ensure Victory well well it's at least a
good start
uh
oh finally tomorrow oh there's more it
was a hundred year one I thought you
know in inside the game it might end
there uh
uh maybe we can do one more which will
probably take another two hours
oh
should we try one more
if it doesn't take more than two hours
then I'm okay with it
shut up
next one is not that long really that
would be good actually I appreciate that
September now that I'm you know in the
flow I feel like we can Moss as a king
once do more
either more effectively games in
Florence with the bull jealousy grows
it always does it always does evil
King always has evil advisors
everyone wants to poison the King's
Children must hurry to fulfill her
mission that's young the true love false
has been under English too
and French Patriots trapped within the
city are eager to escape oh we are now
marching on Paris hoping that the
reinforcements we have been promised I
hope we can see the Eiffel Tower just
kidding
oh wow
okay Joan must survive after you locate
the refugees
Uganda Vu with the king's reinforcements
in Paris just south of the river bridge
Refugee villagers in Paris are
attempting to escape English tyranny
locate at least six of the refugees
but we save the refugees one
do not try and defeat every English unit
focus on your objectives okay
I feel like it's speaking so directly to
me and apparently ain't you need no Ram
switch to trebuchets they do all
destruction from far away
all you have to do is just guarding them
okay so you mean that
um at the time when I was making Rams I
shouldn't have been doing that I should
have been focusing on going to Imperial
age and then make the trebuchets and
then we don't need any of the Rams okay
um are we starting in the Imperial age
now that would make sense at least
no objective only War
that's just basically easy model
campaign you just build units to defend
them and you've basically won all right
yeah
um
yeah they they have a huge range so
definitely very very powerful uh guard
your seat oh there it is we can't use
Siege weapons Towers will be a big
problem if you do not the refugees can
be used to repair usage weapons but they
cannot construct buildings oh okay if
Facebook overwhelming opposition run
away run away really
they're telling me to run
your Scouts reports the French army
under the command of Joe and blue has
reached the outskirts of the City of
Paris red the city is huge and there are
English soldiers everywhere luckily
there are partisans within the city
walls who will rise up against the
English once they see the French army
the French King has also promised
reinforcements yellow
to be sent to the City by ship once John
were just a
is
an island on the Cena River okay I don't
understand anything compian lies to the
east of Paris and is the nearest Allied
town if the attack fails this will be
the only Safe Haven in the area oh so if
I run I run to cyan
that sounds like I will have to run
that sounds like they know I'm gonna
fail
but then I just have to
prepare so much that I don't fail
um
how many of them did I absorb oh you
know me too while I absorbed only this
last part
I have to speed run
what do I do first
what do we do first
I don't know
what don't we do first
because I have a scalp let us locate the
refugees and escort them to the
Rendezvous point with the King's Men
like now we're gonna go now
Goofy
we're just gonna go
wait where are we going to the yellow
uh is that yeah that's not yellow
Scout focus on scouting which one is the
Scout let's light Cavalry where's Scout
I don't have a scout is light Cavalry
the scallop
looking blind
light calories Scott oh okay uh I guess
Scout
where where are we scouting to
I don't know where to scout
huh
don't forget to separate your arm into
cribs okay hi
is this all I get
it wait what are those there's a
paladins and those are Cavaliers okay I
feel like they can go together
one oh
is he okay it seems okay
yeah right I think they can go together
too right yeah they're pretty
pretty fast okay yeah what's that
looking
who is you
oh
[Music]
and some weird or Cannonball stuff or
something okay yeah
and you go fine all right how are we
doing
oh
he's infiltrating the system
all right I've seen enough you go here
so where do we go
first
[Music]
just make the cowboy their own group so
they can quickly attack if they have to
okay yeah okay they're their own group
now
my free Heroes
good fit ah pray okay yeah
indeed I do okay
find weak point
quick Point weak point
[Music]
well they're doing in the meantime don't
just wait or what
you're fake oh yeah
[Music]
we're finishing the John Arc because
last time I started the babarosa arc but
I failed tremendously
foreign
okay
I'm just like I feel so time pressured
you know
when I see people play this game by like
literally micromanaging everything that
makes me think oh you have to because
otherwise if you you know don't I
watched the video it wasn't about PVP it
was p v e but like he was saying stuff
like
you know how you how you maximize you
know [\h__\h] like you start out and you
have to you have like three villages so
you have to use one villager to build
one house and two villages to build the
other house because while because
building and then create Villages
because both building a house and
creating a villager takes the same
amount of time and you have to build the
the second house that you build with two
people faster in order to you know you
know you know because you need houses
for The Villages that you're creating
and blue you know stuff like that the
build order and how many seconds what
takes and how many materials you need
for what and blah blah blah and I'm just
like sitting there like
laughs
[Laughter]
um really do I really have to look like
I think this through so much what
uh yeah I was trying my best
um
totally brain overloading I guess you
don't have to but then why do they do
that for PVP
anyway dude where are we going with you
I don't see any path over the over this
River
there's no path over this River what
maybe we don't need to go over the river
not sure
should I just attack this big thing
oh let me see here
lay Siege to red
what but how am I ready this city is
like way too big
aside and start blasting
eh
thank you for the flex hellbird
well I mean that's pretty much it that's
where the the river is so
there's not much more than I can start
oh there's even more red here and
another cat a castle
oh my God uh watchtowers
okay
foreign
everything I needed to see
let's go
but where
I feel like this is way too obvious to
attack
would be maybe the first choice for
stupid people how about we enter through
here
I don't know
West entrance
oh that's not that's that's its own
small thing there interesting
okay so we wanna go for here
just try anywhere see how far you get
wait I didn't even
see and I didn't see any cyan
hmm
digital ones there's another one of
these walls okay
I'm just chilling
I'm gonna
go in from
where somebody said West so I'm like
I'll try West though
is this West not quiet
uh free
maybe here
the music was good
just waiting for them to arrive
D there we go we're setting up
and they're supposed to just stay close
to the
okay yeah
The Siege weapons right
do I have to give them like a defensive
stance then there we go
on attack these [\h__\h]
don't go
oh they're shooting
one of the Holy guys oh no he's not one
of the Holy Ghost thank god oh yeah
goodbye
to shoot them
ah toshio
protect them how can I protect them it's
not like they can do much when they're
standing around to the Traditions I can
advance now okay
okay
um let's move let's move guys
but they'll take all the damage
yeah that's all okay okay
where are we going next
[Music]
this campaign is confusing me
keep them behind
okay well this is difficult to stand
tall is too small
okay uh yeah bye
stop shooting
um okay
I need to repair these things before
they break
I swear to God
now he runs
he runs
where where to next so I don't
understand what am I looking for the the
refugees but we're adding
how do I know we just run around this
whole city and
just hope for something good to happen
why I found one flag leave it
this [\h__\h]
no no
don't don't attack don't attack
[Music]
you're afraid
leave it
okay yeah
oh I can't repair it anymore once it's
broken I need one of those repair dudes
finally oh yeah
but should I like take down any of these
buildings
no
foreign
we have rescued the refugees
where which ones we should head to the
bridge at the sen River for the
rendezvous with the King's Men we should
wait here which refugees the king's
reinforcements will be along any second
[Music]
they said wait here right
foreign
hey
artisan
I am so small
we are all the king aren't these three
only ones here
two people
and one of them is a [\h__\h] Scout
oh hey
and then we move on right maybe
at least we can repair this yeah
King a little cheap a little
and he's surprised he has no support
here all right when we're done repairing
I mean we can fix this one up a little
bit too
do we have a monk
I don't remember seeing a monk
okay and now we go here or what
Javier that's mean
that's mean I'm trying I'm trying but
it's not so easy
that's what it what is this place
and it's the sign finally
now let's see where it is
the music is so friendly
it's so friendly
but we have to fight
[Music]
oh
asking you guys
what when did they attack Jonah won John
died
what the [\h__\h]
what
it was so looking pretty decent
a refugee
the refugees are not allowed to die
either
[\h__\h] the refugees what
oh all the safe
uh
we need six refugees to win and are
there only exactly six
I mean how did I get to my oh
um note game
yeah of course I have to
continue here
obviously
uh
is this right before it happened because
the other one would be 20 minutes before
that
see
Harry is just ahead let us locate the
refugees and escort them to the Rondo
oh it's a replay
what
oh
21.
this one
oh
oh okay okay are we here we are here
before fighting the refuges I think
uh wait wait oh God
no no no no
it's so close that was so close but this
[\h__\h] worse can't even move there
right
I know just just go there
otherwise he will follow me eternally
and never stop once I turn my back to
him
you will always continue following me
right no see there he is that's sucker
I hate him Goofy
oh yeah
right
you little [\h__\h]
Seth I can't do it with him
yes yes yes
finally
okay
uh the refugees weren't they like
somewhere here
one sweet
show our faces
um
it's gonna die
where are those
I shouldn't point they like here I need
to be repaired immediately we should
wait oh thank God the king's
reinforcements will be along any second
we have rescued the refugees now
okay
I wonder if I've run around here oh see
there's a couple more
we are all the king of the photos did I
miss anything
okay
for example
it's one two three four five six that's
six but maybe there's more we are not
alone we must die
in
mmm
safe
hmm
that's all here
here you mean
I got them all okay so there's really
exactly six oh dear oh dear
okay okay
and
I will Scout
but I know there's some enemies right
there
right all right weren't they like here
huh
make a group of villagers yeah yeah okay
uh villagers
uh let's do seven
six okay I got six of them can I like
hmm Livy as long as they're very far
behind
they will hopefully be safe right I
can't hide them
in the trebuchets or so
um
Santa's got a teal
hopefully he will survive
all right
foreign
such a weird path
we are tired of licking English boots we
follow where you lead Jean of Arc
oh okay so should I go to where they are
see uh wait wait oh so stressful
hey
they understand yeah
[Music]
they got good taste
all right we'll keep on moving come on
why are you not moving oh yeah
although they're not being attacked
seems pretty safe that's a big army
that's way more than what the king gave
me okay okay yeah
leave it okay okay okay
okay
how the [\h__\h] did I die here before I'm
not even seeing the same enemies
[Music]
okay okay let's go guys let's go let's
go let's go let's go
oh yeah yeah I know I know one of my
villagers died but I just there's no one
here now
so I find that interesting
it's looking good now it's looking good
all right all right all right we're at
the Rendezvous point
okay yeah let's should we send some to
kill these peeps
[Music]
hi please
it's going well okay okay okay
uh
can I I want to select
now everybody oh well never mind
they had some horses too right so maybe
I should make a new horse tag
yeah I have 12 now okay yeah
um yeah
what is that I don't know
good fit
huh
there's a difference between
oh
unpacked okay
okay I don't know let's just go where
are we going next to cyan
make a hole with you oh here in this
wall okay
attack
it's the same unit I know I know
Google
snow but it's so cute it's so small and
now it's so big and powerful which one
did I attack I want to attack the same
wall
are the Cannons too
you're free
[Applause]
yes cannons
I came in like a cannonball
foreign
wrecking ball almost the same thing oh
maybe this one too so I have more space
come on okay yeah
they're actually pretty effective too
they need so much time
close enough close enough
that was
really lucky that I found you dude
I would have almost not noticed you I'm
so sorry
all right
uh
horses
six okay
well we're going next this way perhaps
let's follow the Scout for now save just
in case okay
[Music]
just a new safe game save file right
okay again don't know how to move
because they're stuck yeah AI kind of
stupid sometimes not gonna lie
um oh no I can't forget my villagers
burgundy is coming you are vastly
outnumbered
get the refugees into the Fortress your
Fortress
the burgundies oh no the burgundies
uh we can't just straight on straight up
go they're villagers we have to chill
here for a moment
okay
oh no oh
them
stay alive
yeah the purple is fading
so good I think that does collateral
damage too okay
uh
okay we can move on
can I attack this one from here really
yo
the range sick
okay leave it oh but it's obviously
gonna miss
hey
where are the villagers
okay stay safe stay safe good friend oh
yeah stay safe
difference between standard and the
hardest insane of course but I still
wish I had an easy mode oh I've arrived
Cafe relax I've arrived I've arrived
that's it that's all they have burgundy
is this company is that the goal
compian my companion oh yeah
okay yeah hello
oh there's one burgundy here but he is
so scared did oh they don't even attempt
I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared okay yeah oh yeah stay out here
first
just in case
they suddenly decide to attack no no
leave it okay we're good
can't be the end
there must be more
but wait there's more
Cafe okay where is this Castle you are
victorious no peasants are safe
I just hope Jon can make it to his
account is right there don't worry about
it I think that's her
you're John enjoy wait
that was
because I'm the one really embarrassing
fail but that came out of nowhere you
guys were surprised too so
ah hooray
we have arrived in company
with our companions everybody who's
joining us
for the fight
foreign
thank you for believing
uh if this was short I wonder if the
next one's like short like this too I
could attempt it as well does anyone
remember
return to campaigns let's take a look
maybe
which one ah the perfect Mark too
July 14th George
the English put her on trial as a
heretic
John's mind was as sharp as herself
cunning verbal traps of her prosecutors
in the end oh wow George would not
renounce her mission
[Music]
July 14.
a rich World Mead empty and poor
something
John's mind was as sharp as her Source
what do you mean I skipped one
I skipped the last cutscene can I look
at that
before five
September 3rd fast of the Kings must
hurry
true love this I already saw right um
but I just want to see the ending
no I just want to see the ending
load the last auto save
[Music]
what
ah there it was
load game
with 40 That's the different one maybe
this one
that's an important Cuts Daniel
far no I don't want to do that again
it was a replay oh for [\h__\h] sake I
said load game it's so confusing
uh
see it there it is uh 36 hmm
and right IR winner in game chat
I uh that's like a cheat code oh is that
cheat codes to win the vision
well I mean we already won it so it's
not really cheating we just want to
watch the cutscenes
[Music]
wow hey thank you for teaching me that
very useful I feel like I'm playing Sims
right now okay oh there it is
as the refugees fled into the Chateau of
company
Jordan was trapped outside no
volcanjan soldiers knocked her from her
horse and paraded around with their
prisoner
knowing our precious Joan of Arc
languages
the soldiers stare at the uncaring sky
condemning themselves for being unable
to save her
how could you lose her I need your
defeat how could you not protect her
and the King sent the promised
reinforcements we would have captured
the city
yeah it was his fault
oh okay
you don't understand
okay now that makes sense
the English put her on trial as a
heretic oh John's mind was a sharpest
it's gonna be burned she avoided all the
cunning verbal traps of her prosecutors
in the end Joan would not renounce her
mission
and burned her at the stage not like she
ever had a chance
as peasant and Noble Mandalay take arms
my Army
and even without the king
poised to strike at the English
stronghold
forever
should I die in this battle
enough early on oh I die as a patriot of
fox yes
that actually was one of the songs of
the Japanese
um Jean dark uh Musical that I watched
in person in Japan of my favorite Idol
groups who were performing it they had
one song but they were singing let me
say love yourself it was so sad
let's go see
so nostalgic we will love yourself okay
the trade card carrying the French flag
must survive the trade card
Rendezvous the French army commanded by
a constable
rendezvous with the French artillery
commanded by Jean Bureau
plant the French flag loaded in a trade
card on the hill in castillon Colorado
Flags
uh okay
so we're not building uh like an army
again we're just going with what we have
again
the French army can only support oh a
population of 125
most of the land here is occupied you
will have to displace burgundy in order
to build a town ah okay do not knock
down all of burgundy's walls you can use
it yeah okay
for your own defense longbowmen are
powerful but bombard cannons are better
you can order bombard cannons and other
Siege weapons to the no attack stands if
they're hurting your own troops
uh-huh the French are mastering their
forces to avenge the death of Joan and
to drive the English out of France once
and for all
Jocelyn the French Commander has brought
the French flag to the battlefield with
the aim of planting it on the hill near
Castalian
a large French army Waits his command
but it is low on supplies the
burgundians have a walled town to the
west of your position with ample
resources the Earl of Shrewsbury orange
camps to the north of The Burgundian
town
uh-huh
where are the burgundians if he's North
or maybe
this one no
he has brought heavy Calvary to the
battlefield but they should be no match
for the French heavy cavalry
oh
okay
wait are we fighting him at the same
time
as when we enter the moon as we enter
burgundy
the English army is the most dangerous
opponent they will fiercely defend the
hill with long government Cavaliers to
represents
and fortifications what are
fortifications
I'm superior anyway okay at least again
still orange and purple
[Laughter]
walls oh okay
I shall eventually
let's Revenge wait where
where
they don't tell me where burgundy is
okay
I thought I start with like a small army
hello Jocelyn
the Army awaits your command
one person okay oh yeah
one person
oh yeah
more leave it oh yeah
that's why I need to plant the flag
right oh leave it
safter
oh yeah I'm hoping
doesn't have for now
foreign
[Music]
yes
we need more blood blood for the blood
God for blood stream for blood oh we
even have some villagers okay yeah and
well at least they can die but let's try
to not have them die I'm gonna put them
on seven
um you guys and you guys on one
guys
and I guess for some reason I'm putting
you on
three
and oh it
oh let us know
and then this and this my trip is on
four
okay uh I think I got them all okay I'm
still going like this but wait maybe
maybe Scouts should we Scouts we'll see
yeah
against French oh that's burgundy yeah
perhaps we should defeat the burgundians
in establish our base in their own town
yeah just a thought just a flat yeah I
totally agree
I skipped The Villages over here
uh uh okay everybody move oh
you attack oh so aggressive
it's like playing a game of dodgeball
ball will hit none of them probably oh
my God
it's watching this is ridiculous just
ignore them
right oh yeah
okay uh
I'm just gonna shoot this
it's gonna shoot right there oh they're
coming out
oh they're kind of stupid ass mom can he
convert me
[Music]
this is stressing me out again what are
you doing here anyway
[Music]
where's my card by the way
are they still doing fine all right uh
bye
go in
and what do we attack the castle we
should keep the castle right Town Center
or what what do I have to do so it
counts as my place
kill the Town Center
don't go in okay yeah oh yeah
oh okay yeah ah they're converting me
yeah
Castle okay
oh yeah
okay okay now they're hitting the castle
oh this is looking better
oh they're sending some reinforcements
but
now at least everybody is in uh
position that I can accept uh I think I
might actually bring some villagers
to fix this while they're getting a
canopy effects while it's being operated
oh beautiful beautiful we might not even
need their help right now
iraqs
Cafe
leave it
almost there almost there it can we it
can be operated
but then well then
yeah
they're protecting they're protecting
just fine
and
this City's mine I think
I think it's mine may I enter may I
enter please
next to Town Center oh okay
the Town Center I think
we have to enter for this though
it's okay no not too many casualties so
far I think oh yeah
go go go go inside
oh the monk where's that stupid Monk
before he can convert you do it do it do
it do it do it yes
after
it
all right
Town Center I hope that's the only one
where did you die oh no guys don't don't
scramble scrabble
dude you have to go for that wall
she doesn't understand
Maybe
[Music]
ah no no no no no no no no no no
yeah
oh hey it fell down though
Tower and the Town Center
capture the burgundians
[Music]
you're not giving up yet though it seems
the
they're paying tribute
they're still fighting me too though I
think
oh yeah
time to build my Empire Hell yeah okay
all right how about
can I already fix this wall
stone wall Gusty soap there we go
hi everybody come on in this is my my
place now
except
they're standing super chats
build the TC next to the stone stone uh
here
just give them some time move your butts
lazy asses
boy you are
gonna start
we're gonna do the most important thing
uh wait where's Town Center again
Alex Miller
I hear that one I thought that was
before having for making people so
okay so we have berries we have gold
where is normal Stone ah here's some
normal Stone
kind of far but the rest is on here so I
think I should stay here and those
houses are mine too now right
okay okay okay
now we just for a while started building
our army again right
no idea however how much I should um
how much I should prepare how serious
this is
foreign
first of all to heal all of these almost
dead army units
very good
well this takes so long to build huh
bestie soap
okay all of them all of them
oh he did nice hit nice aim
build Tower
built so all right oh what did I just do
okay
you build
uh because they don't have it yet right
they're only they only had some houses
and that's pretty much it interesting
uh
uh a mining camp Rusty soap
oh they're starting with those resources
and lumber Camp
um
I'll put it here
oh and then let's make some
oh already a Max oh okay there was not
enough houses all right
so
build a house wall oh I've seen that in
one of the guide videos you mean like
here
so
check out my new place I did not invite
you
I don't remember inviting you
sir
oh you're running now aren't ya
all right
[Music]
okay
see
is it good to have a house there
this is a good way of blocking
pasty soap I hope so better
but then they can't farm this wood where
is your precious peasant General now
what do you mean you mean
soccer like that
she she may have been a peasant from
your eyes but for us she was like a
queen
hmm
I'm Gonna Keep the first informed yeah
yeah I want to but sometimes don't if
they're like down here don't they
automatically go over here I don't want
them to do that
oh
[Music]
he's not so smart Cafe theft
hey let's build
I can't do a watchtower yet I need to
know do this
and maybe also a mining camp
and let's attack him
unless okay's running
never mind
build Powers Barracks oh yeah he has so
much to do there's so much to do
I know I know I know okay Barracks
should we build yeah so
Cafe
uh stable
then they can quickly walk out this gate
that's why I'm putting them there
foreign
[Music]
by the way
um
I was surprised a lot of people don't
know what is
um
it's an Italian cheese it's similar to
mozzarella
a while ago
sometime earlier this year I discovered
it and I was like
um this [\h__\h] is really good
I ate a pizza with burrata and that
opened my eyes and now I want burrata
all the time and in Italy maybe maybe
you remember from my report
um
I wanna let's get this over so I also
had had muscata
and everything several times while I was
in Italy recently
but she saw
[Music]
good stuff
oh yeah is that really safe
okay yeah
bonjour uh I guess it doesn't really hmm
there's no defense defense here so
I kind of need uh
Tower there but um I still barely have
any materials
is so easy to make guys I know it looks
so delicious and you guys were like
please give but it's so easy to make you
can look up even a tutorial on on
YouTube you basically just need cherry
tomatoes I mean you could make with
everything but the classic one is with
cherry tomatoes
Mineo Cafe menu
okay
yeah
and then some basil and a baguette type
of bread or so
and uh
oh my God
okay so this is not quite safe
so many of them are coming
[Music]
Play Store
oh yeah
oh man I really need a monk too
[Music]
yeah boy
okay okay
I'm fixing it I'm trying my best okay
I I need a I need a monk I really need a
monk I need to heal my my especially the
important people
should I build a normal wall there
but there's more and more of them coming
I'll just I guess I'll build it around
it didn't really work the way I wanted
it to last you so
[Music]
okay can they stop coming now I need
some time to build this up it's not a
thick looks so tasty it is so tasty so
you need a [\h__\h] ton of olive oil and a
basil
um preferably some garlic
cherry tomatoes you can also make it
with salmon or whatever it doesn't
matter
leave it
it's really good
it's yummy it's easy to make I made it
in like five minutes
no attack
five billion million spikes a young
whoa whoa whoa
I don't have an eye on those things uh
constantly so I did not realize that's
the soap
thank you guys
stop it already
villagers
[Music]
don't be so aggressive
this cannon would be
oh yeah useful to support
um I don't know never mind it can stay
it should kill this dude though can I
oh my God this is unbelievable
unbelievable I'm using my constellation
mode
for this stupid fight and he's winning
he's winning but at what cost
back in
ah why that boy
oh is this perfectly walled now is it
working now I think this is enough the
house seems to block that part okay okay
uh
um Mineo
no I need wait
now we can focus on building [\h__\h] again
I think stage Workshop
Cafe
um
Barracks we have archery range we don't
have yet
got some towels
fix that
I am you stupid burgundians want their
Town back
oh maybe if I take down this is that
where they're always coming from
attack that
might be where they are reproducing yeah
monastery
uh
or uh needs a bunch more wood okay
here
oh beautiful beautiful nice hit nice
shot
they're building a town next to me
our day
oh I should start experiment
good friend oh yeah
important people
okay at least this one will be down in
the moment
and
really need more wood
can you actually here
Castle up front as soon as possible
yeah yeah yeah
I need materials first look just look
the yuck
all right leave it
I think
oh sorry
who's that
he's so fancy
they shoot arrows
perfect oh yeah no why did you leave
don't let them
in ah
this is so chaotic they're like they
look like to me
upgrade a light calorie uh-huh
it looks like [\h__\h] asked me
hey
uh no actually never mind can I
I can already make a castle all right
how about
[Music]
okay really go outside Maybe not maybe
I'm faster if I yeah
last Saw
it oh
good fish oh yeah
ignoring them works
I thought they stopped feeling that
meant that this was considered a wall I
mean
kind of is
hmm
now this I cannot just let the stand
well they're going down relatively fast
[Music]
here there you go monastery
it's beautiful up there Rusty soap
[\h__\h]
hey
Cafe
okay yeah
that's all
I'm trying to come and get me at the
same time
oh
no
I thought I
thought I had I should have built this
wall properly in the beginning
[Music]
don't give up don't give up
don't give up
what are you doing there
[Music]
is a good day
hey hey hey hey I took over control
[Music]
I think I kind of took control over the
situation I mean uh two way too many
casualties but wait are you saying that
my holy dudes died
[Music]
I'm done
no
no he's here
wouldn't the mission fail oh they're all
dead for real
I guess it doesn't I can still do the
mission without them huh
uh
wow
should I restart
[Laughter]
the only unit that counts is the car and
look at the card thriving living its
best life they [\h__\h] placed a purple
flag there
their day oh
no okay I guess I should probably like
restart but
oh this is really bad
this really is really bad oh man
oh yeah
[Laughter]
that flag was always there oh really
it's pretty downhill from here
oh [\h__\h]
uh I resigned ah
I did I was not the
first sign
different
oh man
I'll try again but
ah
so my biggest mistake was maybe building
those houses there and thinking that
that's good enough
right I shall eventually
the Army awaits your command
don't rush to tell us if your army
what
um you like my positive outlook thank
you I have to stay positive I have to
now I'll start from scratch it's okay
I didn't save after
taking over burgundy did I should have
saved
it
wasn't made
so happy to see you guys again I hope
that this time you stay alive
um
princess I really don't really have to
do this do I
oh oh right
we'll see how English longboards fit
against French candle
and let's just go
okay
be hacks
let's do this again
we've been here before
but
this time we will do it better we learn
from mistakes don't worry
perhaps we should defeat the burgundy
and establish our base in their own town
that's what I'm doing Justice okay yeah
know exactly what I'm doing
[Music]
oh beautiful beautiful
who's that
what
how fast is that
French flag has been captured oh
don't go inside yet
[Laughter]
[Music]
I didn't notice my cards
run
I shall events
too lightly
did I leave this guy behind last time
leaving
oh yeah
the pink the pink yes leave it oh yeah
uh
it's my last try
even if I failed my last try I have to
read simple chats
she's not bloody enough how about the
cart
just chills here okay like like here
we'll see yeah
oh oh nice day noticed that and
immediately joined oh yeah
and now it's right now we can't possibly
do the same mistake again because the
cart is chilling here spray
leave it
and it will stay there
[Music]
so
attack on the wall one more time perhaps
we should defeat the burgundians and
establish our base in their own town
just a thought
now when all these purple suckers come
I shall protect my honor
me
pretty pretty nice oh
yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes and the stupid
ass Tower no stay here you little [\h__\h]
yeah
I guess you can try let's let's take it
out fast faster faster
okay burgundy
burgundy will be mine
there you go Castle found
and
can I do it from outside yes okay and I
kind of still want to stay outside too
right you guys told me to stay outside
last time I think
right
another Tower down
okay I think I'm doing better
I see less casualties on my side too
short
oh yeah
now let's not get too close to the
castle because they will shoot me leave
it I won't be doing here I'm almost down
almost almost
no don't shoot that we can use that
oh yeah
[Music]
oh yes okay Castle down next is Town
Center
I have perfect control
oh okay I'm gonna do this one mm-hmm
well the trebuchets squeeze their way
through good job good job
hey shut
hey
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
near the bottom of the map destroying
that earlier free a lot of headache oh
kill those [\h__\h] monks before they
take
they died instantly I just looked at
them
yes yes yes yes yes
this place is mine now no no we have
captured The Burgundian stockpile of
research okay
okay
bring these peeps inside
I heard them
I guess so
because otherwise they'll [\h__\h] annoy
me again I'll save this game now
um because this was a good start
stay here
okay so one of you
well build me or many of you
pick me a town center
wait you fix
The Stonewall
okay
yeah oh yeah all right all right
we only have what how many villagers
okay what are you doing
let's build
Stonewall
um
[Music]
make it faster
as fast as possible and should I really
send them down there now
to the bottom
where where might they possibly be I
feel like my mind is too busy to go
there but if it really helps
yeah I get a lot of more units with a
lot more help that is true
mmm
quickly attacked to Yellowstone North
field
just let them defend
Libre
may be hard for me
focus on the offensive milk kill them
one Longbow man in your town huh
oh there he is he's camouflaging
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
oh faster coming they're coming already
know
faster
ah yes scare him scare him scare tactic
okay
you're not finished building
what
don't tell me this is
is this done now or what
searched and tell them to go outside
maybe I don't know
I can't reach it
yeah but does it like if they can't
reach it that means that there's no hole
right
okay I hope so
almost done
locked Brigade okay here we go guys here
we go
hey
start with
the barracks
okay
one of you can fix this house while
we're here
one oh I I forgot you I'm so sorry don't
you get through even if the lock is
gated
the gate is locked
oh
okay
foreign
need to unlock an onion okay
oh oh oh
I'm not sure if you can make it oh oh
he's ignoring her how nice of him
oil
[\h__\h] okay oh [\h__\h] and built me please no
nothing
um mining camp
okay
oh [\h__\h]
menu okay
have to start getting those minerals
okay yeah
I want to build another mining camp here
though
houses first oh
hey
materials don't call
let me build
okay do you guys think this one will go
well
I hope so sincerely hope so why is this
card not golden by the way they should
make this one glow so that I know
protect this card
oh
[\h__\h] oh I still need even more houses oh
Cafe okay focus on house first
crusty soap
okay yeah
[Music]
more
at least this house they only need wood
okay who would wear
okay doing okay okay
but I don't have a lumber camping
hmm
whatever for now we can just bring it
directly to the
town center right if you put units in
Towers castles or transgender Shooters
oh yeah I I know that
um
I know you can Garrison them
um oh you're done nice huh
sure
mm-hmm
AI will funnel for openings and walls if
they are all concentrated there it might
be easier to focus your defenses
so you're telling me to make a hole in
my wall
I guess
that is
strategy
and that sounds risky yeah I don't like
that
hmm make one hole here and have like
five Towers in the castle here or so
um
I think I would prefer to do it normal I
think because I feel like if I try that
with so little experience in the game
I'll probably [\h__\h] it up
let me have more thank you
oh now we have some wood let me okay she
can't even pass
okay yeah I can't even pass oil
if an NPC can't pass they should
make the MPC
they should make them so smart to like
have the others move away
but I guess that's too much to ask
bestie so
okay
um who do I who else can I okay you
wanna maybe take a break real quick
and build me another house thank you
Kim's old yeah
not be an excuse
they've done so many things right
you could have fixed it especially
because this is the definitive edition
but sometimes I guess you keep these
kind of things
sometimes you keep these things too
I don't know keep the charm I guess
keep certain bugs oh did you hear
Pokemon
uh Scarlet Violet is getting okay
a fix a little up updated where is your
precious person General now shut up
Apple [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
bomb guys are really cool
is it already is the patch already I
don't know I think it said something
like in December beginning of December
or so
y
um
no uh I'm gonna do the castle but it
needs a lot of stone
can't do the tower even needs way more
Stone ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] great are
you guys dealing with these people
[Music]
kind of sauce
if I put more of these there they can
kind of do it within the walls
okay let me make one more candy here and
oh didn't I need a boot camp I don't
have one yet right oh look at them
okay this a is genuinely stupid
how do they think they can possibly pass
through
it's kind of noisy though I want them to
stop making so much oh they're dead
you did that good job
don't mind them doing this forever can
my
long distance peeps shoot at them from
Over the trees
they can shoot over walls can they not
also shoot over trees I would be sick
yeah
go pump guys go bump guys sorry Army
passing through ah
they fell into my trap
oh how unfortunate for them oh oh I
almost feel sorry for oh they gave up
okay
don't get too close or you will regret
it okay
house
[Music]
what else we have the barracks okay but
we need everything else right
oh I can't build it more wood
oh wait no wrong tree this one
are the buildings within triple Shield
range which buildings
which buildings oh these ones yeah
this one I could probably get
on this one too we tried that before
I'll take care of this one now I don't
know if they're using it but
oh hey Mineo Cafe menu
I'm so hungry holy [\h__\h]
I'm so hungry
don't find the wood that's acting as you
was yeah I'm kind of right
these ones gonna be okay
in this camp this home
okay I'll make an I'll make a new one
okay
I'm worried about that too that suddenly
I have like an opening at some point
that would suck
it'll be another one a.m dinner oh I
mean you know I had to stay up until 4
30 4 a.m 30 the other day for
here soon
[Music]
or any recording okay
yeah and that kept me up until like 6 30
like the the recording was like until 6
30 but then then I saw I had to I think
I still had to eat dinner after that I
thought no no I didn't I had it before
but
um
after after that I still had a quick
chat important chat with uh Jen ma who
was of course awake always a link
yeah we had the
business Chit Chat
trying to get this one though oh it's
too far what are you gonna move over
there right
so yeah that kind of [\h__\h] up my sleep
schedule a lot so me eating at 1am now
is still considered to be very early
um you know it could be like that
sometimes it wasn't really I couldn't
really avoid it because
um
I it was something I wanted to do I
couldn't turn it down sometimes these
things are actually times
oh
I need food oh dear
[Music]
food
I'm trying to
you know improve it fix it soonish
oh are you even trying
to try to look at you for your hair
and now [\h__\h] you can do it yes
fix it before you can do it again hell
yeah I mean during my trip to Italy
it's going perfectly fine
everything was nice
uh I need some of you guys
take care of him from outside preferably
bonjour
oh he's already leaving
oh this one we can
destroy as well
they're so mean
hey
can we make castle
almost almost there
stop it more
I'm counting we need just a bit more
maybe I watched how I would be no no I
think I should say for the castle
right
I could make a door there what's the
blue
how much does this need 125 Wood oh oh
oh Castle is in reach
Mino
[Music]
where should we do it
oh damn oh this is not looking so they
can't even [\h__\h]
[Music]
can I do that
at least it's in reach oh yes that might
work
yeah
oh they made a hole
um
can you
set
[Music]
okay
defend
[Music]
leave it okay
so
no no no no no no no no
no no okay okay
this level is a real step up it feels
like it in terms of difficulty yeah
Cafe
pasta sauce
make some space for the lady please
[Music]
oh yeah
right
is he like stuck or what okay fish
you're sure
okay there we go
ah
this is really hard I still don't have
my um
my Archer thingy up yet oh my God
busty soap
okay
what is that we still need a stable tool
right
what's happening
okay okay
Cafe
is she hey is she seriously lumbering
you were supposed to build that oh wait
that was never buildable I guess but you
can fix the other things
[Music]
okay
this is really difficult yeah my artists
are really useful to to defend quite
well okay but let me build a tower
[Music]
leave it
game
we still have a hole in the wall but
yeah they would be coming proof there
was
doesn't look like it
okay we'll both Castle boots yeah
I want to save here
I like how my the names of my save files
really tell a story don't they
oh
now we're talking
[Music]
um there's so much to do like I don't
know what to do next you know I mean
there's obviously many things to do but
I don't know where to set my priorities
I will however build
one more Tower here
I feel like that's it
more Villages ah foot I'm lacking food
okay it's time also to add some more to
the berries for now
which is better berries on the field so
does it not matter Villa prepare for
battle we come
shut up
the Englishmen they think they're so
fancy and smart
you got nothing on the French
can I'm just I'm just you know trying to
sound cool right now but I like both the
French people and the English people
[Laughter]
just the game get berries and then feels
okay
okay I mean we already have one so we
might as well utilize it okay
mahu
okay
um
huh
uh build uh why did I always click on
that what is that prepare
um and Stage Workshop I think where I'm
still missing that one too
um
don't have so much space
let's put it here oh wait if I can I
walk out if I build that here I mean
it's too late now and I would assume it
would not be buildable if it was in the
way
attack by free English out there
artisan
can you attack from here
hi smoothie
okay okay
should I send them out oh they brought
the trebuchet
um
that's a problem
the art put arches in the tower are you
an Archer you're in kind of near our
Bell Leicester that's
close enough yeah our burlesque is like
a
crossbow man right oh yeah
leave it can you go inside here
he's going in
huh
no how does he go in
except
protection and healing that's not quite
it
leave it I just do not go in
oh yeah they don't go in right
oh yeah but I don't like this oh
Garrison yeah
oh [\h__\h]
fix it
I need to take care of them
[Music]
um
Cannon people
[Music]
attack these [\h__\h]
I've opened the gates
oh no I'm coming over again
follow me
oh my God Cafe
is this even hit I need some
okay yeah Cafe
okay yeah
it's time for Revenge
looking so good it's not looking so good
again I'm having a problem this
difficulty spike is unreal
and somehow working I don't know if we
really need to oh never mind
[Music]
there's so many
oh yes
bonjour
so don't let them in just just don't let
them in oh
I mean
oh oh look at them here oh
should I really follow the ram but it's
somewhat under control
yes yes okay Rams down
this game
I need to focus so much
I want to be units
um
[Music]
all right
can we take them down can we take them
down
oh my God go back hahaha
okay well
at least at least we have some silence
now right
Another Castle in this small space
really okay
um
oh yeah
a bit of thumbs um oh we ran out of
berries okay I did not notice that
so suddenly
okay
[Music]
are we lacking anything else no just
food more explain
um but also shall we build a monastery
we built that in case
and
oh we should also build
or was it
blacksmith
spamming castles
yeah
almost regret not building it right here
but I found the tower would be enough
I guess it wasn't
okay you can help with this Castle
okay yeah
okay but it's getting really like
crowded in here there's no space
Monastery built
made some monks one or two
uh
we need Knights spam the knights
uh I need to start attacking soon
University
University next up we have some space
[Music]
it's really starting to become a state
space problem I don't want to fill up
all of this because then where do I move
here here could work
surprisingly
bestie so okay yeah leave it
all right all right oh yeah
all right all right all right
Monk
where is he
oh his mom's here let's spawn them here
and you can sit oh here and heal some
people
okay
[Music]
nice nice nice nights
okay yeah
um
I had I made I did the black Snips right
not enough food okay okay
problem okay
running out of food so fast maybe I
should also buy or make a market as well
monk stuck
okay okay stuck [\h__\h] oh yeah
okay
for real
let's just last forever I can't save him
what a waste
can I just
why cut the trees can he cut the trees
I'm gonna cut cut this one I guess maybe
that will help
I'm counting on you you need to save the
mug you'll be a hero we'll give you an
upgrade you won't be a peasant anymore
um okay I think in time thinking time
just on it
yeah nice nice nights
[Music]
okay okay where did I build that
Workshop they're okay but
meat and gold oh
I have barely anyone working at the Gold
okay oh look at that we can continue
do you wanna play some games
oh wait there's one here anyway
you can just chill there
thank you Mildred
yes yes yes I want to see them suffer
make them suffer
[Music]
so much love for me
back I'm attacking him
[Laughter]
stupid AI I'm so stupid too bad for you
way more gold and oh my God the food is
also just
everything is
so so close to the Limit
oh Trevor said destroy streams oh oh
well but no thanks to have fun
Rams Rams Rams
where's mine did I not build it yet oh
there it is
I only make one
need so many materials
did I never hold it okay
[Music]
space
this is there I hope
it's kind of not the closest but
um
so wasteful
okay yeah
I'm also after this I'll be running out
of stone as well
bye
Robin
now not another one this is all I'll do
not enough gold yeah
yeah why is this so difficult
because it's only close around yeah but
what if I what if I'm done mining here
and then I got no more
this would be in theory so easy I don't
oh there's so much to do
I'm Gonna Save another time
hungry
unlike Hungary with a
[Music]
just gotta ignore the attack no this is
because most of the time it seems like
I'm fine
no
can I spam Rams
Rams but no I don't want to spam Rams
should I be spamming Rams
um never strategy
though
okay whether we need burning armor
[Music]
little second TC for more villagers more
research together and push out to secure
more resources
second Town Center
where though
more um
foreign
Town Center
no it doesn't
he's hundred Stone
it's so big
I can build here I guess but then when I
build when I create
the any anyone in that castle they won't
be able to pass
here
here Works tool I guess
not worth it not in there
delete the number can put
this one or that one
how do you how do you delete things here
anyway because I guess this one we
really don't need
[Music]
how do you do it
no point okay
um but
if we need space then we need to get rid
of that eventually delete key oh what
go delete
whoa
oh
there it goes well I didn't know I can
do upgrades here too oh can I do that
oh I can do that here too about just
buying gold 50 what I didn't know that
on it accounts for all mining camps I
didn't know they had that oh wait
okay
[Music]
oh yeah
oh no my tower is going down oh it will
be dead okay
oh no no leave it I know oh yeah oh
they're range oh now now the castle
shoots
leave it
booty legs
oh that also help to put a Pike Mount
into the castle or does it always have
to be like
um long distance
keeps
flakka castle for real
oh scream is sure
only arranged oh really
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
oh that's good
okay
they destroyed a wall it's no money
if she goes there you might be attacked
though
please
I didn't infiltrated
oh no
hey Cafe okay yeah
what are you right
thank you
I'll count I'll count
you are doing Friendly Fire dude
oh man I'm I'm taking them down but what
cause
oh she's trying her best to fix it
working against it
oh my God
I can't do this anymore
[Music]
I'm so dumb I'm so done I'm so done
or something
yeah good job at tanking no no
there's only one stop and then don't
stop coming I don't want to play this
anymore I'm done for it to say I'm done
I'm done I'm done
now I'm not saving at this point we can
continue another time at the safe point
the one safe that I did before
uh
but now now they pissed me off like ah
they're so relentless they give me no
chance
maybe I should have gone to even
um north or south or or wherever that
wasn't you know want to get to take down
one of the other camps early on
this is why you rush the bottom
[Music]
um
maybe that would have helped me but who
knows I already know
I'm not gonna type that no
I'm gonna worry about losing buildings
and units I know it hurts yeah
this this felt like it was just going
downhill again
no difficulty this is already the lowest
it can be standard
well understand my pain in the AO
YouTube I
understand my pain
seems like a skill issue that's exactly
what it is yes
how do you turn this on what
what are you what are you
what did I say
at least the other two missions we
cleared the campaigns or free two or
three
two pretty good progress I would say
it's a cheat oh what's that cheat what
does that do
how do you turn what a weird cheat
what does that one do spawns a muscle
car
I mean
how do
you turn this on
what happened
[Music]
it was a joke what does it do it's like
super powerful oh my God
[Music]
[Laughter]
we should just play with cheat codes
I want to test it out
wait
a second how do I enter how do you
turn that you yeah
he's gonna I'm gonna do it properly at
some point but I wanna I wanna
how do you turn this on
wait I'll open the gate for you I don't
know how the other one made it through
but
[Music]
you think free muscle cars will be
enough maybe not
I don't even turn this on
[Laughter]
yay uh hell maybe five how do you turn
you turn this off
uh historically inaccurate what do you
mean
where are the other ones
are they are they always the color of
your team is that why they're blue
off the gate close it it's broken
okay when do we need to
we need to go
let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm moving the castle
oh yeah bye even with the muscle cars it
looks kind of tough
um
oh
how much damage did I do to the castle
oh not so much
hey down the tower wait
not my cars
yes yes
I don't even know what I should ideally
be going for but
I'm playing CTA again
I'm playing GTA
oh they're really strong against them
against the the NPCs the buildings are
still felt though
hey
[Music]
oh
no inclines are dying
oh it's more cars and the Cinderella C
and B can I copy paste
yes
oh I don't know what that just did
no
no it doesn't work
we just drive around a little bit at
least let's go
[Music]
very nice very nice
oh it's so cute it's so cute know what
would for you
how much wood can a woodchuck chuck if
the Cobra car is coming for you none
is that a paladin that was really strong
[Music]
what's going on this is like here oh do
they need some cars
how do you turn this on
pound
ing your turn this on
how do you turn this
how do you tell us on
how do you turn
how do you turn this on how do you turn
this on I should just copy paste and
turn this on
it
[Music]
how about this
but everyone has the same car
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that's really fixed my mood
[Laughter]
of course the movie welcome welcome all
right
ah beautiful can we get through okay
beautiful
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm tapped Out goodbye
[Laughter]
[Music]
just for living my childhood
with this code but I guess maybe every
game has cheat codes
dare you
[Music]
are there helicopters or so too
boys
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
it's beautiful
beautiful look at it
oh this [\h__\h] where is it ah you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] oh dare you no we
must rescue
it was down in an incident I'm home
thank you
[Applause]
come on everybody
come on
okay okay come on come on that's enough
of course it's a whole Army of cars
this is the most fun I've ever had with
this game
hey
let's take the Watchtower oh oh
no [\h__\h] way what
is a super dog
I don't see a dog what did that do I
shouldn't trust anything you guys say
about everything
here is the monkey boy stronger than
cars what is that
all right let's go
[Applause]
oh maybe I should have just walked for
one of these
so true
what cats are does it have to be caps
lock cats is it a cat
what what the [\h__\h] is that
oh shy cats shark cat
oh wait
okay does that work eh hi
cat sorry
did I write it wrong
we can zoom in
it's like a youthful how my cars doing
no my cars let's go cars let's go
[Applause]
okay take down Castle
oh no
they're so strong we need the cats or
cat sore
so
I want to see one ah oh there's a couple
okay
um let's try join our forces
[Music]
shark or a cat noise
what do I know
oh my car is faster
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] this Castle is strong
they're coming they're coming there are
several ones but it looks like it's only
one
I should probably Place some for
protection
[Music]
they're gonna take care of it right okay
all right all right where's my cats ah I
don't see them
I hear them though
where are they uh here in the in the
house
no no no
[Music]
something shotted so hard
because
I love a pocket but this is what's up
what
make me move big guy
who move
D it could be the Shrek movie does he
attack
whoa need to see this enemy enemy
what's up
[Music]
he's a king so he's not supposed to
attack him oh he's wearing a crowd but
let me see
I am going to attack you
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes Sheila how's it going here well I'm
looking fine I'm just having fun what
what a friend Alfred Alfred
oh friend I love you I love it
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so claim to rescue us
go go get him go get it it's so slow
he's so cute I love what he says he says
funny things Furious the monkey boys the
monkey
oh oh they're they're friends did you
wash before you touched me
yes
he doesn't like dirty hands he's a
monkey
oh no that was actually Alfred talking
never mind sorry Alfred for mistaking
you for a monkey please I love you
believe me trust me oh let's head down
this [\h__\h]
attack
this is the best way to play this game
I've realized why did it take you guys
so long to tell me this
yeah what is with the voice acting
God
can they voice acted this
how's the cars oh the cars are chilling
oh yeah I can place
my flag right there but I feel like it
wouldn't be fair obviously
[Music]
oh damn
oh they're coming with the Rams and
those ramps versus my animals who will
win who will win I think it's an obvious
win for me
ah
no I don't I just don't want to see the
the human
message and then the dialogue without
actually doing it
I
ate the Penguins
you said
hello
he's not it doesn't look very strong
though
foreign
oh the penguin I thought she was in the
chat
come on come on come on faster you gotta
go faster Alfred you gotta go faster
[Music]
oh yo look at the damage
the devil
s
why don't you come over here
I mean the fact that they put voice
acting on him tells me that they wanted
me to experience this I am going to
attack you
I am going to attack you yes do it do it
just do it Alfred yeah don't even let
him speak the [\h__\h] cars I love it
this makes me so happy wow we have to
check out the burgundians the [\h__\h]
burgundians I swear to God
I cannot just let this sit
why are you shouting so loud
this is how you play a-o-e2
yes this is a true history this is how
it all happened if you don't believe it
you must believe
oh not not the Villager not the village
no not the Villager no wait say
all right where are
they inside
oh no Alfred is dead Alfred might be
dead
[Music]
but these are not the Guardians either
oh well
[Laughter]
what do you want what do you want
what do you want for
I miss Alfred he's my king he's my
leader
what do you want what do you want
you're not worthy of my attention
what was Alfred's uh code again
something about alpacas right
okay
Welcome To The Future
simulator
I need Alfred back and maybe I need
several of him
Hello friends
our friend Alfred
her hands are cold
[Music]
we need reinforcements
are they coming oh they're coming oh
wait what the [\h__\h] how
you
okay made quick business of that
no you move
[Music]
here I'll keep one Alfred you touch me
what's up
the king must remain I don't think you
are making me move
only we could have given like a speed
buff
what are they doing well they're just
like having fun here going on the
Rampage maybe we should go straight to
the Burger in the end
they surely want to get to know their
new king
why don't you come over here and make me
move
here he comes as well
I hear the shots in the distance don't
worry about it guys it's gonna be fine I
don't forget they're probably not even
here
I don't move you move
maybe they're not here
oh I want to see something purple again
oh wait that's the end of the map
of a car yeah that's my Scout right
all right go down here
can you take one alpaca in the car
please whoa
damn it it's gonna take a while
enemy they're so hyped
all right that looks that looks about
right
I see purple
oh yeah
oh hello hello hello oh I think I think
of them
good God your hands are cold
they really are actually how did you
know short
[Laughter]
[Music]
no the burgundians are next
I think these are my favorites
the out front and the cars all the cars
protecting itself damn well
hell yeah
wait while we sent this over here as
well
we want to be Victorious without too
many casualties right
we've already lost a car can you convert
alpacas oh
[Music]
I will not let you
oh my God
that is a problem
that I did not consider
whoa whoa
where's the face
this is not it either
would you come over here
why don't you come over here maybe down
here
they are why don't you come over here
and make me move big guy
[Music]
where's where's this what the [\h__\h] at
least for next time I will know whatever
gundians are
hands are cold
what's up
yo I have to kill my own car
no it hurts so much I am to attack you
[Music]
there's a town center
oh yes baby what else do we want to
shoot
is a weird base that they have do they
not have a castle
what where are the alphacos oh there
okay okay
they're so fast and efficient
I don't even have to do anything
where is the castle no Castle
ah there's a trademarking
hahaha
[Music]
oh oh he's just trying to get some food
you know alpacas are supposed to be with
with a farm
oh man
oh man where alpacas go there death
comes
as we've learned but hey I took down
everything and didn't tell me that the
burgundians are dead
[Music]
uh
I just need to protect you know
all right all right all right
we're gonna put onions hiding for Real
Enemy
they're all over the map
you have to take every trace of them
apart I don't move you why don't you
come over here and make me move big guy
Marco to open the mouth
huh
there's not really much purple that I
can see
oh wait look I still have so many cars
why did they not tell me I defeated the
English though
there's no one left here
look at this I kind of wanna I kind of
want to place the flag but now I
shouldn't
pull them oh
foreign
what did that do
Michael
[Music]
don't know where everyone's going now
hold up
ah oh they're still building they still
have hope
though
[Music]
there's some stuff
they're basically defeated
basically done for
he doesn't know what's coming for him
go get him go get him
bye
bye-bye
I'm gonna help out my alpaca friends
help out my alpaca Brands oh Fred yeah I
love you so
our friend is the king I'm gonna help
out
we must abandon funds to the French
[Applause]
are there
let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
[Laughter]
come on my friends you guys are so slow
because of the alpaca all right I'm
gonna go
memory last English man must be taken
down
where are they where are they where are
they hiding I was just not already
enough
how are they still thinking that this is
a battle worth fighting
yeah yeah
I mean this maybe they're not oh wait
there's a couple here
oh
this is correct
it's really some [\h__\h] muscle muscle
car though isn't it that's so amazing to
me because of the whole is this a muscle
car thing
hahaha
amazing it's fascinating oh wait there's
a castle
good God your hands are cold why don't
you probably never gonna make it until
bye
[Music]
this is the muscle car
ah Arena black I don't know if I really
want to do that
it's not a deserved win is it
okay they didn't even ask me to really
they only wanted me to play place the
flag they never wanted me to take down
everything with it this is me doing
extra homework
why are my hands full I don't know I
don't have the painting on
don't complain
it's like in scraps
um what was her name
uh
uh why did I forget her name
[Music]
not Carla no alien yeah aliens see um
there's an episode where you know
she finds out she has very [\h__\h] cold
hands
look at that and as a doctor that's kind
of a problem you know
are they still producing
unbelievable
look at them look at them go
[Music]
hmm
is it
and
kind of ran out of resources right
hopefully
this down
goodbye Tapped Out
oh sure
what's the cause for the win
honestly it's their fault they should
have advanced to muscle car age and
alpaca age
and countered me with the same weapons
[Music]
the ship candy
better better leave it to the muscle
cars good girl your hands are cold
yes yes yes yes yes yes
destroyed him
watch before you touch me
soap at it huh
[Music]
but that's because we want look at that
look at them look at them
[Music]
who are they still sending them
unbelievable
I don't know if I want to end this
they've been building monster trucks in
Secrets no way
they literally can't lose really
nice movie do you hear the the cat shark
don't worry it's on our sides movie
it will protect us
good God your hands are close strong we
stand together I am going to attack you
foreign
[Music]
sounds more like a dolphin to be honest
yes yes okay last Castle they have the
last one standing
[Music]
that's right Alfred it's
who do you think you are making me move
well
foreign
I can't do it it has to be done properly
but just imagine we did it
[Music]
yeah
the Temptation is real in this until
being so real
[Music]
that was so nice thank you for telling
me
it definitely lifted my boots there
oh and by the way in 15 minutes time
um the tree the Advent calendar should
be updated
yeah
uh 15 minutes right until one
one a.m of my time midnight GMT zero did
you see the one from yesterday it was
fun uh surprise I did not know
um when I was doing a Minecraft collab
when I was singing in German or Italian
[Music]
what I did not know that the
uh she was gonna do that
what
oh
never mind the video might need to be
delayed because apparently there's
um
a problem with the video
[Laughter]
I think the person in charge went to
sleep
[Music]
oh no
oh
[Music]
no I mean
her
[Music]
no no no
this is gonna be the first video to be
late
I'm in theory
I have another video
but that one is still private and not
unlisted
and I don't know if it says some
specific day
but another member provided me with one
early
um
bye
ah
nah dosio
I didn't see the I didn't see either of
the videos but
um yeah well one of them apparently has
an audio issue
so even though it's there making it
public will just result in the video
with no audio
oh man
now the other one I can't check because
it's private and not unlisted
um
oof
eh
let me
listen
oh that's so unfortunate it looks so
good
the video looks good and there's bgm but
there's no voice of the member dub it
over we can make one now no
ah
it was you let me try one thing
because she's online but sometimes it
works to
call
when she's still online
maybe she'll notice Senpai notice me not
Senpai though
[Music]
um
no effect
uh
oh actually oh apparently it was already
noticed like
three hours ago and she was already gone
at that point
well this one will I guess just be late
until she wakes up
ah
I just weren't that in Japan girls like
Louise I still even to this day when I
think about them I in my head and in my
fingers when I write something I say
senpai
um yeah okay
yeah no it's not a senpai I was just
joking
uh well okay I don't know when it will
be but
um
within the next 10 hours hopefully wait
hello
yeah but it's are you in bed
no no it's unlisted but the video it
doesn't have your voice it just has the
bgm
[Laughter]
are you like in a really sleepy mode
right now
oh oh you're the best take your time
take your time though like oh it's okay
it's okay thank you for reacting take
your time though
as long as it's like not 10 hours late
or so it would be nice to have it
sometime soon though but don't stress
yourself okay
you're the best you're the best you're
the best it looks really great I just I
just can't hear anything
thank you so much
I'll be waiting thank you
I had her muted on purpose you don't
need to hear her
yeah it will be saved maybe a few
minutes late but it will it will come
soon as soon as yeah
that's weird um the videos there but the
audio is broken it's unfortunate
but it will be fixed okay thank God
uh big relief
okay now I will I want super chat some
of them [\h__\h] it's already 1am damn I was
so into the car reception
that I could not stop myself all right
let's go to my office
thank you guys for watching so far I'll
reply I owe you too again that's so
important the problem is just you know I
have to plan ahead when I play when I
play this and I don't know when I feel
like playing it you know so actually it
might be a while again until I play it
again
mm-hmm
yeah
[Music]
oh
oh yeah tomorrow by the way members only
and supposedly ringford
if if I feel okay I have a bad feeling
about it but members were definitely
doing members and I think oh we're doing
um I'm watching along I think because we
haven't done one in a while I hope
that's okay
and I will
I have to decide on the movie instead of
beforehand though yeah bye
but first let me read some super chats
oh there's no time
um
what do we want to see I don't know
I don't know hopefully something good
Terminator
I don't know I want to watch something
more fun
for me
oh
superchatos where did I stop last time
it's a good movie Christmas movie
oh that might be good because this will
be here
the last opportunity I think to do a
watch along
for Christmas
um
I mean they're
I think yeah there will be another
members only Before Christmas Joe
but then do you want to watch a
Christmas movie I don't know I don't
know I don't know Die Hard
oh
Die Hard
that's a Christmas movie hoping to spend
Christmas with us in estranged wife
is that the only element of Christmas in
there detective John McLean arrives in
La however he learns about the hostage
situation and
in an office building and his wife is
one of the hostages this is funny it's
from 1088.
let's wait
so old
it's the most Christmas movie
is it funny
is it comedy
action comedy or so
how much of a Zoomer are you what
no me Boomer and now you try to insult
me with Zoomer
hey is it it's on Disney plus huh
that's actually helpful it's commonly
okay
has some comedy you might laugh
I'll I'll think about it let's make some
pictures first
uh where was that there it is
um
Where do I
where did I stop last time Chad
where did I stop
the whole talk anniversary
I think yeah I read those right oh did I
did I
did I imagine that when it was pickled a
whole talk that one that I read not
Kiara Hollow talk
start of it um damn okay holy [\h__\h] I'm
really so far behind and this is a big
one there's so many all right
all right
I have to get through it
and
um
I didn't have the timer to finish the
subtitles
for
the later section of that stream online
foreign
Maybe
maybe maybe
let me turn on some bgm
[Music]
pickle is no other
corrected to pitch over them what does
that even mean if you guys watched
pekuna's stream today it was crazy
she was being hypnotized and then she
went bungee jumping and then she went
air diving crazy [\h__\h]
so funny so entertaining
damn she got to do so much stuff and
then she also uh released her music
video for one of her already existing
songs but that's what she I guess kind
of spoilered I think during holotalk
right didn't she say there will be a new
music video
because I asked her about it
pretty sure that happened that's not
just in my mind right
mm-hmm
oh
shh
[Music]
um
it was cute it had some animation in it
[Music]
oh too loud sorry I'm so like
she dropped
but she was so happy that she did it
afterwards
especially the bungee jumping like she
was up there waiting for like half an
hour
[Music]
like she was right there at the spot
where you jump in in all the equipment
you have to wear and whatever but you
just couldn't do it for half an hour and
then it's of course finally she did it
but damn getting through that like
decision
must be the most difficult part she said
so to
[Music]
and then once you're in the air
it's fun she said
this is now the second Home Live member
to have done bungee jumping
now that I should jump tweet makes sense
yeah
yes yes yes
oh yeah yeah she's also now gonna be
um a monster
in
um Dragon Quest
a game that she played many many many
many many many many times on her Channel
[Music]
time to make it free when it's my turn
I don't know I said before that I want
to do one of those things at some point
um
would I say that and then if I were to
actually do it I would probably have
way more issues don't pick what I said
for you silicon less Brave than her when
it comes to that I don't know if I could
really do it
[Music]
then a new upcoming one she's gonna be a
monster in a new upcoming one that comes
out like this month
how cool so happy for him hmm
it has her voice acting and all that too
[Music]
would you guys do it though like for
real or would you be a chicken you guys
are a chicken so you should be chickens
it would only make sense
[Music]
now it needs a lot of Courage hell no
yeah really I have two chickens I'd be a
chicken yay me too
foreign
[Music]
well yeah that's actually
I think in bungee jumping you can do
that too though right be strapped to
someone
so
maybe the first time I would want to be
strapped to a pro
and and then I would feel way less
worried about it definitely but alone
uh I don't know about doing it alone
bungee you can't do it
but skydiving you can definitely and
skydiving is so cool
so cool but one thing that I kind of
want to do even more than those two
things is um I think it's called
paragliding
because it's like slower and you can
really enjoy the scenery a beautiful
scenery
I think I would prefer that mm-hmm
change the position of the Rope
depending on how many jumps you have
[Music]
I'd be more likely to try that to do
that
yeah paraglide over the beautiful
mountains of Austria or somewhere else
but I think Austria would be a great
place for it
fun but takes a little skill but I think
and you can also deliver someone else
right together
you have a GoPro no but I guess I would
buy one for that purpose
you get to really admire the scenery
yeah that's what I want to do it yeah I
feel like for bungee jumping and and
skydiving everything happens so fast and
it's really intimidating and you can't
really maybe take in everything so
so properly
hot air balloon well I've already been
on the hot air balloon and rust
no but that would be fine too the hot
air balloon really does does not feel so
dangerous you just go on a something
like an airplane
and say hello to all the other friends
yes
[Music]
um
uh anyway I should read some super Jazz
jackets for the pinky
wow I want to say thanks for
interviewing my own security
such a sweet girl who works so hard all
the time I hope the chickens will learn
a lot about her today and don't forget
to talk about all the great songs she's
been making
we talked about like choreographers and
stuff didn't we so I think
I think I talked about the socks
indirectly somehow
thank you Jacob's monkey
yeah I think
this is also a good way of introducing
new
um
kfps to kiwawa and kfp so feel free to
recommend it to people
[Music]
thank you Ken
um
[Music]
outside the guests this sounds pretty
cute and hardworking three genuine
talented have a great taste in music and
TV and she's a budding Chef where did
she find her she's pretty special and I
can't wait to see where she goes next
um seems like you know a lot about her
genre maybe you should have been
interviewing her
thank you very much very much for the
sweet words A Satisfied on kitchen
Cruise
[Music]
thank you for making my anime NYC trip
one of the best days ever ah probably
being able to meet camp in person
getting to talk to you and fauna and so
much more it even ended up being the
same day as my two-year membership
Revival oh
yeah yesterday was perfect ah I'm glad
you enjoyed it actually you know for the
anime NYC
um panels they told us you know there's
so in so many slots for panels uh who
wants to do it so it was very voluntary
and then I just reserved one slot but
then I was like does anyone want to do
it with me and then I kind of Loki
invited fauna because she was like
saying in general that she wouldn't mind
being part of someone's panel or so and
I was like
with me
yeah it's appearing that you know hasn't
been seen so often at that point yet so
I think
oh it was very refreshing wait where the
hell not doesn't always have to be the
same groupings and pairings right
um
[Music]
purpose because she asked me like what
model I was gonna use I told her well
even the wall feel the preacher ones but
you only have a small one though I know
the chippy one so I I would adjust it to
you but then she decided to get a
preacher model really last minute
with a cute outfit
and that was first revealed there hmm
unfortunately we both had problems she
had problems with disconnecting and I
had problems with uh my batteries being
worn out because I was recording whole
talk all day before that
I didn't have enough time to charge
these [\h__\h] even when I was charging
like once I would like disconnect them
from the charging device
I don't know sometimes I don't charge
properly what the hell
[Music]
yes I do want to make them watch it they
need to watch it I'll eventually get
them to watch it with me or without me
it doesn't matter
I'm gonna check it looks like the sports
jacket really
I don't think that was on purpose
or maybe hmm
okay
I think she may have
[Music]
actually maybe maybe she took some
inspiration from the Sparks outfit
because when she was like okay which one
do you want to wear I said oh maybe the
Sparks One or another one
but then um I didn't have the Sparks one
ready for every uh VR chat because it
has to be rigged and so on I know it
exists but wasn't ready
and I think she
um
said that she did actually say that she
wants to get something that kind of
matches
a little bit at least in terms of style
so yeah maybe she said
but she designed it so I guess she
designed it with a Sparks outfit in mind
a little bit
um
I landed a spy seconds yeah maybe she
was feeling cold yeah
the pinkies
always been a fun talk show but it's
also a great way to learn about the
whole Talent thanks to your language
translation skills it's a lot of work
and coordination for you but it's a
valuable service thank you here's one
more pinky to say thanks for all your
hard work last week you were juggling a
lot but you kept us giving your usual
150 effort even with recordings anime
NYC Etc I appreciate you boss thank you
yeah there's a lot going on but I try to
you know keep it up and even when I was
kind of sick the past couple days I
still played Pokemon because I I felt
like I had to
um I wanted to though I wanted to I
wanted to stream I wanted to play
Pokemon
and yeah fruit was hard but
no it was still like okay to stream
with I would say and but by the way
speaking of hollow talk
and I said another date for another
whole talk because yesterday I was I
realized oh a whole talk might be
difficult to do while I'm in Japan it's
not a game stream but I like to have my
usual setup with it
feel more comfortable when doing it and
you know so I decided to quickly invite
someone to a hollow talk for all the
week after the next one so we have a
whole talk set for the 18th of December
and look forward to it
[Music]
yeah
no it's not cold
it's someone else we're moving on we're
moving on
um
foreign
[Music]
hopefully and if not then archive is
fine too thank you for always supporting
[Music]
honestly the the fourth gen I think any
of them would immediately say yes let's
do it so it could be any of them but
yeah it will be someone from 4th gen
yes
thank you for the pinky here's the two
years of whole talk wow
I can't believe I actually that I've
been doing it for two years have I
really been doing home talk for two
years with the hill
I mean of course there were some times
in between where I took like
a few breaks but yeah I'm really proud
that I've been continuing a little talk
for so long
foreign
[Music]
partially I didn't think I would be
doing it for so long because I thought
within two years and I would surely be
done with all the members or or maybe I
would be leaving at that point
I think something would probably make it
come to stop but here we are
have you been raided again
I can't rate it so often not recently
huh
hello
we're at the Super Chat reading now
though
so the exciting part is kind of over
what something that's okay with me does
not agree with this is the exciting part
actually
[Music]
ah you guys always react so Trump
um
rest of a chance thanks mate happy
anniversary selling this now because I
surely will miss the rest due to work
I'll talk was a great idea to get us to
know more about the Japan talents aside
from clips and memes I've learned a lot
to discover songs touching stories from
each episode and fun at the same time
thank you I agree I'm I'm glad I started
it and
went on such a serious route with it
yeah because I I wanted it to be a
proper interview program where you can
really get information from the members
[Music]
um I mean
some laughs in between are obviously
also great and necessary
yeah but I'm really proud with how whole
talk has evolved and and how far it's
gotten now it even has its own
merchandise I'm so happy with that oh um
by the way
merchandise sales are still open so if
you're curious I think I just retweeted
the link today possibly yeah I did I did
on Twitter
so check it out check it out check it
out
we got some cool merch
a whole talk and if you guys get it you
know you it will help me Finance the
whole 3D free defecation of the studio
and so on
I already bought it of course thank you
I already ordered thank you try to get
the mug thank you
I've already ordered thank you
can't wait to put people on stage review
yeah I hope it works if not you have to
brute force it just hot glue
use hot glue or I don't know make the
hole bigger or the understandings thingy
smaller
thank you
saves everything yeah
I'm gonna play with my acrylic stands
like dolls oh so cute
[Music]
um
not only is she incredibly smart
beautiful and funny she's also
incredibly hardworking to the point that
I sometimes am very concerned about her
health
[Music]
no no need to my house is okay I mean
besides that my body feels like I'm I
don't know 15 years old or 60 years old
but that's just what comes with being a
internal Phoenix I guess
[Music]
um
calendar unless you came here asking me
what's at the calendar there's a little
delay it was to be expected that there
will be some delays here and there so
just wait a little bit we're working on
it
it's normal it's just for 15 minutes
so break
but thank you for checking it out though
I'm glad that it's I'm such a hit and
everyone everyone's looking forward to
it all the time yeah
[Music]
I'm happy people are enjoying it
she already blew her cover
yeah but I don't wanna like blame her or
anything because like
looks like [\h__\h] it was a really good
video
um it's just probably her microphone was
muted when she was recording it on obs
no one but she did it she wasn't late
the video was [\h__\h]
[Music]
I need massage
backwards
[Music]
don't worry
for your support and thank you for the
sweet words
[Music]
foreign
all my muscles
yeah because I know that works for her
it wouldn't work for me
um but it's worked on Kelly several
times even when she was offline
[Music]
I tried calling her when we were looking
for her and then she picked up or like
she did yeah she knows it's through that
because apparently she has her Discord
phone thingy not muted I have everything
muted so people would never be able to
reach me like that never
oh that's my secret trick on summoning
Cali
[Music]
keep clicking on the delayed slot is it
like knocking on someone's door
insistently
probably yeah knocking on someone's door
even though they're not home yeah
[Music]
no no when I sleep I just don't answer
you can't get me there
but I checked when I'm awake I checked
my phone so often like
it's
hard for me to meow
notice something hi hi
I put my small scratch tree right next
to the table now
he's hanging out there but no actually
even though the scratching tree here the
Cozy one is here now right next to me
she still prefers to lie right in front
of my monitor
rest her head on my color XLR or or on
my uh cintiq tablet screen or on my
keyboard and she's been so
and one more is missing which one she's
been so so so so so so cuddling these
past days when I'm working on the PC
he comes here she curls herself up in
front of my monitor and then expects and
demands
why is moviepat gone
I didn't remove it
that's so weird
[Music]
wow that's so weird why are you here
even though I'm talking you don't like
it when I talk I thought
and I stream
and didn't remove it
other chunkish one has gone too I didn't
do it
do anything since when is it like this
how does that happen
so weird
we're not on Twitter I see uh from Mist
fist I see a tweet missing one smoothie
pet emote last scene in Kiana's
emojiwawa is moving in timeout for the
balcony jump and maybe she is
oh see I see it because I it's not even
I don't even see it because and someone
liked it I see it because it says dakoma
follows
this person that's how it gets
recommended to me
in case you guys sometimes wonder why I
see things I even get recommended things
just by
dakuma following them
uh should I
see if I can fix the email
can you guys remind me during the
members only
[Music]
because I don't have time now
thank you okay
I'm hungry too oh
[Music]
um
how was it seeing your Oshi being
interviewed by your ocean
of this fantastic show I've learned so
much watching these past two years as
the show has grown and I'm so excited
after two years I can finally learn all
about whoever says
yo yo
your back of your puns I'm happy
thank you for the support two years of
whole talk and you probably watched
every single episode yeah
you so much Chihuahua
really appreciate you guys
I know some of you guys don't care about
like other members even though you shoot
a little bit at least but you still
watch all the homo talk because you know
it's important to me hmm
[Music]
um
love so much just content keep it up
thank you
I'll do my best oh my chat just died
I'm glad you enjoy Hollow taco
appreciate it I'll do more next one 18th
December
thank you for the rest of the chat
possibly hold talk possibly the whole
talk I've looked forward to the most for
as amazing as all the other members have
and I'm so excited to hear about my
lesson about this YouTube no you've
shown how special you are as well as the
other members thank you Kiana you're
truly so wonderful
thank you
I I try to do my best
and I hope I can showcase the members
well and do them Justice thank you so
much Taipan
[Music]
wait how do you know Chad died oh
because I said
yeah
I guess I didn't have hyper channels I
have it on now I turned it on I turned
it off
foreign
another one I support quinoa and
whatever form she may take unless it's a
spider in that case the only support I
can provide is in supporting her into
her next life
[Music]
you gonna smack me
oh no you know if you smack me I turn
into 500 more extra spiders tiny ones
and then if you smack that one it will
turn into 50 more tiny spiders
every single one of those will turn into
50 more spiders
so you might want to keep me the way I
am compact in the form of one spider
rather than turning me into thousands of
spanners
I think that would be better for all of
us
[Music]
cheat codes cheat codes don't work no
fries
and passion fruit
[Music]
happy second anniversary for hello talk
and thank you so much for making this
series your show really helps us
non-japanese speakers get to know the
Japanese talents better in a way that's
close to not I'm looking forward to the
future episodes exactly see I mean
I didn't
um want to take it seriously but just
today randomly I saw a clip a bit a
comment someone tweeting at me and other
members tagging us
uh
uh claiming something that wasn't true
just by watching a clip and then I
replied and said that's not true you
know we watched a whole archive you see
that it was
um you know
just cut off at that point so there's
misconceptions for Eclipse not saying
the clips are bad but you can't just
assume that a clip is everything about
that streamer or about the situation
whatever
um
just another reason to watch Hollow talk
to find out more about each member right
I'm not angry at the person at all but
um it's just a good example
yeah it's a good example and I did not
like the the claim that I was ignoring
amen that just didn't sit well with me
so I wanted to explain it
did not sit well with me
candy stamps thank you soon I think
everybody knows I would not ignore amen
right we all know that
but you won't finish till the first shut
up
[Music]
shut up why why did you make me read
that I'm a pinky
I did promise that I'm finishing moving
this year and I went I went I went
I went
[Music]
oh did you know that um since we just
talked about Alma she was gone for like
but she missed her stream
it was like what four or five hours late
or so and then what what was the ending
of it it was just deleted
I noticed really late too because I was
doing my own thing
then I saw that teammates were suffering
oh that's funny
[Music]
um she must have realized and then
oh oopsie and Gremlin love
[Music]
yeah at least she's okay
nothing crazy happened so
that's our relief
in your heart guys in your heart
I'm gonna thank you Javier I promise
okay I promise I'll finish it
this this uh here
[Music]
finishing six magic Direction and a
minute okay
[Music]
no oh she's curling like a snail again
Slavic fellow thank you for the red
super chat congratulations on the second
anniversity of whole talk what an
amazing show and you always keep making
it even better we have learned so much
about uh so many wonderful people on
whole life all of that thanks to Yuki
Wawa only my lovely or she could make it
make a show like this happen
no I think there's other members who
have potential for a cool show like this
but but maybe you know whole talk I'm
I'm glad that it's my thing
and that
I did it first he
yeah it's my thing my baby
[Music]
I hope I can still improve it I don't
know how but I mean
you saw in the studio last time like
some things were so missing even though
they were already kind of modeled but I
guess they didn't make it in time to be
turned into the VR chat space
for stuff like the audience and the band
and so on
it exists already it was actually in the
trailer and the
um yeah did you see it
and the trailer in the beginning you saw
a pan through the audience and you also
saw the band so there's proof they exist
[Music]
the perfect person for a talk show for
sure
[Music]
and else could do it live translating is
hard as heck
I've gotten used to it I still got so
nervous every time though
you know one thing I always have before
idle readings and before I hold a talk
is nervous Idol meetings like uh even
even when I went before like in an hour
or 40 minutes before right before like
five minutes or so before the start I
always I always have a nervous side of
me
yeah
this is the only time when that happens
the whole talk I I get so nervous and I
need to go to an idol meeting
[Music]
I get so nervous every time every time
especially if there's been like a bigger
break in between
and recently always [\h__\h] up the opening
like with I I'm always not like sure if
I have it on like uh there's like
different modes of how to play the audio
or videos in obs
and I'm never sure on which setting I
have
it when it happens and then yeah
it's only yeah for the sponsor one
[Music]
let's see if it will happen again next
time place your bets now
thank you Slavic Fellowship
um
thank you for the red super chat
uh you're an absolute inspiration thank
y'all thank you I'm happy to hear that
I'm glad I can inspire you
I hope all that inspiration you can do
lots of awesome things believe in
yourself
[Music]
question what does one left mean to you
a last chance a last chance you took it
this was already after I said it huh
and succeeding like a true Phoenix he
rose From the Ashes they could have
brought they couldn't have brought on a
better person stay amazing
thank you yeah yeah that question yeah
the whole life members have always good
answers but I think sometimes they have
similar answers for it I think no one
ever said a last chance before the day
that was well how I see it I mean whole
life is more than just that to me
my point but I guess this would be the
most
meaningful
thing
you want some AOE too yes some some once
I lost some
[Music]
yeah I'm glad I got the last chance it's
it comes with a lot of pressure and a
lot of Adventures and a lot of up and
downs and a lot of
problems as well
um but it's definitely a chance worth
taking
thank you Maple Leaf
I run an induction Phoenix 2612
reduction for the pinky comments on the
whole talk second anniversary been
watching the show from the start and
always amazed at the consistent quality
and hard work you put into it thank you
yeah now with the new set
it really looks really fresh and I'm
motivated to use it a lot again I hope
that you know recently most of the
participants most of the guests haven't
really used the singing opportunity
um which is fine they don't have to but
this hasn't been used for a while so I
hope the next member will be open to
using it because somebody also has to
use them
the new stage with the band in the back
that would be nice
[Music]
if I only start in the consistent hours
I do stream at consistent hours
I kind of always stream at the same
times there's just not only one time
slot
mostly a stream between
GM GMT plus one time zone uh 3 P.M to
midnight
some streams start 3pm 4 P.M and some
stream starts like 7 P.M 8 P.M well
that's like you know you know when to
expect me
so that's I would say it's consistent I
I prefer that over always starting at
the same time especially because when I
do longer streams like RPGs and so on I
have to start early
but I see that in general I have more
viewers if I stream later in the day so
that's why I try to schedule shorter
streams later in the day
streams that I assume will be later
shorter
[Music]
I know because I watch all your streams
thank you
I think it's consistent
and honestly
I think the time slot that I have if I
wouldn't use this time slot and would
stream link and more like n a prime time
then Europeans would have nothing to
watch again I mean sometimes Cali for
example streams a little bit uh
until the start of prime time like today
she streamed like until 8 P.M here in
Europe
[Music]
but that doesn't happen so often
so
there's an American who wants from home
your timing is perfect for me oh I'm
glad I'm glad
you're the only stream I'm able to
follow almost all streams of really wow
that's good I'm glad
when one tequila sleep scheduled to
stream an n a prime time anyway
yeah I mean even even without
considering that I feel like if I stream
at any prime time there is already so
much overlap from other members
overlapping each other I feel like I
I would lose more viewers than I would
gain I think
and now we've been doing this for so
long that you guys I think the one the
views that I have now are okay with this
time slots so I don't know if they would
if you guys would even be able to watch
me at n a prime time
would you guys be able to watch me at n
a prime time whatever that is in the
middle of the night for me morning time
oh
[Music]
a lot of no's some yeses of course but a
lot of no's as well
[Music]
it's like 50 50.
but then also have to consider like
you know I I I'm being realistic here I
don't think many viewers would
prioritize my stream of other girls
streams
um so I don't think it would be a big
gain of yours
I don't think it's worth it
foreign
[Music]
from Japan time zone will be very
different and we'll see when I stream
then
it will definitely not be very
consistent during that time so please
bear with me
I always listen to your stream doesn't
work thank you
[Music]
you has the one that's me
I'll make them thank you your first
priority for me thank you
that's sweet you're my priority wow I
love love hearing that
thank you
no guys
you're literally the only one I want I
can watch consistently because of the
time where I stream in till then I shall
stay I mean really I don't want to
change this too much at this point maybe
I could consider doing an early early
stream once
a week or so but
I mean this this wouldn't even be
possible for a while because now I'll be
in Japan for one month anyway
so if anything
there's other things planned after that
too so
yeah if I try to do that then it won't
be for a long time and then then you can
really tell say oh she's not consistent
because then I add another
[Music]
random mass time slot in my schedule
it's already so
like
already has too many variations
of stream starting times
[Music]
blah blah blah blah where was I where
the freak was I
today oh four to nine dungeon of
production for the pinky what an
incredible two years it has been seeing
how to hit my son like this has got to
feel great it's always evident how much
time and effort goes into each episode a
real crown jewel in Ian Endeavors with a
lot with lots of love behind it thank
you thanks feel great to have it hit a
milestone not only one Milestone but two
milestones and yeah to be able to have
so many members come on it and so it's a
nice reason to have a collaboration and
members who come to join me there always
seem very excited to do it too
[Music]
so yeah I'm proud of it
I'm very proud of it
thank you and for watching it R4 thank
you
um
[Music]
thank you for the pinky merch is only
six to six dollars what a deal is it the
set
whoa is it I didn't make the uh
conversion
I didn't know hmm
that's not so bad for the whole set
I hope it comes somewhat soon and
doesn't uh get any delays but I heard
the countries who had troubles of EMS
and have been waiting for merchandise
for
one to two years
yes even two years
have been receiving things
now
finally so that's very exciting
I think now it would be safe to order
again in case you gave up on it because
of EMS
yeah
certain someone got the
myth and the first six month anniversary
t-shirt which was released like two
years ago
[Music]
Now
While most people got it
one and a half years ago or so
yeah
um at least it was received after all
because that is a very special t-shirt
that many other people who joined the
fandom later wish they had no because
it's like an antique
game
um thank you Ems for finally getting
your [\h__\h] together
[Music]
we fall about the re-release yeah I
think I mentioned it once to uh General
before
he really likes the belly rubs I can't
believe she's here she just loves me too
much
she's from the way her principles of not
visiting me during my streams like she
visits but then she leaves immediately
and now she's like sleeping how is she
sleeping
[Music]
foreign
top of her eyes is the white of her eyes
[Music]
it's so scary I can't look at her
it's so scary
though
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
but partially because like the way she
is curled up right now I think kind of
um pulls the skin of her head
uh like back
and then her eyes skin basically is
pulled back as well you know what I mean
so she can't close it properly
ah
yes it's freaking yeah she's upside down
oh now she fixes her poster she fixed it
it looks way cuter
with open eyes it's freaking
there's even humans who do it I
understand with cats because they don't
have to Blink but there's even humans
who can do it how
she's a lovable weirdo oh yes she is she
must have heard you yeah I think she's
like only half asleep
[Music]
isn't too isn't it 2 am for you now yeah
it is um
almost almost I'm still waiting for the
video and I have to research it to
anyone but I'm gonna end it at 2 am at
the latest
but this Super Chat
I will re I will finish these ones
Maxwell the first thank you
176 foundation for the pinky some
I started reading that in an English
German click ones
[Music]
um
thank you so much next episode 8 18th of
December
[Music]
foreign school thank you for the recipe
happy second whole talk anniversary
thank you for always trying your best of
these interviews you're an amazing
person and seeing your hard work every
day is really inspiring for inspiring
for us chickens Viva la quiada
thank you for supporting the program so
much and every guest that comes on to
advice fried screw
I'm glad you're enjoying it and I'm glad
you know I think P also has something to
be proud of that their Oshi is doing
this cool program yeah and being useful
to the community and so on
you can feel like my ocean is so cool
because she does this and that
thank you thank you
thank you soon chat
[Music]
swatter toilet paper tank is
thanks for the fun anniversary episode
no thank you
yeah special episode I wonder what I
should do for the third year but that's
still so long to go so I have so much
time to think about it
[Music]
but who knows maybe the third year
anniversary if I could do that not on VR
but in the proper 3D Studio
that would be another upgrade
not every time from then on but just for
the anniversary episode obviously
them
let's plan for that
yeah I think you know the quality of the
3D Studio now
of the whole talk for you studio is so
good I think it could totally 100 easily
be used as a backdrop for a proper
Studio worthy 3D stream in my opinion
yes
so good
yeah it's very high quality
well paragland you mean to whole talk
interview someone well paraglid
no no
please no no no no no no no no no no
I mean maybe we can do a little segment
maybe the speed segment could be
oh my paragliding was kind of chill
though isn't it but I still wouldn't
want to do a whole talk episode in it
but maybe speed uh quiz while
um uh skydiving
I don't know if I could really
[Music]
Focus while doing that
but it would be so funny
[Music]
what color are you panties
5000 meters in the sky
I don't [\h__\h] know
I can't even check right now
I know
thank you for the pinky congratulations
on two years anniversary of the best
talk show ever this is seriously such an
incredible episode thank you so much for
always working extremely hard Kiana I
love you so much you truly are the
absolute best Emma thank you thank you
thank you
even sweet words
I shouldn't I appreciate it
Tracy Duncan for the pinky
congratulations
this has been such a great idea you
really helped the international audience
get to know the talent's a lot better
add in that is always well made with
great questions it's a major part of our
life thank you not only for people who
don't know the talent much we always see
the big fans of the guests coming to
watch it as well and they seem to enjoy
it a lot to to see their Oshi like
recall
historic moments in their time here and
get nostalgic and all that and they also
appreciate just having their Oshi be
appreciated I think
and listened to and just yeah yeah
look back on
what they have done so far and how far
they've come and all that so yeah
yeah
so that's wonderful for everyone
um
[Music]
oh God I need to go to the Isle meeting
very soon
Shadow pencil thank you soon
we are done with those super chats and
it's like almost two uh 2 am so
I think
we'll leave it at that if I really this
was this was one of those streams that
had a lot of super chats but if I really
still have so many left
and I'm gonna consider doing a Super
Chat only
stream reading thingy next week
uh yeah
[Music]
except this movie
do you mean smoothie
[Music]
oh the people in that I don't mean
well it's only with myself though
sometimes you have to take a moment with
yourself to talk about things and to
really think about things not plan out
things and you know
by the way when I started the Holo Ian
Advent calendar I had no idea what to do
for the finale but I got a good idea and
I told the other girls and they say they
love the idea and I'm gonna get a little
bit of help from fauna possibly with it
she offered it and um
said she can do it
[Music]
yeah but
um I might
I might even do a member stream
to prepare for the video the final video
and then if you remember that you
already kind of know what's gonna happen
not the coming one but the members after
that so close to Christmas in probably
in the Christmas week
[Music]
no it's not ASMR
but she will help me write something
um
it's a really cute idea I hope it goes
well and it turns out well
um I am very very into the idea right
now
yeah it will be it will be a story but
um
in the movie acted out very special I
don't want to learn this spoil anymore
but uh one thing I'll say is that after
maybe 24 hours after it was on the
Advent calendar I will make it public on
my channel this one because it's
It's gotta be watched by everyone in the
future as well
[Music]
in the works
um haven't even started writing the
story so
it's gonna take a while but um I still
have time the 25th is still
a while to go
yeah
now I really need to go to the island
meeting and I think instead of cooking
tonight I think I'll make a my frozen
lasagna
yesterday I ate the rest of those
um meatballs those meatballs you know
they had goats goat cheese inside that's
what makes them different from other
meatballs they're called beef sticky
beef sticky and it's Greek
meatballs meatballs and uh
Sal by
[Music]
no Sabai was in the sauce though so by
what Salva in English
tell me
foreign
[Music]
special flavor
Sage Sage um
yeah Sage Sage Sage cut up some stage
for it
and a lot of parsley for the salad such
a um that sound you know I love parsley
but in the salad The Parsley was
a little bit overpowering and strong I
think I mean that was on purpose but
[Music]
but
um still took a while today I'll take it
easy and just make Frozen lasaga
I'm kind of just um stalling right now
because I uh
waiting for the video
maybe I should eat first and go to the
album meeting
I'm getting tired now too and oh yeah
wait so what movie do we watch
[Music]
I guess we can watch the heart
don't you have like another idea Joker
oh yeah Joker was another one we wanted
to watch
[Music]
I wanted to watch Joker too
Belle
bye Belle
is that also Christmas paint I guess um
is that the one with the Beauty and the
Beast
[Music]
a joker I know it's not a Christmas
movie
[Music]
new Bell from 2021 I didn't watch yet
but I'm surprised it's been
wait it's an anime movie what
okay wait oh you mean death bell what
wait
do you mean
oh that one but how would I watch it has
there been a DVD yet
is it available to buy online yet
[Music]
I wanted to watch that one yeah
YouTube has an Amazon Prime Amazon Prime
has it
it's on DVD now
um
but I think I might want to watch Joker
more
wait where can I watch Joker is that on
Disney too
[Music]
oh no that one's on Prime
should we watch Joker
you guys want to watch Joker with me
then I can finally understand the meme
the whole talk meme
[Music]
we live in a society meeting today I
guess
ah so many memes that I'll understand
why would you want to chill oh do I need
to watch Batman first would you
and I never watched Batman no I didn't
is that gonna be a problem
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no you don't think so
um
okay
let's watch Joker tomorrow 3 P.M uh GMT
plus one
um
[Music]
no I've never seen any Batman movies
but
I feel like watching Joker it's like
watching the Hobbies without watching
Lord of the Rings
[Music]
um
it's none
okay okay okay okay okay I mean I can
see it obviously there's a connection
obviously and it would be good to watch
Batman first but
at least I watched Iron Man
joking
[Music]
I can't watch Robert before Lord of the
Rings you shouldn't
if you haven't watched evil yet then you
need to start a lot of the Rings
[Music]
it's one of those things that are better
to watch in the order when they were
released rather than the order that they
are like
um in terms of time in the story
oh
my my stomach is like
[Music]
help oh yeah yeah uh is the same thing
you should watch that the way it was
released and not the way it was
um in the timeline aligned
[Music]
we're gonna watch Batman 2 at some point
if you are up for it someday someday
[Music]
I love being cute it's gonna be so happy
if I end the Stream
is waiting
kelly didn't like fall asleep again did
she
[Music]
it's possible it is it is very possible
she sounded very um motivated to do it
again though
[Music]
well we'll see my lasagna is going to
take like an hour anyway
so
I'm I'm here
okay I'm gonna go I guess thank you for
watching AOE to stream from me today and
helping me through it
we got through so two campaign thingies
and the last one is really difficult but
now that I know everyone's positions
maybe that will help for another
attempt at some point uh
[Music]
maybe I'll watch someone else play it
see how I can
where I can improve the most
and the cheat codes were so funny
I have been enlightened and you know I
love alpacas
yeah
all right all right guys thank you so
much
[Music]
oh and maybe at some point we can also
try the Skirmish mode
people say it's better for learning
stuff
[Music]
thank you guys good night
thank you for supporting me
and loving me
unconditionally I mean some of you might
have some conditions but
I feel
[Music]
foreign