I wonder if I love Bindarui.
Only the players were so cute. There were
so many things that were addictive, but they
didn't decide on something strange and distorted. That's the
detective-like
scramble for
music. I
don't care.  Because you're the best junior
[Music] I'm
able to walk around doing what I'm strictly dedicating
begging you
[Music]
Hurry up today, I'm
begging you If
you don't choose me today, I can't do anything.  I
feel like it's almost time to search for something important and important.I'm on a
dream journey, and you're not here in this world.You're not a
bird.If you don't think about me
, I feel like I'm dying.I shouldn't be lost in a place like this.
[Music]
Can you hear me? Is that the
microphone? Is it okay? I wonder if it's okay
Live 3rd generation
What's the matter? The
broken marine broke. This was regulated earlier
Tension with Mari Hoshino, captain of the Guarantee Pirates
[Music]
Play
Thank you very much, please. He
came to the captain's house.
By the way, is the volume okay? Is the volume okay
?
[Laughs] I'm having a
little English conversation. I was practicing English conversation while I was eating dinner. My
voice is muffled. I guess that's right.  Hey,
this microphone is in the wrong position.Okay, let's
move it closer to this side.Ah, hey, this
position is also over here.Move it a little bit.Is
this a little dangerous?This is okay.
That's okay. So what are we going to do today?
Well,
Reine, I've
seen people overseas wearing T-shirts with strange Japanese written on them. It's
cool,
for example.  Whether it's in Indonesian or English,
for those who can read it, it's clearly written there,
like something like ``I'm sorry''
or something like ``pee'' written there,
but it doesn't
have that written in English.  Did you notice?  I've
seen Japanese people wearing these shirts before,
so I thought there was something like that.So
what kind of sense do people overseas have when it comes to Japanese-style shirts?  I was
wondering if the captain had been selected, but when I
thought about it, I'd say follow me.There
are a lot of members from overseas, so I'd like
someone who doesn't understand Japanese kanji to choose it.Ok
with the reason.  I
thought it would help to understand people's sense of taste in foreign countries if they gave a reason for their choice.I thought it would help to understand the taste of people overseas.This
time, I made a variety of Japanese shirts like this one,
but it's fine if you don't mind.That
Indonesia group.  It seems like there are
not many children who can understand Japanese, but
there are many who can read kanji as well.Well
, I guess it does
n't matter whether they can read kanji or not, even if they speak Japanese.
I guess I'm completely used to kanji, and I can't read it.In fact,
even Reine, who speaks Japanese so fluently, knows kanji at a level that's a bit
dubious.That's why I
asked the various members of the group to choose this shirt for me.  By the
way, this is an example of a shirt on the shirt screen right now. Can you
read this
? Starting from the top left, do it in order. I
can't read the top left at all, hahaha.
Prince It's just
like the captain said earlier. What did you say? It says
pee just now. It
's pee on your shirt. It's
pee. Lie.
Yes, that's
bad. Then I know what's next to it. I don't know, but it seems suspicious. I do
n't know.  Number 2 sounds
a little suspicious. Ah, I understand the second kanji. It's
aity, which
means big breasts.
[Laughs]
Oh, wait, Rei first, let me choose which one.Then
, the safest one among these is
not this one, that one in the middle.Is it
one meal a day?I think this is it.One
day is good.1  Days are definitely a good
thing.You can
tell by the atmosphere.By
the way, you can tell what the person next to the big breasts is.The one in the
middle is that weirdo.The person
next to her is working overtime.The person next to her is, I
don't know.  It
's half price, this
one is half price, I understand, half
price is uh, no, the price has been cut in half, by all means,
this one on the bottom left is, uh, this one is easy,
no, it's a bit OK, she's
different, she's beautiful, she's beautiful,
right?
Nose,
nose, not that one, flower flower,
flower flower, yes, I see.Then, the one
next to it, sorry, sorry, I have bad eyesight, but what the heck is this?
What do you think it means? This is when you're
popular. What does it mean to be popular now? That's too suspicious. I
don't understand the meaning of popular. I understand. I
understand. Is
this a good T-shirt? That was a good T-
shirt.
And next to that is
this,
I don't know, this is muscle pain.I know
muscle pain.  I
asked them to choose their favorite shirt, and I
put it all together in a video, so watch it with me.
Let's do an audio commentary. Let's
go, okay, let's go. Hey,
you guys, too. Which shirt do you want? Well, I
'm Japanese, so it makes sense.  I don't have it, but it does exist. I'm sure
there
are Brachio.
I wonder if there are any overseas. I don't know if there are any Japanese at all. I explained it to them and explained it to them and said in English, "[Laughs] That's suspicious.
OK, let's take a look at them one by one.Let's go.The
order is random, so it's a bit of a mess,
with ID and en.
Please let me know. I'll try
playing one song at a low volume or high volume. I
'll go. The
little heart is cute too. I
don't understand what it means. It's
cute. How about the volume? It's okay.
OK. Please say it as many times as you like if you feel like it.
Yes, squirrel-chan
chooses a weirdo. I was completely drawn to this little heart.
That weirdo
doesn't look like a lover to me. I'm sure they look like foreigners. I
don't know what they mean, but they're
really cute.
Well, I guess I'm attracted to this heart. I wonder
what everyone thinks of this. By the way, what do you think of Squirrel-chan's personality? I
feel like she's going to choose this shirt. It's
pink. It's pink, so oh, I see. It's pink.  It's a
heart. It's a squirrel color. I
see. Let's move on to the next one. I like this design because it's very abstract. From an overseas perspective, I
don't know if I can understand Sakonosa calligraphy. Japanese
calligraphy Jesus. I wonder if this is cool.
After all, if you
look at it from overseas, this is a flower.I
can only understand this feeling.The
nose of the one that transforms into an exercise crown is probably a
flower that we know every year, but this flower...  I
have a better nose.Elegant
flowers are difficult.Unelegant
flowers are difficult.Flowers
blooming on the roadside.Flowers blooming on the roadside.This can
go in a vase.Beautiful
flowers.Would you like to
take a look at the next one?Yes.Anyway, I do
n't know how cool the glasses are.
Plus,
this is a metaphor for A-chan.Hakosu is
n't quite fluent in Japanese,
but I still don't understand overtime, but
overtime and this are cool.This
design
is cool.What do the kanji feel like?
It's lame. Working overtime in a cool way. I worked overtime. I've done that before. I've heard of overtime, Hacos. Looks good on me. This is overtime. Overtime email.
Jackie. Yes, the tempo is
a bit too fast. I was so
excited because I thought it would be over in an instant.
This is crazy. It's over in 30 minutes.  Let's take
it slow,
take it slow, take it slow, let's
make detailed comments one by one. It'll be over in 30 minutes. Let's
play it two or three times. Let's take a look.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Inanis was also amazing. I
had the impression that I could understand kanji, but
surprisingly, not everyone knows about flowers.
Well, it's probably this flower.
I don't know much about it, so I didn't understand it. That's
true, even at the level
of the captain.  Reine is the
best overseas member of Hololive in speaking Japanese. I'm so
happy that even in that lane, I don't understand her
. She speaks like that.
The power she speaks has nothing to do with the power she feels.  It's
completely different, I see.If you
don't study kanji at all even if you talk a lot.There
was Anya-san.Yes, that's right,
because I haven't had many conversations with Anya-san.I
completely forgot about Anya-
san.  That's right, Anya, who is
doing this, speaks a lot of Japanese.
JP speaks a lot, so I
thought she might already know some kanji.
That's right, this time,
only the members who don't really know how it feels
are applying, so JP, right? You
should have called me here. You
should have called me to the commentary table.
You already have two votes.
Seriously, I'm getting too much dark shock. It
's a little scary. This is bad.
Expand the story further and further. If you keep going like this, it's
bad. It'll be
over in 10 minutes. Also,
1233  That's
not it.
Hurry
up. Once it's over, let's talk with those two from then on.
Talking Talking English
Conversation Challenge
Please explain this video in English
[Music]
Japanese
TalkingOkGoogle Talking
Beautiful
Girls OKJapanese
TalkingBeautiful
GirlS
goodJapanese
yess
Okay, next.  Let's go.
Is that the kanji on the right?
That
heart is
cute.
What does it mean? It's so cute. It's so cute.  It
's cute. The rain is cute. I
really like the way Saame-chan speaks Japanese. Oh, she's
cute. The way she speaks slowly is really cute.
Probably the enid girls,
Indonesia. When she speaks Indonesian, when she speaks Japanese.  It's
totally different
[Music] It's
cute, is
n't it? Even the captain of the ship gets told that he's cute when he speaks English.Oh
yeah, that's right. I've
often been told that my Japanese is cute.
Strangers and weirdos are popular. I guess everyone is attracted to the heart in the middle. It's
too bad it's over.
What should I do? It's okay. Once it's over, we'll
get into the off-collaboration talking time between the two of them.
Or we'll watch it one more time,
twice.  1 rain video Rain video
Rub it, let's rub it, rub it, mesh
Reskit I'm
sure it's Hanzawa on the right.That
heart
is cute.What does it mean when it's pink and black?
This is a heart.A heart
is a heart after all.Even though we call it a heart, it's cute
when you call it a heart.Even
if you're a weirdo, that's true.I guess
if you have a heart, you're a lover.  I
think you're misunderstanding it. I can read it when I look at it, but when someone asks me to write it by hand, I can't write it. Ah, that's right. I can see the shape, but it's just a sudden idea that I get.  Let's
ask Anya-san if she can read. Let's talk to her.
If I have some time, I'll do that. I'll just
send you a chat.
Wait a minute, Anya-san.
How long can you go? Are you
busy right now? Let's
send her a
message. I'm starting to worry about what you're talking about.
Are you busy right now? What would you like to talk about? Please
send it to me. Please send it to me. Let's move on to the
next one. Leave that aside.
Isn't there a reason? I
think you're cute.
[Music]
Even if there's no reason for this, I'm going to
choose a beautiful character and say Beautiful
Flower Beautiful Beautiful
Girl
Right before the broadcast Maybe I'll just take a look So
Broadcast There
's only 10 minutes left I can't do
this I can't do this Well, it's okay
Captain I've
never talked to Mr. Zeta.  But
what kind of girl is she? I wonder if she's cute. I've
only met her once or twice, but she's
cute,
quiet and
docile. I want to hang out with her again.
I play with Reta-chan and I
like Kaira. I want to play with her all the time. That's great. People
say that Sakamoto is so beautiful. There's an
overseas version of her. She's so
cute. It's just a one-word comment, but you
can tell that she's quite cute.  I
think it's cute.Okay, let's move on.It
kind of sounds like Google Translate's reading voice.
[Music]
Wait a minute, the English pronunciation is
not too good.In a
good way.It's like it's
in a commercial.
[Music]
That's it.
[Music]  It
's cool, the style is definitely cool.I
want to write art.Crowney overtime.Suddenly a
black company.Wow,
Colony's English is so nice.It's
so
beautiful.Can I call you
?
Can I call you?I
was running out of time.I'll
send you photos of this and that, and I'll make a new one.
Just send me the shirt list that I sent this to.The
important thing is to do this so that the audio can be included.Thank
you just before the distribution.Okay, let's
do it.Okay, I
'm stuck.
Do you know that I'm with Reine? Excuse me,
but there's someone else here,
can you tell?
[Music]
[Laughter]
What, what, what? I'm some guy. Wait,
wait, wait, wait.  Wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
[Laughs]
There's no sound.Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I'm sorry,
even if I ask you to speak again
[laughs]
Wait a minute, wait a minute, maybe that's
what you mean, it's okay, it's okay, it's on that side. I was
playing with the sound board.
[Music]
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I've
become a robot, I do
n't know why, I don't know why, I
can hear it, I can hear it, it's
weird when I try to put it on the stream, wait a minute,
kill me, do this, do this.  I'm
doing this slowly, I
'm completely sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
why can't I do this? I'm so worked up, I'm sorry, I don't have time. I'm really sorry, I don't have time. I'm sorry, I'm really sorry. Why is that? Why
can't I do this? I'm always doing this  I
can do that, but what's wrong with it? The volume is too loud. You
can try turning it on, Anya.
[Laughs]
Wait, wait, make it
smaller. I think you should make it smaller.
Okay, nice, sorry, oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay.
I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, but I ca
n't go into my room now. It's a
little dangerous.
Wait a minute. There's a
big accident happening. Now, um, I'd
like to ask you something a little bit earlier.  I
sent it to chat, but this is a T-
shirt.Yes, this is a T-shirt.By
the way, are there any
kanji written on it?Can you read it?Some of it
is readable, some of it is
unreadable, and it's a little
strange.How do you read it in order starting from the top left?It's ridiculous.  Okay,
if you don't know
If you don't know, which shirt do you want to wear the most?
Which shirt do you want to wear the most?
It's not too much, but at the time it comes out, it's no longer a professional,
no, it's not a Japanese at all, but it
's not all good
in design.
Well then, yes,
hmm, invincible,
left, left, left, left, ah, yes, yes, then,
yes, I
would like to choose the bottom right corner.It's
too real.Do you have
muscle pain?Yes, do you
know the meaning of muscle pain?Yes, I
know.  I have it though
Hey, I'm sorry, I called you all of a sudden.
No.
Right before the
broadcast. Good luck with the broadcast. Please
collaborate.
By the way, this is the
first time
we've talked. We talked.
Even if it's sudden, we've been wanting to talk for a while.
Yay, if you
have a chance, please do so
. I'll invite you again. Please
do your best to stream. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Please do your best, both of you, and
thank you for the
stream.Sticky, no, it's
cute.Wait,
at first, Nya-san is really
not cute.It makes me
happy when you talk about how cute she is.I'll
try inviting her to do that collaboration again next time.It
was amazing.It's so absurd.  - Hey,
I'm sorry. I had a lot of accidents. I
'm sorry. It was a bit of a spur-of-the-moment thing.
Well, that's about it, let's move on to the
next one.
After all, something that looks like calligraphy is the best.Calligraphy
Calligraphy Something
Calligraphy style is popular.It was the first half-off,
but that's right.The
nose, overtime, and whatever else is popular.Weird
people are popular, starting at half price.It
was also my first time learning Indonesian.  Yes,
that's right, everyone was speaking in Japanese, but the
amazing Japanese characters are now speaking in English
. This font
is a font. Yeah, it's
cute. It looks like a bug.
I guess I felt a synergy there.
Half-auto has this block, and it has a
Fifty feel to it. It's
fashionable.
Fashionable, fashionable.
Navy, okay, let's go next.
Mouth:
The size of the kanji is the largest, so it
's my favorite. You don't like it at all.  Don't you get it? It's a brainwashing method
or a mask.
I think it's cool. Flowers are popular after all.
What's the matter? It's okay. It's okay.
[Laughs]
The design is
good from the original, I guess. Even if it looks weird.
If it's written beautifully, everyone will choose it
Ah, I see, but this is a nice touch. It
would have been better if it had been written in pee. That's right, everyone will choose it.
Kaela-san, the way you speak Japanese is so
cute.  It's my
favorite.I don't understand the meaning at all.It's the
way it draws the lines, it's the mask.I think it's cool.It's nice.It's
always cool, but the Japanese language is
cute.It's the first time I've heard this Japanese language.
If I change the Japanese language, everyone will try their best to speak Japanese,
which is really cute.I wonder
what would happen if I tried to make them choose.They're Japanese.They can
read kanji, so they're a little confused.Completely
yes, let's continue.That's a
really
deep reason.I'll
play it again.
[Applause]
Humans
[laughter]
Humans are
deceiving people, aren't they?
Even the English part is just like that. Thank you
very much for being so polite.
After all, if
there is a character that people overseas also know, this is the character for ``person'', so let's use
this one.There
are only two, so if you understand ``person'', you'll
already know 50% of this, which is
a bit
suspicious.  But, you know, the next one will be the last one,
right?
If things go like this, we'll have no choice but to move on from here.The
only thing we can do is ask the members who weren't here. Well, let's go for the last time.
Hello, see you next time.
This is the ruler.  It's a
ruler,
it's a stylish design.
No, you definitely know what this means, so you're
just pretending you don't know what it means. You
know this and choose it. But
then, the score
is that. Yes, the score is the result.  But I'm here now. It
's a plus 1 because it helped with my muscle pain.
Yes, Nioh is unexpectedly beautiful. Nice words.
However, even though it's an unexpected word, why is it that
no one can choose ``1 a day'' other than the usual years? I
think it's the safest choice even if it's emoteki. It certainly has some good things written about it. ``
Moteki period'' is also a good word, but
0 votes.  You know, weirdos and overtime
are popular because of the design after all.I
don't understand the meaning of the design being carried, but if the design is cool, then
everyone would be like that, right?
Okay, let's start here for a second. I'm
going to go talk to Miko-chan. We've
had a little too much time, so Mikochi, are you
here?
Should I talk to you in English?
[Laughter]
AreYouOkGoogle
[Music] I wonder
who else is out there?
Iwanttoyousomething
[Music]
Iwantto, you're wrong, you're wrong,
yeah, that's okay, I
don't know anyway, so it's okay I
understand
Calliopekaliopay What are you doing now? I'm
streaming Lie
Lie  Was that a
lie?Wait a minute.I'm
doing it.  It
's possible that you can't read pee or read pee. Try lying.
Unless you're a JP, you won't understand. It's so
difficult. Where do you go to learn something like that?
I see,
Kikira La Chiara, where
is it, Aori,
wait and get off, Crazier, I do
n't know how to spell it, but
now
I'm like, oh, oh
[Music]
Samurai
, here and there, I'm the
one who sends chats here and there,
but it's just, ah,
but ah, it's a little bit, in Indonesia, it's night
8.  I guess it's a good time. I guess
everyone is streaming, so Orin
isn't streaming. I'll definitely check it out a bit.  So we're
saying, "Okay, let's send it in.
[Music] Has it
started? Maybe it's
started, so maybe it couldn't start because we got in the way. Maybe it hasn't
started streaming. Is it
okay? It's okay. It's okay.
[Laughs] It's not
streaming.  I
wonder if it's off-stream and has a lot of femininity. I'm sorry for making this a subjugation project. We had to leave at last, so we had a lot of time left over. T-shirt The captain already knows what I mean.
Then, with a body that doesn't know the meaning, I'm going to choose something based on the design alone. It would be weird, but the captain might also be a weirdo. Hearts are nice after all. Hearts are cute. Iris isn't streaming. Pee is pee. What do you
think when pee is noisy?  Captain Cat, I
don't really like the big letters on my shirt,
right?
Overtime is okay, overtime is half overtime, and I feel
like I can read the entire off-duty part.  I'm
going to send it to Iris, so Iris
has turned into a person who keeps sending chats whenever she can read it, but
yes,
Iris definitely thinks she can read it.Absolutely, absolutely, I can
read everything.I've been busy now.I
have a question.So, is
everyone there or not?  During this time when I don't know anything, I'm going to
talk to Reine as usual. OK, let's talk. Today's
topic is English. We
had an English conversation earlier, so let's have an
English conversation.
As expected, it's quite difficult to talk in English.OkOkfood
is
fried French fries
LINE
That French
potato Limax potato is also okokok
[Music]
In the shirt In the meat plan To me
Well,
wear it, you should wear it - fashion
Fashionism I
wonder which one looks good on Reine
Left under left under lift
This stylish stylish
design
You are a stylish girl synergy
Explosive synergy
That's right, beautiful woman A. Does this look good on the left?
I like a certain design quite a lot because I
wear a jacket,
so I can't see the shirt with the text on the left.When I wear a jacket, it's
always a waste, it
's a
waste.
In English, it's
written
that it's a waste. Is that okay? It's a
waste. It's
written in a textbook.
That's why I'm probably that half.  I wonder if it's the
best type and it's the best type,
but it's the middle of such a type,
but it's not in the middle, but I can't speak English.
But
there are a lot of activities in this refrigerator, so the
captain
said to me, by the way, tell me the name of the store and the
activities.It's
so stylish, it's at such an altitude.
I know Lou
Oshiba for a while. Lou Ooshiba is speaking Japanese
while speaking English, which means I want to do some activities at this resort.  I
really
think it's a
language.There's a lot to do.Let
's have English conversation.English conversation.English conversation.English is
good because it's pretty easy to understand.
Because it's beautiful, it's
easy to listen to, like a happy English teacher,
so
even the captain can hear it and have a conversation.Then why do
n't you teach me Japanese?Well, I'll
teach you Japanese that I don't understand.I learned a lot.I can
feel it.  I learned
a lot. I see. Please remember this pee when you go home today.
[Music]
[Laughter] Just
a little bit.
By the way, this is the captain's shirt. I wonder if he
has this. Maybe he has this.  I do
n't have it, but I was wondering if I should release that
shirt.What's this
?It says W.What does it mean?
What do you think it means?
Matcha W is just that.Matcha
ww has a meaning, right?
Matcha Table.  Maybe it's a real word.
Eh, W is a real word.
Japanese, this is a word that Marin coined,
so I don't know what it means, so
yeah, I don't know. I don't know if I'll buy it or not. I don't know if it's fashionable. But in the middle is Reine's favorite center. Even if I wear a jacket, it'll still be fine. Ok
Ok. I wonder
if I'll buy it. I'll buy it.  The
footwork of buying a shirt is light.
If there's a design written on it, then yes. It's
not a marine design,
but Marine came up with the words, so I
see. OK, I bought a lot of shirts today too.
Well then, let's think of Marie's idea.
That's right, I
like shirts at Takarajima Idea Ray. I
bought them so much. Yes, I
bought them today. It was fun. I'm already tired and sleepy
. I'm just
sleepy. We've become very close friends, and later today,
Reine is coming to a stop.  It's like Kana. She
asked me if I wanted to take a bath with her.
But Rei won't stop me today. No, I can't. If I
press it, it's okay. I can go home. Even if I come
home late, no, I can take a bath. It's okay to take a bath.
Okay, okay, let's do it together.
TogetherTogether
togeth and weekend
speakingEnglish
Iwillinthespeak
English's
bath time It
means taking a bath together Yes, let's
take a bath together Yes, let's talk English all the time in the bath
No, I can't do it.  I'll
go home after the broadcast is over. I
'm currently broadcasting it, but
is it possible for me to have a guest join?
Ehomaru Sugiare Kiba is here.
Well, I'll send it to Kiwawa as well.
Hey, hey,
Kiara is out. Chiara, oh no.
Where did Kiwa go? This is not Takanashi.
Really, I'm talking about this.
Wait a minute.
So first, I'll send you a picture. I'll
make a call to say, "I'm going to eat this."  I
won't make a mistake like that, so it's okay. I
won't turn into a robot. I wonder if I can
read the top left
[Music]
What's the matter? What's this collaboration? Wait a minute
Ah, ah, ah, I understand.
That's right.We're doing a collaboration to see
what overseas members would choose if they were to choose a strange Japanese T-shirt.I see.By the
way, Iris
can read all of these kanji.Let's take a look.Please.
Yes, please take a look.
From the top right to the top right.
Hahaha, wait a minute. Even if you can't read it, you can imagine what it means. Half price, half price, half price. Painful.  I
know what it means because she's half-Japanese, so that's why the
upper white, white, and black are purposely cut in half.Yes, I wonder
what comes next.I could
tell by E-chan's glasses.Yes,
that kanji is a little strange, but I understand it.
And
then the lover is easy to understand.
That's the
lover.
[Laughs]
No, I
want it. You
told me what you wanted.
Because, don't put heart on it. Don't
put heart on it.
Don't get me wrong.
That's too interesting, and next to it are big breasts.That
valley is
bubbles
, isn't it?It's not
water, it's water.It has a little line,
so it's
not ice.What is it?I might
not be able to read this.  It feels
good to give out hints.
[Laughter]
[Laughter] I
don't know. I don't know. I
'll stop trying to guess.
Sorry, this is it. It
's urine. It's
weird. It's
better.  Tawa
Excuse me, but there's a
beautiful woman underneath, right?
[Laughs] There's a
flower growing there, and it looks like grass, but it's not
grass. Unfortunately, it's not grass. What, I don't know, it
's a flower. Isn't
this what the nose looks like?
Well, it's
not the flower blooming on the roadside, it's the flower from Beauty Four. I
see. There are two kanji characters for flower, ``yes, yes, yes'
'. There
are three. The flower on the human face.
There's a difference between that flower that's blooming on the roadside and this wonderful flower.Yes, I
understand.The one next to it is 1 day.Does that
mean we should do something good once a day?Good.
Okay, next up is the person
next to me who is invincible. I understand, but
is it a judgment on whether or not they can read?
Basically, it's a test to see what a child who can't read would choose, so I
can read things like Iris, so I understand what that means.  I
thought it was pointless,
but yes, there were some parts
that I couldn't read.It was
surprisingly difficult.Yes, Iris-wise,
which shirt would you wear?Without thinking about the meaning,
design, design, design, normal.  It's
true that it's worn as everyday wear, so
if you ignore the kanji, you're probably in a
popular period. Well,
this is quite similar to the overtime above, but what's overtime? It
has glasses, so if you
don't wear glasses on a regular basis, you're
still an enemy.  is a little more simple
But behind the scenes, I
can't help but think about the image I want to feel.I
choose it.I
hope it will come someday.Yes,
no, thank you for your wonderful mission.Thank
you very much.Finally, what
feels good is the station.Thank
you very much.  Thank you, it's so much fun.
Yes, I'd love to see you. Bye-bye.
No, I'm getting a little heated.
Hey, I'm excited to death. Chiara.
Can I play? Hey, I'm really
excited. I'm going to
go play with my lover.
[Music]  I
'm here. I'm sure I'm in Austria. I
just watched the whole conversation, so I
figured it out. But I was
surprised. Um, I couldn't quite read the half price, Ice-chan
. Ah, the
tiara is half price, of course. Of
course I'll stop.
Also.  Even the weirdos
were drawn to my heart.But
I guess it was because of that illustration that it
made me look like an idiot.It looked a bit sleazy,
but I could read that it was gorgeous.  I think
Chiara looks like a patch mix, which is hard to read unless you're using that computer font
or something
. I
couldn't see it for sure, but
couldn't you see it? By the way,
there's something I'd like to say first, but
Marin and...  Don't take a bath with me
[Music]
Ru means I wanted to take a bath with Marin
No, I'm
neither, but I
want her to explode.  You
want to take a bath with me? I
don't want to bathe with you at all, but
when I do, I feel lonely.
Let's go to my house and take a bath together. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no.
No, let's put the tiara in between and take a
bath together. No, no, I don't want to take a bath. I'm not allowed to take a bath anymore.
What do you mean? I
don't want the two of us to take a bath together.
But somehow, Chiara-chan is amazing.  He
even went on a trip with Reine. They seem to
be in love. I want them to take a
bath together. Reina and I
took a bath together. I don't understand
that Reine, who is so jealous, doesn't need Marin to burn her feelings.
No,
I'm talking about the time you went there.
There was a bathroom there, but
when we went out to eat something, when we
came back, something had been cleaned by the time we came back.
But when I came back to my room,
there was water in the bathtub, and there was a
rose in the shape of a heart, so I
thought they were a couple.That's right,
so I decided to go in there.By the
way.  I asked about Sound Proof, what about walls,
and what kind of proof I bought,
but I was probably thinking something else.
What is Sound Proof? That
sound doesn't leak out.  The
other people there
were all part of the culprit couple, so they
might think they were a couple. I was
wondering what kind of voice they were going to make.
That's right, so the two of us are in love
. I'm sorry for cuckolding you today.
Please
stop. I've entered their world. I'm
sorry.
But if you
just look at the design, it's
probably a weirdo who wants to wear it. After all, it's a heart.  That's why
all girls like hearts.In
the end, the conclusion makes me feel sore, and it
looks like Hasadoko's yakiniku restaurant, which looks like a uniform. [Laughs] There's meat in it.  When I looked at it, I realized that it seems like a
lot of these T-shirts look like shop staff,
but I think it's okay.It's half price, and it's really
interesting, so I'd give it as a gift to someone who doesn't know Japanese.  It's
kind of funny how people walk around looking like they're half-priced.
This has a very deep
meaning. If you ask me what it means, I'll say it means giving love to the world. I'll just say something random. I'll just
have to deceive you.
[Music]
Then put it in that reply.
Please, please.
[Music]
[Laughs] It
was Kibaba's brain being destroyed and disappearing. It was fun.
No, most likely, Chihuahua was number
one. His
Japanese ability was number one. It
was amazing.
Great, I
ended up talking to a lot of people in a hurry, but it
was interesting and fun.Well, it's a bit
late, but I have to go home after this,
so I think I'll end this here.Okay
.  Yes, thank you very much. I had to leave the
whole area a little short-circuited, so I'm
sorry for being unprepared.
Thank you very much, but today
, I went out all day from morning until night. It was
really fun, and you were so polite.  I
hope we can make some good memories.
Well then, let's make out as hard as we can to make Kibaba's brain explode.
OK, it's okay. This room is soundproof, so let's get
comfortable and have fun.
[Laughs] Well then,
let's not fail.  Well then, let's go.
[Music] A
box to
hide, a hidden treasure, fragrant
fried tofu.
[Music]
What should I say to you guys when I open this? I
was looking for it.
Don't follow me. Today I found something more attractive than treasure.
[Music]
Sugar is the
light of the internet. The
basics of the ultimate pirate
[Music] It's
me
[Music] It
's going to rain,
right?
Open it up. It's the
best in history.  Super
[Music]
I don't want to catch the captain, I want you.