foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I keep forgetting and I always like I
always forget to hold it yeah but hello
everyone
hello sorry for the delay we're deeply
we're deeply and humbly apologize for
the delay but the game made it a bit
more difficult to do the walkie-talkie
thingy than I thought so we're just
gonna have to Discord uh uh push talk
yeah so we'll just pretend we're using
the walkie-talkie because we are the
same it's the same button so it'll look
like we're using it in game except we're
actually on Discord which is better
anyways because the voice quality in
this game is kind of it's kind of
but I mean that's also normal because
it's a walkie-talkie of course you can't
be perfect quality yeah that's true
that's true also oh we haven't had a
amatory collab for a million years
yeah
yeah sorry to keep you guys waiting but
this time we're playing we're here to we
no we went we were here together
apparently there's free games with that
I thought there was only one so we're so
happy that we could play this one
together oh man
I don't
[Music]
know
I'm right over here you have to push the
button push the button yeah there we go
there we go smells in my Discord
settings I was changing something
oh God damn it all right uh well oh yeah
what I was saying I'm happy I'm happy we
can play this game together
me too yeah I think uh wait you're
pretty good at puzzles right
no no I wonder how you got that image I
I I I mean if it's like a normal puzzle
you know like a classic a puzzle in the
classic meaning of like putting one
piece and another piece together and
then another piece and another piece
that's that's the most puzzling I can do
oh okay well uh it's kind of like this
it's kept it's a little bit more guided
and the good thing is you'll have
experience with this game like with the
the prettiest one I guess so you'll be
my guidance
he's moving her mouth but I can't hear
you all done hello you can't why can't
you hear me no I can't hear you I know I
can
well maybe you talk it didn't didn't
talk to me on purpose but thank you
oh yeah chat chat I don't know if you
noticed did you know do you notice
something different in my voice like I I
don't know a baby
probably not unless I tell you I don't
know
[Music]
yeah hello I hear you
now I don't hear me I just see your
mouth moving
I am pressing V I'm I'm proud
[Music]
oh yeah no I'm gonna help me adjust my
microphone settings and I thought you
guys maybe will notice the difference I
personally didn't but I just have bad
ears I guess
uh
you're supposed to hear a difference
[Music]
I don't know
no
I don't know maybe who knows
I mean I don't hear you are you talking
to me
hello hello hello
[Music]
do you hear me continuously yes okay I
think it's just me I think it's just
gonna I don't know
but now now when I when now when I uh
okay are we ready to start the game oh I
think so let's go
okay let's go
uh we'll probably do this in two parts
guys because it seems to be like eight
hours long the game
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah well yeah you can
hear me right I can hear you yeah
let's go loading checkpoint
it's so annoying to push a button I'm so
used to not pushing a button
well yeah well too bad
oh my God
very scary intro why is it so scary good
morning
good morning
all right from now on I guess I'll just
talk to you when I really want to talk
to you and otherwise I'll just talk to
my channel right
okay no kidding hey okay okay
and we'll we'll see about that can you
hear me in game and in Discord now I can
only hear you uh in Discord over okay I
guess the voice in this game is just
broken yeah yeah the thing is I can't
hear you either it was like really weird
what's going on in this game and
XX for waving when do I ever want to
wave it said hello
yes yes yes hello
oh my God hi oh
[Music]
over hey your uh your jacket's Orange
that is uh perfect I can't even remember
free buttons this is gonna be difficult
so this one is talking
this one is pointing
uh you're pointing at me what was the
yeah yeah I know what was the winky One
how can I why I forget Winky
wait
there we go
okay okay okay okay I got it three
buttons not so difficult
if someone's asking us for help oh man
uh for help for what oh went outside I
think 47.45
[Music]
all right one second just give me one
second hold on I'll give you 10 seconds
as many as you want actually hmm as long
as I can spend more time with you over
[Music]
let's just let the dude outside die
unless you're staying here it's really
cozy
yeah this is nice why would we leave
I'll I'll cook some soup for you tomato
soup is that all right
uh uh that sounds nice that sounds good
you got it girl I got it
oh what does it say here who changed the
radio signal I can't find my favorite
Channel anymore
please do not leave any of the values
outside valuables I am done defrosting
them anytime I need to use one what's
values what does what does that mean
thank you please take can I squat please
take
what please take note of the sticky
notes dude I can't read that that's too
small do not forget to solve it
something the something when you are
done ah probably like turn off the
something when you're done the valves
valves wow that oh that's valves what
are valves again
what is my wife doing
you
over
uh
sure okay okay I guess we go outside
all right I'll follow you you know the
way right no but okay let's go I'm
probably here I know this is just this
talking can we talk back to them
oh
I know but I took this
you took what
this red thing that I'm holding
I only see you holding a walkie-talkie
um
we can take things
[Music]
oh I can squat yo you look dumb or craps
excuse me
oh so what are we supposed to do we're
stuck at the first puzzle already oh
that's a puzzle that's supposed to be
puzzle
I don't know
[Music]
I'm just pushing the buttons
okay uh we're gonna find a way out of
here okay maybe that door
yeah
no
I'm not open oh
which door uh never mind that was not
the right door where are you where are
you where are you there we are we can't
get out okay so let's go get an ax like
in Minecraft and just mind the woods
all right one sec
tell Emma to fix it what's Obama's dream
I'm a I don't know someone told me to
tell you to fix your stream what's
what's going on over there
GPU is being garbage right now wait a
second
[Music]
no I didn't but I got it I got the
wheelie thing that I probably gotta put
on a door I have one too oh
boy there's ah there's two toys that
don't have the wheelie thingy oh
[Music]
dead I am now
pointing it
oh yeah I tried doing that but uh I
couldn't put it in
I was able to put it in the other door
that opened up and maybe in there
there's another door and then there you
can put it
oh you opened oh wow you open this one
yeah oh there's a big car
that's a cute one
oh there's some levers but they said I
should have messed with them who said
that
game the ghost oh
don't listen to them why would you
listen to the game
oh this door opens
shouldn't be feeling like a snowmobile
s oh it's so pretty
yeah it's snowing wow it's romantic
the jumps feel like I'm on mars or
something hey how did you put that red
thing in because I have a wheel but I
don't know how to use it it gave me a
prompt it only gave it to me at that
specific door though so I think it has
to go into a specific door yours as well
oh laggy what's laggy okay
FPS dying the game what I said what me
or the game
[Music]
lag I'm extreme wonky
me
I'm laggy
it's fine okay it's fine okay
[Music]
you know with my Super Mario skills
Anything is Possible
oh
[Music]
what is this
nothing changes
it was broken in the roof oh whoa It's
all Frozen yeah don't do it
[Music]
anymore
I'm right here
[Laughter]
[Music]
it didn't hurt
it didn't hurt enough unfortunately well
I don't think you could take any damage
in this game oh yeah all the landings
are so soft like it feels like I'm
landing on
hey we need a green wheel if you see one
anywhere okay I'm just exploring this
beautiful scenery can I go in the eyes
no why not I want to go ice skating
10 FPS jump
is that really that bad
[Music]
caught on candy that's it
is
only me or is the game the 10 FPS game
should I make it even smaller I can
probably
[Music]
one of the wheels I put in uh it
connects on the roof
nice
I turned vsync off
does that do anything
wait oh you put it up there noise that
the first yeah
oh wait no that was there already right
was that wheel there before when you put
it there I put it there better no no
it's okay wow what we think
okay so we gotta find more Wheels
uh yeah we need a green one
okay we'll find it uh
[Music]
the game doesn't give me very much hints
unfortunately
[Music]
um there's a bottle I can't pick data
yeah the game doesn't really give you
that many hints in general you just kind
of have to like figure it out with what
they give you okay
um uh
there's nothing
we see we think she don't well well well
what was that with uh automata when
I played what half of the game with was
a missing offer on but then I don't turn
it the other way around and then it was
fixed and I was like what the [\h__\h] I
thought this game could be played
exactly what's the thing above
anyway I just ended my sentence in the
middle of nowhere
was that was that vsync uh on originally
this I'm a baby on on top of the roof
there where like some buttons you could
push as well maybe that's like somehow
connected to the thing below here where
you can also push buttons maybe one of
us has to be at the top and one of us
has to be uh in this room over there
that's a that's a really good uh that's
a really good point yeah let's uh we can
try that okay here I'll go up to the
roof okie dokie maybe maybe it's too
early but let's let's try it out
okay
but like it the only thing it does all
right I'm up here
okay I'm gonna push the buttons and you
just tell me if anything changes or does
anything
[Music]
oh yeah I see it changing so like the
length of the wave is changing whoa
[Music]
I hear someone again
by now or before before now it's not
anymore
yeah we basically got rid of that dude's
voice
[Music]
cancel back our coordinates yeah so that
he told us before 47 45.
okay did you also push something at the
top or yeah I changed it all right so
now we hear him again
47.45 whatever that means coordinates
can I press F3 in this game
uh-huh like a Minecraft yes
uh maybe we should look around a little
bit more because we still need uh one
we need one wheel for the gate and then
a green wheel for the uh snowmobile
garage door I
got the wheels
[Music]
can I open uh drawers no
um
yeah maybe they're outside
again
yeah I don't know I don't know what
we're supposed to do this is where the
other game let's start oh I found a
wheel okay I found a wheel oh it's a
good one yeah I found it next to the uh
next to the fireplace wow noise
[Music]
green whale
a ghost okay the snowmobile looks like
it's ready to go maybe
boys
ah so says we shouldn't be fooling
around
[Music]
okay I guess we're not ready yet
let's try to find one more wheel I just
look around it could be hidden
[Music]
locked from the other side can I jump oh
wait can I go to the other side
over with the roof and then open it from
was I not able to actually
also how do I Dash was there a dash
button
I'll I'll try to get on the roof again
[Music]
no
where is this place I wanna try it like
going on a vacation in a place like this
I don't know it seems so nice I like
snow you know
[Music]
start now
I opened I opened the door
oh which door uh the gate outside
oh uh because you could only open it
from the other side so you had to jump I
found
the rip oh I see so I think I have to
warm it up are you supposed to be over
there
oh okay never mind did I did that lag
around
no no you're fine okay
[Music]
I'm gonna warm up the wheel at the
fireplace I know that sounds weird but
it has ice all over it oh smart good
thinking I don't know if it works though
[Music]
wait we fight if I go down
warm it up it's not melting
stop melting
is that warming up doesn't doesn't work
I'm gonna put something down
I don't know how to track I'm clicking
on the ground
oh wait I can also walkie-talkie
uh
do you see the ice on the Wheel
now all I see is a walkie-talkie that's
interesting I'm holding a wheel that is
not just my imagination I
uh-huh the the tundra is making go crazy
no no not yet not you called for Phoenix
oh maybe that one oh I
did on the fight on the on the what's it
called on the cooking stuff stove
and the wheel is melting
up yes a wheel that will be our soup
tonight
there we go okay a red wheel goes
uh on this gate outside there's like one
section over here
uh that we can't get to might be this
one yeah but this one is blue is the
tiny thingy blue on the inside uh yeah
yeah it looks oh look maybe maybe it
looks like it yes it looks like it yes
yes
how to open this one
I'm on my way
yeah okay
[Music]
oh what is that
shouldn't be fooling around
they don't let us touch you out I think
we gotta figure out the frequency thingy
first okay
how do I figure it out though
I don't know what to do
oh
there's a wheel up there too
I think I can probably take that one
I'll be right there I found something
that I have to investigate
that looks like something
also yeah yeah so yeah guys uh I don't
know okay did you notice anything
with my voice probably not I didn't
really notice either I tried to compare
the
um
there were some settings oh
I have acquired another wheel
where are you finding all these wheels
on top of the roof
oh
this one's red so maybe that goes into
the door inside
really oh yeah good thinking
um
yeah there were some frequencies that I
changed
[Music]
I honestly never felt like all right
nice work whoa what the hell is this
stuff
no I know it felt like
oh oh coordinates oh we can't mess
around with any of this stuff yet oh
Well we have coordinates
47 45 what was it 14 yeah 45 47.
oh 45 37 now I'm not sure anymore we
should listen again
we're used to do it again
uh okay I think I messed with the thingy
so I'll go back up to the roof and fix
it okay
[Music]
ah there it is
real freeze tongue
I'm almost done oh
I hear him I hear him
okay not anymore not anymore
all right so
uh I don't know if maybe we're supposed
to match the frequencies or something
yeah let's try to do that hold on I hear
him I hear him
not yeah I hear him out there out there
he only says out there
try to try to speed up the frequency or
like uh
which one is the speeding up go back one
okay
leave it there okay can you hear
anything no
okay hold on one sec I
he's like repeating oh uh okay try to
make the frequency like longer I guess
oh nice
wait a second wait it's like super long
now
I hear out there out there out there and
you make it like one bigger or only less
now
oh
yeah I don't know what we're supposed to
be doing maybe maybe down down
I heard him before he said I hear him
oh yeah leave it like that leave it like
that I'll coordinate 47 45 okay 47 45.
wait that's good
better four
four eleven some oh my God that's so
much information write that down
47 45 a nine by Echo
I don't know if we need all that
all right
so you can see the different frequency
stuff and then try matching it I don't
know okay
47.
if you imagine then do you hear like
more is there more stuff that he tells
us
I'm on my way
[Music]
but how do I how do I match it oh when
was I supposed to remember what's down
there
I am indeed yes
all right uh we're gonna try we could
try to match it to one of them I tried
to do it to the red one I think or the
pink one
[Music]
uh
what do you mean
oh so so I control the green one now
check check the different frequencies up
there you should see different colors oh
okay I only see green
oh yeah yeah go to the next one oh okay
I see red uh-huh
okay I don't know I was gonna try to
match them and pink
okay okay then uh let's yeah okay
let's let's match them
okay
um okay so I see I see I see and this
one is really really like big so let's
make it smaller oh
no the other way around okay we have the
master green one to the blue one okay
okay
[Music]
and then why the wider wide wide Kiana
that's right that's right more and more
uh I think that's it that's it wait I
hear music
I don't I don't hear music but I I will
listen to it at the moment like we can
dance chicken dance yeah
I'm coming down
spikes I guess that was the wrong
Channel huh
she's vibing
[Music]
I hear it it is indeed the chicken dance
there's my chicken dance dance
I'm going back up okay okay
now I understand what she was trying to
tell me though because I didn't know
what was going up out there then I
didn't get it and she was saying
now we can do it now we have an
understanding
let's go
who made this game by the way like uh
from from what country
out of Interest
it was not not the Germans was it
okay we be matching the red one now so
small small small small small small
very small small small small
small small small small small
stop maybe there at one bigger
uh and then uh not so wide exactly yeah
a bit more a bit more a bit more
[Music]
do you not hear anything yet
ah now maybe no no
there it is there it is okay okay it's
music again okay
but that's like a Dutch Studio jazz or
something or swing that's what it is
that's so something that can make my
chickens fall asleep better
okay all right then let's do another one
okay
okay let's do blue one the blue one is
very very uh narrow and very very tall
I think a bit maybe one more narrow and
one more taller or two more a bit more
taller
[Music]
uh yeah maybe one more and then a bit
more narrow
um no more no more tall one one less
tall
yeah and then a bit more narrow I think
[Music]
oh my God
no but it's repeating so I think it's
okay
yeah I think you can mess with that
stuff now yeah probably you're gonna go
out to save them
we are gonna mess with the I can mess
with the thingies oh what does that do
I know but we probably have to refuel
the snowmobile so maybe somebody has to
be on the other side but let's do the
coordinates thing first because I feel
like we're more able to do that
okay
all right I'm in the coordinates room
all right maybe you want to repeat some
of the coordinates ah okay okay wait
um
okay we have to both do this at the same
time so okay we might have to write it
down
um
[Music]
bring somebody home
wait wait wait one more time
[Applause]
okay
there's a lot of coordinates
yeah I think there's four right well one
two three four five six
actually
okay well we'll play someone and
actually there's three pairs right
there's two there's Charlie and beta we
have twice and then there's Delta and
Echo once each
okay well I guess the numbers what do
they mean
uh they're the numbers on here see oh
all right so I can move it to the side
and you can move it up so
okay oh we're doing Charlie seven five
three first
or wait how does that
I don't know this challenge yeah so
Charlie is the third one from the top
what oh yeah yeah I see it
okay and then what's the second one with
Charlie said beta145
a second one is better 754
let's keep on going down okay I see it
you
[Music]
wait how do you keep us I don't I don't
think we're uh I don't know if we're
supposed to keep it there but I think
that one is um
Scott's Hut do you see that all right
let's let's see what the next one is
Delta 195.
a gathering they're going to use the
machine we could just do with our eyes
Delta 195 and the second coordinate and
that's that's from the bottom the third
one
[Music]
no no no one nine five yeah Delta 195
which is from the bottom the third one
and then we have Echo 169
that is from the left the fifth one
okay I guess that's the radio tower yeah
yeah that's right send signals and we
have beta 481
foreign
from the top with Charlie 447
[Music]
that says here
Ah that's the kiss from a rose
I think what is it
yeah that's the kiss from the rose okay
so we have the the tower the kids from
the rose and what was the first one
oh uh Scott's Hut okay okay all right
send signals God's Hut it's from a rose
I don't know
should we go there first but the closest
is a tower
I think we need to refuel first but now
at least we have wait let me listen to
this again why didn't they give us free
coordinates if if there are one place
or are they in the middle of that
does this mean that they are in the
middle of that because they gave us free
coordinates free places
and then that would mean that they are
at the ancient structure but I don't I
don't know
whoa I'll Trust you on this one okay
uh what does that mean triangle uh am I
going to the far away fuel thingy the
levers and then you stand the one inside
which I actually correct
okay so uh on the fuel levers I don't
know if it's fuel I'm just gonna call it
that there's uh
each thing has like a each lever has a
number so there's five seven eight four
seven eight uh so I guess just tell me
the levels for it maybe I have minus
eight minus four minus four
on on the three levels but on the on the
thingy
on the big tank that's oh well now it's
filled up oh actually
I think we have to get into that green
line huh after the green line okay then
Lowell
or do I have to do so I probably also
have to do something
[Music]
that I'm changing the eight
how's it now ah Wayne
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah
we we're still a little bit a little bit
above green so I don't know what were
the numbers again uh minus eight minus
four minus four
but I turned down minus four and then it
went down uh a little bit from nine to
eight
but we need to go to Six
let's swap now that now that we have
seen these let's swap okay
where is she apparently math is involved
so let's uh oh no
wait where were you originally I forgot
where that place was and the gates yeah
over here ah there okay
yeah
okay so maybe
um
okay it's math so oh by the way
huh I saw you dashing how did you dash
oh let's shift
oh thank you
okay ah okay so I think if the maximum
number is nine then maybe put like uh
I think the next one oh okay so we have
to get the max yeah yeah okay
okay
I totally get it that's all I get it
okay uh add
um
I just just add try adding uh I don't
know I'm not good at math but
essentially the maximum number on this
one is nine and so I can only minus four
twice and minus eight once educated with
Detective Watson isn't the maximum
number actually 10 it's just not written
there because they can't put in so many
numbers yeah yeah you're right you're
right actually okay and now it would be
at one six
uh I didn't minus anything but yeah if I
minus four then it'll be at six oh no
okay wait because I think I put more
than ten in so I think you can only see
10 but technically all the other numbers
that you put in also affect it because
on minus four it goes to eight
oh
yeah because the numbers I put in right
now are eight and four I understand I
understand I understand
it's it's at eight now we say
uh yeah because I minus four yeah I took
that four eight eight eight and she can
she can also minus she can minus four
once and minus something more than that
so eight
eight plus
uh wait we gotta go to ten dollars wait
so which number do we want it to be
again not ten right we want it to be at
five right it's at six six okay we want
it to be at six and it's now at eight
yeah I've got a minus four it's at eight
foreign
um just add add um add a random number
okay
um
okay now it's at eight
okay hold on
my mind is wait a minute
uh
wait
what number do we have now
did you put all of them in thank you not
all of them wait uh
what number is it now
four
oh uh
seven
four seven uh
what
um
uh
and you want to swap again yeah
all right don't minus any numbers yet
okay just put it just set it to no no
minus
which one is
okay
okay I got it
oh plus four all right do two minus four
done
what are we at
10.
you did both minus four yeah
oh wait do I have to put it down around
wait no oh wait one second one second
okay try it again
okay
we are now at uh four
one second
[Music]
okay do minus eight and minus four
actually I don't think that's gonna work
but
okay
uh
um
okay wait one second just do uh minus
two fourths minus two-fourths
[Music]
you did it you did it when I was doing
uh
yeah okay yeah
[Music]
we need to pinpoint oh we do have to
pinpoint it on the map if even though we
already know orange one oh yeah
the one uh in the middle the triangle we
have to make a triangle out of three
destinations and pinpoint it in the
middle which would be the ancient
subject yeah we gotta triangulate the
location the ancient structure okay do
you know the coordinates for that
because we probably have to put it in
the truck uh yes I do uh c624 and a five
two one
[Music]
Alpha five to one
okay I'm not gonna remember that no
problem
oh wait wait I think we have to put it
in yeah okay okay I'll come help
it always goes back
yeah I think we have to be fast
wait what is it again
are you doing are you controlling
something over there
I'm putting it up oh there we go oh
oh we have to do it at the same time
yeah okay
that was nope that oh nothing yeah
all right I'll let you move and then
I'll go up
oops it just resets it
oh that was too high well also almost
there
thank you
stop
stop okay that's it that's it how do we
get rid of the first one I don't know
maybe the second one overlaps the first
one okay okay
maybe we'll stop at the second one I
don't know
[Music]
what do you mean that's rude shut up
sorry what sorry I was uh I was roasting
my chat
oh uh it won't let us get in yet I don't
know maybe we have to cancel it somehow
oh my God
or or it wants us to make wait let's see
I even wants us to make free circles
yeah yeah
probably three sets after we make a
third circle and then they're like ah
that was a rung so it says let's make a
circle oh there we go hey we actually
got the right okay let's try again first
maybe yeah yeah
okay go
got it okay let's get the house okay
all right now the far one yeah
where is it
well not ready yet
random seal noises be like
you're right
[Music]
when we put our brains together Kiara we
got one big brain yeah
[Music]
by the way guys
foreign
[Music]
okay
I'm scared to tap out of the game so
we have arrived
feel
it looks frozen over
that's why we're not with our passion
rabbit rabbit
okay
I don't think it's working
good that we tried though we always
gotta try yeah yeah
oh here's I guess this is the oh
oh this looks
why is this music oh this guy is stupid
a little bit it's like an abandoned mine
I don't like the atmosphere
just pretend it's Minecraft okay
I'm sure our uh comrades are here safe
and sound and we're gonna save them
they're dead um
bless you thank you over I had to do
that
uh so it looks like we got an elevator
it looks like we got another elevator
and another elevator and another
elevator and then oh God uh two more
elevators that looks like a lot of fun
that was irony
hey I'm on the other it's working
I'm stuck
I'm on the second platform
stuff for you can you can you bring that
thing down because I think I'm bugged
but yeah all right I'll come down and
squish you
okay I I when I crouched I was able to
go down
should I go up to the other elevator
uh I don't think you can get in on that
side but I'll see if I can try to help
you get in on that side maybe there's
like a control or something
not real I went down I was able to go in
okay well I can't go this way because
there's a real black oh wait never mind
do you think I'll die if I jump from
here
I don't think so I feel like
everything's very soft I go I'll go up
one more
I know it doesn't go up anymore
but I can go down oh
okay I just this already looks very
Larry complicated guys
going down
oh dear oh something opened up
oh dear
okay so the the uh elevators all have
different symbols on them it looks like
oh
is that a toilet
I think it's a toilet
toilet um
[Music]
okay that's good to know thank you
you're welcome
some like stuck up here
oh
can I help you
over
um maybe oh my elevator moved by itself
what did you press oh I pressed down oh
I guess I'm in the right elevator here
ah because a lot of the times I think
with some uh you want to go out yeah I'm
taking you up
uh no it doesn't go any oh yeah oh okay
you went down with that at first I went
down and then I went up
now it went down
oh is it the other way around so if I go
down now does yours go up
yeah it's going up ah is it it's like
weighted so when one elevator moves the
other one moves then okay I'm in can you
go up or do you mean me you want me to
go up or
whatever makes me go up
can't go no more me lady okay mine too
yeah it has buttons on it but I can't
okay uh
all right let's look at the symbols
there a symbol on the on that one
uh you mean on the ground
yeah like on that elevator yeah it's
like a dynamite
yeah okay
um
there's a one with rails and gold and
there's also
um a diamond one
okay yeah uh I in order to find the
other ones I have to move this elevator
though because I'm stuck
okay yeah that's fine do it okay
[Music]
okay I'm in the one with the with the
minecart okay
oh shoot I'll I'll move it uh yeah so it
should be going down there yeah yeah
okay
okay no I'm gonna get in okay all right
I'm in now go back up back there
okay maybe I can move one for you now I
have one that's a pickaxe
I can't get in it never mind
wait
I came
oh that's the pickaxe I can't get into
that one either at the moment so I think
we have to do something else first there
was one more elevator uh
that I oh
no that was Dynamite
yeah probably okay I'll go back then
oh
what's an elevator that uh
what's a different elevator you can't
get into
um
[Music]
can wait
uh where did that come from original
let's go for the top
oh
I am
I am going from the very top to the very
bottom to elevator with diamond
okay all right I can get that one
oh oh sorry
is that on your level now
yeah but this one it just I mean this
one just lets us get to the uh
other one hold on let let's look for a
different one okay I guess that one
doesn't really do it I'm looking for one
that uh has
it's like a dinosaur eating a diamond if
you see anything like that
and get in there right now oh
hello
uh I think I gotta go and got it
[Music]
no I have to use this one first right
because there's nothing down here
what you doing
uh I feel like I got myself
let's go so I'm checking this around the
surroundings but I think
um
by moving the elevators
uh
yeah I think we have to undo something
okay what elevator can't you get into
right now
um wait
which one was that
Chad are you thinking with us
which one is that
the dynamite one can you bring that one
down so it goes one up for me
nice
um now I guess
I'm going up oh I can't go up anymore oh
yeah can you can you make it go up
uh no I guess so let's go down now
um
[Music]
oh no yeah got it
oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait
okay
yeah I'm back at uh I I can ride the
minecart one
and I can go on the toilet and I cannot
ride the pickaxe one mining a diamond
I can ride that one
pickaxe riding at that wait what oh the
pickaxe uh elevator Do You Are you able
to get into that one
hold on one second
drinking too much cannot fall it's at
the top so go back into the dynamite one
and then take me to the top and then
I'll uh okay
then you go back down yeah
no Dynamite one
okay are you at the top now all right
uh I'm at the minecart one okay
but here I can't do anything let me know
when you're do you have a minecart one
yes yes yes wait uh
ah yeah can we go up with that
[Music]
oh yeah
oh
now I can get in oh
never mind that was one too high I think
oh okay uh are you in the in the
elevator
yeah I can go up or down if you need me
to
ah but
uh
I think you have to move that elevator
down not the one we're currently in but
uh
the the
yeah the pick oh no I think yeah we have
to move it
it wait I can pass it never mind
I am at the very top now
and I see wait wait I see 12 videos but
I can't I can only go on top of them
oh
which what are the symbols on them what
is the the the pickaxe one or the other
one is like a
um
a a drag a dragon in the head oh yeah
yeah okay
all right I don't know if I can get on
either of those either but I'll check
on top of it
I think
yep no problem
this is so quite difficult
those I wonder if uh
the game ends when we reach the middle
all right uh the only way I can get back
down is through the dynamite elevator
uh so I guess we need to find a way
where
uh you're in the minecart one and then
uh
you can use the diamond one oh wait
yeah yeah yeah
now I am however stuck at the top so you
you would have to bring me the minecart
one back up that's right
yes I am in
um all right I'm out me too
um
so on this level that we're currently on
the by the the pickaxe elevator is two
two yeah I think two levels of both no
one level above me one level I think
the only one I can access uh might be
the dinosaur one but I don't even think
I can get to that one either
uh
brain activate
uh maybe maybe we have to go one more
step back
[Music]
okay
uh Chad said we have did I tell you
which I said sure sure
they said we gotta get on top of the
elevator at some point oh I was on top
of them
on top of the uh Dynamite one
oh okay wait on top of any elevator
not any but like sometimes we don't need
that oh
my good top of the dynamite one
oh yeah so okay I'm moving it down so
your ears goes up does that help you
uh
uh not really
wait bring it back to you and put it
back down all the way
okay
and I go up
up again
okay
okay I'm in like a different area now
I'm On Top oh okay I'm crossing over
wait
oh see the dinosaur elevator but it's
too low okay can you
man I'm right by the pickaxe one but you
can't move that one huh
if I move my elevator back up the
pickaxe one should be
accessible
no
no no no current no no I can I can
access the minecart one again
the Mayan car uh oh I see the Minecraft
one okay oh then you bring up back the
dynamite one I'll try to get on top of
the minecart okay
it should bring it up
okay yeah
okay go back then
up
it's so complicated all right uh now the
minecart one can you go back to it
uh yes yes yes
I am in the minecart uh go oh so mine
goes down I guess
all right now go back uh go back to the
weekend
again
okay I'm at the top once again
uh it's still the pickaxe one I can't I
don't know I gotta find a way to access
it so I guess I gotta find a way to get
maybe if I go on top of the diamond one
okay we're gonna go back to the
beginning but I killed the
I can go on top of the minecart right
now okay wow maybe that does something
can you go up or down where I'm on on
top of it so
I I can't control it but now it's going
up okay oh yeah but see the platforms
above you like it is there uh anything
that you could go up to uh yeah maybe
one more
yeah
[Music]
I'm here again oh oh okay but maybe
maybe that's that was maybe that was
necessary for some reason
nah I think uh there's probably like one
elevator that's in the midsection either
on your side or my side where you can
access the uh mine the the
pickaxe one yeah yeah let's go from the
bottom and then we'll try to see if
there's any that we can go on the top
of the elevators
okay okay uh uh can you bring me back
the minecart one so I can jump on it or
in it
other way around
and do a flip
are you inside well I'm on top of it
oh sorry can you bring it down yep yep
and then uh back up again thank you
okay so we're going down
well then I'm gonna get off
okay I'm off whatever I'm on I'm off too
oh okay are you at the uh Dynamite
yeah I can go in
okay can you uh bring it because right
now I only see the top so I gotta get in
all right I'm going I'm going yeah
thank you
are we ever gonna finish this
okay oh
we're back at the uh okay so on your
first one at the diamond are you there
diamond
yeah back at the bottom
oh
maybe a diamond is the same for both of
us
and
oh yeah diamond is uh no wait my
Minecart oh oh how about you get on top
of the dynamite is there anything when
you go on top of dynamite oh good idea
can you bring me down uh actually yeah
the other way around one more
I am on top
okay
oh yeah I was here before
foreign
oh never mind never mind okay I'm out
don't freeze to death if you need some
heat just cuddle the Phoenix
okay oh hey hi
all right enjoy Adventure you too
sweet your room it isn't being so that
if you uh see the other side you will
see it completely In a Different Light
indeed indeed let's check it out
let's check it out okay
foreign
[Music]
taking a lot of time for this nothing
here
loving here uh-huh pickaxe
that is like doesn't go up any higher
than uh
[Music]
oh but that does that connect with
that one
no idea
I have absolutely no idea Watson
oh uh hold on I'm at the like where we
started I'm getting a new vantage point
of the whole area
it's getting here
no more actually it's only found this
uh
yeah
what do we have here oh
oh
I see that's the one that [\h__\h] oh that's
that's that one oh
is that one below or up
what oh it's up at the very top up there
[Music]
guys help
I want to impress
with my brain
who wouldn't impress that man
[Music]
shh
oh this shower my brain cells
[Music]
do it
do it all right are you there Kiara I am
everywhere
Almighty I am Eternal I am Tyler I'm
Thomas
uh can we do the dynamite one of my
Dynamite
uh yes I'm in
okay uh can you bring it uh go down I
guess
foreign
now go back
all right one second
we're chicken just warm and fluffy yeah
that's what I love so much about you
guys
my wall flopping chickens
what do I know is it lining
I don't see a lag
what is she doing
[Music]
uh okay okay okay wait uh go up can you
go down I guess on that okay
again caught me moving something going
down
yes yes I am now stuck but probably you
are not uh you can go back you can go
back okay
but even if I'm here I have no idea
where to go this is I feel like this
area is smaller than the area that I was
in
feel smaller
more than two streams you think so I
maybe listen to like one one of those
free areas per stream
uh can you bring the diamond one back
uh which one is that uh yeah what uh
that was the first one
back as in
ah oh all right uh can you bring the uh
Minecart one back
[Music]
is that that went what what did you just
wait sorry did you say diamond or
Dynamite I'm getting confused it sounds
so similar oh Minecart sorry I said okay
Minecart you want it to go up or down on
your side
uh up on my side okay
[Music]
um the opposite
foreign
[Music]
come on
okay hold on I'm holding on holding on
um
[Music]
yes I am and dynamite
I would like to have the diamond one uh
go one
let's go
actually I have no idea
[Music]
I'm so stuck
um
[Music]
well so the diamond one is currently not
accessible but I guess the diamond one
really doesn't matter because that's
just uh yeah that's just the one is like
the basic so if I go up
um maybe I should try to get on top no I
did that before didn't I and then I went
into nowhere
oh God but but we can try I guess uh
let's see
what I see when I go can you do the
dynamite one and get it one down okay I
gotta get into it first oh okay okay
are you below it or above it
above it
love it
um so
okay can you bring it up on your side
yeah
oh sorry one more uh back back
yeah okay and now let's let's go
anywhere oh uh was I here before yes
okay no that's just okay uh uh down
and one more is that possible oh
it is
what was I here before
what's that one
I can now get
um I can now get onto the pickaxe one
you can get onto the pickaxe and I can
go over to the Dragon one which is
currently not here but not a little yes
I can get on to the pickaxe one what
I can
I can get onto it and I can get in I
mean I can get on to it if you if you
were to move it but I can also get into
it
you can't get into it yeah because I can
walk by foot I can walk uh if I'm uh if
I go up then I could yeah no I can't I
can't get all the way down into it the
flowers I think
yeah I must have not seen that I guess
oh sorry
[Music]
so what do I want to go into it or onto
it I guess we want to go into it yeah oh
no but wait if I don't want oh
I but I can't control it on my side
because I can't really do it okay then
I'll then I'll go I'll go into it
and and then I'll move it up on my side
first to see what happens
oh yeah yeah well then I'm about to get
on oh okay I'm on it
if you want to get on I can't I can't go
higher now but ah oh yeah you get you
make it go down nice and I go up and now
we go up again nice and now
now now I can get on top of the Dragon
no I can go into the Dragon one into the
dragon
dinosaur dinosaur I guess
I don't know where that is on this side
I'm moving around let's see what happens
no wait I think on your side I was able
to go on top of it before so if I go up
then you should be able to go into it
but yeah oh yeah
um can you go into it now
all done
uh shoot I need to get to that side I
need to I need the uh pickaxe one back
again okay so I can cross over
you need it you need it back
yeah yeah I would die it's too low right
now wait I think
but wait
um
no no no probably more I think you want
it you want it to go oh no wait ah never
mind no no no no no problem no problem
no
she said it's too low so
I go down it goes up
into it
uh I'm crossed over now I
guess yes we both could yes yeah I am in
I'm inside the dinosaur
okay we're together then should we go
when you grow up mine goes down so
that's okay
I reached some
oh no that's uh that's nevermind hey
hold on okay I'm out wait and I'm out
I'm at the door okay okay
foreign
okay
I got it done okay
on go three two one go
oh get away sorry one more time okay
okay
all right three two one go
sh
hello hi
oh that was quite difficult yeah I think
it's just I think like in the house and
here as well we both made progress after
seeing each other's point of views yeah
yeah because it's a little difficult
sometimes to like describe it
okay so there's a tent for you and me
oh yeah well I think this is was the
previous people who got stranded
we could warm up by the fire
out our clothes we don't need a fire we
have a phoenix right here
that's why I haven't frozen to death yet
all right
the next one what is it is this a riddle
again there's a turnstile there's a
lover there's a gate oh come on another
riddle everything's a riddle here
[Music]
oh hey there's another Trend style here
yeah let's use it
doesn't work oh
[Music]
yeah I don't know okay
oh I go on the other side
oh hey I'm up on some stairs there's a
gate here a Red Gate okay so we have
different color Gates there's one yellow
one blue
uh one red I pulled the lever for the
red level did that do anything oh yeah
it opened up one
I can close it again
okay I think it's oh do one more time
all right I'm on the other side so I'm
at a Turn Style here
okay
[Music]
wait can you hit the red lever again be
up one moment
gotta run back run run run run run run
run
okay there's no blue levers huh oh no no
try try exploring around with the
turnstiles and see if there's a
see if you can find a blue one okay I
see a yellow lover on my side but I
can't get to it yet I'm in my chat done
are you guys alive or just sleeping oh
there we go you guys are just sleeping
huh wake up
wake up
can't do this without you guys I'm
nervous around it
just kidding that's not true actually
not really nervous around here
odd
maybe something's here no that's where
it came from
order
[Music]
oh
um
is there nothing are you stuck like is
there nothing on your side at all uh
yeah there's nothing here please uh
activate the red lover and then um
yeah it went
there it is
you guys are focused on the game
[Music]
hold on I'm checking one more time wait
a second okay
I found something I found a tunnel oh a
tunnel Tunnel of Love
the one in Minecraft from the Summer
Festival
the fingers now
I I'll move the the red one again so I
can explore as well
okay
[Music]
where was Dad
at this one because this mode
but this one ah it does look good
oh she was probably oh I found a blue
leather
oh I see you hey
oh hi there okay you found the blue one
hold on just stay there okay I pulled it
do it again okay
[Music]
I need a shoot
is there any way for you to get back to
the red one yeah yeah one one more time
before you go oh
okay
but then I can't all right now do the
right one and I don't need the blue one
again the red one and the blue one
okay okay okay
there was a red one there's a red one
all right you know this reminds me a
little bit of
um there's this I think it's called the
blue one when you get back to it
uh for that I think I have to move the
red one again that's fine that's fine
okay
uh that reminds me of I think there's
just like a Swarovski world
in a
in Australia you can look it up and that
one has like ice wait I'm not thinking
about two different things
but there's a lot of tourists that go
there but the it looks beautiful because
it's like an icy World beautiful icy
well have you guys ever heard of it but
the problem is you're not allowed to
take any pictures or any videos there so
that's super lame for tourists and I've
I've heard a lot from tourists saying
like they went there but uh yeah they
were disappointed because you were not
allowed to take any photos yeah okay
ah where are you
I'm right here why are you here again
wait did this even do anything
I think we just went in a circle
oh yeah uh wait
all right let's swap sides you go in
through the other one
[Music]
I'm gonna explore
what is ah
you're you're at the red level now
uh no I can't get there I can I think I
can get to the blue one first oh
[Music]
should I should I pull up the blue one
again
oh hi we're at the same place
oh hi so maybe you you you you should
stay here maybe yeah I'll stay here and
do what I was doing I think you'll see
something that I didn't
ah
[Music]
um oh yeah okay uh balloon level please
okay
[Music]
blue lever again
okay oh
[Music]
um
go to the left like that's where I was
going
yeah but but wait wait uh uh uh wait a
second
I want to see something uh blue lever
again
okay
that was a red one yeah yeah okay okay
okay so basically when I turn the red
one
and and you turn the blue one then over
there the only one that's left is a
yellow one
yeah yeah so there's a yellow switch
there's a I saw a yellow switch on the
left side but I couldn't find a way to
get to it but maybe I just did it wrong
I'll put the red one back I guess
uh probably have to mess with it
put the red one back up again
this is gonna take a while again
yeah yeah
can I be expected
that red one she probably went down here
before didn't she
[Music]
can you do
the blue one
but you can't from there on you cannot
get to the red one in any way
I think I can well maybe try that
although I wonder if you went here
before
oh yeah
you did
uh one second oh shed dead again
Sam what's wrong recently I've been
there on that side
and then I reactivate the blue one yeah
[Music]
I see it moving again
can she keep it like that
and I would be able to
you're here hello
chat all right I activated the red one
beautiful
what do I do here
I wait
here again
this is such a maze
do you have access to both the blue one
and the red one at the moment
[Music]
where are you
I'm gonna activate the red one okay oh
yeah no that doesn't really okay
yeah it's confusing did you see the
yellow switch because uh you can see
like one of the holes in the wall oh
maybe yeah maybe it was somewhere there
this is
sick stuff makes me go crazy
it's at the turnstile that's stuck at
the Rock
oh
[Music]
did you see it no
oh I'm just running around like a crazy
person
trying to understand this place
[Music]
just go through the all the red and blue
beats and tell me what okay blue please
red bluish
once again
it's really confusing here
haven't seen a yellow one once you find
it oh
man
[Music]
well you know my view is all chickens so
aren't amazed viewers all investigators
so
her chat should be more useful than my
chat hold on I'll learn it no problem no
problem
[Music]
hello
yeah you gotta get used to the map you
have to like be able to build like a map
in your brain of this place
excuse me yeah I'm sorry
hey
oh
do I activate chicken yes you have to be
you are a chicken look at your members
icon
[Music]
it's a mineral it shows you who you
really are who you truly are who your
heart desires to be
[Music]
oh I guess I guess if there were members
of both Amit and kfp
then that would be the ultimate
investigator chicken investigator
going
all the time
gosh I'm getting hungry let me eat some
Pokey oh
[Music]
she's not able to reach the record one
second my brain is uh are you not able
to reach the red one
no I can't because I think uh
oh my something up there
I think you have to help me are we are
we both stuck then
I'm not stuck
all right
no no no
but I pulled out the red one
hmm
I think you have to help me on this one
with the Turnstyle just go on the other
side and use it
oh never mind where I'm right now I can
turn I can pull the pull the lever
of the red one ah wait um oh yeah no I'm
stuck
[Music]
oh okay okay
let's eat in there
um pumpkin
oh what kind of like the European
version of it
oh it's like different chocolate or
something yeah yeah
and chocolate tastes different and
they're a bit thinner
on the cookie tastes a bit different too
but I kind of prefer it it's called
Mikado
that was yummy
so I think
apparently
two sources of um the ancient ones
uh you have and I want we we're not
really I don't know if it's true could
be wrong but we we don't really
have to go in together
one person should kind of stay at
deliveries I guess
yeah
and eventually we will we would be able
to reach the yellow one
and then once the yellow lever is
reached that would open up the yellow
door that is next to the red lever so
then I would be able to move on as well
okay Mom I'm
I'm stuck in between the blue and the
red okay I move the wagon can you move
now wow
all right can you move down
I mean I can no uh it's just a blue one
I get stuck a blue one okay wait uh
[Music]
I think I think Kiara you should take
this uh you should take this one okay
this one as in the lovers
okay
I'm not sure
okay I'm stopping
what
in the middle
I had no leather you want me to move
like all their height should I move
leathers
red
but I can't get to right now because
there the blue level was pulled oh wait
um
what
up here
remove that but then
what oh [\h__\h] out
[Music]
uh I guess so oh yeah I guess so yeah
can you pull the blue one
uh I think I messed up
it's so confusing
wait wait
okay okay wait you get now now now
ah okay are you out
did you get out
uh yes yes uh oh okay can you think can
you pull the blue one again
uh
uh I don't know if I can get back if I
do that
[Music]
um okay okay I'll pull it again I'll
pull it again it should be fine
okay now I can pull the red one okay
[Music]
okay
and I can I can also yeah no I can only
imagine I get it now all right can you
do the blue one if you can get to it I
could I could get to look probably if I
moved the red one again okay that's fine
okay I'll try
[Music]
okay
oh I can't I can't again I'm at the I'm
at the blue one okay
okay I opened it or it closed it
whatever
all right I need you to get back to the
red one if you can
shoot should be possible
yes oh finally okay I don't we did
something right there before because we
were both no okay never mind I can I can
no
[Music]
wait The Blue Door makes me stuck now oh
yeah I gotta push it for you oh okay
wait wait wait don't do that yet
[Music]
why does he do that why does it do that
oh
you gotta push it back
up yeah
[Music]
it's got you because you pulled a blue
one
but we're not we're not going anywhere
we keep on repeating what we're
repeating it okay I think what it is is
if I uh so the turnstile which gets you
to the yellow switch it only has three
sides right just like this one and
there's a rock blocking it and uh
because there's a rock blocking it means
that it has to be turned a certain way
before you can go through to get to the
other side right so I think if we if I
keep going around or if I turn it the
correct way and then get into it on the
side you're supposed to get into it and
I can turn it enough to get to the other
side
probably yes
so okay
I need the uh hold on wait
please say it's the red one you need
[Music]
yeah it seems like one person can only
do one switch
I like at least alone when they're on
their own
[Music]
I'll come out afterwards try to make one
more Loop and get into it again okay why
wow I'm at Emma is releasing her full
potential
foreign
oh uh is there any way for you to get to
the blue one
um perhaps yes
no
uh unless I'm no no damn it I'm
currently uh stuck uh both the blue one
and the red one are closed for me
oh uh okay
chicken panic
I'm a phoenix though I'm Phoenix all
right I'll open it or
open the blue one for you but
um wait a second but
I think you need to come this way to get
into the
blue one to your side
yeah okay hi
foreign
[Music]
okay okay so I opened the red one for
you yeah
[Music]
wait I guess you have to do it again
before you leave yeah uh uh okay okay
because okay
did me moving the blue one did something
for you yeah
we're at the right position now I think
yeah okay
[Music]
no it would I know I did that okay uh
did that do something for you
oh hold on one second
because now I'm stunk
it's like an endless time Loop that
we're in
[Music]
well I think I see him moving over there
okay all right I figured it out all
right I gotta get
um do the can you do the blue one again
uh only if I do the red one first that's
fine yeah
on my way
[Music]
yes
okay all right now do it again and then
go to the red one
okay
[Music]
yes I actually uh kind of turned off my
brain
okay red one activated
[Music]
okay I'm at the yellow switch
okay now I don't have to touch the
yellow one anymore I think now we can go
back and figure out the blue and red I
am now in a place where the red one
would need to be opened but yeah
okay uh or do you have access to the
blue one or no no I am past the yellow
door and there's like a turn there's
like a tourney door and then there's a
another Red Gate but it looks like
looks like that's the end
like the exit
but I guess we both have to come here
um
oh that's the place where we uh that I I
see from here I see it kind of see the
place where the blue lever is
so and the yellow one is gone
so in ah
[Music]
uh do you have any access to any lovers
at all
uh the yellow one I guess
oh wait
what
oh oh my God I got through I will check
if there's another liver no
oh I can't go out here don't leave me
behind no not at all I did okay I'm not
coming back coming back okay
okay so inferior the door is open here
the path is open so
I need the red one and then the blue one
to get up
the question is just does that mean if I
do that you'll get stuck and then I'll
get stuck again uh
I don't think so
[Music]
um
I don't think I can get to that
if I do the red one
I I will have to do the red one again is
that okay yeah
okay let's go let's go
let's go guys
okay now I'm here hello oh wait okay
where are you
what I'm crazy
hello can you come over
no but I'll go around oh okay uh because
I have to do
are we doing it can I turn the blue one
I got no problem and then uh
yes yes
one more time oh yeah and then the red
one
can you do the red one more time
oh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
ah there I am
we need the red one one more time yeah
easy easy
[Music]
oh my God you oh so I guess this is the
ancient ruins is it
it looks like it yeah I think so okay so
there's no Bridge
that's a gun really good to know you
should did you lose your gun on it
my what your gun is on the ground here
your pistol
oh this is a flare gun
ah all day we're trying to find help
yeah so maybe they're taking uh they're
taking uh what's it called a shelter in
the ancient thingy oh I found a pattern
this might be useful oh
pattern
okay what is this what is this
all right so this star pattern here
that's the one that's on the bridge and
so I guess the comet is the one that's
on the other side of the bridge
so I guess the sun is before
[Music]
the check over here
maybe we could find it somewhere oh yeah
oh wow oh what the heck this wasn't here
before oh yeah pull the level
you gonna do one more time
I did it one more time does it do
something
no try moving any of the symbols oh
[Music]
if I moved something
try moving some by the comet
comment
this one
this is the comic right
[Music]
just doing random movements though
okay hold on I'm gonna I just moved a
bunch of them randomly
all right I'll go back out oh wait let's
all right hold on I'll report you said
I'm sorry
okay so right now the bridge only has
one square that has the star and one
square that has the sun oh another one
appeared in front of me the moon just
appeared in front oh you killed me
okay I'm back yes uh so whatever you did
there you brought it up and then it it
dropped again I actually did nothing
oh maybe it's times
do they slide back on their own uh they
reset after while yeah
okay
[Music]
okay I see the way that it's connected
okay
[Music]
oh there you go I didn't really see the
other side yet so I'll check it out
okay
was it here the bridge
who made this
who is this in the first place oh okay
that's like a sorry and the sun
oh okay I see that's how you died
would you die yeah yeah okay
um
eh
[Music]
does the gun have any meaning
so much into it yeah
there's nothing here it's just
so we have to find out the red pattern
but what hints do we have only that
there is star and Sun there and
[Music]
okay I I'm not sure what this is
supposed to tell us
so there's a star in the Sun at the
bridge
yeah
does that mean that in this pattern we
want
um the sun into the star also at the
bottom
uh actually I don't know yeah the bridge
starts off with the star and because the
comet is on the other side I'm assuming
that's what's on the other side I don't
know what was on there I decided did you
see that from there no no I'm just
assuming that that's what's on the other
side because I feel a little diagram
like uh
the comment starts in this position
oh and there's a gap in between the star
and the comments I was just assuming but
I don't know
well we can I guess we should try to
start by trying to get the star and the
sun in the red position
right
uh
this is the only thing that the lever
does resetting the this thing here
probably
to play I recently did something like
that so we know the one that works the
moon comes up so it goes so I guess the
star and the sun are already in the
correct position so the moon has to be
moved into a different position oh are
we just guessing then
well I mean it's not really guessing
because it's like a process of
elimination if the star and the sun are
in the correct location
let me see if the sun disappears when
you move it
[Music]
no it doesn't move
foreign
[Music]
trial and error yeah
um
okay well the Moon is at the very top
now but like how do I know what else I
want there
trying randomly
I know do you remember when I died where
you the moon was that time we
uh
you died you died when you did
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh I just died again yeah
so whatever you did to the sun one uh
you just moved it and it yeah it killed
me how how
how is that possible how did they kill
you
did you stand on the bridge yes
maybe I'm not just supposed to stand on
it I don't know let me see if it happens
again
yeah oh my God
okay uh yeah maybe it's supposed to be
we can stand on the star one because
it's connected to two sides and the sun
one is only connected on one side so it
just Falls
um
ah wait maybe while you're moving that
if you move the right one in the right
position it would be connecting itself
to the star bridge to the sun Bridge
piece and I would see it here
yeah yeah okay I'll move uh I'll move
some around okay
um I might be very wrong with that
assumption though
we were dead together that's it can I
jump down here
oh my God again scary
nothing's moving here though
any signs
[Music]
oh is oh
what you can't Me Maybe you can't stand
on it if the symbol that represents it
isn't in the correct spot
mm-hmm
oh that I'm gonna reset it really quick
oh get it
I get what you're trying to say I don't
know if that's true
but that would mean that the star is in
the right position but the sun is not
ah
I feel
[Music]
you you already understood that and I
just didn't understand that you
understood it
but like see when we stand on the maybe
it's not about connecting not not about
the fact that the star was connected
with the sun and that's why it's uh
not falling down but like maybe the star
is in the right position currently and
that's why it's not falling down and the
Sun the bridge part does not fall down
because the sun peace is not in the
right position that's what I thought
first too but doesn't see why it would
appear I know why it would appear if uh
I don't know if you if you can you move
the star thing it doesn't do anything
huh when it moves I can still stand on
the bridge I guess
I'm moving a bunch of stuff around oh
wait the star couldn't be moved right I
feel like I tried to move oh is that the
sun if you look I tried moving the one
of them and it wasn't able to move
ah that one was locked right that's why
yeah this one always stays in place
no no changes
um okay I'll move the star
is that one not locked
oh it was locked in place
the star is is locked in place no okay
yeah it is that's okay that's why that
one will never fall down the first piece
of the bridge so the star is already in
the right position perhaps
yeah okay yeah maybe maybe that's how it
works could be could be wrong but but
yeah
so
the sun would have to be
moved into every single position and we
will find out which one is the right one
uh and for each
position you put it in I have to try to
stand on it to test it out
okay okay then let's try every single
position once you change it I'll stand
on it let me know all right I changed it
that was incorrect
next position please
okay
all right I changed it okay
that was that was correct and I see the
moon now we have to change the Moon but
in order to change the movie maybe maybe
have to change the sun again just keep
the yeah the moon disappeared okay okay
just remember the place where the sun
was at I guess okay yeah okay
okay okay
uh the moon only showed up as it was the
sun because the sun was already correct
okay so now I know that I should not
stand on that way it doesn't connect uh
it's currently not connected
um yeah uh the sound okay so uh the line
appears when the sun is next to the moon
but when I move the moon to a different
spot there's no line so maybe just
something else has to be on the other
side of the moon
laughs
all right not sure if I'm just in a
sentence but what I know is that
um the moon piece is currently not
showing up because it only shows up uh
if the sound piece is in the right right
position so currently I have two pieces
on the bridge but when the sun was in
the right position then I had a sun
piece a moon piece of the bridge as well
a third piece
I put it in the same spot but uh it's
not appearing now oh oh there it goes oh
yeah right okay okay okay uh yeah so I
see the moon piece again
[Music]
now oh wait a second
oh oh I have to stand oh [\h__\h] wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait can you put the sun there again
where where it's correct
okay so now I'm standing on the sun
piece when I don't move anything
[Music]
okay I'm gonna have to stand on there
okay I understand oh my God no wait wait
did you move the Sun
no I didn't touch anything what is it
again
no I didn't do anything it just breaks
out I think it resets every time you die
oh wait okay so I am standing on the sun
piece
and the moon piece is in front of me but
once I get to and walk off of the sound
piece then it won't fall down okay okay
I guess I'm like locking it while I'm
standing on it yeah yeah so when you
stand on it there's there's a line
appearing between the star the sun and
the moon right now
but maybe if I get the right well then I
gotta lock the moon into place I think
it doesn't seem to be timed because it's
not moving yet it only seems to all
right are you standing on the sun one
yeah
[Music]
so someone fell down but I'm back I'm
back I'm back I didn't die you you you
oh you got me back from the death is the
moon is the moon one out the woman is
still there but I'm too scared to step
on it okay yeah don't do it yet
oh
something blocked
wheel
s
okay I'm gonna move the sun one wait
wait wait
I see the planet one the the one the
planet with the solution one yeah
okay
oh it's it's locked it's I think it
locked itself okay wait
something oh
oh okay interest
ing
interesting interesting interesting
how can I interesting wait interesting
interesting things happening here I I I
still I I was pretty much I was walking
up the bridge was complete for a moment
I think and I walked over but I think
you moved something and then the second
piece the sun disappeared
and and then
and then everything disappeared I think
now now I only have the sun and the star
again
I think I went to probably I went too
far but uh we got verified because after
the satorin Saturn uh one more thing
showed up
but let's try to get the bridge going
again because it'll reset
um is the sun in place
yeah I put in the same spot oh there it
is okay okay now I see the moon
do you think it's safe to step on the
moon
uh yes I am on the moon I see the Saturn
okay
[Music]
this is this is locked right
I'm not going in yet
ah it opened up
yeah leave it like that now it's locked
I think okay I see the bridge but it's
not the when the bridge came up the sun
disappeared so that means that you
wouldn't be able to pass over wow
probably pass over oh no no never mind
never mind when I try to pass over even
though it's connected it uh yeah eats me
okay okay
um I am on the moon again and I am on
Saturn and now the thing the bridge
comes up but there's something that
needs to be done uh the Sparkles
something with the sparkles
is that look
okay I'm gonna move them okay
[Music]
all right hold on don't get under yet
okay
don't I have to be on it in order to
[Music]
this is a fun riddle
it was good wasn't it it actually was
good
no stop standing on it
you're resetting my progress okay excuse
me sorry
it's okay is that really how it works
they say we had it though
oh they say we we had it at that one
point
I don't know if you guys are correct
though
all right hold on this reminds me a
little bit of the game I played with
Kelly
[Music]
uh what was it called again uh what was
it called again
[Music]
yeah it takes two that's right because
it also had a bunch of riddles and it
had a winter wonderland as well like but
uh a lonely
like Serene quiet when the winter
wonderland
and a dramatic part to it too like it
had these mountains as well and it had
similar Graphics to
actually quite similar
from like not the character the
character was definitely different style
anyway that was beautiful yeah more like
hell that's true it's more like a winter
hellland
so am I allowed to go on because
nothing's happening
I have I have to go on it
I think I have to go on the bridge in
order to make it work because nothing's
happening here okay okay okay okay okay
okay I'm going on the Sun
yep and it makes the moon show up and it
locks in place so I walk on the moon and
it makes the Saturn show up and it locks
in place so I go on just a tour and it
makes the bridge show up with the
Sparkles and it locked in place so I
walk over there and I am I am just this
time I'm not disappearing don't uh so
what happened is I'm now standing on the
sparkles on the bridge
uh but the sun disappeared
okay so quick can you cross over to the
other side yeah uh I can step on the
swirly whirly thingy but then something
else disappears too it seems uh but I am
on the swirling really I think I have to
go on the other side so then I move
something for you probably
okay so on the swirling really thingy
I'm just missing it seems like
one one or two more pieces to connect me
to the end
oh okay uh you have one on your side
no no no I am out on the Galaxy oh okay
oh my God
okay uh yeah so I'm on the on this
really really the black hole
uh wait wait wait
um
okay
that was not oh my God
okay okay the swirly whirly thingy the
piece I'm standing on right now has is
it looks like a bridge that splits
itself in two and
um
in total there's three signs on it
the first one before the stairs split up
in this one piece
uh is the is the Sparkles the Stars this
one is locked in place this one is fine
if I go up left on the splitted Bridge
oh wait never mind that is one piece
never mind this is this is different
pieces okay the Sparkles is one piece
but it is it it turns into split
upstairs
so when I go up the left side it is
connected to the swirly Whirly
and if I go to the right side it is
currently connected but not locked in
with the comet so I would reckon that
the swirly whirly is in the correct
position but the combat is not yeah I
moved it around okay
um yeah I'm gonna move something you
might die okay
scared
I cannot die unless
as long as I stand Here proud
the left left side swelling oily right
side
[Music]
well I am not part of whole life space
out the world's three seasons Empires
incredible and I understood that well
have you seen our change
um have you seen our collab of the the
bomb collapse no the lock on the right
side of the climate is still uh open oh
hey you think you're there
now you can make an image of that
um and on the left side yeah
[Music]
is still locked
but the comment is not so nothing
changed okay all right I'm gonna move
some more stuff around so yeah what I
was trying to say is remember when um
uh me and Amma did uh keep talking and
nobody explodes explodes collab when
we're talking both in English we were
doing so bad but we talked but when we
talked in like a language that the other
one didn't really understand well
that's when we racked the game for some
reason so when we don't understand each
other that well that's when we
understand each other the most
isn't that beautiful
isn't that beautiful someone quote that
uh and with a screenshot of me and then
the universe has the background uh and I
put it on Reddit like you know with a
with a cursive cursive La uh font that
says
when we don't understand each other we
understand each other the most
laughs
I agree but I also don't understand you
don't understand don't ya it's some deep
stuff there
I'm in
yes have you noticed that
[Music]
yes when we don't understand each other
we understand each other the most
oh yeah
that's beautiful oh thank you thank you
see that that was the case when we
played uh uh uh keep on talking and
nobody explodes oh yeah yeah when we
spoke in English we didn't understand
each other but when you spoke in Spanish
and I spoke in Japanese we did
understand each other somehow
did anything change because I looked
such a good comment locked into the
thingy oh
okay wait I'm gonna be locked in yes yes
it did okay oh when I stand oh
my when I stand on the comet it brings
up the
Moon eating the Earth
uh oh yes okay the double okay okay yeah
can I stand on the other one
I should be able but didn't it like kick
me down last time I tried to stand on it
hmm ah no wait so this one is not locked
in but that one is so I should be able
to add it okay it should be locked in
now
oh sorry uh did it reset
um it is it's not logged in
[Music]
uh I feel like I saw it logging in for a
moment was that just wanted
oh
yeah you had it locking in for a moment
but then it unlocked I think some some
position in between uh yeah no no it's
locked in
uh so we're gonna step on it it moves
almost there oh the rest of the birds
pretty much disappeared
okay but we have now
uh in front of me we need one more piece
and in front of me is uh already a lot
wait a second
oh my okay already locked in in the
right position was a moon and in front
of me is the Sun and it's not locked in
so if we lock in the sun then I'm on the
other side of the bridge
uh
God
and a Chris Crescent Moon Crush
questioned Crescent Christian I gotta
move it temporarily I think okay I'm
going back on the safe piece okay I'm on
the
okay crescent moon is locked in
[Music]
the sun you said you need the sun uh
yeah the sun needs to be locked in hmm
[Music]
I'm dead
I'll
I'm
I'm gonna go on the comment just for
safety
okay let me know if you haven't moved uh
but I have to be on the no I think I
have to be
ah wait ah
in order to lock in the sun I think I
have to stand on the Crescent Moon okay
yeah okay I have to stand here if you
ever if you are about to move the
Crescent Moon let me know because that's
probably when I'll die
okay I'm not gonna move the crescent
moon but I'm gonna move the double
okay yep that's that's uh
yeah I remember the pattern for that one
okay for the beginning at least okay
uh moon is Moon is there okay it's
locked in I know it wasn't hold on hold
on okay now most of it should lock okay
foreign
[Music]
but okay so currently
um the Sparkles is not locked in with
the comet
oh okay
foreign
[Music]
it's not locked in though
okay
ah okay uh
the Crescent Moon is back and locked in
place and now we have the sun in front
of me which is the last piece that needs
to be locked in
I feel like I'm in a game show or
something a game question I think I know
like I have to move stuff around but I
think if I move stuff around you're
gonna
you're gonna fall
interesting you're on the which one are
you on
I am currently on the Crescent Crescent
Moon
same problem again what if uh
what can we like prep what you are about
to move uh if we go like back on like
can you prep that beforehand the level
step yeah okay on this one okay like if
I'm for example on the double moon I
think if I go back it resets though does
it
no okay okay so I am now on the double
moon is there any way you can prep it
while I'm on there or should I stand on
the comment that's awesome if I move it
uh yeah you should probably step on the
comment instead okay
I'm gonna move double okay
oh okay oh
[Music]
y'all going here
interesting
it's just this is uh this is very
interesting this is fun actually I I
don't usually play like puzzle games
like this
I guess the only other puzzle game I
played on stream was What It Takes Two
or can you guys think of anything else
stay in the comment really okay
[Music]
is it the only problem is that sometimes
I feel very stupid oh it locked in place
I see you just locked in place to
comment with the double moon
yeah try stepping on it now all right
I'm just stepping on I see the Crescent
Moon and locked in I move over and the
sun comes up
[Music]
oh man
Zelda technically well get only just got
started with that okay I stopped off the
whole bridge is gone let's see if we
have the same thing on the other side
oh dear please don't tell me it's the
same thing please tell me it's just a
button
oh it's a it's a wheel
a wheel oh
my God thank God yeah I think it would
have been hard for me to tell you how to
do that
oh is that annoying
oh my that was that was a damn good job
man nice thank you
thank you for being so Cooperative I
hear scary laughing Almond please join
me
you go in the big doors yeah
I already regret it
oh it's four elements
fire water
I'm scary I like Pikachu okay fire water
Earth and Pikachu
where are you where are you woman
oh uh okay I guess we're not in the same
area uh but I'm in a room with a bunch
of books on the floor that are circled
with glowing arrows which are pointing
to different books and there's also a
grid in front of me with four stones of
five stones and it says a b c d e on the
left and one two three four five on the
top okay
what about you uh well I have a
okay uh I have two posters
uh pieces of posters which also has like
numbers and two seven six five ten and
then on on the right place so let's do
in the middle there's a minus and on the
right side there's a A3 E2 B4 Etc on the
right side the poster has a different
combinations
and then in the middle I have
[Music]
um like a like a monitor and a screen
uh with a b c d e one two three four
five and I can operate it and move like
five dots
okay and that thing is on top of a wheel
with four elements fire uh water uh
Earth and Pikachu
um
so I guess if I operate that
uh uh
oh I just saw a new Pikachu appear on my
board yeah I did something oh you
connected that for some reason
okay absolutely no idea what this is
I
I see
so for example ah I understand I
understand I think
so I have I have two poses right
um one of them has a bunch of numbers
five numbers and the other one has the
other five numbers so on the right side
I have for example one but on the other
post I don't have one so we gotta
probably start with one and that one is
attached to D2 so on my finger here I
think I first have to do a D2
um I have to pick Point like one of the
elements on my monitor screen thingy on
D2 let's try that okay well I have a
fire on D2 yeah oh yeah okay that's
that's there yeah
wait so that continues number two would
be
uh A3
what's on a free nothing right now
okay oh wait is that it
yeah is that so is that so simple it can
it can't be
okay number three is B1
there must be something that you have to
do too B1 is already there
oh
and then uh uh wait that was free so it
wasn't free
a four is there E5
[Music]
E5
oh E5 is already there
see free
[Music]
that was what that was briefly I did
what
oh do you have any any idea what the
stuff over at your place does
uh yeah so the only thing I could do is
connect between the grid that I have
with all the elements on it and then I
can't interact with them but there's
glowing circles and arrows which uh one
circle is like circled around a book and
then pointing to another book that's
circled with a glowing or uh Arrow so
each book has different numbers on it so
one is like four to nine uh five to one
three two two ten oh maybe it's a code
maybe like the it's opposite so like if
if on your thing it says like a A5 or
something it's actually A1
you mean for example if my if my number
one says D2
then on your book it says one is with
what number
I've five so that would mean that the
first one is not
day two but what it says here for five
which is C3
[Music]
are we overthinking
no
that actually sounds
like I can't think of what else the
numbers would be for but the thing is
like it goes all the way up to 10 like
it says 10 is 8.
hi
mine goes up to ten oh okay
um
um okay let's can I reset this though
it doesn't have to be done in a certain
order okay let's do it
all right
yours just says like one to two stuff
like that right the books I'll read all
the books so it says
uh six to seven or it's 97 I can't tell
which is the right way uh three to two
five to One Ten to eight and six to four
okay so if we have one a day two
um
one of the
and you said one to five which is C free
maybe it's a math maybe it's a math
[Music]
I can change okay we also have the
problem and those have elements how
about
how the hell do it no which one is one
Element
oh God
[Music]
we're gonna be stuck here forever
oh we'll figure it out
[Music]
and try some stuff but my grid only goes
to five so I can't I don't know what to
do with that
my numbers
[Music]
well yeah those are the Pokemon Rails
but
[Music]
this is literally the easiest puzzle hey
again what is it what does the number
say
uh which numbers I have a lot of numbers
uh for example one one is D2
two is a free I think I misplaced eight
two
uh A3 there we go
[Music]
and um
three
is B1
[Music]
3 is there
okay so I guess if it's a code and the
arrows only go one way then if it's one
then it stays one but if it's five then
it becomes one
can you repeat that over uh because the
arrows are pointing in One Direction
then maybe the oh the numbers which
um or at the start of the arrow so if
it's 10 it becomes eight but if it's
eight it doesn't become 10. you know
what I mean it just stays that number
but that is telling me that I'm wrong
oh that is getting close hold on one
second
the chat is getting close
how does the ground tell me which signs
he is
I don't know where like how do I know
like which one is D2
do I just start with red and then I go
on like that look like a two would be
this one for you would be this one four
would be this one five would be this one
and so on
let's just start with red
oh
oh she actually closed the chat
[Music]
okay
ah
that one starts to fire so the next one
is green
I I think I at least figured out one
thing um that's the thing of the element
elements because I have these four
elements and I can decide which point
which piece that I place would be the
elements
um but it starts out it starts out with
D2 the first one number one which is
already placed on my screen and that one
starts with fire so since the arrow is
only going One Direction the next piece
that I placed would have to be
um uh green stuff veggies
oh so number two was a free
and that one is currently electricity so
I'll turn it to Green okay okay okay
okay okay okay so maybe first of all I
just put every every little thing every
coordinate in place and then we can try
to connect them
okay okay
uh I stopped at three years old now
let's check the color of afraid B1
is three and that would be electricity
okay so the next one is blue uh which 4
4 blue A5 blue E5 blue E5 gold
if I below oh I can't
I can't change the color of that
four blue
[Music]
uh well how do I remove them don't you
see we remove them
[Music]
foreign
is there a way for you to reset
everything I did
no
foreign
[Music]
I can once I placed one I can change the
number but I don't seem to
be able I mean what if I place like
everything
oh
okay now everything's full and I get rid
of them though I cannot get rid of them
anymore so I guess it's okay to have
extra ones on there yeah uh oh you're oh
you made them disappear
how did you do that
I don't know I just tried to connect
stuff
[Music]
how'd you do that
um
sorry I figured I'd have to remove them
but I still can't remove that one to the
Comber of that one is incorrect though
okay let me try to remove everything
uh so you have like coordinates and
stuff but there's no indication of what
element should be and what
um it kind of seemed to have it because
the first one starts with fire and so
the second one I go with green the third
one I go over yellow the fourth one I go
with blue but I kind of got stuck at the
fourth one because the fourth one is
already set in place with green even
though it should be blue and that's
where I got confused now
oh
but I'm trying to remove them again the
ones that I just placed okay okay
[Music]
you place it yeah but like what does the
linking even like if this is not the
right element then
what does that do like it doesn't it
have to be the right element
first of all
[Music]
thank you
okay
[Music]
um
okay everything that is on it now is uh
there from the beginning I can not move
them or I can also not change the color
oh
based on your I heard uh can you ah
can you
tell me
uh the numbers on your books again the
first ones
okay a four to six four to six uh three
to two five one ten to eight
[Music]
four four nine to seven
wait okay does that mean like four
number four that I have here E5 when it
when it says six does that mean that
um I have to go around here six times
starting from one two three four five
six and that's why it's green
[Music]
is that I I think I understand
wait what did you say before
six right
yes but it could be nine because it's
kind of I can't really tell oh it could
be nine
uh
those are I know her is on links but I
thought that also tells me
[Music]
got him
it will come clear once that's right
okay okay you know what never mind
um
but I'm I'm not gonna care about the
elements just yet I'm just gonna put
everything in place now okay so okay it
will take a lot of time and while I'm
doing that I guess if you know
which wants to connect then I guess you
could already connect them
okay
um
you're doing it one D2 already in place
number two is a a free
[Music]
I placed it now
oh [\h__\h] sorry
okay uh that was number two two okay now
number three B one
already in place
number four
E5
already in place
number six
B four
already in place
[Music]
uh number seven
E2
foreign
s from the ones that are not placed
[Music]
oh where did I just stop he's waited
six what did that ah okay so the the
coordinates that you're putting in are
numbered
yeah yeah yeah yeah other number one to
ten yeah
oh okay
okay all right have you placed all of
them yet or no not yet okay number eight
number eight is E1
are already already placed as well so
number nine
uh A4
place and number ten
be free okay I placed all of them
okay
I need you to tell me uh which okay so
we gotta connect these books to each
other so we'll do five one first so
whatever the fifth coordinate is to the
first coordinate
so see see free
to D2
okay I missed one
now next I'll wait one second one second
okay
yeah
wait I forgot one
apparently yeah but not is he afraid
can you unconnect that because I don't I
think that was
okay now now it should have all of them
okay now we're doing a
three to two three two uh B1
2 A3
[Music]
this is number one detective exactly now
let's do ten to eight
and don't be free to E1
[Music]
uh be free
two in one
is that even possible
okay I guess I did the first one wrong
what is a five two one
uh C3 to detail
oh
oh uh now
wait we did
five to one we did three to two we did
ten to eight now I don't know if this is
seven to six or nine to sit uh sorry I
don't know if this is nine to seven or
six to seven so I guess we'll try let's
do uh nine to seven first
uh A4 to E2
okay that's probably not it let's try it
okay let's try six two uh seven
before to
eat
ah so those two have to be blue is that
it because that was blue now I always
have to be right four to six or four to
nine I guess
uh four maybe five two
A5 e e five to a four E5 to A4
okay so uh both those last two I just
did are blue which means yeah that the
elements are correct so I guess for the
other three uh they should be different
elements
foreign
is it perhaps
because that one is set in stone and
it's green
ah so it's opposite
I can put it back oh [\h__\h] whichever one
is red then put blue as opposite
so like for the fire one that's
connected to the lightning bolt just
turn the lightning bolt to Blue
okay can you connect it again
and can you connect the other one again
the uh bottom left to the middle red one
oh yeah I can't get it because the first
one started out as green and I the one
that I set uh I can change the colors
and that one has to be red okay so that
one started out as a Pikachu so the next
one has to be blue
okay connect please
[Applause]
we did it our brains are so big oh my
God okay I I you know the problem was in
the beginning I thought that I already
had to figure out the elements from the
get-go but I could only figure it out
once the connections were made then it
was easy then it made sense but I tried
to figure it out too early yeah yeah oh
where are you where are you woman
oh uh I see there was a creepy clown
that I saw what the [\h__\h]
um
I'm good at bunking clowns
okay well
um
hold on one second
I'm gonna stairwell and I'm carrying a
candle oh never mind I'm going into a
deep tunnel that's okay and the fire in
a fireplace is you probably have to come
down to you oh I'll say if you want me
I'm gonna cuddle too I'm in a tunnel as
well I think we'll can find each other
out I think the door closed behind me
okay well I'm in a let me know when you
get to your destination oh I have
arrived I see you
ah finally yes oh wait that's not you
decide that's the dude that we were
looking for now listen oh you have a
different cutscene I need your help yes
you see that apparatus over there
get it to work and retrieve the stone
with him I'll explain later
but you're done meet me upstairs in the
greenhouse good luck friend
met the guy that's like lost in the
tunnels and he told me to make an um
apparatus to go to work
oh my God uh okay well I uh wherever you
are I'm in a room that has some water
and like a big pattern that has these
little orbs that are connected to like
things that look like batteries that
have two stripes on either end which are
different colors
I wanted to say room
is that what it looks like on your side
I am oh my God
what the hell
something's happening I think the water
is rising yeah I jumped into the water
and then that turned on the lights
oh
okay well there's scary music so I think
this is timed
oh no hey
what am I gonna die
if we don't finish it on time probably I
can
I'll take all of those things oh my God
okay uh what the hell what oh my God
what what
I can't change anything on my side but I
could probably tell you okay okay
there's like there's like a bunch of
like uh thingies and
and I okay there's a lot a lot of weight
lifting thingies that each have a color
and I'm supposed to put the ones with
the right color into the right position
yeah uh the fuses fuses I guess and I
have to put the fuses into the into the
right tower thingies now I have for
example green and red but I also have uh
I have a blue and blue and I have red
and red and I have only okay
okay so I see green and red and two it's
left it's connected to blue and orange
does that help and on its right okay uh
uh which one is connected to Blue
uh not blue blue it's just one blue
stripe and you want to know what blue
blue is connected to I want to know what
red blue is connected to
oh red blue is connected to three
different ones uh to the top it's
connected to blue blue to the bottom
it's connected to blue yellow and to the
right it's connected to just one stripe
of yellow bottom
why is it connected to three
oh my God oh my God
I'm not gonna get electrocuted
what is uh what's connected to the to uh
yellow green or orange green whatever
that is uh one yellow stripe one red
stripe and a blue green and also one
blue stripe
is it connected to one like a specific
sign
like do you see
do you see if it's like ah
what it wait what what
oh gosh I feel like I'm getting tested
here
uh
where do I uh maybe I start here where
do I start where do I even start this is
it doesn't matter where I started okay
oh she doesn't seem to hear me
um
um okay
um well I see I see some connections
like the towers that I see the
electricity Towers or whatever those are
some of them have fuses already in there
which is why I was asking you why what
is connected to orange and green however
orange and green has like a wire on top
of it that connects to
one Tower with no fuses and the other
wire connects to another Tower with no
fuses but only two so when you say
there's red things connected to it oh my
God
okay when you say this red thing is
connected to it
um free free things connected to it I'm
not sure like why is it free four yeah
four
who's that connected to it
for like different uh units are
connected to it oh
okay maybe I have to try maybe is this
round can I when something happens if I
put the wrong one in Tell me uh one of
the colors again that's in red green or
orange green
uh blue green
it's yeah in that order blue on the left
green on the right I'm on the left
right on on the fields when you say blue
on the left and green on the right you
said you mean that stats on one fuse
blue on the left yeah oh yeah I don't
know
[Music]
oh I don't have to pull in the left
going on the right
how are you what do your Towers look
like
um
sorry
um in a certain path yeah I I I guess so
oh my god
um well there the pattern is that
they're connected with wires at the top
and there's one two three
four five six
yeah there should be eight probably yeah
um
oh my God
you said blue green also but I don't
have a fuse with blue and green on it I
have blue and blue I have green only I
have blue only maybe that's something
only yeah on that one
okay I placed it nothing happened maybe
that's a good thing
um I'm gonna go to another one that's
connected to orange green and then we
can see what else fits there yeah the
other one that is connected to orange
green
um
I guess I'll put the green one down
what's happening what's happening oh my
God wait this oh I just
I don't know
um we're just sparking with uh very
dangerous electricity is getting closer
and closer to the water
once I put the green one down
oh wait did it wait no it went no okay
that time that's that has I guess
nothing to do with the with the fuse it
has to do with time okay [\h__\h] I'm about
to die probably yeah at least we figured
it out for the next time yeah yeah yeah
I just you know I never died before for
like electrocution as a Phoenix Sun so
this is gonna be new for me I don't know
if I wanted to make that experience but
what is connected to uh blue and blue uh
a red and blue
uh there's a blue blue a blue orange and
just an orange or I don't know it's like
orange yellow we'll just call it orange
okay I place blue blue
okay well
oh my God
for the place where I place
okay I'm dead your journey has ended
that was quite a shock are you kidding
me
it's not fun wait wait does it start
oh it starts from where we just were
okay okay
close by chapters
[Music]
so what have we learned
and I know lagging right now uh he's
loading the game okay we learned how to
connect them
are we sure about that though because I
had a lot of leftover fuses
I'll be fine I think it'll be like a
process of elimination thing
okay I'm in the water
the timer is gone okay does this have
anything is it oh wait there's ah I
guess at the end I have to pull the
lever here and then see if that lets me
out okay
um
okay well
there's no way that the first
combination that we tried is correct
though because you gave me a bunch of
different colors and
and yeah
I just picked a random one
uh well uh it sounded like only one
could fit in that particular like
whatever you're putting it into so
that's why I thought well if it can fit
then that must be it but I put a
different one in there now where
previously I put in green or something I
think I put in red now and it doesn't
there's no reaction
I guess as long as it maybe maybe
because
um it's about the way it connects like
I'm looking at a double blue one that
connects to a red one that connects to
like two different ones so maybe it has
to go via how it connects I don't know
ah wait a second
um maybe the correct one because it goes
green to Green
um but from the ones that I connected to
or a yellow green which ones were
connected to yellow green again a single
red blue and green a single blue and a
single yellow
four different modules
um
I want to try yellow on this side
single yellow because I oh wait that's
not yellow
or orange or whatever the fork it is
it goes okay because ah because like
I don't know if that has any connection
but like left yellow here close to the
left green goes to the right so maybe
it's
I don't know that's why I feel like
yellow goes here
and then it goes over there no eye goes
over there from the to the right side
um is there any
uh is there any rain connected to oh God
now we can't it's too late
is there anything connected to Yellow
slash orange whatever color that is
just just a single yellow yeah there's a
blue red there's a blue orange there's a
single blue and the orange green
look oh man
I I I just I don't I don't see a pattern
I don't
I don't know
which
sorry can you repeat all those colors
again okay uh red blue red blue orange
orange
uh orange green and blue well I don't
have a blue orange anymore red blue blue
orange orange green and orange green
maybe it's orange green wait is that no
that's orange red
oh my God
I don't I don't no I don't know Orange
I don't I don't know
I don't know
I don't know okay do you have anything
like the structure the pattern wise is
there like a circle
yeah like a
I don't know how they're placed but uh
so the the way that mine is there's like
four inside of a circle and then five
outside of the circle like on the border
of the circle so maybe if you have any
like uh in the middle of an area maybe
that'll help
oh yeah
[Music]
um
yeah he helped
well let me let me see what happens if a
pool leather probably gonna die I'm
probably gonna die
oh no
this doesn't mean it was correct oh my
God oh my God oh
oh
certain point does it mean up until then
it's correct but I'm about to die anyway
but okay when I remember that the orange
green one was like all electric it was
like it looked like like it was gonna
bite does that mean I was correct
I I will remember that I put orange here
and the blue here connected to the okay
so I guess it didn't continue here
because I didn't have anything in there
um what is connected again sorry to the
orange green one
oh oh sorry I didn't push the button
what is connected to the orange green
one
uh blue green blue red and green just
orange
blue green from the red blue green blue
red just orange blue green blue
red
okay oh I don't I feel like I didn't
have a little green blue red and just
orange oh
one more try you can do it
all right
we kind of had it Billy pull the lever
at the at the start and let's see what
happens okay yeah if it doesn't connect
anything at all that means that in the
beginning that the last pattern we had
was actually correct oh maybe
because it did connect up until the
point where I stopped putting in uh
fuses
oh man jump
like is there meaning to them being on
one side
well I needed uh orange and green I
think right let's take Orange
ah okay okay I wanted to pull the level
all right let's see
oh okay okay yeah that means that we
were on the right track
so only blue blue
um like shocked I like them yeah I also
saw like connection being made here
actually the connection not being made
even though previously when I had the
fuses in there the connection was being
made did I put Green in there let's see
again
um I'm pulling the lever it continues it
continues electricity up
stop wait let me know I put the wrong
color in there
nothing's happening on my side
oh
was it not green
oops
put it back I can't put it back
Christmas
oh okay I saw
oh okay so I saw a pattern between the
single blue and a single orange yep and
then when it got to the orange green it
stopped why did that one why did that
one disappear Chad why did that one
disappear and that one stained why I
don't understand
wait it's back here
what what does that mean oh well okay uh
okay so I'm up until there is correct uh
so next I just bought this book nothing
something random in there no
okay tell me the colors to uh
it went from Blue single blue to single
orange to orange and green and then it
stopped so there's either blue green or
single red
maybe it's wrong
but it's continued over there
okay
Lauren let's see what happens
pulling the leather
foreign
[Music]
we're probably gonna die again this time
but yeah yeah so from Red it either goes
to blue blue or blue green I'm guessing
blue blue because blue green is between
um no uh ah that One automatically
connects to one that was already placed
there which is red blue oh okay okay
uh
wait what do we have anything connected
to red blue
a single orange blue blue and blue
Origins
connecting connecting connecting
connecting Oh I thought this is correct
oh
that was just bad timing I think because
I don't know on my side it failed at red
this feel it red
what wait I want to try this way
okay but when you trigger it it goes
from like blue orange to like a
different to like a orange and then to
Orange the green
and so like I could see the path of the
electricity going and so it goes from
Blue to single blue to single orange to
orange green to red and then something
was disconnected at the red one
I still wonder why the hell that one
disappeared though was it a bug because
the second time we did it didn't
disappear
okay blue
that must be correct
okay so sorry was a single blue single
orange and orange green and then I think
it was single red
yes
and that single red either connects to a
blue green or blue blue
which is interesting because the wire
connected to the tower is where the
pre-placed fuses which is a red blue but
I can connect it to one one more tower
that doesn't have a fuse in it and I
have left the following colors orange
green only red red blue blue and green
red
I think I would go
yeah out of all those patterns I think
only blue blue is the one that because
there's a red green but not a green red
okay let me try again maybe it was
really just the timing that the time was
already home over
your place is wrong can I remove that I
don't think I could
I know when it gets to Red it just it
just pops a ton it doesn't or something
okay then I guess
it because I can't I cannot remove the
one that's already pre-placed
but I guess the blue one is wrong after
all
right
yeah I'll just put the other ones in
let's see what happens tell me what they
are again I have orange orange
and green only
uh blue blue
green red
and red red yeah
none of those
yeah
wait I want to see one more thing when
we're done
uh what connects with the red blue ones
uh either single orange blue orange or
blue blue
Orange or blue blue
and orange you know orange blue orange
purple
ah wait single orange blue orange blue
blue single orange blue orange blue blue
which one connects with the orange green
one
um
uh either blue green a single blue or a
single red oh
but blue is where the electricity
started the single blue so I don't think
it's that one I don't know
I don't have any of those yet
wait we had red there and it was
incorrect was it yeah maybe it's
supposed to go Blue to Orange to orange
green to blue green
repeat that please we're about to die
properly man oh uh well it starts at
blue and then it goes to Orange and then
it goes to orange green and maybe it's
supposed to go to blue green and then to
red
and then to blue blue
I don't have a blue green
oh I'll try blue blue that goes I don't
know I don't know
maybe we should start on a different one
more try wait wait no those are
connecting fine I think
yeah but it always gets I put a
different one this time
stuck at a orange green instead of red
yeah yeah that one though it's not
correct oh it returned though
interesting why did people want this one
returns
because it's incorrect this one is but
that one previously returns and it's
but it was correct I feel like
next time probably start on a different
one other than just a single bloop well
I don't know how it works on your side
but we might have to start from a
different area like a different path oh
do you have a green oh sorry a red green
to start off on
oh yeah
okay we could do that because the red
green only connects to two it either
connects to a single blue or a blue
orange well okay okay
well I'm gonna wait until I die again
it's gonna happen in a few seconds it's
coming I wonder if I jump into it oh oh
right okay I can just walk through that
thing but that doesn't kill me okay but
this kills me sure sure realistic okay
man the loading into this always takes
so much time
lag
okay maybe this time we can do it
yeah yeah maybe we just uh start at the
bottom of like the electric notes that
I'm looking at and it starts on red
green
red green okay
and it's either blue orange or blue
green blue orange or blue
a little orange or blue
I don't have orange
oh that's close
testing
oh that seems to connect fine
yeah but it stopped at uh orange green
but yeah yeah yeah I didn't put enough
of anything after that so okay uh what
do we put into red green can you once
again tell me the connections please all
right connect it to orange green are red
blue green and yellow
okay I have uh from those I have red and
yellow
it's a single red or a single yellow
yeah
I guess single red
let's do it
actually do single yellow sorry okay
and then from there tell me what you
have
okay
should I test it again I'll test it
again
where did it oh I think it would
oh yeah it's working oh my God okay I'm
just missing the last one
last one did so I have something that
should be connected with red and blue
blue
okay I have blue blue
oh my God is this it
is
[Music]
oh meow meow I saw it locked okay I
think you have to maybe open the door
for me hello meow hi baby okay
oh wait no one I got through
okay I don't know should we
leaving another one more
oh I wonder how far we are like from
percentage-wise
this one looks complicated so maybe we
should leave it it looks pretty
complicated oh well of course chats has
one more
I'll be like if we do the next one would
we be halfway through Islander
chat do you know that chat do you know
that
thank you
[Music]
I'm almost done with the tutorial what I
remember well I've seen a little bit
like of what the hell is that I didn't
do this one but I've seen a little bit
of it in like a stream before
but I definitely don't remember how it
works
45 or so okay I don't mind if you want
to play more uh
uh
a punch
um
eh chapter seven we are at chapter seven
out of ten but it gets harder but that
sounds like we're pretty much like even
if the other one free last ones or four
last ones again more harder I think we
might be fine yeah yeah let's leave it
to death for this site
okay uh I guess it's saved here right if
we continue can we just leave the game
no it's pretty fun because like what
sorry you cut off seven
oh we'll just try we'll just start on
chapter seven okay
hopefully
all right
wow I feel personally very stupid and
partially a little bit smart
uh that is good not as great as my uh
detective investigator and we both got
stuck at certain parts like I think at
the beginning you really figured out a
lot of that stuff ah maybe not sure
well uh I think oh wow what is this next
week is probably not possible to
continue it so maybe the week after oh
sorry guys you will have to wait a
little bit until this continues
because I'll be at dokomi next week very
busy oh yeah yeah yeah
every soon seventh and 8th of oh
actually I think just one day but in uh
the second week of August
oh
that's when I want to talk
yeah yeah uh 14 15 14 15. on one of
those days
I don't know if it's all of those days
to be honest I think just one day yeah
uh we are uh which convinced me what's
it
uh Orlando Maybe oh yes yes
appearance so uh yeah check it out if
you're at the convention I guess
yeah try sending this piano okay someone
you're on camera or one hollow talk this
week I have a perhaps too
well well yeah
one of them is not 100 the
um
yeah public information yeah it was like
people already kind of guess it because
I already gave some hints
it's like
I could probably already say it
oh okay no problem all right oh well
thank you almond for playing with me I'm
glad I'm glad we finally play something
again um we gotta do it more often well
with this game yeah we'll do it at least
one more time at least yeah that's
really fun thank you for playing with me
thank you too
and I think I'll read some super chats I
guess so okay
um I'll I'll see I'll talk to you later
on man okay goodbye everybody enjoy your
Kiara Super Chat really thank you guys
for watching goodbye
yeah man
thank you
wow my dad is meowing at me wait I need
to
wow
[Music]
okay
okay let me close the game and move over
to the super jet reading place
one second
you know because
uh we are recently very much uh caught
up on subject I don't wanna
I don't wanna have that to change
but I guess I'll go into a two minute
break if that's okay
is that okay
superchat intermission
let's do that all right I'll see you in
two minutes
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
sorry that was faster because I'm trying
to assess my
my
my my my my title
I was just talking what's wrong with
y'all
wow she's running around like crazy
meowing mama when I stood up for him
over here I was running around trying to
get me to follow her and then I fell
there and then after a few meters she
flew up in the ground and wanted me to
pet her
audio
huh
yeah sure
okay baby
I think I think
oh wait wait wait
ah okay
uh let me see okay okay we're gonna do
this we're gonna do this fairly quickly
I think
I'm so mad I love you huh guys
[Music]
she's like low-key zooming
I can't decide if the stream was
chilling so I think it wasn't it was
definitely not anxiety it was chill it
was very chill but a bit uh frustrating
for you guys I think because of the
riddles
people get very frustrated when they
understand the riddle before someone
else does
before the streamer does
but I was also trying to not like
completely rely on the chat and read too
much
but you guys were able to do that you
guys were able to get hints from the
chat and then put puzzle pieces together
from the chat and be like oh yeah I
understood that completely all on my own
well you maybe didn't you guys are
looking at the chat aren't you that
might have influenced you if you wanted
it or not
um
interesting that helmet turned off to
chat did she did she really do that like
only on her side like so that she
couldn't see it
why did she turn it off completely
yeah
I'll miss like
I like the way she handles chat
okay
chat was wrong about the time too well I
mean that's that's okay because we're
trying to figure it out together of
course Chad is around sometimes too
um
I guess for the last riddle there was
just like
um
like uh the way we started out was a
connection that was possible but not
possible until the very end
so
like it was able to connect until a
certain point but that's where you know
we were missing parts and that's and
that's why we had to go back and try a
different combination like until a
certain point the combination was was
working and then I just answered another
point it doesn't work anymore so you
gotta try something else
uh interesting that
we figured out so fast that it was the
first one though
the first one that was wrong
um
let's listen
to
some music which one though
this one
yeah
low far let's go
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
happy birthday to your friend I don't
know how to read your friend's name
though if you let me know how to read it
then maybe I can help
[Music]
uh
usual room vision
no the real usual room plays different
kind of music
hmm
I think we I think we got for the last
riddle in a decent amount of time
actually
I was just I was just panicking because
of the time ticking
a cat soundtrack
stuff like that yeah yeah stuff it's
individual like whatever makes you
suffer that's what's playing there
although
well while also trying to make yourself
well we also try to promote uh 10 shows
songs
so that plays at the same time
whatever makes you suffer that's playing
but also spikes whatever most recent
song I have on that I want to be want to
get promoted
in order
[Music]
Italian
foreign
[Music]
yeah for the memories I I uploaded two
new memory remotes before the stream I
want to add a bit more tomorrow because
tomorrow I have my day off and I mean I
gotta prepare a [\h__\h] ton of things like
whole talk and a bunch of things for
hollow talk
and uh oh oh uh Sunday
is actually free streams I will be on
Panama's next Reddit uh stream
did she did she like officially take
over or did she say anything about that
I don't I didn't really follow I didn't
watch the first one she did
but that means that on Sunday I'll have
free streams the first one will be the
Reddit
[Music]
the second one will be uh
something else I don't remember what the
other streams were ah one of them ah
Members Only karaoke and then Zelda
[Music]
she just sort of did it all okay
Okay so
I think it makes sense though because
she speaks somewhat flu
conversational English
and I mean it had to be someone who
speaks decent English
had to be someone who speaks this in
English to take over write a meme review
um
really
Ina
[Music]
cool yeah someday it might get very uh
exhausting actually
but the Reddit meme review should only
be like one hour
the karaoke I'm planning to be like
maybe one and a half hours
and then Zelda
[Music]
oh well maybe four hours without Super
Chat
we will see
uh
[Music]
um
she asked me if I want to be in it and I
said yeah but like um I can't do it at
the usual time
um so it's gonna be in a completely
different time
[Music]
um it's gonna be at 10 p.m jst which is
for me
uh 2 P.M
so it's gonna be before the amazoni and
then I'll have like maybe one hour break
maximum maximum
depending on how on time the club
happens
I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna get up at 5am or stay up
until five I even win even it doesn't
matter that I'm generally up very long
uh for me I don't want to start a stream
after midnight if it's a stream that
starts before and continues on but after
midnight that's okay
but I don't want to continue after
midnight you know what I mean because
that's just that's just not gonna be
good that's gonna go on forever and ever
and ever
and be very exhausting so like after the
midnight I want to like that's my down
time I try to have it my downtime I
don't want to go over it and I'll kind
of set some boundaries you know and with
coco stand by that one time where
uh I had to start at 3am and not five am
I am because the normal time would have
started at 5am I asked her if we can
have it at a different time but I didn't
want to I didn't want to like move the
time too much so
I said 3am but do you like that was also
pretty bad
because it was very long it did it went
down until 5am but that was okay that's
what that was an exception
for Coco Senpai that was fine that was
fine
in terms of time that was also bad for
me
what the shadowverse tournament and I
was in the hospital because I broke my
[\h__\h] neck
all in the 24 hours and then after that
I also had I went to sleep a little bit
but in all those 24 hours I also went to
the Minecraft Summer Festival
and that was insane like all of that
doing all of that in 24 hours I was
insane like I was handicapped uh it
ended up going uh quite well and it was
exciting and all it was worth it but
yeah
[Music]
I don't want that to happen again
it's it's a lot yeah marched on like a
Troopa exactly
forgot about the neck right yeah
that one's still by the way like if I I
can't go any further than this like I I
feel like a block block block blockage
on on the left side and yeah I feel like
also when I go too far to the right side
it's still there it's still there it
doesn't really
obstruct me that much
but it's definitely still healing
um
[Music]
will you'll be streaming on August 2nd
why
I think yeah probably why
August 2nd yeah I'm planning to play
Minecraft
on August 2nd
next week
um
[Music]
next week I I will only like stream in
the first half of the week second half
of the week I'll be gone
but also in uh two parts of the dokumi
where I'll be in are gonna be streamed
like the live performance and the
podcast thingy should be streamed as
well
so everything but the meet and greet
basically you guys can see it on Twitch
as well
ballpark date for the next Honda Memphis
session what does that mean
ballpark thing
is that is that like a way of saying or
something afraid there
[Music]
we'll try and be there thank you
a wrap oh yeah that's next week
on the usual time and uh recently we had
it at different times but it's gonna be
at the usual time on the usual day
oh
on my channel supposedly on my channel
hey I'll be hosting it I guess
oh ref is okay I thought so that was a
weird thing to ask me go to the ballpark
[Music]
and yeah okay
um let me see
[Music]
yeah not this week but next week
this week uh notice
[Music]
ball frank day voice back
why don't you go to the ballpark what is
a ballpark what is a blood plot is that
like when you play like basketball
like a ball court
basketball court
a baseball oh for baseball that's what
they call a ballpark
[Music]
oh
well that is some knowledge that I'll
probably not really use
if your cat's on a walk I wanna I wanna
if you hit something in the area or
something
oh
show my for motion what did didn't you
say you will better yourself
you don't seem to be improving at all
um
[Music]
no problem I was just confused that it's
like well is there a specific reason you
asked about it but it's okay it's okay
no problem uh okay sorry really slow
then that that stream took up all my
brain energy
as we can see
uh but that's uh those super chattels
do I have um
[Music]
I'm not I don't know why I'm yawning I I
took a nap before this week
didn't want to say it but I said it
um
wait
[Music]
is it in my drive this is in my driver
yeah and it's
um I'm fine I'm feeling fine
thank you for asking how are you guys
though how are you I mean again
I'm gonna you know what yesterday was
Monday and I am sometimes orange cat
yesterday my dinner was lasagna isn't
that wonderful oh I love lasagna
[Music]
today I'm gonna eat pizza
tomorrow I'm gonna cook I think
better than earlier a little bit
confused what
tired watching is helping help helping
you watching stuff like this makes me
tired
depending on the content though
now I'm gonna eat tuna Pizza
oh it's pretty good uh
um uh frozen pizza but the frozen pizza
that we have oh this is pretty decent
cook stream one yeah for real like uh
I'm just um
I want to do it again but like it it's
it's uh it needs me to set up stuff and
yeah and and I don't know maybe I'll try
after after don't come and you'll try to
fit it in
yeah because like no no way I can fit it
into next week
no way also this week also too much
going on
[Music]
way too much going on
fish does not belong on pizza with tuna
I think is definitely an exception
tuna Pizza is so good if you never had
it oh my God you're missing out on
something it's really good tuna Pizza
really good oh
actually they have it in Japan too but
there they put on Mayon mayonnaise a lot
I don't really like that I don't like
mayonnaise on pizza but tuna Pizza is
quite the Italian thing I think
that's not just some something that some
country made up I think that's
originally also from uh in Italy
if if you get especially from a good
Italian restaurant and I think you'll
really like it
[Music]
hmm
um
foreign
[Music]
leaves
that is that is a good pizza hmm
no no no no
[Music]
chicken well if it's a big vegan vegan
chicken barbecue pizza
that's good stuff
okay baby baby I'm gonna be with you
soon
oh baby baby baby oh
[Music]
possible while you're at the con see I
will bring my I will bring my laptop uh
uh but
um I don't think
I will have the time except except
except
um
[Music]
on the evening of my arrival perhaps but
during like Saturday Friday Saturday
Sunday
I don't think I'll be
um
I don't think I'll have the time to
stream because well on Saturday I'm
obviously performing and having tested
your laptop nope not yet
um but on the other days I'll be with
um well people so
[Music]
um
so yeah
yeah
it'll be like private private days
[Music]
is that the usual
I'll get the super jet at the end baby
she's finding the the scratch Tree on
her own
it's kicking in she's so cute
[Music]
all right I've said that for the fourth
time now I think
[Music]
Friday is a bread and Jordan yeah I mean
I
in Australian I don't really see Germany
is not really a broad for me
I don't I it is still exciting though
because this will love where tokom
evenly is quite far away
uh Germany in itself is very close
but there's also have this quite far
away
[Music]
it is yeah literally next door
uh mid-rating hydration that will not be
the middle that will be the end
Cleveland foreign
that's a good question well
because I wanted to
I guess I could have done it from being
at home as well but
I want that's that's boring I want to be
there
that's just boring and they were totally
open to it so why the hell not
[Music]
also gives it gives the managers sound a
reason to fly out there
and uh also there's freaking good food
in Dusseldorf I just really want to eat
the food there
is
[Music]
what kind of food Japanese food because
me will be
um has the biggest
um
[Music]
the most Japanese people living there in
all of Germany they are all invisible
for some reason which is why there are a
lot of really really really good
really accurate Japanese restaurants
and yeah
[Music]
the biggest Japanese expand Community I
guess that's the word for it
[Music]
oh maybe maybe General will bring
letters perhaps yeah
[Music]
okay I would have to start reading
Mr can speak
[Music]
to enjoy the game with Ahmed I really
like this game but I learned this game
mostly for streams oh because I don't
have someone to play it with also I'm
trying to find a way to catch up uh your
archives during the day and hopefully
I'll figure it out well good luck with
that you already know how the game works
and once you were here during the Stream
yeah are you sure that's this one though
because there's like free games but they
have all a very similar title
I like I'm gonna play that previously
with Ina she played one we were here too
or we only we were here which one was
the one that they played was it more
difficult
I wonder
was it also it was probably not in the
snow like that right they played the
second one
foreign
they are on the same level of difficulty
it was shorter it was easier okay
there's a there's a split opinions
interesting but Phoenix out
doing okay I'm doing okay we're winning
some time to grasp things and situations
the worst one I think was the elevator
one because that was literally just
trial and error but I wonder if that was
if that really was just what was
necessary and and the one in the in the
cave with the doors and the gates that
one was horrible too because that one
was also mostly trial and error but
maybe that's really just the only option
anyway
um
[Music]
the elevator one
felt very random uh
I'm gonna miss an elevator oh
oh okay because once I went over there
it went
fairly quickly
I guess you missed the one where like I
was able to go down by foot
where I was able to ride an elevator you
know like on top and also inside of it
foreign
did you not realize that she could also
like be inside of it
oh the pickaxe one
oh ah that makes sense switching places
over I always helped so yeah we
definitely need to do that whenever it's
possible and unfortunately it was not
possible in the last two riddles
I am oh well she did a great job with
the with the bridge one
at least from my point of view
everything was working quite smoothly
and fast
can I get my cats really quickly here uh
[Music]
Nicole
yeah
[Music]
let's use the teleport
we have a decent face oh I think so too
because we went for like the like half
of it in less than four hours
but you guys saying that the license
will be more difficult it scares me I
will feel so stupid
I feel so stupid once we get there oh
man
okay
for six uh yeah the one we were at the
end was seven I guess well
thank you Felix
Walker thank you for the rest of my dad
[Music]
hi attention today I'm learning some
English which is used for something
impossible
no no
that reminds me of Santa in your
birthday stream and use incorrect word
absolutely hope you more happy and
comfortable I'm so sorry for my bad
English I have a Wonder have a wonderful
year because you're the best oh thank
you but I've been saying wish in that
situation was totally fine too
if you replace the hope of The Wishes
it's fine too
I think it's fine yeah
yeah
I absolutely wish you more happy and
comfortable sounds sounds about right
doesn't make much difference I think
I wish you a happy birthday yeah I don't
think wish is used for something
impossible
your English is great I care
put put oil in there right
[Music]
thank you the message definitely came
across yeah thank you so much for your
kind words and your generous support
thank you very much
please continue continue supporting me
and do your best with your studies
you'll get there you'll get there you're
already there
is
sorry about that guys
um
sorry about that like uh it was really
weird like I said like the microphone as
the microphone that I wanted it to be
but the game would continuously switch
it back to a different microphone and it
will continue to say disconnected this
one cannot be used blah blah blah it was
so weird and then I tried to do like
like deactivate the ones in Windows
directly uh manually so that the game
wouldn't pick those up anymore the ones
that I didn't want but even then
it used to them anyway and but none of
them none of them ever worked in the
game but I'm a I was also not able to
hear Amish she also didn't hear me so
even on I'm inside it was cursed
[Music]
oh she was fixing the frame rate issue
oh did she fix it in the end
I wonder what caused it
what the hell is that the [\h__\h] was that
foreign
[Music]
thankfully
her fruity 90 seems buggy seems the fact
that really
the walkie-talkies don't make the game
better yeah especially if like I thought
that you
um I found that in the game you can only
hear yours the other person up to a
certain distance
and and that's why I thought it's like
really necessary to use the in-game
audio but but apparently no the
walkie-talk doesn't work anywhere no
matter where you are huh
you said really is your 49 really not
working well
that's [\h__\h] those are so hard to get
aren't they
what
[Music]
yeah I think it was fine that we did it
without the walkie-talkies in the end
thankfully
I just really wanted to fix it but the
game didn't want me to fix it
there's a lot of strange issues with it
yeah
well I'll lose your awesome
General understanding and general grasp
of these kinds of things because I don't
have it
so I have no idea
where to even start
when something happens on my side
because
I have a few things happening with my
AMD as well but I updated the drivers
and I still had something the other day
which I think was closed by the AMD but
I don't know them
um it only happens sometimes though
something's definitely off but as long
as it's not disrupting my streams
hmm
now I have that blue screen of death
and I think
I think I turned it back on and when it
turned itself back on
there was some pop-up from AMD saying
something like
um can we stand up
report
because something happens with the AMD
but I didn't send the report because it
was so it looked so complicated thank
you
[Music]
yeah oh well oh well
um
you microphone fun why
how do I read this
ah riddle reader
thank you for the Super Chat new
microphone friends how to share the
concept why are you microphone fun my
microphone is doing fine
hey but guys do you think my my voice is
weird today or not
do you think it's different because
we've changed a few things
we changed the the short sm7b has
something in the back uh
so we changed that
um because I didn't that was just
randomly there's like three settings
that you can have in the back that makes
it like more flat or
um yeah whatever
I changed that and I changed some things
with on it on in the glory solar
now I don't think you guys can actually
everyone who says they can tell the
difference I think is just imagining it
because I can't really tell a difference
evil
[Music]
um
less peeking hmm maybe
[Music]
Maybe
so honestly I don't know I don't know I
don't know where the problem was before
anyway
and I don't I wouldn't know what the
problem would be now are you guys happy
now with my microphone with my sound
because if you're not then I have
honestly no idea what your problem is
I think it sounds beautiful
yeah you're happy
okay okay
sounds good okay
okay well
I'll take your word for it
from foreign
thank you
Lexington the lion dancing
fgh magic fish tanks
thank you for the pinky I just escaped
basic military training
[Music]
what the did battle against the
U.S for my freedom and the first thing I
want to do is come and say hi to my
favorite chicken
what
I'm not
I don't I don't understand
are you finished or did you just leave
you got out you think you just got out
normally
I'm glad you're back I guess
I'm glad you're back welcome back I
don't know if that was the time where we
were supposed to come back originally
but in any case welcome back and and
please enjoy my streams catch up love
the archives have fun with that we'll
take a while but you'll get there
luckily next uh next week there are some
days off where I won't be streaming now
and uh you can catch up there
thank you
Dominique and will murice
oh last chance thank you everybody
oh
wow she's meowing on the wall what is it
baby
[Music]
what did the wall do to you
oh you're gonna jump up and eyes okay
looking for the top 10 days
did you hear those meows foreign
[Music]
Sparks every time she did
yo that was so scary that thing was so
scary
loud and clear nice
I'm sure 87 thank you for the red super
chat now let me try to understand this
one
did you know that no matter how kind you
are oyster and Australia are kind ah
yeah I guess that makes sense
okay you were trying to use your your
German knowledge that children in German
means Kinder
nice one okay okay okay
I see what you did there
I say once you get there
[Music]
then
um
[Music]
was that by accident
foreign
[Music]
it's okay though it's just a short time
out but
just wondering
and anyway thank you and the shirt 87
wow thank you very much
okay I appreciate the support thank you
for your generosity
uh I hope you enjoyed the stream today
[Music]
um next time you'll give me a riddle
like that
uh give me that riddle after after I'm
done with my own riddles
that one confused me I thought that was
like I thought I was I don't know I
don't know what I thought that was
[Music]
thank you for the thinking good day hot
wings did you ask Kiana yay they might
because I might uh looking a [\h__\h]
beautiful mate
they say [\h__\h] right
number two were great enjoyed the stream
and don't sell yourself short you did
solve some of the puzzles
did I did I know
no we don't huh
don't you say stuff like you four you're
[\h__\h] you're [\h__\h] what wait no
no
[Music]
they do he's lying to you
is this the meme God damn it I got an
iPhone freak Australia me neither sadly
[Music]
a dancing Prince
oh God damn it
I will never learn I will never become a
fake Australian I will always be the
right Australian
foreign
[Music]
I know
um
[Music]
where
uh here okay soon
[Music]
wait one second
I I
I I I
[Music]
um
okay uh Sergey horn dancing
you put so much working hours into your
streams for your chickens and we even
get another member stream okay I don't
get to top it off thank you I love Moshi
of course us I know you guys enjoy
remember is Only karaoke very much
because you guys feel special when I do
that don't ya I want to make you guys
feel special make me feel special
[Music]
yeah
twice
[Music]
you know who I actually uh really whose
music I really like but I always forgot
to mention and I talk about K-pop I love
I love Sunni
I never couldn't pronounce this
correctly but I love sunmi
like
yeah no I freaking love so many oh my
God
and the last album that won the girls
put out
was just Divine
absolutely Divine and everything that
Sumi did in Solo afterwards holy
macaroni exquisite
oh
I I like her too oh
I like her music very much too
I don't like show me a bit more but yeah
[Music]
yeah they are very very talented they
bring out freaking dope songs that stay
in your brain forever
[Music]
you get what I mean
I wish I could pronounce coriander
because since I can't do that
again I can't sing it unless they have
like English songs
[Music]
I know I don't know how to pronounce
their syllables at all
[Music]
yeah they did great in their solo
careers yeah
like haha okay
cool thank you for the red super chat
hello thank you I survived the usual
room and now I don't know what I'm going
to do
with all the free time I have when did I
did I send you to the usual environment
for what I've been thinking about
returning about my friends are telling
me that it's not good for me
honestly I'm confusing very much alone
what to do
[Music]
hey
foreign
isn't that obvious
watch my streams
and streams box then you should not be
confusing very much alone there is only
one goal how is that confusing the goal
is to watch takanasi Kiana
how what what's so confusing about that
that should have been told to talk to
you in the usual room over and over and
over Nova foreign
[Music]
I work with chickens
yeah Chicken brain forget they're
freaking one second
gets out of the usual room again it's in
the usual woman's like yeah
get out of the YouTube room one second
later
Bob
what did I where am I who am I
oh my God that is very troublesome
what am I gonna do with you well
just ride it on your hand
write it on your hand with a permanent
marker do it now and then every time you
don't know what to do you just have to
look at your hand
some
Translate
[Music]
Korean to English
Cube slime thank you Dragon smile thank
you for the pinky
well it was cute saying you slide into
the boatman's dams during a kind of
hookah seems to love you a lot thank you
um
I actually
I I wrote to her before her cataloga
started and
I just wrote
and he reacted to it during her okay and
I just thought it was polite I like I
can't I can't ignore that I cannot
answer I replied but then she kept on
answering and I didn't I didn't want to
disturb her stream or anything
stop answering me on streams so I kept
on answering in DM
I told her that like she sent one little
brother song in the beginning of her
stream and she's kind of well known for
doing like and stuff which I I really
love that because
it's just and she does really crazy with
that game like there's there's way more
like chill with the game which is the
kind of stuff that I learned when I was
at Helen projects band
um
but it really fascinates me how she does
that because it's not not not many
foreigners like non-japanese people know
about
and the chats and all that chance not
many people know about it so her knowing
about it always caught my interest and
um uh yeah and she obviously likes idols
and stuff too so I feel it's like
connection there and um ever since I I
am I ever since I saw her debil I was
like she's my she's my fave she's so
cute
I love I love her personality and her
energy
and uh and yeah the the things that
she's into I also I really really like
that one of the first games she picked
up to play on stream
um after her debut was uh Zelda
um what was that called again A Link to
the Past
the remake
like it kind of reminded me of myself
like going straight for like a I I know
you guys say it's not enough but like it
goes in that direction okay at least
Awakening that was it sorry Link's
Awakening
um I just I I it it felt to me like she
is kind of like like we have a similar
taste in games
and even though dad might not bring in
the most views
we both seem to prefer I mean I might be
wrong but we prefer to play games that
we like very much rather than playing
games that bring in a lot of views and
if that means I'll you know gotta do a
long long RPG over the course of a long
time then that's fine
that's just an impression that I got
um so yeah I like her she's so cute I
love her design too
um because like um
like what her I love her artist isn't
her artist like the designer uh the kind
of designer of uh POI
and and she go there or or am I going
crazy because um I I I I think because I
I was a fan of contact collection before
and I remember that style very very much
so every time I look at her I think of
you dancing it makes me happy
I think I'm right
yeah right yeah
um yeah
yeah I love you daddy boy
I actually all right I have a I have an
IC card sticker with you Daddy on it
because I just really really love the
shiratsuyo class from Kantai collection
I loved you that team
yeah
song
what I want to say is that I like her I
like her very much
and I see you guys in her chat there but
that's fine okay let's go
[Music]
in the beginning I saw some of you with
kfb at the end of your name but uh
yesterday I saw a lot of you guys uh
and decided to take it off whenever you
are in her stream now I will hold
on to you
[Music]
take off and pull down when
ever like a like a badge or whatever and
that's what what that title is to you
huh
no it's okay I think I think that's
probably fine maybe it's for the better
I don't know I mean I I like KFC being
represented here and there but I also I
guess um that like like it kind of like
is maybe something that shouldn't be
brought into like other places maybe it
depends like I I like it both and I
think meow indeed I think that's
something that you guys should decide I
don't I don't really
um
mind either way although I am obviously
very happy when I'm like so when some
other person's chat whoever it is and I
see someone with kfp in their name to
them like oh hey yeah but out of meow
indeed out of respect and and like I
guess like okay why
um like reading the air just for that I
I guess it makes sense to take it off
yeah like going out out in our universe
I guess so yeah so whatever you want
really
um
I think it makes sense to take it off
yeah
oh but I'm not telling you to take it
off
if you if you want to keep it then I
support that till if you want to take it
off I support that as well
[Music]
oh you want the Patty pants
I think like if it was another whole
live stream then you can keep it on but
if it's a non-hallo live stream then I
think it makes a lot of sense to take it
off
[Music]
but I don't know
I don't
I I personally
don't care I think I don't know but you
gotta think about if the other person
cares if they are the streamer that
you're going uh in that person's chat it
matters what they think if they care now
if they don't give a [\h__\h] then that's
cool keep your kfb badge on yeah just be
considerate hmm
inconvenient to change your name maybe
you should have a second account or
something like this
[Music]
um
uh please support Pomo she is adorable
she is uh she deserves all the love
[Music]
please support Pomo I love poem love
poem If you I think I think we're very
not very but we're somewhat similar to I
think I think if you like me then you'll
like
foreign
[Music]
I can imagine that some of you are
already very busy with what you guys are
watching
it's fine that's fine not telling you to
go
out there leave me and find someone else
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
thank you
that's all you can think of my super
chat text is Del SAR Duncan you're
trying to sound smart by predicting what
I'm going to say
no hashtag yolk Stay With Me always
welcome to support other people but
don't forget about me
don't forget about potential the one who
gives you your job I mean I'm not paying
you but you're happy you have a job okay
you have a job here
don't don't just quit your job
Elvis you little [\h__\h] Elvis
that's sweet
uh
[Music]
I'm making fun of bad Idol group names
I I I feel like she's more of a like a
like a anime adult fan most mostly like
icato and and what um uh love life and
stuff
that's the image I have
[Music]
um
uh Direction than me
you know I thought I told you guys
before that you know if you're an idol
fan in Japan
um there's Eva hello project from the
big companies there's zebraham project
or there's akb48
and I mean a bunch of smaller ones but I
I was that was um
have a project is my thing
so
[Music]
friendship gone
yeah the heart the heart of an otaku
connects us
the OTA heart
it connects us no no matter what
Nintendo versus Sega kind of something
like that but made also different
I I don't I didn't watch love life I
have no actually there I didn't watch it
I when it comes to love life I'm more of
an idol medicine person
oh
yeah
I'm sorry
sorry uh yeah idle master
is
although I did I did I don't know that I
love life has a bunch of fun songs too
really good songs as well
[Music]
Eternal from rivalry
yeah we're gonna have a fight we're
gonna have a fight go Bumble fight with
me
for the membership
maybe that's why we ended up in
different agencies
maybe that's why
um
foreign
[Music]
oh my God motion what the [\h__\h]
okay wait Chris Christopher Langley uh
[Music]
message deleted unfortunately
thank you for the pinky can I go home to
answer TV OD and you're still streaming
what a treat yeah it wasn't originally
planning on reading super chats but I
guess whatever
your simple chat ratings are so fun and
I'm grateful to you for taking the time
to read and respond to everyone look for
looking forward to the special surprise
tomorrow oh oh yeah tomorrow
today after tomorrow if you mean the
secret stream
[Music]
but thanks
and I'll be able to read everyone's
messages in front of you so now you can
be sure that I ran and I wanna reply to
you so that you know that I care about
you so
I I will do it as long as it's possible
for me to do it and also every now and
then try to read messages from
non-pinkies and non-writes as well I've
opened up I've been doing that yesterday
a lot and today too I think
yeah I have a break tomorrow
yeah but uh I mean
if you if we talk in my time zone and I
guess today is my break and tomorrow is
the stream yeah yeah if we if we are
that strict then that's correct anyway
[Music]
yeah yeah I'm trying to catch a bunch of
non-red thumb pinkies every now and then
um but uh I usually
like my my my my my when I when I when I
go over the names and say your name is
your name my eye kind of like catches a
glimpse of the message
uh and the sides quickly
if there's something in there that's
like maybe interesting to read
I might still be missing out on a lot of
things that could be interesting but
it's like a really quick moment where I
see maybe some keywords or
um something like that that makes me
interested in reading the message also
when it's a long message I also often
read it
the longer the message even if it's not
a pinky or red one that usually catches
my eye the same same thing on Twitter
honestly when you guys sent me replies
on Twitter
um I kind of like skim through all of
them but the ones that I like are
usually the longer messages after
streams as well
um
I usually give likes to the lava ones
because I don't know
because I feel like you guys the ones
that have a lot of uh like letters in it
they have the most feedback and they
feel feel like I don't know like my
finger just pushes the like button for
some reason more on the essays yeah
then on the shorter ones
yeah a lot of you already write the
maximum amount amount of letters after
each stream
foreign
[Music]
catch
it just bumped into my door and then
they ran away
guilty sometimes
a man of a few words that's okay too
that's okay and I probably read your
messages on Twitter too I just tend to
like the like push like on the longer
ones more for some reason
now with themselves not with a ball
like I can't chew now I catch you
[Music]
why are you guys so confused about that
how do two people or cats play cats with
another well one time the cats catches
the honor cat oh the other time once
that cat cat is caught then the cat
that's so tongue breaker tongue twisted
then that cat tries to catch his catch
the other cat once that cat caught the
cat cat and it goes the other way and
that cat tries to catch the other cat
hey I made up a new tongue twister
hi baby
very busy cat
ah okay that's tag oh [\h__\h] okay
yeah but
no I mean you could say that that's
catching too anyway whatever what is
this discussion
[Music]
whatever whatever
chunk is already exhausted and laying on
the ground now
I like that nickname
thank you thank you motion thanks for
the pinky and I see you you made a
something like a no that I guess wait
that's uh no a total that's a red one
huh oh
[Music]
motion
oh thank you
I'll read all of them even though
there's some in between
you asked for this win I bet I beat
Anthony Ferris and they did so here's my
thoughts honestly when I first started I
thought it would end up as my least
favorite athlete why there was a lot of
walking that I only really cared about
fairies
her desire to leave her cavetown and go
outside was nice and I wasn't happy with
the news we all right it started in a
cave town I completely forgot this but
that was really pretty
and I wasn't happy with the new
synthesis I don't remember that system
at all after completing the Alchemy exam
the game really opens up in my opinion
of the game flipped
you get this cool groom that flies
really fast and makes traveling really
easy
ah
I think I never got that far
[Laughter]
enjoyed the character stories of Liana
and Ill Mary I love it Maria selfie and
Plaza got added to the party and they
had fun interactions
I feel like I remember that
oil
I know they probably no no I just saw
them around in the story and they I
guess they joined later on huh
my favorite artillery or anything but I
can say I really enjoyed it by the end
so in terms of games
left I got is Lady and someone else well
I think you remember that one the most
I'm excited no I I didn't finish that
one either not at all but I I started it
and I I love I love
uh the character designs
they're they're so cute they are so cute
they are so cute
they're so cute oh my God
lydian cell
um
what game did you finish
[Music]
named my first chicken Kiana you're not
the only one who does that with Harvest
Moon
oh man but are they cute they are cute
they're so pretty
[Music]
I did finish rise I wanted to hide it
oh thank you motion congratulations on
clearing and finishing the game good job
well then
we'll have fun with Olivia and so well I
guess
let me know how that one was
[Music]
looking forward to you uh emotions about
that one
but don't forget to watch my streams
yeah yeah priorities always remember the
priorities technically she finished
Minecraft true but we were talking about
Atelier games I think specifically
[Music]
is still one of my favorite things here
yeah me too honestly I think most of the
viewers that were watching that
had no real idea about them about
Atelier beforehand and really got
introduced to it by me mostly or like
maybe you heard of it before but this is
the first time you really watched
someone play it and all that and but you
guys were very open to it and you just
went with it and um we we really grew
together we learned together because I
up until that point I just played Angela
games
in the worst way possible
but this time I actually really tried to
understand the game and we did it
together and it was really um
enjoyable and a big big Improvement
there I think yeah
oh a cute game
[Music]
never heard of this game before the
player introduced it to me
[Music]
you pretty much introduced me to a lot
of games nice
foreign
into all those kind of streams really
but I mean I'm not surprised the people
who are watching the Super Chat reading
usually uh go to the RPG streams too
that one boss battle Yeah
I mean they have a couple that there
were a couple ones that stayed inly
memory
but if you mean the very last one from
ryzen one yeah holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
that was so scoffed so on the level
didn't even have the the final uh
scale thingy
so good so good
Lexington the lion dancing thank you
digital girl yeah I was thinking of
covering that at some point
uh just like kitten dancing oh you can't
put my pineapple literally cannot unsee
it honestly I was just trying to tell
her that because she would say she said
she said she was drinking tea for her
voice and I said you should try a
pineapple juice but then the moment I
have I saw people in a chat spamming
pineapple and Moses when I realized wait
she looks like a pineapple
she literally looks like a pineapple
oh that's funny how did no one ever
nothing
now I used can't be my name because well
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Alice
up until now you did not have Jenna simp
in your name as far as I remember I
remember oh I just tried to ignore it
but I don't think you had it in there
before
you're just trying to trig on me right
now make me jealous or whatever not
gonna work not gonna work
thank you they can't feed my son name is
silent
it is not only silent it is also
invisible spending time for whatever
reason weird must be a YouTube bug right
thanks for the pinky
science secret identity Studio
Ohio
[Music]
I'm always working during casting but
their tails Ambassador really impressed
me sorry not the kfb employee but kfb
service is great thank you you're
welcome uh yeah there will be another
Tales of Ambassador stream this week
because surprise surprise which one
could it possibly means
the secret one on my schedule
I'll announce it ASAP
thank you for waiting
um that one is requiring a lot of
artwork uh a lot of time a lot of
preparation
wow but it's gonna be worth it I'm so
honored to do stuff like that honestly
from all the sponsorships I had until
now
um working with hands over rice is not
only the most fun because I love the
game series obviously but also because
um they provide
so much
um materials that makes it so much more
interesting to show you the game like
they give me exclusive material and they
provide me like proper guides like that
that I'm not 100 bound to of course but
give me like an idea of uh like what I
need to convey and in what order would
be good and all that and what what
material should be used uh at what point
them blah blah
like they're doing a great great job in
like
giving me what I need in order to make
the best out of the sponsorship they
take it very serious I think and I
really appreciate that
and and and all I wanted to say today
like they just they they didn't just
like pick me and then like you know
laugh at that no they I definitely
noticed that they did their research on
me
uh because like
first of all choosing me for that
sponsorship was first of all smart and
proof that they did their research
number two like something like they know
that I like drawing
and they also invited Ina because they
also know that she's very good at
drawing makes sense right then the next
stream let's be real is gonna be Tales
of arise hello talk
which means they did their research they
know that I do hold a talk they know
it's an interview talk show they know
they know it would be good too
um have like
a like a collaboration there
um to combine that into one thing
yeah
I'm I'm just so fascinated that they
that's the best sponsorship I have ever
had
um
members knowledge sounds oh
special version of the whole talk yep
um
tails off top
[Music]
I really appreciate that
um
there I I guess we call that what um
promotion to email or advertisement team
or whatever whoever's in charge they
know what they're doing
um us
nice
marketing team that's the word
social
level
[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
thank you
thank you okay let's finish this super
dance
that's been a while
uh
don't worry about it
don't worry about it don't Joseph thank
you for the pinky thank you for the
undercut I'm looking forward to it best
Ambassador thank you I'm so happy that
there's you guys also excited about it
that there's other tennis offense in my
community uh because that's that's just
that that's just awesome
big thanks for being the sunlight of my
life every day thank you
[Music]
the origins of Emperor that's true
uh anyway I'll do my best though Joseph
so look forward to it
um there's still a lot of great content
coming out until the release of it from
my side so let's go
spanking
is this better thank you for the pinky
um
you could have just put it at the end
but if you would like to put it put it
there right in the middle yeah yeah okay
so
okay so middle in the center of
attention no that's that's good that's
that's fine okay
thank you I'm sure you will change it
though
I'm sure you'll be embarrassed to keep
it and you'll change it soon
[Music]
thank you
foreign
subs don't worry about the my contact
problems I'm proud of the effort
oh cause you're a Slowpoke oh oh
I was very confused about that
and while the Edward you put it in your
Mario series is fun slow
cute I guess that's two slippers hey
yeah he's he's 800 actually 900k behind
that's so yummy you gotta you gotta
speed up a little bit Slowpoke focus
focus focus Slowpoke Focus
ing
I'm not a chicken
no I didn't finish it well that's it
guys I finished your super chats you owe
me a lot
thank you thank you for the chill chat
uh
had a great time
um tomorrow I'll work on my stuff
um
uh prepare everything also I started
the whole talk of asuki senpai I started
uh uh collecting questions so if you
have something interesting to ask please
write it in the community post and I
think you said bye uh
um
[Music]
I need you guys to come out of your
shadows and uh
give me some good knowledge I already
have some interesting knowledge already
though I am because like she did a lot
of life
um
live activities live performance
activities and like life houses and
stuff from what I've seen really
interesting so I definitely want to talk
about that
asuki fans are scared of you sending
them to the usual
why
if they're helpful I would never do that
mine's too busy yeah I know that's why
you guys need to watch the whole talk
then but the ones the few ones in here
who know stuff about her please
please
I would never do such a thing
what is fruit Bata what
what does that mean
is that inside knowledge about I don't
know that
thank you for the Super Chat lft
asking questions
good one rude bitter
[Music]
he has a Blog
okay you seem like you know your stuff
go go go and ask me questions in the
community post on YouTube
on the English one
please
okay anyway that's it for today guys
thank you for watching tomorrow is my
day off but I'll be around and the next
stream will be the secret one right uh
let me see
yeah uh The Day After Tomorrow the next
stream will be the secret one which is
um
half of a rise whole talk
very very very very special guest
very specialist
uh
um I I hope you guys can come up that is
however uh on the time slot that is on
the schedule not the usual holotalk time
so it's a bit later it's uh I'm gonna be
at 10 p.m my time
yeah so I'm excited about that I hope
you guys will be there I know last time
[Music]
thank you guys for watching
I love you you're too hard times in one
week is uh yeah but actually this one is
pre-recorded there will be Parts in our
life as well but most of the stream will
be pre-recorded
I'll be doing the beginning and the
ending in in life and then the whole
interview part it will be pre-recorded
so at least that is already done
but still preparing two Hollow talks
and for one week is taking up a lot of
money brain and time
yeah I hope it will all go well
oh please please please let the azuki
fans know that I need their support and
their help you're at school
[Music]
will it be long yeah it'll be like two
hours
[Music]
no live studio you guys will be will be
the live studio audience watching a
pre-recorded stream
[Music]
becoming a game's journalist I feel like
it honestly I feel like it especially
during that interview
hmm
no the chat will be live the chat will
not be pretty quiet I kept I kept the
screen open you know the table the desk
where I usually put the screen I put I
left it open for you guys I left the
spot for you guys
that's normal talking about nah I'll try
to you know go back with the time but
the whole top one is like supposed to be
two hours so I ended up the tails off
one is supposed to be two hours but the
one without might be shorter again
anyway anyway anyway
thank you guys and bye bye
um
[Music]
do your best everyone and whatever
you're gonna do today or tomorrow
do your bestest
live the day as if it was your last one
[Music]
thank you