[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hi
[Music]
hi guys
I just I might need like three more
minutes because I just got one of my
album songs back from mixing and all
that
the deadline for my producers tomorrow
so I have to give feedback really
quickly
okay wait it'll be four minutes
[Music]
thank you
let's go
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
it's okay I'm done
uh gosh it's so [\h__\h] hot
it's so hot I'm like in a hot pot oh my
God
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is so hot
cat hair
ah hi thank you for
letting me
have some time there thank you oh
left right left
right here maybe here
at the end of GTA
yeah I don't know I mean it's not like I
have a gangster outfit or something like
that
um
or do I
I'm in
oh man
I'm so tired and it's hot and [\h__\h]
[Music]
um
stressed out because a deadline for
everything is tomorrow but things are
not ideal
but it hasn't been finished
I don't even know oh man
um I don't even I
[Laughter]
it's gonna be okay though hopefully
um
oh my God thanks for the memberships
yeah
uh do you need more time do you do you
say need more time yay
maybe but no I don't know
sorry I was talking to Windows
do you do you say
I can spoiler do you because people
already know do you let's go
ah damn I just listened to the song now
I have it in my head not do you but the
other one
until
June
don't accidentally sing it I'm trying
Mamma Mia
a game capture and
GTA
hey hey
oh my God sound is working aren't we
excited
I just have to move my screen and my
chat over there
oh
shh
what the [\h__\h] is this on the
what
[\h__\h] stupid things
go away go away go away okay
ah I didn't add any new music uh why is
game so small small just smaller smaller
game window
why small small game window
smarter smartest man again
oh
the Smash Bros I'll just size it up on
obs
[Laughter]
that meme
uh to oh because game uh yeah layout I
showed that Meme to my best friend and
then I gave her smaller smaller gift
from Japan
I gave her a small small Note book like
really smartest mod and small to small
depends
and I said maybe small small small cheat
uh cheating
in school and she said no I can't I
cannot do s'mores marketing cannot do
any small small sitting or any cheating
because too dangerous to cheat at a
university
but she liked it um
it's really really small small like so
small
so the pens are literally like as long
as maybe half of your pointy finger
unless you have really long fingers then
it's maybe even less than half of your
pointy finger
um
University student here do it cheat ah
no from what you told me it's like
really dangerous because if you get
caught doing it once then it will be in
all your records at least here
um
actually it was a joke anyway like I was
just thinking like what can you use such
a small paper and small pens for
and I mean
it's obviously a joke gift but
she doesn't need to cheat she's super
smart and she's really
really good girl
yeah I'm not gonna make her into Rihanna
good girl gone bad oh
oh let's go another 10 minutes of the
loading screen anybody are you up for it
no it's good
let's get destroyed always
it's been so long where am I what are we
doing so last time my game
everything crashed everything
went wrong that's a nice kid wait you
have a we have our own laptop now
I'll have to go to the computer internet
cafes and [\h__\h] anymore
that's a lot of pots and [\h__\h] even
though I don't use it
was that espresso machine
I don't drink coffee so I don't really
know much about it
but I think I recognize it
sink on the kitchen counter interesting
never saw that before
it's supposed to be the vehicles that
crash though what what are we talking
about what are we talking about
oh
free wall and oh small
head it looks like a bed out of Sims
smaller smaller bed and it IKEA lamp
what the [\h__\h] who bought this stuff
press it change clothes oh yeah you know
what what why are we why are we wearing
this and what are we what what uh view
glasses
do we have glasses
ah you don't own any glasses
um but let's change back into our
beautiful clothes huh
what okay
and then shoes
we have nicer shoes than this
remember
we gotta be dripping it's like our last
GTA weekend oh sexy
[Music]
I'm bringing sexy back
is it like those [\h__\h]
okay that's all the lyrics I know I
should not know
I want to sing that one time
man good old Justin Timberlake was it
somebody please fix that for say because
dang it do be dripping
who's Anna Rex
let me look at her
oh wow what's with that Apple she died
oh no
is that a reference to
was there a poisonous Apple involved
with Adam and Eve
but I don't need one right now
I don't remember what we were up to what
are we doing what how to play this game
are you selling pictures
I don't want to buy a hot dog I want to
buy a picture
this is hot dogs what soft as [\h__\h] no
softest buns right here
I know what it is stop blackmailing my
friends Dimitri you do not want to anger
me more
I don't know those people
let's be friends I made the mistake of
working with you before it's not one
I'll repeat
goodbye
have we heard this conversation before
because the ending sounds familiar to me
you [\h__\h] think you're too good
for these
I mean generally
some of these are fresh
honestly with like stand like these when
I walk by them when I'm hungry often I
feel like I would like to try it
but okay not even like these like we
don't really have stands like this in
Austria much I have I don't see them but
like a little bit more like bulky
um
stands that almost look like a building
but not really like kind of like a
container
so we have those and they kind of
intimidate me and I I don't I don't know
I want to try it but
I never feel like
I don't know do you guys
make use of this
they're good yeah they can be good I'm
sure but I just I don't know like they
they scare me too sometimes because the
people that are around them eating
things a lot of the time where our
not looking very nice like and I smell
alcohol and they look like it's like
usually
[Music]
um
it scares me
uh like it's after the hot spot for
weird people
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
oh dear God these people are funny
yeah
you'd fit right in shut up you mean
tourists no no no no no no no no no
tourists just yeah like sketchy looking
people sometimes but not sketchy like
like I don't know
um
yeah it's it's it's
an interesting type of sketchy
a small price to pay for like a lot
there's no elote here there's no elote
here
um I've never seen a lot I should make a
lot of myself oh I should
yeah
oh I should I should I should
by the way because I wanted to drink
something really cold and chill and
because I'm also still a little bit
tired I have an energy drink and I'm not
afraid to drink it
it's really refreshing right now
oh no uh
ouch
what is this
cute
cute suits cute outfits messages I'm
just chilling but thank you for
what Nico I'm having a panic attack meet
me at po45 love Bernie wait is this uh
the gay guy
because
I don't remember the names anymore and
that that that sounded uh yes okay it
sounded like him
I I got
I got I gotta help him out okay I need a
car
now it's my car you must pay for what
you've done to me ooh nice car though
it's a decent car
not sports car
I would say but it looks okay
don't you agree
it cool trade right
I agree okay no no no radio for now
because I don't want to hear any of that
I hate music
I hate Sound
I hate
hearing anything
I want to listen to silence because
that's all there is in my heart and in
my brain mostly in my brain
is silence
out trying to warm up man
today
and I need I need this right now
ah
we are going to finish this game this
weekend
apparently you guys told me I'll need so
and so much more time probably
I don't know if it will be a close call
or if it will be easy in terms of time
but we have today and tomorrow
and then another time when I'm late when
I'm feeling like I have nothing else to
play I'm gonna pick up the DLC but not
not right away you know not immediately
because yesterday I was just like
looking at my schedule for next week
because I thought
I should probably set up a collab
I'm sorry I'm sorry oh my God how come
that didn't eh
oh my God that scared me so much
see see this is that this is not a good
sign if if you're so [\h__\h] terrified
of bumping into the police when you're
just like carefully
treading food uh uh uh traffic then that
means there's something seriously wrong
with the police okay
oh God
that's good
what was I saying oh yeah I was thinking
I think I should plan a collab
um
that is by like a part I looked at it
and it was so scared of me it fell down
terrified everybody's terrified of me
this is probably acid rain too
um but yeah so I was looking through our
games permissions uh to find to remind
myself of games that uh might be good
for two people
and I didn't find anything instead I
found in the middle of like really
really back back back back
I I I found this whole soda heal me uh I
found Boulder skate perms what the [\h__\h]
which is weird because
is this alcohol
the soda right
um
what was I gonna say yeah you have
really really really really far back I
found the burns and we were like still
waiting on it like to have somebody
notify us when the parents are ready
because last time we checked they
weren't ready which is only a couple
days ago but now I find them far back
and I think it was like sort of
chronologically in terms of when the
perms come in and I found it so far back
and I'm like what the [\h__\h] yeah so I
notified our Baldur's Gate group where
is he
and yeah we immediately got to plan
because uh Bijou wants to play it
immediately
oh
and Cali also wants to play it quickly
so she is
she is
um sacrificing her sleep for it
[Laughter]
yeah we're gonna play on Tuesday we're
still like figuring out some things
because we're unsure ah
we're unsure about a lot of things like
Kelly did some research
um she also played alone on her own time
apparently a little bit already but she
says that it's like really the friend of
multiplayer and like there's different
ways of doing it like even you join in
the beginning and something about NPCs I
don't know I don't know I don't
understand this is what I
was like kind of asking you guys about
last time though like this kind of stuff
like Logistics Logistics you know
um
so I I don't know 100 yet how we're
gonna do it but there will be a host I
guess and then
and then that will influence it somehow
I don't know what's going on
yeah
this is the price you pay when going in
blind whatever is always a first time to
playing multiplayer and all
um
[Music]
is there no Japanese version of balder
is good is that why Japanese members
aren't playing it I mean they might not
even be interested in general but
it was for free yeah but I'll just get
for
kids Bernie what's wrong nothing sweetie
cute basket are we going picnic you're
the lucky one what you could slice
cheese on those puppies because he loves
my cheekbones without cheekbones
been thinking of getting implants but
you sounded hysterical oh sometimes I
can't bear to be alone
I'm so glad you've come back into my
life you may not be able to slice cheese
with your cheekbones but with your nose
you might be what are we doing here
we're going to have fun it's a nice know
fun yes not crook but nice but we can
still ride look long straight no what we
did then alive
I'm working for the mafia he's probably
not happy about that at the government
agency are both on my case the [\h__\h]
I'm leaving
can Fritter It Away online and pay off
debts might be a bit loud a while
people are trying to kill us
what is fun
honey
me are stressed yes I am goodbye Florian
no no no no no no no no you don't Nicole
I
know he has the basket explaining to be
a shepherd
and you wanted to be a professional
wrestler
is he taking me on a nice picnic with
the with the boat
you understand me both of me come on
keys on purpose somewhere I could steal
them oh you drive I'll work on my test
I'm
[Music]
fine I'm all right
let's mid wait where's your midriff
somewhere in the middle right is he
getting naked on on the boat
what a physics
okay
time to get naked I mean I guess I don't
honestly I don't see much sun in the sky
you might not get buried ground turmoil
I think she's suspects
a nightmare I don't know how else I can
help you look how long it took me to
find you I know sweetie let's forget
about him and have some f u n
f u
h
yeah so true so true I love him that
damn British water
yesterday I was swimming in the pool and
I have to say it was a little bit wobbly
not British levels of wobbly but it was
suspiciously wobbly so
[Music]
it is haunting me
that it was still like totally
acceptable
[Music]
shoot guys off the starboard I think
they're gonna shoot us
let me see
they don't look like they're on the
pleasure crew ah there we go
foreign
get out of here do I shoot them hell
yeah I'm shooting while driving now
oh my God multitasking license
it barely moves like curves are so
difficult with it I don't know I just
got to get these guys so they'll just
come back
people are after me and I have to stay
alert is the right gun to do this with
let them keep your eyes open they're
wide open sweetie let's focus
100 oh I don't have my choice
I guess I can't carry the others right
now with only one hand is that the
problem
oh
uh no no you're not making me drive
there I'm gonna yeah
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is he doing
is he gonna go to the rides
[Music]
this reminds me a little bit right now
of uh it's not it takes two or what was
it that I played with Cali where we had
this boat ride around the end it was
really dramatic oh I got one
I finally got one who fell into the
water a way out yeah
yeah
what was the location was it also
inspired by real life
[Music]
by real City
because it looks similar to where we are
now
that was that on the river oh sh no not
policiano
and what the [\h__\h] man
how far is the reach of this gun
[Music]
oh the stars are gone at least that's
beautiful
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
I want to drive closer but I'm slow and
my curves are [\h__\h] ah what am I doing I
should have stayed on the left oh no
[Music]
um
what now
is
what I do
how like this place is really good
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah come on
you don't do these shoot chases on a
[\h__\h] boat that's stupid
is this my apartment
ah where's my message
my redo message here there we go
huh
suddenly this game is being nicer to me
there are some great things playing on
Burlesque at the moment musicals aren't
really my thing Bernie you should go
with price Bryce would never be seen
with me at a player people would ask
questions I'll get them this time guys
tragedy
so dramatic
[Music]
late game privileges really
daddy record a lot of dialogue for these
games huh
I watched the video yesterday about GTA
um like if it's coming what's what's
going on
cute guys and it was showing some
footage from maybe scratch that
I don't know if it's either like a
modded GTA let's skip this again
they don't look like they're on the
pleasure Cruise a model GTA or or just
another game that looks like GTA but
like like in really really HD
uh no it was like a lot of footage of a
car driving through a street button in
beautiful graphics
and I really hope that in the future it
will look like that
I think
[Music]
I think it looks modded or something
yeah
[Music]
come on come on come on I know it's
coming out on the other side I will not
go there
you
come back okay
uh okay wait
oh it's gonna use gonna use Ram oh wait
I want that too
[Music]
I can't do any special tricks I'm so
sorry oh no oh no oh no it's kind of
diagonal that's kind of diagonal
out of physics [\h__\h] stunt jump completed
oh that counted as a stunt jump
when I attempt this with cars it never
works
[Music]
come on I gotta get closer oh God
ah [\h__\h] hell
[Music]
closer Bliss
where are we going next ah there's
another ramp he's not using that well
let me try them
many more stuff jumps to complete after
all
[Applause]
is this realistic can I put like this
really do this
I'm completely
[Music]
I may not be styling much when killing
these people but those fat jumps are
styling
I'm gonna run out of freaking ammo
[Music]
oh this is where I died before
are they talking to me
[Music]
because I don't have any stars
it's confusing me
[Music]
what
that was not me and this why are they so
far
is that bad that they reached land I can
still chase him right
can I get off to him
wait wait it's easy I'll just put them
from here
we go backwards backwards please
you still think I'm going around don't
get up
is he dead but this one another one
isn't there [\h__\h] [\h__\h] how do I get off
uh FFF but what do I do about my friend
Bernie
is this okay
where is he
oh he's right there
I forgot how to play this game
[Music]
okay Bernie you stay safe and wait for
me was this script that wasn't supposed
to happen anyway
hush
if I talk to Bernie is it gonna cut the
chase that's wonderful I think it does
shoot them
hang on I'm sorry our fun day wasn't so
very much fun that was fun I did some
stunts and all that
would have been more fun if you would
have showed me your your mid-rift though
yeah
uh hi hi hi hi hi hi
there go my stars
wonderful
cycle that's best outcome
except for all the ammo that I lost
um
okay uh we're gonna get like another job
another phone call
usually they follow oh orange beautiful
muscle car with muscle car or low low
[Music]
um
soccer
yes
let's not drive over the police man
since I'm not getting a call I guess I'm
gonna go
oh it's so far
we have Phil Bell Phil Bell who
or Derek
and maybe I'll drop off this car at home
where is home
here home
cave B Ryder cave be mobile Derek is the
cursed Mission
you mean cursed as in ah okay
uh
uh wait which is the nicer home this one
or that one this one right this one must
be this one
I think it's that one
oh I never ramp that's asking me to use
it but no no no no no I got this new
fancy car I'm gonna bring it home where
it belongs
okay
the police car chase what
[Music]
what police car chase
I I remember me trying that several
times and
failing several times actually I don't
want to do it
I don't want to do it
that was so difficult
what's up with that difficulty Spike man
just go aggressive
um
we'll have to try a few strategies
I can't oh [\h__\h] I forgot about that
okay that's enough
[Music]
was he really trying to turn around on
this one way path
[Music]
um
not a very smart man
I'm going this one right yeah okay
stay here stay here
yes
see I I am very aware of my map
I am aware of everything that's going on
in my surroundings okay
small felony
I forgot though I
I I didn't want to I've been paying up
so many times already
I really forgot oh you know what I want
that bike next
you think I'm gonna go to that mission
yet I'm not mentally ready for all the
anger that it will cause me I'll go here
first Phil Bell was a different one
right
foreign
is it gonna heal my car
when I'm gone also we should get armor
armor armor upgrade update upgrade up
Refresh on the armor
yeah okay
um
when we're going there there's an armor
Place really close so let me go here
all right
so let me tell you yesterday I had pizza
pizza
I have some leftover pizza too I was
looking forward to bringing home
leftover pizza
um
I got to have
um Hawaii pizza because all of my
friends uh or almost all my friends like
Hawaii pizza too Hawaii is pineapple by
the way
with some nice
oh I think one
it's really high quality ham or
prosciutto or something I don't know
and uh with corn
and then I had a tuna with onions and
corn because my friend my bestie she
also loves tuna with onions and corn
and had a margarita and not the cocktail
but the pizza
obviously
and now I had two weird pizzas that
actually only I had only one of them
um
uh
there was a
zucchini pizza with
zucchinis on top and instead of tomato
sauce it was like mashed zucchini sauce
and on the other hand there was sweet
potato pizza with mashed sweet potatoes
and ricotta cheese on top
which and the others really enjoyed it
seems like it because it's kind of like
a you know
different veggie Healthy Pizza
um
I only tried the zucchini pizza because
I couldn't imagine the
sweet potato pizza even really being
that good because I I like sweet potato
but not that much
you put it on a pizza I love zucchinis
though and it's zucchini pizza I mean it
was good but it's like
it doesn't really feel like a pizza
anymore if you really want love zucchini
and you want to eat something with
zucchini it's interesting as its own
dish
hmm
it's interesting as its own dish just
don't think of it maybe as a pizza no
but yeah my friend is like experimenting
with uh different kind of pizzas thanks
for remember
um
[Music]
zucchini berry water it doesn't it
wasn't watery at all though it was like
really like the consistency the texture
was
really really good
uh the flavor was maybe a little bit too
mild though
that was good it was uh interesting
little
and oh
colorful car
and what else did I have I tried a
little bit of uh Loki spicy salami pizza
pepperoni
uh it was good but since it was spicy I
didn't want to fill my tummy too much
with it I'm not good with spicy stuff
anyway
um body armor
yeah do I need anything I don't think so
what's their helmet doing
can I buy this helmet too
see what can shoot her okay see you too
thanks man for helping me out all the
time
I dropped it was I wearing a helmet I
don't remember that
yeah and then I think that's
mostly about it
uh and then for dessert
we had
fried pizza dough
um that you know it's like little pizza
straps but when you fry them they become
like they blow up
they fill up with air inside and they
become kind of round
even though they were only strips
and they're covered in sugar and
cinnamon which is amazing and then
topped with some chocolate sauce and
open place are you gonna open this thank
you
mascarpone and chocolate sauce and
topped with some berries like
strawberries and raspberries Etc which
is a dessert that I love
um
good for leftover dough when making
pizza and then one of the friends that
was there made matcha tiramisu but I I
don't know I was full and I prefer
like tiramisu generally when it has a
coffee taste I don't like it and matcha
I like but not that much that I would
eat it all the time no I didn't eat it
really was good though
two spoons
so good food yesterday
really good food
okay yeah I gotta go
headshot Ciao Bella
who's the pal feel your mama Nicos go
friend of mine
sure we could talk as long as we don't
talk too much interesting times you know
what I mean did you hear about our
friend the guy with the thing yeah you
mean Harry the uh Graphics
like me
yeah that guy
vocabulary very good so be cool ray
listen same just like me
that's the thing I kind of know what
you're gonna ask and I can't what do you
mean you can't I can't do it Phil I got
a lot of interest right now business is
really taken off and I don't want any
distractions well as you could see I got
my own issues here look Nico is good
he'll do what you need and you say he's
a friend I guess
sure good to meet you yeah come here
hey
try it this big chunk of brown they're
desperate to get rid of talking about it
all over town wanting to offload it at
any price they think it's cursed or
something I didn't get a massage yet
take it from them it floated into a
truck going to Franklin Street and West
Side get a hold of it and give me a call
sure track okay but Mr Bell it's going
to cost you no problem
we want some good money hey nice stereo
you got there Phil thanks yeah so Philly
if you hear from your ex-wife what kind
of question is that
every time
oh
[Laughter]
who's that
we just drove away
the other guy Nam alone what the [\h__\h]
all right
[Music]
very good fun and uh
upon
10 out of 10 would do it again I left
earlier than the others because I needed
to
get home at a
decent time everybody was drinking like
cocktails at the end and you know
I'm like my friends but
um I wanted to get home okay
and I got home pretty late anyway so
yeah
I I leave early and then they said oh
yeah party
party kind of hypocritical because you
always like wow please come to this
please come to this now because without
you it's gonna be boring but then then
they say when I leave that's when the
party really starts and like what the
[\h__\h] that makes no sense
you always want me to be there because
you say without being boring but when I
go you know but it's because they start
drinking alcohol and all that and I
don't really join them so they generally
want me to be with them
but when it comes to alcohol they're
fine without me
about them
because because I don't want to be about
around a group of drunk people
yeah they're just messing with you yeah
yeah they're just joking I know they
they need me to be there because I'm
I'm a little bit of
I don't know I I guess I guess I'm kind
of like the one of the glues
that holds our group together I can't
okay
and they sniff me
because they love the glue
interesting part
you know
I'm the cool girl too
eh
no I think I I am okay
[Applause]
what's happening
do I shoot the people that come out
I'm just taking the truck right
that's what I remember I'm taking the
truck
do I have to sneak
oh I think I have to shoot I mean look
there's so many people and where's the
truck all the way over there that one
try yourself
look at him waddling like a duck
uh
ah
what's that Bruno Mars song
the Grenade song
am I not gonna like throw this against
this wall and like blow myself up
yeah
how does It Go sing it for me guys
I'm totally going to do that
eh
[\h__\h]
what what is this beautiful scene
enough
reset me already
ah I will catch a grenade for you why
did nobody catch a grenade for me
we'll catch a grenade yeah
I would die on the street fire yeah yeah
just so you can steal the truck yeah
yeah I would catch the grenade for you
oh
but I keep throwing at
the wall in front of me and I keep
killing myself
what the [\h__\h] man
[Music]
and I need armor again huh Nanda why why
why why why why why we're steady
spaghetti my armor yeah
where does that reset my armor what the
[\h__\h]
yeah because I died but I
know man
no we traveled back in time I should
still have my armor
okay man okay life's not fair
ah wait did Bruno Mars
what the [\h__\h] are you singing about I
love Bruno Mars songs but
does he mean he would catch a grenade
for somebody
that is
extremely dangerous and dramatic and
what the [\h__\h] that is explosive as [\h__\h]
man are you sure
does he understand what he's singing
about
I don't think he gets it I don't think
he understands I mean I understand you
know it's like yeah I love you so much I
would die for you but
I mean
hey man
it's fine if the pin is still in didn't
say the pin was pulled yeah okay but
then it's really not you know then it
makes even less sense
that makes even less sense to me
okay we're not gonna try the [\h__\h]
grenade again
or are we no no look at the Riskin I'm
not gonna risk it I'm not gonna risk it
[Music]
now we go
it's still so great here because it
thinks I'm still dead every time you die
it turns into gray monochrome mess I
think that's what they're trying to tell
me
Chihuahua be careful you're half dead
right now
don't do it again don't do it
um
anyway yeah I did my swimming reps
yesterday even though pool was small
smaller pool
but barely it fell it felt I was barely
swimming because I you know you keep on
interrupting yourself in the middle of
swimming
my friend was doing the the cool
swimming style by the way that I talked
about so I asked her if she can teach me
she said she doesn't know if she knows
how to explain it
but I think I think she can
smooth
small pool is small okay
freestyle I guess yeah she was wearing
like
water goggle
and had her face underwater
that style of swimming apparently what I
meant was froggy style the frogs really
swim like that then even more doesn't it
make sense that I'm froggy Wawa
or I'm related to Prague
swimming frog Style
because I am frog
Nami ah you guys
I'm gonna fail this again what what's
with these missions man what's with
those missions
okay we just got a brute force it we
just got a bird forces
[Music]
just gotta brute force it
so
one of my friends actually has been
playing Baldur's Gates apparently and
told me a little bit about
character creation
so I know I have to censor something or
just try to not show it that's a good
warning
I I heard something about four options
on male character creation
how why is it necessary
I don't think I know of any other game
that has such
options
man
weird really weird
um
but we also talked a little bit between
the girls about character creation in
terms of maybe we're gonna all do it
um separately
not in the collab stream because it
might take a lot of time
um might even make it its own stream who
knows because
some people you know want to spend an
hour on character creation well yeah
uh so we're gonna do that separately to
the that stream yeah
can I will they notice me if I snipe
from here
who should I snipe first maybe the ones
that are further because no I don't know
yeah maybe yeah are all of these [\h__\h]
my enemy
are you my memory
close it first you think so
the truck driver there's no
um this one
oh the memories
no grenade no
guy with the pony okay
what happened
well great guys great
[Laughter]
all right now this is fun
good stuff
yeah
I'm gonna shoot your bald ass
boom Hedgehog is there somebody there no
no
I'm never ponytail guy huh
oh
come on you guys to put down your
weapons and get down
don't do anything stupid or Reckless
what is that sound I'm here oh
[Music]
what was that
didn't something come from there no
what are these zombies why did they move
like zombies
I was this guy
they move like it's a zombie apocalypse
shoot your foot
I thought you [\h__\h] under the car maybe
you should have a little Rider than that
maybe wouldn't have seen your foot under
the car
ah
ah mistake big mistake
uh there's still somebody alive there
huh
we good
okay
oh no he's still there
but I think I might kill him when I pass
by
[Music]
his hand
that will
okay
I'm gonna go now
you know I should have played Apex with
those girls yesterday
I watched uh the first time in my life I
watched
Apex longer than five seconds
um yesterday I was watching the Advent
girls play as Apex
and
I don't know anything about Apex but you
know I was watching in the beginning
where they were still setting up
was like oh yeah
no before you drive away you [\h__\h] no
hey you can't drive away I I just
friend
okay let's go
[Music]
this is scripted
Tim I gave him a headshot I'm going to
catch you Fred
wait wait wait wait I wasn't that close
man what do I press okay oh there we go
I got it
uh space trip really pull yourself
repeatedly okay
there we go wasn't talking about just
now
I don't remember
ah Apex
was like making it sound like she's good
and it made sense for me because if they
chose full a lot to play it but over
mokuko that must mean that must be good
at the game right
and they kept on like claiming
that they were good but okay the moment
they started I was like
ah it doesn't look good to me I've never
played Apex gameplay before but that
just doesn't look good to me
roll left and right okay
and then I was watching Larissa and
she's my spirit animal because the whole
time she was like um can we go back can
we go can we hide can we not
oh nice I didn't seem to want to
really play shooting game
I gotta turn around
was the only one
decent at the game
nice video
yeah in that first game Bijou had nine
out of Nine Kills
nobody else had any kills
[\h__\h]
yeah thank thank God for visual being
there
there was so much chaos and so much
screaming though I I watched for maybe
40 minutes or so
I don't know why I watched so long
[Music]
I I really don't know why
and then I was like okay I need to I
need to get to bed and
I don't know why I'm watching this
oh
you're my last song screaming Gremlins
ah
but with all my GTA experience I was
when I was watching them I was low-key
thinking maybe I would be better at it
than
[Laughter]
were you guys watching it what do you
think
whoa I hyped all of us up right
I was like she could she could really be
decent
what if she's lying
you'd be better you think so pretty sure
you'd be better than nerissa too really
I maybe I'll try it one day
just for a short short time
I gotta pack it into some cars I need to
proof
to everybody that while I can puke
but they were having actually like
um cute banter I liked it when they were
like still uh I guess in like
preparation time
I like their banter when they almost
Left narissa Behind for example
I don't know it was cute eleven thousand
hmm good and no no police Stars very
convenient
yeah yeah it really made me feel like
Advent has
good chemistry because they were
casually bantering so naturally
I know a guy who needs a man like you
only operates on an outside line though
go to the pay boat
[Music]
felt a lot more natural than any other
admin Club really I don't think I
actually watched any other Advent Club
because the one time they played scary
game that I don't like
I think
some scary game
yeah and the first one I kind of like
Zapped through
after the archive was out and I woke up
because it was in the middle of night
for me
yeah Left 4 Dead I think I didn't watch
it I'm not gonna no um
[Music]
Over My Dead Body
we're gonna fail it five times guys
oh [\h__\h] I didn't look
that was a nice nice fall though
I'm injured don't hurt me no more
What is love baby don't hurt me don't
hurt me no more
it's
excuse me
that is not something you should replace
like holy [\h__\h] or holy God with
um
that is such such a weird
saying to make yourself a habit what the
[\h__\h]
yeah
um
so I'm happy for Advent now narissa told
me that before debut they were
um like calling
in a group like three times a week or so
for a long time so that's probably why
they have really good chemistry
yeah and they met in real life too right
so
it's a power walk
thanks man I appreciate that don't
mention it
more than money
though thank you where where is it gonna
be
anyway hot dog please
[Laughter]
um he's walking and eight
are you gonna get the hot dog or not I'm
not controlling any of this
now he's walking a circle
can I please get the hot dog
hello
[Applause]
what what what what what what what
what's that about
oh my God he's getting hot dog let's go
did we get it oh God thank you
hey what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you I
press F because I want you to get on the
bike
not on the police car that is like 10
meters away from you
Mamma Mia
all these amateurs I swear to God
I'm sweating guys it's so hot in my room
it's terrible
are you giving me a different job so I
can stall on the one that I don't want
to do thank you is that the J
yeah
Bernie is also Bernie also wants
something from me
but shall we go to Jaden
Jake you must call is that the new one
that I just got
the B is this car the Bernie is the car
ah okay okay
well I wonder what kind of car it is
but if I park it like in front of my
house and so on and then I use it in my
pocket anywhere besides my house
it's just gonna disappear forever again
is it not or is it on different
oh I think
somebody is playing Persona 5 Royal
yeah mate
is this a muscle car Nico where's some
respectable clothes
or for the meat oh I am over already how
convenient
convenient yeah probably winner
I think that was Wayne and I didn't
recognize the
icon but I think it's raining
Crystal how long is
it
is that ever gonna end
oh man
the game is like 120 hours oh
well I've played Zelda for 111 hours or
so
but a lot of it off screen
so it didn't feel that long for you guys
probably
yeah I'm here to see Mr pegarino
insurance
so you're here to work from shooting
the black Persona I probably would yeah
life but I'm not gonna
pour to you guys don't worry
with a really long Persona stream
you know how wonderfully
you Nick come on
no no no no
and you'd like it
and then watch Elena or uh who else Cali
and bells
who knows exactly
I mean we can pretty much guarantee you
we're fine I like this office
did you know about it and right now I
don't know the answer to that question
is that the ashtray merchandise I don't
really care neither
I know enough about you can't believe
there's merchandising whole alive I know
a lot of people around you end up in
jail some maybe but that's the same all
over town this is a dying game
I don't understand you bought it I mean
I'm gonna ask you to deal with a problem
and you're gonna deal with it or you're
not going to deal with it and you're
going to be a problem that somebody else
has to deal with
but me I ain't doing nothing no I am the
problem dealer not the problem to deal
Anthony yo okay not yet boss Ray called
of course he did
I wonder is it better to have a talented
snake
a historical lion they got to the climax
and hasn't had time to stream it for a
few weeks oh that's unfortunate
what do you think
I don't understand what you're talking
about
you do
but I ain't gonna push
Anthony get in here
boss
where's Big Pete and Marco oh this guy a
Mafia Boss I don't remember listen to me
here's what the plan is it looks like
one me and two of my guys gonna meet
with a couple of boys from the pavano
food
I need these guys if we're ever going to
be taking oh that house you know stairs
like that get on the commission not a
thing it like split these guys ain't
shall we say that's the appropriate
respect in the past that's that's I want
look at that to run security
keep an eye on things
because they won't be looking out for
you okay ah here they are
yeah I'm the I'm a spy looks like Ray's
here too I know it's them
God give me strength
sexy stairs
sexy floor man I love this
is
written [\h__\h] Rome man cockroaches
or something
fake Italian
kissing his ass
what's inside
pecorino
Pizza
I'm sure there's pecorino Pizza
or maybe there's like restaurants called
pecorino pecorino
this car this is my car
all right was it no well oopsie
's way sorry I'm getting into this one
then
it wasn't clear on the map
what he is waiting for here let's go
is that was that pink
who sings that
Gwen Stefani
you best hope you made a good first
impression
that's me well he's being paid to look
out for me so saving you guys asses
would be overtime that was Gwen Stefani
that's just if the [\h__\h] goes down right
boss
wouldn't [\h__\h] with you wake up you
[\h__\h] Mook he had good everybody's
trying to [\h__\h] everybody we're just
hoping they got the manners to smile to
our faces before they do it you giving
them a nice little offer and they'll
skip they gonna
give me strength
it's like a theater with children here
no wonder I ain't on a commission what
my muscle is this stupid if the povanos
is a Liberty City Family what are they
doing coming out to alternate for this
meat I let him operate out here from
time to time but manners work a little
shy business on this side of the West
River they also control a few bookings I
don't mind them taking a bite I don't
even make them give me a taste hopefully
they're gonna respect that when it comes
time to asking them for a favor would
you guys the latest guy would you guys
say the way this guy talks is uh like a
New York way of talking check to make
sure my ass is covered in each situation
I think about what's gonna happen if
this guy's Scrolls yeah see if this one
turns yes because I I recognize it
from um The Marvelous Mrs maisel anyways
that's why Ray ain't ever gonna make it
to the level he wants to reach and I
think I like it it grew on me
I'm like a [\h__\h] son you're covering
it's really fun when me and the povanos
is just putting our first pawns out
there on a checkerboard
real clever because I'm connecting this
now
the actress from marvelous Mrs maisel
um but I don't know they talk like these
Savage fun people who don't take no [\h__\h]
uh they're fun
and I don't really like I don't think I
can tell all accents apart in America
but
um this one stands out to me I like it
[Music]
it's a great way to describe it
it has like confidence and attitude by
default I love it
I want to talk like that I want my
English to set my dad but I also want my
English just sound British as well
because that's hot and now I mean I can
also I can also take Australian or new
zealander-ish instead but yeah I just
want interesting sounding English please
if this thing kicks off chill chill I
have my own rifle too
here you go I have my own but thanks is
it better than mine
sniper rifle the snap
go up into that building there should be
a spot where you can see over the meat
don't start shooting unless they attack
us I don't want this thing screwing up
for no good reason
it's mostly the sense of intelligence
that's what I thought because to me I
don't know it rarely sounds like how an
Italian would speak if they're in
America
and it fits so well because these people
I guess are Italian descent
it's like this Italian attitude
with the
with the confidence of an American
but Italian people also feel confident
to me but where are we going up
where's the entrance wait
parmesan bloodline shut up don't say
that
here
it's I can't say it's so dark
uh
wrong side
huh so what over here
oh man
close to the car
I didn't see anything
is this a is this a ladder
not really right
I can't see
ah is that an opening
sometimes these colors and lights and
shadows are so washed out it's really
hard to see I'm sorry
like right now it's so bad
on my screen especially because of some
light Reflections too
Brown age it's like sepia filter what
the [\h__\h]
um
me and I
okay this is my spot
this is my spot
[Music]
nice
I like this area
keep a card of a pecolino
I mean I'll end up just shooting these
guys right
are these my guys or their guys
no these are these are their Guys these
are my guys okay
uh are we
headshots in three two oh
there um
[Music]
is it there rescue should I run to him
or
do I run to him
I see no more enemies
okay
upstairs
these are not hot stairs
okay let's switch away from the sniper
wait it's taking me something
[Music]
where are they where are they
what
the [\h__\h] I thought I shot all of you
get down I can't get down
[Music]
oh nice shot
So Long Farewell I'll be dancing goodbye
okay now I got him oh god oh
Friend or Foe diamond yeah yeah yeah
okay nice he will die so now look up
there
what does it do
carry him like a princess I got you I
got you I got you here here I'm here
if the rest of the cup board I'm sure
the whole city will be up in arms the
[\h__\h] trying to whack me in a
sit down I wanna know history about New
York like buying
did the New York and accent really come
from like Italians
spreading their way of speaking in New
York or what
[Music]
oh that's so interesting
so interesting so before they talk like
normal people
look at me having full control over
everything
foreign
myself
no I I just told you I love that but
it's fascinating to me what
the fascinating to me how they
talk and how that happened I need to
study linguistics
um can I reach them from here somehow oh
yeah maybe there you go you ain't gonna
let him get away no no I mean unless a
tree is in my way trees are enemies oh
[\h__\h]
I might be losing them
straight and right can I yeah baby
[\h__\h] don't let these [\h__\h] give it a
shake uh
I think we're losing them
wait they're gone
they're gone
I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
we'll do it again
On and On Again
how to
yes okay
don't shoot the car next time
yeah
why is it scripted again that I can't
get them anyway
oh wait this one
oh okay
[Music]
wait it's not here
but we gotta go uh armor up again huh
it's broken
my [\h__\h] GPS is broken
oh wait I forgot something
pecorino
come in
that doesn't really suit a mafia but
somehow I thought you were gonna carry
us a leather case you know like those
lawyers have or something
he's he's just like like a university
student
carrying a look
we're going to down there so it's kind
of on the way anyway
[Music]
s yeah leather briefcase
I didn't get where I am I believe in
what every schmuck told me
in Japanese
they use the German word uh for backpack
cook sacks
[Music]
it's important but I don't give a [\h__\h]
about them other people what I'm worried
about is our involver with getting back
to Gay Tony and his connections we got a
lot riding on this meeting with the
profanos want to keep relations sweet
but at least one of the families that
got a seat on the commission yeah
foreign
[Music]
right now
oh it's basically there are they going
to offer you a seat then give me
ain't nobody
even give a foundation
Trico was actually German
oh that that word I got a nice little
offer into the pavanos it's gonna pursue
something real quick
but the interesting thing is in Japanese
is like used for part-time work but in
German it's just like
any work
but usually full-time jobs
when we use that word oh is that golden
accents on your black car very very
um
slight gold X is very fancy I like it
not too much nuts in your face
you can't tell me what to do uh what
ammo do I need do I need ammo from
something like something specific this
one
um
shooter
okay
get out of here
we don't even really when I use this gun
for this Mission but who knows who knows
how it escalates
so you guys are [\h__\h] telling me that
the car ride is scripted again [\h__\h]
script [\h__\h] scripted again
and then it I shouldn't be shooting them
because they're gonna reach their
destination anyway
foreign
[Music]
until they get out somewhere
again
yeah yeah yesterday
I was listening to new jeans with my
friends too I like you know we were
playing songs on
uh like a
speaker and
I got them to play some new jeans made
me really happy and one of my friends
actually listens to new jeans too she
wasn't as knowledgeable about them as me
but she knew a lot of the new songs too
and we were like jamming to new jeans I
was so happy
I got so hyped I was chanting loudly
what's your ETA what's your ETA what's
your ATM
I got so excited and then what was the
other one
um
[Music]
I got so excited I wasn't even singing I
was just screaming it
I love this song so much holy [\h__\h]
come on make you mine
it's good that they have so many English
lyrics in their songs because then I can
actually sing it
which just made me think of the fact
that
you know when you make songs in the
actual language of your target audience
they will have more fun with it because
they'll be able to sing it
right
is this wait which
is this a sniper they want me to use
what genres new jeans well K-pop but
it's like kind of like really fresh
K-pop you know
sounds so fresh it's different from the
other recent Kpop songs
all right
is that it for now
maybe I can
ah
what happened I couldn't shoot anymore
okay let's go
I didn't shoot those people the first
time but I thought maybe if I do it no
um
[Music]
gonna take cover here
laughs
oh no stairs
I'm not reloading now reload always in
worst timing man what the [\h__\h]
okay
I'll cut off your [\h__\h] kid and okay
that's it here
again PP lost forever
bye bye
don't shoot just run ah pecorino is fine
look at him
he's fine
um
okay now we drive we're gonna ice those
[\h__\h] sicko
if
[Music]
we kill everyone of them slime balls
then maybe the other families will give
me their seat on the commission [\h__\h]
Liberty City can you drive straight you
[\h__\h] Europeans
name for the pecoritos earned a lot of
good money for a lot of bad people and
this happens they try to [\h__\h] tell me
but at least they had the respect to do
it I love my European Union
yo I'm so close to them they're not
gonna get away from me this time
[Applause]
[Music]
issue
where are we going my friend huh why are
you taking me
showing me the beautiful
New York oh look at him oh he's [\h__\h]
go get my kids and make those
people oh my God I think
[Music]
wait wait I'm not gonna let him go
hey there's a first aid kit
I don't even need it okay you see that
now ah if I
get back
what How's he not dead is he a god
now we're good
how do I take this offering wait wait
wait wait wait wait
uh offering to God
AKA pecorino
I got it oh
yes
um
that I even did extra homework by
killing them all I didn't even have to
according to this to the map and uh I
can't believe that piranhas would treat
me like subtitles pegarino name should
be something important it made something
in alternate even if it don't an
Algonquin they better not think of
Crossing that West River
bad about Marco and Pete Marco and Pete
oh yeah those guys didn't make it did
they what the key dude by the way for
him to be here a victim of language
ah these kids do it ain't worth paying
attention to them until they prove they
can survive I just move on are they
still shooting I want to be Wise Guys
off the street it's that simple has to
be who don't start paying attention to
my crew when they start putting me in an
awkward position either because they
know too much in my rat or because they
got too much power and they're too smart
to get themselves clipped Ray was
nothing to me until we started earning
big and sticking his nose in place
you know is by finding that [\h__\h] all
over the place in the morning feels
different he's been my man for a while I
mean how much can I do with a guy who
ain't a full Italian he's 90 Irish
pecorinos having St Patrick that high up
in our organization
getting out on the street Jesus Jesus
laughs
oh
oh Italians and Irish don't mesh well
what
okay we did well on that
I did well on that
I am satisfied
one one fail is acceptable in this late
game where there's a couple of difficult
missions here and there we're not that
difficult though to be honest
just you know
if you know what's happening then
it's safe pretty much am I close to
weapon shot by the way by any chance no
okay
Comedy Club I I went to The Comedy Club
last time it was fun
ah they had
really that was an Irish mob and the
Italian mafia really
what's with once with all these
Europeans
[Music]
Europeans asserting dominance
in New York
the land of opportunity
land of endless opportunities
cry
those opportunities oh man you know what
we should do crime ah all of these good
things you could do but let's go for
crime
cry
crime we love crime
you'll be good kid kept your head when
everyone else was losing this sometimes
literally we're going to need your
skills again soon
arrivederci
okay
crime is an easy shortcut for people
looking to get ahead crime is also an
easy shortcut to death and to uh you
know
prison
so is it worth it I would say no
but you know
it is what it is what is this
assassin huh
what a Noni
what's this on my map is he gonna kill
me
is this my assassin who's waiting for me
is this my shortcut to death
uh optional okay I gotta go here though
and then we'll go to the DM I guess
can we steal a car here
can I take one empty
empty
the [\h__\h] she
ET no car here
I mean look at this backyard though
[Music]
not wobbly pool hey Europe it's America
and Ireland you want to hang out
what does that mean she's speaking in
riddles sure kid I'll be there in an
hour okay
hey
what am I what did she say I'm Italy and
she's America and Ireland does she have
American and have IR Irish
you did well last job come see me the
boss which boss a pecorino I'm right at
your door
should I call him or just come to his
place
I ain't heard from you oh my goodness no
what does that mean
prison
ah [\h__\h] wait I'm trying to do something
uh
I should
getting killed
no not me not me something's come up
thanks I love rejection yeah [\h__\h] you
I hate her attitude I hate her attitude
not again
do I look like I have time for ladies
also
I want to focus on my career okay
I think I might take a talk see this
time
oh and there is a j up there oh maybe
maybe while I'm here I should quickly
talk to him
I might as well right stall a little bit
more on my mission
on my other mission
ah
hey stinky who you waving at feds I
think they always drive past it this
time does that worry you
when you marry a dragon you gotta expect
a few Knights are gonna turn up to try
to Slayer yeah interesting way of seeing
it
nice talking very positive I guess fun
pick a swell guy to kill hopefully
someone with a young family who really
miss them oh wait no she doesn't seem
all that happy just sarcastic about it
hey hey
sure I'll get them boys
shut up in fact will you [\h__\h] off
he doesn't really know how to control
his volume
second come in here
oh man
I feel bad for him listen we got a bit
of a problem with the povanos yes I
noticed that that you're meeting with
them the way they look at us we're
Bottom Feeders don't scream for me like
that guys just a bunch of Guernsey
Goombas Goomba
cool we're getting [\h__\h] I'm sorry to
hear that sure
listen some of that boys are in town
today gonna collect their piece of an
old in a bookie ring what where it is
they're at the diner an actor find them
follow them to the meat you will disrupt
it and I'll let you keep the money but
make sure you hit the pavanas real hard
yeah I haven't heard that one in a while
drive to the diner oh okay I take this
car now there's a car let's go
oh
wait was not gonna take a taxi dough to
the web and it's close but this car is
nice
yeah but I'll I think I'll take a taxi
we've been driving around so much
already
um
[Music]
if I find one that is
uh maybe over there
I want to see cop cars no
okay ow
my car well actually not my car that's
Mr Taxi Taxi text me won't you drive me
right drive me to my destination uh how
do you do this again
not F right was it f
uh what was it I don't know press the
wrong button hold F okay
I don't want where you want to go any
misunderstandings
[Music]
um
all right
and next destination
[Music]
yellow Dot
two Couture is controlling my brain no
it's on me it's on me today
trust me
can I take this one
is
[Music]
well this car is a bit loud
but I feel like it has good control
of course it's me you should know what
it's me and when it's not me and you
know me so well don't you
or at least you think you do
I think that guy works for the pegarinos
god they must be desperate let's lose
them on the way to the meek
are they talking about me
okay maybe I should have chosen to
faster car
but
I'll be fine I'll be fine
should I shoot this time can't you tell
me am I shooting this time also just
following
help me help me help me
Chase don't kill no no just fall okay
very clear instructions
[Music]
okay as long as he drives like an idiot
like that but I'm also driving like an
idiot I thought that would I thought
that was gonna fall apart
and then I could just drive through
like a McDonald's
did they go up those stairs
impossible with a car like that don't
you think
is it gonna go left or right
straight the [\h__\h]
this
okay
can't wait too okay
uh
they obviously drove through but didn't
break the fence
how
[Music]
ah
ghost car
I think that's the case for
why is it no
no no they're not
wipe them all out uh where are they
ah
uh wait
um
is it grenade time again no no no
no no no no no no
cover not not anything else
holy holy [\h__\h]
I won't [\h__\h] up
another one
[Applause]
um
who's left
uh I need there's a big big one in there
I have a lot of stars I would like to uh
continue this another time should I
should I leave is this over now
[\h__\h] what do I do what do I do I [\h__\h]
it up baby maybe it's too many yeah okay
you think they're all dead
I may have overdone it with explosions
[Applause]
[Music]
it's the result that we wanted
just gotta get out of here with this
broken ass car
[\h__\h] effective yes we gotta make quick
business guys we gotta get done I need a
different car though because this is
[\h__\h]
I can't turn
but let me get out of this circle maybe
I can lose it quickly
so if I'm here
and chill a little bit
because it's gonna be lucky
okay
[Applause]
oh
where's my bunny where's my money
where's my reward money
what the [\h__\h]
to me pecorino
I got that stuff Jimmy well
well
[Music]
I want this car it's cute
I said good thing I'm not to tell you
um
[Music]
all right uh where's my money though am
I not getting money for this
or did I miss it
[Music]
um
famicom car yeah right looks funny
do I need to go to him
it doesn't show it though right now oh
wow
um let's go to PB and J
en peanut butter jelly
time peanut butter you know what I I
will leave you with your car and take a
taxi I'm so nice I'm so nice
this one
[Music]
once you get out
I was holding her
thanks a lot
of jelly peanut butter jelly peanut
butter jelly
strip club
what
time
Johnny graveli I'm already working for a
mafia family they're scum
Lily is the only man
only man shotler Medical Center tell him
he was sent by a mutual friend
affecting you
I guess I have to
okay what are we doing here though
hey Tommy check this out 707 race
hey pal what's going on not too much how
are you I'm good wanna walk and talk
Tommy give me a call if my big buddy
calls don't slap that booty no problem
ridiculous I'm a grown man walking
around like a trump
sorry about this hey no problem
so you're a friend of race yes a friend
oh I do some work for him oh I need a
friend
I don't understand
whatever you say
he's the slime ball but he pays
slime I've been getting Kiara slime fan
art recently
I don't know what to think of it
a lot of [\h__\h] but he's a good owner it's
not something I needed
yeah thanks to Gouda
only the only reason I think it's the
boss said you gotta head down to docs
emergency said you'd understand ah [\h__\h]
it's three days early man on the meal
what am I gonna do what's the problem
Nico
I'm gonna have to take a chance with you
pal
okay
let's go
okay listen there's a truck waiting for
us it's under the overpass off Catskill
Avenue Catskill
you know
watching marvelous Mrs maisel I heard
cat skills so often I was like what a
weird name no but we can be pretty sure
it's clean chill out but that place
exists in reality right the cat skills
that means that certain people my cat
also got a lot of skill opening doors
[Music]
please say it's the first thing
what are we doing we're taking a load of
product off of some Russians the
enchiladas have been dealing you was
helping those Irish idiots cause some
beef between the enchiladas and their
Albanian muscle a while back enchiladas
he says it sounds like enchiladas
are we dealing with
Spanish people know too exactly or
Mexicans
from Mexican Kitchen
we make some money in the process by
selling enchiladas [\h__\h] you sound like
you're saying all this stuff so it's
clear on the wires for the record I
don't know what this man is talking
about we're rehearsing a seed for an
acting class Mexico everything we're
saying is fiction it has no bearing in
the real world watch it Nico
all right
no enchiladas okay
[Music]
funny car cute muscle car I have arrived
already all right this is the truck
7-Eleven truck
I take
a tech truck that was easy
that was too easy the real challenge
must come afterwards
24 7.
be a shitload of coke we're taking it
should be a lot of sugar it ain't the
only reason why we're taking this truck
some of my boys stole it from the
enchiladas this morning it's the one the
Russians is expecting to come pick up
the seat we should be able to turn up
and have them loaded up for us then we
drive away no questions there is that
really gonna work like that give away a
little
ain't that stupid yeah sure this is just
plan a it's the one Jimmy P workout
what's Plan B and that the only way
we're going to be shooting everyone
with the Russians in there
not just drive right into the middle of
it because these is viewers and we gotta
follow them that's the way things work
you ain't gonna be happy about
everything you get told to do are you
you're the boss it ain't like I'm
working for free and I ain't neither
that's why we gotta at least try to do
what we're told to do you're gonna learn
that there ain't much in this life that
you got control of whether you're
putting yourself In Harm's Way because
that's the way the skipper wants it done
or you're staying away from your kids
because of a stupid court order and a
malicious [\h__\h] of an ex-wife you ain't
that much control in anything I've been
around long enough to know that there is
some things that maybe you should turn
on motion control
but then you probably have even less
control every order I'm giving yeah well
maybe you're right maybe you ain't I
don't know
because Marvel controls our [\h__\h] most of
the time
what's yours
my truck is so big I didn't see himself
I mean I kind of did and then I forgot
about you within half of a second I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry
I was right at my goal
oh a [\h__\h] police car there too but
didn't see me no it didn't see me
oh I didn't have a police car hi don't
choose me what the [\h__\h]
I'm not armed totally
at least you can't say it yet so don't
assume
don't assume that I'm armed
I'm legged too after all think about my
legs
don't always think about my arms
my legs want to be considered as well
thank you thank you
all right
enough with stupid jokes
[Music]
back to where we wanted to go
noodle armed
excuse me okay I
tried my best okay
in improving my noodle arms
but it's rough
I'm weak man
Rome wasn't built in a day and these
noodle arms aren't going away in a day
either
how many push-ups uh one
if you're asking how many I could do one
if you're asking how many I'm gonna make
you do in the usual room if you keep on
making fun of me and my little arms then
hundreds
what's with European YouTube is it
stuttering
no Mamma Mia stop
American YouTube too
why do I do YouTube
International YouTube
we're connected
We're All in This Together
okay uh what why are we driving in this
weird Circle
gotta pay up
I'm not gonna try fruit don't worry here
okay open
noise
by the way I told you guys
what is this can I pick this up
I told you guys that I had trouble
sleeping again yeah I
want to pick this up
looks like a light stick
uh my might have just been a knife
yeah I I've been using the pet feeder at
first night
I think it worked kind of well I mean my
cat didn't know
when the feeder was spilling out the
beans so I had to show her like she was
meowing at me but I absolutely correctly
guessed when she would meow with me I
said it for one for six am and another
one for like nine a.m and she did meow
at me at 6am
and then again around a little bit
before nine I think
pretty close call though noise
so I I did still have to get up
and then show her the new feeder that
was the first night but I thought she
would get it soon and also I turned on
um like a
like a alarm I was able to record my own
voice
so that when the time comes and it turns
around
to open the container for uh
sorry uh the next food department
uh it says something that I recorded
like ah babe
it's pretty loud it woke me up today but
I'm not sure if smoothie reacted to it
and understood that that's where the
food is however this night too she woke
me up at completely different random
times several times so it didn't work so
well this time
and has not yet been unloaded
the Boatyard is heavily guarded the
element of surprise will be crucial
um
I'm going to fail
I became an alarm for me instead we're
here to pick up the shipment I don't
speak English
hey amigo let's make this easy I just
want to give this stuff to my boss and
go home anyone in here until I get the
word there's something wrong about you
get out of the truck real slow Nico
looks like we're gonna have to do this
the old-fashioned way shoot these say hi
don't even have to tell me
uh get oh
holy [\h__\h] man that's am I supposed to
get out or am I supposed to stay in
violence
should I get out
get out okay okay okay okay
um
uh okay let's uh Park this thing here
for a moment and think about
should I throw in another
yeah
beautiful okay and now
thank you
that's killed a bunch of people very
nice
is that my friend it's blue why are you
going so far uh what
stay behind you idiot
Mamma Mia
okay
where's friends uh [\h__\h] still shooting
from where
up here
where where did that come from oh well
one time into the box
so he goes down on his knees and begs
for his life but I won't give it to him
yeah
TV
okay
there's still some people there let me
show the beatsies
okay
ammo no ammo
I feel like I'm doing this solo because
I don't even see my friend is this
explosive no
no we're going to die friend there's a
medkit there and I'm out of armor
[Music]
oh
nice stunt
s okay
wait for a moment I wasn't sure if it
was an enemy but yeah he was okay
is there any armor lying around too
because that would be actually helpful
no no why do they never drop armor
eh
the one on the right I take one on the
left what about the what about the truck
okay
and wait wait should I should I should
take cover
um where are they where are they
is this friend no that's friend this is
this is enemies
get into that water
oh I see him
oh is he dead I think he's dead okay
this is the boat I need
is this how I get it
am I supposed to drive this or what what
sorry I'm stupid I'm stupid
doesn't seem like it wants me to drive
it
how do I take what I need
hey I was pressing F nothing was
happening now it's happening gotta press
it longer okay
follow Bell to the Dropout board oh it's
again the cat feeder boats oh sure wait
I'll try to ah can I lose him I don't
want to lose him
okay
y'all these curves
very very mean curves
[Applause]
more
protection from the attacking boat that
sounds to me like I am going to shoot
them
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah that's what I'm talking about that
sounds more realistic to me
instead of missing all my shots
[Applause]
have been killed follow Bell okay
I'm coming
down
[Music]
how much did you miss you missed a lot I
think we've been doing quite a lot of
missions
but
it's okay we still got a bunch more to
go
and I still am stalling so that I don't
have to do the one
that I failed at last time
trying my hardest to escape from it
hey buddy I caught up
[Music]
you plan on playing the other stars in
me in the DLC
yeah perhaps in a different stream after
I take a little break from it
hello 29 months thank you wow those are
some big numbers man
membership number is very very big
wait what's happening oh my God I'm so
sorry
I wasn't trying to hump you
boat humping let's go
I was looking at the chat
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry uh
uh disembark he says
that's not so easy
um
did you lose no your winner
you don't need like a million months
to be a winner at kfb thank you guys
okay let's get out get out
I'll swim
oh wait but do I need
[Music]
um
do I need the boat to be really parked
there is that important
foreign
touch the boat anymore and get off now
[Music]
how do I how do I escape the wobbly
water okay
this is not how you like it wait I just
need to stand there right oh okay
I ruined my suit now
it's all salty now oh [\h__\h] you're [\h__\h]
man look at all that blood
hmm
you handed yourself real good back then
thanks first try this time right thank
you
I think so
my memories are blending into each other
but I think so
I did run him over with a book
[Music]
all right 7 500. bike
okay I'll take the bike
um
we could go to Jay again but I've uh or
P why are they blinking
why aren't I blinking
that's supposed to tell me something
love train love train yay join the love
train love train
because they're new oh okay
Japanese bike it's a Japanese bike that
Bernie's car I don't really care about
the car but do I need to pick it up in
order to continue my Bernie story or are
we actually done with Bernie's story
train laugh train
I don't know the rest of the song I only
have the melody and the instrumentals in
my head but I can't recreate it
it's done that's why English it's like a
farewell gift okay well then no no
stress and picking it up it's orange is
it
really
how do you know huh
how did he know my favorite color
oh no I don't wanna
let's go here first but man
do I really have to do that mission I
don't think I can ever
clear it I have no confidence in regards
to that mission
I mean I've done similar stuff plenty of
times
like clearing out a whole building of
enemies but that one for some reason
like it starts like it seems inevitable
to have the police on my ass
so I'm being attacked from the front
from those uh [\h__\h] and then from the
back for the police so what am I
supposed to do
he's got work he pays grenade
what the police no that's really my
problem
sorry Ray I'm freelance I don't buy into
that tribute stuff this work has many
disadvantages but uh who's the police so
I should leave that building is that not
gonna make me
um fail the mission
[Music]
are you sure
I feel like if I go back and start that
whole firing again they'll just want to
show up again
can I really just drive away and lose
the police first
just a few dude there kill fast and
Escape well you guys tell me to go
aggressive but I tried that once uh or
twice even just going in and people
but then while I was at it in the middle
of all that fire
police just walks into the door from the
back
[Music]
um
damn you I'm sorry thank God you forgave
me
[Music]
um
per times the charm and I feel like I
already did it more than three times
did I not browse buddy but don't try
anything fun oh he does wear a helmet I
just noticed it now
okay
um
a lot of cocktail would be fun too can I
take that
wait it's not a [\h__\h] what is
that oh it is
I'll buy it is it good
replace your current weapon and Slot you
mean the grenade is it better than a
grenade I can't imagine it will be
better than a grenade
nah
okay
how many grenades do I have left
20 hmm yeah that's fine
see you later alligator
um how do you guys have an overview of
how many grenades I have left
you keep inventory of my inventory
inventory Tori
watch that more
yeah
um
[Music]
I hate this
I hate this part right here
[Music]
pie fighting
I think
[Music]
um
our first original song is coming out
for me in in the night
well the MV is coming out in the middle
of the night I think I don't think I'll
be awake for it
but I saw the Envy it's really fun
you're gonna like it hey I'm behind
being taken care of that have we watched
this before but we'll watch it again
it's been a while
hand
looks like you need
more cool
masks movie to wake you oh yeah she
might
without me asking him awake I was just
wishing you'd leave
hey hey
sit down
okay actually I have no patience for
this
okay uh find a cop car
there was always some parked over here
I just stay like this
you think that he'll see it
I mean he might hear it
oh wait they don't make a sound
oh yeah it's too easy
uh police records uh [\h__\h] now I don't
remember the name guys what was it
says Bucky Sligo Bucky's like oh what a
weird name
yeah who's talking to me
doggies Lego okay
in the game
hi colleagues how you doing I want to
get some donuts after this
ideally
hey Derek apparently your guy hangs out
at the Burger Shop in the Alderly go
check it out let's make sure
we are not colleagues
[Music]
suddenly easily first try it
or
I'll [\h__\h] up again
uh for real though I want you guys to
answer me if police is like on my ass
can I leave the area to get rid of the
police first and then come back even
when I already triggered the big fight
[Music]
is that really possible
yes no idea probably never tried
yeah
okay there's only yeses and I don't
knows
Maybe
you think they'll say by the house who
the police
oh
well I don't wanna you know when I have
to redo this Mission I have to do this
whole
whole take the police
are in a drive and then first is before
we even get to the house we have to do a
Chase too
why why
yeah some other recent missions
when I have to redo something they start
like pretty close to where I left off
but this Mission you have to redo so
many things
which just adds to me losing my patience
huh
Main
this mission is just badly designed it
really is I'm sorry but it just is
hey yo
missions
okay
so long
please retake driving license exam I
never took one in the first place
[Music]
wait okay so first we're um chasing
but not shooting right you guys also
told me no need to shoot for this one
because we have him reach his
destination anyway
on this [\h__\h] is gonna drive for all
those tiny alley anyways
okay this time I I went out backwards
nicely did I know
[Music]
not this time he's actually destroying
the fences because I'm seeing it that's
why the game is registering it
oh
money I can't pick it up but what the
[\h__\h] I never saw these normal people
dropping money when you drive them over
that never happened to me before
ooh nice curve
[Music]
this is the best Chase I've ever had
even though there's so many curves
okay I jinxed it that was bad
still good
like I'm in such good control right now
ah but I'm scared of what's to come now
because we have arrived
[Music]
okay okay what do we do what do we do
what do we do what are we gonna do how
are we gonna do this I don't know how to
do this
I should watch a tutorial of this
mission
is there really a back door
gotta go like around the house
enter grenade get out
maybe I will maybe I won't do that
but aren't there people like two people
on the outside too
um
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
weapons
well
at least there's no police on my ass yet
where is he
pull up a chair and relax boy you're not
going anywhere
I hate this position I'm in
okay
still no police
maybe if I'm I was just like really
unlucky and the police was always
driving by in moments where I was
shooting
the outside ones are taken care of now I
take a grenade
um
they're still alive
okay
it's still there one why why why why why
why why they're still like free in there
are they upstairs
somebody alerted to [\h__\h] police
okay okay
I got I think I have to kill them by
hand no
[Music]
um
try leaving for now
just one cup right now let me let me try
to
um
oh [\h__\h]
one more
I got it I'm going in hey we got you
from every angle
all right
[Music]
okay and I didn't kill a cop I was about
to kill the cop but it was probably
better that it didn't
okay all we gotta do is escape let's go
come on
get up that hill get up the hill yeah
yeah
yeah the hills are alive
the sound of shootings
[Applause]
[Music]
I can't press it I thought that was
going to be smart for a moment okay I
guess not because I wouldn't have seen
me this time
I can't wash it here
what do you mean
discrimination
do I look like I'm gonna pull over guys
no no no no no no no no no no no no am I
missing a tire
sounds a little bit like it but I'm
still driving quite well
I'm so glad that worked out man
I'm so relieved that I don't have to do
that [\h__\h] again
ah the freaking cop cars keep on
refreshing my circle
and go this way
[Music]
no no no no no no
please leave me alone
foreign
[Applause]
do I have a flat tire
because the curves uh
pan spray
yeah
too late
[Music]
okay
good old Prius
celebrates
oh [\h__\h] they're so close they're on my
ass
yeah this will take a while
I don't have time to change the car
either
mm-hmm
I just gotta show off my Pro driving
skills
run run this could be it
out of the circle
bye bye
did she drop money just now no they
don't see that don't drop money normally
I don't know what that was before
lucky
[Music]
Derek you okay it doesn't sound okay
I speak to you when you're back about
the living
[Music]
all right okay time to visit to get some
new armor I think yeah and then
now that I'm finally free of this
Mission I don't give a [\h__\h] where we're
gonna go we can go to the close mission
ah
feels good
load up my shoulder yeah
Hallelujah
Nikki we want to keep an eye on you
we'll have you close there's an
apartment we got a new apartment again
don't worry about your cousin sleeping
alone he'll be safe ciao
oh it's over here
right wait didn't we have this one
already no I'm confused about this one
hello okay okay it's close to DM
they're gonna slide in my DMs
because we're so close
yeah I gotta open my eyes
let's see
new creep Welcome to My Crib MTV Cribs
[Applause]
that's where that
side job is I guess
but I'm not gonna do that
hi I'm probably your only guest at this
point Bruce
he don't want you to give it back to him
does he [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I was just telling him how you know
you can make things happen I guess so
sure I have an ability to find stuff if
the price is right give him my number
[\h__\h]
okay
uh
uh what he wants me to find cars
right I guess don't know if I have time
for that right now
it's a side mission disregard oh okay
okay
is it never one of those things that if
I don't do it it's gonna give me a
thumbs down in the moment
DM Derek
PB or DM I could heal myself at the safe
house if I go to DM
but PB is very close
let's go home
actually maybe if I find a tax sale take
a tax yeah
to save us some time there's one
teaches us
oh
a man
and leave the Prius yeah me and the
Prius we've been through some [\h__\h] and I
am very thankful and grateful for what
we've been through but I'm done this
doesn't look so luxurious what the hell
I mean this oh this door looks nice
let's see what's behind
ah yeah I mean
the walls and [\h__\h] are run down but it
still looks kind of cozy I like the
the splitting of the apartment ah it's a
one kind of a one-room thing though huh
open open everything
hmm
okay now how do I heal myself again if
here
why do I get a downgrade from my
previous apartment
um
good enough I guess
sometimes you gotta
just accept stuff like this
to stay in the game
all right
yeah not this way
it seems like my apartment won't let me
use my bathroom though because that door
was shut tight
okay I need a car
your mother was right
and talk to his mother huh
get out I need this
no no let go you're gonna regret it
you're gonna request
let's go
apocalypse okay we're going into a very
close spot uh
yeah the crop's not reacting I was like
still in the middle of stealing it
well I guess that doesn't count
um
down there
well does he want to see whoa a stick
six stunt that was a sixth stunt I
I that wasn't even that much damage
hello
hi
okay
all right I'm here oh both times
[Music]
take charge
this is the place
[Music]
go to Kim's boat
okay
let's go in the Korean contest
we
came together for a cause we believed in
at least I thought I believed in it I
was
a while ago then yeah so ain't got
caught with something when he was
somewhere he wasn't meant to be needless
to say it'll be inside for a Time him
and Bucky think I talked couldn't see no
other way how he got caught but what I
hear
what
[\h__\h] yes
you Parks boy yes I Kim you dedicated to
America we're meeting your friends in
bowhead I'll text you around you gotta
take best way to avoid checks we'll
cover you came to America with this boat
damn
what
or did they because she says welcome to
America arriving in this city trying to
make something of himself brings a tear
to my eyes from Korea with this boat
is
[Music]
this thing stinks
what the [\h__\h] did I do
okay you're dead
oh we're going right into the action do
not hurt my Korean friend okay
go somewhere else you [\h__\h]
yeah yeah I guess so
I have experience
[Music]
but so oh wait there's some here too
blow up blow up why are they so easy to
blow up by the way what exactly was I
shooting
to make it blow up
is that a police helicopter
[Music]
uh oh no it's an enemy helicopter
it's in the back
at home
oh there we go
thanks for the rocket launcher can I
keep it and now what now
move away from the front
of Kim's boat okay
so what about the back
follow him okay
[Music]
for personal use too I thought they know
we were here
I told my dealer I was good for the
money I owed him maybe a few people at
the pub I borrowed money from as well
the same I think for a fix I would could
be a coincidence anyway I love RPGs
jrpgs
Kaboom RPGs
all of them I do not discriminate
between RPGs
why is he driving so slow
[Music]
did I push him
push push
[Music]
come on
come on I don't want to do both humping
again
[Music]
[Laughter]
I don't have a choice but he's so slow
oh my God you like one piece too oh my
God not such a smooth Journey yeah
yes if your time here is more peaceful
that's all you can hope for in this God
forsaken world so what'd you say about
someone who has
oh no
it doesn't feel sick on the sea or what
what does that mean
[Music]
oh seven thousand
ghetto okay
that was fun I barely lost my armor too
so that's good
uh oh but we went all the way around New
York and ended up here oh what the hell
okay
I guess we can pick up the car really
quickly
um
[Music]
hey what was that uh oh red light you're
gonna pay for what you just did
what was it what was it e oh yeah e
are you stopping or not do little [\h__\h]
thank you
looked like you were about to drive away
[Music]
I'll take the long way thank you very
much what do you mean it took a long way
take the short way what the [\h__\h] just
ripping me off where's this car
oh my mistake
oh
it's not Orange it's yellow close enough
though nice car
thank you cute whoa surprise dark kids
wow this didn't come out of City funds
oh wait it is maybe Orange
oh
my new car why would you park it here
it's pretty it's like it's like a orange
juice orange but really bright
refreshing orange wow
he knew my favorite color
wow it's a special car I'm gonna park it
in front of my really cheap looking
house and hopefully it's not gonna get
stolen
[Music]
the taxi color man what the [\h__\h]
same color
others pokeballs on the back of my car
my car is just floating but I think this
is normal with this kind of car orange
mobile
put into
haven't done anything with with manatee
in a while
I feel like I haven't seen a car like
this before in the game so it's just
like custom
must be custom right you don't get this
anywhere else oh look at those sides
whoa
it's rare
[Music]
kind I don't know
they're very uncommon but I can't find
them
so if I leave this anywhere on the
street is it gonna despawn I don't
remember your guys's answer
what [\h__\h] hey hey hey what the [\h__\h]
hey it's the same car
kind of you should know how precious
this is and to not hurt another fellow
same car owner
they kiss cartoon
maybe I will wait maybe I will maybe I
will
wait
up quick
man is that also the same car though
right the red one was different ah [\h__\h]
he saw me okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
ah
but I don't know
mine's told me one of those [\h__\h]
birds in my head told me to do it
please help me to do it
they manipulated me
come on
but that's what he gets that's what he
[\h__\h] gets
for hurting my car
I didn't really want your car orange is
better anyway hmm
revenge and I lost the cop too with
style yeah huh
they probably thought oh no need to
chase him he killed himself just now
but
they don't know they don't know Orange
book is this orange boat
no not quite it's just the red and the
yellow blending together okay
then
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum all
right we got nice car parked in front of
our house
apartment
and down
oh
what is that
what a weird shape
car shopping
it's a weird shape bench
hey let me look that up does it
is the the real equivalent really
looking like that Banshee car
what does
is that a
sports car consider the sports car
Dodge vipe ah a real name is Dodge Viper
from the 90s
yeah
okay oh my God
I bought a d-spawn
is considered a Widowmaker what do you
mean what what how why
do I lose my wife if I take that car
look at that beauty it's fixed now oh
yeah
looks like a frog
know the wife loses her husband
and ah the man dies for driving it crazy
okay
okay choose PB J or DM what do you want
what do you want to see
a high performance cars done are very
dangerous the end everybody wants DM
you know you know that doesn't mean
you're getting a DM from me right
um
[Music]
[Applause]
should I bring a car
oh bye-bye
my taxi now
fun way to go damn I thought that was
for you menu I'm sorry there was a time
where I dm'd a lot of kfp viewers you
know for my garlic phone to give you
guys a code
Yes actually no that was kfb artists I
guess
sometimes you are you have a chance to
get a DM
look at me
like smack on a [\h__\h] nice camera
I don't know that I got off so lightly
you all got a team
is the demon in your arms
you
indigenous a god pigeon it's glowing red
to bed
get off the drugs
live with the memories
Hayden's being moved by then from the
bacon Factory
he's been talking [\h__\h]
whatever
please Nico boy look at the contagious
oh my God coming up
I love it I love this [\h__\h] up angle
to me
I would ride I was supposed to kill
pigeons in New York
flying rats
this guy
I think we would help him even more if
that's why it's glowing red
if we bring him to a facility that will
help him um today
um is it expensive the the rockets for
this rocket launcher
because I want to try this
I think they're expensive I would assume
they're expensive but
worth it get wrecked flying rats
yesterday I was talking with shiori
about rats positively and now I'm
blowing them up with rocket launches
don't let her see this
what's the big deal
for you in an alley off the Apple White
and alderney [\h__\h] sorry Becky I'm not
listening because I'm still so happy
what am I meant to do with him
did you just say rocket launcher I'm all
ears now
okay uh the truck picking up okay okay
with rocket launchers
uh yeah I was I was uh writing a lot
about shiori yesterday like
um I had good timing I think because the
moment I wrote to her I wanted to tell
her that I watched that video that she
uploaded yesterday
[Music]
um
it's a
you know a little experimentative video
yeah the insect one I thought it was
really interesting and killed and really
well edited
so I wanted to let her know that I
really really love
what she's doing there original cute
funny creative content yeah so I wrote
her down and she was online in the right
moment and we um ended up chit chatting
a little bit
via text and she showed me pictures of
where she was at at the moment
and then we spoke a little bit about
food and then she showed me a picture of
a pigeon that she was looking at at the
moment and
she was hinting at wanting to eat the
pigeon and I said it's not gonna be very
expensive very yummy tasty
yeah talking about the pigeon
she sent me two pictures of that pigeon
apparently he was pecking at her
attacking her
thank God it was not a chicken because
that would have hurt my reputation
what kind of P's reputation I don't want
you guys to have a bad reputation out
there
um
she was just joking of course though I
mean obviously who the hell eats pigeons
although
I mean
I guess
it's possible right isn't there
something called pigeon's pie but
there's not a pigeon in there is there
I mean if you're really really really
really uh
like desperate for food
somewhere I guess yeah you know you
gotta eat a pigeon if that's all you
have at your
um hand
well
like I feel like Gollum would love
pigeons
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
but I'm glad I talked a little bit
because I
uh didn't get much opportunities to talk
with her until now yet
[Music]
I'm here gotta get the truck right over
here
oh that's a nice truck
to play at a truck
whole live song right now
let's go why is not driving let's go
hello
do I sound like a cat
when we haven't blocked in we take down
the escort and make off with the prison
why don't we just kill the
kills there and then that's probably
what derracuda told you to do in his
smacked out State problem is he's the
first one they talked to if that
happened we gotta make this look like a
prison break great
just follow
just follow for now right
I'll tune back at the three hour nap
okay a block of the boob tunnel okay
is that my car oh it's my home oh we're
here
see you later
[Music]
transport
imagine [\h__\h] a truck full of possible
and you just jump into it like it's a
bathtub of waffles and they are so
fluffy and Light
that then you bounce off off of it like
it's just a bunch of feathers
Feels Like Heaven
and then you bite into one because it's
conveniently also edible I had a
cholesterol for breakfast today
have a croissant for breakfast a lot of
the time hey
hey familiar and this time I'm actually
here when I'm supposed to be here wow
this is random SMG doing here
anyway
I am blocking the road
come pick you know I'm in position
all right man we're coming to you what's
up
Chief Derek's pal alive take out the
escort
let's keep the pal who's the escort
how life would take out
oh oh great uh uh come on
[Music]
there's a lot of people that I'm taking
out in scenes
wonderful this is fun
[Music]
uh three stars wonderful I've never I've
been successfully escaped three stars
before that's not gonna end well but
it's a mission so maybe
maybe I'll be fine
get down do I take the cop car oh what
what's going on
where's last person
no no
no no no no no no no
why why are you hiding you cowards
yeah okay still The Stockade
it's like Gatorade
uh what
what I take this
wait for Packy pocket
is coming right right
I know they're the [\h__\h] cops we gotta
lose this heat before he can send this
[\h__\h] away get out of here
oh I gotta push everything
slow moving
moving truck
what
you're kidding me right what are you
sure
wait it's not even that slow hmm
okay if we get out of this then
[Music]
gambalu
okay they are coming from me from over
there but I have no choice uh nice Dodge
maybe I should invest in Dodge Coin
okay
[Music]
don't no of course I want it was a joke
there's a spray and paint or paint and
spray or whatever but I doubt I have a
chance
but we're for a try maybe
can I
I can ah they don't take police cars ah
okay
um
I'm gonna go straight because the other
cup went that way
oh wait I'm out of the circle though oh
mother
let me chill let me chill here for a
moment how long do you have to wait for
free stuff
that's fast
whoa I thought I had to wait longer if
it's like more stars the more stars the
longer you have to wait or so
I doubted her I doubted myself too so I
don't blame you
first try
let's go
um
had to run away for like 10 minutes damn
son you chose the wrong path you gotta
choose the kiwama way
the Chihuahua way is the way
to get away from the cups
the curve is [\h__\h]
[Music]
traffic
I'm sorry for making New York traffic
worse okay I'm ditching this truck
exactly how much money do we get for
this this seems like a big job more or
less
Orange
beautiful
take us over to the cliffs in leftwood
okay
[Music]
this must be paid well
I mean it wasn't that difficult but it's
I think it's a big job
is there a report coming or something
where am I going you've gone to a far
away place man he's Irish isn't here
somewhere the cops are never fighting I
did say something about Irish guy
[\h__\h] I don't even know who sent you guys
who do I got to thank but this sounds
like a fake Irish accent though I don't
know yours I knew I was better than mine
again no matter how long I wanted in
there people on the outside world
memory all right
people's minds well who is it not Julia
she stopped writing and coming on
visiting days but I could tell she was
still thinking of Miss pirate knew it
sounds like the ghost pirates of
SpongeBob in the meantime shut the hell
up buddy all right friend thank you
sweet that thank you was sweet
healed what did he do
they may have told us but what did he do
to get in trouble I guess I'm like Mafia
trouble
the mob versus the mafia
[Music]
can we keep him
he ratted people out oh I think you're
killing him what no wait look
yeah
come on
oh
I mean I guess the whole time we are on
the side of the Italians
doesn't make sense to suddenly help the
Irish guy
I'm supposed to go for here
[Music]
yeah I feel bad
oh well we're at least letting him watch
one more Sunset before he dies and this
is a really pretty one
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h]
out you come old boy it's nice oh does
he know he's getting killed the sea here
no no things with freedom right you've
made me a happy man boys now it's time
to tell me who asked you to do this name
Derek McCreery he knows he's my brother
Derek but he ratted me out he's the
reason I ended up in that place to start
with the spineless so you thought you
Ratt him out this is the last Sunset
you're ever going to see enjoy it Nico
send him packing
oh man
I don't want to look at him he's not
even like doing anything
man
you don't want to hurt you look at you
look at your cute feet
what
[Music]
oh my God
thank you leg
and seven thousand five hundred for
something so evil
that's sad we got him out of prison just
to kill him
and he thought she was out Hayden is
dead
good for you to you oh wait it doesn't
that sounds like we finished his quest
line
did we
kind of an anti-climatic
ending
I want a party I want more emotion I
want
champagne bottles popping
and confetti
flying and ruining my frame rate
my bit rate I mean
foreign
that's all this and we're close to J's
but we might as well go to Jay
finishing up everything
well I might as well ignore Kate because
I'm not ever gonna like I don't care
about our is that even gonna have any
concept consequences on me besides our
friendship not being good but if I never
want to maintain a good friendship with
her then it doesn't matter right does it
I'm never gonna
try to
you know
do something with her so
no need to fake it
unnecessarily oh
we saw we saw we saw we saw you know I
was saying
oh she's complaining to me probably now
in SMS I was saying I was watching the
Apex stream for like quite a while this
is I've never watched an apex footage
longer than five seconds but yesterday I
watched you girls like for 40 minutes
because
I don't know I suddenly was interested
in seeing first of all if I was really
as good as she claimed
and then she wasn't so
I it was interesting to watch you girls
panic and
um every time you were like saying
something it sounded like you were
suffering you wanted to get out of there
and and and FPS wasn't your jam and I
just felt for you I felt like damn this
girl she's me for real for real
but you did well you did well Lisa you
tried your best
we're not great my method is too high
don't like yeah let's go I love you my I
even wrote in the comments I don't know
if you saw it but I said oh she's my
she's my spirit animal whenever
you win FBS is my spirit animal
can we can we hide can we stay inside
can we not okay we go back
love that
yeah
I feel you
but looked fun you girls were bantering
it was cute
not you as well tell me it ain't you as
well
king of spank you [\h__\h] piece of [\h__\h]
I'm done with you done whatever what the
[\h__\h] did I do but I Ain't Going Quiet Mr
pecorino I don't know I came as quickly
as I could
he was wearing a [\h__\h] Warrior oh that
is a
is my personal body God we're in a wire
I raised that kid like he was my own
that food that was screaming
when my son killed himself Anthony
became my son uh-huh nowadays the world
is a [\h__\h] where is Anthony
I heard he's wearing a wire so why freak
out I call him up he's such a [\h__\h] he
leaves his cell phone on so we speak
uh-huh
he's got states of course oh already
Jesus
what a chump
he freaks out on the phone and I put the
fear of God in him oh I think maybe I've
talked him out of it
then he has a goddamn heart attack on
the phone what I'm thinking problem
solved he's dying right in front of my
ears
in the left one Hospital under heavy car
is that New York of course he's got you
on the [\h__\h] tape too of course
do you want me to talk to him I want you
to welcome after that I want you to kill
all the other rats I surround myself
okay okay don't worry you mean the
flying rat the pigeons
oh God this Mission hey what's wrong
with this mission
sounds like fun though but there's a am
I sensing uh we're starting a shooting
situation in the hospital
this mission is easy this one is tough
what the [\h__\h]
what why are you guys split
eat easy watch out duality
this one is East what East or easy
I saw two people riding its East is it
East or is it easy
what do you mean
run over that guy why does he have money
what do you know that I don't know also
what is that roof
it's that roof
I'm cuddling
the car
cozy
cozy cute
going on with me
maybe I'll ask for a doctor in the
hospital to help me
oh it's right there boys
excuse me
both humping and car stuck
I
I guess I'm kind of lonely or something
silence Anthony
um I learned of a way to silence people
in the handmaid's tale
that might interest you
what why is it time to talk about balls
but I got him
um yeah how about uh sewing
did I say it correctly this time the
mouth together they do that in the late
season of handmaid's tale was [\h__\h]
terrifying
how do I get where I want to go
you have to go up a floor it's not a
there's no there's no um Arrow
is it error
any inquiries look at them leaning so
cool
any inquiries so okay wait I keep on
saying I saw that's so German
slick
hello hello hello they won't talk to me
No Scrubs subscribers in my life for me
and everything on the passenger side on
my best friend's trying to holler at me
I don't what I can still go through I
don't want no scrubs subscribers in my
life from me hanging on the passenger
side on this message back this thing
just like me
try to holler at me
I didn't know there was a path here
what is this door
was in there because the doors ah wait
that's what it has guards because
look after him oh yeah well of course I
I I I I that is my priority
get out of here wanted to stretch my
legs anyway you're good boss
Peg is that you shh no it's not it's not
pecorino of course
[\h__\h] I'm getting really like so hungry
that I I'm feeling sick let me I have a
snack here thank God
I'm gonna take a bite out of my
snack
um
[Music]
it might be hi
you little [\h__\h] I love you
mom
yeah so listen yeah
oh can I just pull the plug can I do
that instead of shooting him that would
be more discreet
what could I now just I don't know
suffocate him with a pillow
they won't notice that one so quickly
either I think
oh
sure he's not in a Como hmm
[Music]
I'm gonna use a RPG again
Overkill
oh
my she's chilling on the floor now cute
um
I can't close the door guys
what is this um this looks like a lot of
Lotto lotto machine Lots
bingo bingo machine
hmm
can I close the shoulders I can't do any
of that what you guys are suggesting
this is not real life okay guys
what are we gonna do how are we gonna do
this
how
what
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm so sorry guys so sometimes sometimes
I I I have some moments where I
mess it up very obviously
um
God damn it
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
I panic because
they got the first shot on me that's not
how it's supposed to be okay
I call the shots
[Music]
oh yeah right it was really close this
mission is good
destination very close like it I like it
do you think I'll have to escape with a
car afterwards then maybe I'll park it
in the right direction first
pre-planning
oh this car is a nice color
this is how most people park at a
hospital wait I'm having issues right
now
okay this should be good
mama
uh there may be cops okay do not enter
the building with a weapon John there
may be cups okay okay I don't have the
weapon right now but I also I also have
any more armor now
but it's far away so I'm gonna tribe
about
it
can I wear it already oh wait I'm
wearing it
it's oh
weird time
travel logic hello
oh okay
I see it
um
[Music]
how are you supposed to do this
sneak out while like killing every
single one slowly or run
run run run
without armor I don't think the running
strategy is a good one
um
what boss oh they're actually oh
oh
oh looks like I messed something up are
you kidding me can I just leave
okay I need armor I need armor I need
armor
[Laughter]
don't run when you exit
what do you mean don't run
why
why what
do you want me to kill them slowly
walk them you think you think if I do it
slowly they will not expect it with me
and this guy has a new car every day
if you walk it takes some longer to
notice okay okay so you're saying just
don't be suspicious okay no
and
okay okay
just be cool man okay
[Music]
I got it I got it
they make us come all the way outside to
smoke [\h__\h] fast We're Not Gonna
notice it at all
oh
you don't have that you know God complex
thingy I guess it's my bedside manner
John you're terrible
foreign
okay uh let's hope they never notice
it's looking though
you're here to see the boss he's just go
to sleep Anthony you look tired
[Music]
go out this quickly and discreetly
quickly
can I run now can I run now
no okay
I think I'm gonna notice
okay it's over
[Applause]
[Music]
I didn't get the Mad Kids oh my God
stay in life unlike him
I'm staying alive baby
just need to learn how to do a curve
[Applause]
[Music]
I did it
so the mission was kind of easy
kind of
[\h__\h] him no I'm driving
[Applause]
God damn it New York
okay that was good good maneuver
can I go to his house
no
um
I don't know what I'm doing
[\h__\h] I thought I could travel
and they're not finding middle for some
reason are they not allowed to drive up
here
are they scared scared of the mafia
[Music]
it's a beautiful thing
Oh there's uh at the end of the circle
okay all right all right all right all
right all right
there it is birthday
said okay okay yeah
[Music]
oh I can't believe it's only been three
and a half hours I feel like I've done
like a million missions today look at
that car I don't think you will be
seeing Anthony on the witness stand
or anybody else I know for that matter
this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] turn in everybody
hmm
a robotic color like it's black
but it has green metallic finish
now I'm more curious about the color
than I mean the combination of the color
and the color
hmm
it's like one of those
stopped working on it's like one of
those stinky beetles
or those flies that are like green shiny
shiny green
that is not really a thing that you
would want your car to be compared with
right so maybe don't choose that color
all right what do we got um
why we gotta go back to the first island
now
gambetti
I'll do PB first
and I'll also go wait wait first two
get me back some armor
maybe different car on the way
[Music]
um
no beetles are fun
[Music]
um
yeah
sorry I'm
trying to
eat fast I feel like I'm choking
I'm joking
as long as I'm choking I'm dying on
stream
is actually preferable because
if I die offstream then nobody's gonna
notice
at least for
I don't know two days
sometimes I think about that what's
gonna happen if if I just like
don't function anymore
for some reason alone in my apartment
huh
who's gonna notice I think the first one
to notice would be janma
like you guys are going to notice it
because I'm not keeping up my my
schedule
and then I know I know
it what
is my keyboard
my cats will eat me no no I don't think
they would do that they have enough
Kibbles to stay alive for a while they
have like backup Kibbles
I gotta tell Jen mom
uh
actually no that then it's too late
already
I'm gonna say I'm gonna tell her how to
call
um the the healing people
in Austria but How's that gonna help her
when I'm already dead
what a weird [\h__\h] tangent man
[Laughter]
I'm feeling people man
science the energy drink it's it's the
energy drink
can I get some
ammo for my rocket launcher um
where is uh
wait ah as this stuff
[Music]
thousand
one two mm-hmm and I got plenty of money
when am I gonna use that oh I can't
carry any more lamb
lame
what is this color in New York what the
[\h__\h] are we in some kind of like 50s
movie
and hearing jazz music somewhere what is
this why am I here why am I here what is
this mission is this which man what what
no it's
no it's it's a sharpshooter thingy hello
I didn't want to do it
let's go baby
I ran into it because it looked like I
had to go to my instincts
I get you when you've taken care of
something for me call me on my cell
can I just ignore this now that I
accepted it I
have the targets over in the actor
Industrial Park make
no
um
your contact will leave you
weapons and body armor for each mission
that sounds like there's a lot I don't
want to do it
what if I die then it's basically
canceled no
I need to heal myself though somewhere
oh
um maybe I'll just do just one
um
[Music]
uh food
food taco
[Music]
I'm taking your car
what's up I need your car it's close and
short yeah okay
but kind of need some food
let me know if you see something on the
way
I am eating in real life but I need food
in game as well
how are we
gonna kill this person are we doing a
sniping thing here
[Music]
I wouldn't mind
uh
sniping someone
someone
can we get McDonald's
no we should get kfp
why about the targets making a deal okay
uh where's weapon I'm just gonna I'm
gonna use this
oh wait um
how's the AOE damage on this one
oh
let's see
oh that's bad well waste I went way too
far
[Music]
mistake
I'm gonna do it anyway
I'm gonna do it from the car
it's the most comfortable
there's someone elsewhere
did he
run away or was he always there
that's weird
but no one left
in the original spot right
comfortable violence and he's moving
he's on the Run
the memory is he in a on a bike
oh
yeah
attack what
oh
yeah what now Target got away
ah
whatever
Fred those eggs got broken before we
could uh make an omelette I've made
Provisions for this brother you'll be on
the outside
no I'm not so good ending
hmm
[Music]
all right
back to the main missions
[Music]
ah this way
I'm surprised that I didn't get any
stars for that because
the police was shooting at me no
and I just ran away from them they
forget about me did they what happened
there
were they shooting for the other ones
well then good that I controlled myself
and didn't shoot back at the police
very good
wow police for once working with me
on my side
as my
as my friends
[Music]
guys
how much gameplay do I have left
what do you think any anyone who played
this game
who can guess it
not much
[Music]
at least two minutes yeah
five hours not so much
six to seven hours five six seven
one two three four five six seven you
make me feel like a lover doesn't sound
a pause menu that just says the
percentage but that's for like
completing it completely and I'm not
gonna complete it completely
um here
fifty percent but that's like obviously
like you know not about like uh clearing
the game is clear clearing everything
Roman Roman
my man
okay all right man let's play darts I
pick you up in next hour actually okay
because I never played darts in this
game before and I'm kind of kind of
low-key curious where is he though hey
I don't know if I can even reach
in one hour
yeah
it was taxi okay
[Music]
um
um wow
if I find one
I'm in the middle of nowhere
what's up wait that was right at PB
though I was right there I'm sorry yeah
so you wish to leave the current game
and enter the video what
I'm a little sorry wrong man I'm sorry
I'm sorry
the thing is I'm right at my mission
cousin I am no longer able to do darts
with you sorry all right Nico we should
do this another time later on
thank you for being so understanding
if you watch the Vault later Roman you
will understand
here we are
and I have like two bikes left
did you see a [\h__\h] helicopter on your
way here no I don't think so okay let's
go come on quick we gotta head towards
Fortuna
Factory off of August Street
[Music]
a lot of [\h__\h] Russians have got to
Charlie mate they told us
um
that it was us that took the sugar who
knows how the [\h__\h] they knew I didn't
tell nobody it don't matter what has to
happen is that you gotta take out chubby
Charlie before he Choppers it into
Algonquin to tell the commission that
we're knocking off the enchiladas action
so I go into this Factory and I ice this
fat Charlie that's right I'm gonna go
make a lot of noise so no one thinks I
had anything to do with it
thanks I guess okay
[Music]
I finished eating my Pizza snack
so
I can talk properly again sorry
I can at least thanks to that
uh survive a little bit longer
[Music]
I am my health is still [\h__\h] oh
how close are we we're very close I
gotta find some food here
uh is that the strip club
[Music]
is there food at this strip club I'm
sure strip clubs have food but
at least like like potato chips or
something right
but that's not really what I need right
now
sodas
sodas well there's no freaking food and
whenever you want to look for food you
can't find anything what is this I'll I
that alcohol
let's go finally I can is that one open
wait it looks close no no way
it's dead
what the [\h__\h]
take off the logo with your clothes
because you are giving me false hopes
for real for real
um don't make me think that you're
saving me from my demise and then bam
went out of business
what the hell
closed by health inspector
yeah because they were using pigeons
instead of chickens for their food it's
gonna make it easier for the feds to
tell us
candle can I Uber some food or what
tench over what is this like
what is this this is uh Trend recently
with everybody adding the name in front
of over
what is this
why is this happening
put these eggs
this is supposed to be like eggs that
look like pills and they're in the pill
in the egg carton that's funny that's
cute
Joe
who is Jova
I see hot dogs
show body
oh Joe Biden meme
ah
okay no more dances I just want a hot
dog
no he's dancing or is he okay I think
we're good
[Music]
I can't move the camera when he eats a
hot dog
this hot dog is my savior
Bill why'd you get out did you also want
a hot dog I'm sorry I thought he was
just a random pedestrian
okay while are there free hot dog stands
all here
and not more scattered in the city
so that I could actually find them huh
you're just making yourself more
competition
would be smarter to spread out a little
bit more and it looks like they don't
have brains
um
yo I got five DMs
I'm sure that at least half of those
are my music things and I need to look
at them
moving on
a little bit I'm so popular no I'm so
busy
sorry
oh my God
happens sometimes happens to the best of
us
give them a look soon I walked to yes
[Music]
should I check them let me check them
really quickly
maybe one of them is from narissa
no oh
[Music]
okay one of them is a voice message damn
it
okay okay
um okay okay
[Music]
um okay
um
okay yeah
[Music]
way good
no need to immediately reply maybe
didn't listen to the voice message Joe
all right now the way I seize it there's
two ways it can go down you burst in the
front and hit them in the face with
everything you got otherwise you slip
around the back go into the basement and
[\h__\h] them up their asses
yeah
decisions decisions I'll leave it up to
you see you later
oh dear uh
um
I'm looking like JD out here my face is
so oily too uh what do you recommend
um can he laughing with no car what the
hell
okay
I I'm gonna go where life leads me
two
I don't even know where front and back
is
they're almost the same okay
where's the entrance
I recommend getting Turk for help
can I I love scrubs so much
here
um oh wait can I go for here this looks
like I could even break it
is it are there inside
it's it's no inside
it's outside
ladder
there's nobody here
nice car though
do I just walk in
who the [\h__\h] just walks in
oh what do something like that
whoa nice
I hear people but I don't see them
they're out there aren't they okay
Dead Brother dead [\h__\h] where are
you guys show yourself
where are they
wait wait
I love me some grenades
[Music]
it's gonna blow up some some good stuff
yeah
second one
hey beautiful
that's what I like to see
that's my cover now
if if Q would react Mommy
[Music]
okay it's really hard to say
ah
are they alive
someone's still talking but I think he's
above me
oh
[Applause]
headshot for there even though I didn't
see [\h__\h]
all right
wow
chase him is he going
is he going is he escaping right now
because you saw me is he going down he
must be going down he must be leaving
the building right
up really
I feel like his next step would be to
leave
okay
They're All Dead you
saw
honestly I might be pretty good at Apex
if I gave it a try
in your butt
mm-hmm
anybody still up there nowhere
okay
looking good
should I be fast oh
okay yeah yeah yeah show me your faces
chocolate Chopper Chopper Chopper
Chopper
okay what did he say is he living on a
in a chopper because he's living
on a chopper
you like
yeah oh
sneaked up on me hey okay
where is this uh Chopper that you're
talking about uh where's his exit I just
lost track of where I am out this way
that took away all of my armor at once
that moment is not but I think isn't he
Oh I thought he was dead where's he
going
no but I don't really need it
I would prefer some armor but okay what
the [\h__\h] where where where
how do I
oh
is the script that can you not die
before he gets into the shopper
can I go from here nope
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um
yeah it was the worst time to reload
thank you for nothing
I'm a stream tonight oh
is she streaming
how about using a real weapon what's
your problem what's up all the hate on
the SMG
hey
here we go you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
is there another Med kit somewhere
SMGs or close coffee though it works for
me for everything don't you see I just
shot him really far and I shot him
really close
I have some g-sniping
isn't she comfortable because it's like
small but I'm literally going to die
uh
um once I get up there he's probably
going to show me
someone over there
okay that's it that's it that's it
that's probably it
laughs this one is for the old country
I'm Gonna Eat You Alive
one HP and their dreams
what the [\h__\h] is that
Oh I thought that was an HP
okay uh which way
is it
I'm so scared you full
foreign
[Music]
getting sniped
please please
oh Hallelujah
yeah the dream was
fulfilled I almost fell off I almost
fell off
because these characters they walk like
get up how do you
sometimes
oh
okay super scripted could have never
killed him
I I
I I let me bring out my rocket launcher
first
oh
wait let me uh which one is my there
we go easy easy
the easiest way to take uh down a
helicopter
quick business oh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
was that my car
and all right all right
[Music]
nice
I think he's dead
yeah I think we did a great job how did
I get down here though uh where was the
ladder
I'm stuck here forever somebody
I'm scared scared what
what
how do you
jump down here what
[\h__\h] ah over there
use the shortcut to the hospital no
no I don't want to go back there
okay uh
gosh slippery shoes my shoes are so
slippery
mmm
I'm just gonna jump guys I'm gonna jump
and lather is there
we don't see it wait a minute here Ah
that's up
I'll wait maybe here
step by step
there wasn't even a ladder there but
this brings me a little bit lower this
should be okay
yeah it's fine broke my ankle
but
my mental strength is going to keep me
alive yeah and my my super cocky
attitude
confidence
[Music]
ah
yo guys I just made your heart stop for
a moment didn't I
wait
oh what's going on over here
she's stealing the car
yeah
water
is this what I think that was like
wasn't she
offering uh
service and then
she forced herself
onto the passenger
uh
you will not reject me for a night out
with your friends drinking no uh
I will have it my way
NPCs are doing very suspicious things
here in GTA 4.
they think I don't know this honestly
like no it's kind of weird
it's kind of creeping me out because
most of the time the NPCs are just you
know doing nothing
nothing of importance nothing
interesting
but then sometimes you you see crazy
[\h__\h] like that and you just wonder maybe
they have a life and a mind of Their Own
and maybe they're not just NPCs
but maybe they're like real Souls stuck
in the game
and asking like screaming for Help by
trying to get my attention with these
weird Acts
you know what I mean they're real people
more or less it's like they're they're
cursed to be in the video game
because that is not normal NPC Behavior
as you can see like normally GTA NPCs
wouldn't do that
obviously a cry for help
[Music]
I mean
this
but that's just a theory
a game theory
man
either tell me more tell me more tell me
more
about Henry VII tell me more tell me
Which lady is he gonna take next
can I still even a big big boat like
this a ship
or is this like I guess you can't steal
planes in this game either so you
probably can still ship like this
you know okay
[Music]
so much for the land of opportunities
and freedom
lies it's all lies it's all lies
okay I'll see you later yeah okay
thank you
it's not what it looks like
okay it's not like that
we talk
so do us all a favor and keep quiet at
there
isn't that the wife from right from
pecorino
I was gonna say what is she doing here
maybe I need help on time maybe I can
give you a call
what do you mean
yummy
I need to find something out about
someone maybe you can help are you
[\h__\h] blackmailing me huh
asking for a favor why is everybody here
so jumpy why do you think I put my neck
on the line for you
because I need help with something
you know since you don't look like
you're full of crap
how could I say no
sweet that was sweet Chit Chat come on
let's go let's go
we're heading back up to that old house
off beaverhead Avenue in West Ike
take a bell to the old mansion I'm gonna
take this car you want this car
okay leaving the American Truck behind
that age that my nephew
he's just been sitting there yeah call
it a cooling off here yeah we took it
but we don't know who was watching it
beforehand so you'll just left it with
Frankie yeah we put it in an isolated
Place hopefully any attention it was
getting would be noticed Frankie's one
guy he can disappear real easy with
defensive plus he's a smart kid he's
related to my ex-wife and she was smart
enough to rule my life with one lawsuit
so it's been long enough you think we're
going to be okay to pick it up no
trouble look I don't ever assume
Something's Gonna Go Down easy without
any trouble that's what keeps me alive
and out of the pen we'll see when we get
there as long as we don't see any
helicopters fans suspicious gardeners
talking into here please if none of
that's going on then we're okay it's
okay I have an RPG that works for
everything we can take down the
helicopter the gardeners anything
all of an RPG
no
what the [\h__\h] was that curve you stupid
ass truck driver
man
the power to paralyze pain in 24 hours
her last Pain Train is a chiropractor in
24 hours what the [\h__\h]
it's 99 bucks or your money back
[Music]
interesting
armor ah mamma mia again it's like after
every [\h__\h] mission I have to go buy
some armor can I deliver it to me
automatically at this point or can I do
double armor
like a genius I wish man is it so
annoying
I'm sorry I'm sorry for lashing out I
will be calm now
please don't
have an intervention on me
I am getting a little bit crazy from
doing so many missions okay
ah
[Music]
and I think the
energy drink
because I drank almost all of it
was making my heart go Doki Doki Doki
Doki Doki Doki
[Music]
Little Jacob might have armor what
and I think it's okay I'm going to the
usual place
they could at least like have a few more
of these armor shops around the islands
like
why one in one Island
can you at least give me two
the usual place
don't worry it's different from the
usual room
if you mix a little chicken you can buy
ammo enormous
what if I'd have known this since the
beginning and if I'd have known how
annoying it's gonna get to buy armor
every single time
was in the wrong place
then I would have focused on
that
game tells you well but
did I look like I was listening and
really registering that information
now
of course not
get in
get in come on come on we're on a
mission
all right
yeah I'm feeling the after effects of
the energy drink
nice car cute
cute I like the
American Diner
car looks like a diner
[Music]
um
I'm crashing
yeah don't do energy drinks kids
don't do it
they don't feel good they make you get a
heart
attacks to tell us
I can't believe like those people who
drink them like every second day or so
or even every day like oh my God
it's like almost as bad as
chain smoking Maybe
on the long term and I don't know it
might really be don't you think tell me
tell me I don't know exactly
but I think it's bad
yeah some people drink twice and I even
drank a small one some people drink the
big ones from Monster and so on
[Music]
a few weekends do that please no uh
please don't my God
me meeting isn't that crazy doesn't that
mean crazy makes sense because it says
crazy tattoo machine
and song
foreign
[Music]
okay
that's cute what a cute truck making
sounds should I get a hot dog I'm not
completely full in half so maybe I will
surprise
[Music]
two please
doing your contacts are the best I saw a
chart
uh the other day maybe on Twitter or so
of all kinds of hot dogs from all over
the world
oh
it was really interesting because they
look really really yummy I'll take this
car now it's no it's like
it's like even better cute
um
yeah some hot dogs were really weird
like there was a picture in the
description of what's inside and some
somewhere really weird
and some I would never even describe as
a hot dog but okay
[Music]
but it
can try them all out
maybe I should go on a hot dog Quest all
over the world travel every country
and and and and make it to a little
little side goal side quest
to try
this car is nice to try a hot dog
everywhere
that's actually a fun thing to
do when you travel a lot give yourself a
go like that very specific fun goal
is a hot is a hot cup a sandwich
I mean in some way yeah I guess
glitzy tourism what is that that's just
it some of you guys are saying Glizzy
what is that what the [\h__\h] I've never
heard that before
Lizzy Glizzy
it's a word for hot dog oh what
what it sounds cute
like it's uh sparkling you've seen
anyone
I ain't seen a soul boss it's a ghost
house
oh so there's no souls but there's
ghosts inside
Souls of ghosts so you're lying to me
you're lying
into this for you
a horse
wait that ain't a horse
sorry my brain my brain is thinking
everything must be taken literally right
now what the [\h__\h]
are these FBI people
you can't follow me because those are
not police cars
are you shooting for me thank you follow
Bell oh
Olympics
I don't have to shoot get me close to
the boss and I'll take out that bed car
okay I don't know if I should really
trust you with that job maybe we should
do it the other way around
but okay
should I help I'll help
I'm better at this
[Music]
oh yeah bye
okay let's see
all thanks to me
I'm also a little bit on fire though are
you [\h__\h]
not good
it's not good that's not good no no I'm
not gonna
get it did it fix itself
oh it fixed itself
okay [\h__\h]
I mean he's not gonna get busted anyway
it's okay he's gonna be fine
I fought fire on the car was a clear
indication of it about to about the uh
you know what I mean how much time being
about to be blown up was so English
he won't let me switch cards man
beds are all over me I'm sorry man it's
just I only got can I go this way
got that kid you
want you
back
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah okay
okay
let me do it again
look at that car man
clocked up absolutely clicked up
and we're still being chased
he's the Bell who got away
come on
okay
okay one more time
shut up can I please skip this dialogue
there was a wedding present for your
nephew he's my nephew for my ex-wife I
might give him words
[Music]
I regret my life choices
Man Ray runs his mouth so much that no
one pays my
face I believe I drink water I've been
drinking some water dough
you think I should drink more is that
gonna help
they have such problems I have no more
coffee I don't
drink coffee I should force myself to
get to like coffee
coffee's at least not kind of negative
side effect does it
as far as I know
[Music]
what addiction
I mean besides the Dayton is it it's not
bad on your heart or anything right
[Music]
yeah do you get like caffeine crash of
coffee as bad as you do with energy
drinks
[\h__\h]
that's why people just don't stop
drinking coffee all day
I mean okay that was obvious kiwawa
thank you for pointing out the obvious
you're welcome kiwawa
sometimes you just have to State the
obvious you know you know you go outside
and you say [\h__\h] it's hot everybody
knows but you say it anyway
or or it starts snowing and you say oh
my God it's snowing and we know but you
know you gotta say it you gotta say it
to make it real
yes
not as bad as of energy drink
s maybe I didn't need to do that just
now because he was gonna stay behind
anyway
what if I shoot no okay I can't use the
rocket launcher when I have a hand on
the wheel I guess
okay
that's not good a bell are you okay
wow that blew up right in his face
okay stay calm stay calm stay calm
you don't notice the 50 fans watching
these cars and Phil was just paranoid
give me a break man I got a lot on my
mind you know I didn't have much time to
scope this out my Ma's kind of sick I've
been looking at him and my sister I've
been putting her through college shut up
these feds are all over me I'm sorry man
it's just I only got married the other
day God I love that kid
I don't want to see a [\h__\h] picture
trying to get this out of this situation
maybe then you can spend time with your
wife instead of some jailhouse [\h__\h]
of course man I got nothing we're
probably gonna get back up to three
stars again aren't doing
because now we're dealing with the
actual cops here apparently
left left left left
and right right right right
damn they're fast
[Music]
this is scripted because last time Belle
was busted really early on too
but is it because of the distance
we're gonna lose the boss
Get Wrecked
okay as long as I stay close maybe he's
not gonna get busted
nice Buzz
ah took the wrong path can I go here
[\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h] where did I go
oh [\h__\h] they're destroying us
wait please don't give up on me yet
please please please please please
please please give me another chance
I'm trying I'm trying
maybe maybe
how many times
all right
Lord have mercy on me
what what did he say
something about they're on his ass or so
but I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm here
I'm here where are you are there up
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
[\h__\h] ah
I was so close
fisherman
[Music]
we're heading back up to that old house
off beaverhead oh shut up I'm gonna
listen to the stupid sport again
don't don't talk to me we just listen
hahaha
oh beautiful silence
ah
sorry I was losing it I'm losing it
I feel uneasy I
move on move on GTA silent GTA
this is so relaxing though you know it
could be such a relaxing game
oh [\h__\h] oh
my my ears hurt my ears hurt
no they don't they don't hurt they don't
hurt I'm okay I'm imagining things
take a deep breath in
it's okay it's gonna be okay but when I
turn down the audio
it's not only that he's not that I can't
hear him I also can't read the subtitles
isn't he supposed to be talking or do
they recognize
and just turn off all conversation
when I turn off the audio
what the [\h__\h] what's up
what's the thing is controls
where they gonna listen to the radio
why last time you wanted to talk to me I
was gonna say like that sounds like he's
about to say let's just listen to the
radio
[Music]
is that a thing that I
uh
uh that that he says only when you
repeat the mission a million times
okay
they don't talk after the third or
fourth try oh my God okay
anyway
[Music]
third fourth try what
I am already losing control of the car
let's blow it up let's blow it up let's
blow it up let's blow it up early early
yeah
I'm too close I don't want to be so
close when it blows up
all right
nice
well it's just me behind you don't worry
I got you oh
what did I do do I shoot this nah now
it's just normal Chase right until he
reaches his destination like last time
I don't have to kill this police car
s are all over me
okay
It's gotta stay close
[Music]
no problem no problem
I can't get much closer than this oh
although I'm losing speed because of my
tire being [\h__\h]
I am tired of this Chase
honey
enough
that was good though wasn't it
foreign
I'm keeping up I'm keeping up
right son
don't worry I got you
I got you
Pikachu what
speaking of Pikachu I found I saw like
some Pokemon merchandise today that's
like Pokemon mosaic
whoa [\h__\h] that I I I I tried my hardest
to go to the left side I swear
it looked really cute it wasn't only
Pikachu it was like several Pokemon
um
and like they were made into a mosaic
pattern
where are we where are we
here
really really cute
big recommend
but I don't know where you can buy it
where the [\h__\h] are we where is he
ah
all right that's in the cars but not yet
right I don't know man he's so he's
still in Balance soon look wait oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] eh
but you just you just said how am I
supposed to get back up here
okay that's a fail everybody that's a
fail
yep
[Music]
what
um
I'm sorry I'm on the energy drink crash
it's hard it's hard to understand
I'm just trying to register the most
most important information
and my brain
sensors everything else
um
oh man
I'm feeling sick again
a little bit only a little bit
um
I'm going to finish the stupid ass
mission
no matter what
um
chunkers break you have a
great idea you should be the president
you should make decisions
[Music]
in the USA
you seem like somebody
who knows how to make the right decision
when in doubt when in trouble
take chunky wonky break
you can be my vice president
then suddenly I'm ranked
as your what assistant
the power Dynamic is being flipped over
[Music]
okay if he is the president and I am the
vice president
sounds good
let's do it
I want to
I want to be on the passenger seat
instead
hey
all right I was supposed to shoot uh
let's lower this thing up
yep see how early I can get rid of those
oh wait be careful be careful
honestly how that doesn't end the
mission is beyond me
fans watching these cars I thought Phil
was just paranoid give me a break man I
got a lot of my
mind's kind of sick I've been looking
after her and my sister I've been
putting her through college
fans are all over I'm sorry man it's
just I only got married the other day
what I love that kid you want to see a
picture I don't want to see a [\h__\h]
picture look at this out of this
situation no I want to see the picture
though show
we're gonna lose the force
no no no no we are not don't talk so
negatively just think positively and
everything's going to be all okay
Google
I'm going to mess it up again
[Music]
oh my gosh beautiful I love that
good job
love Buzz
good bus
appreciate Buzz [\h__\h] that also repeated
itself
I did a barrel roll
but this time this time I'm gonna catch
up
[Laughter]
yeah okay
um
where where how where exactly here right
like what what am I what exactly am I
supposed to do now
what
I didn't get the calling yet
give me the controller there's no
controller it's a keyboard
okay ah there it is
this this is better this is the good
timeline
I see where he's going out
I got him I'm I'm I'm on Route okay
so they ditching it here okay take uh my
car here take me
ah grab the stuff from the truck and
follow me I got a van we could use
grab the stuff
where are we going where are we oh
you want some of this
where are we going
no more
I'm sorry
go go go go go go this seems like a big
mission again here huh okay I think it's
time again for the rocket launcher
[Music]
more
okay
you want more you get what you asked for
and more
did I just throw no okay
he's so lucky lucky lucky lucky I
followed through it like against the
container again
don't fail the mission and do it all
over again
what are you doing there sliding through
with everything
okay we did it
we [\h__\h] did it what what how strong
am I the impact of takadasikiara
moves cars like I'm the last airbender
is that a helicopter
no problem I got the perfect weapon for
that
but my stars might oh not look good
after that
get in the bed
okay okay
is that gonna blow up
you're welcome to blow up after I'm gone
okay here we go
here we go this circle is huge I don't
even see the end of it
next time
[Applause]
it's my European jeans manipulating my
every move
[\h__\h]
the tire is so [\h__\h]
at least like shoot my other Tire too on
the other side so that I can keep
balance please oh let's see the end of
the
City ah
now I don't see it anymore but I'm gonna
continue going that way yes yes that's
that's the right way unless suddenly a
car is gonna show up over there but I
think it's looking good
looking good it's looking good
yes yes yes
how much more of this
it's been some [\h__\h] up [\h__\h]
but you're a good earner I got respect
for you this better be worth a lot of
money because it was kind of dramatic
okay I read it it's five times
you did it yes I did I saved his life I
saved everybody's life
as I always do
[Music]
yeah
um
this should probably be my last mission
today if I
don't want to
lose my mind
[Laughter]
but what do you think guys if I ended
here now
how long will it take me tomorrow five
hours
last time I asked you guys it was an
hour ago or so
oh I'm I can read some super jets yeah I
think so I'll I'll Gamble
four or five last time I asked you guys
for an estimate for uh what was it totk
you guys totally overestimated the time
I would need um I did it way faster
and I even was stalling I think
I was stalling
fine I'm just gonna assume it'll take me
five hours tomorrow but today
I I'm already exhausted at four hours
40.
but I'll just try to not drink an energy
drink tomorrow
then I can go on for longer I think
yeah
but we gotta pray for this movie to let
me [\h__\h] sleep
[Music]
um
because now I still have to get up every
time to show her that there is food in
the new cat food dispenser
and she also just doesn't
she doesn't have a like a routine in
terms of time not a very like
clear one
I see a pattern but it's not always the
same so I can't even be
sure
[Music]
yeah we'll take some time for her to
learn but I don't have time I need sleep
oh
nice driving Nico stop feeding her after
you get up it's not an option it's a
choice just holding me at gunpoint
I swear I try it I tried for weeks to
just ignore her but she
has no mercy she has no mercy on me
twelve thousand really what the [\h__\h] we
only had one single job in this game
that gave me like 100k
and every other job after that was
mediocre
well 250k wow that was that was the
money
compared to all these other jobs that's
ridiculous
Kate believe me you don't want to deal
with me right now I'm not the same
person that you think you know
also I've wasted so many RPG shots
so much money 5 000 bucks for each shot
but it's okay right we're ending the
game tomorrow we gotta use all this
money
[Music]
I love that song it's cute okay I can't
find a [\h__\h] taxi so
you know what this means I had no choice
I ran around long enough trying to find
a taxi and I failed I'm sorry it's not
like I didn't try
[Music]
I guess I could have called one
but well you know my brain is working at
only 50 capacity
no tell me
you want to flex on me huh
Flex it try flexing do you know how much
my car cost
nothing because I don't have one
[Music]
meow meow meow
I have arrived
it's home sweet home where my orange
homeless wear your orange car is isn't
it
yeah I'll I'll park this car
random ass car
I don't have to use my beautiful orange
car next time
okay
let's
take a break
in my luxurious
apartment I mean if you have so many
the upkeep is possibly a little bit a
little bit expensive
can't
uh
what
can't have all of them be luxurious
Apartments the cost
000 bucks
per month
what are those
nice okay
let me save
thanks for playing GTA today thank you
[Music]
hey
did you enjoy it guys
[Music]
I mean maybe the past 40 minutes were a
bit painful because I was in pain but
did you enjoy it anyways
[Music]
Nico what the [\h__\h] I ain't heard from
you in a [\h__\h] age let's play some
pool
oops my game crashed packet I'm so sorry
my game crashed ah oh no oh no how could
that have happened
huh
that is so unfortunate oh
no what a tragedy
[Music]
guys don't go yet okay there's Super
Chat reading and I have to show you uh
my new ending screen
before you go
a GTA specific ending screen let's go
[Music]
um
thank you for memberships okay okay I'm
going to calm down and read super chats
which nobody believes me right nobody
believes me I am not very
believable right now
[Music]
I'm going to calm down though I'm going
to which which which
OBS scene do you want to see
which one do you want it to be
let's go here
oh no
there goes Kate the chicken
sorry I'm not interested in a
relationship
I'm busy
I cannot go do darts or whatever reveal
go find someone else take a hint
and find someone else please
let me fix the size of chat
wait ah keep on changing something else
isn't there a kfb viewer it's called
Kate doll
I I think I remember actually
particularly
I'm pretty sure
I'm sorry
[Music]
I just don't love this other cages
educate is stupid you are the better
Kate
okay
is this
looking better almost how about
um
like this okay
Kate Kate doku
one of us is likely okay no I remember I
remember there's a kfp with the username
Kate
I'm pretty sure I remember
okay
BDM BDM
[Music]
we will
Read Super chats hey
[Music]
I will not drink
I I
hereby vow to not drink an energy drink
tomorrow
and hopefully never again never ever
ever
um at least not for streams
[Music]
this is Water by the way
is this out is this how coffee people
feel all the time or do they get used to
it coffee people
do they get useless do you guys get used
to it or this is how you feel all the
time
[Music]
you get used to it damn okay
[Applause]
um tea definitely doesn't crash me like
this but it also doesn't make me that
awake I mean it helps like a tiny bit
depends on the team
[Music]
coffee doesn't give you sugar crash ah I
guess this is caffeine and sugar yeah
but I I I I daily consume sugar in
many many amounts
[Music]
some tea has caffeine too yeah yeah yeah
I I used to at work and in my hotel job
when I really really really needed to
you know be a bit more awake when I
really didn't get any sleep
uh it wasn't like a magical solution but
I would drink lots of green tea
I know a lot of people think that uh
black tea is the way to go but for me it
was honestly green tea I think both were
um but I mean green tea also tastes
better in my opinion
and it made me pretty awake
[Music]
yeah I prefer green tea because black
tea is usually so so bitter
mmm green tea
[Music]
is
foreign
many songs are in my head too many songs
[Music]
actually I maybe want different
music
this is nice
I've gained a big appreciation for green
tea since I went to Japan me too and
like different kinds of green tea
different
um like strengths of flavor different
types of yeah
[Music]
you gotta skip that I love how you say
skedaddle
thank you for coming
what
suppress what with salt what
a triangle type you like to try how does
the how does that make a difference
[Music]
my favorite has been roasted green tea
tattling like Aladdin on the horse he's
saddling but I don't think doesn't use a
horse what are you talking about
what are you talking about
[Music]
he uses a [\h__\h] carpet man who doesn't
know that
okay guys
tell me
tell me tell me you know what I want to
know you know what information I want to
have
now
tell me
do you know exactly what information I
want yeah
I know you do
ah
oh yeah
final collab
thank you is that so
final collab ah okay okay oh my God so
many freaking cat stickers
the CAT scales all over again [\h__\h] the
cats are frightening me the cat the
cat's all wants to kill me
sorry that's the brain worms in my head
right now
help me somebody help me
there it is
[Music]
oh shut up
don't even don't
even no
um
don't let it get to you thank you
I will not
bad bad chickens
[Music]
um
thank you
redneck 64.com
it seemed fun yeah
thank you uh Nova extension anti-skill
anti-skill function Kevin all right
YouTube The Mohawk Duncan Ricky though
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
feedback about someone who went to the
Lord of the Rings musical because of me
[Music]
Heartland
heart Liz my my mama my UK friend
Heartland are you here in the chat I see
your beautiful super chat right now
you don't ah
yeah hey let's see went to the Lord of
the Rings Musical on Friday I live 10
minutes away
[Music]
but only heard about it from you never
been as immersed in an experience as I
was shaking Bilbo's hand and wishing him
a happy birthday you shook his hand man
did you go alone or or did you did you
go with some friends or so
[Music]
ah tell me more tell me more tell me
more did you like it just me
I hope you had fun was there like still
like because on the day I went was the
opening day and there were like so many
families and groups of people
how was the audience when you were there
because I we were saying maybe there's
so many families here right now because
it's opening day and those are maybe
some families of the of the performers
was it still really packed because it
was really packed on the opening day I
just hope it's doing well still you have
to answer all my questions by the way I
want to know what was your favorite part
what was your least favorite part are
you writing all these questions down
did you see the Ducks did you feed the
Ducks did you eat the food that they
have there because they have food too
you can book a ticket with the food okay
I bought a ticket on the day before
there were only two left when I moved oh
oh okay
cool so they're still filling out the
whole audience okay next answer my next
questions please
you have a backlog of questions now
don't eat the Ducks
foreign
[Music]
tell me more tell me more
don't have time to clean it up is there
another answer I don't see another
answer yet
[Music]
did you did you forget all my other
questions
[Music]
um
I also forgot them that's the problem
[Music]
the dinner was fully booked when I put
ah I didn't have the dinner huh it was
pretty mid anyway so it's okay
what was your favorite part was what was
your least favorite part um
[Music]
away this bgm on the screen isn't that
on this OBS scene
it's fine
hey
let me know tell me more did you tell
them did you tell them that your
favorite birthday yeah that's so nice
right such a such a like interactive uh
moment especially at the end too when
you go outside again it's so interactive
because they want you to help to put up
the all the
um Furniture again right that's so cool
it's so cute and and and and wait I was
gonna ask uh what was I gonna ask uh
[\h__\h] I forgot ah I interrupted myself
what did I do what was I gonna ask
do you guys know what I was gonna ask
what was I saying
did you see the Ducks but that's not
what I mean
[Music]
um
yeah did you thank you did you tell them
that you came uh because of
um my recommendation you didn't tell
them why
why didn't I tell you
didn't I tell you guys to tell them that
you uh came because of the
recommendation of the Austrian girl huh
I told you guys to have told me a Bilbo
directly should just tell oh by the way
I came because of this Austrian girl and
this Phoenix you don't even have to say
Phoenix you don't have to say YouTuber
just because they don't know I was a
YouTuber just just just tell them you
gotta go again if you live ten minutes
away you gotta go again and tell them
tell them maybe just go there to tell
them don't even watch it again
it I wonder this seems to me unless
nobody told me and they got they went
anyway but this seems to me like the
first person who went there uh through
my recommendation
hmm
where are the other British people and
what's your excuse for not going
[Music]
hmm
here should I go in yes and tell them
don't forget to tell them about The
Offspring girl
on the other end of the country but you
have to go before it ends at least what
about the wobbly water the wobbly water
is only in that weird Hotel just don't
go there
mmm
[Music]
I've worked booked up to the end of the
month and but you have at least one day
off no
um
I'll look into it until really I mean
don't actually don't tell Bill that's
kind of weird because he'll be like yeah
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] do I do with
that information tell the people when
you when you get there
um there's like a little stand that I
showed you on the picture too where you
have to like uh show them New York
ticket I think and then they give you a
ticket in paper form maybe tell them
um
so by the way do you remember on the
opening day that Austrian girl actually
those two Austrian girls oh my God
you actually it actually sounds
like gonna do it oh my God I love you
it sounds like you actually gonna do it
I have too much control this is like
almost a cult now
yay
hmm
[Music]
I wonder how much longer it's running
for now
you guys gotta you guys gotta go you
guys gotta check it out please
wait why do I have three DMS again
we saw
Lisa
all three of them are from narissa
okay I'm happy thank you for going there
Heartland
next up is swatter make sure to report
back to me in a way that I noticed it
because I want to hear your feedback
afterwards
I do plan to go in September family
a hotel nearby I wonder if there's any
hotels nearby it's like really in the
middle of nowhere
you remember that bus ride I took is
from that from that train station
it really looked like I was going into
the middle of nowhere and we were
walking by like some
speed Road looking not highway but very
Speedy Road
um there wasn't even there were for part
of it there wasn't even a sidewalk
after you get off the bus stop hmm
speed one yeah in German
um maybe there's a like an inn or in a
village nearby yeah yeah I hope you find
something because
if you find
it's probably gonna be cozy and nice and
yeah
comfortable hopefully
yeah I've been interviewing a kfp
okay okay I'm excited to hear
everybody's opinions actually you know
you know and because I
need to use this background
I really wonder if I'm
gonna get to use my
swimsuit ever
my casual outfit swimsuit version I told
them I told them can I have it before
summer ends because it's supposed to be
for my birthday anyway the request
but
now I'm starting to doubt it
because I think I'm very low on the
priority list
oh what the hell why ah ah wait
well at least you get this use me outfit
in October 2025
man you're gonna make me sad
yeah there's there's been some
things recently
that have been a little bit
disappointing in terms of
things related to that but yeah not that
the outfit but just in general
things behind the scenes
ah this Bingo by the way had to send it
in and you know what when I sent it in I
actually removed
um
the barbecue one
thus taking two bingos away from me just
because I thought maybe it's a stretch
after all because it was pizza
no I I I could have kept it on there
nobody was gonna ask any question about
it but I I just took two bingos away
from me and I saw
um
like some details about what we might be
getting
for each row that you clear you have
like one ticket for the route for a
raffle
and they didn't give like
like a clear list of hey this is what
you get but they put some like example
uh prices as pictures on there
and they looked pretty dope
I don't know if that's exactly what you
get probably not
but maybe
something like it
where was it
um
where was that picture
here now wait where is it
[Music]
now of course I can't find it
where did it go
but I feel like I saw like for example
an air conditioner on there
and uh
now this is not it
no
[Music]
I can't remember but it's it seemed like
pretty decent prices
ah
no I can't find it whatever it's not so
important but
what if I'm in Austria am I still
a little ball for prices but I have to
be right
because otherwise they should have said
it in the beginning that ID and Ian
can't get the prices they should have
they should say that in the beginning
obviously
before I make an effort to participate
um
[Music]
foreign
and use the AC there
nah who knows if I even win anything in
the raffle I think
uh I might I may have like
four
chances or so of Entry I'm not sure
right now but
wait let me count again what did I send
one
uh two three four I think it's four yeah
four
four raffle entries
let me win one thing please I could have
given myself six entries only if I would
have kept the barbecue in but I felt
like
I want to be a bit more fair
[Music]
should I have kept it in
people use Minecraft to complete it you
did not have to be that honest see it's
the same thing with me being too honest
at my Lufthansa interview
um
saying I'm taking a medication even
though I was only taking it
experimentally for a short amount of
time
stopped right after and it wasn't even
for the actual you know reason that they
thought it was gonna be for
yeah yeah that's what it was yeah yeah
yeah
had a health checkup and
um there's like all kinds of tests and
then there's an interview with a doctor
and he asks you some questions and uh
and I think it's also written on the
sheet that you fill out I guess and it
was like what what
um
meds do you take and I at the time
for a really short amount of time I
think I told you guys before I was
taking
antidepressants because there's
something in there
that uh uh apparently it manipulates
your feeling of pain or so
or something like that
and my doctor my general doctor at the
time we were just starting to try to
figure out what to do about the
fibromyalgia which wasn't really
interfering with my life in a bad way I
was used to it and and it was
interfering with me in any way really I
mean yeah it's not nice but it wouldn't
stop me from like any any jobs or
whatever you know
and it's not a reason to not become a
flight attendant I would say
yeah but
I think I even explained that but
they probably just heard antidepressants
and then thought okay no no not as
painkillers but apparently they're look
it up it is
it is really yes like supposed to help
in some cases it didn't help me though
so I I wasn't even taking it for that
long
um
I don't think I even took it for a month
yeah
or maybe I didn't I mean I must have
taken it maybe at least for a month to
really see
uh to give it actually a chance
but yeah
yeah it was such a bad timing I only
said it because I was so honest if it
was like after I gave up on them then I
wouldn't have mentioned them no it was
it was also because I was really scared
that uh because they did a blood test
that they would see it in my blood and
then later on I find out
um that you can only find
antidepressants in the blood if you like
really specifically test for that
yeah but I didn't want to have it be
visible in the blood test without me
telling them
that would show that I lied kind of that
I wasn't completely honest and I was
hiding something
I didn't want to do that but I I I I
couldn't know that you would have to do
a really really specific test to see
antidepressants in your blood
I couldn't have known but honestly
no idea where I would be yes see James
Jackson I was gonna say no anymore no
idea where I would be today
in terms of career choices
if I would have gotten that job I highly
doubt that I would have done it much
longer than
two or three years because it's such a
taxing job
most people don't do it for very long
[Music]
oh yeah that uh not right after uh
one or two years after
Corona started
so that would have probably affected my
job
[Music]
I don't know if I would have lost my job
but it would have affected me for sure
hmm
because I was destined for her life
[Music]
is there records of Lufthansa laying off
a lot of people for because of Corona
[Music]
because then I could have been one of
them
in that timeline
[Music]
um
I mean are you even allowed to do that
fire people for such a reason I mean
what else are you supposed to do right
but man
like
I think I like in my hotel
uh there were some this was like right
before Corona really hit
but it was already like really
empty and we were barely getting guests
and we barely needed all the staff that
we had but and that went on for a long
time like throughout whole Corona my my
colleagues told me afterwards while I
was in Japan that it was still going and
there were way too many staff but like
most people even left on their own
because it was too boring at the job
um or we're just like you know using Up
Older vacation days endlessly and yeah
but I don't think they were being fired
really because I don't think you can do
that anyway uh
they would have fired them if they could
have I think
a lot of people and and ended their jobs
on their own
many airlines bankrupted during the
pandemic
that is
bad
unfortunate but yeah probably a lot of
hotels too
anything with
a touristic connection
hmm
[Music]
000 jobs were cut at Lufthansa
wow that's a lot
[Music]
yeah working hours probably got reduced
a lot yeah yeah I think I remember my
colleagues telling me that a lot of them
switched to like a part-time
more or less
model
yeah anyway let me read the super chats
froze for like half an hour at least
Heartland you'll lose it
[Music]
unbelievable
distracting me
simpleton Kaiser Ranger danger
versus not such a tongue breaker tongue
twister
foreign
[Music]
because it breaks your tongue yeah I'm
done with the saplings looks like it
yeah more or less
foreign
[Music]
why did I get rid of it
I accidentally got rid of it because of
this uh bingo
okay
[Music]
Richard Richardson
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the time meow
I'm hungry my small cat knocks things
like anime figures off of shelves when
she when he's hungry really you think
he's doing it on purpose [\h__\h] Savage
I love it
ah
unless there are really expensive ones
that could break easily you gotta put it
into a class uh thingy class between
between
no way that that word exists in English
which rain
Germans are laughing at me right now
[Music]
oh it does oh
cabinet
but you don't say if it's rain do you
in in Spanish there's Patrina vitrina
[Music]
now you don't say it in English like
that I mean with retrained
oh but many languages have a very
similar word so they get it they
understand
[Music]
oh French Finnish Spanish they all got
it except for English language
they're being extra
feeling extra anyways speak them thank
you time to get a glass cabinet
for your anime figures and then let's
see what your cat is gonna try to knock
over next
[Music]
chocolate chocolate
another
[Music]
um
and last but not least
Pinky
Funko off tantrum remember from us
advice read Kiana Reed today is my
birthday at least in future time zones
I don't know what he sent these kind of
super chats but after all why not why
should my Sunday
big mistake
thank you Mrs
to say that in the same Super Chat as a
birthday superchat
[Music]
ah hmm
too bad I can't read so I also didn't
read that it's your birthday how I don't
know about it
too bad can't say happy birthday when I
can't read that it's your birthday
[Music]
check mate
no but you're generally usually you're
nice so happy birthday
happy birthday congratulations
[Music]
oh I can't be mad at you
don't
tease the wow next time
is a lesson you will hopefully learn for
your upcoming years
at kfp and in life yeah hey
[Music]
um
hope you had a lovely birthday
[Music]
did you celebrate did you eat some cake
cake by the ocean
[Music]
hot people hoping they'll eat cake by
the ocean
[Music]
happy birthday you watch streams
well if that is your way of like
spending a happy day then I'm glad you
did it
um
sounds nice if you're having a good time
um the GTA stream that comes after that
has no super chats uh and then there's
the Pokemon unite tournament
right after
this one
is
what an unusual team to get together huh
this combination of
people in a collab is very unusual but
we had fun together
um who made the film these for these
thumbnails for these oh I think
I think
either cover or Pokemon stuff I'm not
sure they were just there and they asked
us to use them
hmm
[Music]
oh
thank you for a look I mean I don't know
there's like
I think one of the reasons why I was
able to
stay interested in this one is you know
it's it's rather simple as a
game of its genre and also the visuals
are just easy
on the eye and cute
so that helped to keep me interested
um I don't know if I'll pick up any
other mobile mobiles
Never Say Never I guess but
yeah
as long as we don't have perms I'm
definitely not playing this one again
and about the others I don't even know
what other mobile terms we have
oh
they all seem like kind of toxic wow
what the [\h__\h]
um
and scary so
[Music]
it was kind of a triple actually one of
them was a double
they like crack on several levels and
dimensions
[Music]
many
many ways of cracking mine
body
yeah that was my neck yes
yes
yeah I made a pose but it didn't start
yet I said I need to do it I need to
start with like a massage
and yeah get myself to like a
somewhat comfortable
state
of body
you're gonna break your neck again you
have no idea ever since that grease
incident
I've been cracking my neck
daily
a million times
and nothing ever happened again I think
I after that I definitely started doing
it with more feeling probably
more uh
coordinated I don't know
[Music]
I know how to do it without killing
myself
but there's been some crazy cracks that
I've done so far with my neck
[Music]
where I thought holy [\h__\h] I'm close to
breaking my neck probably
uh
yeah it's it's
easy to say please don't do it don't do
it but you know you don't understand I'm
I'm like it feels like it feels like
it's constantly
tensing up and constantly
like in need of relief and if I don't do
it I'm like going crazy because it I'm
doing I'm not doing it
uh
on on or subconsciously I'm doing it
very consciously I know that I'm doing
it when I'm doing it
[Music]
um
yeah but it's like yeah
I have to do it it's
um
you know
but it's not like I'm not trying to help
myself right now you know I'm going
swimming
[Music]
no
and I'm going to massages so often to
sometimes I use those
um
pads sticky pads that help me a little
bit
um with the pain
only a little bit
oh
now the massages they don't really help
they're just for the moment
I don't know what to do it's like
I I really think that
uh at some point a couple years ago
somebody was trying to help me
when I was feeling I guess a little bit
stiff or whatever
and cracked my neck
and I think that's where it started for
me
that I kept on doing it on my own I
think this is like something you want to
um
try to
um avoid at all cost because once you
get started with it
something happens in your neck
that tells you you have to do it again
and again and again and again
it's like you're opening up Pandora's
Box
[Music]
um
but even if it wouldn't have happened
back then maybe it would have happened
uh in the future because
when I go to Thai massages at the end of
My Time Massages they always
like will crack me like this and that
and this and that in many ways they love
doing that at the End of Time Massages
no t-a-i
ah
[Music]
I wish we could help I wish it was like
an easier thing to fix
it it makes me feel so tense and it's
hard to explain
but it's just it's like it tightens up
and it tenses up and and feels it feels
like I need to do something
[Music]
ah wait not here
hi I forgot something
[Music]
um
I feel the urge say out loud that you
want to crack your neck tell yourself be
aware of the feeling and Breathe It Out
the Feeling goes away you really think
so
by telling myself I'm very aware of that
I'm very aware that I want to do it do I
have to tell myself
[Music]
are you recommended by a doctor to stop
it no but as not in person but
um basically what doctors say is
if it's done by a professional
um then they know what they're doing so
that's okay
but
if you do it on your own
especially if you do it in that amount
maybe it's not so so tragic on like
fingers finger knuckles for example
but on your neck
[Music]
a little bit different and I watched a
video that explained
um in detail
what you are doing to your spine and
everything when you do that
it's a bit different than your knuckles
and Knuckles whatever
um
but if you on your own
[Music]
without being a doctor
do that all the time it's not good
and yeah it's not getting better either
it's not like I'm helping myself with
this
I know that
I should stop I should stop too
[Music]
and you do it too well I don't know how
often you do it but I do it very very
often if you do it maybe once per day
then I would say it's probably not an
issue
um I should try counting it one time
before I stop
to have a medical record
of how often I do it per day
yeah because I think
I would guess maybe 20 times if not more
and even if I crack it once it cracks in
several places many times I don't know
if I would count that as
separate counts probably not
[Music]
I had like six in the Stream really
so often today in this stream
yeah
you tell yourself to do push-ups
whenever you feel the urge to pop
wow
but what if I don't want to do push-ups
and it's torture
[Music]
um
I heard of that 5 17.
is that how you spell that
[Music]
there's an SMS in there
I'll look into it
got it open on
[Music]
Amazon but
um
[Music]
isn't it just a like a roll
I wonder if that really works have you
guys tried a fast fascia fascia roll
before
are you swimming in yeah I've been I
swam three times this week maybe I'll
swim again tomorrow if I have time
before the Stream
[Music]
no no no
not for me but other people like them
um
yes keep swimming
[Music]
now I'm keeping up with it
um
I would probably
if I would swim
what's it called freestyle
it would probably be even better on my
neck and my shoulders
[Music]
but I can't I don't know how no time
most of the time I'm trying to keep my
head above water because I need to keep
my protective gravy in my hair
if I lose the gravy in my hair
my hair Goes Up in Flames it the gravy
is basically heat protection from myself
new lore
mm-hmm
[Music]
how's that work what do you mean how's
that like the gravy
keeps my head and my hair to
um you know take up all the heat that is
coming from my head
[Music]
and if I wash it off
then
my hair is going to go up in flames and
I'll be bold and we don't want them
[Music]
building core strength helps it gives
you better posture does less fun yeah
that's what I'm hoping to achieve but so
far I
still don't feel much difference
at all any anything really
I don't know
work that core I will I will
foreign
[Music]
how long
give me a date
[Music]
yeah but I'm doing froggy style really
properly I'm trying my best to like
stretch my arms and spread them really
wide and
keep my arms straight
and do big circle motions in the water
three to six months that is very rough
estimate man
yeah
but okay
[Music]
what do you think if I go like three
times a week you think it's enough
[Music]
in some weeks I went even more often
um
good enough right okay good
good good
if I go tomorrow it will be the fourth
time
I think I'll go tomorrow we are
it's been so [\h__\h] hot
[Music]
I should read Super Chat shouldn't I
I'm feeling very lazy and comfy
I did calm down from the
energy crash crash
[Music]
I can't imagine not having a scene
I can't imagine evil man
it sucks I am
I think I'm gonna get myself AC
for next year
proper AC
[Music]
yeah
I'll be it'll be a whole Construction
but
I gotta do it
I just wonder should I do it in every
room
like definitely in the office on the
bedroom
and then I normally don't spend much
time in the living room but it would be
weird if the living room doesn't have
the AC wouldn't it
oh
[Music]
yeah no the plan is that I built it in
a place that I own
right now I don't own it
[Music]
but then I have permission to do
whatever I want
yeah now I can't do it I can't even get
the the one the window one
I don't think so and it's not worth it
anyway at this point
because I'm already
thinking about the future I'll I'll
survive this summer
but next summer
hopefully I'll be living AC comfortably
in a a place of my own
yeah
when the ones are terrible they break in
a season for real
oh wow
[Music]
in your home at the Maldives
get up my hopes my dreams I'm never
gonna live in the Maldives but honestly
like I don't think I would want to live
in the Maldives because there's [\h__\h]
sand everywhere no
um
[Music]
Maldives
yeah I don't know I want to live in a
place that's familiar to me in terms of
like culture and all that it's in the
end it's the most comfortable
and most secure feeling
um
[Music]
I heard that now there's influencers
moving to Dubai
YouTubers and influencers moving to
Dubai because you have to pay no taxes
apparently
[Music]
well I would never move there but
it's a thing
like European uh influences they even go
apparently to Modern Madeira
or Dubai
hmm
but yeah there was some kind of I was
just told about this yesterday there's
some kind of like what's it let me look
it up
content creator no tags to buy
[Music]
Aya Dubai offers influencers complete
Tax Freedom allowing them to keep all
the profit they earn from their
activities
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
um
holy [\h__\h]
how to commit tax but this is not even
tax frame
remember
[Music]
aside from all year round Sun pristine
pristine beaches amazing service and
complete safety you also benefit from
being able to keep more of your
hard-earned income because there's no
tax in Dubai
sounds like
the people who are writing this are kind
of biased but
yeah brought to you by the dupai
government
complete safety that's that's a
interesting point to make
[Music]
no I mean I believe the tax thing I
believe it but
[Music]
I don't and I want to stay in a familiar
place
I think
sounds nice good weather but I think
it's also freaking hot it's probably
hotter in Dubai than here but I guess
wait Dubai probably apartments in Dubai
don't come without AC I would assume
right
anywhere where it's hotter than here in
Europe I'm assuming they built
everything with AC
[Music]
um
you die without it yeah
[Music]
it's a desert so yes no thank God
it's like the US AC is everywhere I'm so
jealous why does Europe not do this
there why is it not like by default in
Europe
the Earth is getting hotter hotter I
feel it
it's not just me being a phoenix I'm not
just imagining this
oh
uh yeah
[Music]
huge waste of energy
I guess so
[Music]
oh well I will treat myself to an AC in
the future I'm looking forward to that
future very much
where was I here
what Pokemon typing would the kfb
chickens be
um
flying fighting or flying fire or just
flying
maybe not even flying you guys don't fly
much do you
fly normal oh
maybe you'll just be normal
to evolve you get a new type which would
be
um fire
[Music]
I don't know if it would be
five maybe fire fighting
maybe you go from normal to fire
fighting how you like that
that's really interesting
[Music]
yeah
noise
[Music]
I'm down for that let's go
so we become torchics is that what
torchic's type is
but yeah basically
we really become Blaziken yes
[Music]
powerful fire chicken
then I would be way too wild and I'm
stronger water
no no no no what are you talking about
[Music]
be the master of the Pokeball
yeah I tried
and I failed sorry I didn't become the
master I'm sorry I failed you guys once
again I feel like kfp
you always cheer so hard for me when I
participated in these kind of
tournaments and I always fail
as a whole
and
damn
when's the last time I was in a team
where the team ended up winning
hmm
because I think last year's Minecraft
sports festival I was also in the losing
team
got a passion I think we lost
I always lose
hmm
oh by the way I got a notification about
Summer Festival Minecraft Summer
Festival and I said I'm not
participating
[Music]
I am too occupied with my brain and I
don't want to have another thing
occupying me and I don't yeah thinking
back on Summer Festival last year it's
it's fun and cute and all if you have
your group or whatever
[Music]
um but I mean I don't think I'm really
missing out on that much
so I said nope also because I don't know
at what time it will be but usually
Japanese tournaments
or festivals like that I think that
would be in the evening Summer Festival
because they do like
um fireworks and stuff I would think
that it might be evening it might not be
too bad for me in terms of time but I
don't know and
I I don't I don't want to I don't know
it's not that I am being anti-social or
anything I just
um I'm not feeling it this year I'm
sorry
[Music]
bonding experience I'm I don't need that
it's honestly not gonna make much of a
difference
I think
yeah I I I'm not missing out on much
it's okay I don't feel I'm missing out
on things so it will be fine
[Music]
yeah there'll be more events for a
future Minecraft sports festival though
I will
probably participate I guess
now there will be again even more
members so
maybe there'll be less challenges that I
have to be part of I don't know I mean
Japanese sports festival
I helped probably
participate I guess yeah
that one
[Music]
um
I guess
the ID games were a lot of fun but I
wonder if for the Japanese one they're
gonna repeat the same games again
because I feel like generally they reuse
the games that they've had in previous
years and maybe add like one or two
different ones
but they've repeated the flying one I
think they repeated the
um the one where you sneak up and then
run and then sneak and then run
um and the marathon and all that
they repeat a lot of them and the what's
that one called I never did that on my
own but the one where they were mining
all those materials
um yeah they like to be consistent
well if I participate
[Music]
um
I think I was doing pretty good at the
that dunking game that we were playing
so I could do the dunking game again and
maybe the flying game but I don't wanna
I don't want
pressure on myself
I hate the pressure in these
competitions I get so nervous I I panic
and I feel so bad when I lose for my
team
um
if they have the same games then I'll
try to get into the same games as before
so just so that I
I can possibly do well
yeah but we'll see maybe inspired by the
ID sports festival maybe they'll add
some exciting new ones
inspired by ID
would be nice to
I wouldn't mind seeing more of badminton
or soccer
but then they have to implement some
mods
[Music]
I want to see a whole badminton
tournament me too
and soccer soccer was really really
interesting
I was
more aggressive at practice I guess
and everybody was just playing kind of
uh carelessly so
I got more goals in
the real deal the axle tournament was so
tense
wow
you scored a nice goal yeah I scored the
only goal in my team let's go
that at least
proved the point that I practiced so
[Music]
I yeah that was last year I think just a
few people but I don't know how they're
gonna do it uh
I think they're inviting everybody who
wants to be there again
[Music]
but I don't know I feel like I heard
something like that foreign
[Music]
first check time often they don't have a
time yet though they only often have a
date but no exact time
when they sent me these
things these requests
[Music]
for chats Uh Kevin C Duncan
kitchens
celebrities
[Music]
thank you for the pinky gotta catch them
all
yes gotta destroy them all and get their
exp and Duncan
it was fun it was really fun if if they
weren't so freaking strong
and Keanu Fred Pebble ah cute what cute
afford people
uh thank you for the recipe chat wait
what was your name before if you changed
your name recently
who were you before
picture doesn't look familiar either
who are you
I love your avatar you look so cute also
love the alola nine tails good luck
tencho you'll always be fine thank you
I ended up not being able to resist the
urge to buy some cute clothes but they
were pretty cheap and honestly not as
bad as length fauna and Cali I think
they ended up buying uh quite a bit from
the cash shop
and then they were sad when they were
told that we have to wear
um that team t-shirt
and in the end
none of it was really invisible much
anyway but
I bought a little set of clothes and I
think it was only like five bucks and I
will say as long as you don't go
overboard and buy endless amounts of
clothes in these from games then then
and it's just one thing okay if it's
just one thing
it's fine I didn't want to do it at
first because I was like telling myself
well I'm only playing this until the
tournament
but I couldn't resist I wanted to look
cuter for the tournament
uh yeah
[Music]
regrety spaghetti but it was only five
bucks so all okay all okay thank you
Kiara fried pebble
see you're you're complimenting me
looking cute already worth it
already worth spending the money
I would say success mwah thank you
[Music]
um
Jackson thank you for the pancake it's
called a team effort great job Kiowa oh
thank you
thank you thank you team effort indeed
yeah it was too bad that I think not
only Amir but Kelly also said she was
lagging a lot
um
yeah I I saw AMA lagging
I can confirm and you know I was trying
to in the moment where she would just
like lagged away I was trying to also
protect her in those moments somehow
but
um at the same time not completely
losing
track of what's going on in the game it
was a difficult situation I wonder did
the others lag at all the other teams I
didn't check their archives
[Music]
and I did see
um feedback that
me
meaning the bait
uh was actually
possibly the reason why ID lost that
match because they all focused on me and
you know that made me feel a lot lot
better about the whole match
but honestly think about it I understand
that maybe when they were watching the
first match they saw how bad I was and
thought okay then we can take her down
easily but you're not really even doing
anything any significant damage right
when you gang up on me all the time
because I wasn't contributing much in
the first place
so maybe should gang up on the better
players like fauna or so yeah
I was free EXP
yeah I guess
[Music]
but in the end it didn't help them
really
and when they while they were attacking
me apparently in like because we were
mostly up at the Top Lane they were able
to get objectives at the bottom and and
dunk at the bottom and all that so
yeah yeah they left Cali Iris and fauna
to run around at the bottom in hindsight
maybe Kelly should have joined us at the
top a bit more often so that we would
have had a higher chance of survival but
if Cali was also lagging then I would
have two lagging players and me and who
knows how that would have went
but yeah Cali was really motivated and
she was really quick in our practices
too we were having a lot of fun and
whenever somebody was like Cali we need
you which in the practices was most of
the time me and Amir Cali would show up
immediately and help us hmm
she'd had three times to lag what oh no
that's so bad ew
[Music]
bam
that post analyzation makes me want to
play in that really
she wants the video so she was useful
um
she was so into it
I love it I love when Cali gets really
into games
[Music]
um
and it was fun the teamwork was fun
and
yeah
[Music]
but yeah I was I was a big beginner and
I feel like I really needed some
had to say some uh instructions like I
told both Army and fauna to just tell me
just tell me what to do I don't I I need
to know I need to feel like confident in
what I'm because otherwise I'll just do
I'll just do whatever and then maybe
regret because then I'm unsure like oh
[\h__\h] what do we do now are we doing this
are we committing and what are we doing
what are we doing
should we go in should we go to the
objective should we go what should we do
yeah
need a good plan can you guys shut up
about reading like this is not about
that now
[Music]
um
there was not much shot calling in
regards to actions yeah
yeah
I think
probably you know I'm in Fauna maybe
just don't
they're not the type of person to give
orders normally so
yeah maybe they didn't feel confident
enough or so to give orders
um
[Music]
they didn't want to maybe seem like
they're
ordering people around but
that's what I needed though
[Music]
I need to be bossed around in that
situation
um
it's okay though we still won at least
one match and we had fun and it was very
very adrenaline pumping
exciting
yeah and even in the one the Japanese
one the first one that we lost we felt
like damn
we didn't even do that bad when you can
feel good about the way you lost
that's a good sign
[Music]
both games were extremely close
honestly I was watching so much of that
Championship the world championship
and the stuff I've seen there was really
interesting if I would have seen all of
that beforehand I would have suggested
some strategies
yeah
because uh
okay I didn't see any other povs but
maybe you guys know where the other
teams like
camping in the in the hedges
in the grass when Rayquaza showed up
because professional players
for them both teams usually hide in the
grass when Rayquaza shows up and some of
them some of every once in a while they
like poke out and they say you know they
look around and maybe tease them a
little bit but nobody really starts to
fight for quite a while yeah I did it oh
yeah they probably
knew some real strats yeah
and then you wait for some moment but
I'm not sure exactly what really is the
moment
maybe when somebody just can't take it
anymore when somebody loses their
patience somebody
takes a shot
attacks they start ganging up on each
other first before really attacking
Rayquaza
trying to get momentum
to completely eradicate one team and
then they try their best to with the
remaining members quickly kill Rayquaza
um
it's exciting
so exciting
but it's also so I feel like 90 90
percent
of the matches that I watched in the uh
championships the World Championships
where like one team would lead
throughout the game
and then they would be doing so well and
then suddenly the other team gets gets
Rayquaza out of sheer luck and it turns
around
completely with such a huge gap that the
the other team who was doing so well
until that point can't can't possibly do
anything to fix it and I think there's
two sides to this on one hand it's great
to have a reason to not give up
because the other group may be in a lead
and you're already giving up because
well there isn't anything to latch on to
to save this so it's good to have
Rayquaza being such like a big effect
but I feel like you could have still
kept that
you know that glimpse of hope that you
can turn it around without making it so
extreme maybe nerfing it a little bit to
still give the team who was having a
good lead and who was playing really
well
keep their lead now I think it's a bit
too much it's good to have something
that turns it around completely
but it shouldn't be a hundred percent
guarantee even if you had zero points in
your team until Rayquaza suddenly you're
dunking 600 points
why
was it like I I only played like you
know recently before the tournament but
uh I've heard from other people that
before it was like that that spiky
Thunderbird
[Music]
was it the same with that one or is this
only a thing with Rayquaza Zapdos yeah
was it does anybody know
Zapdos was worse
that this was the same
uh okay
[Music]
interesting uh
that's unfortunate
[Music]
Zapdos negated the defense of the girls
oh was it a different effect but it
still made a huge difference like uh
Rayquaza
[Music]
you know the only case where
ah
where I didn't see this happening even
though the team got Rayquaza was when
they waited so long to get Rayquaza that
they only had like 10 seconds or 20
seconds left when they killed Rayquaza
and there wasn't enough time to actually
dunk
at all and then the match just ended
yeah that was really a rare case though
Rayquaza
think of that until now
yeah that's when you wait out way too
long hmm
[Music]
but that doesn't happen so often
wait puzzle
yeah but we should have used that bush
grass technique a little bit more
yeah
I didn't really
know how important the grass was
[Music]
there's a fan of Rayquaza and Google no
way
you only had one day to practice
together hard to come up with strats
yeah I guess so
um
yeah
[Music]
you girls killed Anya instantly
well maybe we used it a little bit but
not really that
purposefully I think I don't know
[Music]
um I wasn't really aware of a grass
strategy at least
like not I knew it was hiding me but I
didn't really realize how important and
useful it was
yeah you did well the amount of time you
had yeah I would say so too
again it was a lot of fun
um
I think um if it wasn't for the
shitty time in my case
uh it was a good decision to join
if it wouldn't have [\h__\h] up
my life for
like two weeks
minimum two weeks
um
yeah good place like telling Amber to
commit doing the yeah yeah I did I did
and we did get those two kills yeah I
feel like sometimes
when even when we didn't commit I wanted
to and I feel like we could have we
could have but I didn't want to be at
fault of having all of us dying
[Music]
hmm and I backed out a lot she played it
very safe yeah
but I mean it's understandable also
because of her internet connection and
everything
it's scary like man I know how it is to
play with legs sometimes in an important
situation in a situation with lots of
pressure and you don't want it to mess
some things
um man
[Music]
okay
going 1-1 with a bad internet and sleep
depressed member is super impressive
uh you know being together with armor
but maybe we should have switched it up
maybe
maybe I should have been
at least after playing the first game
and already knowing that ama is lagging
and I am that good on my own
baby we should have switched up our uh
what's the word
you know our teams
like have
I'm gonna go with fauna and me with Iris
or me with fauna I'm with Iris
yeah I will links leaning Partners yeah
that would have probably be a good idea
[Laughter]
but in the end we won the second match
right so
the second one even though it was the
same team up
yeah we did win
oh well
yeah just a little flashback to what
happened last week
um
[Music]
you didn't do much that much that pick
on Anya right before the big team fight
near the end really turned the game
around I honestly don't even remember
that any mistakes you felt you made were
due to being newbies I don't mind thank
you I don't even remember that I have to
re-watch it ah
I guess we did a good thing there
you guys nuking Anya secure the win
really
[Music]
did it
yeah
I honestly have to re-watch it
afterwards I don't remember a thing
I have to watch it slowly because
everything happened so fast I think
right before Rayquaza showed up
[Music]
it became a four versus five and Kyla
was a bit further back
[Music]
oh is that so plus the sleep deprivation
yeah
it's like it was all a fever dream it
really was
could here we watch it on stream uh
maybe if I turn off the sound yeah but
that's awkward
yes
you did awesome Kiana
all of Ian's hard work came from the
match is super proud and thanks for
staying up so late for this yeah
anything for the sponsored stream
um
[Music]
thank you for all of kfb also who were
there who even stayed up but watched the
archive
especially the ones who suffered with me
you didn't have to but you did thank you
thank you very much
thank you carbon for supporting me and
sharing for me
Patsy please
[Music]
people
these are taking me longer than they
should
I'll read the Minecraft ones
[Music]
on
yeah don't think we really probably
talked much about the Pokemon unite
vignette though so
I had to
Japan to the Limit but you also picked
up a huge win over ID you guys put in
nowhere trained hard and made us all
from oh thank you
yeah yeah at least compared to like the
expectations at first that Ian would be
an absolute mess
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh
hit wait wait
[Music]
hi it's moving
I gotta try something really quickly
probably not gonna work out but
um
oh
foreign
[Music]
I'm trying to reach
somebody who was probably oversleeping
for something important
because trying to help
but
um
[Music]
let JMT sleep
she's not the one over sleeping though
uh
not JMT
ah okay
she's
she has awoken
no it's not Gouda
the person has awokened
eh
oh
um
okay
there's um
there's a
anime convention panel starting in now
well things are okay I think
things are working out I think
can't believe chonkers overslept she's
always oversleeping chunky monkey
okay yes
yes back to business
where was I
ah nowhere
in the beginning right didn't read
anything yet okay
is anyone there is anyone at the
convention
[Music]
move is dead on my floor
I love when they just walk in and then
just flop down and then they just look
dead
but they're just chilling they just
don't have a single worry in the world
[Music]
actually like looks like she's low-key
sleeping
cute and Jacob 47.
[Music]
um
I did read a couple those oh yeah thank
you Jim Tracy uh sodium for the pinky
thank you
thank you so much
my cats do that when I get home right in
front of me right
right
you read a couple I did I did skyduction
thank you Mouse clicking oh that one was
fun too I could have participated in
that game but our team actually won that
one so no problemo really proud of them
because during the practice they weren't
doing that well
but then at the actual game uh the tug
of war
they won so happy
so glad
uh production
I think at the time I was like
cooking finishing up my cooking so I
wasn't paying 100 attention I just heard
suddenly whoa team uh Pink win yeah yeah
hey
so good
I really stress
extension Adam xnt Duncan Patsy Duncan
black Christian dances
motion thanks for the pinky thank you
for your service uh the goslar
yeah I'm still using it
um
but I'm gonna set up the other one at
some point at some point when I need it
when things next time something goes
wrong and it triggers me
um it's over it's [\h__\h] over
it's Rolex solar Rover it's go over
I'm not gonna destroy it on stream no no
no
I think it was about 10. ah ah about
telling her about actually oh yeah yeah
yeah
I was happy to hear she did already like
some Atelier games yeah
[Music]
honestly
I I marvelous taste
in games
I love it that was in the neck correct
no it wasn't it wasn't really in that
crack
I can give you one if you want
[Music]
Exquisite
um
I just I just just need to talk to her
more
our our game tastes overlap but I wonder
if we can hold up a proper conversation
I'm a bit scared to test it out
I'm scared because I want to
get along well with her
but I'm scared
[Music]
but I guess I can hold a conversation
with anybody really so
[Music]
hmm
we had a good conversation yesterday so
I get along with it or well with
everybody and
because I'm putting a lot of effort into
it because I don't want to be like
isolated and unknown again I don't want
to be a stranger again and
um yeah
I want to be involved I want to be there
like
at least for for these girls the time
zones are strangely not really holding
us back that's the weird thing
um
I feel like for Council the time zones
were holding us back way more
I feel like they were never around when
I was around and um
[Music]
most of them have a decent sleep
schedule yeah and you know now for about
this gate visual when I first talked to
her one of the first times when we
talked about you know time differences
and all that she said oh I would I would
get up early in the morning for you no
problem yeah and she's gonna do it for
Baldur's Gate
but we're gonna rotate the times so that
it's not always them we will do anything
for you of course I know I know I know
you will yeah I really am happy with how
it's going yeah
I hope it will continue to be like this
and next I'm planning you know
unbelievably believable with Advent so
yeah I feel like I'm Advent
kindergartener
[Laughter]
it's fun making projects for them
involving them and
doing stuff for them so
yeah
[Music]
I gotta set up a date
for that
teacher eh kindergartener is is it's um
oh yeah I guess oh I uh okay teacher
then
not next week
next week is um Baldur's Gate and album
right is it no no no it's not uh it's
not it's not but um
no I have too much going on I think I I
wanted to do it in the end of August but
I think I'll have to do it like
beginning of September
no it's not
no no it really isn't I just already
feel like it's already the end of the
month because because of the deadlines
for me finishing in it it it it
um
it's basically tomorrow
so I'm
because I feel like there's still things
that need to be fixed
yeah
but it's okay
it's
[Music]
oh yeah song in a couple of hours too
deep breaths it just feels like I am
very stressful and kind of lost I I'm
trying to juggle a lot of things like
communicate with between producers and
mixers and artists
Etc
uh
video creators
[Music]
it's a lot of work man
um
yes there was an announcement on Twitter
today
uh it's coming out even Saturday or
Sunday I think
[Music]
oh tomorrow so Sunday or today is
Saturday oh then it's Sunday I guess 12
hours oh
at noon this call
I might still be half asleep
I have to be sleeping because I want
energy for my last stream GTA stream
[Music]
um
eight hours after Holiday Dance okay you
guys gotta be there for all of that okay
I may not be there but you guys gonna be
there
[Music]
please don't stay up for the song
Premiere yesterday I ended up like
accidentally still being awake when when
the hotel Ian repeats 3D thing came out
I wasn't planning on it
that one was funny though did you guys
see it I posted it on I reposted it on
the community board
I hope you guys saw did you guys see it
did you get a notification
from my community post
[Music]
balance
the run run was cute
it was good it was a cute moment
if you guys have any
um special moments that you think would
be good to turn into 3D like this
let me know
can be really old ones can be somewhat
recent ones
just let me know and I uh arm wrestling
didn't isn't that already hasn't that
already been done
[Music]
actually that one was kind of 3D so
yeah it should be things that make sense
to turn into Freddy
and has been done anyway then there you
go
cast president I think they prefer
moments that are with more than just one
member but I guess they have done plenty
of moments already with
uh
uh one member but also often I tell you
guys funny stories but it's better when
it's not just like a tall story but also
just actually happening on stream yeah
the rise up here oh where I was standing
on the chair
[Music]
that might be kind of short though
was that what happened I just got up on
the chair and then I fell down and was
funny and that's it
oh that could be funny lots of like
suffering expressions
[Music]
wait
wait let me Kiana laying an egg on the
stream that's old
two years ago
[Music]
oh wait there's there's two occasions
one was in a Pokemon stream
and one wasn't was a super chat reading
you get a wig I don't know Pokemon music
not good to listen to it now
[Laughter]
this one
is this someone
[Laughter]
[Music]
hahaha
you know what else because
your fault
imagine someone standing in line for
horuket yeah without the earphones not
gonna happen they're not gonna listen to
this without the hair see people still
complain about about my voice when I
sound like a different person but
imagine someone listening to this who is
this
this is so awkward to watch this is so
awkward to watch when I speak over it
with a different voice
I literally can't who is that
I'm a different person right now did I
have the it doesn't quite sound like the
old microphone to me it sounds like
it may have already been the shore sm7b
maybe without the gloxalar I'm not sure
cement
it's a man Papa
no but it's not just that it's just I'm
speaking in a higher tone
can I recreate this
can I have a minute
wait where was that
oh listen to this without the earphones
but without their earphones standing in
line for hope
imagine someone standing in line for
hold up imagine someone standing in line
for isolator
without their earphones without without
the earphones oh oh that that might be
it what happened they're not gonna
listen to this without the earphones but
they're not gonna listen to this without
the earphones button and
Madison
earphones
imagine someone listening earphones here
earphones in line for entry to
horrocketo in line for entry to horo
kettle
is this me
I'm trying to recreate my old sound
don't say basketball sounds cuter
I forgot how absolutely baby you sound
that's why I hate watching old footage
of me
[Laughter]
we're to be confronted with that
thank you
right now
I hate this girl
I don't know I mean I was definitely
speaking in the high tone and then also
yeah some of it is on the mixer
that I have but not completely
definitely not completely
um
no
uh I will say that I think the first mic
and everything also before the books
like gave me like weird acoustics
especially listening back on it now I
just like the podcast sound you know
um compared to that
but yeah especially in the beginning I
think I had weird acoustics
I don't like it
don't like it at all and now I feel
really awkward about talking to you guys
where was I
here maybe
[Music]
and some voice I fell in love with silly
stop I love you
thank you
foreign
[Music]
no one
no one can
love that person
[Music]
everybody hated that person
um
you only loved the the inside of me
wait what
um
thank you
I came across your past words of Age of
Empires 2 and I adjoined them very much
I know you have a busy schedule but I
hope you'll play AOE 2 again someday you
know I would really like to but I just
feel the difficulty Spike
was rough for me
[Music]
um
I honestly should find uh
that female AOE two player that I found
before again
and have her coach me
yeah I don't I obviously don't want to
just rely on cheats all the time it's
fun for a gimmick but it's not you know
[Music]
you know I'm not child Wawa anymore I
don't need cheats to play games I play
games probably
um
yeah like previously I was a long time
ago I was watching some
aoe2 content and I found this like lady
who was um I think she was uh
like the
what do you call them again the MC I
guess the emcee of like a AOE two match
[Music]
um she knew what she was talking about
because she had a lot of experience in
the game
yeah the Caster yeah English speaking
commentator yeah I don't know anymore
who it was but maybe she could help me
get over the difficulty Spike and I'm
sure there's more than just one female
good AOE 2 player out there right
yeah because I feel like without that
alone I was just
it was so difficult I was trying to
follow you know the usual flow and do
what the game tells you to do but still
it was so difficult what the [\h__\h]
um
I wonder if any of Advent likes and
plays RTS games they haven't mentioned
anything have they at least not AOE too
[Music]
right RTS is fun though it's fun when
you know how to play
it was fun while it wasn't too difficult
for me
yeah
[Music]
but it's also annoying because I have to
ask for permission to play it every time
really far in advance and that's
annoying
but
[Music]
it's okay okay
it's only with some games like that
[Music]
and then if I cancel it because I'm sick
or so that's also not really good
or if I just don't feel like it
[Music]
anyway uh you make stanka soon Adam
accentation
guys if you find me that that
commentator girl
then I'll DM her
if you find me that girl because I'm
gonna forget about finding her if you'll
find me that aoe2 girl
I will DM her okay deal deal good
soon motion thanks for the pink wait I
read that
thank you for your service the [\h__\h]
motion
[Music]
Santa's twice motion
thank you for your service Pinky from
motion
I guess I read it
I guess I did read it Adam accent but
this one I didn't read the read the red
from snake
Australian's name snack oh no no
definitely poisonous y of it stay away
from the Australian snack finally got my
two-year badge and Phoenix are you sure
it looked like a snake to me snack
um
[Music]
speaking of no cat here why
snake are you here probably not
Australia very very bad time right now
first ever and the first I've ever been
subbed to someone this long yeah really
I'm proud to support utensil you and
your never-ending tangents are a ray of
sunshine and many canopies lives never
stop being Who You Are
thank you so much wait I see you you are
here oh my God again every time you guys
are here when I'm calling you out it it
fascinates me that you guys actually
watch my streams
I love you and I love you I am
thank you so much for watching me even
though I stream at the worst times
possible for you
thank you I love you
I'm glad you enjoy my tangents sometimes
I am
cringe at myself while telling my
tangents because sometimes they really
are not interesting but most of the time
I think they're interesting and you
should be interested in it so
I will continue my ways of tangenting
you know never stop being Who You Are
[Music]
you know that's such a such a beautiful
beautiful
to say thank you
thank you there's many times where I
doubt myself but when you say something
sweet like that it means a lot to me
thank you
my chicken snake
oh wait I know I understand out there
can't be chicken is inside the snack
and is controlling the snake from inside
so it is a chicken
but it looks like a snake because you
know the snake ate the chicken
[Music]
but it probably made the snake choke
by being so thick
and so the snake is now forever just
like a dead snake body that the chicken
can't get out of because it's stuck
laughs
yeah it's using the snake body
[Music]
instead but it's actually a proper
chicken
[Music]
um
confirm
would you mind confirming
it's a Ratatouille type okay okay that's
pretty much the same thing though
I guess the snake is
is it dead
or is it alive
[Music]
a chicken wearing snake skin yeah
honestly it's all it's a good like
survival strategy
I think people will try to stay away
from uh his snacks of life oh [\h__\h]
people will try to stay away from an
Australian snake and they don't want to
eat you either but people will try to
eat you if you're a chicken
the big brain
survival strategy
he's riding the snake like a horse is
that what's happening
I need
a visual
representation
what
[Music]
Hawking Australians bloody hell mate I
quote I was actually almost eaten by a
snake when I was free LA Mao that's
Aussie for you
[Music]
foreign
what the [\h__\h] what kind of snake was
that
kind of I mean okay three year old
probably really small
so must have been a big ass snake holy
[\h__\h]
tell me more about that
please tell me more
what kind of snake was it and what if
what kind of situation were you were you
at home was it outside was it in the
park
when you were playing or it was was what
the [\h__\h] I need to know
that is really interesting is this
common
in Australia
if yes and that's really concerning
really really cool
okay tell me
I'm waiting snake I'm waiting
[Music]
oh lived on a farm it was a Tasmanian
tiger snake gotta look that up I went up
to it because I was a dumb toddler oh I
mean yeah I mean toddlers don't know any
better but a kookaburra grabbed it
before it could attack me oh
my god did your mom like how did you go
back and then tell her mommy I almost
got eaten by snake
oh wait it doesn't look so big
can it eat a toddler or is it like a
poison thing do they not eat them but
poison them instead
I guess wait maybe they poison them
first because there's the snakes who
straight up eat them right like strangle
them and then eat them and then there's
the snakes who poisoned them and then
eat them
[Music]
well this one's a poisonous one oh
sheesh
geez they come in different colors huh
tiger snake is a large and highly
venomous snake highly
yo
especially
to a toddler to him including the
coastal
Southern Australia including the coastal
Islands into Tasmania these snakes are
often observed and locally well known by
their banding black and yellow like a
tiger although the species can be highly
variable in coloration patterning damn
[Music]
wait did I miss any more replies
crazy [\h__\h]
how do you remember that
must have told your mommy
who what
Australia and their funny animal names
but that is a
hub
and so [\h__\h] Brave it looks tiny
though
that bird protected you from that shitty
snake oh
they make the best sounds they sound
like they're laughing
oh
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] are they so brave would you
think it tried to save you
or was it just like messing around
so cute it looks so cute
I know
I forgot the word for snake in nihongo
foreign
[Music]
that's amazing that's a life story to
tell honestly that story with that story
you could go unbelievably believable
but I think I would believe you
yeah they might birds in general birds
are always the saviors of people
kookaburra attack snake it even Auto
fills it
kookaburra catches snake Pizza to death
and eats it whole
well this is a tiny snake I think these
are tiny snakes how the [\h__\h] do they
think it could save you from that huge
snake
[Music]
kookaburra versus tiger snake five years
ago is this you are you eight years old
Are you eight years old now is this um
video from your case
oh [\h__\h]
well this one looks pretty small too
still but I guess if it's poisonous fast
you can just quickly attack a toddler
anyway it doesn't matter
what this this bird has no fears
whatsoever
is it
does it have the head and its feet
must because otherwise it would have
been bitten it just shakes it shake
shake
damn I'm quite fast damn what a bird
third
they laugh at Danger
listen to that audio Yeah it was just
like no comparison Cooper sound maybe I
should do an AM kookaburra
what that sounds like when you have
water in your mouth and you you put your
head up and then you go with the water
like wait I can do it right now
laughs
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
that almost sounds like an opera
[Laughter]
cookie
cute
what is this
a kookaburra
this must be their pepper so look at
this look at this look at this look at
this you're so pretty
oh
it's so close up oh it's poofy are you
poofy are you so smart
hi
whoa it poofs up
oh my God
are they do they just like hang out
around people's homes like pigeons or
what but this one's oh I think it's got
a leash I think it's their pet
ah it's so rounding cute and small
oh my God
they can't be very annoying no how could
they look at them
God damn it they're so cute
this has like the perfect shape friend
shape
what's your only friendship
oh my god let's not wish that's the
thing on this oh is it
no you guys are also friendship
perfectly round
you guys are just like these I love how
round chickens are
[Music]
I thank you I take care of my figure
so is there a dent on your head because
of all the stuff on your head all the
time what do you mean
okay I'm going back to but this was so
interesting though you can't expect me
to not
ask someone to uh elaborate when they
tell me they almost got eaten by a snake
when they were three years old
right man Australians and their stories
man
and that was insanely cute Birdman a
savior not only does it look cute but
it's so brave holy [\h__\h]
ah okay okay
happy to tell my classic awesome tale
damn you must be telling like every like
like like when you get to know somebody
and you just want to make them think
you're interesting you just gotta tell
them that trivia and they'll be hooked
on you
damn
I don't have a story like that I think
too no I mean I was in an airplane with
a bomb so I can keep up
damn
but maybe it's not so special in
Australia maybe maybe everybody has a
close to death
story in Australia
maybe that's normal there
ask pay about kookaburra she'll tell you
about how cute they are oh she likes
them too I mean how are they not
likeable there's they are cute as [\h__\h]
understandable
um
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] chicken snake hybrid what
the [\h__\h] why is that not banned from
this server
why is that not banned from the server
that sounds like a glitch
[Music]
yeah I mean what the [\h__\h]
it sounds like something that shouldn't
be existing patch it out come on
[Music]
I'm speaking teardzu
multi-class
I need hot picks well reported I'll
report it to the server owner
[Music]
ah where was I man will I ever finish
this I mean actually it's not much man
where was I
[Music]
well no this is the wrong window isn't
it
this is the right window found it so
snake here's a kiss mwah don't get in
danger okay be careful
and I don't know if you should be really
watching the stream if you're 80 years
old so I hope a parent is watching with
you you are now eight years old I have
decided
hmm
that was obviously the video from that
incident
the one I found
[Music]
no way that happens like daily in
Australia
or does it
mean
thank you
[Music]
without getting too deepwood limitations
or whatnot that you have living in Japan
oh like
um job like if you do a job
it has to
uh like you know they're really strict
with
um what you can do
depending on your Visa
um yeah it's really
restricting uh
I can't get too deep into what
like really was my limitations uh before
for working holiday I had like pretty
much
all Freedom that's the good thing about
that Visa but when I lived in Japan and
had a different Visa
um in the end
uh it was kind of the reason
that I left Japan that the limitations
of the Visa were holding me back more or
less
so yeah it's difficult it's not that
easy
but yeah gotta follow the rules but the
thing is it's not even easy to get a
Visa in the first place unless you have
a University degree or you know you're
like a specialist in something
um unless you're like you know if you
want to teach English I hear it's pretty
easy but you still need like a degree or
something
and then it's pretty easy to get a job
because they take English helping
teachers everywhere it seems
but if you want to do anything besides
that I think it's like pretty difficult
oh yeah
yeah and I didn't have that so my
options were very limited
um
now if you just want to be in Japan a
lot of people also just do uh uh like a
student visa and just go to language
school or pretend to go to language
school I hear a lot of people who go to
Japan just for the sake of going to
Japan they get that language School Visa
they sign up for expensive language
school and then they like skip a lot of
classes and you know it's not good
mm-hmm
but it gives them quite a lot of freedom
in Japan when you have the language
School Visa or the school Visa it seems
like you can do a lot of jobs quite
freely as part time and all that so yeah
[Music]
but seems like the language schools are
often not that good or enjoyable and
kind of like rough
oh so I understand why a lot of people
just don't want to really go but they're
really expensive too so
yeah but what after the language School
uh have a friend who did this with the
language School the strategy and then
after they were done I think that was
like a two or three year thing which is
quite a lot of time to you know build up
a base for the next thing and she then
just basically instead of a language
school went to another specialized
School
to stay continue staying in Japan
um
and all this time she also had like
part-time jobs yeah
but the next thing wasn't the language
school was a difficult so apparently you
can also go to other specialized schools
yeah
no she actually learned the language I
don't know if she really went to school
that often but she was good at the
language as well
can you just marry someone in Japan to
get citizenship
kind of yeah but uh no so uh there's a
difference between
um like you know uh being someone's
spouse and getting a spouse visa
uh and then you can get the after many
years you can get an like an age you can
I think like a permanent residence but
citizenship you're not gonna get that
for a long long time I think
[Applause]
I think yeah first is like spouse visa I
think then a permanent residence or so
but you gotta uphold this status for a
long time to get a permanent residence
I've heard that even that takes like
maybe 10 years or so
um
yeah I think you can't get
citizenship but you can if you uphold
the marriage and all that for a long
time
then you can
I guess
yeah stay in Japan forever even after
you
uh divorce if you already get to the
permanent
uh whatever I don't know what all the
terms are anymore I I don't know
but
they also of course check if it's legit
I've heard
if the like which is weird because I
think Japan still has arranged marriages
but when when it comes to you know
foreigners
marrying Japanese guys or girl ladies
yeah I mean I don't know
what
[Music]
uh requirements are but
I think it has to be legit it can't be
actually I don't know they still have
arranged marriages so
huh
okay I don't have that much deep
knowledge about that part because it
wasn't a thing that I ever considered to
do just for a Visa
but I've heard stories of other people
who did marry for
Visa in Japan some people get very
desperate for getting a Visa in Japan
because Japan is the land that everybody
wants to be in
doing that just for Visa is crazy
I I
it's not something I would do but I
guess I mean if you were
really really need to be in Japan I
guess
um
yeah usually it's a mutual agreement
[Music]
s
no
to improve your own living conditions uh
I I know of some girls who didn't do it
to improve their living conditions they
just wanted to live out their their
dream weave life honestly
um
yeah
[Music]
the weeable dream
and that usually doesn't go very well if
that's the reason
you marry for
[Music]
um
but maybe it's good for
a certain amount of time
and you're living the life
hopefully it's worth it but guys don't
do it
don't do it just just
if you want to live in Japan
I think it's smarter to just like first
of all test out the waters obviously
test out the lattice with like a working
holiday I always recommend working
holiday if you're still within the right
age
um and you have your country has a like
a contract thingy an agreement with
Japan
um then you can do it once in your life
and you have lots of Freedom during the
working holiday or if you're out of that
age range you could also do uh
you know the language thing then you can
learn the language while you're there
or I'm from many countries uh even
staying as a tourist
you can be there for three or six months
and even if you just leave the country
for one day you can come back again and
restart the tourist visa
yeah then you probably need a lot of
money saved up
to survive there
um
Well yeah if you just want to test out
the waters let's say you you know you
have a lot of money saved up and you
just want to figure out if Japan is for
you
hmm go there on the tourist visa and
then have fun I guess but but then
you're obviously never gonna
be able to test out the waters in terms
of work environment and work culture and
all that which is I promise you unless
you're like I don't know from Korea or
China Etc then then your working culture
is gonna be very very difficult
different compared to your own country
like Asian work cultures
crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy crazy
crazy
yeah
yeah uh
probably best to find a company
that has a lot of foreigners in the
higher ups
[Music]
yeah
uh who are understanding of
overseas people's normal
working expectations or whatever
[Music]
um
yeah
Gaijin friendly
there are quite a few so
you could find it
I think most people who are used to like
Western work culture
are not gonna be happy with Japanese or
like Asian work culture
and not gonna Thrive but not gonna be
feeling so well wanna go home
[Music]
that's my working holiday is good
because you can test the working culture
in Japan without committing too much to
it
and then see if it's for you or not
[Music]
I should stop dancing so much
can't help it
where was I this time
Aya here check your channel that's what
I get for reading a Super Chat that
wasn't a pinky or red one I'm just
bringing myself to more tangents
not good
play a class that can cast fine Familia
for a really cute cat
wizard Ranger Eldritch Knight Arcane
trickster or warlock packed of the chain
what the [\h__\h] are these names I heard
that if you can cast spells you can
always cast spells like talk to animal
or talk to this and that talk to cat
talk to whatever
and it will help you
apparently
you know my friend told me
but I don't know what class I should
play
I have no idea
[Music]
you guys know what I should play
pick a palette no
I would even wanna do
[Music]
um
what's the word
like a
not close combat
um
I want to be further away
[Music]
ranged yes are there Healers
I haven't played like you know I used to
be always a Healer in MMOs
should I should I be the healer do we
need a Healer does a party need a Healer
in BD free when you what do you think
[Music]
yes you don't need one
climbing through it and Bart can heal
healing and DND not worth but clerics
are strong Clarks are powerful
[Music]
what can I do as a cleric besides
healing
[Music]
healing and D kind of bad and Claire can
also deal tons of damage this is a mix
of healing and damage well then maybe
I'll play cleric
they do that much okay okay
only Magic on that stuff killing Undead
Bard and Ranger are the classes yeah
probably
praising the cleric so
I want to be cleric let me tell them
[Music]
I am gonna play cleric
should I say I will be your heels
I didn't say it
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm looking forward to being uh blamed
for the party's deaths let's go
[Music]
clerics can be pretty durable too
depending on how you build them really
well I have no idea what to expect to be
honest from this game
[Music]
when
interesting
[Music]
they will they will need me they will
um have to
rely on me they will need my healing oh
oh
foreign
[Music]
did they do musical damage
those are the ones yelling at everyone
else for getting themselves good yeah
[Music]
okay let's go back to reading guys
uh when you have your
yeah you didn't uh recommend a cleric
but
you know
I think Clark sounds fun for now maybe I
might still change my mind but who knows
maybe I'll watch some videos on some
classes and maybe something speaks to me
call Galleon thanks for the red super
chat thank you thank you for always
working so hard and doing your best
you've honestly inspired me so much I've
moved to Japan to study some new hongo
around a year ago oh hey we just talked
about all of this stuff so I don't get
to catch James live as much lately but
I'm always happy to catch dreams when I
can
oh so you're still there are you at a
language school
I hope you are
um getting your money's worth and if
it's if it's a language school which
kind of sounds like it I hope you're
probably going there not skipping your
classes
yeah but
make sure to also socialize and interact
with people in Japan because otherwise I
don't think you know
I think it'll be good I heard that a lot
of language Schools students just hang
out with each other
in their Foreigner Circle and don't
really use the Japanese language much
yeah oh nerissa says she is interested
in doing Bard oh
I wonder what calian visual are gonna go
for visual should be our tank
I won't be here to be our tank because
somehow I find the idea of it funny and
cute and I want Cali to be our DD
[Music]
as a rock huh
okay sorry
no no nerissa Wants To Be The Bard
Cali wants to be Barbarian
did you repel of the Norbert yeah she
should be a paladin
[Music]
she'll be our rock that we hold on to
that's a big crack no it just sounded
like it honestly I've had way bigger
cracks
these days that was nothing
anyway yeah cool Galley and I wish you
lots of luck I hope you're hearing this
at some point in the archive or so
thank you for saying hi and yeah I wish
you all the best I hope you're not
melting in Japanese heat I would be yeah
is on fire that's a sign that she's
dying so like how our Kiara went up in
flames in the lore video
you have to if you see me on fire
if it's still only a small flame you can
still put me out with some water or so
or hugging me really tight
basically choking the fire out of uh air
oxygen yes isn't that cute
[Music]
isn't that a cute thought
saving me by hugging me oh
hey I'm almost dad's movie
thank you
narrow two to seven six times
thank you thank you thank you bye
my fancy
uh RPG outfit is gonna be good for the
Baldur's Gate streams Maybe
oh
it turned out turned into a small collab
with Kyla and risu very rare yeah
I'm just telling you about Metal Gear
was to say you might have perms don't
know whereas until October and don't
forget to get Mew in Pokemon's card
uh I don't really care enough to get Mew
but I saw pecora playing metal gear
today and uh hidil Kojima tweeted out
that he's watching her
[Music]
then
he posted screenshots
of her saying I will try to watch pecula
now
um
it's it's his game is it MGs
and he also made depth stranding so that
made me think like does he know that she
played for depth stranding because I
really liked her death stranding
playthrough
he should check out her
death stranding playthrough
I wonder if he knows
he also tweeted onion playing gifts
running my back what maybe I should play
death stranding and he'll notice me
[Music]
if he noticed Anya playing death
stranding
nah I I I think I'm good
maybe MGS though maybe don't don't don't
tell pomu
because she'll get her hopes up
[Music]
anyway
thank you
yeah I had fun with Kai language so that
was a good time I like the practice
streams deeply thinks also for the pinks
very much appreciated
thank you so much hope you're doing well
and it's midnight now and I was aiming
for that I will go now
that's it guys I've
tangented too much it's over man it's
Kiara Rover
this movie is waiting for me and the
pizza leftovers are waiting for me
um
[Music]
I'll finish
GTA tomorrow wish me luck that I can
sleep
that's movie is not gonna wake me up
all the [\h__\h] time
[Music]
yeah
but I have no hope
I have no hope at all
[Music]
yeah thank you guys though thanks
I'll be sleeping through Iris showcase
most likely yeah
now you guys have fun with it
if you're gonna watch it it's it's oh
wait that's not what you meant
foreign
[Music]
yeah I should not
be awake for it I shouldn't I should be
trying to sleep
5 a.m for me
well well
have a nice uh evening guys
[Music]
I'll see you guys for today tomorrow the
probably final episode I will now make
thumbnail quickly hopefully
and
maybe give feedback for music
[Music]
okay bye bye guys and here is the GTA
ending yo
[Music]
I'm tired of the same song
Every Day
[Music]
I'm sure she would have opened the door
for me
oh that's funny
all right then