[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
hello hello
sorry guys for the surprise
um originally the stream was supposed to
start at 8pm and then I changed it to
half as a PM but before that I told my
manager please change the stream to 50
minutes later but that was at the point
where we're supposed to start at 8pm so
that would be 8 15 p.m but then she saw
it too late so she changed the time that
I already changed to half past 8 pm to 8
45 and then I was like
and now you guys were like it so well
here we are
yeah miscommunication
yeah but here we are now
let's start we came to Louis I want to
say Senpai
welcome
yes yes I am the simplest I am the
Senpai but yeah I came to Louie's home
thank you for having me and we also had
a little bit of a dinner yeah yes we ate
beforehand the Japanese Curry
[Music]
's I didn't
I didn't it was good what's good I ate
the sweetest Curry amokoti
um sweet paste
sauce no more no mouse flavor a little
bit yeah a little bit but normally you
eat a bit more spicier yes but not today
because bad for the fruit yes yes yes oh
by the way and self introduction please
okay in English okay hi
[Music]
guys uh I am a whole live sixth
generation and a secret society hologues
nice to meet you
here we go but actually yes we met for
the first time yes they're dead the day
before yesterday
the day before yesterday
I I actually I didn't know that you
would be there until giddy giddy kitty
kitty kitty
so I thought today would be our first
meeting but it is two days ago no yes
yes so we already made me warmed up a
little bit yeah
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I played it before Oh what about you
yes it's a bit of a stressful game
and just a like
a corporation yeah incorporation right
Corporation game not not fight right
yeah I don't think so I mean when I
played it before I was alone but I think
when you play together it's cooperation
Corporation together pray together yes
together we will play Loreal wear but it
has lots of different characters I
wonder how many she has because if she
only tested it she probably doesn't have
so many characters let's do that
character
um
yeah no problem okay okay let's play
yeah let's start
[Music]
okay and prayer one is
me okay we're playing with the tiny
joy-cons yes
so two people I'm not used to the tiny
okay oh oh full battery nice
Warrior hey Warriors
which one do you like more why Luigi
menu okay
okay
we start from the beginning Maybe
yes
okay it's in Japanese no problem though
because I'm sorry no no I think there's
not much like dialysis does that
um
and we saw if you guys want to see this
in English
um I think it's on my stream from before
okay
and we all all know Wario okay
just attacks in the direction you slide
okay okay
let's go
um
by the microphone arm
handicap okay yes okay I'm sorry dude
handicap no problem and still I will
anyway
did you know today I am not
takanashikiana oh today I am
yeah because okay in English let's
translate takanashi means no Hawk oh yes
yes and you know the little birds are
playing you know yeah yeah but she's
Hawk
so today
yeah
you guys were calling us Firehawk but I
feel like takataka is better
hmm
[Music]
let's go
are we fighting the nose
[Music]
let's go
what's going on
okay okay uh I'll wear them okay hi my
area no this way
hey good okay good great good
communication okay
oh cricket
why are you gone now worry on Cricket
ERS okay
let's go so big jump big jump huh
let's go this one's easy
for me
[Music]
and because you have the handicap
microphone of the microphone um
okay okay oh we already got the third
character okay okay
[Music]
oh
yeah
okay I see ah I see
nice nice good yes okay so now we have
three characters we can choose okay
I have to do this
okay
no problem
beat up
come on
[Music]
oh my God uh it's
you know
just chaotic yeah
okay okay we'll try again I guess okay
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
Tulsa
is good good good
and why you'll only come back
oh okay
okay nice
nice okay I'm light three yeah
we both died at the same time oh my God
oh same level yes oh wow okay okay I
will do yeah down okay okay
oh nice
and I will like Light Side okay
let's go it's a difficult part yeah be
careful can't attack yes be careful okay
okay
Last Chance let's be patient yeah
[Music]
I'm so sorry
no no no no okay
we try it again practice practice this
practice part don't panic yeah be calm
okay let's go in yourself I go up okay
okay okay
side
okay
good okay here it gets difficult yes be
careful way
be careful
okay nice
that was dangerous totally yes
be careful
nice
Zoo
oh good
french fries
not bad so far
oh what's with him
it's that virus looks like a virus
get rid of him
I have to clean up
[Music]
they didn't invest enough time into the
game developments
[Music]
no you need bug testers before you
release a game
thousand coins oh
next stage
okay
let's go
oh we got a cute girl I think yeah okay
okay
come on now
[Music]
I Wanna Be the cute girl but I think it
keeps on like randomly giving us
random characters
[Music]
so cute
almost
okay boom Miller
um
oh sorry sorry
no it's so
difficult yes
normally you don't play games like this
um
[Music]
bring it on baby okay yeah
anything about toy
oh
character oh
well we will never get a hangover well
who's that is that her house
her boyfriend
oh oh my God
oh she comes back in
it's a man to see hungry
[Music]
make us her angry
oh my God oh
is that
that her pets or her children yeah
but okay it's back to beautiful
I see that's a background Story the lore
next day oh
oh oh did you not learn your lesson ah
they did um
listen
uh Louis so I think we should not have
an elephant or a monkey as a cat right
it's not a good time
oh nice
okay we're all ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
same same thing yes yes yes good good
hey you didn't do anything that's it
didn't do anything again
[Music]
beautiful beautiful so far no failure
speed up okay
now that's it
[Music]
guys
that's so difficult
I'm just going to the nose that's it
okay
no problem no problem okay
there's a lot of games
you are helping him
okay
[Applause]
it's so difficult
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
yeah
boots
[Music]
yes
hey
okay
we're here oh yeah
ah
all right
[Music]
and blue I think as well okay
yes oh this is
[Music]
okay nice
yellow
egg yellow
it's like a married couple
oh
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
okay
nice finish yes finish I think finish oh
good communication
oh
easy stage
she's now part of our team um
[Music]
well we're getting rich we're gonna do
with all this money
we can go to Disneyland Disney right
okay
stage oh
dog and cats
three ball speeds three bro and sweet
Curry yes more curry doing your English
is amazing yeah she's so good
[Music]
thank you
English perfect English
let's go
maybe Louise English is better than my
Japanese no no no no no actually no
speeds
oh
one prayer to prayer oh okay
yes
okay
oh but I can only shoot into One
Direction
[Music]
oh Only One Direction that's kind of
lame
I don't like this too
okay
okay by the way yes I don't know if this
stressful game will allow me to tell you
a story but are you ready for a story
because I saw that you like oh yes yes
yes yes yes yes I I love the nagisaka oh
I have I have them
[Music]
a little story that I told already
before yes many many years ago
before nagisaka was created yes I
auditioned for it
yeah oh I sent in an audition
and then I got okay
uh yeah really I got into the next round
oh my God what they said uh please come
to like see us
and for like men tattoo yes yes and then
I didn't go
why
because I was like you know what I'm not
that interested after all
because I actually I like Hello projects
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
same picture okay
wait I'll tell you the rest of my story
in a second
no no no touch no touch get no touchy
nice
[Music]
uh catches
oh my God
this game I have no idea what's going on
all the time catch it
they say catchy it's okay we gotta never
try okay
[Music]
good
[Applause]
nice
kiss kiss okay
[Music]
how many three yes three I know
what's up
oh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] keep it inside
Hilo inside okay but I have to remind
you yes yes let's go 20 of the screen
that's sweet
oh my God
[Music]
we made it so finally now's our time to
shine let's go both stage
okay protect yes
[Music]
yes
no it's okay
the career don't worry guys we have no
idea what's happening either this is
just worrying where what happens oh now
let me tell you the rest of my story so
after I auditioned one or two years
later yes I was in a convention anime
convention oh yes in Paris oh yeah Japan
Expo yes and a guest was
the recently debuted new nagisaka 46 oh
but I didn't care I was just there for
another reason and then I was like just
sitting somewhere chilling yeah alone
and suddenly
in front of me nokisaka 46 with camera
and they were like coming up to me and
they were like hi I'm like
why are they talking to me
oh but they were like like kind of just
like trying to film like a vlog at the
event and then they came up to me and
and said hi and I said oh I know you and
then because my audition right no it
didn't meet but you know I was just like
I know you're existence
and yeah I I I I I got to meet them in
person
and I imagined
I could have been maybe part of that
Idol group now ah
what do you think Louie it's so
surprised yeah
and did you see them in a concert or so
yeah yes yes yes yes yes like the bus
still alive
February February
uh Oshi is a Kazumi takayama and my
ishiraishi
Kazumi Kazumi takayama
time
yes like cheese
[Music]
yes yes and his personality is very very
kind
remember from ikise yes yes yes
[Music]
and I also love to my shiraishi
oh but she graduated yes already
[Music]
so your Idol
no I only knew because when I came into
her place I saw like a picture
I was like what I feel like Tony sucker
sorry for yourself
[Music]
do you go to akshukai yes yes yes yes
shaking hand even handshake ribbon when
you go to handshake event what do you
tell yooshi
I love you oh like that I love you I
support you every time
[Music]
[Laughter]
but how long are the handshake events
only like a few seconds right yes yes
like uh I think Tim
yes
so difficult so fast okay I remember you
know I would go to idle uh handshake
event from Hello project too and there's
also not much time they push you away
after like five seconds
[Laughter]
okay
yeah yeah yeah
my favorite
animals
you know hello projects right but now
they don't exist anymore no yes yes
in hello project
I love it wait
when did you get to know Angelo when
they were still a smart engine
[Music]
you know you know them when yes yes
I love the Tucky Chum
oh yes yes she's very uh good singing
and good dancing right and but uh can
talk a lot I don't know funny girl so I
love it
did you know um an original member of
smiling
she follows me
[Music]
when I saw it I was so happy
yeah okay we should have budget
hey I didn't know I thought maybe maybe
you would only like AKB groups but you
also like hello project
I I also love the AKB group and tomorrow
have the have the promo promotion slow
motion and with AKB I I will create
imagine
[Music]
uh MSC is AKB what yes
yes yes yes yes
so you will talk with the members
not yet not yet yes
someday
I don't know maybe maybe
yeah I want to do something
foreign
and what we do what we should do oh what
should we do in there
[Music]
a Seiko he is correct
I played this game from beginning to end
that was actually by accident
the logo
before no oh my God it's the best
[Music]
I see
there's so many references right now
wait nice
speed uh
have you played at some money
um
I watched the video yesterday
uh explaining or like oh no
no catch it
[Laughter]
Crossing uh animals okay the most uh
which you can eat exit because it's nice
oh
my God
sorry no I also mistake
this game is so stressful it's fun
so difficult if we talking a lot so we
shall think so difficult to pray yes of
course I recognize that yeah
Louie did you see recognize all the
references that we just saw
there were so many references to other
games
okay
[Music]
how to put this we have to go
okay nice
[Laughter]
I can't even see the screen what stage
okay
come on scream out of panic yes what's
the challenge here yeah yeah okay
problems
[Music]
we have the same character so sometimes
okay
[Laughter]
yeah hey let's go
I have to wait a little bit this is so
difficult
oh my God
no patience
no Louie has no chill okay
now go
[Music]
go
okay wait for me okay okay
come on
big boy
this is fun I'm just gonna heal it's a
different way of playing Super Mario
okay yeah okay oh okay
oh my God bye-bye come on okay I'll say
bye and come on come on come on here hi
uh hi let's go yeah
[Laughter]
that was close
[Music]
we finished the level yes Hallelujah
very hard yes
exciting I've been screaming so much my
throat hurts you die
that's a stressful game
can you play this game uh also
um not couch pull up guys let me know
I'm not sure was this only couch call up
because then I'm glad we're doing it
though
where is Waluigi
Gore this game I mean this game is only
officordable yes yes yes not online
collab
or flying only
I want to do idle talk again
yes please
make in whole life yes an idol Grill and
with let's say five members
who which members do you choose for the
perfect Idol
cool yes you produce ah okay
if I produce
and you have to keep in mind whether
idle group doesn't mean that you need
five members with perfect beautiful
voices no no no no no yes maybe two good
singers but also one good Entertainer
and so on your own balance yes good bad
luck dancer and like personality skills
where I want to write out why the like
parents yes yes uh I think uh first yeah
I will choose the Subaru Senpai oh yes
about the Senpai is very good
personality and like mood magical yes
yes and uh like dance skill is a bit
like powerful yeah yeah yeah okay
energetic yes energy energy
so the first person is a Subaru Senpai
okay okay wait we make together I say
second member okay how about second
member today
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
um it's okay good singing voice yes
yes yeah but also funny
next to you okay
uh I think cute boys you
just cute person is oh moving
[Laughter]
the very cute or have the cute boys
yes yes yes like uh like um
[Music]
and like my face
no is it going not right no it's not the
right word like
oh
there's a new member in whole life who's
a good singer oh and also uh
I think she has beautiful hips oh really
oh
[Music]
I think so too oh
shiny
in the cheek and like a sexy
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
and good communication yes a lot of the
uh rankish speak rankish connect yes yes
yes everybody so Kiana
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what else do you want
good balance I really think so I think
we need like to perform together in
Koski why don't they like push yes I I
already say to manager yeah
let's go Horror Story like that really
yes yes yes but money channel oh okay
I don't know I didn't know you were so
supportive
[Music]
well then I will also I think I said it
before to my manager but I'll say it
again
support please
[Laughter]
yeah I think it has so much potential
because it's like kind of a natural
and we have a theme I like it
oh oh what is this like secret uh
Factory secret Factory oh no
so Robert
what are you doing with the robots world
domination oh like oh this is
foreign
sexy
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh not sexy
probably make
I really don't understand a single thing
what's going on
okay oh
okay oh I see nice
um
he's privatized uh remember
okay green
um
green one
[Laughter]
nice
thanks
oh okay we don't shoot it we just run
away from what is inevitable
okay I'm on the photo okay
okay good portal Good Nice Shot speed up
Focus time
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's so difficult
[Music]
IES
present
okay
[Music]
oh yes okay let's go oh God
speed up
please save me
okay okay okay okay
hello
[Music]
okay
you cannot mean
[Laughter]
okay maybe it's an easy bus stand maybe
uh catch it
okay
[Music]
guys
okay okay hi hi sorry
what do you call that one
let's go no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
I got it
[Laughter]
we failed wait you had two choices yes
I only had the rice yeah
after two choice I think oh God will
sweet choice will will be sure okay well
then let's pay attention
yeah
yeah okay
guys
see it
okay first rice and then
oh my God
okay okay okay okay I will
Shawty okay come on
the face one more one more
yes nice what
a telephone
[Music]
don't eat your telephones guys
it will not be good on your tummy yeah
[Music]
oh welcome could I go on welcome good
do we have one last area yes okay
what the wagon
okay
yes Minecraft
[Music]
somebody
singer
like microphone ah the Acoustics are
good in the wagon okay
hi Mark what's up Mike
um
just upwards
[Music]
you'll see
hey hey hey Ya
Michael Michael yeah okay
don't call yourself
um
actually I think we're making it more
difficult yeah so my Cafe is difficult
otherwise it would be too boring oh okay
all right you have money
[Music]
hey beautiful wacky yeah we're in a
beauty salon
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
last time I think we failed that way yes
is so easy easy
we have a feeling for it though
oh okay
okay
yes yes okay okay
[Music]
how many one two three four five five
okay
[Music]
hey
we're on the roll oh my God okay nice
shake shake oh my God no ribbon feeling
sorry
okay oh no
good
uh we only have one knife left yes
[Music]
nice what good good
guys
good
[\h__\h] up yes yes yes
[Music]
nice nice we're living on this
guy
did you play Fire Emblem
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
problem
s
with the Yoshi coins this moment just
moment
okay
[Laughter]
you said easy
ah not easy One More Time
[Music]
come on come on
don't go too close
[Music]
I wait
this looks good Yoshi coin okay uh here
we go
this moment
okay okay you were almost gonna die at
the same spot okay get close and just
wait and wait okay wait in the wait
[Music]
very easy in reality
I'm so proud of you Mike you did it
now you can go back to making music in
your Minecraft wagon yes
uh alive
already alive oh
oh
go Mike
you're welcome welcome
yeah
we got it okay I think
that was enough
yes yes
let's go to Talking room okay oh thank
you for watching and yeah
[Music]
let's go
I was so so exhausting
tired
I think one hour yes Wario wear is like
five hours of any other game
because uh use the like
um
[Music]
so is that very fast paced yes very hard
well my dear bird call hi my Tucker yes
my Hawk I saw a Hulk yesterday
[Music]
oh yeah they have
hooksima
I want to go yeah they have special
Hawks over there uh
many many times in my life but I never
went to the
now at enoshima
stationoshima they have like a jellyfish
aquarium at the station
yes yes yes it's so cool the jellyfish
I like jellyfish
I I I want to go with you well first
time yeah or maybe we can also bring
Subaru oh yes yes yes
[Music]
the better you are the enoshima yeah
actually you know what was a bit more
time yeah
um actually I think
a few days weeks ago
all five
were in Japan at the same time ah yes
yes yes yes but we did not meet together
yeah ah because I didn't know that Elena
was coming to Japan oh I I I also didn't
know I only knew like much later like
giddy Guinea yes and then there was not
much time because Elena was here only
for I think a week maybe oh I see it's a
few few yeah few days right yeah and
Moonlight also wasn't here for us but
they met right yes yeah I went to their
Sky Tree oh yes Sky Tree yes
have the uh for Life collaboration right
three you went together you
[Music]
[Laughter]
like just write a elevator
um and do you know the uh Skytree top of
Sky Tree yeah uh real alive uh will
arrive 50 minutes 50 seconds oh yes so
fast yes like a roller coaster very
first oh by the way
I think uh
a hawk and an owl I think aren't they
like like predator birds like they
attack
what's like an apex bird ah I'm not
describing Japanese
but yeah Birds of Prey you are the same
type and then
duck yes well people say I'm a chicken
so let's just go with that duck yeah
[Music]
Turkish
PayPal yeah so beautiful
not not so dangerous Birds apparently
when you guys are dangerous Birds but I
I think you know an owl to me looks just
cute and fluffy I don't see it as
dangerous but maybe it's moment
dangerous
no not dangerous right not dangerous
what about Louis
attack Louis
no dangerous
very kind and kind of
the hawk will not try to attack mume is
very dangerous yeah they say it
means dangerous
oh so cute we should oh oh I have an
idea you know this I feel like in
general maybe this is not the most
exciting hobby but next time when all
five Horror Story yes is in Japan at the
same time we can go bird watching
watching in Japan
mountain right yeah which is good idea
go on a hike bring some the what do you
call the goggles and so look we we can't
eat right yeah a little camping and bird
watching and eat yeah eat bad right
nah eat fish
grill some fish oh yeah binoculars bring
binoculars and look at the
birds in the sky and see which one can
join next okay
friend friend friend
[Music]
hey will you go bird watching with us
I want to I want to go camp Camp have
you been before yes yes I I love the
camp in you you went camping in Japan
yeah and like like camp Camp do you know
the glamping yes yes
yeah I love it but I want to go glamping
and camping normal camping I want to see
too because I haven't been normal
camping in a long time and I feel like
glapping is like easy mode yes yes yes
just like don't have anything it's okay
right yeah but Camp is hard a lot
should
get a lot of zinc yeah
so yeah
difficult
cheating it's too easy yeah
let's go camping yes okay like you do
Camp you do camp
and then we sit by the fire and we roast
marshmallows even though I don't like
marshmallows and I cook some Japanese
food oh Japanese camp food yes what what
do you make in Japanese camp
Curry
[Laughter]
awesome I love Japanese Curry and do you
know the pumpkin pie
like pumpkin like
sweet sweet one
like pump Curry Pumpkin Curry yes yes
yes yes
it's very very
delicious I love pumpkin soup oh I see
as a curry I can see it working as a
curry oh it sounds good and then we put
in marshmallow yes marshmallow much more
oh yes yes
I love the mushuma mushroomallo like uh
sand yeah uh chocolate yeah yeah yeah
yes more I never had s'mores before Oh
okay we will try it we will try it
do you do you like why
ah Mushroom in the curry okay yeah
I think it will blend in yes nicely you
will not know like Sweet Cow but I hope
you know we can do more things with Hulu
Tony especially because it's
true
fact coincidence that the two Japanese
horotoni members speak okay English
you and Subaru yes both speak good
English ah really a Subaru Senpai is
very very good yeah yeah English skill
yeah
no not only passion not oh my God not
only person yeah so actually I even
though Lumia doesn't speak Japanese
we can communicate well yeah yeah and
maybe if we may learn some more Japanese
yes
she improve yeah because Elena and me we
speak Japanese mostly all holotori are
bilingual isn't that amazing
it's amazing it's a coincidence ah so
wild wide yeah worldwide International
Call of Duty nice Idol cool yeah
worldwide group yeah yeah we have to
make use of that
worldwide
yeah we wanna make we should make
theme song
I also warned
um
oh yes yes
thank you for being so kind to me today
letting me in your place yeah uh thank
you for inviting me no problem because
it was long overdue and maybe next time
when I come to Japan again we can do
something again yes enoshima
I know
yeah Camp somewhere uh can we camp at
fujisa oh yes yes because I never saw
fujisan
okay do you know the humpback uh famous
humbug sawyaka do you know handbook
Hamburg
is it made out of birds like uh
fujisan is at chizuka right
famous uh Hamburg humbug shop
it's very very delicious
delicious yes delicious yeah no back
Hamburg hamburger yes
hamburgu
oh oh
yes it is so delicious oh
very famous very famous in the house
really is it a chain chain yes but only
shizuka
so if we go to the Fuji Sam
after the fujisan
[Music]
yes and she when she woke up
wanna eat and then
and then of course the taxi and light oh
my God Tokyo too oh my God
I think I heard that story before it's
so far so expensive yes very expensive
but she won't she very very want to eat
because very delicious yeah oh come on
I'm sure you can have great hamburger in
Tokyo why it go all the way to sizzling
because no not same maybe it would be
cheaper to hire a private Chef for to
cook for her might be cheaper for one
day than one trip with the taxi to
shizuka like special special one
well okay that sounds like a good like
reason to go there
[Music]
but this game is freaking exhausting but
I think we still had a good time yeah
yeah
so now I go I go I go back
I see you again wanna sleep right yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you for coming in my house thank
you I like your place
come again I will come again
thank you thank you guys for watching
too and tomorrow I do Sono stream uh
earlier than this time okay I see you
there guys I'll try to put up a
reservation later and your school
I promise
oh you're nervous
a little bit
yeah yeah just do it don't let go sweet
dreams
yeah
[Laughter]
okay yes thank you on Kiana channel in
the end we say auf wiedersehen it's
German
so maybe you can say it with me Alf Vida
scene
yeah okay okay and in German we say Alf
redo
[Music]
oh no more tacos
thank you
foreign
[Music]