[Music]
do
wow
[Music]
uh
do
[Music]
what
is
[Music]
is it stable now or what the [\h__\h]
is it stable
not stable
what the [\h__\h]
it's skipping a lot
oh what the [\h__\h]
it does also tell me uh oh [\h__\h] dropped
frames uh ten thousand
don't know what that means but something
bad i think
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
hello
[Music]
well how's it now i i changed something
480p it shouldn't be 480p
okay okay
[Music]
1080 okay
crispy all right all right
[Music]
it's down here it's hard to see it's
here wow you see that wow
[Music]
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray if i go wrong what awaits me
[Music]
that's not on me
oh
not this is it just me
[Music]
should i not be streaming today
i got a lot of dropped frames again
i got
i got 10 drop frames 805
um
i wanted to show you something
[Music]
money
i mean we can move it to tomorrow but
tomorrow but i wanted to show you
something today
nani
[Music]
it's fine now
it's stuttering again
why is it such a [\h__\h]
[Music]
my internet connection
sure
speed
test now where's my favorite speed test
okay
i'm turning the vgm off right now
because it stresses me the [\h__\h] out now
testing it
is it back to unstable nanny the [\h__\h]
no no no no
hello can you hear me is it just a video
or is it the voice or is it a like
everything
let me ask amen
if she's here i'm in
i think she's sleeping though
i'm buffering again
what the [\h__\h] well my my internet speed
is normal though it's so doing pretty
well actually
oh wait i know why
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's see let's give it a like a minute
to see if it's better but i think it's
better
[Music]
yeah i think it's back to normal
yeah well kick it again
[Music]
okay okay
wow
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
hello it's a kiasi
i mean i killed the stream
no no no leg no leg allowed no no help
no i fixed it
no i fixed it no i fixed it it can't be
no no no no no
no i can't beat
my entrance was ruined by youtube
sometimes by youtube
it's not looking good for twitter and
youtube today
i must destroy them all
hello i say a you say b say b go
oh
okay okay there we go beautiful all
right then we must be good now because i
fixed the problem okay
hello everybody i am
uh
yeah
uh here i have everything prepared i am
in the perfect outfit i have the
transparent logo and i'm not even joking
i got bamboozled when i was making the
thumbnail
[\h__\h] ridiculous mate uh [\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you fake transparent pngs [\h__\h]
fake everything's fake i hate it
[Music]
yes
so the thing was
you may have seen
today
there was an announcement
oh thank you
today was an announcement um
from annapolis annie annie plus korea
you know what we can
i will say this now and then a korean
clipper can clip this in the hopes of
reaching all the koreans who don't have
twitter or so and maybe don't notice
this otherwise
uh so
i will just you know do everyone a favor
and announce this properly
starting from the 21st of july
in korea
whole life myth is having a
collaboration called cafe with annapolis
there's also one starting a little bit
later like this is uh starting in seoul
in the capital a little bit later uh
also in a few other cities like
john
i want to show you because i'm so
excited when we first got informed about
this i was so excited
wait maybe maybe i should be
wearing these things when i'm announcing
this oh well uh so we have like a cafe
menu okay i'm so excited about this
because finally you know kfp is all
about food right so finally we get some
[\h__\h] good damn food yeah so i'm using
too loud oh my god oh yeah wait i have a
double oh my god so professional all
right all right so
we have some drinks yeah it looks like a
cherry drink oh check maybe cherry coke
i can't read korean so maybe it says
cherry coke i'm not sure uh but
it says our names in the big font i'm
sure um but it looks like a cherry cook
i think for cali and like a orange uh
orange
lemon
iced tea or soda for me
uh
some
uh what's it called the dark the dark um
what do you think that is rina
it could be
come on come on you can do it
orange soda your favorite totally oh
yeah uh
blue no blueberry i was thinking yeah uh
grapes like the dark grapes maybe who
knows gotta try it out and then the one
for
gouda i'm honestly not sure that's ice
cream though at the top i think ice
cream or i guess just whipped cream but
i feel like you know i had ice cream
floats before i never had whipped cream
floats before so i feel like that
doesn't make any sense so maybe it's ice
cream
and then a banana smoothie i think
maybe banana vanilla maybe for almond
looks [\h__\h] delicious i love it
already
yeah
and then we go down and there's some
desserts yeah desserts desserts we have
uh oh god i [\h__\h] love cakes
even though i love cakes i am the only
one who has something savory that's not
dessert
we have some kind of very um several
layer berry cake on on cali's side uh we
have oh more berry cakes on inna's side
whatever the hell that is from gouda is
that like uh the
is that
ice cream with a macaron on top and some
jelly
jelly sharks on top it's apparently
funny
childish cute
uh
dessert those dots right the dots maybe
um
interesting but maybe not all of it is
made out of that maybe just the top
maybe the bottom is like something else
kind of investigate and then uh
on the very right for ammo it looks like
a cheesecake with caramel
i think
yeah and then for me you know
i
i think we all know that i do have quite
the sweet tooth um
but
yeah gotta stay in character here right
so for me we have a
fried chicken korean fried chicken with
some fries as a dessert i don't know
maybe this is maybe in korea this is
considered a dessert who knows
oh olivia's family oh hello thank you i
used your your graphic for the opening
today sorry it was kind of scuffed no
um and then continuing
uh
i'm just gonna say this is not all the
food
there
is gonna be more food
uh
so the thing is i checked i wanted to go
on their website
to check if maybe only on twitter they
didn't announce everything but on the
website they did but when i tried going
on the website i can go on the main
website but once i tried to go to the
collab cafe thingy it stops me because
of my austrian ip
so what do i do
i'm like okay this could be the first
time since i bought the several year
subscription of nordvpn
that it could be useful and come in
handy because it's been [\h__\h] uh
useless so far
um so i use my vpn
change it to korea
and it still doesn't [\h__\h] work
because i changed it to korea but what
does the ip block say it says oh your ip
is from us
bye bye we don't want you on this
website
huh why
why
i want to see the website
so if anyone can get on the website uh
please show me screenshots or like a
video of you scrolling down because i
want to see it as if i am looking at it
myself
uh
wait why why why do i get a us
supposedly a usip when i get a korean ip
that's weird so i think that's the
reason why the stream was so laggy in
the beginning just because i kept it on
apparently even though i restarted my pc
that's weird
um but yeah apparently i kept it on
and i realized kind of late okay so
never mind that um
there's there will be more food and i
checked out the website to check if it's
there but i don't know i don't know if
it's there on the website but then
there's some gifts here there's like uh
i guess those are like the thing is the
the coasters that you put your glass on
or so one thing i found funny is that i
cannot actually put the burp on my hat
like it is in that coaster i wish i
could i can't do that both at the same
time um but we see more and more new
things these days happening that we
thought were impossible like putting
pngs on ourselves so you know you never
know unexpected this is just one of the
many things they have they have like all
kinds of merchandise there too
dramatic music
here there's someone there's callies oh
puffy i love puppies and she has a cool
glass to go with it now
korean bros
what does the top right say i want to
know limited something something
something what does the top right text
say
can you tell me
made in korea
one day unlimited supplies limited
limited edition daily limited amount uh
huh one per day
i mean i'm sure it's more than one per
day being sold
limited i think it means something like
limited then quantum quantity is daily
namely aha
okay okay i see scse so um i'm not gonna
say
too much detail but now this scally
thing you might be thinking why only
cali then there will be more okay that's
all i'm gonna say there will be
so
and then there's uh these uh takeout
menu
i think they're cookies looks like
cookies
of our mascots and they come with
something
looks like
could be it could be a sticker it could
be uh
what is that down there does it say what
it is in korean
[Laughter]
i don't have very very information
um
what is
that you guys know somebody who reads
korean
stickers stickers okay okay okay
okay okay so we have that and then we
have like oh my god
a lot of merchandise a lot when i say a
lot i mean a lot
uh
i don't even know
what the one on the left side is
what is that
and then on the right side ah a2 that
must be like either a poster
or wait a2 how big is a2 it's pretty big
right
it could be uh like the hanging thingy
the um yeah
default pose
but not only that's just a little bit uh
default pose but then you see already
yeah yeah we see some original art there
we go
[Music]
yeah
it's by i think you guys may have seen
his art being used before by jazz jack
uh as far as i know that's a korean
artist
and
he
does a lot of these cute chibi artworks
and they commissioned him for some cute
stuff uh i guess the left side is some
cards that you can collect maybe
and then on the right side those looks
look like stickers judging from the
other thing but now here we go
now here we go oh my god i'm just gonna
show you everything holy [\h__\h] it's so
much stuff
oh my god you know i'm not even being
paid for doing this i was just uh you
know
i don't have to do anything of this but
i want to
so
that's not sure what this is postcards
and maybe more collecting cards a4 a4
that could be unlike those um those
things where you put paper inside uh
yeah clear folders yeah judging by the
little the little dip on the right side
uh those look like ah
battery packs the left one
ah the left one is battery packs that's
so cool oh my god
i want the chihuahua battery back then
because i actually don't really use
battery packs
yeah
so i need one and then we have um
the left one
could be a note block
no not
maybe
uh and then the right is obviously
buttons badges
in every outfit
and then that looks like the one of
those heavy
acrylic stands uh
not acrylic maybe glass i don't know
something like that and then more badges
we're not done
it gets better
glass wipes
what
something was a glass wipe oh my god
incredible and here we have
uh apparently
the thing on the left side again is a
battery pack seems a really popular
choice for merchandise in korea
and then we have uh
i don't know that looks a4 it says a4 so
it looks like um again like a memo memo
kind of thing
yeah yeah
yeah
clear oh clear files oh yeah that that
also has a dip okay okay okay here we
have some cloves ooh looking clean
oh i like that parker you know the front
looks so cool but then the back with the
jazz jack uh fan art looks a little bit
dirty because the art is so derpy it's
so cute
but you almost don't notice it or if you
look at it
yeah and it's nice nice nice with our
names on it i like this stuff the porky
looks so comfy too
damn oh oh there's xl and free size oh
so free size is kind of like probably
probably like a medium sized
yeah
now we have
some okay these are like really
memorable thingies or post-its and then
we have on the left side we have mugs
nice different versions of them
oh cute
yeah they're eating good there they are
eating good
hell yeah
i wish you guys could have that do
wherever you guys live but now we're
starting off with korea and i'm so happy
about it oh my god
thank you korea for doing this i'm so
excited oh my god and i love the pillow
with the pastel colors i actually love
it is it just a pillow case or also the
pillow inside
maybe by the judging by the price we
could judge that but i'm not sure how
much that is
ah
and on the left that's coasters again
definitely but a different type of coast
coaster like the cork coasters
yeah
pillow inside uh-huh
and here we have on the left that looks
like ah acrylic standees the small ones
and the different outfits so far our
acrylic standees
have only been
the default ones right
so this is a first
and then we have oh
like like a straw but not really like
the cocktails stirrer thingy maybe it
comes with the nah nah it has a price so
i'm guessing it doesn't come with the
drink but it seems like a set maybe
it says 10.
uh oh it's just not a set but it says 10
because it's 10 different
things i'm not sure it just keeps going
it does wow there's so much stuff i know
right it's crazy and there's even more
like as i said for the food i'm not
gonna give up details but there's gonna
be more food so
oh my god
oh yeah
okay oh i want the phone stand cause
that's really useful when i travel
somewhere and then i have a an off
collab
uh like my usual
phone thingy arm thingy it's really
janky and big i don't like it
uh and now this one will actually
be really helpful
it charges too doesn't it wait wait a
second it charges two oh
i need this it's a charger and a phone
set i need this i actually want to need
this
[Music]
ah what the deal
what because finally some good [\h__\h]
food hell yeah
and then a little bag like uh
it doesn't have handles
but it is kind of like a bag or maybe
the handles are hidden
wait are those pants
maybe it's wait because there's like a
slit it looks like a slit
what is that on the left
should be a bag no
[Music]
they can't be pants i don't know because
there's like a slit in the middle
it's a curtain
what i thought it was a joke
oh come on who do i trust some people
say bang and some people say curtains
where do where are my koreans just why
did you want to just a piece of cloth
cloth cloak
maybe like a
handkerchief like a um yeah like a
napkin for the kitchen
uh
okay this one's a mystery
and then we have oh others on the right
side those are clips right
oh and the left side oh those look like
um
like the like the plastic uh soft soft
plastic type of
either
magnets or
magnets oh nice i like them
i like them they look like they have
this comic style
yeah the rubber magnet it looks like a
rubber
like it could be rubber
ah
cool
oh my god it's socks nah those are clips
on the right side
if it were socks i feel like they would
show like because that looks would look
like i guess packaging but then where's
the real sock now i'm pretty sure those
are clips on the right side
oh i'm pretty sure yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
there's so much stuff is there more
oh my god there's more i was like ah
this must be the end but
i just just keeps on going here's more
oh my god
uh so there's uh this
a mouse pad oh a round mouse pad with
two sides or two different choices
and then there's a there that's a tote
bag then what was the other thing i
guess it really was like a handkerchief
merch for days like what the [\h__\h] right
it's so good i love the designs
wait inside what is this uh
ah that's just a clean art i guess cool
it's cute
oh
wait is that
the left one is like it has a like a
security pin thingy but it also has a
stand
uh so i guess it's just like whether or
not you want to put it on a bag or you
just want to put it somewhere to
decorate it like just have it as a
standing thing
uh okay okay i was like why is that so
shiny is that a mirror okay and on the
right side
what is that
is there an imac
oh
hold on if imac just kidding what is
that
what is that
rimmel board a cr a chrome memo board
how does how does that work
can you like
paint on it but wouldn't this be like
the art being the way
memo board
[Music]
it's magnetic
i guess you can put sticky notes and
then
like attach it with magnets
who knows it's it's interesting
interesting merchandise and then we have
oh my god i'm doing this for like half
an hour now
what is this ah
card sticker you know we had this before
and last year for my birthday
merchandise we had card stickers because
they're pretty popular uh from what i
remember in japan i guess they're also
pretty popular in in uh korea to put it
like not only on the bank sticker but
like if you have like some kind of um
public transport card or something like
that usually they're all about the same
size uh
yeah so
that's cute that's cute
ah fans for the summer let's go
i love these those are the uchimas
uh not the typical fans they're the
uchivans they're like uh
they're more stable i feel like like
it's easier to fan yourself with those
than with normal classic types of fans
uh the the foley ones
they're also derpy and they are
and prices seem reasonable see i'm not
sure about that because i i have no
feeling for korean currency right now
but yeah so that's so far what they uh
showed on twitter
now
that was a lot of merchandise
i was crazy
i want to put this here but for people
probably wouldn't know what it is
okay
yeah well so uh check it out guys in if
you are
in the area for some reason it's uh in
seoul starting from the 21st of july and
then um
i don't know if they have a public
information of how long it goes
so i can't comment on that uh but also
they have in other cities in korea they
have it as well as far as i know there's
no online shop as far as i know i could
be wrong but yeah maybe you have to ask
a korean friend
to get you some stuff yeah
sorry guys but i'm just so excited
because there's so much and it looks so
good and yeah
yay and it's um you know kind of a great
timing because i'm going to korea but it
was not supposed to be like you know
synced i decided to go to korea and then
i was told about this and i'm like hey
yo
[Music]
hey yo
wow
what are the odds
yeah
i was really surprised because i knew we
had a growing korean fan base but this
is totally me playing by the way
this is me playing look look i'm such a
pro yeah yeah
i know we had a growing
uh fan base in korea but i did not think
it would be so big to make a whole cafe
out of it
yeah
so this was so exciting that we
completely ignored the fact that we have
a new feature
um i can now be daisy and mario and
everything at the same time
i can use png's on my body now baby
[Applause]
hell yeah so
i have a new outfit i should just say it
is an outfit reveal
[Laughter]
yeah
well i have a nice hat too
you know the one that ina made before
for the mario kart tournament i got
myself a dress unfortunately the sleeves
are looking sideways and i can't t-pose
to be honest
daisy cho my beloved yes hello luigi
oh
i chose daisy because i'm orange and
daisy is kind of underappreciated
so uh sorry guys we changed the game the
original game plan because i just feel
like playing something else and
something new so here we are we're
playing
soap
no
super
mario
bros
you
something ah
deluxe or something like that why does
it say playing you super luigi you ah
luigi
you're in the game
[Music]
now i haven't played like a
side-scrolling
uh
mario game in about a million [\h__\h]
years i must have been a baby last time
that's a dlc originally a dlc
gamer
yeah so
okay we're doing a story mode i guess
how many people are playing
only me
where the [\h__\h] is daisy
are you kidding me
they put two different toads in there
oh my god does it matter is there like a
stronger one and a not so strong one
it's not too hard at first okay that's
okay
we're not gonna play so long i think
gotta read super chats afterwards daisy
knife on there not me the [\h__\h] okay well
then we'll have to play with luigi
because we have to complete this
[Music]
destiny
oh wait is there like a
ah what does that mean the the maybe
that's just my controller
the the
the four dots at the bottom below the
name oh wow oh yeah
no daisy so sad wait lucy what happened
you suddenly look so
squished
with a huge [\h__\h] bobble head
you good mate
i'm not sure if daisy likes you if you
look like this you're kind of too small
oh this looks better and now we can make
the video right
[Music]
i am so surprised
oh no
it's not the castle
are you guys taking peach no how can you
with those fat looking hands pull can
you so accurately without even looking
take oh you're not taking her
oh you're taking the others
[Music]
oh those look nice those look cute
what are those acorns
messed up yoshi's
cursed yoshis
we're so far away
no we need to save the princess
[Music]
dramatic
those are babies they're not [\h__\h]
babies what kind of babies are those
terrible terrifying
adventure begins apparently yeah oh my
god
so i'm guessing we gotta yeah destroy
all those little ships and then to the
big ship
where are you going where are you going
going buddy
are you good he's very happy he laughs
very loudly
i mean i get a bit louder
well i don't know all these characters
names and even if i knew then it would
probably be in the in german
maybe it's too loud after all
how's that how's the audio
nobody does
this is boom the one up there is boom
boom
i heard of that before yeah yeah yeah
okay
well uh i just wanna
put a disclaimer i suck
at
this game in particular i am obviously
the whole live english gamer girl
so i only suck in this game in
particular probably i don't know how to
play this i will need a lot of
trial and errors and yeah okay there you
go
i guess let's just start with the first
thing it shouldn't be too difficult
right
acorn plane's way
you know my myra 64 skills yeah but this
is uh different
let's scarf i hope okay
slowly carefully
okay okay this is a baby playing the
super mario game
oh cute
ah i didn't land on you wait give me
that oh no
could i is that i know that that's an
item uh that there is at least an item
that gives you those
wow
oh now you look much better lady and it
gives you those those raccoon flying
raccoon wings thingies oh i'm gonna go
up there
we're going very
slow guys are probably not used to this
speed i need to take it one by one you
could you could you could
oh can i go down there
no i know there's like secrets
some of these are
usable
some of them are not okay
what can i do so i can crouch i can jump
what is that
this is that is a and b the same thing
and at least in a moment
that's i think all i can do no
wait normal jump and double is this
what does that do i think i've seen
professional players before doing that
just like you know um
[Music]
you know being the air a little bit
longer
yeah
like this wow professional
wow
[Music]
yes okay see that's that's now i'm
really cool um i look like uh
look like a cat almost
ah
okay i can't go down there i thought i
could and maybe destroy them
[Music]
there we go i'm learning to fly let's go
okay so i can just like
get some
altitude and then just flap flap flap
flop okay i got it i got it i got it i
got it go away oh it's cute it's so cute
sticks to the wall
oh my god it's so cute
[Music]
oh there it goes i cannot fly anymore
i want to go up there
thank you i want to go up there
go into the pipe there's oh so this one
has a secret oh my god
how did you know
oh there's one of those special coins
[Music]
why is everything so slippery
oh we skipped some things but i want all
those coins
[Music]
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die at the first
level of super mario
something something bros
[Music]
what's that
you guys enjoy my newbie enthusiasm
[Music]
oh i did that jump did you see that guys
impressive only something did that just
spawn in on this
only something a pro gamer like me can
do let me get let me get that let me get
that let me get that let me get oh
there's more oh
yeah i didn't get it all
did i would i have gotten a
a present if i would have gotten all
those
my time is running out for what oh wait
there's an overall time
oh no
wait okay okay
62 seconds i don't know how far away am
i
can i do a how do i do a ground pound
there we go whoa
secret
wait isn't that the checkpoint
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
she got knight
i'm gonna fly over there
[Music]
i thought it was easy
on the first level yeah i was just i was
just taking my time i didn't realize
there was a timer i thought i could take
it easy
[Music]
okay well i didn't know that
until later on so so
now i can totally easily if i know it i
can easily
you know
how do you like slide down because i've
seen
[Music]
okay this is just proof that i'm really
a beginner
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] what happens if i go down to zero
wait what
i want to start from the beginning
are they babying me
[Music]
just embarrassing me shut up
oh wait it wasn't what i always started
from here after the checkpoint okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay
let's just let's just try to not flex
too much and just go
[Music]
suck let's try this out no i laughing
okay oh red coins red coins
work it's like watching a chocolate
how much time do i have oh i can just
bump them from the top
you didn't think i would do that
hell yeah
yeah emma would be so proud of me
check it out check it out check it out
check it out
oh no it's a flying level
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh no oh no oh no oh no i got the coin
that's all that matters anyway
i want that thing back i want to fly
again please
oh well
i'm not missing out on anything down
there
see i i
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
we're just having good time guys we're
just having a good time
oh
it didn't go down oh oh [\h__\h]
i was scared i didn't go down till two
because did i get an extra life
somewhere
when did i do that
on mario time
[Music]
yeah i'll get used to it
i'll get used to it i'm a beginner you
have to work
[Music]
i thought it was gonna kill me
[\h__\h] you
i can't do it again right
i'm stuck
[Laughter]
maybe would not be proud of me
come here come here good job okay wow
incredible incredible gamer skills
and we can do this again
[Music]
first go here and then wow
what
how did i do it the first time
[Music]
land
i did that do i need to coin again
oh was that the third coin anyway
there's it seems to be free total
let's just
[Music]
would love to see here play cuphead with
this level of gameplay
well you might you might actually
see that sometime
nothing oh god what's down there i'm
scared
oh the gold it looks like a goat yeah
oh you get more points the higher you go
is that is that is that a thing is that
a thing
because it looks like uh i got 400
points from landing there but maybe i
could have gotten more
yes i must walk before i can run
okay that's why people try to style and
go all the way to the top okay okay okay
but hey we got free coins what what else
do you want huh
better than the game journalist
press b but no no give me time i can't
go so fast this is all very overwhelming
okay
b button i'm
not pressing b button
it just makes me jump it doesn't make me
run
it's why but when you average you don't
even know the game
[Music]
you know nothing you're trying to teach
me no nothing okay fireflower perfect
that makes everything so much easier
how would i have lost it already
not even i lose it that fast
impossible
[Music]
wait but does it run out
whoa did you see that
gamer skills
come on yeah
wait there's a timer i forgot there's
your timer don't go so slow
let's move thanks yeah
i know the game is not like you need to
kill every enemy but you know we want to
practice
oh shiny
okay that's that that was some next
level [\h__\h] man
oh oh and i did not lose it yet i want
to say what they did
nice well they expected that okay i'll
give you that one
sliding thing but i guess maybe that
doesn't work
okay
and then when do i jump when do i jump
now
whoa
incredible
okay wow holy [\h__\h] look how fast she
oh improves
this this jump scares me though
maybe i should slide and then jump maybe
it does does that give me more momentum
[Laughter]
can i like throw them upwards or do they
always go downwards oh [\h__\h] there's a
timer
[Laughter]
get that
oh it's uh not really reachable but i
don't need it anyway i don't need it no
no no
no
oh
wow
[Music]
come on
nice beautiful
oh yeah there might be some pipes that
have secrets ah [\h__\h] yeah i miss one
maybe i should go all the way up here
cute
oh my god
you're cringe for saying this is cringe
you'd cringe yourself
[Music]
i didn't even have to do anything what
was this
well that's nice that's how i like to
play my games
[Music]
i don't even see where i'm going
why is it saying down
what
did i activate that just now
[Music]
okay i thought you know i might have
missed one already
because of uh
mamma mia
because i was like just running um
aimlessly
take this little [\h__\h]
no
no i
came so far without dying how is she
doing so well yeah the right moment when
you said that i died
i got a i got a checkpoint did i get a
checkpoint
i don't remember seeing a checkpoint ah
that was a checkpoint
oh but i don't have my ah
wait it's up there it's up there
no hey it was a flame
[Music]
no problem man let me go get that coin
oh i'm small oh mom what the [\h__\h]
um but i'll go get the
bitcoin anyway i can do it
get on
[Music]
wasn't there more last time i did
why is everything so mean to me now
[Music]
one more okay let's get it let's go
let's go let's get him let's go
seven
one more
[Music]
there we go
that's the thing i was like remembering
[Music]
i love sliding it's fun
with my butt
[Music]
hey
look at him
[Music]
guys warn me next time when that's
coming up
i have to run for that jump okay okay
okay
okay okay
next time you better warn me about that
ah
i don't i'm a baby i don't know how to
run yet
okay
i think
i received
okay
[Music]
i'm supposed to always be jumping and
running oh because the jump and run
i'm not part of your system
i can do what the hell i want to do
i shook the controller oh wait there's
motion control
[Music]
that was the fault of the motion control
okay let's go
slowly
there you go
[Music]
don't hit yourself there we go
it could probably be possible in my case
shall we do this again
it's gonna be a long stream no not
necessarily
ah i'm not planning on clearing this
today
[Music]
[Applause]
of course daisy outfit
okay
don't don't can i do it like with a
ground pound will come out in the bottom
or
anyway
never mind oh it's just a point i
thought it was something more important
all right let's get him
[\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] i hurt my nail
[Laughter]
[Music]
wow that was some impressive stuff
kiwawa
and you did that the first time first
try
holy [\h__\h] skills gamer skills
[Applause]
backwards
impressive gaming thank you
thank you
everybody who's [\h__\h] on me right now
[\h__\h] you because it's the first time i'm
playing this game
how salty
and mean do you have to be for [\h__\h]
on me for being bad at this game
get out of here you don't understand fun
okay okay wait wait you're not doing
that again again okay so you're run
but how do i
oh
god focus
i get it
is there a secret here
there was a secret there
i understand mario games
i knew that on my own
oh my god usually i don't understand and
i don't get this kind of stuff oh oh oh
this time okay okay
this is the end
all right let's go
[Music]
oh worse than before i wanted to go to
the
ah beautiful beautiful
the dirt puff is getting longer what
what nanny oh
what's happening peach feel good oh no
it's taken over completely
well peach no one cares about you people
only care about daisy today okay
this needs more appreciation so i'm
guessing this is a extra bonus level and
you don't have to do
whoa who's this pick a block and i'll
give you whatever items inside i'm gonna
shuffle them now so watch closely you
don't want to pick the bowser thingy
okay are you gonna show me what's inside
first ah okay oh god
[Music]
i think i know
i'm going for the like the the the
crowned one the princess
thingy
yeah let's go what is that i don't even
know what that is
do i have to pick it up
[Music]
oh and that was by accident what the
[\h__\h]
that was by accident i didn't even i
didn't even want to hit that book oh my
god okay
i thought i could only pick one
yeah
[Music]
okay what what is that stuff
what is that
what is that that to that crown
can i crown her she's gonna be a
princess like she always dreamed of if
you switch to that you can use the crown
oh
[Music]
use art to check your items if a course
is too tough an item might help all
righty yeah not that i would need
something like that i'm guessing that
this level ends with
this
enemy as that we're having a fight okay
[Music]
all right
i can turn to ligi yet
what
really
oh no it's already scary i don't like
the scary levels in super mario no are
you coming down no
kind of scary
and the lava levels are the worst though
i don't like those okay well jump
maybe not
but bitcoin oh
we have to get that
that doesn't hurt them
and it's [\h__\h] useless though
okay
yeah okay i got it where's the
[Music]
and applause
well funny
does it come back to life oh god it does
oh god
give me something good oh does that work
against them or blue fire
oh it's ice it's ice and then
wait i know it kind of told me what to
do why an art is that like i can like
pick it up or something
let's go
i didn't i didn't listen to what the
game was telling me to do i'm sorry
[Music]
wait there's a timer
i always forget there's a timer
oh
not that
oh not bad
oh wait no
i see i have to go to the top of this
wheel
spins beans bean
can i get that
oh it's just another one okay uh do i
want to go right or left maybe for like
an extra oh sure we go here yeah
okay what was that about that
why an art
okay so i can
pick it up but it only does that when
i'm standing in front of an object i'm
guessing
yeah
get it get him
smashed
obliterated
one more i want to do that again
how long does it take them to
get back to life there we go doesn't
matter we'll never know
we'll never know
my nose is so itchy because of cat hair
excuse me
there's a coin there but i think i have
to go first the right side on the wheel
and then jump down kind of from the
wheel
to get that coin i'm guessing
we'll do that
uh i already lost track of where it was
[Music]
a little bit more
find a bite
how how how
do i need to do something different
if it's difficult
the timer oh [\h__\h]
how can i run this like
i was running but he attacks when he
runs and it takes him a moment to run
there's not even that much space to run
we need a running start
what the it's not where can i run
i was definitely running there though oh
my god you know what [\h__\h] the coin i
don't need all the coins
i don't need them
i'm running out of time
i'm yeah i'm probably still not gonna
make it
wasted too much time already oh yeah no
[\h__\h] that i don't want that either
no time for the head maybe another time
maybe we'll have time another time
let's go
checkpoints
many coins oh big wheels so many wheels
the wheel of time
was that one of them
oh man
no that's just me
[Laughter]
wasn't that one of the the game of
thrones thingies
no that's another show right like game
of thrones but
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay that's okay that's my first death
right on on that map
[Music]
you can't be helped
amazon picked it up as a show there we
go
now we know all the details wait i'm
starting with so much time again can i
go back and do like you know
some stuff here
i'm sure there was a way to go down on
those blocks thingies no
it's more luigi
he's so small i can't go back on you but
can i choose to start from the very
beginning instead of the checkpoint
i want to be given another chance
um okay chill chill chill hi hi
uh
[Music]
okay it doesn't only give you the
upgrades when you're like already big
hey
are we going left
we better go left
oh my god okay
oh my god of course i thought it was
gonna smash me again
how else would you get the coins
oh there's so many of them
okay i didn't get the other one
we'll get them now
smash that feels good give me those
points oh yeah
okay
i thought the game is a little bit a
little bit laggy on my side for some
reason must be the capture card are you
already at the boss fight
how do i get up there
wait wait this will take a hot minute
for me to get up there welcome to the
membership thank you
i was scratching my nose i was scared
for my nose wait a second
no i'm not playing remotely yes
[Music]
yeah
oh my god
yeah yes seriously well sorry
i put a disclaimer in the beginning of
the stream that i'm gonna suck okay
i warned ya
are you the type of person that
complains when they go into
ando into
what could it be
into a clothing store and you complain
when they don't have plans there
wait let me get oh god i want that
[Music]
it's right it's smart okay okay okay
that's okay that's okay
[Music]
one more one more one more
youtube what's youtube doing
you're back welcome back
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah
here's the secret flower beautiful blue
[Music]
flower there something over there not
really okay i don't care about the
enemies
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't panic trail what do you mean a
panic drill i just twirl all the time oh
god
oh god
okay just um kill him kill him easy
okay i'm guessing he has like uh
two lives
uh free lives i mean oh god i'm i'm
absolutely rocking this
okay maybe not yep
[Music]
not too
bad
not too bad for a beginner
[Music]
you guys thought i was gonna die didn't
ya
alright we'll save
thanks for offering that to me game
[Music]
here we go
next up back to the everyday life on
acorn planes yes yeah
so i got to play with your [\h__\h] i love
your [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
is that a secret
[Music]
[Applause]
i've mounted yoshino how do we can we
like fly
[Music]
oh
there we go okay i have to hold it
longer okay i thought that was all all
he can do
what did that do
i can kill those enemies too i suppose
excuse me what the [\h__\h]
it's a yoshi's stopping device yoshi
escapes stopping the buzz there we go
[Music]
yoshi lives matter definitely i love you
i need to protect yourself
yoshi with your fat ass yeah i'm son
hell yeah
i get an item when i get a full circle
all right okay oh can i eat those two oh
i can yummy plants can i have a longer
tongue than that no
oh it's so yummy
[Music]
i already got two coins
i remember you know when i was really
really young
i played some kind of yoshi game
um
i don't even remember the console but i
played some really old yoshi game
uh i didn't even uh get it myself it was
like the person that was taking care of
me at the time brought me to the dentist
and i was a child and i was like nah
i don't like it here
yo i i don't know
it could have been yeah yoshi's island
on sne yes that sounds about right like
in terms of oldness
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah and then i was i played uh i
think that was my first yoshi game and i
fell in love with it so much and i have
such fond memories of playing that yoshi
game at the dentist that afterwards i
wanted to keep on playing it so that's
why yoshi is one of one or the
favorite
um
nintendo character for me
[Music]
it's so [\h__\h] itchy so much hair on my
nose
from my cats by the way because you're
wondering
oh wait wait
wait and we almost got it probably i
think we almost got it
[Music]
oh god
thank you
maybe this time we can get to the top
of the pole
okay i'm stressing the [\h__\h]
okay i'm pressing the button so hard
right now
[Music]
that's also why
[\h__\h]
that's also my super mario sunshine was
one of my favorite mario games or it's
my favorite maya game
uh because there's so much yoshi there's
so much you'll see
and so many different colors of your
scenes
oh there's nani baby you see chunky [\h__\h]
baby you'll see
we go up and then go
[Music]
okay can i just wash my nose real quick
holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] why is there so much
cat hair on my nose
[Music]
right
the princess
and kiazi is back
okay
i see
it's gonna follow me
do i have to raise it
if i was gonna be like a little game
again
my stream heights okay
wait don't die you'll see it
[Music]
honey
how are we gonna do this
he's dancing
okay i have to carry it no
what balloon
normally oh she can't even do this is
this because um
is it like bloated
[Music]
it won't fall off anywhere right i'm
kind of scared of letting go
[Music]
i'm like pressing all the buttons now
what that one is a baby too oh [\h__\h]
it's a baby too a baby toad i can't even
be mad at it it's so cute
oh i'm so fast now that i'm running and
pressing the button all the time they're
so cute
everything's so cute
i've never seen baby toes uh not told uh
oh what are they called a goomba
never seen them before
[Music]
hmm
nice
perfect luigi's getting rich
as long as i have my baby yoshi i'm all
good oh what was that spring
[Music]
i need a little bit of a
body upgrade a physical update please
upgrade upgrade update upgrade
[Music]
i'm so bad at this am i um
i don't know about that coin man
i think i'll just
give up on that one for now maybe one
one time when we get better i can try
again to
uh
redo all of this
whoa i can like
go up like that like three times like
maximum three times maybe
[Music]
that placement kind of worries me let me
just let me just clear the level oh
wait wait wait wait you can do this
yeah
another one up let's go
i think now we're pretty safe thanks for
the membership welcome
yeah we made it there luigi
if you bring this baby to daisy she's
gonna get so so so
hyped up she's gonna be like a parent
she's gonna be like oh my god i need to
adopt this baby but if it only comes
with you luigi oh no i guess it can't be
healthy i have to take you as well luigi
it's just you know this little baby
you're shitty's parents and now i guess
i shall be his parents
wait a second
come back baby
come back i guess it was you know
warming up time but holy [\h__\h]
eat the baby that's exactly what i did
and i'm so sorry
it wasn't my attention
give me something
give me something please not a coin and
god damn it wait i can
i can jump normal too
i'm a bit confused with the controls
right now
okay well um i obviously need to get
that one that one's too easily placed
[Music]
baby cannot eat these plants huh it can
only fly does not seem to have
that much of an appetite yet
[Music]
accuracy
hey
can i please do that
thank you
oh we're back with the fireplace i don't
know how to use it while i'm you know
embracing this child let me just uh
do this
and then let's get the baby back
and now i want to slide down [\h__\h] that
was not what i wanted to do
what just happened
[Music]
i mean i can't slide when i'm holding it
is that what's happening
[Music]
okay
i'll gotcha
sometimes
learning is very painful isn't it
[Music]
um no problem no problem guys
i didn't get hit this side surprisingly
all right
[Music]
if it gets like really close does it
just automatically eat them
without me pressing anything and i don't
have to be so scared of running
again a little at these
monsters all righty oh it does it's a
human shield oh
only little ones so not the piranha
plants
[Music]
yes as chad has been saying well i can't
look at the chat all the time
at least i still look at the chat more
than others
roasted
i i do look at the chat a lot probably
too much i should be looking at the chat
list
like overall
more games
these cannons are about to fire barrage
barrage
of coins and 1-ups collect as many as
you can get more thingies than thingies
to earn one-ups oh they're okay
[Music]
money
more money
oh
no i got the oh i didn't want that one
[Music]
i didn't get a single one
[\h__\h] oh never mind oh okay i have three
and two now i think
[Music]
is it over it's over
that was close there at the end yeah
they tried to get me i got free yeah and
two there you go i got one one up
all according to kaikaku
why are you dodging i was dodging i mean
i was dodging the bowser thing is
[Music]
what are we doing what are we doing
what are we doing
[Music]
come here [\h__\h] it won't come here
that was the challenge to just kill them
with the star
let me get that treasure oh it never
starts an item i mean like i can use it
anytime
there you
did we do this one
i guess we did
because two coins
are we at the end
of this
map of the acorn planes
we can take down the first one
wow okay okay okay
blue means that completing level okay
[Music]
oh no
i got it i got it i got it i forgot how
to use this
okay that's all i can do with that right
why is that no double jumping
[Music]
uh i'll probably get to your super chat
in about a million years
[Music]
wow how
beautiful it's like i'm like a like an
ice skater and i do all these beautiful
moves and i'm i'm gonna get like rated
for it i'm gonna get the i'm gonna get
the gold medal obviously
for the grace
and the performance
oh
the beauty and the grace
yoshi's don't do castles they wait
outside yeah it's safer i don't want
yours just to get into a hot place like
this because the moment they enter it
they probably melt into some goo
some gooey [\h__\h]
[Music]
mommy
are you guys surprised i didn't already
fall into the lava huh
i wonder how miko would feel if she
played this game
[Music]
so far oh i'm first trying this baby
in the very corner no i don't even need
it i'm not sure how to get that one
though
okay we can try
okay i can't i can't i know
no i can't
[Music]
what what was that secret skill
i thought
i missed one
whoa
i can like okay now she was like that
again nice
[\h__\h]
okay we have to survive without that for
a while
i wish you know all the ones that i
collect when i already have the item
would be
added like a stash you know like
goddammit i was so close to first trying
it yo
i
[Music]
oh in super mario world you like can
stack them
and when you lose one you
you get it uh
you get the next one is that a thing
really
let's see if i can get the recline this
time hold on
[Music]
not without sacrificing my life it seems
only on the ones you get you get
specifically i don't know how what that
means then but okay
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
i'm sorry sorry i slipped oh there was a
banana peel hold the [\h__\h] left there
[\h__\h] banana peel there you stinky
stinky pigs
hold it in your [\h__\h]
recycling no what do you call it in
english we call it bill but on it
i mean good for you for eating bananas
because they're healthy and you need
that those vitamins
just leave it out there
you did it on purpose didn't you
the compost yes
that stinky thing
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe i need more confidence i'll run
how about running huh
[Laughter]
should i wait i'm just scared to wait
because then there's no no probably
gonna
you know go away the coins are gonna
leave me
red coins
[Music]
okay i guess i'll wait
[Laughter]
you didn't see that
there was another banana peel man
all those damn banana peels man
you should be laying
putting like handkerchiefs
nap
[Music]
is it babying me is the game
no thank you i just want my [\h__\h]
mushroom
give me the mushroom
oh wait ellis over there
it's baby
no
as a part-time warrior i cannot accept
that no
no
no baby mode
and even then i feel like mario he would
just also slip on the banana peel i mean
it's not my fault that it was there oh
[\h__\h]
wait i mean
okay i just had a bad start there
and i was i was agitated by the offer
they're
absolutely rude
author
of having mario guide me i mean that's
just what the hell
who do you think i am
okay and i want [\h__\h] the coins don't
even don't even think about the points
don't even think about the words
ah
[Music]
oh thank you
she can do it after all
oh mommy mommy
mommy
no
thought it could fly more
[Applause]
no
all my extra lives and they're all
leaving me no
shut up
big red box
have some respect
r-e-s-p-e-c-t
r-e-s-p-e-c-t yeah that's it
[Music]
are you having some
troubles telling me your true feelings
no
i'm looking swallow
[Music]
the only ledge crack was a thing wait is
it a thing
[Music]
okay
i left it there [\h__\h] you okay um ah but
i want the up oh wow oh well
[Music]
okay
never mind then
nevermind
[Music]
she did that though
is it already time
i can't do it as small luigi
[Music]
wait they won't even let me in oh thank
god
at least something can i am i allowed to
get in now was i just not allowed in
because i'm small i gotta get in
oh my god hello
[Music]
oh no
yeah um this is not gonna go well i
think
i i don't even have like a special
weapon
how are we doing what
i'm gonna do are we gonna shoot some
with this yeah
oh i'm gonna be have to pull this over
there we're gonna fight on your ship
already
at least you found a mushroom yeah oh
oh god
he's pretty tall
[Applause]
how
i don't know how to find them
oh i can do pretty high gems here
[Music]
[Applause]
luigi's gonna do this
against everyone's expectations
yeah okay it's not so hard it's not so
difficult
there's no no slippery slopes now
oh i did it even though i thought you
know this time i didn't quite jump on
top of it and more like
yeah yeah let's kicked him from the side
and his guts
let's go
clutch nice
first one
yeah die die die
it didn't seem high enough but
apparently it was high enough
they gave up this is our castle now
daisy can move in here happily ever
after
saving my cat loves watching the stream
oh
that's sweet hi cat
oh it's like a oh sweet dessert layer
cake desert whoa nice i like the idea
oh
yummy yummy yummy
all right it might it looks more like
you know chocolate or nutty cakes uh
i prefer more like fruity cakes but all
right let's go
let's go stone
[Music]
come back to me
uh where are we going with this
[Music]
i'm scared i'm i'm not so good at
controlling this yoshi as i could be i
think
oh what is this
okay land first do it again
[Music]
can i push it
almost
can i do it endlessly no until there's
no more air all right come on
[Music]
[Applause]
okay we were in a dangerous situation
where i had no lives so
yes
here we go it happens it happens
now we're gonna
get the mushroom before it disappears
where's yoshi
[Music]
get out there get up
yo she left me was that a time limited
thing
i don't squish to death
oh my god
[Laughter]
does he come back i love you what about
all the child memories that i made with
you oh [\h__\h]
how do i get out of there
it seems like i could do it almost
quicksand let's go
oh
okay spam jump button i was i feel like
i was spamming it well
it was definitely
okay this time i wait for the stone to
come back oh it has a funny face
[Music]
man this sucks about your [\h__\h]
funny face it looks so concerned it's
waiting for me how sweet
are you gonna lift me up no
really
okay
okay everybody is like freaking rude to
me now it's like okay kiwawa tutorial
time is over you have to be a real adult
now
okay i guess uh i thought you know in
games i could
get away from that obligation
of being an adult but i guess i have to
be an adult still everywhere i'll
[\h__\h] go
squirrels burn
how do i get that thing without never
mind i don't i don't even want to think
about it
[Music]
i could use baby no i'm not using baby
mood
i need baby mold
oh there's another one okay get one lift
me up lift me up
what is that orange soda fanta
how do we get over there can i ride on
it
is it not gonna
okay we're safe i thought maybe
it would suck me in
i'm ignoring most of the enemies now and
i saw there was something there at the
top but i guess we're not getting it
my favorite soda
nothing beats the ground pound chino
does okay okay i see that's what it is
so it will not suck me in
it's a bit difficult to tell the
difference
you're gonna go again this will just
give me a one up huh that's not even
wow that's just rude
that's just rude
[Music]
you can only catch it with confidence
and i currently have none of that
i need to go buy myself some confidence
where can i buy that guys
nah
i don't think i'm getting this coin
today
i buy it on the pharmacy amazon
at the liquor store
okay i see what you
i think oh
wow safety wall jump
i see what you're getting at
what
what what holy [\h__\h] the panic
how do i go on from here
[Music]
i think
this is it this is how far i can get
today with this game i'm never
continuing because
oh it carries me
[Laughter]
what was that what was all of that
ah
it's getting dangerous we are two left
or two lives left
it's getting really close here i need
some winning moments
was very lucky
no not really
[Music]
use item oh
oh
okay i have my i don't have a one up
though i only have those all right no
we'll see
i don't need them now
i don't need them because that star will
not stop me if i'm falling down oh you
again
you again my best friend mm-hmm
you act as if you're a friend of mine
but you're not you're fake
you're just trying to hurt me
[Music]
this time i got it this time i got it
so okay
thankfully it carries me up which is
incredible because i just had a really
bad jump and this saved me from it
okay okay
[Music]
no oh my god
to save y'all
[Music]
[Applause]
wait what exactly happened when i got
game over
what exactly happened
do i have to start from the beginning of
everything
uh nothing i just get more lives so
that's amazing
i would why wouldn't i aim for that
i get five more lives
[Music]
i saw that tube hmm
i wish we still had a yoshi
[Music]
oh sick wall jumps
okay pro gamer
don't have to flex that much but okay
[Music]
i'm out here
nothing happened we just collected a lot
of you just closed your eyes and while
you
were closing your eyes
oh
uh i just collected a lot of one ups
because i'm such a pro
where's my yoshi can i get my yoshi back
too
[Music]
yeah yeah i've seen all of that before
you know this i want to finish this
desert within today that would be cool
and then we'll read super chats
first continue out of 50. now
hey hey hey
that box there
why is that here it shouldn't be here
we're starting fresh from the beginning
also apparently yeah we're not we're not
able to use our checkpoint
that's just sad
[Music]
okay
any of those coins
points
apparently today i don't know if you
guys saw it yet because i didn't see it
yet but apparently today
the trailer for the new lord of the
rings show the amazon show
has been
made public oh mamma mia
how exciting
oh hello
oh got him oh
this makes things i think easier
[Music]
yeah definitely i want to do a water
long hell yeah but i don't know i don't
know i kind of also want to say it alone
because then i feel like i can like
enjoy it more like like focus more you
know
uh
let's see
oh
there's a tube i want to go there
we're gonna go there
i can do it
but still yeah someone gonna watch it
with you guys
wait ah how do i do it
special people club
[Music]
oh there we go we got the second special
coin
yeah
[Music]
so we got to skip some
like a few a few sections that would be
nice
oh
i don't know did we
no no you're not gonna get me no no
okay honestly
this
if i can't clear it while i'm flying
then i don't know
what else i could ask for now
[Music]
you know the moment i was like jumping
on this i was thinking won't it override
my current skill
[Music]
and i was like i guess we'll find out
because i'm too fast and faster than i'm
thinking well
all right
wait can i
ah
okay i thought i could collect it like
this okay i guess not okay okay it's not
like like yoshi's
[Music]
tongue bye
here we go
this one
this one spot is curds
[Music]
i need that acorn i need a [\h__\h] acorn
i want it so bad
where's where the flying [\h__\h] huh
[Music]
where are the flying books where are
they
[Music]
they're somewhere up there
there's one man
[Music]
whatever
i wanted to die
that that was
my plan because i already gave up hope
to be honest in this run specifically
[Music]
tilted
now not tilted
[Music]
mario games could never make me feel
such feelings
never ever
[Music]
why did i choose to play mario king
today
why did i even feel like playing this
again no never mind i'm having fun i'm
having fun so i got from one game over i
got five lives am i getting 10 lives
from the second game over
just asking for a friend
who is close to a mind break
situation
no
that's too bad for my friend she's like
really bad at this game
but that's her problem i guess sounds
like a
sounds like a her problem
not a my problem
stop dancing
[Music]
you can only dance if you listen to
favorite night
nope not scared no no no i'm not ready
for that i wasn't ready for that
well that was
a nice safe
okay take care of you first now here's
once again
this spot
[Applause]
i was gonna run because you said you
guys said run but then i was like [\h__\h]
up too fast
[Music]
i wish my brother was here so i could
give him the controller
[Music]
like in the good old days and i would be
like yeah can you do this part please
okay mario come the [\h__\h] out you my
brother now i mean you're literally my
brother
come here
[Music]
wait i'm just looking at you can't even
move with you that doesn't help me
okay let's take a look
[Music]
he's not moving
why why did he wait so long
does he think i'm a grandma or something
i don't need that much time
[Music]
loser
wow
oh so amazing you think you're so
amazing don't ya
[Music]
it's wasting my time we're already past
that part aren't we
shuffling faster
faster
[Music]
why did you get that why didn't you get
that acorn mario oh he's not even going
to show me how to get that i'm learning
nothing from this
i'm learning nothing
slow mario
sick
[Music]
you want a place that good
duh
didn't even care for that
but that box that was so easy to get
okay so this is important let's see do
we learn something from this
[Music]
wait is that really the spot that's not
the one where i keep on [\h__\h] up right
that's not the one no now now this one
this is the one
[Music]
okay is he gonna kill
bastard no okay
[Music]
uh-huh
and now
what you gonna do now
[Music]
okay
what
wait
wait what
what
i can move him
huh
i was gonna i was gonna be like okay i'm
going back to luigi but what you you
continue as mario
oh i thought i was just watching and
learning
oh
that was that was me um
that was
already ended the super guide a while
ago
[Music]
yeah
i did see uh i could probably do this on
my own
[Music]
it was right there
that was right there
that was so close
oh my god i feel humiliated by mario
i feel
i feel [\h__\h] humiliated
i feel so
eh humiliated do you mean cleared i i
cleared it
what do you mean i cleared it
oh that was me that was me
[\h__\h] stupid mario
how did you beat ori
but loose so bad in mario
yeah well
what orien was yeah more difficult and
all that
but it took me i meant for ori it also
took me some time as well
oh this is terrible so i'm a random
stole a bunch of my stuff and he's so
fast i never catch him please you're
gonna help me that way
and we'll go back to the house
it's kind of cute though
do i have to can i do it later
is it like do whenever you want kind of
style
or it was austrian so she understood it
more
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah it's in my blood yeah yeah
totally totally that's exactly the
reason why i was better at already
because it was by austrian developers
no yeah i'm still learning mario i can
get just this good and already
okay so it's for bonus items okay ah
this is no time to stand around you
won't say the crank oh wait no i don't
care you go uh you can do it on your own
yeah pipes
i know they could do that that's sick
left or right
harry lowe's pokey cave or
fire snake cabin okay
i'm going to the pokey cave that sounds
less dangerous
i don't get those boys i [\h__\h] hated
them in super mario 64.
they tend to meet
me not joe
okay i don't really like them but we
have to choose one of the options and
this is the one i'm going for apparently
are you gonna okay you cannot go there
good to know
okay
can we
what you can ride that thing too
hello
[Applause]
wow wow
that's the first time i heard about that
oh no
oh no that thing's riding it
wow
give me that give me that give me that
so far pretty good now i can get rid of
all of those ooh
i don't i don't dislike it that much
it's actually going pretty well
oh wow
sucker
i want that coin
maybe i should kind of on one of these
blocks
should get on one ah [\h__\h] one more one
more
oh no
okay okay everything's [\h__\h] now
everything went so well
[Music]
i want the coin i'm gonna just be
wasting so much time again
[Applause]
okay [\h__\h] you i don't want the coin
anymore
i never wanted you anyway
i don't care for big golden coins
[Music]
that is so mean
i'm gonna tell my mommy
i'm gonna tell my one life left oh [\h__\h]
so fast i was jumping pretty fast you
know when they change the color does it
mean they're not spiky when they're
like the bright orange color
it's not changing anymore
what does it mean
no no super guy for me
[Music]
oranges
spiny oranges
[Music]
let me thank you
i need it i need it i need it
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay we're playing hard mode
sick dodge
okay jump on that one
jump on you
okay
why why the hell are there bananas in
the desert too game
over not again
[Music]
people gonna make so much fun of me
no one's gonna tell me all everything
again as if i haven't seen it already
wait i have to do the level again the
first one
[Music]
let's see
yeah he knows it
why do i have to do it not that one
[Music]
a safe one i don't think i saved after
doing this
i gotta restart the world
oh
no
god oh my god
well we're gonna be we're gonna be
better at it now
probably
definitely
[Music]
we got a
fireplace
let's get some points here
yeah
okay
those points what are they for
exactly
nothing
[Music]
okay checkpoints so far so good see i
just now that i know that the end is so
close at that point where i have had so
much trouble i feel like
i'm gonna do a much better job
yes
[Music]
when you know that the end is near don't
you like
play better in games huh have you never
felt that way
yeah
look at those big skills
you got the moves like each other got
the moves like
wow i can throw money around
more stress-free people usually work i
don't believe in that
but see we have so much time
[Music]
never mind i don't need the fire at the
end section here i don't need it
i was gonna you know jump on him and be
like
yeah
scaled and all that
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay we're on the
second one or the second one that's
something now
what did mari what would mario do
he would just jump over like this as if
it was no problem ever at all
[Music]
and what did we learn from that
you play better when you know that the
end is near as kiwawa told you
yeah my pride is restored now because
now i did it without mario's help
now i don't have to feel so humiliated
anymore
feels much better
gay mervyn oh thank you so much
we already heard their stories um
i wish there was a skip button
they keep on showing us the same things
as if they really just want us to suffer
look at our suffering look at our
mistakes
probably trying to give us some time to
reflect on upon our reactions okay that
is a very important thing
you know in german
in german i actually i never
heard someone use that word like that
before i think like reflect on your
actions and i don't even know if it's
such a common thing in english to say
but in japanese
they say it so often
like when some
some celebrity or so had some
scandal or even if it's just something
at school or something
they did something a little bad
and they would be like okay hanse she
must
say she must stop
i've reflected upon my actions
i am deeply
sorry
you're in the way buddy
i can kill you i forgot
much better now it's common in english
really
see i really don't think we use that in
in
german for some reason we just don't
i guess we
we too reflect on our actions
i would say
but we just need don't need to make it
so obvious maybe
[Music]
whatever
too much you do it too much you can
never reflect too much
but still
i'm still big
all right there's probably a new flower
in here no there's not
ohana hide the name
[Music]
oh my god
okay i do like this scent because it
saves me from a lot of embarrassing
situations
what
is there secret there
it wasn't worth it wasn't worth checking
it out it was not worth it
is there
just like why else would there be that
thing that blocked there
there was a secret there i got them and
i couldn't reach it
monkey's so cute do i need a like a
monkey outfit
the monkey persona
now's the moment now's the moment
oh there's so many of them
[Music]
so
give me close to work with come on
a monkey p and g parts oh yeah look
think about the possibilities guys all
the things that we could do do i get a
checkpoint did i find a checkpoint
i got further done before
no
almost was good no no i think that was
pretty good it was a pretty good run i
would say
[Music]
okay
mushroom
[Music]
no i'm scared
i'm a pretty lady i deserve some pretty
flowers come on come on come on
[Music]
endless fire spam
reminds me of polo cure
manhole here was so much fun last time i
wanna
i wanna play more whole cure
but i'll play it in my private time
because i don't wanna spam too much of
the same game on my channel which brings
me to the topic of persona
i know i
uh
i know i considered to play persona like
five probably on my channel
but here's uh two things
or actually more like one
um
i realized it's
really
freaking long like not even joking uh
i thought you know people said it's long
i thought maybe you know long like my
other usual games like tales of arrives
you know
or any any kind of long jpg game that i
play the fire emblem but even fire
emblem
is shorter than
uh i think that's i mean i guess you can
like play it longer if you want to
yeah
so i'm not saying like no never ever but
for now no i'm not i'm currently
not open for such a commitment
um and then catherine
i would like to start soon um
but uh sorry guys i actually need to
wait for catherine a little bit longer
because
currently it's like uh i can only play
the japanese version um for reasons i'm
not gonna go too deep into it
uh we'll have to wait a little bit
longer for catherine but once i get like
you know before let's go
i will
get to it
that will be my next pick but if it
takes
too long uh-huh
oh if it takes there's a checkpoint if
it takes so long
found something
then
i'm actually considering playing a
a tails off game
possibly one i haven't
no you're not gonna take the flame away
from me there you go
you're not gonna take it away from me
either
what is this approach
yeah um
maybe i was thinking symphonia too
because i've played sinfonia one before
but now i'm just wondering maybe for the
sake of the stream i should not just
start with sinfonia too
should i be playing
the whole
series
i don't know that would take so much
time and would be such a long commitment
have any viewers here play symphonia one
before
but it's one of the few towns of games i
haven't played yet
that's why i want to do it
yes nope yeah oh quite a few
oh [\h__\h] okay can i make it oh yeah it's
right there
oh [\h__\h] you
uh
okay
one of my favorite games yeah right
tails off one of my favorite titles of
games too because it's my first one
[Music]
thank you if you lost it yeah that would
have been shocking
it would have been entertaining maybe
too
have you played japanese only once
japanese only i
don't think so
oh should i have saved oh [\h__\h] well i
can save if i die again like
what is this
i oh can i get that corn please
[Music]
shut not be so hard
i know you guys are probably saying
just run
[Music]
but i'm trying to get used to the
controls you know
i got it i got it
it's a bit difficult to run when there's
like no space you know
at least it feels difficult for me
oh i can bring it closer
[Music]
oh
nice okay we got a weapon that we can
use to destroy these
[Music]
wrong direction but okay
interesting i wonder if those also
only
uh die with the blue fire or
ice i guess
or
i see that
because of those skeletons
i don't know if we can make that one
coin
am i not going to be stuck anyway i
don't know
whatever i don't need it
whoa
it's like an all-in-one package deal
let's go
did you see how fast i did all those
actions you couldn't even
you couldn't even see what i was doing i
was so fast
i think it's about time that we get a
new um a new one anyway
probably soon
i'm hopeful
okay that was of course gonna happen
why why are you going that way
that was very unnecessary
i'm going to lose it again am i
i'm going to lose it again i'm gonna
lose it again
let's wait for that buddy
let's wait for him
okay okay stay safe
it's just a coin why didn't oh for a
moment i felt like that deactivated all
the music
[Music]
you have to get into the tube
in time there we go
just a coin how disappointing but hey
look at that we got the checkpoint
already here
oopsie
why does he look so big was he always
this big
is he like a boss skeleton
ah was this my job to squeeze him squish
him
there we go there we go i made some
stairs ah
[Music]
i wish i would have gotten that how do i
get you without hurting myself
[Music]
oh so many
that gives me a little bit more room to
play with
it
besides the cafe
what else was there to talk about was
there something
so i see that too but i don't know i
want to just you know make it in time so
go away
is there something else i was supposed
to talk about
crunch oh crunchyroll looks cool yeah
that's a thing that's gonna happen
are any of you guys going to crunchyroll
xbox
[Music]
i feel like i lost it before
i attacked that thing
hacker
hacker style
i live nearby let's go
wasn't planning on it what about now
what about now
[Music]
oh
i think there's a little bit of a boss
spot going on here
[Music]
two of you
i have no weapon
okay it's okay
boom boom
i noticed the playstation
wait are they making advertisements for
playstation even though it's nintendo
[Music]
i was uh clumsy clumsy clowns are clumsy
oh
uh
can i just fight him directly or do i
really need to
go from my
save point again
i have to go for my save point again
[Music]
let me do that again where we use squash
ah there we go
why is it so stupid
[Music]
i just saw that secret
i wanted to go back and then i got
squished
okay okay i see i see i see
i see uh
let's go
i will go there now
that's that's something i found by
accident
first we take care of you
how do we do that
you just always do it by accident i
don't really know how to do it
okay
it doesn't matter
oh
[\h__\h]
he just goes there
he just walks in there
as if it was no secret you're letting
everybody know the secret
you can't do that
what about the pact huh here we go
let it go to the corner
okay okay patience patience patience it
is
push him over
let him go to the corner how about
ah now we need to let them pass and then
okay there we go now we have a
clear path to work with
oh yeah i didn't really say anything
about crunchyroll expo uh i'm doing
i'm doing like a panel there
and with ian
so
it's gonna be like a double double
trouble panel
let's go
i think there will be meeting greets too
yeah yeah yeah yeah what
we got a present
i can use any of these i get the one of
the weakest ones all right all right the
weapon would have been nice but i guess
i'm not
getting that i have to earn it
first taco totally panel i guess so yeah
i did uh oh
[Music]
right
i'm waiting for them to like go
somewhere where they're not in the
[\h__\h] way
don't hit me
ah so not worth it
can't reach it again
okay the salt is getting strong
yeah just go there together
beat
and whatever no
my thumb hurts no
[Music]
i don't know how
why did i do it so easily before i'm
sorry guys i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
i know
i know it's painful to watch i know
oh there's a secret
secret
cubes again
whoa whoa
critical damage
is there a way for me to
kill those
freaks
without hurting myself maybe like a
twirl
[Music]
i can't reach it won't jump
where to
go
just being a little bit faster getting
the timing right is key
ah
i don't want to scream but i need to
read super chats afterwards
i don't want to hurt my friends
[Music]
you know i had such a positive
let's go attitude in the beginning
not anymore not anymore
maybe a little bit faster come on
[Music]
i'm gonna go get the secret again
i mean i guess i could but whoa well
all right hi
hi
that's enough
well here once again don't worry it's
really close
[Music]
how i was just about to say i wish i
could squish them
not sure how i did that
now he's right in the way uh that's not
good
we got a clip yeah i wanna do that with
everybody
[Music]
wait for him
okay well everyone's telling me to go up
this way so let me just first take care
of this body
okay
go up this way but those will probably
make this go all the way
as far as it can
[Music]
can she make it
yes she can
[Music]
[Applause]
incredible
shoot shoot shoot
shot
the ice should help a lot right or does
not work on him by any chance
[Applause]
okay
what for trying
i hate you so much crazy
you stole everything from me
okay
[Music]
it's not healthy
it's not healthy we're gonna worry super
chats now
bye
princess
daisyara
is now gonna just read subjects
i'm not gonna do it too
no no need to save okay i'm not going to
destroy
my voice any further
because that's not worth it oh thank you
austin
ah
tokyo mirage sessions
[Music]
i don't know about that
as a stream i don't know i don't know i
feel like i considered that one before
my decision was no
tactical retreat yeah we complained
another time but
thank you for watching though you're
welcome stay because we're going to read
super chats now
yeah yeah
[Music]
yes i can attach any png i mean not
necessarily any i don't know about
copyright you know
[Music]
yeah
preferably stuff that is copyright free
would be good i'm gonna make dinner if
he doesn't
ah
have fun
my office looks messy and how about you
clean it up huh
if you're complaining i don't hear
anybody else complaining
so i think it should be you
i'll show you
[Music]
just tell us what png you want
i don't know what i want there's so many
possibilities it's just new i don't even
know what i want yeah i look like i have
no arms
oh man look at me look at me looking
funny
ah
i look funny don't lie it's so wobbly
hats work pretty well clothes you know
you know especially when the oopsie when
the
anatomy is so different
from you know
what i'm working with
a little bit tough one
[Music]
i'll keep this music i think it's
actually pretty nice
[Music]
yeah finally i mean i won't we wanted
this feature for so long and they'll
finally finally finally have it
took a long time now it's finally here
uh it's gonna be fun using it i can put
like you know glasses some cool glasses
on my
face or on the outfits that don't have
sunglasses
or doesn't even have to be sunglasses
yeah just notice it look how did you
just notice
wasn't it so in your face
yeah
yeah yeah we can do a lot of things it's
gonna be fun to attach these things uh
also like during mario kart tournament
you know we can all properly wear it and
have it at least move a little bit with
us
and uh oh the the blankets you know the
movie watch along blankets
you know because i move so far from side
to side they never really like work well
with me right
but now i can put the blanket on top of
me and it will actually go with me it
might be a little bit wobbly but it's
gonna work much better oh the tails off
sash for example yeah
i don't think i'm gonna use that anymore
but yeah stuff like that
today
[Music]
maybe we should play another zelda game
or or any any i guess this doesn't have
to be a zelda game anything with weapons
so i can put a lot of weapons on myself
[Music]
i can try if i find it
oh my god let me try it
i want to try this
let me try some things
[Music]
where did it go
there it is okay let me try it
ah
[Music]
experimentation time
i guess i'll take off my beautiful dress
and my beautiful hat
[Music]
new
we'll start off with this
wait that's not a real png
okay i got bamboozled again
let me quickly make a png out of this
how the [\h__\h] is that not a png oh my god
i'm so mad
jpegs why why you do this to me
but actually the one that i'm trying to
attach to myself is just so perfect
right now so i'm going to go through the
trouble
oh sure
might look a little bit scuffed but
yeah that's gonna be very
scuffed oh
shut up
shut up wil you
what the [\h__\h]
so cursed
okay i'm gonna turn this a little bit
like this
all right save us png
[Music]
okay i'm gonna look beautiful with this
it's going to look beautiful
[Music]
ah
where did i put it
[Music]
okay
okay i need to share this with you guys
[Laughter]
oh no
i'm so sad
life is suffering life is pain nothing
is worth it anymore [\h__\h] mario [\h__\h]
louise you [\h__\h] ball i don't want to
say that ever again
life songs
i just want to cuddle my cats all day
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
okay i'm just gonna i'm just gonna keep
them on while reading super chats okay
[Laughter]
welcome to the stream
are you suffering yet
what else what else well that was not
the one that i originally wanted to put
on
oh yeah i wanted to put the leg but i
don't know where it is
[Music]
maybe for another time i need to find
the leg again and then turn it into a
png because i think it's a gif
[Music]
i am
i can
i let's see can i learn
[Music]
i can be oh
i can be i can be someone else
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
and it's my channel now hey
suck it
[\h__\h] you mario
at least we share the hatred for mario
yeah
all right all right all right
all right around the ride
actually this is really not what i
wanted to let me get done this
for sure
[Music]
my god
okay let's get rid of the cursed eyes
oh
oh my god i have peeked
i have pink
i have picked
close your eyes
i know it makes no difference but close
your eyes and then
hello
[Music]
remember to smile
i can i can
show you my tongue finally
[Music]
i mean if i don't move too much
it's really not that bad
like for screenshots
[Music]
it happened
oh my god
heart eyes
hard i can give it a try
[Music]
uh
okay then
another one
[Music]
okay
all right
i got it
oh my god
um
[Music]
what does this not look cute
something weird
i
i'm trying to look cute
[Music]
something weird something off-looking
it looks derpy i guess so
oh man
i really tried
hard i say so cute idol
so much idol oh my god
i can do oh
i need
i need some more pngs
on myself please wait a moment
please hold the line
[Music]
all right all right all right
okay
and then
[Music]
okay we can
add
this
oh
baby
that works so good
uh
[Music]
here come on come on you did it before
okay okay
so we can do shenanigans like this
wait
okay
shenanigans like this
i have an idea and i also have handcuffs
that move with me yeah let's go
let's go
oh i should keep the handcuffs that
actually looks really smooth
that looks like a hand pose that's like
integrated
we're so ready let's go
now i'll have a nightmare why
why there's nothing wrong with this it's
all beautiful
i was so smart i have a light bulb above
my head constantly so so inspired so
creative
hell yeah
let's let me get my final form let's see
what is my final form
what's my final form
[Music]
what's gonna write out this
my final form oh
i can do that
ah so many possibilities
are cute
[Music]
oh i can become a christmas tree
cat i know i don't know if i'm ready for
my final form yet but
let's do this let's do this one maybe
oh yeah
[Music]
okay
oh yes
that is what i'm talking about
cafe
who of you in the chat was making fun of
me for being a bad mario player
who was it
who wants it huh
you want a little ass beating huh let me
get your ass kicked huh
come here come here little chicken come
here come here now oh
no there's no place to run
you can run but you can't hide come here
little chicken
look at this beautiful bat it was a
present
present for majima
yeah he wants me to use it you what what
you would want me to use it too right
make majima proud
and no more no more making fun of me
no more of that i don't want to see any
more you better be quiet quiet and be
good little chickens reflect on your
actions yeah
all right now that we cleared that one
up
i shall read the budget now
but i will keep the bat
i'll keep the bat
you can't stop me
can do nothing against this
huawei is in control oh but i would like
a hat
i i would like a hat please
i need a hat
a new hat please
[Music]
what's a good hat
oh this one
wonder if anybody remembers this hat
[Music]
it works so well let's go
okay that should be fine
[Music]
what do you think about this kfb
what do you think
[Music]
remember you said i got it from my i
think my last birthday
howdy
let's go that that uh updo works so well
with hats let's go
even the sideways hats doesn't even look
so weird
no i said milady howdy milady
not a good time to provoke me that's
right
you will see him to be understanding the
situation and reading it correctly
[Laughter]
we're my favorite deputy tenchuk
cowboy with a baseball bat
baseball bat
i guess it is a baseball bat
it's more powerful than that you should
give it a more powerful name
[Music]
yes all right
all right mommy kiwamo is going to read
the super chat now
my eyes there we go
oh no they should i i understand now why
they waited so long
to give us this power because it's too
powerful we're too powerful it shouldn't
have given us this much power
oh my goodness
[Music]
here
where do we continue reading you guys
know the number thank you for the pinky
ronin thank you
october 2020 holy [\h__\h]
thank you so much
i will get to your super chat eventually
2016 2018 okay
[Music]
i'm
hungry i got potato chips
i guess i'm gonna quickly snack on some
potato chips through them
let me just uh
pull out the
stream
um this one
let's go get him let's get him with the
baseball bat
and maybe an idol
meeting would be a good choice too so i
feel a bit more comfortable
found it
okay
[Music]
i don't
okay i'll go get the idle meaning and
the
snack snack snacks
okay
but
no fooling around kfb i got the bat
i got cameras here too
careful i'm here i'm just right here
i could show up every time anytime
surprise [\h__\h]
okay oops wait i'll just stay here okay
[Music]
do
i had the cat i had junkers in my arms
and now i lost her
i lost her
[Music]
why was that potato chips back open
i just pulled out oh no this
is potatoes everywhere
[Music]
oh god okay give me a second please
i need to
pick up
oh they're everywhere and they're
[\h__\h] tiny wait i have the vacuum
machine right here okay i'm just let's
just take the vacuum for a second
i'm just gonna
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
it's everywhere
housewife
it's [\h__\h] everywhere
[Applause]
all okay
[Music]
did not expect that
let me grab a new closed
potato chips bag
okay
nice i did not miss a spot
[Music]
these are really tiny
um okay
i deserve a snack now right i even
vacuumed
[Music]
no jonkers hates the vacuum
she's probably somewhere in the corner
of my closet now
[Music]
thank god bales sent me these potato
chips
they really pay off
goodnight
yeah
[Music]
i'm not eating them from the vacuum
ew
no not the shapes the
red rock deli chips
[Music]
prove it didn't you hear the sound of me
opening a new bag
[Music]
i'm vacuuming them in my mouth yeah
i'm getting here
now i really want to do a movie watch
along
because i want to use the the
i want to use them a blanket but don't
worry tomorrow actually when i'm
planning is a city skylines for members
only
it's gonna be a series
yeah i actually i got us a lot of um
game permissions for membership streams
we used to like only have two
now i kind of like i got us quite a few
quite a bunch
[Music]
no it's not the movie it's a game
you're playing a game because i had in
mind that we play a game next time we
can watch a movie again maybe it's been
a while
yeah city skylines i think it will be
nice like a chill project of chill game
series actually for the members
we can
make it into the series play it several
times
[Music]
high school musical
no no
yeah
how many expansions eh
i know i just have i didn't even buy
anything yet but uh
i don't even know if we can only play
the base game or the expansions i'm
guessing for now we only play the base
game
i got a hell now onion
hmm
so many expansions okay i gotta ask
about that
it can get complicated fast no no at all
you need permission for expansions maybe
i'm not sure
kind of play it safe though
two hundred dollars worth of expansion
oh my god
yeah finished wind waker
finally
[Music]
kiana your chest is really mesmerizing
i'm sorry to point that out
are you wearing um
[Music]
you can only point that out to me if
you're also wearing a hat
you know out of respect and then tip it
tip that hat
there we go
you're going to miss the the kiara wind
waker music i think it's on concurrent
channel
he tips ten percent what about twenty
percent ayo
twenty percent minimum
oh
thank you 30 oh
imagine
the ah
a guy with a fedora
in a restaurant
in a bad mood or he just doesn't like to
tip in general
imagine that kind of like person you
know in we situated let's say in america
where tipping is so important apparently
sits in a restaurant doesn't feel like
tipping at all
doesn't tip ever anyway
girl walks up to him says where's my tip
and he's he just tips his fedora
and thinks he's like cool or something
okay i made up this whole scenario in my
mind but i can totally see that it would
have happened sometime at some place
before
[Music]
i'm sure someone did that before
okay i'm done with the potato chips
[Music]
i'm already mad about it nah
i'm just seeing it as a you know outside
point of view
[Music]
yeah
oyster
you know i feel like with these pngs oh
man i have so many ideas for like
if i ever have a new outfit revealed but
i feel like i might not be the only one
playing around with that in that
situation so huh
[Music]
you know like you can actually like put
oh you can oh we can ask like the people
you know their suggestions the outfit
suggestions we can ask them to submit
them in pngs
and then like actually put them on
ourselves when we represent them
when we show them off
[Music]
yeah i know i'm unleashed with this
she's gonna use it every freaking stream
i'm just gonna do so much with it
[Music]
i'm cool
um doesn't really need it to be moving
i'll just poke out my face with those
and fill the whole screen with the image
[Music]
well i might test it out though see what
i can do with that but it's not like i
really need a dot for the msu show
series
um okay
yeah i really liked what anna uploaded
on twitter today with the the trash can
[Laughter]
i like that idea already whoo lamin
let's go
she must be so inspired
i might have to go get some water later
i'm already running out of it
okay reading so potatoes once again
from
[Music]
i think we can get this over with today
here we go here we go
music is nice too isn't it should i make
it a bit louder maybe just
there we go
and lord eva thank you for the pinky ah
perfect that we continue with you today
mama mia it's auntie algorithm
this means best one just happy birthday
oh i'm surprised i never heard about
i've never heard the
the italian version of happy birthday
before
oh
my legacy hello devo okay
what's up bloody book
thank you so much
thank you for teaching me italian once
again
and and for
bearing with my
shitty italian
[Laughter]
my wannabe italian
all the time yeah so kind-hearted so
sweet and open-minded
thank you so much for the support thank
you soon
hope you had a great time on your
birthday and also in america while you
were there
thank you very much
yeah
i had them besides you know being very
busy and uh
exhausted
i had a good time in america yeah um
i mean
[Music]
i feel like maybe one or two extra days
would have been nice to see a bit more i
do a bit more sightseeing
um
but you know back then when i booked the
flight uh i was like
yeah
10 i think it was like 10 days i was
looking at and i was like oh man like
i feel like you guys are gonna
suffer a lot and you did
let's be honest a lot of you missed me
missed especially the the one-on-one
streams during that time
so i feel like any longer than that
he's a bit tough if i don't really you
know stream
in between
i didn't i mean we did stream we did
quite a few collabs in the end we did
the
one with admin we did the super smash
brothers we did the pop-tart one we did
two kinda okay ones we did the arm
wrestling
and
i think that's it but that's a lot i
think even though you know we were
really busy so
um
it was tough but we survived
yeah
i think if i when i go to korea my plan
is to um stream
in the evening
you know
late in the evening after you know
eating dinner when everything is done
for the day
uh
so
evening
evening time korea
will be
pretty ooh what time if i stream at like
11 p.m i i do sometimes start my streams
at 11 pm jst already while i'm here so
actually
it could be my usual streaming slot for
long games like 4pm
uh cest
because i often start at like 11 p.m jst
and korea is the same time yeah
actually yeah so then it might not be so
unusual for you guys
oh yeah might not be so unusual so i'm
planning to do that
and yeah play some games and so on as
well so i don't want it too much to be
like oh i'm gone bye-bye sayonara
i will be around i'll try my best
so freeze the frog anyway sorry i went
to the tangent there but thank you so
much
for the support
yay
kyler sand wow thank you for the big red
super chat thank you
happy birthday wawa your 4d concert is
awesome and those dance moves are fire
thank you so much for all your hard work
oh thank you donkey shoe yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah and and they were
they were pretty good i was like
my dancing was one thing i'm very proud
of so thank you for seeing that and
praising me for it thank you soon i
appreciate it now here's some choo choos
thank you
you know what i should do
oh my god
i want to
we already have the key arsenal hashtag
i want people to um
i want i want to do like a like a big
you know
haul
on everybody
to
make
more pngs now
like what they want us to put what they
want me to put on myself specifically
you know
how to say
get them to post more of that kind of
stuff
hmm
[Music]
preferably an actual png's though
because i think a lot of people would
like mess it up and just post it in
jpegs
please try to post it in pjs easier
paper donkey wobble ah so cute
that's that yeah that's good cute paper
though
like paper dolls give pee cave props
why can't we not use key arsenal
why do we need a new one isn't it kind
of the same thing
chiara assets
[Music]
twitter twitter's transparency stings
well yeah you have to keep it pretty
small in order to make it work
unfortunately but i do want to do that
get more stuff
you know fan made handmade
personalized
individualized stuff for me to stick on
myself yeah
sounds like fun
so kaisen thank you for the rest of
support
[Music]
let's check out 47 hours for the pinky
yeah there's some stuff but simple being
able to see you like this is amazing
great choice of covers and the music was
so great that even though the calling
sections are lovely i was wishing they
could go faster so i could see more
yeah actually
uh during the the calling sections i was
like you know
it was like pretty much unscripted and
especially the energy one was like the
first thing we recorded
and i felt so unprepared like suddenly
thrown into cold water and the the suit
was still so unusual to me
um
and yeah i was kind of like yeah what am
i doing blah blah blah blah yeah thrown
into the water
in a shark tank uh
next time i feel like i will have more
control over it especially if
everything's planned out a little bit
better and not like uh people being late
had to move some appointments
uh
some call-ins because of certain things
happening actually that was really
stressful too because like originally
on the second day i was recording i was
i was supposed to record a call in
and then
certain someone i'm not gonna say who
overslept not the person you would
normally expect uh i guess
but yeah someone overslept and then
on the
then i had to move it over to the third
day
and then
uh
yeah a lot of things had to be moved
around but you know on the first day i
already had to record like 10 songs
because nothing worked out before that
so
yeah it was really really really really
really a tight schedule on the last day
[Music]
so next time i want to go into that a
little bit more with like
more time so it's not so stressful and
so [\h__\h] tight man
hopefully that will release some
pressure and stress
it was kiwa no it was not me
i was there
i woke up so early and went to bed so
late for like all of those days
[Music]
i woke up like before
around before
before 9 00 am
each day
and went to sleep
like
around 2 a.m
if not later
each day
because we had so much to do
yeah
[Music]
and i you know i wanted to sleep as much
as possible because i knew i knew it was
ahead of me i knew i had to you know
dance so much and i wanted to have some
energy
ah
yeah
i i kind of expected though that things
wouldn't all go according to keikaku
unfortunately
next time we'll go smoother yeah
i hope so
[Music]
oh
morrow
[Music]
red books behind me oh wait where was
that again
what's those books again let me see it
how to
run a business ah well i have to run the
business one two and three
those are the books that's what's
written on them
i thought it was gonna be like some some
reference to my streams it's actually
not huh
[Music]
now don't worry about it it's okay
they're a mess is what they are excuse
me
they're not
anyway continuing fuzz buns thank you
for the ride super chat happy birthday
kiana your friday concert was wonderful
all of your hard work really paid off
and your tenacity is inspirational us to
be expected of the strong majestic
phoenix thank you
thank you very much
i'm glad you enjoyed it so much it was a
lot of work and it did need a lot of
tenacity
thank you so much for watching and
appreciating it thank you another kiss
[Music]
thanks to you
please continue supporting kiwawa
logical paradox function
attention is an idol without a shadow of
doubt and lady yes
oh i'm so many things now aussie
you know you know what's up thank you
for not forgetting about the lady title
a lot of people are forgetting it and i
am
tolerating it but i don't know for how
long
mm-hmm well thank you so much aoshi
i can imagine you tipping your hat in
front of me
with so much respect i'm sure you're
doing it automatically thank you very
much for your support gentlemen
the chat just emojis with it no text but
thank you so much
[Music]
big kiss for you
thank you so much
nene diesel thank you for the red super
chat and wordless your stage was so
amazing past tense is this already the
end it is everyone's writing in past
tense
oh i guess it is it really is
i can't hold my tears so proud of you
you are the best congrats on one million
followers and happy birthday and thai
gift be really happy to see you love our
tuck ducks project
means love you in thai oh
raknaka you too
thank you very much yo that's so it was
so sweet it was so cute thank you i
don't know who organized it maybe it was
you but yeah
thank you very sweet cute surprise i'm
gonna if i ever go to thai i'm gonna
ride on a tuk tuk and imagine that it
was the kiwa
[Laughter]
right
maybe what
callie has a stream of cobble
ah
nani
honey
i knew she was eventually gonna go for
her she likes small small
people god damn it
father daughter
kelly you know what you're doing right
you know what makes uh what that makes
us
do you do you
[Music]
gonna love her more than me no no
yeah i guess we gotta fight over custody
i see i see i see
[Music]
i feel like you know soon
look at her eyes and thumbnail
her eyes look dangerous
[Laughter]
visit her and get her that horse
oh man
i guess i have to
oh man oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
17 hours 17 hours
8pm
oh man
okay well
[Music]
mommy's the best pride kofu
you're not gonna leave mommy for daddy
right
[Music]
uh
don't leave me
what's up jebel well can't we give up
jebel
i want cooper
don't leave me
i'm sure chloe is gonna fall in love
with the coolness and all that
oh man
i need to be as cool as kelly
i just don't have it in me you know
[Music]
okay
oh man
show her your rap she's a rapper
ah she's gonna like me more when i sing
her song i'm sure
oh man okay
i love that
[Music]
okay wipe my tears i'm gonna wipe my
teeth and be happy again howdy what's up
nene diesel here's a kiss for you
all right oh my god
oh it's 176 thank you for the ride
first off collapse and now the friday
birthday we're chickens are truly
blessed right now
yeah that's right
your performance both singing and
dancing was awesome right afternoon
heard oh deutsch
[Music]
ah
hello
it's been a while thanks for the pinky
you're pretty confident what's the best
today you're always the best for me
and
oh
yeah
you know
[Music]
thank you so much thank you soon it's
nice to see you again i hope you're
still watching all of my streams yeah
yeah yeah you better you better thanks
for staying up so late to watch it thank
you
mystical saplings
thank you for the rest of the chat i
really love kiara
really you really do you really really
really really really really really
i shall believe you
thank you so much ellen john i love you
too
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat
oh so many chihuahua hearts
thank you soon for the for the many many
many many hearts i want to give all of
them back to you
i'm not like a return kind of thing but
you know exchange kind of thing you give
me heights i give you hearts
thank you
[Music]
the brady concept was spectacular your
beautiful dancing and singing has easily
made it one of my favorite 4d lives
really
hi junkie monkey
i
couldn't be more proud of you you nerd
did you really just call me a nerd
dissing me in the birthday super chat
they sing me the birthday super chat for
real zones
i'm not a nerd you're a nerd you're a
nerd
should i be scared of course you should
always be scared if you watch my streams
of course anyway why not thank you so
much i'm glad it's up there in your
favorites if that if that made it into
your favorites and i have a
good feeling i'm pretty confident
to say that soon
or soon the next concert will be your
number one favorite then because i can
easily top that
easy
thank you
marty
thank you for the pink super chat come
sign me down and it says
you're the best
let's go thank you
you're also chekota
thank you
a pink bacon thank you for the rancho
bachato happy birthday thank you for all
your hard work you did amazing oh thank
you for being there to watch it and
appreciate it yeah
thank you soon
ah
you know i only gave
it my all because i
i wanted you guys to be proud of me and
appreciate it yeah
so thank you so much pink bacon
thank you soon mwah onto many more
concerts hope you will be there again
to
watch me dance yeah
we are proud thank you thank you
so so proud of you the proudest what
proud of you more than you can imagine
thank you
one could say i could put down my bat
now
because we're so titan here but now i'm
gonna keep it it's nice it looks nice
i like you know leaning my head against
it
cuddling with it ah good bat i love you
bad
[Music]
story corner thank you
you know the way i pronounce bat bet bet
it sounds like bed in german b-e-t-t
and i do definitely love my bed as well
so
accurate feels very genuine to me
yeah
story conan thank you
[Music]
oh
kiana i don't super chat to you much but
i want you to know you have my support
with everything you do and i'm always
watching and keeping up with everything
you do
thank you love you tanja keep giving it
all you're all for everything you're
really special thank you it's really
sweet
it's nice to know that no matter what i
do you'll be there to support me even
when i do something stupid
right that's what you say right no
matter what i do so even when i do
something stupid thank you glad to know
you'll be there
thank you so much
yummy thank you soon milo it's thank you
soon frog on toast oh
do you need help why are you on toast
should i help you down
oh hi chunky monkey
what are you doing
[Music]
she was about to run away but i stubbed
her
now she's on my on my lap hi chunky
no
did you hear that
little tiny
this was amazing thank you for all your
hard work also kiara hips please have
mercy on us
even though they were nerfed they still
look so good don't they at least from
like the front
from the side yeah
yeah
not so much well don't go away yes she
would no not quite it's more like a
complaining
what the hell are you doing mommy
thank you frog on toast
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed it so
much
no don't go
goddammit i'm losing jokers no
[Music]
no you got some moves oh thank you
i felt a little bit you know embarrassed
doing some moves um
but
especially the hip first but the hip
presses thankfully i was actually quite
relieved when they were kind of nerfed
thanks to the motion capture
there was not so much frosting
that was actually good the one nerf that
i appreciate
hypnotizing aha we already heard that
one go get a new one
that is in front
of tom watson
[Music]
simpleton thanks for the pinky
have your potential knowing all the hard
work you put into this has has made it
more enjoyable than ever never been so
invested in our lives thank you for
taking us along on its journey you know
who helped to make you helped you make
this is uh this a reality are incredible
thank you
yeah i i do share so much about anything
i do so the process even before you even
saw it i wanted to share
a lot so you guys could relate and
understand why i'm so busy
and why i was away and all that i didn't
want to make it all into a big ass
mystery so
i want you guys to be able to
you know understand and
wait for it patiently
because you knew what was coming
so thank you simpleton for waiting thank
you and supporting thank you
hey sir bandit thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday what an
amazing concept thank you i'm glad you
liked it
thank you very much
uh please don't leave your belongings
take everything you brought to the
concert hall don't forget your umbrellas
that you needed because you cried so
much one could have fought it was
raining
exposed just kidding i don't know if you
actually cried some people said they
cried at the end during blackrock
shooter i'm glad it had that kind of
effect it was supposed to be a really
emotional um
special ending but
first and foremost it was supposed to be
emotional and special for hookah pop-up
yeah
it's an extra that you guys cried
thank you thank you thank you you cried
oh it's okay oh oh really so many of you
damn yeah you guys must have some really
special feelings for me
[Music]
i'm so
sweet
i'm crazy but i appreciate the work you
put in thank you
all right so much with beers triumphant
climax oh
that's great i'm i'm happy with the set
list i feel like uh four blood and
ladylike could could have been switched
maybe
but i wanted to do that you know the
look over the shoulder i wanted to do
that right in the beginning but then
four blood was actually also a great
beginning song because of um the lights
being out and then the silhouette
being seen only would have been a good
one too actually in hindsight i might
have want to switch those two but they
both work well yeah
i guess yeah they're both good
[Music]
no
no no
no no no no no no no
[Music]
good set list
thank you
many hearts many beautiful orange hearts
thank you you're next thanks for the
pinkie i'm sorry canada but i need to
watch this again i just started bawling
the moment you danced on stage
you moved so beautifully with so much
confidence and purpose nailing the
choreo perfectly you did it so proud of
you i love you my aussie thank you
ah
it's it might have been good that um
uh
and although if we could have recorded
properly on the first day i probably
would have taken some retakes too but on
the first day you know when i was
waiting
for everything to work out i was still
practicing so much
on the second day two
so if i would have recorded it on the
first day some moves might have still
been kind of like not so confident kind
of scuffed maybe
i am but those two days gave me a little
bit more extra time to learn the choreo
hammering it into my brain so that was
actually good yeah it was i was quite
confident in most
choreos by the end
um thankfully
yeah
worked out well not really but
you gotta deal with what you're gonna
get
you know santa maria
[Music]
are you writing the pronunciation too
thank you fusai shiyumi
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
and have a perfect potential it's my
first red super chat thank you so much
for bringing us such an amazing life
today your streams and inspiring songs
have given me energy in times of
difficulty i'm proud to be a kfp
thank you
i'm proud to have you in kfb thank you
very much for your first friends of the
chat and thank you for being part of
this of the audience of the lovely
audience yeah
it's a blessing thank you so much i'm
glad you get something good out of my
stream so continue watching it and then
you'll become number one happiest person
in the wide wide
[Music]
well the real girl didn't please stand
up please stand up please stand up
red super chat all of your practice has
paid off
whatever army put into this setup it was
worth every penny
whatever it took for kanado to finish
this his dedication is proven out thank
you inna and gooda for helping make this
possible
yay
yeah you know you know i'm good i helped
too so they appreciate them
they deserve some appreciation too
especially inna she was like on the on
the day
on the on the
second day yeah
uh there was no guna so most of the
figuring out was done on that second day
by almond you know to get it somewhat
ready by the third day
yeah so glad i couldn't really you know
help out that much even if i wanted to
because like i they kept on like sending
me in and out and in and out of the room
like okay well can you leave the room we
need to recalibrate the room and then i
go back in and then we try something and
then something's like [\h__\h] up again
and they're like okay i will leave the
room again and every time now this is
the thing this is the reason why i
love henry so much
every time i left the room
henry was there in front of the door
right in front of the door henry was
there chilling and waiting for me and he
let me pet him all the time he really
liked the the suit there there were some
nubs and knobs on the on the suit
he liked being pet by those
you got the hair all over it though
because it was a black suit
i had his had henry's hair everywhere
stood out quite a lot
that's why henry was in a credit yeah
exactly that's why i put in there
because he was always there like as a
mental support
yeah when i had to go out of the room
and wait until they were done i was not
allowed in the room so
the bubble was mostly like
in the room where ammo was like away
from the whole dancing area
yeah but
they were kind of um annoying sometimes
not to me but like i'mma kicked them out
sometimes because they were like running
around
and
in the dancing area mickey and mickey
mickey
not wellington wellington was hiding all
the time
sometimes she had to kick the doggos out
to yeah into the hallway so sometimes it
would be henry mickey and bubba
that would greet me after i would leave
the room but most of them was henry so
yeah
henry i love you thank you so much
for spending your time with me
thank you
yeah
you tried to help
oh no
they were um
i mean the pets overall they're just
eventually
sorry but the pets all around you know
they raise the mood a little bit with
their cute antics
hmm like ami might be used to them but
the rest of us
i would say you know they had a
a subconscious effect on us
yeah
just for being cute and
running
around even just sitting
pets are the best they are they are
they left the mood yeah
so thank you
[Music]
thank you for the red superchatto
please don't worry about scaffold scuff
there was no scuff no that that was
definitely scuff let's be honest yeah
this was a wonderful concert and
everybody loved it now i just want to
cheer you from the live crowd at 3d live
and i hope i wouldn't need to break a
lot to do this but i will if i need to
no i think
that those restrictions have been
lifted pretty much everywhere by now
yeah
so
next time we have a
proper in-person concert like the dokomi
one it was no problem there either
people were
shouting
with their cheers yeah
so next time silverado if you get a
chance let it all out let it all out
yeah cheerful kiwawa
hell yeah
i would be very happy if you would do so
thank you so much and see you there
right
there somewhere oh the rainbow
at kiwa's concert
oh any good place to visit in austria
because there is the house facebook and
hashtag well that's already great places
i don't know how much time you have but
i guess obviously i guess you should go
to the capitol
i feel like the capital of vienna is
kind of like a big version
of south book
and pretty similar i think like in
architecture and
and
you know
things they offer
well besides that i don't know i really
i'm so sorry i'm so useless like i don't
even know much about my own country
yeah
but it really depends on how much time
you have
if you're like for a whole week then i
guess yeah free series is
maybe good good
good thing to check out
uh thanks again thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday i love the
concert you did amazing before you i
didn't comment much or interact with
anyone online but your outgoing
personality drew me and so many others
in
you have built a grand community and
every chicken here will attest to that
much love
yeah i hear that a lot and that's really
really really nice to hear thank you
landscape i'm glad you found
a place where you feel comfortable to
like share your love and interest and
your excitement
coming out of the shadows
where you were lurking
it's nice thank you so much
[Music]
thank you so much landscaping
i hope you will stay in kfp for a long
long long long time aka forever
has to go
once again in tears for the great
performance
thank you
thank you so much
don't cry
[Music]
i mean it's okay to cry i guess but
don't cry
brian king thank you for the pinky as
well
happy birthday attention comments on
your first 3d live concert wanted to
send you super chat already after third
fest but you disabled it
we're probably only for one day or so
how dare you lol you are always the hard
work and we all know it's so be
confident in yourself that's good that
you're into
[Music]
thank
you yeah thank you soon thank you soon i
ah i did my best so
i'm glad you enjoyed it so much and i'm
glad the hard-working
thing came through
i'll continue
working hard doing my best even though
there's
tough days and tough moments where i
also i also lose my
my
my confidence in my
motivation
every now and then but i get up so fast
oh man
oh man i don't know how i do it i really
don't know how i do it oh my god i swear
when i think about
all the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
that i endured so far
i do wonder how the [\h__\h] i'm still
standing
but yeah
yeah until the end
over my dead body
i will not give up apparently over my
dead body
which you know as a phoenix is kind of
difficult
[Laughter]
friend thank you duke from distance
thanks for the pinky this has been
amazing tinto i'm so happy we got to see
you really flex your incredible skills
on the stage i hope you get to see more
dancing and maybe a true 3dw sometime in
the future
i hope so too yeah
uh
i mean we've been planning for the 3dw
for such a long time
uh
like
really a long time
i already like
made a whole
whole like run-down run through last
year
a long time ago
yeah
everything's like you know
ready whenever we go to
is ready ready to happen
once we are able to go to japan
at some point so we gotta be patient do
you i hope you're patient person
because there will be necessary and some
more waiting
[Music]
ah yeah yeah me too i'll wait with you
jason thanks for watching chad happy
birthday kiana i love you my
there we go perfect just like in the
script
thank you so much
for the lovely words and the support
keep on wishing
this is seriously so amazing i'm crying
this is definitely the best birthday
concert ever okay
i love every second so much you and
everyone who worked on this did such an
incredible job i'm extremely proud of
you kiara always believe in you
thank you unknown
such a sweet heart thank you
you said the best birthday concert ever
but unknown i think you're quite the
oshi type of person
i wonder what other birthday concerts
you've even seen besides my own
tanoshi when you only have one oshi
instead of being a ddd
i'm i mean i could be wrong but from my
impression yeah you you don't really
care for anyone else
thank you
yeah
sounds based
that's pretty based
i mean
i think
i think you know there's a lot of great
people and whole life and also the whole
life too but it's your choice and i
respect it and i appreciate that too
yeah at least then i don't have to be so
worried that you'll leave me for someone
else
thank you
[Music]
andreas thank you and katie
long time ago i already wanted to see my
all she's shining on the stage today my
dream come true
oh
believe me i wanted to see it for a long
time too
and we're all in this together in the
end
you guys are
about as passionate about it as i am it
seems at least some of you
oh thank you thank you very much for
waiting it's finally happened but it's
just the start we need to do more stuff
with freddy asap
thank
[Music]
you are the cutest sweetest kindest
funniest most amazing most hardworking
most incredible
most wonderful person ever if i would
get an award for every one of those
traits i would need a whole shelf for it
i genuinely think that you really are
the absolute best love you and always
forever my aussie
yeah
so charming thank you so much
mom mom you get another kiss cause yeah
it was a 1.5 red
yeah
thank you so much
papa oh wait father also followed it up
with a pinky thank you for not giving it
up it was a particularly meaningful
concert
even without professional resources but
you all completed such an amazing job
love you love me thank you
yeah that's true
without professional resources just
amateurs yeah
quite impressive indeed huh although
at what point can you call someone a
professional because i think i don't
know at this point we can call him
professional he gets paid for what he
does now
i mean on a commission base but still
is that it's not professional
but still still i wanna you know proudly
say that we did this with amateurs
so let's just say
let's just say we're all amateurs yeah
yeah yeah
but definitely conor has the skills of a
pro um
thank you fava dragonfire thank you for
the rest of the chat thank you thank you
absolutely amazing classic you're such
an amazing performer so happy you and
the girls could get this set up so
everyone can enjoy a wonderful phoenix
for me happy birthday thank you
yeah i'm really happy too it was you
know a lot of work and kind of like
my vaga mama
but
it was also a good way of you know
finally getting us all together
yeah
and
big bonding experience
with amit especially
so thank you dragonspire for waiting and
supporting
hope you can enjoy more performances of
me sometime
so stay stay in kfp
[Music]
i really like this mario music man
it's not chill i don't get sick of it
[Music]
can't wait me neither but we'll have to
wait a little bit
[Music]
how come you pronounce it
amen
it's chill without being mind melting
yeah
a hat and lucille
wait are you
[Music]
okay i was gonna check if you're
referencing
oh i thought for some reason if it was a
uh arrested development reference
because there's a lucille there but i
was like did they name a bad lucille
there for some reason i don't remember
that
okay the walking dead
[Music]
i prefer to lucell from arrested
development
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i was wrong
tanjo i was not prepared at all when i
was assaulted by your beautiful
movements and cute voice and die thank
you forever
don't die
no
please don't sue me for assaulting you
please uh
please
have mercy who knew have mercy
thank you
bye
for the
thank you for the hard work extension
and also to amen canada i'm dead thank
you forever oh oh another one
there's a pattern
you are welcome thank you for watching
it i'm glad there is an audience if i
have an audience it will make no sense
yeah
my korean rose
hope you can check out the cafe by the
you want my other korean bros i wonder
you're here in the chat do you think you
can check it out
and miniature prince john what about you
can you go to the cafe
who's planning on going
[Music]
what about you
drowsy kid what about you what's you i
want one in tokyo
we will boss
i already have a plan with friend noise
production
[Music]
oh
i'm glad you guys um i know not all of
you use twitter doesn't seem so popular
in korea but i don't i only you know
i i don't know how else to see you what
you guys are up to
in korea so please make a twitter
account and then share your experience
with me okay
okay all the music stopped no the switch
turned itself off
i think
ah goddammit
what was that soundtrack do you guys
want know what it's called
oh super
mario bros you sound track
switch music stops
oh my god
but what about
we can listen to this one too
[Music]
i know it's too loud
pub
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
[Music]
oh
it definitely sounds like
[Music]
it stream has taken so many turns and
loss
[Music]
[\h__\h] eh no bug here
[\h__\h]
[Music]
back
nice
[Music]
are you here to catch some chickens
they're all here now they're all here
they don't expect you right now go
attack them now chocolates
[Music]
are eating chicken tonight
come on not just half a meter away from
me the moment i move she's going to run
away so i have to do this smart
do i want to pick her up
[Music]
don't blow me
does anyone have a tissue for hakutsu
he needs a tissue somebody give him a
tissue hair tissue remote
[Music]
is this a pigeon
of course we have tissues i would hope
so
[Music]
ah that one there we go that's something
it's already using it nice hot glue good
for you
thank you for your tears i'll take them
i'll collect them
and then
treasure them
i know it's down too soon
i'm totally not crying happy birthday
kiana you are the burning sun that
brightens every morning when you hit
that go like button
every morning yeah cause probably it's
usually morning time for you
i'm so happy i've witnessed everything
you have accomplished potential goal
kiara thank you
you does that mean that you get up early
for my streams or maybe for work but
then also watch my streams
thank you i'm glad to be a part of your
morning routine
hell yeah
thank you so much for watching my
streams
thank you soon and for following my
journey for so long
thank you
[Music]
see aliens thank you for the right to be
chad
the fruity concert was everything i
could have hoped for it's really
emotional for me oh
you did an exceptional job and thank you
and also your gentleman and kano do so
much for making this possible i was it
was really wonderful hoping for more
eventually
i hope so too thank you so much sick
aliens for for watching and enjoying it
i'm glad it was so special to you
i really tried hard to make it special
make it high quality thank you for
enjoying it
[Music]
thank you
star cruiser
thank you for the red super chat black
book shooter thank you thank you you're
the best happy birthday why is there no
emoji at the end
probably press the wrong one but thank
you blackbox sugar
i waited so long to perform that i'm
waiting for the right moment
and there it was
[Music]
yeah thank you i'm glad you liked it
thank you so much ian here's a kiss for
you
[Music]
was amazing don't mind the scuff it was
really super awesome exquisite it's been
such a journey to watch you and finally
seeing you dance so beautifully and
pretty was a dream come true for me too
happy birthday and keep being you love
you
[Music]
oh get out of here
should i bug you
get out of here
anyway sorry um thank you thank you
thank you love you too after you're out
there thank you so much for the support
i'm glad you were able to
see over the scuff and just see the
beautiful parts thank you for being so
great
generous thank you
[Music]
and concert this good shouldn't be free
that was amazing happy birthday
channel whole life yeah
thank you good copy paste there buddy
well yeah i guess so i was pretty you
know high quality yeah you know it's a
birthday stream can't be
can't be uh
you can't charge money for that but uh
you could buy merchandise ah
how about that go get that merchandise
yeah if you want of course i'm no
pressure not gonna
i'm gonna you know force you or anything
[Music]
ch that's what you get no
i never said that
it says it's channel i wouldn't say that
what the [\h__\h] i would never say
something like that
[Music]
no
whatever in my case it definitely
doesn't stand for chicken and stands for
channel
cannot hear the bug bug yeah
bug bug
[Music]
this this [\h__\h] doesn't work at all but
i'm gonna use it anyway
fruit candy
it's what i got from the pharmacy but it
works i feel like less good than the one
i got from the supermarket
[Music]
hey thank you for the red super chat
thank you to everyone who made this
great event i couldn't find a better
word to describe this
thank you yeah from me too big big big
big big fans speak ups to everyone who
was involved
[Music]
on my special day
special day
yeah thank you so much i'm glad you
enjoyed it i'm glad you were there oh
man wait that also means that you you
you were awake for a long time as well
oh man
uh
3 am huh
i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry also by the way for the
member stream this week we're doing it
at a late time but next not next week
then the week after
um i'm planning it to be early so that
next time the member stream can be more
accessible for sea
fans okay
[Music]
gonna try to
keep on switching
the time slots for the member streams
[Music]
happy birthday thank you for supporting
us with this amazing 4d concert now
thank you for being there
i need you to be there thank you for
being part of it
thanks for watching i wonder what your
favorite song was
and i hope you will be there again next
time please continue supporting me right
now thank you
[Music]
only fire chicken
would you change your name
[Music]
you know i was really excited about the
reaction from the korean fans now with
the cafe
i wonder i wonder i wonder how happy you
guys are in korea
my fans in korea are being treated
really well
you know we'll gladly do this all over
the world but in the end you know the
system
this is because
aniplus
any plus in korea wanted to do this with
us
so it's thanks to them thanks to them
that we are able to do it
[Music]
even before doing a themed cafe in japan
you know japan would have been like a
bit more you know
logical right
[Music]
but i'm so happy we can do it in korea
a good timing too
good timing
[Music]
foreign
can you buy me some merch while you're
there
there's so much though what the [\h__\h] man
even if i oh god
i bought all of it holy [\h__\h]
my suitcase would be filled with all of
it
i wonder if they can send us some
if i get them for free
i don't want everything i just take a
few things a phone stand
and the charger the
the separate charger
would be nice and maybe the parker
and i want all the food at least if it's
not spicy
and uh
[Music]
i love the most is the phone stand and
the battery pack
the other one everything's most of it
[Music]
get me some almond cake oh the
cheesecake you could you could you know
make those cakes yourself at home and
just act as if you're there
if you really want to go but you can't
[Music]
i should read a little bit faster i've
been going so slow to enter your singing
and dancing are amazing always loving
this concert happy birthday thank you
thank you
i tried my best i worked really hard for
it thank you i'm glad i finally get so
much praise for my singing my dancing i
mean for the third fest as well but that
was just one song and i feel like this
time i could you know
show off that i can do way more than
just one song you know
well thank you cosmere fact optimus
prime
dominic
happy birthday the last year was full of
events
and uh this pretty life really shows how
far you have come overcoming challenges
or vibing along you always try to make
it if you smile and so this gives me try
to make you smile thank you
i love kfp so much
every single one of you
so glad i had you guys
because yeah
[Music]
yeah since i've joined her life and also
before her i've had many many many
struggles
[Music]
but
we overcome them together
[Music]
thank you
it's really ending i think this stream
at this point is really ending
but it still keeps on going a bit with
super chats
thank you so much cotton glad you liked
it thank you for coming at the late late
late night time slot just for me
thank you
[Music]
no
no okay okay it doesn't look like it
unless it's really far away
and thank you dominick thank you
for cathy coffee too thank you for the
red super chat my first red super chat
just for you my lady my queen
takanashika you forgot one title empress
it should be my lady my empress my queen
actually in the queen one is not so
official i don't really use that that
often lady and empress is more accurate
well i'll take it i'll take it thank you
very much
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that's all right it's all right i
got it under control [\h__\h] baptism
eight thanks for the awareness of the
chat happy birthday
the content was amazing all the hard
work you and the others went through was
worth it in the end black rock shooter
for the ending what a great choice thank
you denzel thank you yeah
i was really nervous i hooked him up i
couldn't watch it
because of the time and then me even
delaying it i know that you know he had
actually something to do
originally right after
um
it was a time pressure i just really
really wanted to see it i wanted him to
see it live i'm glad it worked out yeah
thank you matching a glad you also were
able to see it live and makes it more
special
thank you so much yeah
wow please continue supporting kiwawa
and her endeavors
thanks for being part of kfb thank you
[Music]
oh there's a couple of red ones coming
up dear lord vadaya and douglas jones
thank you for watching i've always had
my attention's ability to work towards
the things she wants to do things might
not work out always but without her hard
work and dedication we wouldn't have
been able to make so many wonderful
memories in the past two years
[Music]
thank you
so flattering come on
so sweet thank you so much i'm glad i
can
you know make so many amazing memories
of you guys together
yeah
play so many games together you know
even even just playing games
[Music]
even that is special
yeah
doesn't even have to be no special
events like
birthday or anniversary or whatever even
just normal streams are all very special
at least to me
thank you guys
if i just want to give you a short name
what should i choose bedaya
[Music]
what is your nickname
where do you go boy
are you here
[Music]
foreign
want to jackson thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday kiara the
concert was freaking amazing i'm so
happy that you finally get to show up
your dance skills to everyone the future
looks right for you and everyone else i
can't wait to see what you do next
thank you although you say dance skills
oh man people
know i'll say i'm so good at dancing i
just wanna one more time say it's really
just choreographies okay
if i need to dance somewhere on a random
dance floor so
i would embarrass myself so
yeah
i'm not that cool
bales would probably be good at
freestyle random dancing probably
from what i heard
gotta have a dance off with fails
no she's gonna destroy me oh no
but i don't wanna dance with the veils
sometime and pretty like a proper choreo
if she gets pretty someday
i want to invite her
on my stage to dance with me
[Music]
i feel like if anyone
in her live english
if anyone can live up to my dancing it
will be bales yeah
she would probably be able to pick up
the choreo
pretty easily too i don't know i really
don't i didn't really talk much with her
about that kind of stuff but i've heard
i've heard things
[Music]
you're dancing ladylike and pop up was
so good but that that wasn't really like
i mean i came up with it but it was not
like random suddenly
freestyle you know what i mean like
i planned that one out a little bit like
i beforehand
i was like okay i'm gonna do this move
during the chorus i'm gonna do this move
during the bridge and all that
no
so it's not completely freestyle
because i wanted it to have like a
pattern yeah
and not just be random
awkward moves
after one another
[Music]
happy birthday for tomorrow
happy birthday
yeah
you're lucky i saw that
thank you walter jackson once again
[Music]
thank you for the recipe happy birthday
thank you
i appreciate it thank you soon for the
generous donation
[Music]
thank you thank you for the rest of the
chat
so glad you can show your full power to
the world again all the hard work was
totally worth it you are the shining
star the hottest i do
thank you keep on fighting we'll always
support you thank you thank you
i hope in the future my
my concerts can reach even more people
make waves
let people know wow why is top i don't
do let's go
[Music]
that was incredible i'm sharing and
laughing and crying such a powerful
amazing performance thank you i loved it
so much oh
thank you
[Music]
very very very sweet i like your
reactions very passionate
these chickens are so passionate oh man
thank you thank you thank you
f
[Music]
six free
v
i i i
[Music]
this was an amazing concert happy
birthday bravo oh thank you thank you a
four no it's
it's free
[Music]
thank you for the roses oh beautiful
roses i'm gonna take them and put them
put them in my bathtub
take a nice rose petal bath like the one
day with routine
[Music]
yeah
one more
not for now okay
now thank you i'm getting tired oh my
god
[Music]
it's coming i think it's coming things
thank you for all your great efforts in
staging this amazing pretty concert i
really appreciate how you and all those
girls presented such an exquisite stream
yeah i was so touched i couldn't stop
crying once again happy birthday
attention
no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
thank you so much for your sweet words
thank you
hope to see you again in my streams
[Music]
more often hopefully
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much
foreign
[Music]
she wants the belly rubs guys she wants
the belly rub so bad
jokers don't run away if you want belly
hunts
[Music]
all right
you'll have to wait until after the
stream then
no another call says
yeah you're amazing my oh she's so cute
with two kids i'm so proud of you i can
only imagine how much work this took you
spoilers hearty forever buzz
big you love you too
thank you so much
yeah i think you can do more than
imagining because i told you so many
stories about it
thank you so much i'm i'm glad you liked
it so much thank you thank you thank you
we put so much work and
love and sweat
into it partially even tears on my side
so
yeah
take all of that
[Music]
take it in take it in
and enjoy
yeah thank you so much
we're too generous but i appreciate it
thank you
[Music]
maybe a different one
or buy this one
ah there's more box
where's howdy version
[Music]
box box
wow
[Music]
let's keep going and growing can't wait
for what you have to show us
what else you have to show us
indeed indeed
i am curious to see as well
what kind of stuff
i can make happen in the future wanna
make more different kinds of concerts
yeah
different kinds of
productions
let's see what we can do together okay
shall we
promise
your boy stephen adam sanchez
[Music]
i always have to miss some of your
pretty birthday concert happy birthday
i'll go jump into the commercial deep
fryer to show my apologies
oh good that i have this bath with me
just kidding it's already been a while i
forgive you if you watch the vod and i'm
sure you did because you feel so so
sorry for it
i can see
it in that case and
that's this one
no more oversleeping next time
no more
[Music]
yeah we watch the dough
with the knife
thank you
thank you thank you venue you made it to
the very last [\h__\h] second
even though there was a delay
which means if there was no delay you
would have woken up way after it
actually ended
mommy
okay you do deserve a little bit of a
spanking for that
we'll do that behind the scenes
and like
even though time may be irrelevant to an
immortal phoenix like you every moment
with you is precious to us could be
employees no it's the same for me
here's many more years of kfb with our
very own attention thank you
just because i'm immortal
that doesn't mean that
i don't you know see every moment
there's a special one with you guys
every day i want to make the most out of
every day
i mean i still could make more out of it
but you know i do have some
some tendencies of being
of having a lack of
motivation sometimes too and not only
that you know
also don't want to overwork
genma
i can't do
everything that i want but um i'm trying
my best to
keep up and deliver good stuff thank you
eric for being there and making it all
possible thank you
spice waterfall thank you
[Music]
for the reservation it was so good
thank you
i will take you
up on that word i will believe you all
right
you say it's good all right must be the
truth
thank you
[Music]
great i'm glad you are able to make this
all work thank you yeah what an amazing
pretty content
i'm really glad it worked out in the end
yeah there were some times where i was
like oh [\h__\h] i went all the way to
america it looks like everything is
going wrong
i can't make it happen
i'll come back with nothing
really
some moments of doubt but thankfully
ellen have been
really frustrating
[Music]
thank you happy birthday
even when you're nerfed you're performed
greatly and i can't wait to see more
also those hips damn imagine he kept
picking his hips at full power
you know there's a nice waist to hip
ratio
from the frontal view
as i said the side view
leaves some things to be desired
i told jenna
and gemma
says she's gonna ask what we can do
about it
but i don't know
i don't know
i saw the petition by the way i saw the
petition there's a petition guys
signage uh
i already showed it to genma
even one of even one of our staff
probably as a joke but maybe partially
seriously signed it
one of the managers could not not
generally maybe she signed it too in
secret
um
yeah it was taken offline excuse me why
why was it deleted
[Music]
why
i need that
to put pressure on them who took it down
community guy excuse me it was an
important matter
it's not a joke it's real
okay do it again
do it
[Music]
i again it
maybe a different host can
will allow it
[Music]
i mean because actually a good way to
show my my audience's opinion you know
and if there's a big enough audience
saying my ass is too flat then maybe
they'll think about changing it
maybe they'll see how serious it is
[Music]
permission to riot no no no no no no
riot you know
just do it you know peacefully
and if then they don't comply then we
can talk about rioting
yeah i mean especially in certain
positions and certain angles it really
does look
off
[Music]
i'm counting on you
friends from thank you
[Music]
absolutely amazing concert you rocked it
also finally black or [\h__\h] i remember
you mentioning wanting to sing it ages
ago i did
i did i wanted to take it for my debut i
couldn't and i wanted to sing it for
i don't know anniversary and birthday
last year i couldn't
and finally this year oh my god it was a
bad time but yo i'm the daughter i'm the
daughter of this man hey yo
[Music]
thank you but at least you know waiting
so long for it made it more special and
emotional
yeah and unexpected for hookah papa as
well probably
yeah thank you manuel i'm glad you like
it i'm glad you know the song because
it's pretty old song i'm sure that
there's a lot of zoomers in here who
didn't know the song
you don't know why so special
even you know back then
it was a legendary vocaloid song
really well known back then
even still now i would say but what do i
know
do i see a chunkers a stranger
no you can't run
you can't run i've got you i got you
hi baby
oh your paws are so so
wow
[Music]
it's like mommy when are you stopping i
can't stop i need to read super chat's
chunky wonky
i need some resume
i'm sorry
[Music]
oh my god
sad sad
ah
my back
he's so cute are you gonna be my leg
warmer no
[Music]
i'm getting so close let's go devil
jeans jacket thanks for the pinky thank
you
no words with it but thank you
your love has been transmitted
iron iro iron d duncan daniel's going to
show him crows and jim tracy duncan
blackburn
i'm getting excited now that i can see
the end close
closer and closer
[Music]
no
i wanted to play underwater music but
it's not so exciting let me know give me
give me a different one
[Music]
did you hear that
ah
that's not the ultimate one but i like
it i like the sound
thank you
[Music]
peach and yoshi i'm
already loving this
[Music]
yeah
oh yeah oh my god nintendo makes such
good music
[Music]
[Applause]
he's on the cat tree
he's on the small cat tree
you can chill here chunky monkey
yeah
oh yes behind the monitor is fine too
[Music]
stronger likes to play with the bed
hello move
move myself
my question says what an amazing time
god bless you girls actually turn up oh
never stop racing for new heights kiana
yes i will become taller and taller no
matter what kelly says i will reach for
those new heights i will be the tallest
i will become a mountain that
the others have
i wish i could give you a hug when you
tear it up and be like good chicken good
chicken it's all okay it's okay mommy
loves you
become chiarazilla hell yeah
man yeah
yes my thomas
oh you have to excuse me travertine i
didn't expect that from you
[Music]
[Laughter]
i did expect that from you
from you i did
not from trevor
saying the same thing on the two
different kinds of
people your father wouldn't see it huh
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
manager today's birthday 3d concert was
amazing happy birthday manager on aha
take me
take you to where where are we going
[Music]
horn's at a different kind of take me
oh dear
thank you so much
okay
[Music]
thank you for the right super chat
here's a case
[Music]
thank you for watching
you for staying
to watch
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you so much
for giving us such a wonderful concert
here we can tell how much work put in to
make it happen and it was fantastic i
really loved seeing the cory of the
heart challenge and female knight and
then sea parts were so much fun oh thank
you
[Music]
your favorite night
and heart challenger both very fun
although heart challenger was a tough
one to learn
yeah i don't
i don't um
and i did not envy the girls back then
when only you know my backup dancers
they took me were able to dance in
i was like oh i would totally dance with
you guys but oh no i can't be freddie in
this concert but now now i have to do it
myself
that was a tough one
very energetic very
a lot of different moves and even during
the choreo
there's some parts where you would think
oh that would repeat itself but it
doesn't bamboozle
that kind of stuff
but it's a good one a good one a cute
one
the footwork was godly thank you
rob duncan cream hollow thank you so
let's keep playing thanks for the pinky
absolutely perfect i love this entire
concert there were so many fun moments i
had a big smile on my face the entire
time you're truly not only an idol but a
bourne star
i can't believe i managed to hold it
together you were too amazing
thank you thank you did you fall apart
afterwards on yo did someone collect his
bones and his wings and his feathers
put them back together like a puzzle
thank you thank you thank you
i'm glad you enjoyed it
yeah
glad it made you happy and smiled
and excited
hope you had a good time thank you so
much for the support
[Music]
extension
it's like i'm running a marathon
i say that the finishing line people are
pouring the water bottles over me the
paper cups are everywhere on the ground
[Music]
for the pink super chat
in
[Music]
thank you for staying up thank you thank
you thank you thank you means so much to
me i know it was so late i'm so sorry
maybe next time it will be at a better
time next time i have a big concert i'm
gonna try to
you know do it at a better time slot for
other people okay
[Music]
thank you
and and maybe you can come to the cafe
with collabo cafe and with any plus
[Music]
this was phenomenal and gorgeous and
more than everything i hoped for
thank you the caps lock
makes it look so passionate
thank you so much i wish i could do it
like weekly you know
concerts like that
but we gotta keep it special if we do it
too often it's not special anymore right
so tiny delta you will have to be
patient and wait
it will be worth the wait i promise
i'll do even better next time
wow
captain meow thank
[Music]
you gave us all a dream and you made it
come true thank you you were amazing
i'll always be your fans
[Music]
thank you
really happy
that you liked it
thank
[Music]
now put on some goddamn cloves
is that the first time i read that joke
did i do that before
[Music]
happy birthday i'm proud of you thank
you for the concert i love that you are
my aussie i love that too
i like that you said
i love you you are my oshi but you said
i love that you are my ocean that's
i love that too
that's a great thing
thank you i love that i'm your ocean
hopefully that never changes other lines
look at this bat and remember it because
it will come to you at night
yeah all right got it all right
[Music]
your moves are so good that it's truly a
joy to get to finally see you perform
them in full can't wait to see them
again thank you for the wonderful
constitution everyone that worked on it
i want to move my body more more more
more more pretty no but but for now this
one hour concert a little bit more than
an hour must suffice
i think it's you guys got quite a bit of
content i have so many
gifts tips that i can use on twitter now
too
so many dancing gift chips
[Music]
we're almost there
almost almost
[Music]
it's been it's the best concert ever
thank you for your hard work to make it
viva la chiano thank you
thank you for your support see us
bullying i could not put so much hard
work and effort into it without you guys
thank you for being there
nine times
foreign
[Music]
that was amazing seeing you on stage you
were made for it you were stunning
gorgeous i'm so proud to be careful
right now
i hope i
i hope i never disappoint you guys
i'm glad when you can say you're proud
of me i don't ever want to disappoint
you
[Music]
i've not been too many concerts
especially ago but this was the best and
emotional one i've ever experienced
wow
thank you so much for all the hard work
you put in i wish i could support you
even more you're already doing enough
love you forever attention never stop
being you love you too
thank you i'll continue i'll try i'll
try
it's hard to change anyway even if i
want to change it's really hard to like
change something when you're like an
established person
where your everything is just so put in
place
well then at least you like me this way
so not too much to worry about right
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
cypher
[Music]
now get back to work conquered
bad
words cannot describe this moment you
were in your element for all of us to
see the shining beautiful idol
you absolutely owned that stage and i'm
so thankful that i was there to witness
it all your hard work really paid off
wish you a very happy birthday thank you
oh i think for you it was also kind of
pretty late
but you're used to it aren't ya
always here for me no matter what time
it is thank you patsy i really really
appreciate it
thanks for being there during my streams
[Music]
and the important moments especially
thank you i'm glad you liked it i gave
it everything i had i poured my heart
out and my sweat
oh my
every single drop of
something that resembles water inside of
me
was let out
okay maybe not every single
thank you
[Music]
amazing concert your dance is fire you
were so damn hot i couldn't look away
from
jesus you finally singing vrs on the
stage brought me to tear spanky and
happy birthday best girl
thank you from your best grill is my
action
i'm sure those were really manly tears
thank you so much
i'm glad you liked it i'm glad it looks
so special and emotional
i think
i think it's a good thing because it
means that you guys you know everybody
who cried and even though once i didn't
cry of course somebody some people just
don't cry as easily as others but it
means that you have a very special
feeling
feeling of love for
[Music]
thank you
thank you so
the much
water cups
yeah i'm running i'm running and running
running and running running and running
running and running running
settling started engraving during
delegation fgh magic
[Music]
and everyone who helps and inspire
inspire you love you leave a lucky other
glory together
thank you
i love you jg thank you so much
i did my best
and bloody appreciated me
[Music]
uh thank you for everything you do and
being such a positive voice for so many
i hope you feel all in love with sending
you today always
yeah i feel it in the shape of pain in
my throat but
i also feel it in my heart
yeah doki doki doki
thank you
okay
someone always
[Music]
that would carry me like in scrubs when
aliens carried uh jd that would i love
that
that was such an amazing concept not
only do we get to see a dance and have
fun in 3d but also the sun choices the
games of guests they were all so good
sassaganma
thank you
[Music]
although
yeah i i liked the game choices and all
that too although the idol shiritori was
i guess kind of biased because i was
just the one deciding which words were i
don't like or not but i have to say then
she threw in so many words in there that
are not idol-like at all like how is
superman a dried fish
i don't like or girly
explain that to mean anything
that's right you have no explanation
[Music]
she just ruined random words and if it
was normal shitty toy
and she damn well understood the rules
she works in strange ways and she can
make everything cute but no no no no no
[Music]
you work so hard on everything you do
from music to streams to even the things
we don't see
and you truly care about your friends
and fans you're the greatest oh she a
chicken cook ass play
and i'm proud to call myself kmp
thank you so cute
so sweet
charming
i'm proud of you too
being such a good example of a chicken
yeah
thank you for all your love
it was a full rainbow oh my god where is
it local oh you mean
a reverse like
handstand
oh
do i gotta scroll up to see the rest of
it
[Music]
there it goes there it is
you know what can i read it quietly
i'm reading it right now
[Music]
hell yeah
myth strong cannoli strong
[Music]
what comes off the yellow
i can't find the rest other green
thank you
okay
i see the end oh my god
[Music]
it's on
my monitor without scrolling hallelujah
cyberpunk [\h__\h] game tucker thanks for
the pinky happy birthday i got thank you
for the unforgettable memories even
though that weren't so great
yeah they were great right game taco
thank you
thank you as well for being a part of
the memories
anderson the con dude thanks
thanks for the great super taco proud to
be part of caffeine thanks for all the
hard work you put i added the word
hearts to it apparently
freestyle into everything you do and
happy birthday thank you
thank you thank you very much
[Music]
someone i don't know oh my god another
one thanks for the pinky
super proud of you for making this
happen here's another year with the best
and my favorite feelings boss ladies
very correct
[Music]
not just a spark
but a great fire in us i'm proud to be
part of pvp thank you
i'm proud to have you happy to have you
you always help so much with like the
german stuff
dokumi which is obviously just a
different way to write dominic k
thank you
elstein
tv table try donkey koalas
[Music]
and everyone else that supported you
created something absolutely incredible
i can tell you that all the hard work
you put it really paid off you really
are an idol
i
am yes yes
thank you for supporting this i don't do
this idol's dream
thank you without you guys i couldn't do
it
it to be true
[Music]
oh yeah
it looks like it tried to make a
[Music]
rainbow but it's not right
did i miss
it's not it's not right but it's not
right it's okay it was okay
thank you
for the sweet messages though thank you
[Music]
please
is
looking for the top
at the very bottom
which means i don't have to look for the
bottom anymore
i look to the top
because i'm done so
but that one was a red super chat so let
me read it happy birthday well thanks
for the concert i'm amazed how you
didn't lose your smile for a single
second but captain energetic being an
energetic and cute girl everyone knows
you're such a strong girl your
expressions are so adorable for you way
more than a magic listening oh
where are you gonna write more
i think this is gonna be more than that
if there's ends there
listening
where's the wrest
[\h__\h] cliffhanger now i will look for
the top because
can't end like this
listening
i'm listening i'm listening where's the
rest
suspense it's killing me
[Music]
i'm honestly like how
how did i do this like last year i feel
like there were
like times like these more often
where i had to read this or even more
amounts of super chats how did i do it
oh how
feels like it takes so much more time
these days
[Music]
oh my god yeah the 12 hour super chat
how
[Music]
[Laughter]
how did i do it
[Music]
oh man i'm gonna die
oh i'm tired
[Music]
what time is my members tomorrow
what time is it tomorrow
[Music]
up all right buddy
it's probably gonna be late because i'm
gonna sleep a long time
and then before
streaming i need to record something
[Music]
for it you know stuff
don't ask many questions or i'll bring
out my
bet
aka bed where i'm gonna sleep tonight
if you ask any more questions i'm just
gonna hide under my blankie
because i'm scared of the real world
don't ask so many questions
you know what i can do now
oh
[Music]
i just saw something in my in my image
folder
[Music]
i kind of want to put it on
all right
perfect oh my god
[Music]
remember this thing from last or even
last last year
[Music]
it was a
really old one
myself my froggit but it doesn't even
you know i left you know these pieces
for my
for my feathers only when i look down
makes kind of sense but this way it
doesn't make sense i can fill it up
again because now i can i can fit it
perfectly on my head oh oh it moves with
me oh i can be a frog
yeah
quack quack
quack
[Music]
a little bit
the princess come out after the case who
knows try
[Music]
oh no
i'm transforming
oh
i'm becoming a princess
[Music]
oh princess transformation wow
oh what's happening to me
ah what's happening
oh my god
wow
that's the most princess like i can get
i think
surprise
[Music]
there's some some chibis coming up with
me wearing all the items that i was
wearing today
[Music]
i'll be playing tomorrow i'll be playing
games
or a game during
um
the member stream
city skyline see you there guys brain
empty
throat heart
but
heart so full
thank you arigato thanks
i love you guys
[Music]
do
what
i didn't say it
oh my god
and in german we say
[Music]
i was just hanging on twitter and then i
see it in the chat what
unbelievable
bye bye
[Music]