[Music]
hey everyone I'm
korei and I want to kill
you tonight Lads we
go let's
[Music]
party I'm
Mar you know what here's a little C free
style if you want to bite me get wrecked
kidding me I'm pretty good a grim Raper
what do you expect spout sounding cool I
would say so I'm inclined to agree this
is my line of work this what everyone
wants to see bird cute K them time to
redo the fight this is called being a
Pro Gamer I won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you off he's right
though die
hands weapons of mass
[Music]
destruction half HP in a dream boys it's
F me and my natural lessons I'm a
workaholic by Hobby I'm cooking I need
to teach you a lesson say Les howdy this
is the
Westy Sheriff's the best I'm going to
get a big jump emess anything to achieve
that B Dream let's go Kori heart
palpitations on the
stream just let it end just let it end
my friend plays the recorder better hey
your
friend hey guys two quick
question number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready go
that's a
Mori me the ball that's a Mor yeah
that's a check this
[Music]
out baby what I'm
talking hey everyone I'm CIO Mor and I
want to kill
you tonight Lads we
go let's
[Music]
party
I'm you know what here's a little calii
free style if you want to fight me get
wrecked you kidding me I'm pretty good
my girl Raper what do you expect this
about sounded cool I would say so I'm
inclined to agree this is my line of
work this what everyone wants to see
bird cute killed them time to redo the
fight this is called being a Pro Gamer I
won't die right try
aiming I want to cry you go he's right
though
[Music]
die in hands weapons of mass destruction
half HP in a dream boys this F me and my
natural essons I'm a workaholic by Hobby
I'm cooking I need to teach you a lesson
say l howdy this is the
W Sheriff's the best I'm going to get a
B jump EMP anything to achieve that
dream let's go korei heart palpitations
on stream
just let it end just let it end my
friend plays the recorder better hey
your
friend hey guys two quick
questions number one what the am I
looking
at number
two are you
ready
go that's a
Mor do me the ball that's a Mori yeah
that's AI check this
out yeah baby that's what I'm talking
about
[Music]
dang it f I had a really good intro I
was muted you would think I just mute
myself on my
goler hey everybody whoa thank you so
much for wonderful gifties sorry oh the
music's way too loud let me put
hey everybody HHH it's
amori I'm here for SC no they wait they
wait in the dark crevices in the corner
for me to fix my chat look chat has been
you guys have been great it's it's this
it's just YouTube with the chat it's
just it's not the same you guys are
going to have to deal with it going off
the rails I'm very sorry I hate to say
it but it's going to have to go off the
rails did you guys like that did you
guys like it's amori as many of you
guessed that was by
arand arand is the person who made the
fauna sweep
intro and so I asked Aran to make to
make a Mory specific
intro and I sent a bunch of clips and
then arand also chose some moments as
well so that's the new that's the new
intro sounded like his work yeah there's
a bit of like a JoJo Essence to it and
then if you listen really closely you
can hear Elite motifs with I think red
go-getters make them afraid it's pretty
cool did you ask him to make it sound
like Jojo no that was his idea he was
like hey I made it kind of sound jojoes
I was like
oh do do you think I don't want because
I do want that so big UPS to archan as
well I will link archon's Twitter in the
description in just a moment let me go
grab it so that you guys can go check
out archon's work AR also made fun of
sweep very very
important I'll put it right at the
top Intro
by and there you go also thank you so
much for the many super chats you guys
we will be reading all of these and last
year's at a following stream after the
premiere of my cover but we got to get
started cuz we have a lot of
guests that's right many people showed
up thank you for the happy four year
wishes can you guys believe it's been
four years I can't that's as long as
someone's in high school or college for
some people undergrad for example
so short time it feels like it was just
yesterday I feel like that's a common
thing to say though but I've prepared a
very special stage for all of us so
that's
exciting let's see it's just the
question is who do I sing with first now
I want to do a quick
disclaimer de beats okay here's the
thing so all of these had to be um
recorded by my guests in their own homes
therefore if the instrumental is bigger
than their voice or so on and so forth I
I feel like I balanced it out well
because I checked all of these
beforehand um I had to stop Midway
through ol's though cuz she was on some
crazy stuff I'd like to react to um I
guess naturally uh it was very strange
Oli is showing up um but um anyway
anyway anyway uh the volume may not be
perfect and that's just how this goes
when you ask people to pre-record stuff
um additionally with my own voice
whenever I use Reverb it kind of sounds
it sounds muffled because of the
compression in OBS uh and my friend's
audio so I'm not going to be using
Reverb for this
karaoke yep it's just going to make it
sound muffled so yeah um with that being
said that it's not over I usually say
with with that being said when it's
about to end but it's not about to end
get more Ganky music popping off in the
background okay this works tide it's
part of the fun no worries it's just fun
karaoke after all right but I do want to
celebrate this momentous four years
together since we can't do a 3D live I
wanted it to be as maximum fun as
possible so I have I brought my friends
I was about to say I have friends can
you believe
that sometimes I can't hi hello hello oh
man I'm a little nervous but once I get
into it I'm sure it'll be fine hey you
know who we should start off with you
know who we should start off with the
strongest Idol what do you guys
think run to the dark into the dark you
and
me okay sure if that's what you want to
do
yes
together oh I'm the one that starts this
one okay
K here we
[Music]
go here we
go D out
everybody together you want I'm shy
though I feel nervous all of a sudden
here we go
[Music]
for
for hey hey we are
together that's a really long
[Music]
time
for I'm believeing
in you are escaping her hi hi she does
look really
cute I can't look at her I can't
[Music]
look
for fore
[Music]
hey and welcome GRS how goes it thanks
for
the you're welcome
thanks thanks really
fun fun
bye-bye bye-bye
H there she goes she ran into the night
we barely saw her oh yeah I guess we can
wow it makes a really loud noise when I
do that thank you so
much hi GS and
Gigi where
where I hope you guys are ready for lots
of
fun fourth year anniversary which is
perfect for Shinigami hey because Gigi
just came in would you guys like to see
something hi happy anniversary everybody
ready she here rock yeah I'm ready to
rock let's run it g here we go let's go
a beautiful
star a beautiful
[Music]
here we go
Happ
honey beautiful star
beautiful
star a beautiful
star beautiful
star fore
[Music]
Beau
star beautiful star
[Music]
Happy
Lucky baby
soet
[Music]
beautiful beautiful star m a beautiful
star m a beautiful star m i
[Laughter]
Beau thanks
Gigi there she goes that was G
mooding oh my lord it's so loud when the
windows gets angry at me that was
GG
sorry
well as you can hear I'm still a little
sick I'm still a little sick that's okay
I'm I'm better I'm getting better every
day though thank you so much for the
redirect GG Grims I hope you enjoyed
that I hope you guys
enjoyed love the gigg mor are you okay
um I was diagnosed for bronchitis about
well I've had it for about a week and a
half but they diagnosed that I that I
had it about four days ago talk about
terrible timing am I right especially
with anniversary and then myths
anniversary is coming up and it's just
it's a busy
time but will make it through like we
always do I've got my tea with me get
well soon oh bi's
here get well soon bibu and I should
sing then if bib's here let's sing with
bib how does that sound we're going to
do bi song okie dokie H let's see oh
this is this is going to be a fun one
here we go um I'm I don't know how much
confidence I have but oh okay bet you
didn't expect that
Vio did I surprise you here we
goie happy annivers AR thank you I
thought you going to say happy birthday
first K together K booots
monster okay
hurt
hey hey please if you could just St in
your St
[Music]
let's
go repti
[Music]
come on four years
y I've got a little one-year-old on my
lap door right
[Music]
now for
hey hey ouch again with the again with
the
slaps please stop
[Music]
stop do you calm a child on your left
how do you calm a child how do you calm
stop stop it
oh my God she was wigging
[Music]
out you good you need a hospital okay
bye bye babe there she go that was B
singing Kai boots with
me K
boots
KSU never watched a be a vtuber before
but yay bunny girls I'm kind of a bunny
girl right now I'm wearing shorts but
thank you babo for singing with me that
was
fun even with all the penl hitting I can
forgive that I can forgive you for that
boo that was
fun that was very fun press nine on her
holog gr why is that a
reason we forgive her because she's cute
no
oh okay bio doesn't want me to press
that button so I guess I'm oh Wiggles is
it
the where she's like swaying her
hips where she do the wiggle I love that
I saw that in a short it was cute okay B
thank you for singing with me next time
please don't hit me in the head with
your pen light though it made it a
little hard to focus on the song and it
messed up that's okay you're cute so I
forgive you is there a way to delete
this with no promises she's
diabolical that's a diabolical girl
right there I wonder what we should sing
next um let's see maybe before I forget
it cuz I learned this one I learned a
brand new song and this one's with a JP
Senpai are you guys ready I'll do my
best Happ
aniversary s with you let's he some nice
H let's singing with me
W yeah I'll do my
best let's
go let's go pink not a St I'm sorry I
mess I keep messing with
ah sorry I'm sorry
[Music]
hey for
yeah take it
[Music]
away
we
for let's go
[Music]
happy
yay thank you very much
[Music]
byebye not
Senai
jpai it's like JP members just feel like
everyone's a senpai it's hard to
explain that was fun that was a fun song
to sing I don't usually sing songs like
that but it was fun to challenge myself
yay bye
byi that was fun you know it's really
good to challenge yourself oh music's
loud sorry it's good to challenge
yourself sometimes though I
[Music]
think I want to keep challenging myself
with different songs I've never sang
before you know that would make me very
happy let's see I wonder what we should
do next
let me take a little Gander it what I
have Senpai in speaking Japanese true
enough oh here's a good one I've been
waiting for this all right I've been
waiting for this I've been waiting for
all of them but here we go and the audio
might be a bit low for this one but just
bear with us
okay hi Kellie hi happy
anniversary you too what this is a
coincidence that it is also my
anniversary seems kind of strange don't
you think that's strange yeah thank you
for inviting me to your karaoke party
you're welcome uh my audio is kind of
scuffed right now but uh and have no
Reverb but I wanted to join in anyways
me too me too I have no re too and I
want to S Violet with you cuz you know
cie you're known a lot for your rap but
I really like your singing too i' be
really happy if you sing Violet with me
together
I have no Reverb but let's go me too
that's okay I wonder if there's a better
r i could do let's see for
Violet this one seems
calm start us off Ena here we
[Music]
go
fore
[Music]
for
speee
[Music]
foree
foree fore
[Music]
oh just kidding here we go
yay thanks for singing with me Callie
you're so sced no it was fun you did
great yay happy anniversary to us bye
bye thank you wonderful rest of the
morning afternoon and evening take care
byebye byebye there she
go wow what an iconic
song I love that song what the heck
[Music]
it's only fitting it's only fitting that
we included a special
VJ a sweet memory associated with with
Violet don't you think I think so I
wonder what we ought sing next what do
you guys think let's keep let's keep the
energy going shall
we was even more iconic last week
true that it was H I wonder what we
should say oh okay how about a bit of a
calmer song well they're both calm songs
CU I'm just trying
to get my voice back on track hold on
one
moment good news is I have plenty of hot
drinks with
me yes yes hot
drinks are you guys having fun I hope
you guys are having a good time I had to
make sure I had to make sure that
[Music]
that we had the best time possible even
without 3D so y of course heck yeah lots
of fun y it's only going to continue
whoa
really you guys have been going crazy
with the suas today thank you so much
for that I'm excited to read all of your
messages
today let's see the next one okay I know
what we're going to sing
next this is going to be good
um here we go I'll do my
best take it away later
[Music]
oh I feel a certain way right now it's
kind of
strange maybe a beautiful lady will
serenade me to you to me yes my love to
you to
me yes my love to you to
me me to
you oh my god to me
stay with me crony forever
[Music]
stay with
Mee my
[Music]
with Xbox Mike oh no
it's an a0 Mike you
[Music]
know I miss her
it's on
purpose stay with
me
[Music]
my Stay With
Me
[Music]
for I feel like I could stay with crony
forever what do you think crony
[Applause]
[Music]
stay with
meiss my with me
[Music]
with Stay With Me
here she goes wow that felt like a dream
that was like a a dream that happened to
me what the
heck I felt like that that wasn't even
real a beautiful blue woman appeared to
me in my dream
is that really is that supposed to H can
that
happen anyway crunchy crunchy no no no
she sounded beautiful she sounded like
she came to me in a time machine you see
uh let's see who shall I sing with next
um how about somebody crazy a crazy
person
even maybe the
craziest happy anniversary
bye thank you it
is so high and I am here today to be
singing with you wow she has crazy
exited I even have my pen lights up
they're pink which is your color and
we'll be singing green sheen on them
which isn't pink but we don't think
about it pink for the name of a song is
a little too girly yeah I'm in cool okay
I'm going to oh you have Windows issues
too I'm going to start the song now
let's do it here we go let's go it's
time for red I always wanted to sing
this song with you all right here we go
I'm ready nervous you'll be fine don't
worry
ready two one tonight the Moon is ring
Crimson but Rose got so I live forever
instead now I can't get rid of all of
these thorns in my head bring on theing
I guess I live inside your memory take
it away another beautiful day with our
loveliest Miss olive inside of your
breast fre I'm never released I'd rather
be kicked in the dungeon cuz I'm That
Kind of Beast I don't want to be a part
because you're always my Feast youring a
love to be mounted press the moment by
do add
it huh I love
you Clos in every side of
me girlfriend now and wife today
what dread sorrow can't turn
away can't
[Music]
bre and when run I'll
ask you imagine when my up the sun's
falling
down
again Ollie every day want to be more
every day I want to be more the biggest
just call her mommy please take me now
baby I'm ready what it's ins spite of it
I I I say curious comes after it yet I
resist she beautiful ey bow I want her
boobs on my face now Rising soon regard
the moon reflected in the Crimson s
tonight huh kids tomorrow day absolutely
not what dread sorrow can't turn
away can't turn back
your tomb behold your breath yes who's
owning the throne so come alive now once
again so I can chase you down we are 5
minutes away from the end has come
continue spashing forward I must or else
[Music]
just I didn't nail that part and I might
sucked part so excuse me we have to work
together you'll be fine there's a all us
never ending ouring way deep down
because Escape how F has a funny way
shaking the we am I
PE can't turn
back I'll dance
your and when this r like
a everything you imagine when my tongue
up the sun's falling
down
again so come alive now once again so I
can chase you down we 5 seconds away
from the end from here now it's only
just
me rather just fade away no wait no I
forgot to change the lyrics on that part
I want just fade away I love you very
much I would just fade away when you're
with me especially when it's only me and
you you know what would happen when
there's only me and you inside a room
locked together all sweaty all we would
we would sing
karaoke we would sing
karaoke um
anyway when is the official recording
coming
out
never she completely stun locked me I I
didn't even sing the song right because
she stun locked me wow all's literally
me you get your
butt back in line I need to cleanse my
get
somehow words bleach in my ears no
listen
listen I I allow her to do
that better than the official I'll kill
you man that's what I do cheny got me
what do you expect so when's the Blu-ray
dropping we're singing a different song
now um if you don't
mind I do love when my friends get
creative though that's wonderful all
right let's sing something kind of funky
shall
we actually I'm going to take off my
jacket for this next one
mhm and I'm going to change my
hair hold on one
sec that's not quite what I want that
looks a little uncanny there we go
all right
um who would like to join actually you
know what it'll fit more if we do
this yes yes all right get in here
friend oh hi kaori hi M happy
anniversary thank you let's sing this
rock and rock song Together rock and
roll with M hey Cowboy we kind of match
to be honest look at us we're totally in
a band together don't you guys
think it's me yeah it's Misa not but
that's fine it doesn't matter it doesn't
matter let's run it here we
[Music]
go foree
Godless hey hey hey come on leave it
leave the bass guitar to
me leave the B guitar see look I'm I'm
ping it right
now this actually goes on for a while
[Music]
look anyway back to singing oh my
gosh oh that's that's it's
wrong this is what I get for goofing off
[Music]
You Lonely
Heart
[Music]
fore fore
get down here we go this is not a guitar
by the way this is a bass
[Music]
I'm on a stool
now I'm on a stool she's moving on the
track peace out peace out thank you
m
bye-bye
bye-bye There She Goes wow thanks Mo I
appreciate that wow people who say
bye-bye sound Super Evil by the way I
don't know if you guys noticed that but
they sound Super Evil let's
see anyway back to my F this is my
favorite I like the black streaks we
could have matched pretty well but I
feel like we both looked like we were in
a band together that was
cool the reason that I asked for the
combination of like bunny Suites thing
and the ears and kind of shorter hair
combo is because I wanted to do a Hardy
thing sorry I wonder what we ought sing
next oh man so many people are here
thank you so much for coming I just
wanted to say I really appreciate you
guys being here for my fourth
anniversary I know we're not doing any
3D or anything but that's fine as long
as we're together I'm happy you know
let's see um o here's a good one this is
one that I usually always
do you may notice a theme these are
songs that I know I feel like they
picked songs that I know anyway this is
pretty intense now this particular
person that I'm singing this song with
cannot be contained and additionally
used so many cool effects I didn't want
to to take that away so her head shape
might be a little strange it might be a
bit small but she had so many good ideas
here we
go get in the robot Shinji okay I'm not
Shinji
[Music]
that's right get away from the hospital
bed but hospitals help you don't you
know that shei I feel like you know
[Music]
that foree
3 2 1 Let's
[Music]
Jam here we go that's a break let's go
sh do you know the the version that goes
got to testify breaking dimenstions
wasn't enough break some uh things I
shouldn't mention on your stream I guess
ouch why do you do this to me
shiori happy anniversary by the
way thanks I love you or is it more like
death adversary I don't really know
these are not the lyrics okay I'll shut
up listen three 2 1 Let's Jam got to
testify come up in the spoty
the day I die going to touch the sky
we're going to touch the sky baby girl
got to testify come up in the spot
looking extra fly from the day I die
we're going to touch the sky oh my
[Music]
gosh
for Here We
[Music]
Go
for I got you
sh I miss my
[Music]
sing woo happy anniversary get out of
the room about
Shinji not
Shinji and someone just rang the door
but I'm going to lose my mind it's an
important package I'll be right back
sorry e
wow
um that's embarrassing oh my
gosh there are a lot of people here
thank
you sorry I just got back um it wasn't a
package no the um the cleaners couldn't
come in I said oh this is going to be
embarrassing I'm singing right now they
said oh we could
hear I didn't even think I was singing
that loud
oh oh well you didn't yell at them did
you no no no no no no I I let of it side
like I usually do
let me do a big cough that you won't
hear fighting through bronchitis just to
sing with you guys but it's so fun I
can't help Shori shiori is so creative
how is she so dang creative I'm not
Shinji though I don't know where she got
that um all right how about another
person who can't be contained by the
confines of please sing behind me shall
we
oh hey oh my gosh oh do you see what I
mean happy birthday Callie happy
birthday happy
[Applause]
birthday
[Music]
for Here We Go
happy birthday C happy
[Music]
birthday oh I forgot to like it's
okay now they're saying happy
birthday it's not my
[Music]
birthday where sorry
here we go
[Music]
head Bing moment what do she do she
can't no one can control her she's just
out of control
[Music]
that's that's use
that oh my Lord what is she doing in
front of me
[Music]
okay I guess that works anyway this is
shiny Smiley
story singing the Holo anthem together
with
[Music]
you happy birthday kie thanks for
inviting me I hope you have the best
birthday I just realized that I haven't
blinked in minutes H happy birthday
Callie love you I think she's joking
I'll I'll I'll give you anything I'll
give you my entire world it's not my
birthday so happy birthday cie you
always been um such a big inspiration
for me boy love
you wait goodbye pose where's my goodbye
pose uh where is it I can't tell you
where you're hiding it I can't leave
without my goodbye pose uh my birthday
is
44 sorry that was a really good cough
you guys didn't get to hear it
though that was special that was really
special
Zeta thank you so much for the special
performance it's very nice we go a we
got to rush through them happy birthday
narissa I swear to God
narissa I swear to
God I swear bo boo RIS is
here oh oh hey she
says narissa ravencroft I'm going to put
you on the spot right
now beloved father Miss Mory KY thank
you so much for having me today and
happy
anniversary you've been here for a long
time now so how you feeling pretty good
old very old your head is just so
beautiful well sorry I want to thank you
so much for having me today special day
here to sing with you what I personally
think in my in my opinion is one of your
most Banger songs of many bangers All
You release or bangers but this one is
really special to me cuz when it first
came out H it made me cry a lot
a sometimes but I really love you so
thank you for letting me sing this
special song with you today together and
as as we should together together both
cute so happy anniversary end of a life
Mor X Nissa version let's go here we go
our mics are
touching cool take it
away
we right
through those nights I'll never find my
way back to you inside this Labyrinth of
Lights there was Madness in the meaning
never laugh lless we were screaming at
the top of our lungs to the num City
[Music]
never I'll fly
no
[Music]
proof those Heights I'll never find
another chance to say thanks for serving
my life I was hopeless it was stinging
running roadless we were singing at the
top of far lungs to the N said he never
died was the RO of it all couldn't say
used to jump in Then Fall rugged and
cliched would trug get off without
complain not a sound are us in trying to
find friends cuz in the end no body
sticks around it's when you shoved
yourself into a crowded place that you
turned around and found yourself in love
and out of space Kill The Reckless
nights no strings laughing out of own
dreams just what the hell was so funny
up the stumble used to Falling Great
Heights concrete jungle singing of right
we mix the on we in troubl rhy in our
discontent and though it's history I
can't forget the time that we spend
convinced that this could mean another
end exist between real and pretend a
twisted out to fiction where I miss my
chance did not Ascend disappearing into
the M of never Happ is the me that I can
never befriend I let it go fade in Fade
Out this crazy dream without a direction
floating
aimlessly there's
nothing back there for me Brea but it
won't stop the rain froming
run right
through those
I'll never find my way back to you
inside there was Madness in the meaning
never we were screaming at the top of
our lungs to City
never was there ever aide Chasing
Fireflies between the S and high eyes
has left a trail behind to find a wasted
time of our lies silencing her
overworked and underpaid thinks in
office is a coffin until office where
you laid yet a th assist an optimist who
ought to be afraid saw the nothing wrong
in right and songs behind the lonely
shade is the world it's s a place
without the words that you convey when
the ladder fell and shattered every bar
that we have played does it matter in
the end the sound of M and decade and
your friends tired of fantasy you're
wishing they had stay you don't get to
say I miss you you watch your Heroes
Fade Into the rear view mirror of the
villain you portrayed stop the petty
party listen you don't get to be
dismayed you don't get to be emotional
feel blessed you got it made these the
best of years of life because you chose
to make a trade recollect the days you
hoped and you prayed for this what is
that a Miss f in Fade Out this Hy dream
without a direction roing
aimlessly there's nothing left back
there for me pretend it's the end of a
made
story no
proof those Heights I'll never find
another chance to say thanks for saving
my life if I was hopeless it was
stinging driving roadless we were
singing at the top of our lungs to the
numbness this city
never say goodbye to
[Music]
the the know it's time
the up now to the life let me
[Music]
I'll keep waiting for
you you're beautiful huh you're amazing
the things you do blow my mind every
single
day I think I might be in love with you
I'm sorry with me on
stream Rissa I'll be normal since it's
the end no no need for it being nor it's
you can be whatever you want with
me waking up now to my life let meam to
the next flight
drowning I got old now the cr's gone is
it over it
over song is
over have a happy
anniversary byebye bye Nissa
peace there she goes there she blows
both of your oce she's singing end of a
life has Maj your whole day I'm so glad
we got to sing that together Nissa is a
gem I love hanging out with her and I'm
glad that we got to sing together at
long last I was waiting for that a thank
you
narissa we got to we got to move right
along but that was
great that was
great now we have another friend here
thank you so
much oh you want to sing this song with
me Cece yeah that's Karma yeah get
down chat made I'm a superstar stand but
rock with it yeah like 247 I'm a hot
miss you love get less boring oh my God
R swing my
shots Like a Villain villain bring home
the
jackpot just a not stop the fool around
okay got a good is Peak right now I can
to your house yeah don't get confused we
are not the
same no way no
way good ver
[Music]
evil just leave it
to loose my lips loose my lips yeah Ah
that's
karma my lips I'm about to say some
get it yeah that's
Karma sorry I'm just
[Music]
sck while running think
clever whatever can I hit it right
now hey y'all checking this out
yeah funky with it yeah yeah hi CeCe
thanks for coming to celebrate
[Music]
yeah good versus evil but I'm
oneck in the middle that's not any
fun my lip myps yeah that's
Karma
whoops myps
[Music]
while you think
you're whatever
[Music]
by thank you
C byebye CCE thanks for coming she's a
gem no bi's a gem but but still CCE is a
gem to me we got to keep this train
rolling so let's do the next hold on a
sec oh whoopsy doodle this that was was
really fun I love singing P who that is
that Elizabeth fro blood flame hi is
that what I sound like to you I'm so
excited to be singing this song with you
happy anniversary thank you you are
amazing no you and yeah I'm so excited
we look nice together don't you think
let's go I do love the color red
[Music]
hi hi I see in is I see in the chat
together
[Music]
the bo bo do hey I'll choke
you
[Music]
for's go
together let's go
[Music]
I'm going to play guitar right next
space she remembered it's my
anniversary I I just feel so blessed to
be even singing with you right now no
Honor's all mine Honor's all mine what
are you talking about you're a legend
here we
[Music]
go
for Fore
[Music]
yay I can't thank you enough Mor I can't
thank you enough hey hey I was I was
wondering uh would you be uh uh the K to
my
in can I be the
moku Just J joking yes yes of course
I'll be I'll be your goodby
[Laughter]
no one can quite do it like
Liz thank you for singing with me I had
fun will you bear my children it might
be a little difficult to do Liz but I
appreciate the thought thank you for
thank you for
asking thank you so much for singing
with me I had a blast Big Ups to
you well that was fun I always wanted to
sing with Liz finally we got a chance to
I hope we get more chances to in the
future as well I bet we will though I
bet we will I got a good feeling about
this oh um dang uh 40 minutes until uh
the premiere of my brand new cover yay
more let's do it okay it's a pinky
promise um how about a
song that I suck
at Miss
K yeah let's
go wel wel oh my God I can't focus now
for
[Music]
yum Yumm
here we go take it f let's go she's so
[Music]
cute okay okay
spot
[Music]
yum yum yum
3 2 1 Let's
[Music]
Jam my turn
yummy yumy
yumy bye fauna oh she did a strange hand
sign at me and
left that's what I call fun
sweep I get too excited when I sing the
mogu part it makes me really excited to
sing
anyway a little too
excited okay let's see
we've had a lot of ens and IDs what if
we did another JP how does that sound
another JP
guest a JP guest Yes Yes sounds good to
me let's
go together
let's go let's
[Music]
go leave the B to
me hey hey hey hey hey hey he hey I get
to sing with God
[Music]
today
fore hey good fore
[Applause]
hey hey come on hi hi he he he he he he
he he leave it to
[Music]
me fore
oh
[Music]
yeah we're swaying
together
[Music]
hey
foree fore
[Music]
love love
youo thank
you
bye hold
on that was fun I'm working through the
cough I'm working through the busted
voice thank you so much Matsui samai
[Music]
that was amazing I'm glad you guys liked
it I do worry we've been rushing a
little bit I'm very sorry if we've been
rushing too much rushing rushing russan
anyway thank you for the PCH PCH PCH we
still have more to go don't you worry
but I wanted to give a quick thank you
so much to everybody who's been so
supportive for my
anniversary you know these kinds of
things only happen once a year right I I
guess there's birthday too but I'm
really happy that there are so many
friends here to celebrate um such an
important year for me right four years
Four score and four years ago Mory
joined whole alive English in fact in
fact the five of us didn't just join
Holo live English well we did we did but
we were we were the beginning isn't that
crazy me and my friends me and my four
gen mates 4 years ago started off on a
journey that we didn't know where we
were going to go we didn't know where we
were headed or what it would be
like the
Genesis I don't know if I can say that
we started H and there there are people
that that facilitated it it's not like
not like the five of us got together and
said yo we're going to start H life
English or anything like that but you
know the beginning the beginning was
crazy we didn't know anything or what we
were doing oh and look at how much it's
grown you guys see how much it's grown
how many new friends we've made along
the
way I can hardly believe it sometimes to
be honest but I'm really happy you're
Legends now I hope no matter what
happens people can still look fondly
back on the things that we all did
together you
know i' say you guys did pretty good I'd
like to Hope right
sorry bad cough is bad always will I'm
so proud of you all thank you so much
that's all we can hope for right I'm
inclined I'm inclined to
agree thank you never forget the te days
that was pretty
silly that's pretty
silly you could say I either had no idea
what I was doing or I knew exactly what
I was doing but I'm not going to I'm not
going to be that person I'm not going to
be that person it's up to your
interpretation right maybe I really
didn't know what I was doing was
probably the more likely one right
anyway myth forever did you guys check
out the voice
drama have you checked it that was fun
we all got to work on it together that's
something we don't get to do together
often you know sit around and make
something cool like
that yeah I hope hope you guys enjoy not
yet but I will we listen to it not yet
excited though I did take a peek it was
super good it's fun you know one of the
things about voice dramas and especially
the voice packs and stuff like that is
that I try really hard to to tow the
line between acting and being natural
right because I don't want to sound like
somebody who's trying to sound like a a
a dubber does that make any sense like
somebody who's dubbing anime people have
gotten really good at making English
dubs sound natural in recent years but I
don't want to go in there and be like
are you ready to climb the the rock wall
together all right grab my hand you know
like I don't want it to be too different
from how I talk to you
guys during my my normal streams the
door
top see if you can see sniper sniper
it's not sniper it's swier
[Music]
that was a gross cough sniper sniper no
sniping what an image anyway we're going
to sing another song Sorry Sorry for the
little
tangent sniper is sniper in the adult
[Music]
version sniper no camping oh let's see
what shall we sing next I'm looking
through my little
list I sang all of these and those are
so fun how about I sing a song with two
[Music]
people how does that sound a two person
it becomes a three person song what do
we think about that
H here we go
let's sing together okay please listen
to buly you guys like that song a lot
thank you both of you we'll do our best
oh sorry you let's
go my
dogs me and my
dogs here we go she's dressed up and
Diamond D I love her after
Ked lashes Soul Of Ashes what more can I
[Music]
say around what I found is a treasure
indeed a friend to can bent to my ever
need I'll use and abuse you and never
for bad until suddenly finally you take
my head tangle you tighten the Ys that
I've spun and I'll do it again to get
what I want pretend that I'm harmless
I'm actually alarm is something Charming
to anyone the fact you can actually make
one the one that
you say s word different night
[Music]
when
oh you know I want you to care that I
want you to stay so I swear I won't
blame you if you turn away at the end of
the day I will smile and give into this
burning and vile original s is the
realization I you when honest and prise
say it
again so much love on the person that
hurts you like I do cuz can't hide can
you and if I'm the world of you surely
you never stood even a chance at all
didn't you it's me after
all dogs with bars rap gods dogs
you
call hello
[Music]
don't be
afraid I give
you keep it to yourself hello the hungry
world come to give you help
once again I'll treat you nice twice
before you fall and smile while you do
love the me that's killing
you let's go
[Music]
you thank you
guys thank you you B see you later
fuok and thank you for watching too fuok
oh
whoopsies whoopsies thank you for
watching
Fu they're here
some people in chat were like whoa they
can rap yeah those dogs can do anything
if they really want to do it they can do
that there's a reason why their Rivals
are so scared of them
right thank you Liz Liz is still
listening thank you so much for
listening
Liz dogs can rap their their rap is
powerful they are not rap gods they are
rap dogs hardcore rap dogs I really
respect
them thank you so much for joining
in be scared Kevin be scared I'm coming
for
you watch
out in
shambles that's even stronger sometimes
a rap dog over a rap god yeah 100% I
agree with you I'm inclined to agree
let's see these last three are a little
difficult that's why I held them off to
the last I've been listening from the
start Senpai always cheering you on
beautiful
me could I
be
beautiful thank
you thank you so much thank you thank
you I'm so happy the r in Erv stands for
Riz no it stands for Rose close though
very close
H close oh yeah I think that um there
may be some there may be some vacuum
about to go on so let's just chat a
little bit shall we we got a couple more
songs close LOL close enough
right sorry if you hear vacuum
noises I don't want it to ruin anyone's
performance so I just wait a minute but
20 minutes until my cover yay real quick
though I want to just give a quick thank
you to all of my guests who have stopped
by we still have a few more but all of
the ones that have stopped by not only
stopped by in the in the Stream but also
contributed their lovely vocals to my
show you call it Riz I call it the
truth okay I believe you I believe you
go off queen go off
Queen I know that that that Liz isn't a
a queen queen but I think she's a queen
you know in that way in the slang way
you know so I agree with you
guys amen amen thank you so much for the
many many supas by the way it's very
very kind of you guys and they're over
300 new members welcome new members
there are two wallpapers up for grabs go
get them make sure that you download
them okay oh like the stream for Cali oh
I would I would definitely recommend
doing that cuz for whatever reason
YouTube does not really notify people
about my streams anymore I get a lot of
messages like that from from fans saying
Why didn't YouTube notify me even though
I had notifications on I don't know
what's going on so if you if you like
this stream definitely let me know and
leave a comment about what you liked
okay fix your side
he oh well there are a lot of uh there
are a lot of how to say glitches these
days but it is what it
is I like the mor
part then add it YouTube needs to be
reaped
sometimes yeah but I'm willing to be
diplomatic because of YouTube you know I
get to do many things
so you don't get to watch often much
more when you do it special today's a
very special day especially so I'm glad
that if you chose a Mor stream to come
to you'd come to this one it's me
singing with my
friends so uh it's very important to me
I I loved when you said it's morning
time probably some Regional issues ah
who could say anyone who doesn't sing is
a traitor no no no no no anyone who
doesn't sing didn't have time to join in
already 20 guests is a lot of guests but
if you think about it it's good for my
throat because 20 guests means like 10
songs for me to sing that's a basic old
karaoke right thankfully they're helping
me out today even though my throat's
been in bad shape but I still got a lot
of recording to do today and I got super
chats but I'll try to be very careful
with my throat I have many many warm
things and if they get lukewarm I just
got to heat them up easy
easy oh man recording to yeah see there
was a there's a bunch of songs that I
had to record that were actually due 4
days ago was the deadline um but I said
to them listen I got the bronchitis
please my singing is going to be
terrible so there's saying they'll see
what they can do so I got to try and get
to work on something if I can
right yeah oh well drink tea it's the
best they've been pretty nice about it
I'm not going to lie
so definitely understanding folks it's
just you know schedules exist oh there
goes the vacuum hold
on it is a Thursday isn't
it go went up on a
Thursday feel better cie oh I'll try no
I want to hear the cough it's
gross but I can imagine some people
actually might like that in some kind of
weird strange way it's kind of
satisfying for me to hear because it
feels like my lungs are getting cleared
out but then for you guys to hear it's
just kind of nasty yucky yucky so I try
to mask it it happens a lot when I'm
laughing too though these
days no you don't want to that's yuck oh
still Wednesday for you guys though over
in the states huh in future land of of
Aya it is indeed the 12th which is the
day the day of days the day where it all
began four years
ago around this time too I think
huzzah the day of
days you just think it's normal so
people get better I appreciate that but
it is kind of yucky sounding
also maybe the the reason that I feel
that way about it is
because I guess I um I get I get kind of
squi out when I hear a a cough and like
I run away it like it makes me and it's
not the other person's fault it just
makes me cringe in a sense so I think
about how I feel and so that's why I
uh I I likewise try to censor them for
you guys cuz I know how 15 minutes
anyway Shall We Begin
the last three songs all right here we
go we'll do this one this one's kind of
fun this one's very fun actually here we
go oh I got to move back what's up I am
chaos the end of end it's the end of
Trapped in a cage of ice your best
friend
and's little sisis Bellos from Whole
Life English promise witness me winess
and witness Callie cuz it's her annivers
happy anniversary thank you so much for
inviting me to sing with you I am so
excited to sing this song I know you
like this song it has been living in my
head red fre since the moment that I
heard it I know you like it want to
say so good a such a
b everybody please listen to our
rendition of let's end the world let's
go
this is
L A
heame sick
game ba shake it I'm a walking disaster
and half with the last girl you say
St I go faster talking Slaughter and
laughter bo bo bang
a I think I want to blow up this going
I'm I'm such
a shut up no
hero up now this is what I'm
saying this what waiting for good lordis
Bo Welcome to The Killing Floor no to
run don't look at me like I'm D I swear
life ain't fair I don't care
and get the M yet
and
shitless and
cous
KES make youceful
lips they hate my guts or read my lips
don't take the bastick to the script
then play them like a fool when the
numbers dip they shut down
a round what's on your mind don't want
to die price is a little bit of ego but1
I sit in these robes Andis got hella new
club this is what waiting for good Lord
spard welcome to the K
floor hold this that means let me you we
can
make line
single the style get on some AR
like kill end wig out oh headbang
headbang or do this this is good
too are you
good are you okay hey
all
[Laughter]
right let's
[Music]
go and you something's get burn get on
some
like
and and
and night didn't get the memo yet didn't
get the memo yet and it's
night
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah BS hate those
anniversary she remembers this my
anniversary
see byebye oh she's gone rabbit and rat
Sing Sing Banger song by Giga Teddy
Lloyd thank you so much for singing with
meet B hios that's
fun now uh let's see let's do oh boy
this is one that I practiced but I still
feel like I'm terrible at but I love
this song so much it's another JP member
it is their original song so I'll do my
best are you ready ladies and Gentlemen
please welcome to the stage
takad I'm from congratulations Senai I
respect you a lot thank you I respect
you too so let's sing together we sing
my original
song Here We
[Music]
Go
for for
[Music]
Bring It On
here we
[Music]
take off he take
off nice job thank you you're
amazing you have great
Originals by
bye I love Tak we have one last song
speaking of
birds what's
[Music]
up hello it is
I you came in here too our four years
anniversary a long time god let's
go together wao wao amazing amazing so
I'm here to
party take in the
party are you ready to sing together cie
kind of It's A Hard song what song are
we singing answer vampire that's right
let's go that's so nostalgic for me okay
can you take the hype Arts I shall play
the music are you
ready it may a few please take the high
parts I'm so sick it's fine cuz this is
slow no watch this I'm going to kill it
here comes you'll see oh there it is oh
boy here we go
[Music]
help me Kiara hey hey hey hey hey hey a
little louder piece there we go hey hey
hey all right here we go it's up to you
ki do your
best
[Music]
for
for hey hey hey
hey that's
[Music]
get
for hold
[Music]
sweep hey hey
yay let's go talk duo in our new outfits
thank you KY for singing with me thank
you for singing with me
gu yes so once again congratulations on
our four years anniversary honestly C
years I am so glad that I have you by my
side I know that I can always rely on
having you I can always count on you I
can always know that you know you got my
back and you're also the most dedicated
and and and motivated person ever so
like I never have to worry about you
thank you so much I feel like you've
grown so much in these four years and
we've grown closer and you've grown as a
person and like I really I really am
happy with you know what you have done
for us for myth for as a generation as a
whole branch and I I love what you've
done with yourself I think you've really
like like a like a like a Shiny Pokemon
you have evolved into a shinier version
of yourself so keep on doing that okay
keep on doing what you're doing I'll
keep striving to be better let's have
fun together for a lot more time
together takon
strong
forever let's keep doing our thing bye
kiaha what a great one to end on thanks
for coming to my anniversary everybody
wow I feel very emotional from that I
need some time to process that well I
got to send you over to my brand new
cover now but thank you so much everyone
all of my guests everyone who came to
watch and cheer for us I'll catch you
guys on the flip side okay thank you
Kiara that was
awesome all right I'll see you guys soon
thank you so much for four years here's
to many
more okay bye
everyone
peace hey everyone I'm Kio bore
and I'll