mean a
song Take
myy I'm
my everybody's everybody's
here o we've got we've gathered the
whole crew the whole the whole
crew everyone's
here except wait are we dancing already
wait can we hear everybody is there a
mic check can we get a mic check in the
least might be a good
idea yeah no g g we can't I can't hear
GAA can you guys hear
G I can oh you can't hear G cuz oh
that's cuz oh right okay I see that
makes sense yeah um I don't know how
to you can't even though you watch your
Discord stream it's fine guys just
everybody in the chat go watch somebody
else's POV I'm sitting out the first
round so so so I can't hear gooda but
I'm haunting
her oh wait what if uh what if you watch
gura but also watch my Discord as well
does that workz I but will you get
double audio I'm not too sure yeah audio
or something all right don't worry about
it I'll figure it out you guys you know
you're going to get fired you know you
have to make a we can we can also use
Discord audio but I guess I don't know
when someone dies coming to kill
us
I but that's okay I'm going to figure it
out it's just something that we're going
to have to deal with I guess because you
know where the lights I know a lot of
people have been mentioning mods we
can't use those we
can't Mod's allow yeah it's not allowed
it's it's not allowed guys so we're
going to do what we can with what we
have that's what we've always done
that's what we'll keep doing
dance
it's not the same without
a well surely we can afford one soon
right uh well our we did just begin this
journey the quota is pretty small the
first
day PR F accessing terminal and your
favorite animal who's going to be our
nerd obviously describe your Ro in a
team operation thingy it's a lot of
button
I mons
moons mons
moons ex
experimentation it's so clicky I can you
like have the system so it'll like
us that's above my pay grade the auto we
we are orbiting the moon o which moon
moon there are
multiple ah oh we your moon experation
experimentation okay we just
experimentation let's go want to see my
moon just you just go you going to Moon
me I crank it
Captain Crank That ping the
captain K be
Captain am I the
captain that's right I selected as
Captain ah I see great I haven't been
selected I made the room big difference
but you know what that's fine ladies I
can leave the charge here I've played
Lethal company a few
times so the only one who hasn't played
the game yet lead the way you haven't
played yet uh is GA the only one who
didn't play yet oh ga I've consumed the
content but I've not played the game
okay yeah I knew no we just we just go
and take stuff scraps yeah main entrance
is Right dead ahead ladies just find a
ladder no no please no we
start to avoid the bees you have to spin
in a circle three times okay is that a
real thing or you just pulling my leg
watch three it's real look the chat says
it's real right guys hey Chad I know
what you're trying to do look it worked
for G it worked for her it work I'm
Invincible sounds like a lie I'm I'm
getting mixed reviews from the chat
right now main entrance you got to make
sure you over there
cently what do you mean
no it's at five it's like Five Nights at
Freddy's if you're on the ship and
you're looking at the cameras exactly
oh um we have nothing we have no
flashlights just find metal things and
get out of here and if we stay together
only metal things I found is
brave brave
bra very brave I found the key oh nice
one I feel so safe with Ena more
jumping ooh there's a deep door here you
can do it
gooda nice time
engine I got an engine nice one Ena nice
going to go up these stairs here's a
monstered I'm going to be a great asset
to the company locked there's a locked
door up here we could use your key oh y
great I can't hear you by the way nobody
can hear you me you're
alone no you need a key I
do oh okay we can open it let me let me
drop this is this it I was really
feeling alone upstairs right up here
upstairs oh yeah see what we can find
key all right there wouldn't be a
monster in here right why would they
locks in oh you got to right click go to
right click that's how you scan stuff
you can see stuff in the dark it'll show
you the value items okay I'm going to go
too Ena don't leave
me
Marco there's really nothing over there
um gu this is the exit W wo wo there
St is this the way out I don't know
where remember where we came from I
think this is it I feel it this place
pretty big for like a first area yeah I
I have huh wait where is more there's
steam here okay we're fine where's the
exit hi is that the exit found it nice
nice is the exit y I need this are
popping off it's only 12 yeah
12:30 yeah we're doing so good
already I wonder where Kiara is do you
think she's safe yeah I hear her who
footstep are those are those your
footsteps I want headphones anymore I
hear big
steppies okay that's all Bud time to go
time to go time to go time to go whose
big meaty footsteps are those I don't
know man but I I'm a coward I'm I left
I'm a desert big matey claw matey
claw I wonder if they're okay
uhoh bye you got to jump five times hero
that uh takes one for the team and gets
the job done anyway uhoh that'll be
me that'll be
me yeah nobody can hear you you're ghost
did you jump five times in a row that's
how you get away from this one two three
four see I told you sound a freaking
meme I don't
know great great great
great all right
don't die Mory don't
die you're speaking into the
void you yeah
Hello's dead ah how'd that
happen did you moners there were
footsteps and then death I mean I
definitely wasn't there you know I don't
know if you noticed but I'm a big old
deserter you guys only got one item I I
brought the Bott yeah we got three oh
nice yeah hold on I'm kind of hurt oh it
w really it's fine we're not going in
anymore are we are we are we are we are
we I mean unless you guys there wasn't
anything else someone should stay behind
regardless that is true it's 3:00 but is
stuck I mean I don't know if there was
anything else any other rooms yeah I
didn't see anything it was hard to see
um hold on there we go fixed yeah
Callie do you want to get the bees
Callie bees bees collect the bees fast
you asked me if I want to get them yeah
how do you get behive
behive do I punch the be they're worth a
lot I'm being ganged up on here hold on
a sec grab it and run there's a can you
spectate Callie so I can
watch thank you Callie
pressure's on huh God speed I can scan
maybe anyone know where it is on the way
there right yeah it's on the way or you
doofuses are going to tell me to go grab
the hive and not tell me where it
is to your right yeah my right I'll I'll
leave you I'm basically Zoro please you
have to help that way this way yeah I
see all right I think I oh there they
are
wait did you gra it I mean I don't
really know how hold on somebody need to
distract
them CL you guys want me to be bait hold
on get a your
timeout
no purpose going to die he's a don't go
after I didn't know they St you when
they killed
you I see her corpse
can you bring her a CO stack what kind
of bees are those what she's worth $5
hey yeah but her body is still close to
bees hey how' you
die all right I got e by
a with arms it was like Geodude but
flesh ah I see some Metroid [\h__\h] nice if
you die don't die to Too
Close you got finish the miss
I thinky guys I tried to bring but I
realized we don't the
be okay
she God the dogs why is it spooky why is
it spooky dides she not know that at
night time she's played this before this
is like that movie where that
[Music]
kid behind you behind you wait where the
kid dies baby death
there you go Kiara there we go one of
our bodies do I still have time to
bring got go got go how do I even get
this I'm going hear you tell me how do i
p the L P the L
the the the door closes on its own right
turn well the bees have to be
abandoned but it's
okay
I was already hit so probably
not just the body now
yeah
just well I'll take
that
iived Kara most paranoid makes a lot of
sense that was her end game excuse me at
least I survive 28 yeah thanks for
trying to go me into dying with the
bees oh we pretty much reach we just
need like one more metal scrap so let's
try and save up to get to this far away
moons
ladies honestly we can sell like the
clipboard and stuff apparently it's
worth something if you're desperate but
I think we can definitely be
over over the the the quota you know
become Employee of the Month who here is
anybody here part-timer is everybody
intern unpaid
intern right now how do I see intern get
paid no um your intern you want to do
some Amazon shopping for us find some
sales confir who's inter
turn please enjoy flight I don't know do
you think we need or
flashlights I don't know where we part
time Warrior yeah Mario some flashlight
no there's lots of stuff if you go to
the computer and type in shop yeah
flashlight would be good all right I got
this leave it to
me top stop one shovel confirm we have
to go grab
it store and then we'll do
flashlight you have like a little bit of
money oh I should do flashlight and then
a certain number okay store um let's see
home box we I don't think we can afford
anything else no how many flashlights
just one baby we're going to have to
single flashlight and a dream we can get
more later though and like a transporter
and stuff like that shall we go dude I
can pickle
all we go floating
Seed where we
going in March I believe we go to the
right Hazard March oh is H Fest time
already oh no time F too fast wait guys
it's a cliff watch out what what a c
yeah look for the bridge Cliff there
should be a bridge someone almost went
off the edge I saw that was pretty
funny don't jump into the wall know
you'll die for sure me neither me
neither I'll be right there to greet you
a
cliff all right check
it nice all right ladies collect f goes
good uh somebody needs to hold her hand
we need to put a leash on
her ice cream hi guys I immediately hear
footsteps oh my God the goods yeah I
heard I heard it yeah I heard it I yeah
oh well maybe maybe different ex maybe a
different enter entrance is better no I
mean the stuff we ordered is uh oh
didn't pick it up oh is it just us what
what we forgot about it yeah oh oops
that's my
bad just got a little excited
anyway safe I don't think we can go in
there oh oh gura grabbed it maybe what a
legend but
um whoa whoa whoa you good maybe there's
a different entrance we can use yeah
yeah let's go somewhere else uh um where
did you find where are the
others you guys forgot to grab
those I know someone's going to have to
be B I thought you were for real now
since Mor was bait last time I recommend
Ena be bait this
time she come
out attack he you want to go in there G
oh yeah attack where do you have the
things from did you pick it up from the
deliver oh just go in the present
there's a present in the front room are
you
sure
okay I got a shovel can you beat him I I
have one piece of metal at least we well
you can bring that back for now it's got
to be made and it might have to be me oh
she's not coming
out for me last time
man is it like aul hit it hit it okay
okay pressure
pressure blushy blushy
blushy we shall play with
it we shall go
allive we should go all in different
directions and make it
choose
take where are
there's nothing here hold
on so we got to go I don't can get
through the door if you guys just close
the door can we trap him in here he's
close the door he can't open the door
door me there's nothing the other way
there's no door no time for baby cowards
yeah we can lead him into the other room
all right I'll have him follow me and
you guys look for
scrap he's
gone who's got the flashlight I do no
we're
not looks
like
again H
it kill
him oh no yeah oh he dead you got it
there's a casualty
on uhoh I think g hit her by accident
all right girl you did what you had to
do I will take up her flashlight in
herstead give me
that maybe we should take her body I did
I got it yeah feels more noble that way
hey that was sick
though that was pretty
cool
o you can stay
here hey I found a
place
what the you
ghetto I found a there's a place over
here did Ena live ena's got the
flashlight I thought I flashlight
flashlight yeah yeah hello okay there's
another
flashlight where is oh here we go I got
a tea
kettle let's see
um who was it that got the metal sheet
was that
you
all anyway tea kettle's out front oh
it's starting to get um it's close to
Five
Guys uhoh
um it's a big area I think good is big
kind of far
away
oh holy what are the odds that's amazing
it's meant to be wait does it do
anything like does it fake swim she
found a fish nice this is really
heavy it's made of
TST po po po hi hi yo let's
go got a tea kettle and then I guess we
should carry kar's body
but this seems like a different door
it's probably the same door anyway let's
get out of here before the uh the dogs
come and the Forest Giant they're not
very
friendly oh what is the Forest Giant oh
he eats
you yeah he's like a big treeman and
he's got like um an orifice in his face
that looks kind of
weird and then he puts you into it and
you hear a munchy
noise yeah it's kind of gross where
where is it I don't know it it should be
around here Jase
Dead's dead dead
we lost I know
actually that's all right hey look we
found the
ship nice one bone Bros right
again is GL for
punishment oh she went back body let's
go wait this is OHA is that ena's body
is this ena's body well it's not mine I
thought this was you I was car the whole
time you had killed en well I was bitten
by the monster but I quickly run away
and survived somehow nice my a button's
a little stuck again every time I go to
the ship it ends up that way anyway I
got the
kettle nice we were great assets I
really did do the uh switch of Maru then
sorry you rest in peace look I found a
fish Eternal BN fish that's a heavy boy
oh plastic ni has still that value
we're killing it exit
time yeah let's go everyone keep your
hands and feet on the ride please don't
be body no no no no wait I really think
wait
oh she yeah that was a close call better
be inside when the door
closes close call on Big Fish I
sustained the most injuries I think Ena
sustained the most injures cuz she died
yeah she's lazy didn't injuries I can't
cuz you're dead you can't be anything sh
looking
monster bit me I'm a
parttime now yeah part what does that me
me being part-timer it just means you
take the most risks in the next
Expedition let's
see I
C all right uh let's see access terminal
all
right yeah uh let's
see vow let's go to
vow vow yeah
wow like vow with the V or vow with the
yeah with the v b what other bow can you
read this did it sound you said bow bow
bow bow bow bow bow
don't think anybody said
that let's go sorry I'm just trying to
entertain myself cuz I know I'm going to
be interned forever and I'm just
entertained why understandable forever
intern you know why you intern forever
who's turning off the lights you think
you're being funny it's it's my second
shift I've seen many many other other
same employees of the same group um they
they got promoted and
haard level C it's all right always oh
we got to go it's all right you can
prove yourself now yeah surely this is
the day all right um didn't order
anything I'm a little Hoy any new stuff
was anything order do we buy stuff no
not this time no
okay I'm pretty sure this one is either
straightforward to the
right kind of forget I see a
bird bir oh I don't think you'll let's
try going to the right oh there's the
bridge it is running off into the
unknown uhoh running off into the
unknown she'll find her way do not do
not see Marco Polo Marco Polo again I
had this dat chip before scre we're
getting L now H all right well girl can
use either Bridge maybe I bet she'll
find it that'll be we found the nice oh
I'm not a
dummy there never seen this
before you jumped is there fall damage
in this game um not really kind of chat
says there is but I haven't seen
any oh that's a face door hey guys I
like is it's pretty dark over here ooh
bottles nice found some bottles you guys
had a flash
but it's gone now oh I got one I found
the key dropped it I think so it must be
in the last door that needs to be opened
I have the key
cool o this is pretty
big no no
g g to grab the
core God
g g
no stop I'm
lost where we go you can't fix that
right once it's activated no the
monsters are coming now Kar they're
coming to get
us if we stay I don't have anything if
we stay to the right if we just stay to
the right oh wait that's everybody if we
stay to the right we'll eventually find
our way out of the
maze oh
nice I I opened the door oh sorry sorry
I did that fish it's fine
fish nice fine I don't sense the
radiation is it really happening um no
it just means that there are monsters
coming oh okay all right nothing the
finish we'll find our way out
together stay to the right we have to
find our way out eventually okay not
this way so that means we just go okay
this way any more loot maybe it' be good
to get yeah fish this one's locked too I
think you guys are fine you guys already
made the quot go
backing you behind
me
that okay where you go he I'm still
here left monsters to the right as long
as you don't see the glowing
eyes
oh it's just a loot bug it's fine that
one is not not so dangerous where the
[\h__\h] is the exit I don't know K I don't
know you have the flashlight it's and
there's no more
battery now you going have to
climb
Kara Kara we're lost in the dark
together help me we're so lost at least
I'm leading the charge into the
darkness
oh new creature dat what does that mean
does that mean I don't want to meet that
creature I spooked him run it's locked
no you're going to have to go around I
think well if she screams like that
maybe she's going to get the monster to
her [\h__\h] why are we always I don't know
oh it's just a loot
bug why are we always going to the same
place as I
think that was nothing
you just kill
me Kar I don't know why I'm the one
leading the way I need you to take the
charge Teno our brave Teno now leads the
way okay this way she was J that thing
like she was jumping on a bed oh
[Applause]
no God I hope they leave without us
bro where even are
we going in
circles maybe if I just sit in a corner
they'll leave without
me oh I wonder why they're still
collecting oh they're lost they're lost
inside oh no Kiara's dead yeah that was
pretty
Brave sir Robin ran away bravely ran
away
sir did she make it out I made
it but I don't know about the
others what time is it
um I'm going back to the ship I'll wait
for them until the last moment oh she's
crossing the
bridge time to leave
time to
leave be a great asset if I get to the
ship mean you don't then we don't lose
all our stuff yeah
she's it's not worth it yeah
uhoh now I'm lost hold on that was went
straight to
that then I think it's up
here definitely not the one that you
want Left
Alive there's ship there's a
ship there's a
ship I'm here oh you guys are alive
let's
go I thought
you
[Music]
hey
nice gone the generator she bravely
walked before me and um and took a bug
to the face and we evaded the Bracken I
can't believe that happened there we
shouldn't be alive after that but okay
let's go well made it nice hul you guys
good work we were pretty useless but I
think I like to think we lured the
monsters away from you guys maybe we
were we were pretty shallow in the uh
when it happened I broke a
bridge yeah that happens too with my
butt yeah but too big all there is to it
butt too
massive I thought the tungsten fish was
massive stop jumping it turns out I'm
the tungsten thing please stop jumping
just not jump oh hold on sorry it's just
my jump button is stuck there we go the
door
open no no no no
no did it open oh we're leaving
okaybye oh the bees almost came I mean I
feel like if you want to be safe before
we leave the atmosphere yeah you choke
and die you can die like that necessary
I don't know it's like space for science
probably I can see that wait why am I
the laziest
employe it's all right you're doing I
went back to intern I went back to
intern because of that yeah if you die
that
happens oh we got we got to go hand be
to the company all right I'll take us
there o what do I bring 100%
the
the cool on the
way well I think we all know I think we
all know what happens when somebody
rings the bell right so let's do
yeah what does g know get a you get
sticker when you ring the bell you ring
the bell make hit the Bell like a bunch
of times not just once like a gazillion
can you get a
lollipop
huh yeah something kind of neat
happens all right how do I hold
on
no I would take leave it leave it just
leave
it
oh maybe the counter was kind of
full mhm give it another shot hey she
wasn't taken he loves the apparat she
was not taken there you
go sells for a lot too and the fish
uhhuh fish no got to say goodbye to our
the fish anything last I didn't personal
token you lost it wait one more thing
one more thing I've lost it
hey it did it on its own I didn't was
that you ringing it over my shoulder n
my oh okay what a deal what a
deal nice one team we got the fish not
the fish you're going to lose the
fish can we can we sell the post it oh
no she's ringing the bell and running
away I feel like we had so much more
money though more than 146 we barely met
the quota we barely met the quota yeah
when I scaned it was like 240 something
or
another he ripped us off we got
305 no
huh went back into the
ocean she went home she went home fish
oh what's this did you throw them in
there I think
this yeah car might find the fish over
there oh sh what is this it's
lur this he actually jump I don't know
oh I kind of forget what is in
this sound behind the wall it was a log
a journal
entry is it a will did we lose her did
she jump into the water and swim to the
sea I think she went
home all right well I was no way we'll
see you on return to the ocean see you
on the ship well I got her
journal nice all right all right wa
should we should we buy some yeah that
would be a good
idea okay I think that was lag okay M us
the minus the
quota um probably
by something should
Weis should
we switch members or should we just I
wonder if someone left would I be able
to invite someone again what are you
doing think I'm should I'm should be
able to play next round this
round let's see if is that how it
works what I wonder if we
have re recreate a room it would be
better not if we did not do that cuz
then we can't go to the further away
rooms but I wonder can can we invite
from here apparently some you can make
it saves an orbit oh yeah that's right
you can true yeah like I have a save
file so if we quit out of it it saves
your
progress cool so I'll quit out of it and
reinvite
people okay sound okay is that going to
work yeah let's do that we can't play
save and then close lobby yeah sure we
can go to orbit and then save okay go
into
[Music]
orbit monitoring big fish
the darkness so who's going to SP out
she's in the deep deep darkness of the
waters so dark I can't see
anything G gar will sit out so watch and
but you're new to the game everybody
else has played
it oh maybe I'll sit out for well I I
don't know if I can wait you can't cuz
you're the you're the host true maybe
I'll sit out the last game though I
don't mind being the ghost of New Year's
past okay well I'll go ahead and quit
out then we're in orbit now quit Farm
all right now let me reinvite everybody
okay nice there it is you guys can't
hear me or I can't hear you guys right
now it's
okay time for invite how did you did you
show the Discord shair yeah yeah I just
had um like somebody's main POV and then
somebody cuz you can watch two streams
at once and then I had both audio
playing at the same time and it wasn't
that bad it's kind of echoey but it's
not that
bad Okie
doie all right IIT am I sitting this one
out I can sit out I don't mind oh I
didn't invite you I'm sitting
out already been
made okay welcome great assets I guess I
should buy some stuff Hello who
W hello okay
wow go explain what were you doing at
the
end uh I took my tungston fish and we
both went back to the Sea together it's
kind of sweet
yes can one more person also stream
their do I do okay cuz I think if I do
it like recently when I screen share my
my voice gets like correctly and then
crackling
uh okay just buying some stuff there we
go chat now you guys can hear maybe I
should buy one more walk maybe two more
walkies look who taught you those dances
huh
you want to spend much familiar to me
have you cheated on me by going to a
different dance teacher yep no I would
never do that are you kidding
me never I don't know those dance moves
they look unfamiliar to me I didn't
teach you those it's okay it's just your
old age you're you're forgetting things
you've gone CA that's fine just do a
little gas lighting here and
there just a little
bit good fun Bon farted probably it
Waton you're stinking up the ship you
guys can't even get
out no got to light a match hold on I'm
trying to
get this to capture
Moon
Moon let's go to um moons the Moon moons
let's go to Assurance
again that seems good off we go
ladies follow your lead I want to see
the powerful skills of Amelia
Watson show us your scrap collecting
skills Watson pretty good yeah
Master trinket collector collecting the
your trinkets o I'll take that you can't
catch
me
Wy yeah we B Stu listen for Christmas
crbo
music this is my
PO
you want this where is it keep your eyes
to the scare
Cowboys there it is
coming it'sing the there go
oh
Santa
prank
what is it
walkie walkie talkies ladies walkie
every yeah everybody and some
flashlights one
flashlight flashlight still got your
shovel
girl with
you was whoopsy doodle it's all good
it's all good ladies no wonder I sunk so
fast yeah Mak sense all right where's
the entrance I'm going to go drop off
the boom box
come in
one you sitting out right
sheating this one bo bo
boom she got a GRE box yeah it's very
important all right which way is it um
not sure don't really remember this for
this
Moon we're going to have to find it oh
wait this is am's point of
view uh really embarrassing if we
couldn't even find the entrance but
found it found it this is it this
way forward
ho forward ho is it is it
Amit no this is
Amit I think I need
to think this is
yeah okay we got to run and jump I'm
confused Run and Jump yeah Run and Jump
like
[Music]
this that was sick let's go nice parkour
I didn't even believe but it happened
yeah that's what happens when you don't
believe in yourself well is this scorus
I heard smells here stinky
winky oh yeah she's calling out okay now
it's you can go from here yeah no fall
damage right
I don't think so well good well not for
now at least at least from this distance
they're very very
lenient all right let's do this are you
guys lost no we found it my flashlight G
use the oh there's something right here
um you want it it looks like a
flashlight what is this I know the pipes
maybe it's a red it's a laser pointer oo
you can play with cats cat oh there's a
turret there's a turret be careful
there's a turret over there oh
oh does the laser Corner help with
anything did she get
lost Red soda ooh soda can don't mind if
I do a little hope soda iisa soda oh
this is guras that's good a yield
sign I'm already full good
loot good
loot for great I can use this to hit
things yeah as a weapon okay I'm going
to find Skipper turn it off drop this
outside wonder where the the other two
went I wonder where the other two went
can you hear
me go that way Marco Polo Master turning
off listen to the sound of my
voice I'm here I'm going kind of
downstairs I turned off the Val it's
easier to see now oh
nice
cool good work good work I'm Super Mario
AKA Ki what is this I didn't even know
you could do that maybe another lock
door there's another one there's another
one all right keep it up Mario sounds
like a it's a me I'm Mario I'm going to
see if I can check some other areas hey
guys it's already 2:20 p.m. and you
haven't entered the
building yeah they might need to oh hey
could be goodies here stop sign break
Breer hey we are like the Super Mario
Brothers we're the super sign Brothers
oh guys there's a lot of stuff in there
get get it really okay Kara we're Super
saan
Brothers a gift uhoh oh no oh no Super
Brothers there's a monster yeah uh we
might have to use it the hair brush I'm
no coward you know no one to leave the
monster the monster's probably we could
kill it with the with the signs or
whatever beat it together like yeah but
Are You full inventory cuz I am we might
as well go yeah and then they just went
in will they be okay ooh yeah that'll be
fine fish yeah let's get out of
here I could give them the flashlight
though that could be a good idea if
they're still there we should be using
our
walkies uhoh activity
detected near activity detected let's
get out of here a I'm going get out of
here too
noise Watson all right yeah you want to
leave let's go bet bet Watson let's get
out of
here um someone dropped their
walkie-talkie oh wait I left my stuff
back there uhoh and they
uh I have to try and get something to
the ship what what just
happened I'm not marooning wait what
she's
alive what was that
noise oh there's
a there's a
lot there's at least
two yeah go monitor
them you left kiaha behind she said that
she was going to go give them a Flash
run
alive I'm sorry okay
someone
live I actually survived that it's kind
of a messed up the messed up deserter in
space it's me it was me all
along the deserter here doo doo
doo all right I'm going to tell them
here do do on a
sec I
Dro who a good boy are you outside
there's many snacks
here oh hold on I'm opening it I haven't
seen any dog so far oh get in here worm
wor
[Music]
worm oh that's that's a worm yep I made
it I made it inside everyone made it
worm see the giant red dot on the screen
the timing is impecable what what
you who got a blue it's important music
is important when you're lonely and on a
ship in
space play some tunes sing us a song
near the piano
man
yeah uhoh no dropped
it sorry La laest employee wait how can
you be lazy and profitable at the same
time mean do again seems like there's
something wrong are you just pushing
your tasks to the other employees
yeah no I I even I literally saved Amy
from Death a monster was on her head and
I killed it the only
reason hero moment for Kiara big
hero big clap I Ked it on my own it was
the my is the the strength of my will no
my B is the proof Thank Me Later chat
tell
her does she not know does she not know
all right yeah I'm send you you're a
hero to me the sun thank you let's go
toen okay sounds good french
it's oh I've never seen this screen
before hey maybe we should order some
flashlight
50 we're too poor goba we can't afford
it the stronger moves we we'll go to
offense because we are you little
oh know Friendly
Fire like a high school Friendly Fire
love
yeah sh it's someone twerking in the
corner over there what's going on you
kidding me twerking I'm not what I'm not
twerk what are you talking about you
were doing some some movements behind
the cabinet I wasn't sure you know you
were
uh you sure was she's doing
spy the boom box yeah I mean someone
could stay here in theory and uh direct
us with the walki Takis stay
back going to use that precious carg as
a weapon why is it what it's please do
not bson Watson announcement from the
company please do not kill your other
fellow employees
I don't need the walkie-talkie so I'll
leave it here I need more space
everyone's lives matters in this company
okay sounds let's go be good assets
though the great assets they definitely
value the great assets more though what
did you say to me yes huh heard
me no she did not call you an a great
asset an asset he said you're a great
asset to the company
wait yeah I don't need it I it's okay I
I left it on purpose all right she
doesn't want to communicate with us all
right
Kiara I see how it
is crying out to you in Peril and you're
not going to hear me no no I will I will
be around when you need me and when you
need me the most that's what she says
but can she I'm not going to respond to
that I guess we can go off to the side
there's a big bird
oh yeah hat no they hate me untrue now
you're just making up
fibs let's see oh maybe we can go up
here you're going to lead us right to
the all the
loot wonder if we can jump this there's
a different way we can
go I think we can just go
around this way it's a longer route
well
it's a longer
routee
oh no I didn't I'm going to do it
now she for the jump she it coward I can
park with the rest of
them you know I just the other day
finished my first ever like um platform
of Mario game a wow yeah ody
yeah it was very nice to me it's a good
game so good y oh Dy jump up in the air
the sign is a bad choice why that's all
right they they're justers you never
been able to do this it's good thing you
stayed in the ship they
can't understand the met with the signs
our third member where did Goombas
go all right I need I need some uh I
need some coms here oh where is go huh
CLE see dead down dead
down hello this is Morrison speaking uh
Grim Shady open
out what was I can't pick up
anything can we kill spider spider yeah
sure oh there was a treasure over there
huh where you sure
sure the the green Doritos oh I found
something I lied I found nothing there's
a door
there can you keep a look out for Red
Dot on on
[Applause]
me no it's a valve nothing good down
here maybe it's below nothing good down
here sadly yeah there's a green
oh
[\h__\h] oh did I see two eyes oh it's the
generator it's the generator oh do not
touch until the end it's not recommended
that's for
sure why is there no
it oh
boers oh sounds like a lights
saer
it
now
wow all right I'm going to grab the core
and we can go I hear muffled the
screams
um
yikes
um teleported out of there pretty quick
though not going to lie
I'm going to get her body did you guys
go past the
monsters
oh I'll carry her body you can carry the
core I think there's one more thing hold
Oh What A Brave
one good idea grabbing the items very
nice yay successful wow what a
legend we did it you should the clutch
that's really admire that I'm a bit of a
coward though not going to
lie a bit of a I can't I don't think we
can talk on the mic with the thing I am
afraid to tell you that
oh did gar gumbus die someone has passed
away I mean we oh yeah we have to make
the jump okay oh yeah I think a couple
people away very cold wait call did you
pick
up
sorry couldn't be a good asset this time
really was pretty Barren I'm not going
to
lie yeah bad
haul we'll get it next time we get it
she left us with a single a and pieced
out pieced out of
existence huh wait I heard them wait oh
oh oh no that hey just kidding it must
have been on the walkie see I knew
they'd be useful
I have uh Kiara's dead body oh what
about Kiara's
sign dang it must have lost it in The
Fray oh I picked it up I got it oh nice
nice
one MV MVP what a legend all right let's
Mosey on out of
here someone else can choose where we go
next leave it up to you guys
okay right on ahead CH can pick
yeah where does chat want to go this
closes on its own right yeah yeah I
think yeah it would be pretty funny if
it did nice one team um we have about
one day left for the quota I think we
can we can f
it how are we doing for the quota so far
hi
check I'm alive again welcome revived
Like a Phoenix
yeah we're at
26 most profitable because I brought
back a body like a noble a noble
Spaceman yeah thank you for carrying me
you're welcome I'm laziest but I was
Button Pusher I mean that could I pushed
one button oh wow Assurance really is
the only one that we can mess around on
huh don't don't don't me please no
vience on the sh quing
no violence on the
ship oh well in that case all out Battle
Royale Doo go for
it your radio is going to run out of
battery no yeah you got to charge it you
turn it off no you know what I should
also grab some flashlights wait mine's
on too I'm going to grab some
flashlights real quick and then we can
go flashlight let's do
three come f
righty now let's land um you know have a
report to make to
uh yes please
please harassed by
what H is
listening she excuse me there seems to
be
l oh my God the
radiation excuse me you have a witness
you just committed a crime here yeah I'm
reporting you to the
company did youill report has been made
please
Kiara Kiara I will kill myself now
Kiara really wait oh God don't do that
explain that no stop okay all right G
last day of the meet the quota let's go
you and
me oh oh oh oh oh
you um I do what just
happened
first hold on oh no what just happened I
can't I can't hear El cuz she's
dead hey
girl she's alive oh thank God hello I
can't do it Al I can't go in there alone
that's okay you got oh I got two yeah it
was supposed to be one for each of us
but plans changed clearly wait wait wait
wait I going drop his off yeah me
too how are we going to explain to the
bosses that two of our te well one
committed a crime and the other one
killed one committed soku um it's a
great question um for now let's not
think too much about it I'm sure that
the company you know will understand
dear boss can I please I can't believe
you've done this take on the raise that
my fellow employee was going to get love
you say yeah can I get the lunch coupon
it's kind of different from the love I
know can I get that meal
ticket yeah that CAF school cafeteria
Pizza watch out there's bees I'll take K
steamed potato I don't think she'll need
it anymore true oh steamed potato sounds
yummy cafeteria piz yep up this
ladder that's what they all say Kiara oh
boy then we
I didn't mean it I didn't think that was
actually going to kill her or like she
started it ni One all right Run and Jump
B Bros to the rescue it's like if
someone else is going to kill elit it's
going to be me kind of thing you know
hey
understandable understandable seems the
baby shark has missed her jump
uhoh do I wait for her do I go collect
you know what
she could show up and then there will be
stuff to gather at the entrance do it
sometimes the reaper got to do the hard
job here I
go leave it to me I'm not afraid I'm I'm
the bravest one here I was going to make
a plan but I stopped myself is that a
bird is it
hostile it's it's just a
bird huh just a
bird open at least Jesus
my let me open it all
right oh oh oh M goat takes the present
hello oh she made it I'm alive H made it
before found a present present I can't
open it for some reason I pressed y but
it didn't work maybe you can open open
it oh jar of pickles that will help us
meet the quar for sure all right we got
to we got to we got to
survive oh should be goodies in
here oh key nothing
spotted darn it
a there got to be some goodies around
here no way can you use
it did you find something good yeah dude
what' you find you're not going to
believe it
okay all right uh I'm quitting the game
I've had enough of this I've had enough
of this fre had enough come here come
here come here come here come here come
here come here come here come here sit
on it come
here yeah there for the content Gall
pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it
up
really sticky you know what you've made
a mistake G you're letting me hold this
now which means you'll never get it back
no it's only worth eight it's not even
worth
anything our fun
times yep I can use this as leverage
now there's a fire where is it there's a
turret be
careful
Grenada turret that way does it say ass
what does this do hey Kuma you can use
that you
know we're finding some good stuff use
it hang on uh give me my whoopy cushion
back girl you need to trade it with me
yes trade it for other Goods find
her flashback Flash
a okay I saw that I can't
see well I've got my jar of pickles I'm
so proud of you you flashbang that
spider like no
tomorrow we're not making it off the
moon with this one you did I could go
back and look for more but knowing me um
I'm going to get eaten by a dog I don't
think that killed it though just letting
you know
maybe it just got emotional damage not
sure no there's just
multiple I don't know which way should I
go
no be is that
Kiara oh that's
a Dodge Dodge
DOD run run run for it
run
disgusting you made it though proud of
you it's very
slippery
ah
no
Marco
might have run out of
battery oh she's back home feel kind of
bad for
dur maybe the whoopy cushion will make
her happy and then she'll be sad when
we
she's leaving oh is G still there
oh
oops
um
oh didn't even check the cams real sorry
about that
[Music]
one you know on the bright side I saved
your woy cushion for you I'll have you
know I was fighting for my life in there
ah well that's fine you wouldn't have
made it back anyway the dogs were
prowling I did us all a
flavor we have fine maybe
enough I don't think it is are we all
getting fired is this we might be
getting fired I mean asides from being
fired there has been some allegations of
you
know members there's mine killing
members so there's that employ use body
sell for five each so H is definitely
going to hear about this three Warm
Bodies that could increase the quot the
quot you can actually use
it there's no bathroom in the ship just
to let you know it
poops I figured she'd like
that that makes
sense so uh if we want to rotate someone
out we could this is a good time to do
it if we want
to I can the before we die I can I can
it's my
turn okay how is it your turn we're
going by the life
the is that how it works all right I
guess we're going to the company
now you got to sell everything we have
no days left on our
deadline I want some
pickles
what is this [\h__\h] well you can check if
you meet the quot or not first maybe
yeah know I kind of did take a look and
I think
if even if one of us even if all three
of us gave up our bodies if three people
gave up their bodies it wouldn't matter
we can give up our bodies for points for
money Oh you mean yes only like five oh
it's not a lot oh that's what you mean
oh yeah like if we beat up each other
other right but we'll need something to
beat each other with so maybe don't sell
anything maybe don't sell the SOP sign
yet I mean you can just ring the bell a
lot of times uhoh can't pick it up again
see this yeah Dar I got a sniper o a
laser pointer wow where' you get that I
found on the floor I see the apparatus
sells for a lot that's good ooh yeah if
we sell the whoopy cushion we might
cushion G we might need a to
out we have to keep Spirits High I think
us
no give you money do
it that's too bad oh it's a step gun me
oh 301 holy
moly just doesn't show the
scan to keep your your whoy Pion I guess
she was going to keep it anyway she's
going to keep it any
bot items okay all
right goodbye whoopy chushan
remember damn
[Laughter]
it let's get moving maybe we can go to
some better moons we're going to go into
orbit and then we'll switch
out is everyone here I don't know is
every sorry I also didn't check again
I'm not the best Captain I'm not going
to lie seems to be a reoccurring thing
all right now listen here the company
hear about this no no no no the company
doesn't need to hear about anything
anything of the sort the quote is going
to start getting crazier though from
here on out um so we're going to need to
go to further away moons with better
loot you be the voice that everybody
hears so maybe lead give don't lead us
but give us give us give us useful hints
yeah like
a a GM now let's see what we can buy
first oh let's see store I can spell
store um so we have quite a bit of money
in fact we could get a transporter which
might be kind of nice oh no we what's
the point if the ship leaves before you
can teleport I mean good all that too
but we we actually can't afford it so
I'm going to grab some
shovels
shovel two we need two fighters and
then after that um I think we should be
us organized we should be using the
money to go to big moon charging
everything
mhm number one employee H will hear
about this for employee
expensive um all right what's the
cheapest Moon I wonder is it Dy by
chance we won't go there cuz it's
eclipsed but oh
no is
Ren yeah maybe St be
nice we're changing that's right correct
swapping out
boss doodle okay going to close out the
room
now quit bullying
girl what is going on she's dancing the
wall oh
whoopsies all gono now friends make new
crew oh I guess I got a launch now huh
yeah come on hop right
in
then that should do it oh I can unre
stream now in the
Discord
[Music]
Callie did you see it you rece the
present present I haven't oh the I
haven't looked
yet invite me again see play I'm excited
thank you invite needs another invite oh
Ena needs another invite you got it yes
please okay no problem Captain's got
your back all right youa Jump On In pour
out
yeah guys I basically did up almost
everybody maybe except for one person
coola yes a did you see I I sent you a
present over theme did you see I don't I
didn't see anything pop
up it's probably in your emails or so oh
I'll check my em it'll be in there you
double now double all right fine I
received the
gift accept gift I got it don't have it
yet do you have I don't I only have the
first
one please play it I want you to I want
to see you play it okay I will I'll be
the Artist Artist yeah I ended up giving
her something else guys than what I
originally said in the
Stream not Secret Surprise you had a
game Secret surprise more
more yeah let's go be sure we gra
stuff passport to two the second
one I'll grab a walkie glad she doesn't
have it yet okay who's staying in the
ship you can stay in the ship or you can
stay pick guys not very good at
breathing learned that I'm just like ooh
pretty shapes oh right I have to tell
them double ena's echoing for me
oh sorry I forgot to mute all good there
we go
switch display
Mar hey how do I do it
again oh do the ship com you got to look
at the
monitor I think you can type in switch
view monitor yeah that's what it is make
sure you have a walkie-talkie are you
staying inside yes all right forward H
forward
H my delivery should be coming she's a
Mur chick chick chick chick playing
Freddy
reset how you watch two
streams just press the little plus
eyeball on
Discord oh my
God thank
you this is grim Shady calling in
um from the
ship from the ship go ahead and take a
right old is
HQ call in break
break affirmative Grim shady is now
entering the is waiting to enter the
building but I'm also waiting for my
friends Grim Shady over Grim Shady
over's
lost I have found the main Eng
over where's guua k can you hear me over
and out Grim Shady over and out I don't
really need to put that Grim Shady it's
pretty good right yeah she's lost I see
she she didn't take the walkie-talkie
with her like I told her
to ah there it is I'm not blind I can
see
everything you know be is she going to
be fine who botles H looks like she's
okay I think she found a different
entrance oh I see tell her to jump on
the bridge jump on the bridge fun bouncy
yeah jump on it a million times you'll
be
fine
sorry found another whoopy cion oh Jesus
Christ no fire exit
I The Collection grows
larger I don't I don't have a walkie
talkie so I'm just going to stay with f
repeat what that I don't have a
walkie-talkie so I'm going to stay with
you okay Watson can you repeat that
please there's should be two items in
the room affirmative it's an
a yeah maybe
don't o rubber
ducky I don't see any red ducks right
now uhoh oops sorry trying to crouch
dropped it yeah I dropped it on purpose
sorry trying to get the rubber du can't
take them anymore what can
we Pi up oh there you go there you go
okay nice nice nice nice good find yeah
nice finds let me turn the walkie keep
the walkie
on wat let us know if there enemies
coming there's a monster behind you uhoh
monster R it's like running away e e e
e need help need
help oh boy I saw that happen running
right towards her she she's to the right
the right mon taking her into the it's
too late they gone I did see that happen
follow her there's T
of I don't I don't know what we could
have
done you know come in slime slime slime
slime slime slime slim slime SL
fine slime is fine not messing with
that can I hit what this no but I can
use this is maybe if an enemy shows up
it will stop them for a moment all right
here's all right so the enemy took this
is where the monster is Kiara I'm going
to go forward and if it comes out enemy
coming right at you
guys did someone just snaap their neck
what was that I think it's called a uh
break breaker braen is it crunch Watson
this is grim Shady reporting in I have
two big b that
I that I don't think that I could handle
by myself if you wouldn't mind coming to
pick one of them up to help me out I'll
try to I'll try to do both
but that I'm on my
way thanks watching Grim Shady out there
all
right
full look at it for one second then Look
Away hopefully the bridge doesn't
fall mine the cliff mine's a cliff
indeed Watson on the way I think we
should be able to gather everything
before the monsters start coming
out
[\h__\h] this way oh I hear
Watson I'm going back all right sounds
good
that bridge looks way too
sturdy
yeah sadly going to have to leave the
whoop think the bridge will break if
you're too heavy like
someone yeah like someone's big butt
over and out Grim Shady over and
out we're talking about you I love bread
rolls yummy it do be good right maybe
man and I can switch places I'll go
watch
her a sick burn let's see a few
monitors monitoring
More's going to leave you better
runy
oh
[\h__\h] oh Lordy
coming what is
that uh Watson do you read me I hear big
steppies Watson do you just stay quiet
what is that oh my God what is
that let's go let's go let's go let's go
oh nice one nice one Watson let's
go yeah
[Music]
Jam there we lifted did we lift off I'm
pretty sure we
did yeah thankfully just got a chip
imagine celebrating early couldn't be
yay anyway nice one Watson that came in
that came in clut oh it's lazy I
definitely would have died zero
experien
yeah sh left if we pull about the same
amount it's all right it's all right no
problem if we pull the same amount again
um a couple more times I think wait you
can just step on it yeah be D
easy
easy oh youed I'm order some flashlights
no I can't geted any first oh my Lord
they really punished you for that
huh all right let's see
try that's cute she's mocking you look
at
her you're just an
inter there will be no bullying on my
ship knock that right off right now did
it she started
it you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] I am
done being your go they're fighting
again never
again I want to get in the middle of a
couple
squirrel they like gross
grossling nice that was actually pretty
good so we're going to land and we
should look listen look listen for the
delivery I got flashlights for you
guys oh thank you owe you my life make
sure you charge your walkie
talk the best good play proba oh true
where's the Christmas tree should be
[Music]
coming oh
nice why are we all looking into the Sun
at the same time again he bad for your
eyes raise the sun o oh there it is let
me turn off
[Music]
mine
I just got flashlights for you guys it's
flashlight praise the sun
CHR all
right ready to enter oh main entrance is
over
there let's head it's coming up it's
coming up it's coming
[Music]
up can't help
myself
yeah
bless
got we got watchs and speed
running
okay Grim shady is there anybody at
comms over and
out
hello what up Watson Over and
Out ooh found a
present is that a
bomb which is his that's weird oh it's a
pipe a ly
pipes oh maybe down
here BR my
there's nothing
here whatson this is grim Shady are you
detecting any hostiles over
now not at the
moment oh stuff there's like nothing
here pretty
bar we got to meet the quota
though just need to keep the
walkie-talkie on for walks and
updates
perfect key I got a door over here but I
need
light
oh there is nothing over here
either let's get
it oh okay maybe really isn't anything
over
there where must we go maybe
here
was dead end funny
items huh this
way what is that
[Music]
ew uhoh what is that sounds familiar why
is that just got to follow the
to Jesus it's Chas Chas thought you in
the
ship
sound funny sound funny I I only have
one item but I might as well bring it
back have
a it doesn't sound like an air
horn it doesn't sound like an air horn
it sounds like something
else no one wants to
you take that
back if there is anyone using these
these things it's Grim shady and I think
I found a continuation but I really need
a flashlight over and out oh if you're
talking about that I think we we already
explored that area oh I understood over
and
out also I found a present be right
there the present's freaking sick oh
nice
over
o o oi what is that ew ew R oh my God oh
God you
good you
know is anyone even still in
here oh they're outside I can't open
this for some reason
so open it yeah
here
y let's go thank you appreciate it oh
you guys are coming back in I mean we're
all
alive wish we had more stuff but this is
easy yeah there was nothing there was
like nothing in there fire exit C say
fire
exit let's see what
we is still in
there well I think she's dead all right
if I don't come
back wait she's moving oh wait she she's
moving she
lost I want to be a
hero oh my God oh my God oh my
God she's insane I
canane oh there's another
entrance
ttbook Serpentine
maneuver why we just even
wow is there anything by the door to
carry oh Ena you need help hello
hi I have a emotional going look for you
too oh no I'm fine I just want to check
the fire exit don't check the fire exit
go home let just go home if you say
Selena it's been a long day let's
[Music]
without are you
been everybody made it pretty brave of
[Music]
me we have we're going to have a
Minefield of whoopy cushions yeah at
this point iong with that hey we know
what we're selling first if we're low on
quota Jesus should be
enough it should be
H anyway we got more stuff than I
thought No
[Music]
Monsters wait air is
worth2 it's actually a lot way more than
I thought a lot nice one yes no notes is
better than being called
lazy great eight great eight nice part
one day
one day left anything you guys want me
to buy oh cute anything you guys want I
could use a walkie I didn't have one
okay I don't have one either oh really I
thought for sure we had four I
definitely bought four
that's yeah all right
two we go someone needs to go to the
bathroom or what gu
not pooping in
space would it just float out there
forever I mean maybe it's going to March
there's a toilet that you I mean gravity
helps
right how would you even get it out
anyway all right we're on our way all
right where's our next destination
March yeah all right let's go March
time oh in isn't that right ladies I'm
going to get my anyone stay in
behind well there's a there's a hi
nearby be
careful you don't really need a
flashlight technically oh it's not
really charged no no you can just go
into the darkness and it's fine you know
charge head first into the dark
ohy one sec I'm just going to charge
this where's the Christmas tree is
anytime
now is that it Oh that's oh that is
it
yay she's going in by
herself prin yay nice is that it I think
so B if you enter the building
over I'm waiting outside hurry up swag
over
where is the a building this way oh
um yeah I think from March I think it's
really all just to the
right from the ship
so I trust your direction sense better
than mine please don't trust my I I
don't know you know we might gam it
might be a bad combo
then go t go t go t straight away oh
yeah it's this this place straight we're
we're on our way
over all right all right all right all
right all right all right okay okay okay
okay okay
okay
wow kind getting hungry do you think the
company has St meals probably just like
space meals and stuff like like um
liquidi I don't know
yeah
oh nice I'll go this way oh there's a
key uh oh oh I didn't mean to drop
there's a mine over there there's a mine
uh maybe oh my God good
find you find a good find be nice if we
can bring the mine back you know there
was a way to
oh oh that's uh yeah that's a she's got
the
goddamn the quot though
guys all right how are we going to do
this some be bait need this qu I felt
something you sure I don't mind being
bait we don't have AEL running away oh
uh you sure going through like the
fire
okay um oh it's
[Music]
still I don't know where it is but we'll
just walk around and oh
careful oh bra they don't know who to go
after H Kong Hong Kong L that oh no oh
[Music]
no there
another I just wanted to be a great
asset the slowest Reaper in the west I
think I had to press X maybe three times
something did she die there's controller
user problems
listen are we meeting this going to
bring these things I don't know that we
have at least something I mean true
but
be my body could be worth something yeah
we could have done some like teamwork
dang are you back the ship someone here
yeah you're going to have to toss Oh no
you're not you
just worth a whole
$5 that's how much my corpse is worth to
you God the ship's like a barren
wasand something weird is happening huh
theing oh
team I think we could do
it would the reaper really body maybe
not I don't know where the fire exit
is did anybody see the fire egg
anywhere I don't know maybe he's deagro
who could
say yes S A that's true I am alone in
the void right now I realized the
there's a lot of them around here oh no
you don't need to fight those
guys left of the ship is the fire exit
which left oh God oh my God oh God oh my
God I'm almost dead oh yeah I guess I
took a big hit sorry I'm sorry you got
this girl you go
girl you better you better
h
okay I'm staying I'm looking forward to
losing that part
time Jesus Kiara woo
yikes found the fire make sure you keep
the door open for a while I'm
coming the little one before she put it
away all right we still have time it's
500 p.m. it's 5:00 p.m. hey chat you
guys really know is it actually over
here in there
now
God that
safe what just happen it's 500 p.m. oh
boy en what killed you I should probably
get back to the ship I went through the
fire exit I found the I found the horn
and then I
died
uhoh what is that that's the GI a coil
head must have been a coil head I should
have
waited he's
why is he just staying
here he want to play
Adventure surely he can't go around the
mountain it's like a lot of mountain
between
them I am dead I am dead
yeah darn
it it all went to [\h__\h] after that uh bee
situation yeah dang dang
it we'll meet the quota
someday just not
today we're dead it's just a giant here
right no like doggies or anything like
that back ship um I think they're
doggies I'm not sure but I think this is
the right wayant for sure maybe there's
anyone who can get around them is
definitely
Watson hey guys are you coming back
yeah she's
here thought wait so is dead in the in
the
thing it was a noble sacrifice though
you really tried to get the air this our
last
day yeah but we made a lot of money
before I think
did Kar I don't know I see two okay okay
we have I I just
cleaned
sa don't sell the whoopies we're going
to have to sell all our Whoopi cushions
G
sorry oh a not bad yeah we're going to
have to sell all the cushions will
playing a song for you guys cuz you
[Music]
died away with this well maybe they'll
forgive us I don't
know I think we're going to have enough
we're going to make it you think
so I believe K somebody I
mean do we have as long as one of us is
alive all right do we have something to
hit each other with
times do I need to buy a shovel that's
the
spirit I'll buy a shovel good to have a
shovel all right yeah you could buy a
shovel wait but if we buy shovel will we
have no it won't affect the money that
um okay it won't affect the
money sorry I'm not really good at math
all good well I guess we can
land question out yeah oh question after
this should be maybe just like chatchat
a little bit and do the like talk about
the things we're supposed to talk about
oh yes oh yeah we're supposed to be
uh we're supposed to do something that's
true I forgot about about that cuz I
think another round would take uh too
long true yeah
probably okay play somay can
play yeah I mean I let's get a let's get
a board yeah let's get M perms yeah I
want to I want to play I need to ask
what else anything
else all right now the shovel should be
coming my nail
there it is that's so obvious
[Music]
trou oh
no yeah doesn't seem
good I think even selling our bodies
isn't going to
work no it's what the [\h__\h] no was
coming all the
toys no
got to sell
youa no we could have used that
bite I mean oh no ena's
dead what the
[\h__\h] what was walk oh I don't think so I
don't think I can anyway hey how much
money do we
make
PL I would say
PL oh is this a
he's got to take I can't take it back
it's okay whatever it's okay it's pretty
aggravated it's fine I can't take it
back anyway it's okay please come take
the it there we
go come
[Music]
on yeah we'll be fine you think so
wow now we hit it yeah we did no we of
course we did no we didn't oh no we
didn't okay if we sell
our or
the true enough do it okay oh it is a
good ending although it is a good ending
it is a good ending isn't it when if we
get sent into space that's a nice ending
I mean that is
true but I could still kill you with
where are you where you could but you
wouldn't would you hey hey don't I mean
hey I'm not worth enough anyway need a
more convincing
argument uh uh Takami
[Music]
Takami this the
argument all right
okay for
now for
[Applause]
now yeah you know what you make really
good point Kiara a should beat up both
of us gone should beat up both of us
yeah that's her dream come no the other
way around we should beat up wait did
she jump into the water did she go after
G mil
Watson hey
[Music]
Watson Watson I hear her I think I hear
little sounds or is it is that ga ga
Watson I know you're like only in
Discord but say
something say something oh
see something she
heard stop with the
te targeted she's like hiding
somewhere no I
mean what else can we do guess guess
we'll go yeah I'm we're
leaving IIA
Watson check the camera check the camera
o good idea oh it's just like in the
black wow what I don't know where'd she
go we're in the ship she's ah she's
coming oh what was she doing messing
around
being Amia hi well where were you
hey
yo you
hey hey I didn't close the door on you
that was I think
I'm I see you guys wanted to be alone I
he
it
I'm no man left behind she probably
already sent the [\h__\h] did she no no okay
wait something's burning she bought
something oh we can buy something here
for my
stuff it's mine I take I think you mean
mine she want she wants to die I knew it
get her I took your
weapon my shov we survive you will not
be the end of Me no this is a
murder go let me in open open
up a don't do
this you can't do
this open
the
me oh I mean I was going to show her
mercy but I murder she was leaving
so wait did she order another one no uh
we should go shouldn't we steal our body
first um no I just witnessed a Cold
Blood
murder oh my God at the end of the day
there's only room for one sheriff in
this town now make the quot
again Kelly Make the qua H you're
right that's a really good
point there's only room for one Captain
it's like the ending of a bad Space
Opera
all righty G
me just doing what has to be done to
satisfy the
[Music]
company anyway oh I should probably sell
the shovels
too that might
help any whoopy cushions I'm sure I
could sell everything maybe he doesn't
want these
things what you doing more
did he take the
bodies why aren't you
hungry here we
[Music]
go there you go eat
up
man a he didn't want the stuff well I'm
not selling the boom box that's for sure
um with that being
said it's
over there's only
one one remains there can only be one it
can only be one
yeah
um can I a little [\h__\h] you are little
[\h__\h] 25 look you are I was just doing
what needed to be
done we were so close as you
have play some
music I don't want to die go
dancing wasn't charged sad we could have
had a musical
exit you are fired all right girls well
it do be like that fired fired nice
G can't believe I got fired again oh
suddenly the
double I leave the
game okay I'll do
this a
lot this is your very own autopilot ship
where you will eat and
sleep to
talk home to complete the on boarding
process you will want to
checkr wait wait
wait hang on a sec I
need she's still she's still feeling the
end of the
movie why you crying mate crying you
look like you're sad me about your
actions like you're regretting what yeah
don't you feel you know guilt regret
shame I feel little worse I do I do feel
that for sure um for sure for sure what
you don't believe me
yeah yeah I a little bit really I you
don't want to show it but you're so deep
in your heart you have remorse okay well
yeah I would say I mean that's AB that's
about right maybe a little bit I just
had to do what needed to be done you
know for the sake of the company and we
were never Mee in that quota but you
know I should I had the opportunity to
take the ship and leave you guys and
kill you should have taken it in
fairness Waton I wasn't going to kill
Kar until she killed you so what were
you up to I saw you hit
her look just doing my
job
everybody
everybody first of all happy new New
Year from myth happy
new and
holidays May
2024 a year yeah it's a new year it's
2024 oh my
god um do we want to say like what what
we should say yeah well I guess we have
talk about I don't either what are we
talking about
we pictures no it's just like you know
the usual uh the small myth stuff right
we are here to
advertise the small small myth stuff
that is still on sale
until oh my God no way cute cute a
little while longer um I don't know when
it ends it doesn't say here you guys can
go look at's channel for
while don't miss out you're hugging them
wait yeah there's a lot of stuff there's
uh the t-shirts where we're where we're
poking out of the the pockets there's
small metal charms there's also random
stickers and the plushies of course
again are also still on sale so I'm
going to put the link in my chat if you
guys I'm waiting on my shipment
interested cover Corporation Hey where's
my small
stuff I hang all them on my my backpack
but then just keep it in my
house say you go out with that stuff no
no no no no no I just look at it I put
it in like a glass case and I'm like
yeah cool also can't forget the
plushies plushies give me all of these
line them up on my bed so the whole crew
oh they regular restocked item oh
they're regular restocked item oh there
is nice so I don't know whenever you
want them go grab them okay nice well
well well well mhm so that was just a
reminder and then there's uh I guess a
re announcement that we have yeah kind
of a a re oh wait hold on a sec first
did we mention the figures we've already
talked about the little figures
right the
boxes yeah they're part of that oh
they're part of guess they're random you
mean those random ones right yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah they're part of that yeah
okie dokie well then there's another
thing you guys um that other thing being
we announced something a little while
ago which is a brand new song right by
can we show the picture yeah I showed a
picture of it I think we showed it
during we announced
it well guys we finally have a release
date sorry for the sorry for the guys
but the song will be released a music
video for it will be released on genu
Art son of a you would think
thatu no January 11th January 11th
2024 12 a.m. jst so when the clock turns
to January 11th hooray hurrah uh the
song will release on the official Hol
live English Channel so make sure that
you guys check it out I'm probably going
to do a little unarchived karaoke
beforehand to lead into it
so
F those check out our new song yeah c
can you play it am on that ukulele yeah
play it
play it down there whoa the uke showed
up I'm ready wait that can you can we
can do that now yeah we can do it now it
shows up in the groups
cool let's
[\h__\h] it's a cute song I hope you guys
will enjoy it um
it's it's like a silly one you guys like
it it's silly and cute and
change exciting soon TM soon
somebody flashbacks wore flashbacks
every time someone says T [\h__\h] being
targeted anyway oh anyway that's that's
really about it and then we also just
kind of wanted to play some lethal
company today together because you know
only seems fitting funny that we all
join the frey together that was that was
a good time someday we got to get on
those more expensive moons we'll we'll
be able to do it I'm sure yeah since
this is the first myth collab of
2024 do we want to say something nice I
don't know goals or so together down the
line um give a not a speech just say
something I don't know start just a
short
comment know I should start I should
start you know what we put the pressure
on myy um because I'll be the example
okay cuz I was today's captain and I did
I did betray my entire
ship go ahead and take the punishment
that is starting off um so let's see
2024 since the number four is included
in the year I've decided that this year
I'm going to go um 5 million per um hard
and so I hope you guys will support me
going hard real hard um next month a
bunch of things are happening there's um
a special stream on Valentine's um
that's going to be um about love but not
romantic love it's going to be love for
platonic love love of there's going to
be a charity stream on Valentine's Day
okay I'll be streaming for like 12 hours
so look forward to that um I'm not going
to announce the charity or anything like
that for a little bit but that's the
plan right now so look forward to that
and then I'm announcing something big
next month um two big things actually
one is significantly bigger than the
other um it's it's the it's the big it's
the big thing um and so I'll be doing a
24-hour stream before that so come check
it
out
and yeah so look forward to that I'm
going to work really really hard this
year um and I love I love Holo and all
my friends and um I'm having a lot of
fun thanks to you guys and I think this
year is going to be amazing um so let's
keep having tons of fun together and um
yeah that's all I wanted to say
anyway next
up uh yeah let's go by the
line uh well well well we have re I look
so stupid no you look perfect we have
recently n we recently expanded gotten a
new
generation um who are doing their best
working hard um but I'm I you know I
hope that as myth we can still do a lot
of fun things together it's a new year
so let's let's do some cool stuff myth
my cutest gen mates thank you for a
wonderful year 2023 and on to another
one with more power than ever more
energy than ever
let's be
strong go strong go home
[Music]
baby let's not lose to the new energetic
girls all right we're still young and
peachy peachy we have it in our nerves
and in our jeans we we are we are the
strongest let's go let's
go girl next you wearing pants go good I
I want to I want to actually get a mushy
gushy for a second mus mushy gushy I
apologize um I just want to I want to
say a genuine thank you to not only my
Miss girlies but also to uh everybody
watching right now for your patience
with me as I uh get my personal life and
all of all of its things together and
the time that I've been way I I really
do appreciate it all of your sweet
messages uh that they do make it back to
me and your fan mail makes it back to me
and my myth girls who are patient with
me and they check in on me and they they
say hi and they they invite me to do
things and they wish me happy holidays
and all of that stuff I want to say
thank you I appreciate it very much and
I hope to be strong for my myth girls in
2024 because I do I do want this to be I
want this to be a happy fun strong year
um with Miss and H live so thank you
everybody happy happy New Year every
Happ nice nice nice good well said
go s well you guys said a lot of things
you want to say something too you guys
already said a lot of the things I
wanted to say but I hope that this wait
am I muted what hell no no hello hear
you you're here what oh oh I muted her
cuz like she was doubling in the game
and here
wow
yeah you were double at some
point I can't believe you were saying
things so far damn it I was please
repeat everything for
me no I just wanted to say you know um
it's been a wonderful wonderful time
with you guys with chat with everyone um
I hope 2024 is filled with more fun
things and exciting things and let's
let's let's all do our best let's have
fun thank you always every one to you
guys love you love you
too
yeah right back at
you I guess it's my turn it's your turn
it's your turn
detective yeah it's been really you know
the time has gone by so fast it's still
crazy to me you know fourth year pretty
much you know we've been holding strong
and we've been we've been doing so much
everybody's always so busy so um I hope
this year we get to have more fun
together and also get you know some a
little bit of time to relax and and
chill but also do the stuff that we
enjoy cuz you know that's what we're
here for cuz we enjoy
it y yay
exactly also I will be having my
birthday stream
tomorrow studi 3
special
[Music]
birthday birth I can't believe we're
only 5 days into the year what the
heck crazy I'm excited I'm my birthday
everybody make sure to mark it on your
calendar if you haven't already 5 p.m.
PS 800 p.m es y
tomorrow tomor
I'll be awake I'll be
there can't miss out on that it's going
to be exciting I got some
stuff well after this you guys may have
seen But Advent kimono reveals have been
delayed they're after this they start in
50 minutes right
exting they'll be matching with us yeah
their first outfit so cool I wonder how
nervous I want to see yeah they're
probably nervous it's true remember our
first reveals we were just like oh
God you know I realized something
recently now it's my turn to get like a
little mushy gushy I
guess in the beginning we like we really
didn't know we were doing like at all
and it was just the five of us you know
like kind of fumbling around in the dark
and trying to figure out like what what
kind of identity is holoen going to have
and now that it's gotten so big right
the group has gotten so big I don't know
it is kind of like a family to be honest
I didn't like saying that before but I
do kind of get that feeling you know
it's it's expanded our our little H Ian
family has expanded quite a bit and I
really appreciate all of you guys being
here beside beside me and and all the
fans of myth to kind of like grow along
with us and grow together and I don't
know I'm just I'm really thankful
you know to you guys and to the fans and
I hope I hope we can still keep having a
great time together you know and and
just thanks for supporting us for so
long thank
you thank you yeah thank you myth fans
myth fans you guys are the best thank
you we love you thank you for supporting
us for such a long time yeah oh jeez
been here from the bearest start from
the
from the
yeah it's okay you're still moving on
our hearts yeah yeah yeah oh I guess
that's that's about it I can't seem to
send everybody to shor's stream but I
wish I could just go there yeah just is
she first is she up first I believe
shor's First
yeah yeah all right guys you know take
lots of screenshots and give them lots
of support I'm sure they're very very
nervous right now need your they look so
good birthday then yeah so please look
forward to it and um yeah I guess that's
it thank you for watching today
everybody thank you everyone hope you
guys have a wonderful rest of the
morning afternoon evening I guess we can
say
timate Okay 3 2 one timate amk you bye
everybody
byebye by byebye
byebye bye bye-bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye mut
[Music]
it