foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
assistant foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you foreign
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
sorry guys oh my God what's going on
candy keys
oh
hello uh I didn't do that those were in
my hands
did you hear that beautiful buzzing I'm
so sorry guys
oh
and I'm snuggling
oh smoothie smoothie you want to leave
the room because now I'm streaming
you want to stay I feel bad
um
it barely bothers you really but wait
when I turn on music it's gonna be a
noticeable hopefully
what was I saying how the wow doing why
am I not doing so well because
Tommy horde
um
but Wawa has [\h__\h] to do so
like streaming
uh I'm reading super chats yeah but I
have tea the only thing that like I
noticed all my my painkillers are
um
uh the date is
you know they're all uh I don't know
spoiled and I looked up you know how
serious you should take that of paying
with like medicine painkillers and I
don't know yeah they're all expired
thank you I forgot the word oh God why
am I feeling so hot
hot
a few months always fine yeah and then
but then I think most of mine were uh uh
more than a few months I think
um but yeah
it's okay
wait wait I'm what what music do we
maybe this one
oh yeah this one's nice
why don't you get your refills there's
no refills like normally
[Music]
um
I only ever have
painkillers
when I'm like for example I I
catch a really bad colder so when I go
to the doctor and then he's like all
right take this too and he gives me
painkiller for that thing
and then I ended I end up not really
using it
usually or I only use like one
I'm like really really
careful without taking too many
um
not even have a prescription not even
not even that bad
[Music]
painkillers for colds I don't know it's
just an example
oh
[Music]
you want to take a week off no
the hell
[Music]
yeah
you just finished on your project
and you feel like dying but suddenly
when you got into my stream you feel
like you're able to still live
shouldn't you feel like relieved from
finishing your project come on
be strong
drinks help with tummy hurt yeah so I
have one one cup in a no one one tea in
a normal cup for drinking now
and then I'm thinking ahead because I
got one tea and a thermos
uh stainless steel firmness cup so that
one should be good for later hopefully
and then I got some water
and some cookies
okay Key by the way I didn't say it
is
[Music]
hello
I just I did say it but I'm sure or I'm
just imagining it I also feeling it when
I don't say it might just be Auto
filling it
did you see the schedule I just uploaded
during the right before I started the
Stream
so you may have not seen that
um
basically now Super Chat reading
tomorrow
at night
1 am for me
so actually already Wednesday for me
Tuesday for n a
we have something that's
TBA it's a short stream
it's gonna be an hour
what kind of streams are always like an
hour long I wonder
[Music]
um
we no we is me I just sometimes say we
to feel to make you guys feel more
included
[Music]
um
getting the dough yeah
maybe time for some dough baby haven't
gotten the dough in a while
yeah when was my last stream
I guess the Pokemon unite thing was
somewhat sponsored
yeah
that's all I remember oh
Marathon
[Music]
following our way
we're now at like
one point
four nine five point eight
it's almost 1.496
so almost 4 000 delay
back in the day
you know the last time I did a marathon
was for a million
and that's a long time ago back then
marathons very easy
uh I don't know about now because I
haven't done one in a while I haven't
seen others do one in a while
um I waited for 1.5 to for the
opportunity because like in between
those are all just smaller numbers
didn't want to spam it
um even though each each 100K Milestone
was a struggle
um to reach
um but yeah so I don't know what to
anticipate but back in the day like even
with 10K subs left
it was
definitely impossible
normally like 5K was done in like 20 30
minutes
but nowadays I don't know we'll see how
it goes
it's still on it's still Wednesday until
Wednesday we can still get a bit closer
to it anyway
um
don't
you guys have to believe in it okay
what are we gonna do if you guys are
doubting that I can accomplish this
believe in it
we might be surprised
nobody has done it in a while guys we we
don't know
we might be surprised guys
and I don't know I'm doing it in
Japanese prime time so maybe some
Japanese Bros
will come to my rescue
and Korean Bros
um
you never know guys
untouched markets and stuff
[Music]
oh it's gonna be uh unarchived so I can
sing more songs and suffer more
let's see if this tea is ready I I
noticed they're selling the Christmas
tees in summer too
this is always like that or
so I bought
because I ran I just now in September I
finally ran out of my Christmas tea
stock
[Music]
um I just have one box
for two since Christmas season
um
and uh I didn't drink that all the time
until now but mixed it with some other
teeth
but now see it held up strong until now
now I checked and they they still have
Christmas tees in in the shelves in
September
oh
[\h__\h] that's
marvelous
that's not the one I sent
[Music]
like there's three different ones and I
sent two
um bales
but this one is the third one that I
didn't send and I didn't buy myself in a
long time oh
um
wow this one's I think it's um
but I think that one is like apple
Orange
[Music]
coming
yeah it's Apple Orange
uh cinnamon
[Music]
yeah and um uh
ah
[Music]
uh
and
what's Anis in English and it's
oh hey why did I stop tracking
[Music]
[Laughter]
and
hey this app doesn't want to work for me
or what
[Music]
I don't know
a niece
a niece they were all confused
ain't ain't a very a very Christmasy
what is that an herb
is that considered an herb
herb Urban kills annual plant
yeah it is
[Music]
a spice well aren't spices herbs too
huh
haha
yo
[Music]
um
so anyway uh yeah Marathon
who knows how long that will go but I'm
starting early in the day so
[Music]
let's pray for the best
foreign
[Music]
because we'll definitely not get done
today I won't be doing it that long
we've already we're already 20 minutes
in uh I have a limit for today three
hours because I have a meeting then
um
my voice sounds weird really I did
change mixer
um so
do I sound different I don't even like
everything's confusing me these days I
don't even know what my voice is anymore
I sound normal I sound the same okay
I really don't know anymore I'm so
confused I'm having like an existential
crisis
um
crisis yeah when you stream for so long
that you for some reason forget who you
are
[Music]
sometimes it do be like that and then on
Friday I I I really like
in my schedule Tuesday looked like a day
off to me and then I when I was making a
schedule I realized wait that's 1am for
me it's kind of still a Tuesday stream
does that mean I don't have a day off so
I was like okay let's just in case even
though Tuesday is a short stream just in
case you know let's keep Friday as a
joker
you know
and then Saturday we finally want to
tackle the GTA 4 DLCs
uh definitely finish the first one
and then on Sunday uh we were able to
um squeeze in another bubbles gate group
collab
originally I was just gonna do solo but
then it seemed like a good spot to
squeeze in another group collab because
after that I ca probably babo's gate
group is going on Hiatus for two weeks
because I'm I don't think I can play for
two weeks
[Music]
um
I think
[Music]
foreign
for two weeks
um
not vacation no no
this tea is so good
before we get started let me tell you
success story
[Music]
um today and like like two or three
nights ago
I think smoothie is calming down because
she I gave her dinner and then she did
not did not wake me up in the middle of
the night for breakfast
[Music]
and instead just waited until I was
awake to meow at me but especially today
she didn't even do that
she just went to her Kibbles she needed
her Kibbles I'm like what's going on
I made her breakfast anyway because she
was so good she was I made her wet food
I mean anyway because she was for once
not annoying the [\h__\h] out of me maybe
she understands that I'll give her
breakfast
even if she doesn't annoy the [\h__\h] out
of me
as I always did until now
[Music]
um
what are you talking about
[Music]
Doug what are you talking about
bro Tony will come over and she'll get
back into her bad habits soon thanks for
that no no no no no no no my mommy will
take care of my cats uh again during the
next trip
but I mean she also has very different
habits compared to me so I don't know
I don't know how they're gonna really
Act
she's gonna spoil them no no no no she's
not gonna spoil them
she's not the cat spoiling type if
anything they're getting a break from
being constantly pampered
by me sad
bubble gate on Steam deck oh
oh
well I wouldn't stream it but that's
okay because sometimes I think we
decided to just you know
some of us just don't stream it
sting
I could bring my steam deck
[Music]
huh
put that oh the controls
would that not be hard to see the UI
with the size right
I can connect the steam deck to a TV
though right can I
and then use the steam deck as the
controller
[Music]
yeah
like I could connect it to my hotel TV
to have a bigger screen for example
pretty much hinting at what you're doing
I mean I told you guys I'm going to
Japan
[Music]
before
put one on one together I mean I'm not
the thing is what I don't want to do is
how to say this
I don't want to how do you how do you
say this phrase correctly I don't want
to take you a fool what how do you say
this I don't wanna I don't think you
guys are stupid
and I think you guys deserve
to be treated
like you have more than one brain cell
take take you four fools
I don't want to trick you guys like that
I feel like
um my audience deserves to be
treated with respect and I don't want to
unnecessarily lie to you or hide things
from you
I hate that
so that's why I also I I mean certain
times I have to for example like I can't
like next week I'm not gonna put out a
schedule because I can't have people
know that obviously if I take that day
off then obviously I'm I'm traveling on
that day
well people can figure out what flight
I'm taking this and that
so
those kind of things
I kind of have to hide
but you all know what I'm doing
[Music]
yeah
but in any case if it is my choice
my on the mind control then I will
always tell you guys what's up I don't
see any like I don't think you guys are
stupid like even if I were to attempt
to lie to you I feel like you would even
figure it out
probably why if you don't then I would
anyway feel bad about having hidden
something from you
that I could have avoided
[Music]
yeah
I mean
anyway
[Music]
you have a budgie cute
I don't know I'm pretty stupid no don't
say that guys what
I don't I don't want you guys to be
taken for a fool and then thus I will
not do it
[Music]
how long did we take to realize it was
newer and not useful
not that long
you definitely immediately knew
something was off
good example man also that was
neat
it's creating content so that doesn't
count as me lying to you or anything
like that
and you well I was hoping I could
I could fool you for a while
as long as possible
[Music]
[Laughter]
well yeah you know something was off but
how could you have known that it was
such a genius plan of mine
turned myself into an AI
man I I have good stream ideas don't I
like man of course we're streaming every
day there have to be a lot of like
normal streams in between but every now
and then I'm just like a great content
creator okay
I come up with some genius [\h__\h]
I'm so proud of my anniversary stream
okay
so freaking proud I wish more people
could have seen it I will upload those
Vlogs separately because I think it will
get some more people to watch it maybe
yeah the pizza making stream the ironing
stream this and that I'm a genius I know
it damn I'm a genius
hey
[Music]
would love a separate upload okay
I I wonder if I could get them subtitled
to Japanese maybe at least for Japanese
viewers
um just like CC subtitles
let me let me make a note
question
for later about
titles
okay
[Music]
thank you bye bye
I'm with agree
bungee pretty soon no please
[Music]
more
Korean translation to okay I don't think
we have staff you know that translates
to Korean I would have to like
like commission from outside and I don't
really feel like doing that
yeah too complicated
just a paraglider portion that's got
over 100 confused I think I saw that
clip they clipped they they cut out a
little bit I think it wasn't like the
complete thing right
but yeah I thought yeah
um good advertisement for me
as long as they link the OG in the
but if they um
yeah from what I saw I think that that
they cut something but not much so it's
like it doesn't really leave you with
the desire to go to the original stream
anymore I think
I think that's important as a Clipper to
just for the sake of the streamer
to leave something out obviously to give
something some reason for the viewer to
go to the actual stream to check that
out
that that would be nice General as a
general guideline
um
but it's okay I'll I'll upload my Vlogs
maybe soon actually I guess
next week uh could be really good
for filling some days where I'm maybe
traveling or so
sup one minute Clips are best under one
minute clips
that's kind of short but I mean for
attention span they're good you know
[Music]
I'm just destroyed still
looking forward to the uploads thank you
oh yeah maybe we'll start reading super
trucks it's been half an hour
I'm just feeling so comfy right now man
I don't know my Pace today my piece
my piece
my piece my pace is an English word but
in Japanese you know it's a phrase they
like to use my base when when somebody
takes it easy at their own pace
[Music]
let's go on my my not my space my space
is [\h__\h] dead
hmm
there's certain things like that that
are English and they use it in Japanese
but I mean my place
I think would you say it like that in
English I'm so used to it in Japanese I
don't know if it's natural anymore like
I'm I'm going at my Pace that that 'll
very much English right but then there's
like
um
when someone's really energetic
uh one thing I remember is like high
tension
[Music]
someone is really high attention wait
instead see I don't even know anymore is
that a normal thing to say it's not
right not really
hi
attention
[Music]
hi yeah you would say high energy
but instead of high energy
they would say high tension
[Music]
that's so legendary how do you say let's
go in English
uh let's go
[Music]
I was so funny man that's such a long
long time ago meme
that was created a lot of people here
might not know the origin of that
who who doesn't remember that
this is like two and a half years ago if
not more
[Music]
but most of you are so
old school Baba fans you remember I
don't
I had my one of my first uh Japanese
senpai collabs
it was in Minecraft and everything was
falling apart
and then we just talked but somewhere in
there
she was like
let's go nothing you know and I'm like
let's go
[Music]
it was Among Us oh it was a mangas
you remember it better than me what the
[\h__\h]
uh
foreign
[Music]
what's going on
eh why why is why do you all see it
recently what's happening with this clip
going making rounds
are you guys just like
regularly training your Wawa memories
just in case I test you
always be ready
is this like a weekly thing for you guys
making sure you remember everything in
case I ask you a question because I ask
you so many questions
[Music]
foreign
there is no kfp quiz
maybe we gotta do kfp Jeopardy and you
guys are the contestants
[Music]
don't you guys already do that anyway as
a community without me behind my back
yeah you did didn't you
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't even don't even like invite me or
anything
so you don't even consider like telling
me about it or like inviting me to watch
it like you don't even care about me
hello I exist
[Music]
we don't want to buy you
I was not I did was not giving up
invitation
[Music]
man
man they don't know I exist
[Music]
no no no there is no Discord of course
there's a Discord maybe I should
advertise it again so you guys get a new
Rush of new members you haven't gotten a
new Rush of new members in a while have
you everybody join the kfp Discord
um I don't even know where you could
find the link nowadays is it like on
Reddit or so how do you even are you
guys like a closed community how do you
even enter the kfp Discord these days
where would you find it
just Google it
really
kfb fan Discord
uh whole life fan Wiki comes up with a
fan Discord list
ah nice ah
all right let's join
where is where is there join click
no
yeah okay guys so maybe maybe they need
some fresh meat guys if you're not in
the fan Discord Google fan Discord kfp
and then join the Kiara one they need
help for projects probably
[Music]
[Laughter]
then you can be included in projects
like the ones that show off on my
anniversary and my birthday
and you can help out with those
[Music]
but I hate Discord well okay fine then
don't need to join
[Music]
you're bad communicating oh no problem
hey why did I stop moving again that's
not cool
[Music]
that's weird
it's not even really crashing
oh
did I say I was gonna Read Super chants
[Music]
why do I should I just go into the
anniversary Super Chat so where should I
should I like
should I tackle the big ones but I think
we still have like some smaller ones
right
oh thank you uh from Holland Miami
monkey screams ah okay
I guess we can how far is that away from
what I actually want to read oh just one
stream oh
okay okay okay
so foreign
[Music]
can you read this probably not on the
phone but
then then
[Music]
and I'm planning to put up the
um
the window again so you guys can see
what I'm doing what I'm looking at okay
[Music]
better not be anything there that I
shouldn't be showing guys
whatever something that will embarrass
me
[Music]
um
you can correct me if I missed something
or so okay wonderful isn't this wow I'm
such a professional super jar reader
Discord popping off really is it did it
work did people join did you get new
recruits I just want to help you guys
you know
I'm thinking surely you need a new
influx
it did
a whole new chickens come back there
surely you guys were bored these days
right you need new people
[Music]
professorita hasn't read the single
super jet so far wow wow wow this was
warm-up okay a professional
Sports person will always warm
themselves up before they get into it
otherwise it's dangerous you will injure
yourself if you do this professionally
you gotta be very careful that you don't
injure yourself you know
I'm just being professional here
[Music]
so
okay here we go
[Music]
here good to know Super Chat reading
wasn't start it just started
see I waited for you
just waiting for you
okay
I guess I could start now
[Music]
should I start
I guess I'll start
I guess I'll start okay
[Music]
foreign
oh you don't see it you don't see the
icon I can take it for one
and even says welcome back from the
harsh
that's forgiving wild Central
I can't even begin to imagine how you
survived such grueling conditions the
lack of Wi-Fi alone would have would
have me shivering your mother's backyard
must have been excuse me it must have
been one scary place well it was yeah it
was terrifying it yeah I was so scared
but but but I needed to remind myself of
my uh hero heroism and my
um yeah my skills and my survival
instincts and with that it was no
problem
it was no big issue at all
the snakes there was there were snakes
everywhere yeah
[Music]
my mom was like so
so
uh ruthless towards the snakes
the probably the Instinct of protecting
her child she was like
smashing them like she would step on
them but not to step on them she would
like step and then like
[Music]
you know with her foot she was like
how to say
[Music]
um
like make mashed potatoes out of them
basically
[Music]
yeah grind yeah yeah and I'm like Mommy
that's maybe a little bit too much but
then I got kind of inspired by her
eventually
and I did something
[Music]
that surprised even myself
I
because she doesn't want them right
because they're like a pest for her
garden
so it's okay to
kill them right
I
I'm
I maybe put one into the fire
[Music]
and the moment I did it I felt so bad
and I'm like oh [\h__\h] did I really I'm so
sorry wait I'm a monster I'm a [\h__\h]
monster
foreign
is this will I get canceled for saying
this I was a bit worried about it
[Music]
or is Slug as long as it's a slug is it
okay
[Music]
why is bouquet why is it okay just be we
should care even about the Slugs and
then the noodle
um worms and and the bugs like man we
kill so many ants every day by stepping
on them don't you feel bad like man
I don't understand why we make
difference there
[Music]
we should we should feel bad about all
of that
think about fauna man
[Music]
okay okay the ants maybe the ants is
where we stop
but don't you feel bad about I don't
know
I don't know man
[Music]
you wouldn't want to kill a butterfly
right
[Music]
because butterfly is so beautiful that's
that's your bias so then we also
shouldn't kill any like caterpillars and
worms our pills are so cute
hey
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah anyway I felt really bad but
um
I felt also also very powerful in that
one second
before I started regretting it and
feeling like a monster and not being
able to look at myself in the mirror
anymore because I couldn't recognize
myself anymore
[Music]
for that just one Split Second I felt
powerful
uh
um
playing retrospective I can't redo
Franklin and Margaret I showed by the
way I showed the Vlog
to my bro
he was laughing so much too he really
liked the Vlogs
um and he laughed really hard at the
moment where Franklin pooped
yeah yeah and my mom is so happy with
the Vlog because I mean it's her garden
so you know I was originally the
original plan was really
I wanted to didn't I even discuss this I
don't know on stream that I really
wanted to go uh to challenge myself for
real for real to go camping in the wild
because I I don't like
um camping videos and I do like survival
videos most of those camping videos
though I see in like normal camping
places
um but yeah I wanted to try it but then
you know when discussing with my friends
too they also told me like well you know
you can't really like
legally just go into the woods and Camp
there and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
there must be some Woods that allow it
like I mean that's like
I guess the danger of like making an
open fire and then burning the whole
Forest is like
they don't want to take that risk but
it's so boring like how can you go
proper camping like going camping to a
camping uh spot thingy designated place
is like it can't be nice but like if you
just want to go
like camping in a lake for example but
if you want to do the actual capping
experience
it's kind of lame like you need to be in
the forest otherwise it's not the real
camping experience you know what I mean
I feel like those are two different
camping experiences camping at a camping
ground and camping like for real for
real
out there
in in the woods yeah
[Music]
there's gotta be actual places in Austin
right seriously I don't know I mean
there might be but like generally it's
not allowed so I was like well that
makes it a little bit more complicated
complicated I don't want to just do this
video in the camping ground that would
be so boring
and then then I I skipped something not
me
sorry I snapped at you
this is not the one one Whatever reading
this one now
what was I going to say
um
yeah and then I was trying to figure out
what could I do and I realized my mom
she has this huge Garden
and there's like she told me before like
I the parts that I've seen of her garden
are by far not the full extent of her
garden she has a huge
huge part behind that that's like
not like she didn't like get rid of all
the bushes and trees like you can't
really walk through there like it's
really really
like fully grown like
it's like a mess like you can't really
do anything there you have to start like
by getting rid yeah it's like a jungle
it's wild so I thought I could go there
but the part that I actually used for
the video
was just
because
right in the beginning when I started
filming the the Nettles they threw me
off
and I was like you know I I'll say I'll
stay where there is not so much of that
shitty
[\h__\h]
can't even take five steps into this
because there's Nettles everywhere
for [\h__\h] sake
um so just I just took a nice looking
spot that was
um had you know that looked good
and we're still close to
yeah
yeah I mean everything else sell yeah I
could have gone deeper
[Music]
um
and they you say they prevent rheumatism
if they string sting you but do they
really
there was a brick wall ah but that's
just like a random brick wall that's
just it's not even like
on this like on the edges of my mom's
yard
no it's like in the middle of it like
it's just like a random uh like ruin
yeah
which is actually kind of nice like she
she I think wants to make use of it
[Music]
um
yeah she just didn't like take it apart
yet um
the mom yard
my old neighbor drinks novelty yeah
natal tea is a thing really healthy
right
okay first tea is drunken
feeling good right now except I'm
feeling a bit hot
yeah yeah I am has some ruins I guess
do you plan on doing more of those type
of Vlogs I wanna yeah maybe
I wonder if I can do one in
Japan but like in the future when
traveling I I wanna uh I would like to
try doing stuff like that
um
yeah I mean I got a really expensive
nice camera that's literally for that
purpose so
um
would be good if I could use that more
[Music]
where was I
um
thank you for the rest of the chat hi
Tanto my birthday was yesterday and I
was wondering if you could tell me a
German pun or joke to say to my
german-speaking friend oh man I'm so
late I love seeing who grounded my bad
jokes it makes my day and I figure one
in German would be even better thank you
a German pun or joke
I
I know
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh wow I'm you you're catching me off
guard I'm absolutely like
brain empty
Deutsche Deutsche
Deutsche uh
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h] what kind of joke is that
[Music]
why is everybody saying the hunter one
never heard of that
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
these jokes are stupid
um
[Music]
oh my God what
oh okay
huh what a weird joke
two eggs meat one asks the other why are
you so hairy
that's where I thought this joke was
going a weird Direction but then the
other one says shut up I'm a kiwi
[Music]
what
oh
you know in German we say
um directly translated
or like I mean this pay please the bill
please but you could translate it as
number
numbers please
um you know just has a different meaning
too
so here's a joke that's that relates to
that
again a customer to waiter numbers
please or check please and waiter is
eight seven six five wow
wow
[Music]
huh oh
ah
thank you
what oh
I like this one it's also stupid but I
like it
um
Rome Rome guy
Ro Roman Empire guy
goes into a bar
makes a peace sign like two fingers up
and says five beers please
get it
[Music]
because the tool looks like a V and the
V is five and yeah
whoa
whoa that's the finger
that's a finger
okay
[Music]
um
oh my God
[Music]
yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
two two magnets meet one says
this works better in German but what
should I oh oh yeah what should I wear
today but like in German putting clothes
on and like attracting another magnet
you know it's like the same word
refuses in
[Music]
I like this one here let if you wanna I
don't know if you want to use it in
German or translate it to uh
English for your friend but this is now
my winner
this is the winner we have a winner
[Music]
it doesn't work in English but you know
there you go it works in in nice and
German good luck explaining it to wear
or attract exactly
um
man haven't seen so many jokes in a
while
so thank you very much
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know why you need these German
jokes but
hope your German friend is happy
with this one hope you didn't hear it
before
probably not because I haven't heard any
of these jokes before ever
yeah yeah love to you
I'm so it's facing the pinky I'm gonna
miss the anniversary stream pain so I'll
say it now thank you for being such a
massive ray of sunshine for me for the
past three years you've helped me
through quite a few very sad times and
inspired me in a lot of ways you're a
cool bird no you're wrong I'm a hot bird
you're so wrong how could you be so
wrong blank calm down
thank you
thank you so much man
[Music]
what a chat
yeah anyway
thank you I hope you were able to match
your VOD because I'm really really
really really really really proud of the
um anniversary stream like honestly I
was so worried
about putting something together
because like it was close to so many
other things that I was working on like
my birthday and my album and this and
that and I didn't have that much time
and I was quite under time pressure and
I wanted to think of cool original ideas
and you know
it was a risk to take
um and not much time to edit either and
you know you know not much time to
record either
but I'm really glad I could do something
special because already with my with my
birthday streams
I mean for me like making a cake on a
handcam stream and all that that was
special to me too
um but I wanted to like
you know
make it even more special ideally and I
couldn't do 3D Stream So it ah
three years you know I really feel like
I would like to do 3D streams for these
occasions I don't know why I can still
not do it like you know but
yeah it's just like rough to
think of you know something really
special that is like suitable for such a
special occasion like it really has to
be special you know
special special the special type of
special hot Tech producers are overrated
don't say that I haven't
gone properly yet like besides my 3D
debut
so
I I would like to experience this it's
my Birthright
since I was born in whole life
it's my Birthright I see it as my
Birthright
hmm
[Music]
and it's like you know the things I
would be doing in the in the 3D stream
is like
one of my biggest like
reasons and
goals for joining whole life
you know dancing singing I want to let
all of that out there
so
um
[Music]
man I need to you know Duolingo keeps on
reminding me that I still have Duolingo
on my phone
I really need to use my Duolingo
subscription to at least practice some
Korean
I mean if I'm already paying it I might
as well use it right that green bird
it's it's kind of like threatening it's
honestly scary the reminders are
honestly scary because I saw that like
uh when the green bird gets ignored
who's it Lily or so
next is like someone else who reminds
you like hey you you ignored the the
green bird now here am I
like well it's actually scary
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I'm a window
and window so funny like I know what you
mean but M Window I'm a window I have a
window
I always thought I was a bridge but now
I'm a window
on The Window Man
um on
and window
[Music]
Wawa
I'm your window
oh I'm gonna win in your book am I
just come on cartoon Kevin thank you
[Music]
oh that was I need to I still need to
figure out which ones which and that's
not it
um there it is
[Music]
oh thank you
I'm glad you're playing it too
a logical Paradox
[Music]
Moonstone oh wait
we were just talking about it
wait what
I thought 4 300 Euros what just sense
when if you win
the trivia quiz your prices to give me
money
what I
I am now thinking very fondly of this
quiz
[Music]
the rules where you had to give Kiana
the prize money
oh and you actually received 40 free
Euro for winning did you guys like put
together a little bit of money was it
like every participant give like one
Euro or something
[Music]
no you didn't pay them
we have reverse salary now reverse
prices it's it's just going by kfp Logic
yeah
you know the rules and so do I am
[Music]
that's how it works
reverse price
so if you take part in it you're
automatically agreeing to send me a
super chat in case you win
that's funny
[Music]
um
that was imayonda noga
Hotline Miami 2 selfing in Miami
oh no no
no high end I was so happy thinking I
wasn't so far behind
oh man
you fooled me you freaking fooled me
I mean it's not your fault but
yeah okay so
okay I'll be fast now because it would
be nice if we could like
get there at some point
I'll be fast
no tangents time
I know it sounds incredible
this should be
yeah
okay
[Music]
thank you for
two no oh uh kind of like two what's
going on that's so many what the [\h__\h]
and like two red ones in total I think
my mom YouTube cans for representing
kafi at the convention oh
oh the Canadian one right the Canadian
one
adding the leads link to get him a kiss
a birthday song in his shoe aha
I need another birthday song for Pat
top of these songs wait did I already
sing Pat the birthday doll
I think I already sang it for him
I'm gonna read them and just don't read
the midi chill I'm trying to combine the
ones that he sent so that it makes sense
but it doesn't really make sense
actually just in this case I did for Pat
okay okay okay okay so that good thank
you that is done
and okay says I don't know what day this
will be red on but today I get to watch
my beloved Oshi scream
her head off playing Hotline Miami while
I eat some cake
what cake and there's no other way I I'd
want to spend my birthday thanks for
everything Kiara I love you
and also I've been wondering what
exactly does it mean when you wish us a
happy birthday in our shoe and in our
pants too
um
as fluffy timkins usually have neighbor
true
oh well Stream Point of View stream
pineapple yay thank you triple chocolate
you should try it Austrian if you like
chocolate cakes
that question should not be asked Yeah
Boy the thing is it's uh you know German
Birthday song actually
uh so you know what I'll sing it
partially in German for you so maybe you
understand that I'm not just making up
[\h__\h]
and
happy birthday
it's true
happy eggs
Maybe
[Music]
your birthday is today
it was a while ago happy birthday to you
I guess there was no shoe happy birthday
[Music]
to you
you are an important
link of the community
[Music]
I know what you doing
I know where you're sleeping
I know
[Music]
it all
hmm
what something weird
[Music]
happy birthday
happy birthday in your house too
[Music]
but you know I'm just
just trying to get to your birthday
party
and you didn't invite me so I'm inviting
myself
got a problem with that
anyway thank you guys you crazy
chickens thank you all of you thinking
for being such a chat trying to help
everyone out and
man he was making it apparently into a
red one anyway but you were you were
helping him so sweet so sweet it's just
the sweetest
[Music]
thank you although the POV love not a
good username but it's not Pinky
[Music]
nice seeing you at the panel tension oh
hope you enjoyed seeing the province
where pineapple pizza was invented
wait I feel like we like talked about
you know Canada invented pineapple pizza
which already shocked me but we were
actually even in the right province
wow uh we have some
some really deep connection
we we should marry
me in Canada we should marry Canada
marry me
those pen Liners in the center show were
intense pretty sure I nearly caught one
of their loose glow sticks sitting next
to them
they were intense but I loved seeing
that man it's it's great to have people
like that in the room because they make
other people maybe feel less shy about
cheering as well yeah
so thank you for being there thank you
for checking it out I don't know if you
were already planning to come to the
convention even if we weren't going to
be there but
um in any case I'm so glad you were
there and helped fill out the the panel
room because I was really concerned
about that hmm
my name is Canada oh really
I'm sure guys
now I have converted into a Canadian I'm
I'm not marrying each person I'm
Marrying the country
The Entity I don't know man it's not
really the same guys I'm not marrying
you
they had to make an overflow room at the
last minute I don't really understand
that at all like what does that mean
[Music]
they didn't use it though did they was
that supposed to be like what was gonna
be behind the the side wall
can you Bridal carry Canada
no Canada's Bridal Carry Me
obviously
foreign
but I'm glad so many people were able to
be there yeah really happy Canada
you and me we still have so much to
experience together
game eight nine one zero dancing you
were also there
the front row let's go no you owes you
don't need uos just any any pen light
will do I don't know no no no thank you
for the pinky don't read if you're tired
I'm not tired but I don't really have
you know time but I'll read it anyway
the splash party day one refund was
outrageous
I bought a ticket specifically to see
you perform and how dare they give me my
money back I'll spend it on you one way
or another they can't stop me oh my God
so aggressive help me he's forcing money
onto me help me
thank you I don't know
thank you so much
can't stop me
that's right you do your thing you do
what you want to do they can't force
this on you and you know you don't want
to be refunded you don't you wanna you
wanna give them the money hell yeah
you gave it to the right person
Jackson FB thank you for the pinky
Fibonacci panel was so so great thank
you for coming to Canada to treat your
lovely pfk
thank you for noticing
our pineapples you are one of
the pine pineapple
[Music]
PF the whole pfk thing
maybe he did do it on purpose no he was
pretty clueless overall so he probably
didn't do it on purpose
no not nipple no pineapple
the people pineapple people pineapple
[Music]
[Laughter]
does that sound not so good
do we not want to put this in the
dictionary
it was so funny man seeing free
pineapple I saw free pineapples at least
three pineapples fresh pineapples you
guys are so cute for doing that
pineapple Superior this is a superior
Apple
the best apple
it's also the Earth Apple
in German we say Earth Apple uh in
Austria we say Earth Apple to the
cocktofel but actually I say toffer
but yeah some austrians will say Earth
Apple
to potato yeah
but pineapple is the best apple
that's why you said that in the Vlog no
actually I didn't even think about that
in the moment I was just like trying to
sound
like some nature
uh
uh like you know someone who knows
things
and and like someone no like personally
was trying to sound like I know what I'm
talking about and partially I was trying
to sound like I made new discoveries
like groundbreaking discoveries
and that was supposed to be a ground big
breaking Discovery I think
[Music]
I don't know what I was doing I was I
bullying so much and I felt so awkward
rambling to myself partially my mom was
like close by and listening
and made me feel awkward too
but she was she she praised me for being
able to just continuously ramble
endlessly go on and on and on and on
the mountain yes the mountain mountain
Mama they say Mountain Mama West
Virginia she's the Mountain Mama
[Music]
ramble troll
yeah I was I was embarrassed to send cow
carrot on my rambling footage but I cut
some parts out anyway and in the end
I figured that
if if edited the right way all the
rambling will end up being pretty good
so
there will be useful things there
[Music]
the Vlog has a different tone when you
imagine Mama 22 meters behind Kiara the
entire time
[Music]
oh
that movement you Canadian were you at
the panel
imagine us doing a q a in a Canadian
convention and then this guy showing up
on the mic and then asking a question
like this and I'm like well that's not
what we expected in our q a
h
imagine
[Music]
would be funny though
how to bless food so it can increase
someone's luck you can either feed Bijou
coal
or that she only write a page of the
Canterbury Tales on your back
what why will you do one of these to
give this food to narissa what none of
this makes any sense to me I don't feel
any connection and to anything in this
one what
huh what does anything have to do with
anything here
[Music]
you lost me you absolutely lost me try
again
try again but differently
think it's funky things to the pinky
just want to say thank you for the panel
it was my first Con in this hobby really
and even though I mostly just attended
the panel it was tons of fun getting to
see you two and meetings on kfp I hope
pfk will get another chance to see you
there again
I hope so too yeah I I'm I'm happy you
got a chance
yeah the few Canadians actually
surprisingly more than I thought
according to these super chats few
Canadians wait Julia
Canada
wait you were there
the [\h__\h]
you only go to car shows
[Music]
oh my God wait did I forget that you're
from Canada well so many people from
Canada what the [\h__\h] what was I gonna
say oh yeah I'm I'm glad we got a chance
to be there and
um
all my Canadian Bros and
girls
and Rhymes man got a chance
but I wish we could have done the mean
and green
foreign
I call myself a hoe too come on
girlfriends call each other hoes who man
you're such a hoe yeah no you you're
such a hoe
[Music]
I mean I I don't do that I don't call my
best friend a hoe
but I know there's some people who do
that
and it's acceptable in that situation
[Music]
especially in German I would it would
not feel appropriate to me to call my
best friend
[Laughter]
[Music]
ship that we have a thing we have a very
close friendship but we just don't
like that I guess
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah in German it's
um that
[Music]
it's so much worse in German you think
so
where was I
[Music]
um
increasing CA statistics let's go let's
go thanks
to Phoenix thank you thank you
green wielder thanks for the pinky my
bad we'll Super Chat more sorry I wasn't
there but Toronto is more than 3 300
kilometers away from me thank you for
saying it in kilometers the one distance
thingy that I actually know but even
then it's hard to imagine not exactly a
trip I
I I
can maybe it's a can typo yeah V is next
to the C
can make on a whim
that's okay
you wanted to it's the font that counts
it's the thought that counts
uh sorry I don't know what's wrong with
me
I apologize
um I am ashamed
[Music]
English language
so funny
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry blame it
on the team if it's spicy drink some tea
so true
[Music]
anyway thank you for super chatting you
know maybe I'll see this uh you know it
makes up for you not being at the
convention
no it's fine though it's fine that's a
long long distance maybe maybe one time
we
are able to visit a place that's closer
to you I hope
but you never know so maybe next time
we're
far away but still like close by far
away like reasonably far away like
instead of you know 10 000 kilometers
maybe maybe at some point you should
accept the three thousand kilometers
because maybe we'll never gonna be
anywhere close by I don't know where
close by really is
um I don't know you know and you know
you know you know Midwest
[Music]
because maybe maybe
narissa will inspire Midwestern
conventions to invite us hey I have
three DMS where are they coming from oh
Wayne
[Music]
choreography okay this and that this and
that
[Music]
boom
okay guys chill she messaged me not you
[Music]
well
well no those are two different things
and choreography is my sleep talking
choreography update
what the funk it's not fair
no she messaged me
now
[Music]
Patsy Danielson iron Citrus Danish and
jilliance and Jackson another good
username
I like that name it's funny I don't even
understand it but it's cute zesty slime
thank you
[Music]
for the recipe that's an expensive
swimsuit maybe I could buy a Louis
Vuitton swimsuit from that
hmm
thank you I went swimming Yesterday by
the way I did my swimming reps
right before the Tommy Port came so that
was a big brain big brain
um
but I was a little bit more out of
breath than usually but usual but I
still did like my
my average laps
like a little bit more did you use it to
cut yeah yeah
this link I I have like two
deep cut swimsuits and then a couple of
bikinis and I still feel a bit more
comfortable in the swimsuits than in the
bikinis so oh
[Music]
still covers more than the bikinis do
ironically
yeah
I gotta buy a new one
a new sporty swimsuit
I wanna
hmm as soon as fit the body more and
lowers the chance of water no actually
not though like I noticed
um the swimsuits make me look
fatter
because
uh
let me show you
[Music]
down
because where's my mouse here
uh huh
okay side view
I'm using my mouse so
maybe I shouldn't use my mouse okay this
is my arm
my hand
okay
this oh [\h__\h] you don't even see all of
it
okay let's see let's say this is my
actual body and then the swimsuit
like here it will stay where it should
be
[Music]
but here okay I have a v cut in the back
too
but it ends like here I think and then
it goes like this
it doesn't adjust to my very thin
beautiful waste
yeah let's just stretches probably it's
too small then
because there's not enough fabric there
for it to like you know
you know what I mean I guess it's too
small
um
so when I look at myself from the side
I'm like wait was I really that fat and
then I put my hand
here to push it down and I realized oh
okay no I'm not that bad there's like
still like so much air there
um
yes it doesn't fit properly
can't handle the dumpy
yeah it's like difficult to find the
right
size and the right cut that's why in
theory I guess bikinis should
be better
because that can't happen to you with
the keys
[Music]
this is freaking me out my my curtain is
freaking me out
ah where was I
uh this
yeah
possessed yeah
[Music]
okay where was I uh space wonderful
donation oh wait spanking time did they
give you a kiss more there you go
[Music]
yeah now right now I don't mind putting
my head into the water especially
foreign
[Music]
um thank you soon I gotta write this one
is
please don't sue me I forgot to pay what
was the qmo attacks about
oh remember thank you
thank you so much it's okay I forgive
you you you're you're not you're not
late or anything I think
like European Austrian visa thing ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you are right to pay me
you will not be thrown into jail none of
you will be thrown into jail good job
except you will you will be thrown into
jail because that wasn't a tax payment
hmm
uh
[Music]
looking for the top Junction
hello
everyone
[Music]
isn't that what the membership is for no
that's for you paying your salary to me
or you know you know you know how it
works and that's that's a different
thing that's for you being able to enter
Europe
[Music]
what's next
is it uh
[Music]
wait what is next
Minecraft oh that should be over quickly
yeah
[Music]
also from Canada
tomorrow's my birthday here
's tencho
Canada the living example of why we
should never give up on our dreams my
gift to myself and to my fellow Jenkins
is a smile on the face for the of the
number one Idol who Knights are way even
though what
sweet and so selfless what
[Music]
you're so sweet I love you
cheeky burp eh cheeky
what am I being
tricked I see nothing cheeky here
oh cheeky for giving me the gift instead
of yourself maybe
um
[Music]
thank you so much
you're so good we shall swing don't let
your dreams be dreams
[Music]
I hope you had a wonderful birthday and
I hope that all your following birthdays
will be beautiful too and that you can
spend them with kfp
in your pocket
and me on your TV screen or pc screen
whatever
um
foreign
[Music]
um
sometimes I accidentally save them
somewhere else
[Music]
now where is it
ah Maybe
[Music]
thank you
that that I replace something
[Music]
there it is
yeah
I'm so happy in that roomie again yay
it's because she liked my
outfit so much
[Music]
and I have to use it immediately but you
don't even barely see the full beauty of
it in this
small cut
hmm
shame Jacob's monkey Duncan Brandon
thank you
for the pinky oh okay you're not saying
goodbye okay hey Kiana
unfortunately this will be my last Super
chat for a while sadly I've spent all my
Super Chat funds on pre-ordering 50
copies POV really
I need to wait a while before I send
again I promise I won't sculpt the other
chickens when they come in love Wawa
I did you like really
you didn't get that many for real right
eh
you saw receipts
[Music]
I believe you
and what
fifth how much was one album
[Music]
I don't even know the price
foreign
[Music]
200 400 400
wait
two
wait twenty fifty wait 20.
[Music]
yeah I came
[Laughter]
oh my God it's so much it broke my brain
wait Brendan you're absolutely insane
one pound
[Music]
you saved a lot on shipping you saved
did you get free shipping or what
oh my God thank you thank you what the
[\h__\h]
what Brendan
then
[Music]
Brandon
what the [\h__\h]
I are you okay
when are you
what are you doing with all these
are you gifting them to people or
helping
[Music]
Brendan will make this home a success
tiling his wall
you're gonna listen to all of them oh
yeah yeah and it might be different
songs on each one well I'm going to see
if any kids be missed the window that's
so sweet yeah because there's always
like people who maybe can't make it in a
like specific time frame and they just
miss it or they become fans afterwards
[Music]
they're so sweet
thank you so much for the insane insane
the support
inside
[Applause]
[Music]
should I DS Myself by the way
is it too much S I can do that like I'm
still like I don't know like about all
these settings you know
[Music]
how do I
I forgot how to do it ah there
there's something called a DS sir guys
here
um
see
oh
see it's
some more s
less as
generally I guess but wow I can barely
hear myself like it turned me down
generally
it's like
um
generally I think it's more comfortable
if you turn it off a bit more but it's
also it gives you a clear sound I guess
I don't know
[Music]
I don't know what I'm doing
I asked
snack
yeah whatever sounds so important I
think
[Music]
anyway holy [\h__\h] and wait did I even
read the whole thing because you say I
promise I won't scalp the other two yes
I read it love Brandon
love
Brandon
oh my God I can't even like how do I
even thank you appropriately thank you
thank you
thank you soon
[Music]
just remember me
threatening you better remember me
no you remember me you better remember
me
I guess out you will definitely remember
me now
I left the permanent dent on your bank
account
I will remember you
but you might regret
you might regret me remembering you
eventually
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man crazy crazy chickens crazy
chickens but this is like such an
honestly it's just such an idol
Idol fan thing to do like an idol
world like when I was still like uh
you know big into Idols this was quite a
normal thing
especially for like AKB because like
yeah you know the system do you
like for AKB groups it's like if you buy
CDs you get like a vote ticket or
something
inside the CD and then you can like yeah
[Music]
it gives your favorite Oshi a vote and
then they'll be higher in the rankings
and then if they're they're higher in
the rankings then they like they get
into the like promotional group
[Music]
uh for mvs and all that because there's
too many members to put them all into
into the MPS if you're really lucky you
get like you know
important
top seven or so
yeah this and that
and then even even for like hello
project where this wasn't a thing
often for the CDs you also got like
handshake
ticket uh thingies in the CDs or just
even without that they would often buy a
lot of them but yeah often it's for
handshake event so that you get more
entries am I officially an Isle fan now
it was definitely an idol fan thing to
do
based
I I was hoping I could put like meet and
greet tickets into my CD but that didn't
work out
[Music]
I do remember like suggesting it didn't
work out man sad
um
thank you for the pinky ah I read this I
read it I think just in the pre-chat
yeah yeah oh sorry to make you
misunderstand oh no misunderstanding
corner I had really good experience in
at Cafe in Vienna I enjoyed punch Cup oh
the pink cake right
I don't even like the pink one because
it has alcohol taste I think
another is oh my God you ate so many I
just didn't enjoy dessert when I was in
Korea forgive me please so that's what
you meant if you don't like dessert you
just don't like them in Korea really
I'm sure Korea has great desserts too
but ours are just very everything's so
sweet
hey I'm so happy you like
that kind of shine
did you eat it
there's like several several like
variations of what they will serve it
with there's like a darker purple plum
thingy sauce or there could be
um the apple sauce
do you remember what you had it was
you also tried Cashman nice
[Music]
the one oh okay yeah that one's really
good but next time if you get a chance
maybe you can find the one with the the
um
the plum plum sauce thingy
that one's also really good with vanilla
ice cream oh that's something I usually
don't see kaisersman with vanilla ice
cream but it worked like I couldn't see
it working I like to eat like pancakes
with vanilla ice cream you know and
Crepes and all that
mmm
so much sugar yeah it's gonna be
mistress
swimsuit reallocation fund hopefully you
get a new favorite yeah the the old one
that I had that was actually it was
doing the same thing with my back
[Music]
actually I'll I'll try to get a bigger
size next time then
hmm it was also like straightening out
my back and making me look thicker what
the hell
Santiago Martin thank you for the red
have a nice weekend you look prettier
than yesterday but not as much as
tomorrow
yeah we have a chicken that can see into
the future
you know how I will look like tomorrow
[Music]
private to me
apparently very pretty
one hour of violets oh no [\h__\h] thank you
to Santiago Martin
um
oh yeah this one didn't I read it live
I did I did I did thank you so much wait
did you see it
you must have seen it by now
did you sweater did you see
[Music]
you're only October the lady I spoke to
was open she remembered
why were we kind they were so kind we
weren't the kind ones
we were just like lost and confused and
I tried to be kind of like I was very
open and excited
[Music]
see don't you feel very connected to Me
Now by going to a place that I have been
to talking to people that have talked to
me got a special bond now
yeah
once you've been there you have to tell
me an update about how it was
[Music]
from the bucket ah it's you huh
are you sure guys I didn't read this
before because I remember talking about
your your profile picture
[Music]
the least power social moment
many more to go I live I fry I live
again Viva La Canada oh [\h__\h] I really
need to wait wait wait wait where is
members anniversary yeah
[Music]
switch
27th oh [\h__\h] okay guys keep on reminding
me so I can upload to the next [\h__\h]
we're gonna have some new
memory emotes in the chat soon guys like
remember badges
[Music]
I don't know which one yet
I don't know maybe we'll make a vote
somebody will always be unhappy though
if it ended up not being what they voted
for foreign
yeah I have a few options
I don't even remember all of them it's
been too long
say
and we have the nice that's what my Once
a Night
biased may I say
but
now that I have the alter Kiara outfit
the nights actually fit that very well
where do I have that like
I don't even know where our place those
files
[Music]
what did you name the files do you
remember I could look for the file name
where could it be
I need to pee that rhymed let's go
yippee
[Music]
foreign
we'll just send them again
[Music]
Maybe
I don't know where they are
[Music]
yeah well you'll send it to me again and
I'll choose
wooden Knights also fit your color dress
yeah yeah
um I'll look at it again on the side
where was I oh yeah acrylic thank you
many more to go indeed I hope you'll
reach the final
outfit
thank you for your support so far I hope
you'll continue supporting me down
puppet reborn
space
elephants with a pinky keep up the hard
work now you
thank you thank you for your support
Evans L thank you
what what happened actually wait this is
weird oh it's because the stream was
already over right that's why he felt
like he could send that I didn't even
like think anything about it for a
moment
[Music]
[Laughter]
this was very very out of character for
you
okay wait I caught up I think like in
terms of you know until the anniversary
because I read the other part of Miami
one I caught up
all
okay good
now we're reaching the sappy
sappy endless but I need to
oh I've been drinking so much
[Music]
milk
thank you
[Music]
foreign
cookie
[Music]
I sent them hmm
ah
[Music]
one
how can I decide
thank you
[Music]
but you gotta look at them small too
all right
small
smaller
it's my heart a smaller chicken why
smaller smaller chicken
the in small I think the RGB one stands
out the most and the bestest
to be honest
but
[Music]
that I'm the one still kind of works
well I think
because uh
the one before that is basically it's
almost the same pose just without the
armor so it looks like an upgrade but
not very noticeable
you want the armor one
let's do a pull
please save RGB for four years will they
be around then I hope so
I guess it could be four years yeah
it could be like the ultimate
Enlightenment state
of chicken
um
foreign
[Music]
wait let me think logically
what year what year is this gonna be
the
fourth year
[Music]
free oh okay
three years then this is gonna be the
fourth year
and this one is just a cute honestly it
looks like a trophy so I'm gonna put it
like
[Music]
next to the golden Jago
takuma can you put this on the like a
trophy trophy
um thingy like Diego
I want to put it somewhere
hmm
probably up here would be good
I don't know
it's hard to hard to choose
to we earn that if we're good chickens
hmm maybe
all right
cleaning up
for sure
[Music]
I forgot what they looked like they look
cute
all right it's not much more time left
so let's try to
get into this
[Music]
starting with
um
thank you for changing my tears of
sadness to tears of joy
[Music]
that reminds me of a Wonder Girl song
and for shining a light into my dark
little world for these past four years
he took my sad song and made it better
you're so sweet so you're robbed
oh
you're in the way
oh let me put you here
yeah
uh tears of kingdom
is it a reference
is it huh
perfect spot perfect spot looks good
there
kinda you were making a joke
polished with gravy yeah
I'm a bird lost what no no I didn't lose
this is just like the the this is the
loser so I'm putting it there
to not feel like it lost anyway thank
you so much to the rock thank you for
being with me for such a long time three
years like man I feel like most of my
audience is just like
people who have been here for a long
time like at least two years
thank you
mwah I hope you will be here
forever
with me otherwise I would be very sad
and happy free wait did I give him a
kissing guys keep on forgetting Jim
Tracy thanks for the red super chat
happy
Peppa it's hard to believe that it's
already been three years of streams
three years of music and three years of
memories time sure flies when you're
having fun much love the best OCR
chicken could ask for thanks for all you
do no
for being the best chicken I could ever
ask for thank you for your support you
you are so sweet always I love you
thank you
the best
I love you
day one sort of lurker hey coming out of
the Shadows
thank you guys thank you members for the
member messages
uh I will you know since there's so many
like red and pinks you know I wish I
could spend like 10 minutes on every
single one
but you know I gotta be business woman
so I'll be a bit more faster but I I
feel much much gratitude to every single
one of these okay just so you know
ultimate MK too I'm fine thanks for the
rainbow
breaks out the microphone oh okay
happy third anniversary to our most
beloved potential gamer Empress holy
[\h__\h] that's loud oh my God
can I make this less loud
how do I do this
[Music]
yeah
I show
there
this one
edit oh yeah oh
[Music]
uh uh uh
oh oh no that's something else
I don't know how to turn the volume down
of this I think it's all the same volume
[Music]
thank you
it's supposed to be loud I guess so
[Music]
and to our most below potential gamer
Empress Angel dancer Floyd line Idol
Guild leader and number one MIP speaker
that's very important
away cause an explosion in the
background
I will Afraid from writing too much and
now I'm too quiet in my head
uh so that you have an easier time
catching up besides one rainbow could
never be enough
to convey all the wonderful things that
I can say about this cute funny and
highly talented Phoenix right in front
of us so since this is our third
anniversary since you're always working
so hard for us and you truly deserve it
and because I think that this is
something that should happen way more
often he has free kisses for you
you know what since it's you here's a
fourth one don't tell the others
[Music]
that's right I barely have kisses I
always kiss you
[Music]
thank you thanks for thinking of me
thank you ultimone you've been also
around for a long time
I am so so thankful thank you thank you
thank you
especially for showing me that beautiful
rainbow
and it didn't even rain didn't even have
to rain rainbows when it didn't rain are
like very very rare
thanking for being such a marvelous
chicken supporter love love love love
love
and Paul thanks for the pink the pinky
get a happy third year thank you for
always helping all of us to smile in
Love Without You last three years would
have been uneventful
so for me too probably thank you for
always motivating me to walk towards my
dream there's too many more great years
yes
[Music]
I agree I my life would probably also
not be this exciting and very much more
depressing
so I'm glad that we can all appreciate
each other's presence yeah
I changed something with my mic now that
I sound different to myself again that's
weird
something's off
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
I don't know I understand I knew this
ah
[Music]
um
nothing's changing
my opinion
[Music]
oh
ah versus
uh
[Music]
no
I don't know
thank you
whatever
sorry it's just so weird with a new
mixer
I don't know Coke's alarm was easier
you understand you're going to stand
that code thanks for the Super Chat
though the red one especially
[Music]
laughs
that's funny
[Music]
that you're so sweet not good I love you
too
you got me you got me
decide to find action for the painting
I don't think I can put into words how
thankful I am for all the things you've
done in these past three years I'm here
since day one
to think about
[Music]
every dates are so wonderful to be here
you're awesome Kiara I love you so much
platonically ah you'll have to say that
again
were you I heard that before someone
said that to me before and I wonder it
wasn't you was it someone else
[Music]
why do you need to specify it
was that not you last time someone said
that to me like that I I felt very very
sad
it's okay I guess
I guess but why I mean
platonically why why do you have to
specify it it feels like you want to
keep a distance from me and you you you
you just you just don't like me that
much I don't know and it's just like
you're like you you're like you it's
just just platonically okay besides that
it's you
[Music]
[Laughter]
think about me and you're like ew
[Music]
I'm sorry man sorry I'm sorry this is
the only reasonable thing anyway thank
you
alphabetically
alphabetically is um
also ill
[Music]
no no
oh
um
[Music]
I was joking boss I love you
and now you made me go Doki Doki go away
stop
[Music]
malfunctioning a malfunctioning a
malfunctioning
thanks for the pinky
Moving On Moving On Moving on that's it
that's it
that's it you've been
you've been living in my head rent free
years and enough time to collect the
depth of interest for all the time you
lift in my head if my calculation is
correct you owe me your brightest smile
smile happy for an anniversary
that's it
I'm gonna say it back to you you little
[\h__\h] Kiana I'm so done I'm so done with
you
but I need more of you is that what
you're saying thank you
funny Super Chat how can you still got
it in you
you still got it in you thank you for
the support J1 thanks for talking again
recently I didn't achieve my dream that
I've been preparing for a long time no
but you Kiara and the pap you've taken
that gave me the power to move forward
and keep challenging again I'm proud and
happy to support you as my own sheet
Angel while preparing for the retest
Nike oh was it like a School exam thingy
University or something like that
and be hired to watch live streams than
before but I'll keep supporting you in
your dreams with the bottom of my heart
thank you Kiara for being here for us
happy third anniversary
[Music]
now I feel bad maybe maybe you're
spending too much time on me
so there for me I was maybe the the
reason why you failed it in the first
place
but I hope you can like balance
everything better
and like attempt it again and follow
your dreams
because you deserve being happy in life
and reaching your dreams
just how you imagine it just how I did
it
yeah I wish you all the best and
together we can succeed day one come set
me down
fighting fighting
hmm
it's not that it was so close it was so
close oh that hurts even more but that
that also shows you can do it just a
little bit more and you can do it
um
[Music]
crows thank you for the red super chat
for years of wow even though it might
seem like time has flown by I see and
appreciate all the hard work you put it
put in on and off screen which is my why
my love for Wawa is unconditional and
forever I couldn't be proud and I feel
so blessed to have such an amazing
Aussie thank you I'm I'm really happy
you you see or you think you see at
least to a certain extent the hard work
that I put in off screen too
yeah that's also important thank you for
trying to see it
I'm sure that you know not everybody
really realizes how much is going on
because there's only so much you can
really notice from the surface
well thank you for the support thank you
for always always thinking of the Wawa
for always being here always loving and
cherishing every moment thank you wow
thank you soon John be there thank you
for the pinky happy first anniversary
thank you so I have watched you since
day one until now huh oh my God again
that's so crazy you and I and kfp have
come this far for years time flies fast
it does it does cheese
I think it felt faster than my like free
year uh
apprenticeship thingy
I think and then
or didn't maybe not like it's so weird
when you feel like a time went by fast
but at the same time it also went by
slowly
I think it's both it's kind of both it's
weird yeah
yeah it's a strange feeling
[Music]
but I'm definitely like
making the most out of it I think trying
to make Every Day Count
without overworking myself like that's
important if you want to do it for a
long term I think you have to be able to
pace yourself and balance find a good
balance and and don't don't overestimate
your limits um
yeah
that's uh what I hope for all all the
cool highs to also understand because I
want them all to be able to be in whole
life for as long as possible I don't
wanna have any of their careers be
short-lived so in order to do that you
really have to make sure you don't burn
yourself out or overwork yourself you
know
it's very important
foreign
[Music]
you also don't just like Sprint the
whole Marathon
gotta save your energy
[Music]
Sprint a little bit in the beginning
Maybe
and then relax a bit
I guess I know I ran a marathon once
maybe when I was like seven or eight
I only it's so hard for me to guess age
even my own age I know at what age I did
certain things
it's hard to imagine what what age I was
I used to really love running
when I was younger
and my my father was really really
um sporty
and yeah he took me and my bro to do
some sporty [\h__\h] every now and then
and then I think they are he took me to
some like Marathon
but I stopped running I'm sick of
running now because I have asthma
hmm
I'm out of tea by the way but it's okay
because we're not doing it much longer
[Music]
I love buns though I wanna I want a
running thingy
every now and then I think about buying
one
for my home a treadmill yeah because I
just don't feel I don't want to go to
all Fitness
no I don't want to go alone and I
wouldn't be able to coordinate like a
time to go together with friends
regularly
I just want to have it at home I don't I
don't want to go outside I don't want to
go where all these buff people are who
can like you know run so much longer
than me
I just want to do it on my own
you know elliptical could be better
what's elliptical
[Music]
my indoor treadmill would be nice to
have
or maybe the bike the biking one
[Music]
cycle step I think I know what you mean
the stepper uh-huh
with the pedals where you're still like
walking kind of and this is the thing
that Rick you you can like hold on to
some sticks
okay okay that's what you call an
elliptical
yeah I like that thing like why is that
is that why you think is that better
[Music]
I do remember like trying that sometimes
in my friend's uh basements
yeah it's kind of fun it gives you like
this wobbly feeling
easier on the knees Works arms to true I
guess so a little bit huh better for
knees
hmm
but you know the thing is for treadmills
I found like some smaller ones that you
know don't take up too much space at
home I kind of doubt that they would
have that for the elliptical get a
rowing machine I I have one
foreign
I have one but it's a cheap one I don't
know if it's good
it doesn't feel so good
hey what using it huh what are you
talking about I need to rinse the
potatoes I can't use
I need to read super chats what are you
talking about
uh motion things of the pinky can't
really put into words what the past four
years have meant to me
oh
especially about repeating myself I
really found a place to be long be long
here alongside you and the rest of kfb
and it's really changed before the
better thank you for the three years of
joy
[Music]
classic
kfp chicken
motion motion thank you for being here
man I'll never forget
our Atelier times
and I'm happy that even when I don't
play after their games anymore you're
still here you still you know Finding
joy in my content
makes me very happy
what's better at Gathering does
[Music]
my rowing machine isn't Gathering dust
it's dripping oil or something it's so
weird because I got it like leaned
against the wall
and it's like I noticed like stuff is
dripping so I'm guessing it's oil that's
I mean what else would it be right
[Music]
like not like constantly a lot of oil
it's just like you know I noticed some
things like stolen
[Music]
you're not supposed to lean it yeah but
that's like a good way to store it
it's crying from the lack of you okay
okay okay I'll use it today maybe or
tomorrow but I got tummy horde okay
in the future more in the future too
talking slob thank you for the rainbow
what's up thank you it's been long three
years and through all the changes in my
life there's been one orange bird who's
remained a constant as a shining Idol in
my life pushing me to do more I've
gotten a job been promoted changed jobs
again let's go find that job that fits
you and even went to Japan again for
coming kids I've pushed the lemons off
my comfort zone and gone out more and
talk to more people I only got a handful
of days to work from home a month when I
can catch Dreams live but I'm always
working double duty as walking while
commuting oh my God thank you
there's been few things in my life as
inspiring as watching your journey I was
so Overjoyed one new album came out I
was pretty close with tears hey yeah
bought a dozen copies to spread the good
word of the orange bird to others
sweet you know I was gonna say like I
don't really see your name much you're
apparently very much bot gang
but still like watching over me
so carefully like in the back thank you
been three years but I'm still in it for
the long haul looking forward to
watching your journey continue love your
attention I told you it might still be
my favorite but I've had retrospective
playing on repeat in my playlist can't
get enough of the album thank
[Music]
me watching me and living your best life
at the same time like damn I'm glad you
are finding a great work life balance
and then I could help you a little bit
here and there with it
I'm really really really honored
and happy thank you talkings love mwah I
wish you all the best in the future and
I hope I hope every once in a while
maybe I can see your name in the chat or
in the super chats again just to know
you're still there show yourself okay
thank you for everything
[Music]
hmm
Chase Lockport faced with red super chat
in three years this incredible dancing
bird lady it changed the way I think
about achieving dreams she also changed
the way I think about quaffle
corn pineapples fried chicken lasagna
the Rickroll meme
oh it is a rainbow
Never Gonna Give You Up because you
never let us down kiwawa never gonna
turn around and walk out of kfp yeah
because I locked it you can't get out
but I sure could go for the good right
now maybe a croissant with butter and
ice cream what
[Music]
cheese walk
okay
love you Lala keep being the best
yeah I'm trying but like can you like
what fix this
doesn't seem right are you okay
you didn't actually
do that right
it's so weird change that ice cream into
Nutella maybe because
Nutella that is a amazing combination on
any bread
had it today too on transport I decided
[\h__\h] I'm I think I'm gaining weight I
don't have a scale but I I think I'm
gaining weight I need to
maybe for once in my life be a bit
careful with food
[Music]
so um
I switched from by sport to schwartzport
white bread to the I don't know what you
call it in English I don't think you
call it black bread
oh
like it's like
um yeah dark
whole meal
I know we have a lot of different
variations here
black Rye Maybe
[Music]
oh yeah yeah German German
um black ripe yes stuff like that
or variations of it
the pictures from American black rye
bread look disgusting
the [\h__\h] is this
that looks like the driest
muffin I've ever seen
like it doesn't look like our bread
you you Americans know nothing about
making
dark rye bread you know nothing
[Music]
leave it to the Europeans please
just being honest here
what I'm seeing here doesn't look good
ah there is something
[Music]
I love how I can roast you guys and you
just accept it
man
say I'm honest to you and you're honest
to yourself that's beautiful
[Music]
I mean can we just like
what the [\h__\h] is this okay let me show
you an example of what I'm comparing it
to
oh
it sounds better
[Music]
which one which one do we go for maybe
there's so much choice
[Music]
so much choice
oh
[Music]
oh God
um
love me some pot
[Music]
this seems to be an American creation
oh
this is very German
Austrian German European whatever
[Music]
I mean
we have also schwarzport that looks a
little bit more like this but still
better
[Music]
look like yummy
this looks good
yeah this somehow looks like cake but
not even good cake like looks like a
chocolate
microwave chocolate cake or something
[Music]
but that one's also darker we hope we
have like darker one too
okay how about a bit more nutty
[Music]
or oh oh my oh my
hair this is a bit more similar but
looks like so much more well done
doesn't it
it's like fluffy Airy
yeah
that looks delicious
sometimes
sometimes I I would also go for
something like this lots of nuts this is
good with like a a good cold cut of
something something we have so many cold
cuts here
[Music]
um
yeah that's bird food no
[Music]
I've had so many like chocolate
croissants recently
and cake
I've had so much cake recently
I need to
calm my tits a little bit
[Music]
anyway you guys should come to Europe
and eat bread
yeah yeah at least with croissant you
can't really go that wrong I think
[Music]
chill the Wawas
oh sporty yeah yeah yeah yeah that one
is very very sporty bread I agree with
that actually
[Music]
also a beautiful rainbow
sorry for
food shaming you
um could be good could be good now
although butter and ice cream like why
both
I don't know I don't know man
I know thank you for free
oh sheesh calm down
calm down oh God someone's bothering
with it already yeah I would still add
butter though I still like to add butter
to that though
[Music]
uh Happy third anniversary tangible
thank you for making these pass for
years of my life so much brighter with
all your amazing streams and all the
incredible music that filled me with
happiness every time I listen to them
thank you for always trying your best
and working so hard all the time to make
your dreamkins happy thank you so much
for all you do kiwawa there's not enough
words in the English language to
describe how amazing you truly are
you're the absolute best ever you always
make me extremely happy and proud to
have you as my one and only Oshi hmm
you really are the best or she any of us
could ever ask for and will always be
here supporting you forever no matter
what I love you
Grandma thank you
I said it before I say it again unknown
you just
you're like
you're so
positively obsessed with me
[Music]
but like you don't do it in a way that's
like creeping me out or feeling like too
pushy or like invading my privacy or
whatever and I will forever appreciate
you not breaking that like
barrier you know what I mean
yeah you're you're like able to walk on
that thin line
so well
back and forth back and forth
yeah thank you I love you for all the
like sweet words you always throw at me
always so supportive you're so sweet so
loyal I can always count on you hmm
my Australian mate
hey
you're always always supporting me and
everything that I do and like
thank you thank you thank you for just
being the best chicken ever
thank you
wow too much too much
too much money
that's the only thing you're doing too
much
[Music]
Trevor thank you for the pinky what are
the two things what happened with your
name what's private ayas what's
that what's that I got a new name what's
that mean
[Music]
and you still refuse to pronounce
debuted
[Music]
means young hog oh huh
somebody debuted
[Music]
foreign
well somebody debuted
that's hard to say though
that's so hard to say
you didn't know either
there is also the question marks hmm
they don't even know how am I supposed
to know
debuted debuted for you since you
debuted and you still refuse to
pronounce debuted correctly debuted
debuted
that's quite a difference wow
wow
they distributed
debuted
[Music]
they've debuted the beauty booted
debuted
[Music]
debuted you know what now say debuted
what was it
somebody debuted debuted
debuted they no I don't know man that's
difficult
but that's silly
long yet short years
what else can I say that I haven't
already said except thank you for all
the fun crazy frustrating tear joking
mind numbing cozy hilarious and exciting
times we've become a cardinal part of my
life and I wouldn't want it any other
way happy anniversary
Kiara my beloved and to many many more
travel
[Music]
forever sometimes don't worry maybe you
don't like me so much anymore damn I'm
wrong right I'm wrong you still love me
the same way as
as like two years ago
right
is it because of the yeah I thought ever
since the who knows
there's just
something between us
it's just not the same
you don't do you have any like
laughs
and any cold feelings
towards me since I left wholes behind
was the GTA advice why what what
happened in the GTA 5 streams
[Music]
they're like you you just think you know
if you go back and find the last ones
I'd be happy
I don't know maybe maybe I'll get a
chance to go back with the DLC I wonder
like how
that works because
huh
would you like like normally I guess
when you do them if you already finish
the game you you load the safe from
before you killed the boss right
I still didn't watch the trailer by the
way and purposefully so
so don't spawn on me the trailer but
they did say the DLC can be standalone
huh
does that also mean that like it doesn't
take over the levels and thing I wonder
[Music]
it is a post game continuation
there might be more this week on
teachers
man I should have flown to Japan a bit
earlier [\h__\h]
they said your levels will be set you
think
it's supposed to start you at the
specific level
[Music]
interesting really interesting but if
that's separate then I guess I can't go
back to the Hulu but maybe there'll be
new holders that we can collect
baby there'll be new hoodles
and I'll try my best to get all of them
okay if there will be noodles
I promise and then please let down your
guard Trevor Jean that you have put up
ever since you were disappointed in me
for my lack of poodle collection
foreign
thank you Trevor team
play please forgive me
please forgive me
I do think yeah there's just something
something feels off
remember Pippins thank you for the
rainbow
hydration check oh thank you okay
I feel pretty hydrated
so much that I had to go to idle meeting
like two hours in like that's that's
crazy
[Music]
well I'm fine thank you
very very considerate of you
you could totally play through cookie
yummy and and win it easily 100
everything
spankenheim thank you for the recipe
the kitties and I always look forward to
streams and tanned in tears to handle
more thank you
I also you know I'm I'm really I know
that sometimes maybe especially to
non-cat owners my cat talk can get a
little bit annoying but I'm happy that
with people like you I always have an
open ear and open mind who will always
always listen so carefully to what you
know it's just with cat owners
cat owners always care like what you
talk about about your cat you know the
non-cat owners just don't understand
and I understand that you don't
understand
but with me you just gotta deal with the
cat talk you know it's like inevitable I
love my cat so much you know
like even after all these years every
every day I wake up and see them
it's like the first time I'm seeing them
this is legit how it feels every day I
am freshly Amazed by their cuteness
it's fascinating to me
[Music]
it just doesn't stop and sometimes it
makes me go crazy because like I'm still
obsessed with them
um yeah so you have to deal with that
I'm sorry
it's it's also
it's all I live alone no I have is the
cats so you know I there's such a big
part of my life you know I'm their
caretaker so it's like it's like they're
my babies
me it certainly are my babies I can't
help it
[Music]
no
all I got in the real world is them and
then I go on my PC and I got you
you know I tell you about my cats
imagine if I told my cats about you guys
maybe maybe I do
yeah bank is bankenheim for being such
such a chad
cat chat
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you for
these three years filled with So Many
Adventures and growth you are and will
always be my coming Lucy you helped
create a dedicated and diverse Community
divers
kfb I'm so glad I joined you and KFC
don't stop being you love you Mom I love
you
thank you thank you
I'm so glad you joined too thank you for
becoming a chicken for joining Kimmy
when was your meeting it's like I'm
about to start in like six minutes it's
fun I'll do it until like last minute
it's fine it's fine
um
yeah thank you for watching over me and
and and supporting me on my journey
chicken
okabe thank you love you too I would
give you a kiss but you didn't send a
recipe and I have to save my kisses but
I feel like I could kiss every single
one of you guys
um
yeah yeah
I'm gonna get salmonella
I'm gonna get salmonella hello hello
[Music]
laughs
you're just so cute how could I resist
you I need to kiss you come here my baby
[Music]
since you're W
you've always kept me company with fun
streams and friendly tangents doing very
difficult moments of my life your
positivity and determination is very
inspiring here's the many more many more
years of happiness and success
[Music]
life can be so difficult right
I feel you
being adult is so difficult
but you're strong you are strong you can
do it somehow we'll get through it
others did it before us we can do it too
we'll get for life somehow one way or
another
yeah can't be that difficult if so many
others made it well you can do it
androgas we can't do it let's fight
though
[Music]
from Japan
oh yeah Japan now
enjoy Japan man there's like and so many
people I know are like going to Japan
like
now and like recently and it's like so
so weird
it's so weird because like
two years ago it was like still Corona
time and nobody was traveling now
everybody's going to Japan everybody's
saying
[Music]
you know
hmm
relieve their urges of going to Japan
yeah one of my friends is like in Japan
right now
um I mean they're like they're a couple
the other one has been in Japan before
many times but the other one
the the kitchen uh the pizza of
fans specialists
that guy
uh he yeah yeah he he is currently
enjoying Japan for the first time it's
interesting to see like Japan
Through The Eyes of someone who's there
for the first time fascinated by
everything hmm
[Music]
yeah I don't have that feeling anymore
everything's like so normal to me
Siri
[Music]
meeting in one minute ah we're fine
yeah well I hope you're enjoying Japan
as much as you can
get the most out of it
oh no problem Andrew goes thank you
and so yeah we're gonna thank you for
your support I'll be there too
soon
let's do high touch uh I shouldn't but
you know uh what's the word
not we're not really doing it but like
in in our minds we're doing it okay
High touch high five
[Music]
what's up high five
yeah in spirits figuratively yeah yeah
mind five
yeah thank you
and we'll leave it at that we got so far
but we read other super chats too you
know 58 right Ghana
this is this is what's to come guys
bye
[Music]
bye-bye Gotta Go Gotta Go Gotta run
goodbye
[Music]
foreign