[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hello
oh
ah
okay
okay i'm good i'm good
my cable my headphone cable was
stuck
under my chair
uh
so i had to free it
excuse the noises
that have been created by that hello
good evening
hello welcome to my record
stream it's actually been a while um
ever since the tournament
uh
it felt like we all needed a little
break from that
but
[Music]
let me resize myself a little bit oh i
got the nice hat that he not drew for me
back then
noise are my hands too big i think
they're a bit too big now
oh sure
okay how are you guys doing
i didn't say the key oops
when you went chat when you went i did
say oh i did okay it comes natural but
then i feel like i forgot it
hello
good evening hello it is 11 p.m i know
10 p.m here
yeah yes
we're gonna play a little bit of maya
cart today i want you guys to play with
me i want you guys to join in today
uh
but it won't be it won't be a long
stream it will be a fairly short stream
uh perhaps one hour or one and a half
hours of driving
and whether or not i will read super
chats i will decide after that but i
think i will
uh
yeah one hour one and a half hours
yes short stream
for real souls
because i still got stuff to do for
heliturk
so we're gonna
open up my tournament as per usual i
have one request
everyone who joined
last time
um
[Music]
please don't join
cat hair in my mouth gosh i got it
everyone who joined last time
please don't join uh unless maybe later
if we lack people for some reason then
you're allowed to join if if it looks
like we're lacking people
but i i think i think there will be
enough enough people
to join here maybe
as in last tournament the last race uh i
mean
and last last time i streamed this game
everyone who joined back then please be
so
cool to let other people join in that
would be
nice unless you're a new i'll make an
exception for noah's akies
cause uh they're funny i always enjoy
seeing them
[Music]
the famous the famous nowasagi racers
who are literally in every stream i have
to make an exception for them they
probably don't understand this anyway so
let me explain in japanese
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay time
[Music]
which one do we use today i will not
tell you yet one second let me hide the
screen
uh oh i was looking at the obs screen
yes yes
one second are you guys ready to battle
me
are you guys ready are you guys ready
what the freak
ah
game capture hd don't be such a pain in
the ass come on
wonderful wonderful
wonderful
which one do we want to use kusa tori
okusa 32
or speed i'm ready to watch nice that's
good too you can it's you if you watch
you know you can calmly
uh check whether or not
i am i am decent today
okay let's go
oh [\h__\h]
i tried to warm up a little bit before
the stream why are you guys so quiet is
it because half of the audience is
banned in the chat
i tried warming up before the stream
or so
uh i did one cup against npcs
most likely that's so sad
so sad youtube give me my people back
give me my paper bag
oh sure
yes yes open it up open open the gates
join
this tournament
and
i will go with the
or something like the same combination
that i used last time even though
apparently it's really not the best one
uh i didn't send anyone to the user room
oh how the hell are you people already
and hey i see a face that shouldn't be
here
i think
judas
jejus
just just because you added pickle at
the end of your name judas doesn't make
you
a no saggy
get out of here get out of here do this
i'm heading okay
i don't know about the others if whether
or not they were there or not
sorry judas
those are those
bottom left is where the code is
yes yes yes yes let's let's go
please john
[Music]
i'll give it my best shot good luck
lucas
let's go
oh there they are oh cute
i cut hair in my mouth
where are the people
not rainbow road
hey one two three
did you guys not get in bottom left is
where the cold is
oh i mean
it won't let me join why not
why is your cup just turned on the
switch slow slow way too slow
all right less less enemies means higher
chance to win right or does it no it's
the other way around is it lower no
higher higher chance higher chance to
win
let's go wait a minute no this is the
wrong screen ah
my my that's my obs
ah
my my ah
i didn't move that i didn't move that
oh well it's okay i can deal with this
my game capture screen is on on the
screen to the right side and i would
have to look over there the whole time
and that doesn't feel good
it shall eat this [\h__\h]
oh
the banana almost got me
[Applause]
wait do you guys hear audio yes you do
okay
we shouldn't be racing when it's raining
why am i eight hello
[Applause]
[Laughter]
i swear i'm better than before
i've swear i've been done before this is
just a shitty warm-up race okay
[Applause]
[Music]
looks baby the same to me now
i'm definitely better than before i i'm
just not i haven't played in like a
whole month i don't i don't i don't have
the feeling for it anymore and this is a
shitty [\h__\h] road to get started with
[\h__\h] already it's ended already i don't
want to be here anymore
i really am
i need some warm up
i'm rusty
[Music]
problem is the star doesn't keep me from
falling down it's not not much of a help
there oh god
[Music]
well this is a bit embarrassing
i keep on getting the same items
are noise actually caught up
i actually caught up yo whoopsie
okay now let me get uh the the actual
game capture screen here
that will change everything
thank you cuties i love you chickens
okay okay okay okay
everyone who was in there once please
leave
everyone who did one race please leave
thank you
thank you thank you
guys
no they were not waiting for me
no no no no no no don't get me wrong
they were actually driving normally and
i just managed to catch up
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
if you fix the screen you decided i'm
looking at the game capture screen which
supposedly also has a little bit of a
lag but
i i have been playing like this all the
time so
no sagi net
i think you're asleep it's like six am
or five am there
did you practice shortcuts no why the
[\h__\h] are we on this road
ah
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait no
you guys
i wanna show my skills
why did we have no oh
why don't we have to come here oh my god
i'm getting dizzy
omega megan
oh i got someone with my banana
this really feels too close
i forgot how to do everything
[Music]
oh hello i i joined you on purpose yes
yes yes
that was not me falling down and just
what what
excuse me
what's happening
don't tell him
it'll be a surprise early christmas
present you're welcome
yay
okay see at least i can
chill chill why is she i i stepped off
of the gas and she
keeps on pushing the gas like an insane
person
i
stopped pushing the gas millions of
years ago oh my god i missed the items
why what's going on why am i driving
like a maniac stop driving oh my god
i don't know where the break is why why
is she driving like this
like she's drunk or something
dude just perfect this kid's plan okay
it's only going to be
[Music]
who needs a goddamn star
no no no i thought i stopped
[Music]
i was thinking about making this stream
into a
stream ends if i uh place below
like six or seven
good that i didn't do that huh
bye-bye
good that i didn't do that i felt you
know i felt you know that's my that
might
yeah
um
not work out well
hey hey oh
[Music]
oh my god
three
um
eh
we're only four people
hello
hello everyone are you guys oh there you
go yeah i was i was getting worried
i was getting really worried you got the
sticker
[Music]
yeah the thing that keeps you from
driving off the edges i don't have that
on
what happened to all your training well
i didn't play for a whole month okay
i i i i i hate
do you remember how to just read i've
been drafting did you not see it
a little [\h__\h]
oh fellow australian in there hello
hello
and a fake australian as well nice all
right
i i've been drifting shut up
yeah i'm drifting off the track is still
drifting
girl
now i'm gonna destroy all of you
oh my god oh my god
oh my god
see i'm drifting
normal complaints please
i'm even doing tricks sometimes
this stupid boomerang i hate it it's so
useless
oh my god oh my god who built those
rounds
it couldn't have been the germans
because german roads are pretty damn
good i would say that
i would like to claim that
how dare you steal that from me
who wants a ghost
[Music]
i was useless worthless meaningless
okay chill we're gonna get back on track
[Music]
okay i'm just really unlucky have you
seen that also why am i driving as if
i'm drunk
[Music]
oh
don't send me friend requests
we won't be friends understand
okay use that up i don't want it i don't
want it i want the bullet i want the
bullet i want the bullet i want the
bullet i want the bullet yes
what
i didn't know about that shortcut
[Music]
hey
not last not less not even second to
last not even for to last
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
let's see what should we do next
which one shall we do next door
[Music]
i think i got the most experience with
uh
either one of those
i think i want to go with rario stadium
are you guys coming in or do i need to
change the rules and let people from
previously come in here
oh
[Music]
let's go
someone looks like edelgard
oh that is so funny it's a japanese tv
show meme
[Laughter]
oh my god that cracked me up so i told
you about the show before
in japan from um
it's a it's a it's a
this is this person is called matsumoto
and uh oh
my rocket
[Music]
yeah from downtown and they have the
show every new year's eve uh on japanese
tv
where
um they have to
be
i think was it for 24 hours or 48 hours
i think it was uh
what
was it 24.8 but something like that and
um they're like stuck in this building
with a theme
for example 24-hour uh policemen are not
allowed to laugh and they turn into
policemen and they're they're like being
constantly
uh
yeah tricked into
stuff that should make them laugh
does it make sense i'm it's really
difficult to explain right now
and there's this ongoing gag
uh
for like they've been doing that for a
couple years now
where uh
a certain member of those
uh
a comedian called tanaka
he always gets instead of you know they
get punished normally when they laugh by
just
getting a
a slap on the butt
with an actual bat
but tanaka
gets bullied sometimes and gets instead
of
instead of you know
a normal slap with a bat which is
already bad enough if you get like over
100 or over 200 in 24 hours and you're
already old as hell as well
no he gets a thai cake sometimes
and it's a big big running joke in that
show it's really funny so that person
named himself kiara there he is yada
taikiku why are you so far behind huh
why are we also bob hunt
oh my god
[Music]
i'm i'm holding up pretty good though
because everyone is so far behind
oh
my kiana's rock are you called kiana's
kiana's rock
sock sock duck
mine is socket
where did you get my sock
oh no
no
no no
mikko b you are bad for it turned
it's
headed you had to do that to me at the
end there i wasn't even doing so bad
what happened he shut up
there you guys are not supposed to
believe it
[Music]
that was
i'm that was pretty bad at the end i had
the blue shell but it was too late i had
that thunder but it didn't matter
[Music]
how's that practice working out for you
yeah you lose me some [\h__\h]
shut i
show him your skills shut up
wonderful
have a nice day
i'm gonna go back into my uh
thingy
why did i lose connection
let me join let me in
[Music]
maybe no tangents i was doing better
with tangents though
just now
oh my god
bottom left here you guys don't see it
why don't you guys see it
a bit rustic yeah no i'm not rushing
cute
hello everyone
what is that on the bottom right what is
that supposed to be
what is that
is that a cat
who is that
yeah i am rusty i am rusty
a dog
a bunny a dog
um
sampling happy birthday today slash
yesterday depending on what time zone
you're in
and i i don't know if you guys saw it
[Music]
yeah
i was a korean watamay senpai fan
worldwide senpai now i was saying just
now
that um
i don't know if i can really talk right
now
[Music]
stupid black yoshi
i shouldn't talk you know what i
shouldn't talk i'll keep the tangents
first sunday because we're playing town
level rise
[Music]
oh my god this angle is horrible
horrible
should have known mario would be a piece
of [\h__\h]
i wanted to play warioware next week but
i decided to replace
that
with a fps game
i told you guys on twitter
that next week i will be playing my
first ever fps game oops what the hell
where did that go where did it go
that was the wrong time to set that one
off
[Music]
i will not tell you which game it is and
honestly i have to i think i have to
test it out anyway first so that we
don't have any
issues
but you will know you will know when i
publish my weekly schedule uh but now oh
no
now i'm thinking
uh
if i even
will publish that on sunday because i'm
i will be gone
the first couple of days of the next
upcoming week
oh my god
oh he dodged
i
[Music]
please be kind to me please treat me
kindly
[Music]
guys why don't you give me an item
what if i go left what happens i don't
want to risk it now
oh no oh
i didn't get
i didn't get pondered someone was
waiting for me there thank you
who was waiting for me there oh did he
get disconnected because he waits for
everyone
richard who are you waiting for
oh
arigato gozaimas
i'm not less yeah
is it is the place
that well you guys don't see this on
youtube look at her over here what about
what about what about here do you see it
now
thank you
thank you thank you thank you it was an
a pleasure to drive with you guys
a pleasure
thank you so much
that's better really
okay
hold this on the bottom of the screen
yeah it's not that difficult okay uh
doco don't go can you please leave i
don't know about the white hat girl
i don't know if she was here before or
he
dogo
i know
thank you
eh we can't start now we don't have
anyone here hello hello are you guys
trying to get in
hey
are you just trying to get in or or is
no one trying and is the connection bad
one verse
mike you're canadian so i know canadians
are very very you know kind and uh
polite so you know what to do right you
know what to do
one race is one others are trying okay
let's go 50 50. i'm gonna destroy you
get out of here we're both lightweight
classes i think
mike that's not very polite of you
that is not very polite of your master
oh wait
hey does that's not very polite eh
is that
mike please mike mike mike don't do this
to me
mike
mike please i thank
you ah
mike
wait for me
wait where is mike where's mike mike
where are you
[Music]
i can miss you i miss you so much
i wanna see your face
come on
come on mike i already forgot what you
look like
it's so sad
hey it's so lonely here
i have no one to play with but eat this
[\h__\h]
it's because you're not polite to me you
must be must be a fake canadian
it has reached him do you understand
this now mike do you understand how
we're supposed to play this game now
these stupid things don't help me at all
can i get better items what the actual
[\h__\h]
oh my god it's gonna hit me
no the cow hit me first wonderful wait
wait like
[Music]
get out of here mike
mike
i will remember your face what the [\h__\h]
is that other face though what is that
face
[Laughter]
be gamer
oh why are you not here time i'm not
sure okay you can stay
you may stay i don't know if you were
there last time you probably were though
second place yay thank you
amazing amazing let's go yoshi
[Music]
aha
oh she does look like him
you mean uh on the bottom left first row
second from the left
it does look a little bit like him
his name is kidio in japanese
hello
hello everyone let's drive let's study
though
come on come on come on go
go
[Music]
number not one
you have to take that away from me
didn't ya
i'm number three i'm number three
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go
let's go let's go
oh yeah get those curves get those
curves mmm greasy curves
[Music]
good did someone just steal my item
oh no wait was that i thought that was
uh a bit longer
i thought you could use that one a bit
longer than that
but okay we're still doing fine i'm just
six
it's not bad
what's up with you mate
what's up with this book we gotta get
out of here you weren't supposed to be
here
[Laughter]
why is vegan with 11 of them wasn't he
just in front of me
[Laughter]
yay
[Music]
i told ya you shouldn't underestimate me
anymore
yeah yeah yeah thank you thank you
third
you underestimated me i got the crown
beach i got the crown who's got the
crown
who's got the crown
who's the queen
who's the best
welcome welcome grandpa
i am now recruiting new opponents if you
guys aren't scared of me
which i would totally understand if you
guys are too scared to drive against me
um
[Music]
okay thank god not not many people are
choosing rainbow road is that the same
miko on different mikkopi
and yeah it looks like uh
uh nami senpai kind of
good app
you want to drive against me good at
want to do it one one-on-one after this
we should fill one-on-one
i'm planning to play
a few more ah
[Music]
maybe maybe in 15 minutes do you want to
do a one versus one
well uh wait did you write boku boku and
you said it's broken
you guys tell me what she answered i
gotta focus on driving now after all i'm
a professional driver
as you have just seen on my placement
there
oh i hate someone
i hate someone
[Laughter]
when you're not sure if you should go
for the two item one or for the one item
one
then you're so indecisive no no no not
yes yes yes
when you're so indecisive that it bites
you in the ass oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i need some items
but even without items uh i'm i'm not
doing that bad yo i see all these people
in front of me which yes thank you uh
that was
[Music]
did you guys see that
did you guys see it
[Music]
who was that ghost kid ghost get banned
forever
i don't want to see you anymore i'm just
kidding i'm i'm just kidding
i'm not that salty oh
finally finally is this my first item no
my second item today
in this race
at least
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
now i want to go down
[Music]
my
oh
worst possible moment for that thank you
your time's that didn't you bullying is
not okay
bowling is not okay
that's
uh kind of
sliced apart off of my uh cheeks
it felt good though
yeah
i got those uh
i got rid of those dead
[Music]
those dead
skin cells is what i was trying to say
all right i could have been six let's be
honest i could have been sixth
it was a a lot of bad luck here
oh
it what is this connection today
oh again someone who looks like me
but those those uh kind of look like
tears at the same time
cute though i know she has senpai
this is so cute
this is so cute how you always
oh you guys always try to kind of look
like someone i like twisted mansion
i let's go
i need to go
imposter that person looks more like me
than i do
oh that looks like okay senpai somehow
oh alex
and another alex
lucian
okay okay okay oh what a cute pacman hat
oh yeah right there's a pacman character
huh
hello
connection horrible today
hey i took that item away from you
you're not allowed to have any items
nope nope nope okay i'll show you my
real power
i'll show you what i can do
hey fire is my element
bishop
oh i love this music
oh bowser is angry
rage
sorry i'm passing through oi
that must have been the swiss dude
i got you on my
radar no why do you move like an idiot
[Music]
okay um
the air is getting a little bit thin
or thick
which one is it
but it's okay
it's all right i can still fix this
bonjour
my nose feels itchy
okay
oh
smokes morphs ball
and get that item yes
fruit
[Laughter]
yes
see you later
buddy okay okay catching up baby
[Music]
that wasn't supposed to hit me
[Applause]
it did warn me but like what the hell am
i supposed to do besides just driving
no
no no no
[Music]
okay that's just
that's just not cool
dude that's just not cool ah
um
[Music]
okay okay good i said yes to one versus
one we're gonna do it after
one or two more races against you guys
okay i am we've done told her good today
already
i went on this one today
i like cloud top crews i think it feels
very stressful but it's actually quite
quite manageable
there are the people uh welcome why that
why does that person run like a
naruto
can you change your running style
your mies running style is that
changeable
what that my standpoint cute so small is
that the same person from before
[Music]
he may have not understood the rules
because uh
probably uh from korea which is okay
it's okay it's okay it does
[Music]
yeah that's the same person it's okay we
forgive we forgive
we're not that strange
anyone who looks as cute as vitamin
senpai we can't be mad at them hold on
hold friends stoko good question
i'm probably for you know more european
whole lifers even if they're just in
whole live english that would be fine
with me
more more europeans go go go
oh i'm bonking against the wall so much
not good
here we go
can you imagine
cute cute girls speaking
english with french accent
yes no
everyone went there
and then you know what i'll say to them
i'll pick him up i got my pickup line my
french pickup line
[Music]
who was that who was so surprised and
thought i could actually speak french
when i flexed that in a collaboration
before
[Music]
someone was like yo yeah you can speak
french wow
it good
i wonder if she's never listened to
muran rush the song
before
that's that one song that i sang in
karaoke before
[Music]
hello
i oh of wanted the two items but that's
okay
those corners man those corners
[Music]
okay the thing is if you're like in the
middle end of the like in the air
uh it feels like
really bad when you get dropped there
but at least like you kind of get fl
fluent back i wonder i think you don't
even lose that much time
[Music]
but yeah okay okay
[Laughter]
ah
a fire fire is
inside of me
okay one more last one last last stop
for now
then we play with guda and maybe after
that we do maybe one more review guys i
don't know we'll see we'll see we'll see
one more come on
me na last that's the commercial night
that's the machine i'm not okay
i don't need to watch the video tutorial
again
salt no it's fire fire fire i want to
play this one i'm gonna do this one
don't stop just go your own way that
does sound familiar
[Music]
i thought there would be no sakes but
there's a lot of tomatoes
today
[Music]
oh they're hanging out cute
and simple is vibing she got those
glasses too
you know those vitamins and my uh i
think they're star-shaped glasses though
and that that's mr bean though oh my god
on the left is mr bean
didn't make sense sell those uh glasses
too though as merchandise
or am i
imagining that i feel like that came out
as
merchandise as well
yeah right
that's so cool
i like this one i think
f-zero
i'm number one i'm number one i'm number
one number two now okay still ah
it's getting crowded
only a coin really
oh i've never been up here
he stole before
police officer please arrest him
[Music]
okay i got my two items now i'm
satisfied
[Music]
i'm gonna go this way
oh dear
oh my god where am i
[Music]
is there a vr version of this game by
the way because that would be i think
a big trigger for emotion sickness
oh i'm sick yeah baby
oh my god
[Music]
get those herbs get those curves
okay i still have a bunch of items
though i'm fine i'm fine
[Music]
gotta make up for my mistakes here no
again
oh wait that's the end already
oh please please
okay that is not cool i was i'm
officially here number six i'm i'm six
actually i'm number six actually
that's not cool
[Laughter]
okay everyone bye bye
sorry thank you for hanging out with me
i'm going to play with gooda now
let me hide the screen for a moment
because i need to figure out i think
we're already friends on
nintendo i would be surprised if we're
not but let me uh see one moment
friends was it friends and rivals
online play
friends and rivals
pretty sure we're friends huh
how how did we make it through one year
without becoming friends
wait
oh
how do i add friends again
here
okay
yeah i think i think we'll play the
well a nintendo game together before oh
by the way i'm gonna add we're gonna do
voice chat as well just one second
are you sure
and those are the magical numbers
hell yeah
friend request sent
accept my humble request
mrs gura
oh sure
and then
friends were crushed
and now
let's hang out in the voice chat maybe
she's
uh there we go
[Music]
hello
hello how you doing gua
magi
[Laughter]
i'm here to kick your butt
the first thing you greet me with is
machu picchu did you get out of the
wrong foot or something are you having a
bad
i woke up morning my racing foot oh
you woke up you got out of bed and you
the first thing your foot touched was
the gas pedal right
yes i woke up with violence in mind
sorry i have to kick your butt in front
of kfp sorry kfp i highly doubt that
that's gonna happen it's gonna be a show
since you last played uh mario kart
well i see after after the tournament i
had i got obsessed with the game when i
come stopped playing it right yeah yeah
but now it's minecraft's turn yeah
minecraft turn but yeah i know
yeah i got really into playing how do i
join you again i so i opened like a
friend's lobby yeah i think you could
find it yeah like if you click friends
and or something like that friends and
something
and then go down and look for my name i
think
that's how it works
uh
yes
coming
let's do not one only though let's do um
best out of three
oh you're giving me a warm-up match oh
you're so funny
it's not a warm-up match no it's a
chance for you to win a tiny chance tiny
tiny time
and then you hit quite you hit quite a
few walls so i think as long as i just
stay on the track i'll win
you're you're invisible i don't see you
here are you scared of me
i'm hurrying give me
i don't remember what my setup was
oh god oh god
baby eyes are bigger than her freaking
heads
so shut up
and wait a second wait one time
i wrote you one message on discord
please check okay okay hold on let me
queue up berry the light to get me hyped
up
do you guys have some milk for gouache
baby can you give her some milk
you have your blindfold kfp for what i
have to
beat your oshie live on stream i don't
want you to have to see that
oh man okay let's go gula
you ready
let's go
oh yeah i have to set some settings okay
teams no teams items normal items cpu no
cpu or do you want to mix in some cpus
no cpu only game
oh vehicles for
free 48.
four six eight oh we can't do three we
gotta do four i think or do you wanna do
48 races
let's do four
oh if you got time minecraft stream
starts uh one hour earlier than usual
right but it's still time
no teams right normal items yeah no calm
okay i i i will i will crush you
i will
am i choosing the the cup oh we're doing
a cup hmm
i don't really
care which cup do you care anything but
my only question my only request is
anything but the rainbow ones
oh you don't like rainbow road oh no
well
that will aid in my choosing um oh oh oh
my you oh you also get to choose oh i
see i see oh damn
i think it's just doing a
a course a track
ah oh oh yeah right oh oopsie i i
miss uh judged dad all right those are
good choices i'm fine with wolf all
right
goodness choice first
oh let's go let's go baby let's go
or jungle fever don't go hong kong you
like donkey kong
this ain't donkey kong this is roy
what's wrong with you
there's donkey kong barrel over there
oh i i didn't mean your character i mean
i meant the roads
did you not get an item go up did i
steal the item from you oh i'm so sorry
a lot of chatter for second place back
there
oh there's not much choice right now
[Music]
i'm coming for you
i want you back
[Music]
i don't like that giggling
stupid items
stupid
but i have to discuss something with you
about our future
yeah
come on please i need to talk to you
[Music]
okay one of them one of them hits that's
for sure
yo
oh no
how could you do this kiawah
can't believe we've done this
[Music]
good i have to say that foundation and
that eyeliner really just doesn't suit
you at all it doesn't work for you at
all
oh
i'm concentrating you don't like my my
my glass my sunglasses
no and i i just can't look at your face
that's why i'm so far away
it's all right i'll use the trophy to
cover my face
and you don't have to worry about it
can you stop shooting me with your red
shell
get your ass up here and race me like a
real man i'm coming i'm coming if you
say so all right i'll give you one
chance to hang out with the famous
kiwawa
thank you
oh off the map oh no
oh no wait you actually fell down
no well okay i'm i was pretty close okay
yeah i felt like i fell out of the map
but gives you a chance to catch up
oh yes it did fall down oh
i did it and then i went boom i didn't
give myself enough speed
okay that's that's where you belong
oh so
[Music]
what do we do next
cool where shall we go next well
you're in a competitive mood today huh
i've been playing too much minecraft
placing block down i need some i need
blood what are you doing today in
minecraft
i'm building i've been building a lot at
the the portal ah
so yeah i want to finish my build oh
you've also been uh
uh uh
oh this one is yes that's my choice
you've also been getting quite far with
your um
uh atlantis spilling thingy
[Music]
i learned i like how you put a question
mark at the end of that
is that is that supposed i don't know is
that supposed to be atlantis i don't
know
the thing that you're filling with the
with the quartz
[\h__\h]
in my temple you like my temple you're
the temple
is that not supposed to be some kind of
atlantis temple
you know what at this point honestly
shirt
is
it's atlantis what are the uh what are
the
what's the order of like alpha and betas
and all that uh alpha and then beta and
then and then delta and then everything
that comes after that
because yeah all right it's definitely
it's definitely the beta at this point
oh
it looks really good when i saw it last
time
good grandma
i just don't know actually you know how
you can put items on the back your card
is protection i don't know how to do
that well i will not tell you so much
for using a lot of uh mario kart okay
how can you because i'm on skill i'm on
skill mode oh sh okay you can hit that i
didn't know that
i know kfp will tell me who i can't be
you're telling me i will not tell you no
if you
no don't tell her
wow you make me nervous so i'm driving
kind of badly right now
on you must steady your heart rate
do chickens have fast heart rates they
must be because they're brake creatures
i literally understood no word that you
just said
your heart rate like rabbits have really
fast heart rates because they're always
gonna tell you but your chicken and
chickens and rabbits are the same
thanksgiving oh oh oh okay it's kvp that
i'm thinking of uh huh yeah that's right
that's right
i'm just chilling on this road right now
it's all good that you don't oh [\h__\h]
good that you don't know how to put
something on your back though
but i got your big shout coming for you
oh yeah
oh no
oh
hold the item button but don't let go
thank you kfp what a champ i think that
was a kfp it might have been a
non-member i don't know
regardless thank you chat
[Music]
would you like to call it quits now
kiawah would you like to go again i'm
sorry i think it's the music that's
hyping me up we are going again we are
going again lady
i'll give you the benefit of that i'll
choose the okay never mind i'm not
choosing that one i just saw what you
chose on your stream i'm not picking it
out with that one oh what do you think
that like
are you not able to ski or snowboard
baby grabs
[Laughter]
i like this one because it's uh it's not
a loop it's just one one thing
one review
yeah that was called a mountain ski
thing i've never done ski i don't know
what it is
i want a snowboard let me educate you
now
oh sure
because i am
from the snowy snowy australia wink
and we like to be on the snow this is
our element you know
oh
[Music]
god oh thank you for waiting for me did
you just wait for me
did you wait for me
it looked like you waited for me but i
can't believe that that the courage is
trying to do that is waiting for me
i've never done i don't think i've ever
done this one before i've only seen it
seeing it
[Applause]
let's go
bye
okay
this actually feels different from usual
did this race get an update or something
looks it feels and looks so different oh
[\h__\h]
oh no you didn't get that
no i'm not giving you that
i know
i don't know how this goes
this looks like that sonic game
sonic
ah
you did the same thing okay good
good good good
okay show him those tricks
show me your drifts kiara no
[Music]
oh baby
you better hurry i see the finish line
[Music]
oh no
no i need something better than that
[Music]
can i wait for you
no
okay
it was close though you know what i kind
of want to see how you how we would race
against one another if there were other
people in here because then i think the
results may differ
here to add in the kfp then i kind of
want it yeah
but uh i would be difficult because that
would have to be a public one and then
getting you in there is difficult unless
no i could make a new tournament and
then give you the number first
and then yeah what else the number
yeah i think that'll work all right
i think it has to work
okay let's um does does we don't need to
finish that tournament it was already
three out of four wins for you
one second let me quickly make a
tournament i'm gonna hide the screen so
the people here don't know the number
yet uh
create a tournament
create an online tournament sure sure
sure whatever blah blah blah choose a
symbol i don't care anything is fine
enter a name
um dwawa
i don't have time for that
no proper tapping no no
tournaments rules mode one of those
teams normal items no no cpu yeah all
vehicles smart steering okay no not okay
not okay
oh i had that setting off or on for
others i wonder
uh active i don't know
i never know what to put for that
well let's just say weekly whatever it
doesn't really matter
[Music]
public private open to everyone oh okay
code require call to crowd yes yes yes
yes okay google
give you the number now
let's do that please
there you go
okay and then i'm gonna change it on
screen as well
[Music]
i know you guys already see that let me
know when you finished typing in
uh
okay
uh-huh
is this touchscreen
oh it sort of is once
ever
right now not on pc
yeah handheld wait that's not right how
do i do that wrong
oh dear it might still be
no now it should be open
i'm coming okay
and let's see who wants to race against
me and goober
but you have what it takes you guys are
now uh welcome to join again if you have
joined before on the last stream you the
rules are now
cancelled my best kfp racers help me out
here
no no
i don't see you yet
are you coming i i'm i am i'm i am
boarding my bicycle okay okay good i am
i should be coming up right now
okay okay okay kfp people have people
i'm counting on you
i need your mental support please come
and help me but no bully no booty no
bully no booty good night no boy
thank you thank you oh
what the hell here i am
hello hello
all right
all right all right let's do familiar
faces
let's go with
maybe this one
oh that one's really popular
it's a good one
yeah it's so pink cute
who's your favorite mario princess
daisy don't you see that cause i'm
always playing daisy
is she orange
is that why you like her because she's
orange
[Music]
no i don't know it's just kind of like
her vibes you know
yeah she's like i think i described her
once to my chat is like the cool aunt
taco spence
see that name
no it's tacos bells
it's supposed to be taco bell isn't it
you need to see it in order to
understand it i think let's go
kind of miss on the first um
push was distracted god damn it
tacos the reds distracted me well who is
your favorite princess then
girl selena oh
very fancy
she said now bully
i'm not bullied
not you
who's bullying you i will kick him out
no no no no
oh god are you behind me oh what's going
on
hey i'm outnumbered here i'm surrounded
by kfp it smells like poultry and they
always try to beat me too
all right fair enough
geez it's savage up there
okay okay come on come on quickly come
back
ah what's going so well
hello thank you for waiting for me why
don't you have a name
oh i'm getting the speech
though oh hey joe
ah man dude
[Music]
oh no why am i so far behind can't beat
him
[Music]
helpful
okay
thank you kfb i believe that that was
sent by you guys
a gift from heaven
from the chickens in heaven who have
already been sent to the fryer thank you
for sure
okay
time to catch up
[Laughter]
wish you could control that bullet
sometimes oh okay another one a double
bullet
thank you kfb
what are these bullets my guy
oh did you get one too
now
an army of chickens is attacking a shark
isn't that wonderful
it's blasphemy
[Music]
oh
oh garbage
oh you're behind me right behind me oh
garbage oh
good idea
if i had a penny for every shell that
just hit me
oh my god why are you hiding behind me
because you were scared of all the
chickens you chickened you could only
win if you had all your
[Applause]
me as well kills i have some bad times
too
but no i know i know let's do it can we
do one more community yes yes as many as
you want god
okay let's do one more
dude i know
[Music]
a famous one has entered a famous nosaki
welcome welcome welcome you my name is
[Music]
what is that dude with no face
it just has a tiny mouth is he okay who
took his face away from him
that looks painful
oh it's like um you can't even look at
our beautiful faces
maybe his his eyes are inside his mouth
you
oh this one okay
warriors no
i chose this one i think it was a random
one
did they add flags to this i don't
remember there being flags
it maybe it really got an upgrade
did they are great questions good try to
try to get number one now how about that
try to get number one now
let's see if you can do that now
ah don't worry i'll catch up oh i am
doing my best
here put those pokemons there
well that's mean that tactic
you shoot your fireballs against the
wall so they ping-pong back and forth
and end up hitting somebody at least
once they are so smart
they've been studying the youtube
tutorials i see
[Music]
okay well that will help a little bit
i don't like being in the middle of the
bunch here this is kind of dangerous
oh yeah
there's too much speed
okay
a blue one for whoever's number one
right now you're welcome
oh good i see you again
stupid baby luigi that's why daisy
doesn't marry you that's why she doesn't
like you oh
[Music]
here comes the star oh my god
stop telling me stop throwing it
backwards
cheeky kfp that's so good that's a
technique that i haven't really figured
out yet
behind me
like where the hell how do i know where
i'm throwing at i mean there's a
backwards uh angle but i can't
do so many things all at once that's
crazy
okay that was a good curve that was a
very good curve yeah
[Music]
the luck is on my side
why am i getting mushrooms now i'm in
lab please
oh my word
[Music]
[Laughter]
sitting in the fire that i created and
you say i'm fine this is fine
this is fine
i love mario kart mario kart suki
will you want to do another one oh yeah
are you upset guru are you awesome
anything but that one oh no
clown top cruises you'll be i'm not sure
which one i think i'm gonna go with this
oh i shouldn't have chosen so early
people are still coming in the
connection is so bad
come on guys
there we go
oh
no
okay
all right let's go
oh a lot of uh the same choices
the electrode oh you chose it too that
was fun there's so much music happening
there
no come on not that one no i hate that
i really don't like those no
i don't know
oh it's this one this one's not that bad
it's easy just straight line
oh yeah so i got it wrong i thought it
was a different one oh that's okay
should be good
should be good for sabotage
oh no i was too late
see you later sucker
i'm number one
okay not anymore
whoa
speed
okay
shoot something tony eiser just shoot
something what the heck was that bro
[Music]
but i really appreciate you being so
spontaneous in joining in on this i've
recently realized or like noticed that a
council and everyone if ever since
council joined everyone is like so much
more spontaneous and and active
i was talking a little crony about that
too i was like ever since you guys
joined we've been more i don't know open
to
collabing with whoever whenever yeah
it's like a party ever since council
joined it's a freaking party oh oh
garbage yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i like
that
yes yes beforehand all of our collabs
were super strict was like you have to
schedule it has to be at this time blah
blah blah you know
[Music]
yeah but i mean that's kind of also on
us though
sort of but i do appreciate the way it
is now us only being five people in very
different time zones it's just like
difficult to
randomly bump into one another in
minecraft
it's just it didn't happen much
yeah that's also true
marshall oh who's who through that let's
where that shot
oh he's not me
i am
i'm a good child
what a good child
i would like to get some items again
please hello
get out of here
are you which place are you
i didn't even see you when did you come
when did you come by me it was very
clutch it was very last
[Applause]
[Music]
would you like another one no we're done
we're done
we can be done i'll let you play kfb
some more i'll go start
more minecraft oh thank you i'm ending
it too though
oh okay okay thank you
thank you okay
i don't know when but soon
yes i'll see you soon let me know if you
like a rematch bye bye anytime anytime
girl oh
okay okay
i'll send you some bandages and
band-aids you didn't hear that but i'll
send you those bandages for for your
wounds or some i don't know you need to
lick your wounds i can
i can help you with that i guess i don't
know it's kind of weird but
i i if you need some therapy i also can
offer you my cat scooter therapy cats
how about that
it's really
was soothing
thank you cuda for joining thank you kfb
for joining uh it was a lot of fun yeah
um i was very rusty but
um yeah i just really didn't play it for
a long time so yeah can't help it but
but but but but again scooter with you
guys i'm glad i could show a little bit
of
a little bit of skill tiny attack itsy
bitsy tiny little bit
uh so that she didn't win all of it but
it really makes a difference whether or
not you're playing one versus one or you
know
with a lot of other people it makes a
big difference
your show
okay guys
we're gonna read super chat those now
and then uh tomorrow is whole talk so
please don't miss whole talk tomorrow we
have choco sensei
the asmr god uh
will be visiting us tomorrow in hall
talk on my sofa
yeah
and she will also do a live performance
as well
mm-hmm
the god is herself yes
yes the sensitive asmr goddess
so
let's move on over to my
uh
wonderful i just need to fix some things
first of all i'm a little bit too big
yeah that's comfy look if you missed the
stream yesterday and you missed the fact
that i added cats to my desk
the cat yes
one of them is green one of them is
orange
the orange one is called smoothie and
the the green one is called movie and
the orange one is called uh a chance
on stream at least
my cute cats
i also have a frog as you can see
and i have a rat can you find the rat
comedienne jedi
it's not a chameleon it's my my little
support
mental support animal
all right let's find super chat
yesterday i read until
uh everything but the the egg egg egg
super chats
so we'll read those
and the ones from today
thank you guys for being so supportive
and generous
i will try to read uh
the messages at least i'll always read
the pinkies and the red ones out loud
and the messages but i read all of the
names so
uh scrolling scrolling scrolling
yes top right is where the rat is
get back into your hidey hole oy
or mate get back in there yeah good
get down there where you belong into
your hiding hole that's where i tolerate
ya
nowhere else
i'm still scrolling okay there we go we
read all of diablo right
yesterday my voice was really
breaking
too long too many long streams and too
many screams but
today i'm feeling fine so i think we can
finish them all up
something else there we go
let me put that there
from yesterday
there we go
okay
casper looking cuter than usual
that's because that that ain't casper
casper looks quite different
i saw that trick shot you did with the
egg that was epic oh i did i did a lot
of trick shots
i know a lot of them not only one i
didn't know how to handle my eggs
okay uh i think you guys still hear the
a little bit of the mario kart beauty
i'm gonna get like the calm one the
lobby museum let me get out of there
it only sounds weird if you want it to
sound weird it's not because of me
mine is those nine hundred plus a brock
you mean thousand plus
i like how you keep it below 1000
but
you don't have to do that it was it was
over a thousand eggs that i broke
yesterday
it's okay
we can be honest about that
all right let's uh play this one
or don't you guys want to go on audio
stock with me look for one quick song
what do you want to hear today jazz or
we don't i don't i don't really really
want to hear jazz
is there a genre that you guys want to
hear today
audio stunk
um
i want to hear something
maybe
wafu
and cute
so yeah i'm sorry i'm actually ignoring
everything you guys are saying
rafu
okay let's go what can we see you you
can you can choose with me though
let's listen in
audio stock
show me what you got
no
code
[Music]
waffle edm
oh
[Music]
i like this one
i just want to download it like in
general
[Music]
i don't know if it fits the current mood
though
[Music]
it's cute
oh
well i i want to buy this the writes
this song and make an original song out
of this
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe no the lyrics no let's make some
proper lyrics let's let's make this into
a real banger
yo this is potential i'm downloading
that
uh
down low gel
give me that mp3 thank you without the
audio stock though
ah
oh
what
kawaiku tonight was
a cute but
uh
sentimental
japanese style waltz
what since when is a waltz japanese
oh it's style
[Music]
oh
oops
that's cute
oh it's dark
whoa whoa
that's beautiful waffle monster internet
[Music]
i'm ascending
audio stock does sound like cronie yeah
[Music]
why is wahoo japanese style music so
goddamn beautiful it doesn't i realize
though it doesn't really suit me it
doesn't fit me at all
let's just look for how about retro
[Music]
let's look for kawaii
have to look in japanese
okay retro and trumpets you got me there
what is it
[Music]
oh my god
this is gorgeous
[Music]
if i turn down the volume a bit
would that be nice as a super chat music
i don't know it seems a little bit too
too exciting
[Music]
oh it's gorgeous though
oh my god
i'm vibing with everything yeah
i gotta name those before i forget what
they are
[Music]
what would you name this song trumpet
trumpet or shah ray
or shot it and the one before waffle
cute
oh my god
oh it's so good like the quality of
audio stock uh material is is so
high
asadora
there's a lot of jazz here
clap clarinet jazz
[Music]
you orleans feel
sounds like something amelia might use
true maybe i should send it to her i'm
like i thought of a lot of you when i
listened to this
let me download it right now
i'm gonna send it to you
it wasn't even worse than like me who
thought of her but let's not tell her
that
i got this from audio stock
and
had to think of you
when i listen to it
maybe you wanna
use it
[Music]
that sounds ridiculous
i mean i had a laughing emoji otherwise
this is um
this is embarrassing
[Music]
so cozy all right get out of here
we should look for city pop there's city
pop and audio stunk
[Music]
oh my god
this is a modern city pop though
[Music]
oh that's a jingle
oh can we get a nonjingle city pop okay
that's what i'm looking for i got it
shitty
pop
this sounds like never gonna give you up
[Music]
we're no
we're no strangers to love
you know the rules and so do i
know what i'm thinking of
you couldn't get this from any other
girl
i
just want to tell you how i'm feeling
gotta make you
understand
wait where's your chorus
[Music]
baby let's go
this feels good
kinda wanna i can't this is kind of like
an aesthetic that recently i've i've
been into um
like 80s 80s uh aesthetic
i kind of want to
make a song like that
yeah i'm downloading that this is so
good
i found a gold mine looking for city pop
on audio stock i found the freaking gold
mine
all your stuff okay
downloading downloading to all the uh
the
wait a second this one this one is
called for amir
and this one is
uh rickroll city pop
okay we're going with that
for now or are we wait there's so much i
want to look through them
oh
what about this what about this what
about this
should he pop ballad
chill out city pop lo-fi oh lo-fi fight
city pop are you killing me
well if i see the pump
[Music]
i'm ascending
stock
oh yes
oh
this is good stuff
[Music]
you guys need an audio stock
subscription by the way hashtag not
sponsored though i want to write a
raptor disc
if only i could think of lyrics on the
fly but i can't even if i drank
who makes these tracks i don't i don't
know these are like a [\h__\h] ton of
different kind of people
uh office who ride these tracks
and you can even buy one by one or you
can get a subscription all of the whole
live members have a subscription which
is really cool
[Music]
i love it oh i'm downloading i'm
downloading i could literally download
every second song there's so many that i
like there's like barely any misses
and even if i find something that's like
oh this is not what i'm looking for
right now it's like oh maybe maybe i
want to use this uh sometime soon
i keep on downloading all of these songs
no-fi i wouldn't really call it city pop
though
really nice
chill slow fly
okay oh that's it's really nice okay let
me put that into my obs
um that might be really loud let me do
it for vlc
okay that's better
than what we've had before
um
yeah
that's quite an endorsement for others
like if i ever heard one kiana
i'm just being honest though
i'm just being honest
[Music]
with you
just a little while ago
we were told like yo you can use audio
stock now you all have a subscription
now was it it
for real
it was really cool
to have that really useful thank you
so
super chat time guys
tell me when you get sick of the music
then we can go uh look for more
is it a good volume now
[Music]
if we're subscribed to honestly can we
listen to the tracks without someone
saying i'm just like yeah yeah yeah
that's that's the thing like you can
first browse for them and it will say um
audio stock and then you can even get a
subscription then you can download
everything without the audio stock
or you can
buy single songs if you don't want a
subscription
push up the volume a little bit
[Music]
part of the package oh yeah the audio
stock is very charming very charming
lady
[Music]
all right
sorry i'm vibing so much
miffin thank you
mr cosby stun pirate homework
and
i need to find out how to read this name
oh my god this is oh this feels so
refreshing
this this audio volume was good before
okay i'll lower it a tiny bit there we
go um
this feels so good
it kind of that melody
for some reason that reminds me of old
blackout peace songs
i don't know why
i don't know why um
uh what am i looking for i am a
translate
yo give me that repeat yes
[Music]
issues like they don't show up in the
chat a lot of people
since like one or two days ago
so many people don't show up in the chat
so they have no choice but the super
chat
it sucks sorry i can't really do much
about it but
yeah
youtube already seems to have replied to
some of you on twitter so let's hope
that they uh
you know tackle it
i hope so
[Music]
i hope you guys can come back to me if
it's a bit lonely without all of you
[Music]
honestly could have gone better
but i still had fun i still had fun and
i just wanted to to do a quick fun
stream with you guys where i can
interact with you guys by playing with
you that's all i wanted so i'm satisfied
[Music]
in training for a week oh well i can
already tell that your reoccurring
headaches are not a great sign please
take proper care of yourself as your
health is precious and you are a source
of happiness for a lot of people thank
you thank you thank you that's very kind
of you
um the headaches have been way less
though than that one time where i had
like a headache every day
oh it's already much better but
yeah who knows it could be so many
things the reason for why i'm getting
those headaches
uh recently it's not been that bad
though i just genuinely feel generally
exhausted
from streaming and
i also feel like
um after one year of doing a lot of long
streams where
i
i talk
so much
and
want to give you guys some
anecdotes from my life and all that i
just feel like i ran out
and you know i can take a day off and
hang out but whatever happened in that
one day uh i i will be done talking
about in one stream
in in like five minutes so
i wish i had more things to talk about
i feel like uh with long streams like
minecraft or
jrpgs i need something to talk about
otherwise it's just getting really bored
and boring and it stresses me out too
um
[Music]
yeah
the problem is also that i don't
remember much from what happened uh
three year or more than three years ago
i really don't have many memories
uh i wish i remembered more childhood
stories but i think
another problem is that i just had
not a very spectacular childhood i don't
have so many crazy stories like ahmed
does for example
and my
my time as a teenager
like up to
up to 15 or so
there's also like nothing spectacular or
what do you call so-called a child no i
would call it a teenager definitely
and uh everything from after that is uh
some some clouds are
clouding my memory
for from everything that happened after
i was 15.
for some reason i can't remember
anything no but honestly i really i
really don't remember much from the past
10 years
[Music]
and even the things that i don't i want
to tell you there are some things that i
can't tell you um
so
i've been like really grasping for every
little straw
uh
and writing down everything that so that
i don't forget it like i wrote down one
thing that is so trivial but at least
it's something and i will keep it for
sunday to talk about
it's during my jrpg stream
uh
yeah
[Music]
it's something that i've been
uh battling with the cat the past couple
of streams
also during like the the egg endurance i
feel like if i had more topics to talk
about i kind of used all of them up on
the day before that because that was
also a long stream
um
but if i had more to talk about i
probably would have gone longer and
longer and longer but i felt like really
nervous
especially because it's a game that
gives you nothing
the game gives you nothing to talk about
besides screaming every once in a while
like eh my egg broke
so you really gotta step up your
entertainment game time to make more
memories yeah well i'm going on the
vacation soon but besides that
in order to make memories i have to take
days off and and do things and go
somewhere i don't know go to disneyland
or something that would be cool but then
again there's the problem i don't have
anyone to go with me and uh
unless i pay for everything
um
what's the name of the song oh well i
can give you the audio stock link
um open link in youtube usual
it's it's on on the japanese audio stock
though
but
you should be able to navigate it
here there you go
girls in the u.s you know what i would i
would totally do that 100
but you're you're asking for something
that's currently very difficult
[Music]
um next year i'm 100 doing that yo i
will i will travel all over america i'm
telling you i'm doing an
n a
[Music]
east coast anyway east coast west coast
middle coast i don't know
i don't know where they are i'm gonna
find them i'm gonna look for them
i'm gonna find them all i'm gonna catch
them all or or they could all come to
europe
they could all come visit me in europe
[Music]
but i really want to travel
and
[Music]
i've told you guys before that i've only
been like uh once
to america
and that was for a very very short time
so i don't only want to visit
north america for the sake of visiting
other members but also for uh you know
sciencing
and and i also want to go to canada
because i've never been to canada never
and and except for that mike guy i think
canadians are probably really cool so i
want to go to canada
sorry mike
[Music]
it's okay i don't i don't dislike you
i'm just being a bit salty i'm just i'm
just teasing you
yeah
like you teased me in mario kart
[Music]
world tour
yeah so eventually probably in 2022
i suppose because it's already october
now
yagara falls falls yes yes yes i want to
see that kind of stuff
must be like
it must be like so so stunning
i have one but at what cost exactly
that's mike right now
i want you to try soul food you mean
just like um you mean like for example
chicken waffles
is that what you would count as soul
food although that one is very specific
i know that is from a specific area
i know the existence of chicken waffles
dino food hell yeah give me all that
that sugary [\h__\h] give me those
milkshakes mmm
give me those burgers oh i'm all in baby
i'm all in
chicken waffles yeah i ate that in japan
there was a there was a restaurant in
tokyo
that specialized on food from there
where where is where is the chicken
waffles from again
what area in america
specializes in that where was that again
don't say the s word that's a bad word
which word
what did i say
south the south uh-huh
can we be a bit more specific america is
big
america is freaking big yeah california
it's from the from harlem not the south
where is the harlem
okay anyway there was this restaurant in
tokyo that specialized on that and they
had chicken waffles so i gave it a try
and i have to say it's interesting but i
just love sweet waffles way too much
like
chocolate syrup on top of it with
berries and ice cream vanilla ice cream
oh
all that kind of stuff i love that way
too much i'm i'm such a sweet tooth
butter
[Music]
caribbean food real caribbean what's
real caribbean food
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
is jamaican what's aki
[Music]
oh
oh it's a it's one thing
it gets recommended as one thing aki and
salt fish
oh
oh interesting what is that what the
hell
it looks
good
what the hell
salted cod
looks it looks yummy
does it have a very fishy taste
[Music]
ever heard of that same for me
it is a fish i i don't really eat much
fish dishes but this looks
like noodles
would you try durian i've i've never
i've never tried durian before
[Music]
isn't that really in
is that really stinky
i've heard that a durian is really
stinky but i guess the the actual taste
of the fruit is good
i don't even know if i've ever seen a
durian before
i don't think i've ever seen one
oh funny thing in german it is called
stinky fruit
stink fruit
apparently
stinkfort
they gave it the name stinkflocht stinky
fruit very original
[Music]
it gives you a um
explanation of what it is already in the
name
very cool
[Music]
the german yeah
german names of things are very
straightforward
all right let's continue in the super
chat a little bit captain from the bolt
thank you
he who eats faces tankish and saric
dankesh and centennial robot
kfb project channel duncan
is it just me or did viva la chiara.com
update or do you mean the
what an advertisement
do you mean what i've built the picnic
because i saw that or did anything else
change
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god there's so much here
let me move that mute
there's so much going on here this is so
cool
so cute
[Music]
you guys should check out
vivalakiara.com
do it
so sean tuckert thank you soon flavorful
defensive language and thank
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh apple fact number two apples don't
shatter when you drop them hahaha apples
rub
eggs are better still but apples are all
right
apples all right
you you've received mixed messages in
terms of whether you want me to let you
win i pass you and you tell me to slow
down but then i come in 11 and you're
confused with that i don't know i don't
remember i don't understand what you're
talking about i don't even remember that
i don't know what i wanted
i wish i could tell you what i want what
i really really want but i don't know
what i want what i really really want i
wanna i wanna i wanna i wanna i wanna
just really really really wanna win
mario kart
give me your dance
[Music]
no no i saw her coming that's why i read
it so slowly he didn't change his name
yet i know that name already squiggly
mustache thank you for the pinky
so many kfb depths takadashi will take
over glory to tentacult
[Music]
i like the tentacles and i like the taco
dances they're pretty sweet they're
pretty cool and chill
but no we cannot let them take over
hey feet revive
everyone who died yesterday i will give
you a feather to revive right now
we can't be outnumbered no no no no no
[Music]
belle stop thank you for the pinkie
what is chicken's favorite shoe brand
[Music]
rebook
is that a shoe brand i don't even know
that so it's not really
not really funny to me
reebok
is that a shoe brand
well at least the chat is laughing
[Music]
at least the chat is laughing so i think
they'll start that one was successful
[Music]
the next day the kfb warehouse came to
the tangible's office to report on the
inventory potential this month we lost
24 times more eggs than before
eggs do you have a clue how the hell
would i know
um
i need to i need to um could you could
you hand me those reports um
i just want to check them
um
i just want to check if everything's
correct on them
please hand me those reports so i can
deal with them accordingly
to the policies of uh this company
[Music]
okay
i'll send you some
spices for your curry over by the way
later
i'll send you some spices dark gray
spices
look forward to it
alcatraz one three three one damage
[Music]
korean name
you died quickly
alexis hinojosa
just use it a bit to raise the amount of
word they would be willing to give you
interesting thank you
we are begging you egg
these eggs can't handle
much longer any more depths and we'll
have an issue with the poultry guys
ah that's the first time i've heard that
one yo
very original i wish you much cluck
thank you moon dog
[Music]
thank you i should i should treat myself
again to some oreo shakes and
and crispy chicken burgers oh
yes
today i'm eating um something i ordered
today though i ordered breakfast
and it arrived while i was um
while i was helping out pick when i
simply on minecraft
and
i i ran over to receive my
my order
my food order anyway i was so smart to
order a
dinner for later as well
that moment and the whole uh everything
about that was great
i'll keep that story though for sunday
my commentary on that i'll keep that for
sunday because i need something to talk
about on sunday
um how was that breakfast that was 5 p.m
what well i mean
i actually know i i did i was awake long
earlier than that but i waited on
breakfast because i was doing other
things what was i doing i i was picking
questions for holo talk even before i
had breakfast
because i need i wanted to get it done
early so that
genma could help me and didn't have to
wait any longer
[Music]
treat yourself before you wreck yourself
i heard that in a show before
is that just a general saying
yeah breakfast technically is just a
meal that you you're taking
first on the day
it is from parks and rec
i love bikes and wreck
i've been recently uh feeling like
re-watching
some old show that i watched before but
i've re-watched parks and rec and all of
those
fairly recently
so i wanted to rewatch um the tutors
sometime soon
cuz i really really really loved the
tutors when it came out i was quite a
lot long younger than i am now
no i'm not done with superstore yet so
i'm still
watching superstore and it's really fun
really funny i can really recommend
superstore i've had some giggles and
chuckles
normally i don't laugh at all when i
watch something alone
squidward game yeah i'm not gonna watch
that
even in the holo in uh discord
it has been mentioned and some some of
the girls talked about it
and i was like i'm not gonna watch that
because that looks like something i
don't like and
who was it i think was it callie or
let me see
[Music]
yeah kelly was like i don't i don't
think you would like it at all kiara
yeah
she enjoyed it though
yeah i i looked at the description and
it's just
not something i would want to watch
i'm i really for those times when i'm
not streaming i really just need
something uplifting and happy or like
something call me comedic
[Music]
wow well my voice is already starting to
get rough already how is that possible i
think i know why
because the the heating
turned itself on
even though it should be off
in my room
and the air is getting dry because of
that i think
[Music]
i think
it really feels different if it feels
also very hot
it's weird
no no no no
no
i do have a humidifier i just didn't
think i would have to use it already now
it's literally just started being
october
happy and uplifting like the handmade
sale that's a different story because
that is just so oh my god the quality of
that is so good
and the tutors isn't uplifting either
but it's really nostalgic to me and i
just want to watch my beautiful
beautiful
anne berlin
aka natalie dormer because she's hot
she's my bae
and i haven't watched the tutors in a
long time so it's time for a re-watch
time for a re-watch game of thrones i
rewatched that this year as well so i
need to re-watch something that i didn't
re-watch in the last
one to two years
no i'm not going to watch skit squid
game that's what i just said i'm not
going to watch it
not too endor yes
i'm i'm i'm glad there's some cultured
people in the chat who appreciate her as
well
[Music]
that henry actor is also quite handsome
but
natalie norma
is my waifu
this court
what are you doing here
in my super chat ratings
you should have been here doing mario
kart discord let's do one versus one
mario kart discord come on race me
raise me
you for coming though hello i'm i'm
flattered
discord loves my tangents too
hey
they all come for the tangents
[Music]
one versus one me bro
cash me outside how about that huh we
are scared at your scooter
i think they didn't watch the actual
mario kart part
or they just they just know how to
flatter a phoenix
they know they know
discord
you're a good good good chicken
i respect you know how to treat a
phoenix
smooth
at least i won against kura once it was
uh a 12
12 people
tournament
yeah yeah yeah with more more uh
more opponents it's a different story
they were just simply in another v2
stream which one which one they scored
which one
which one where it was more important
than me tell me
tell me discord
cashing our good kfb card and higher
bills
you want to take bails away from me
what
this girl you want to hire bail she's
busy
she can't work for discord
are you are you are you telling me
you're
you're a bail stamp now
she's busy in the bottle right yeah
she's she's in her little hidey hole
not taking
new jobs
she's already multitasking too much
so
so who were you stepping on before me
[Music]
you would if you would say that you
would kind of be breaking the full fruit
but i'm asking you directly we can't
hire you because you are a ceo
oh you say that you would you would
prefer to hire me over bails
but i'm already in the ceo
hmm
i am indeed very busy i'm in the very
busy but we we we
can't we can be good partners
partnership with discord
[Music]
bae is picking up everything true
true i must i must uh close the door
from her hidey hole so she can never get
out of there
i must i must create a door first of all
there is no door at all
your squad is playing kia like a fiddle
hell no they're not playing me like a
fiddle now
no no no if i told discord to do
something for me i'm sure they would do
it for me i'm just i'm just nice i have
a nice tension so i don't do that
i don't i don't have many requests at
all i'm satisfied with this chord
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
no they didn't answer my question
they're scared they are scared
[Music]
are you predicting what i was to say
very funny and very very interesting
writing in korean
norman nomu kamsa
[Music]
does that come across as what i wanted
to say
it sounds so short
[Music]
please
use it again
oh this is completely different
[Music]
it makes me feel more useful to hear
that not even our feathers go to waste
yeah
true true true although i'm not sure of
the cleaning soul part since i think i
probably need someone to clean my dirty
soul in mind
what
surprise pikachu face be like
what you have a dirty soul in mind
feelings no way
i always thought of you and say so you
never show the dirty side of yourselves
to me and i don't don't worry i don't
i'm not saying i want to see it but i
thought you would say so feeling sal
felix say so
isn't that your name
he never said so yeah but but he didn't
need to say so because i knew he would
say so it came across that way
i've been deceived
i i don't i don't care i'll still think
of you as say so
thank you for the generous donation
felix
as always
thank you
[Music]
thank you for avenging the fallen eggs
how did i avenge them
[Music]
i don't remember
i don't remember i did something good
apparently
by winning oh
i guess so i guess so i guess so
yes you did super chat
thank you jackson you're welcome
anything for my echoes
lo naivety thank you and centennial
is this violet evil garden
you changed your profile picture to
mummy
what happened
i thought you were violet evergarden
simp
what
why is it
you're such a ddd
oh my god
you gave up your violent evil garden
waifu
is that how much she meant to you
nothing
[Music]
wow okay
i understand
[Music]
m
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the pinky
excellent job daniel thank you thank you
thank you
i appreciate your support
thank you for believing in me
and being there
on that marathon was not much of a
marathon but still
i was just too good at it
[Music]
thank you tanja for completing it and
taking good care of the thousands for
egg proud of you kiara aka golden
eggiana pro gamer
the golden egg
has been given to me
as a reward
i should i should put the golden egg
somewhere in this office
you know like the
maybe someday something will hatch out
of it like a dragon or something we
should put it in the office
[Music]
a gamer
it beside you golden yogurt wait is
there golden yellow here no
actually there is no golden yellow here
only in the kitchen
do you play one two three four that is
your naked chicken nuggets
[Music]
[Laughter]
he doesn't want to be a watermelon
anymore i told him you have to stay in
watermelon what happened
we need a watermelon here
good watermelon
stay stay watermelon you're yummy
[Music]
to improve listening skill it's so sad
when i can't understand you
improve listening skill
um
watch
and netflix with subtitles
with subtitles
so but but not korean subtitles
watch a show in english with english
subtitles
that's the only advice i can
easy advice that i can come up with
right now
but so that way you can read it while
listening to it
i think it helps
[Music]
of chad
big kissy to you
no message with that well thank you for
the generous writes of the chat i
appreciate it very much thank you your
sweetheart
it was not necessary but
thank you thank you thank you monkey
five one zero donkey shin
there's so many korean names you
because i streamed at a good time for
them for once i think
i'm gonna
kill the high school
why did you and your name kimara
it sounds like my name
thank you for the red superchat kamsa
september 30th it's my birthday please
congratulate me p.s
[Music]
uh wait
is the most popular in the world
oh
well happy happy birthday to you ah
[Music]
kimada
congratulations it's one day late but or
two days late actually i hope i hope you
still get to hear this
you're probably sleeping right now but i
hope you had a lovely birthday
thank you
[Music]
logical paradox
kfb
wait but the gibson asks for the title
of usual room security guard yes of
course
no wait no no no no i'm not giving that
to you i don't trust any new people
working at the usual room uh you can be
usual
uh
now
usually room
button
cleaner
button polisher that's your job
and calorie court also asks for a job
kell mccoy
i i don't know much about you or
anything at all but you may be the kfp
um
[Music]
burger wrapping
machine
[Music]
i hope no one already has that jump
pudding channel dancer logical paradox
and misfits
thank you for the red super chat
wrapping with w
liquid p says hello tanja i would like
to give you my first ever super chat you
have been an amazing person this whole
year and you as well as the girls
brightened up my life just an hour ago i
had my alright i had my wisdom teeth
taken out
all right i already gave you
words of encouragement by now i hope
you're doing better how long does the
pain continue after you get your wisdom
teeth
taken out how long does it continue
this is like two days ago now
i hope you're fine by now
i managed to see a stream thank you
a few days oof
oh man i'm up to a week what ouch
well liquid p
please get well soon
and thank you thank you for your first
ever super chat it's an honor i will
gladly accept it
thank you for your generosity and your
support and your love
mwah
thank you also for a red super chat
let me join the brazilian gang i'm not
really good with words dancing i'm shy
but i would like you to have my first
red super chat i didn't know about whole
life before you oh
you've changed my daily routine for the
best kiara and i'm very thankful
obrigado my ocean and i wonder how you
got to how you found me if you didn't
know how life before me
maybe i asked this before
thank you though i'm glad you found me
you're very very talented
i think nowadays you don't use your
phone anymore but i know that otakumari
art oh interesting i know that you were
doing your clips
with editing on the phone and that's
crazy
already back then you were so good so
thank you for your support it's really
cool that you decided to
jump in by
doing something like that
thank you
thank you for all the support
elvis also a red super chat
yo
the
brazilians thank you
thank you thank you you added some
russian text
could you see
what
[Music]
what is that what's that mean
what does that mean
oh it means chicken
elvis
i see you in the chat
[Music]
did i already give him a kiss
i want it back if yes
i want it back
[Music]
i did give it back
refunding the case now
give it back with back but but just i
don't know throw it don't don't give it
directly i don't i want it directly
elvis
didn't you used to be a bit more polite
to me now you now you're trying to tease
me
oh i understand you must be in love oh
you must be head over heels for me i
understand that's that's how boys do
that
[Music]
boys
boys be boys
oh
[Music]
i'm not even gonna bother to look up
what that means
is that gorilla ramos thank you for a
red super chat
[Music]
it says there was a poll and talking
with people in the comment section
apparently i'm down bad for takanashi
kiana
a porn where
a king of people outside of caffeine
not sure what they mean anyway really
enjoying the content
oh i don't know what you're talking
about what pool is that
[Music]
but it's good to know you're down bad
for takanashikiya
[Music]
isn't it like your birthday in a few
days
[Music]
isn't it your birthday soon
i think i saw it on twitter
the fourth
oh in two days
[Music]
i hope you have
a great great birthday
with friends
and with presents and with a good good
good cake your favorite cake
thank you for your support and your
pinky thank you soon
treat yourself
not only me don't treat me treat
yourself
[Music]
beautiful beautiful honey
back to super chats here is that korean
ramen thank you for the red subject
again
big kisses to you thank you for the
support
hot today
[Music]
and jacob 47 outstanding looking for the
top thank you for
two pinkies why do i feel like i already
read this one before
i did
i did didn't i because i sang that uh
not
yes i did i did i did i remember i sang
the nut birthday fit song
yeah yeah yeah thank you again looking
for the top
boo hoo seven two three dangerous and
black friction thank you for the red
super chat
one kiss please
real talk though thanks for always being
there your streams are always so fun
made this past year much more enjoyable
[Music]
you're quite a charming woman keanu
by the way still haven't missed the
stream yet hey what
perfect attendance let's go holy [\h__\h]
are you insane how did you do that
how did you do that
but happy did you like watch everything
live or or or at least some of them as
vods i don't realize you're like
very often you're here
are you here now black friction
oh there you are you work from home
that's nice i hope that doesn't change
anytime soon
because a lot of people had to change
from working from home to working
normally again
and therefore can't catch my stream so
much anymore
i hope not to well if they tell you if
they tell you that you gotta work from
their office or whatever again then you
tell them that you are um
you have an illness
the chicken
pox or something like that
and it's been going on for a year now
and you just
you're uh
if you get too close to anyone they'll
they'll get it too
and it's very dangerous for adults
especially
so
you you can you can convince them that
you have to stay at home for working
[Music]
it's a special case it doesn't it didn't
go away for over a year i don't know why
but it's a special case isn't it i know
i know
i know i know if they have doubts about
it they can call me
my number is
zero zero
five zero
nine one
eight seven
one one one
two
just have them call me
okay
good wouldn't wanna
get rid of you
[Music]
more than one kiss
i tune in while delivering pizza yo can
you deliver something to me
please one uh pineapple and pizza pizza
thank you
so
much and now we're done with the ones
from yesterday
yes
i'm gonna read the ones from today
indeed
i was running out of ideas for mario
kart thumbnails because up until now my
mario kart thumbnails always looked so
energetic and
and rainbowish and crazy
and now i went for a simple style
but it stands out that's good
many mario tutorials
[Music]
why are you blushing and looking at
mario on the thumbnail
because i'm about to eat him up
[Music]
can you give us the image you used
you mean of my face or of mario
i don't have the image anymore
i just
i didn't save it i think i know it
actually i still have it open on
photoshop
[Music]
why would you want that you want it
without the phones
and without the mario
give us the mario
let me see it
i can give it to you
[Music]
it's nothing special though
it's
nothing special
[Music]
you gotta take a screenshot though
there you go
here
take the screenshot do it
[Music]
it's just me
staring
did you get it okay done
done
okay patrick and daniel wait do we want
to change the music i want to change the
music it's very repetitive i love it but
it's very repetitive
yo my mind
[Music]
oh
no no no no no that's not it
hmm
[Music]
guitar
oh this sounds like something that you
could play at the end of a movie when
the credits are rolling down
[Music]
after a happy ending
oh
that reminds me of something it's
october
wait i forgot something
ah
wait come with me guys i'm going to be
in the office again one moment
[Music]
where was it where was it
where did i put it
[Music]
i can't find them even though i'm so
organized
all right all right all right let's save
it again
uh where is it where is it
there it is
[Music]
now let me find the
let me find a a spoopy let's go to the
office one second
i wanna uh spoopy music for the opening
screen can we look for that too
[Laughter]
one second uh uh i need the second
second window in audio stock here hey
hello
how about the retro retro halloween
music halloween
hello
hello halloween
it is super cute isn't it dakuma made a
mental
version for halloween
thank you
i love it
halloween
oh my god
[Music]
it's retro it's swingy it's jazzy
oh hell yeah
but does that sound like halloween
it doesn't
i think does it
it's fun
i think i can see this as getting you
hyped up for a stream
[Music]
i can use i i click at one song and it's
already so good like i don't even need
to look at the other ones
i'm a replied
alpha says oh
cute i love it thank you i will use it
she got really excited about it oh my
gosh
she really likes it
she likes it
okay let's go over to the learning
screen
and
sorry this might be loud please turn
down your volume volume for a moment
sorry i should have warned you earlier
was that was did that
hurt your ears
[Laughter]
i should have maybe waited for a moment
all right
i did warn you i didn't want you but i
shouldn't win one more move
[Music]
okay this is our new annual waiting bgm
i love it i love it i freaking love it
so
uh we are still missing something for
now though
which one was i listening to this one
i like it but
oh this dog
oh
oh my god
[Music]
oh
no no this is not for halloween
it's just for super chats
oh it's so good but it's not really
super chatty
[Music]
should we get a halloweeny song for
super chats too though
maybe we should
halloween
what is this it's a jingle
[Music]
no i don't like it
i need something more like um
like happy
happy
[Laughter]
[Music]
halloween
famicom
[Music]
you know what this would fit for the
opening screen uh even better maybe
because it's really 8-bit like the like
the
like the actual
uh
image
[Music]
wait and then combine that
combine that here
[Music]
oh
it fits well doesn't it
because of the retro maybe we should use
the other one for now
i already forgot what it sounds like
let me listen
oh it's right so much so this just for
now for now for now i'm downloading the
famicon the 8-bit one
[Music]
i wasn't even reading super chats
okay
[Music]
i can't watch today sorry agent is busy
you know what i said sometimes joke like
a spy
and but the reason i did that i i did
keep that hashtag work hashtag yellow
you're only one who i am watching and
agent is my real life job
you're joking right you you're joking
right
don't misunderstand me too i'm a spy
at my pinky super chat i meant hashtag
yo classic yolo is my mistake oh no
don't worry
i didn't think i'll i don't know what is
owl
oh
yeah because if it's yolo it could mean
you only love owl
no problem
i know i know deep in your heart
you love me
and me only
[Music]
what does it say though and there's some
korean text here as well
[Music]
what
um
are you are you trying to eat me
[Music]
who is that
where is that mod i don't uh
i don't remember giving mud to someone
with that name honest question who is
that honestly just on this question it's
okay to make a mistake
by accident writing uh
accidentally writing uh
in the chat but who is that
[Music]
i gave out three new mods yesterday
who was that
oh you didn't i it was midnight okay
okay
no problem don't worry about it it
happens
so thank you my fame
hashtag will catch you remember that
remember that write it on your hands
with a marker or something
looking for the top tangential
[Music]
just gotta imagine me cheering you on
what the hell come back
chocolate insomniac dance
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky yeah let's say
that bregenz is in danger of being sent
to another dimension
there is a way to stop this but it will
make goodness speak in maltese for a
moment what if a monk what
with knowing that kuda will not be mad
at you make you feel fine about doing
this to her
that is so random
i don't even have a connection with
brilliance
i don't care
also what how do you what smell tea is
that language
[Music]
i am very confused
but anything if gooda wouldn't be mad
then of course that would be a relief
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
it's the language from malta
oh i know about malta i didn't know they
had like their own language though
yeah bgm is too good i know
it's troublesome
and thanks zombie
zombie duncan
cyrus
and thank you
i swear i was planning to wait at the
finish line for you but i forgot the
gliders on her brace ah
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
we talked to a japanese super chat told
me about that that show that i mentioned
during the mario kart driving
that uh comedian show that i really
really love that happens every year at
new year's and they told me that from
this year on they're not doing it
anymore because one of them
one of the
guys who
one of the comedians he's just too old
for it and he doesn't feel like he can
do it anymore
which i understand they've been doing it
for how long 20 years or so and he's
like 50 over 50 or so
no it's so sad that show was so good and
everyone was looking forward to it at
the end of the year it was like the
highlight
it's really sad
[Music]
it's a ninja
that's unfortunate i hope it comes back
but
dots
[Music]
gotta watch the old ones then
i think i i've definitely missed one at
some point i don't know did i watch the
one from last year
did i watch the one from last year
i might haven't
[Music]
i've come to offer you a choice you take
the red pill and you have to watch
birdemic till the end
is that a serious
take the blue pill you play it safe but
you have to give this rebellious
takodachi a hug the choice is yours
what
burdemic is a movie a bad movie a
terrible movie
let me look it up
[Music]
very damage
shock and terror
came out in 2010.
this is a funny movie
oh my god
[Music]
there's gonna be a third
third birdemic in which sea eagles
attack excuse me what there's more even
though it was so bad
watch along
[Music]
let me i want to see a trailer
let me mute i want to watch a trailer
which one do i watch
the official birdemic shotgun
terra theatrical trailer
okay i'm gonna show you guys
why do you all know about this and i
don't
severine
is that
that is horrible acting
silicon valley dream
present
driven by passion
oh my god do they do they take
themselves seriously
the producers of this
is this supposed to be serious
one million dollars
they did at first
no
way
no way
flocks of seagulls and crows what about
the chickens and chickens safe
it's fake it's photoshopped in there
this is the whole movie just a big
photoshop
oh my god we have to watch this
we have to watch this
the bird behind the window
no
oh this looks so bad
oh
my oh what did they just [\h__\h] on them
but like
20 liters of [\h__\h]
liquid [\h__\h]
terrifying animal
uh
our new crazy movie of the greatest
night of these are fake
these must be fake
this movie had to be seen to be believed
i believe that
nice critic
no
this is horrible all right
[Music]
i don't know it's like you know watching
shitty movies together like for example
the b movie i suppose
uh or cats
uh which was great though
can be very fun
because it's so ridiculous but this
seems to be on on a whole nother level
i would recommend violet evergarden more
well of course of course of course that
is like no that's two different worlds
uh
um
i
i will have to think about this one
that's a tough choice squiggly mustache
i'm not sure if we could actually really
have fun with this in the first few
seconds i thought yeah maybe but by the
end i was like
um this might be so bad that it's like
not even ironically enjoyable
oh my god
was a pleasure losing to you in the
first race
i totally won without you stopping
i believed that
[Music]
burps are dinosaurs
megan dinosaur is not extinct
we are dinosaurs guys you hear that you
hear that
action are in
oh
what
that's interesting
[Music]
foreign
you just want the hook off
[Music]
i sent you a hug please receive it in
the mail in the following free uh
workdays
kotoni 87 gaming function
you're healing from a vr related injury
what
thanks for keeping me entertained while
i cannot play have you ever suffered a
gaming related injury please be careful
when you play no
i don't think so
but i hope you get well soon that sounds
uh [\h__\h] up
[Music]
an opportunity
[Laughter]
[Music]
i lost my bet let's go what did you bet
did you bet i would win against gouda or
i would lose against gulen
what did you bet
[Music]
are you on my side or not
i bet you would win
[Music]
and you lost it
i love you though hi chokers by the way
thank you for believing in me see i lost
i i won later on so hello
i went against her when other people
were involved so i think you
you you didn't lose your bet but i will
not refund the money though
hey
hi
[Music]
thank
speaking of talking a lot on longs and
long streams recently homo memphis have
been having voice problems or managing
their streaming voice
huh managing their streaming voice do
you think about this for yourself
i'm surprised your voice hasn't given
out once since you provide so much
content
i mean it does it does give out though
i'm
i'm i don't i don't my voice feels very
rough a lot of the times when i stream
uh especially around the end
mm-hmm
so we say changed her voice
i gotta be honest i never really noticed
such a big uh difference
never really noticed such a big
difference
cough drops yeah even with those it
doesn't help that much
[Music]
yeah but no i'm fine um i'm struggling
more with the
content
but in general i'm fine content and
mental
exhaustion
if she hadn't said it i wouldn't have
noticed oh
me neither susan sounds like susan
that's what i thought it's just a bit
deeper that's that's about it
yeah
wasn't a big change which is good i
suppose it's a good thing
yeah martin senpai i
i'm glad she's taking a full month off
um
and really trying her best to properly
heal now and and i hope that also gives
her
you know not only time to heal her
throat but also
just really chill and relax for a while
it's good like how long has she been in
a whole live
now without a freaking break
so many of the whole life members have
yet to take a single break
like when i say break not only one day
but
maybe a week at least even a week is
like for one year
a week
[Music]
i mean for japanese standards that's
that's
not somewhat normal
but like for me for someone like me
[Music]
it sounds crazy because like people here
they take like several weeks of
vacations per year
and and if they don't do it they get
like
in my old workplace the boss would like
force us to take vacation
the option of not taking a vacation
didn't exist
so i always always
like to advocate and tell the japanese
members whenever i can that they should
take more days off
yes
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
thank you
did you hear me album junkies
[Music]
oh they're getting impatient
i only streamed for what three four
hours today chew three and a half
huge king cobra thank you should make a
little donkey soon
gentle chainsaw thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
hi boss i was just wondering if you've
ever given streaming um
streaming oh the game
looking forward to serving kfb as always
ah almost like i haven't
no
i'm not planning on it
uh
i know it was a very popular anime and
phone game
for a while but currently no
no no no sorry
hey cake thank you for the red super
chat again thank you wow
let me read why are you writing in
korean
[Music]
in korean he writes japanese
it's japanese but it's with korean sign
uh um
letters
and it says
[Music]
good work on your stream uh
ah he makes
he kind of makes in
he he makes the lucian senpai regular
senpai
and marine senpai
good job
did i miss someone
big brain place yeah
[Music]
but but none of this it was something
that russia and senpai used to say but
she doesn't really say that anymore
i watched a clip about that the other
day
where she talked about that because it
got recommended to me recommend it to me
sneeze
nope it's gone
it's gone
yeah she used to say that but she
stopped saying it because
she feels like it
there's like too much distance
between her and her viewers when she
says that because it's very polite
i shall be blessed another day thank you
you don't have tonight yeah what the
hell man
know this one right now
happy spooky mom thank you
[Music]
there there will be some special collabs
i think at the end of the month around
halloween probably not on my channel but
i kind of want to do something as well
on my channel
for halloween uh like a collab but it's
already so busy
[Music]
so i'm like i've there's probably not
even any time to squeeze in any more
collabs on halloween
[Music]
but i will play
one or two or three horror games
um around
the week where halloween happens by the
way
what is little nightmares
i've heard that's kind of a spoopy game
so i thought maybe we play it
around halloween
a platformer
little nightmare
a walk a fun little one that sounds
ironic horror side scroller more
psychological oh poor irish platformer
really
a very scary platformer oh my god i
might give it a try then
in the halloween week
as someone who hates scary stuff i think
it's a great game really
then then okay that motivates me to give
it a try thank you
yeah we got permissions recently so
um
[Music]
oh i i just assumed so
i think it should be fine
very kind of you don't shine ahoy indeed
ahoy
[Music]
mclrn zed said thank you
thank you for your first super
chat honey i'mma thank you for the
thinking again i don't know if you're
here still but thank you for your love
oh thank you thank you
thank you so much it says i must send
more love for you i work very late and
always get a lot of happy while
listening to your life thank you
oh i'm happy to hear that
i hope you can watch my streams more
often thank you so much for your support
i'm glad to see
your name pop up every now and then
miguel danke and i think we're almost
done
[Music]
this turned out to be a bit longer than
i thought it would be
[Music]
i i tangent it too much and i had too
much fun with the music
[Music]
the thumbnail is scary what's scary
about that is so cute though
i don't understand
kawaii
[Music]
then my my face is just scary from the
get-go and that's a bad thing
[Music]
the person who made a kfc christmas
family made it can't be halloween medley
[Music]
i have to listen to that
oh my god it exists
[Music]
oh my god
i love you
it's perfect
[Music]
let me tune that up for you guys oh i
love it
you guys hear that it's a bit quiet
[Music]
oh my god
i love
[Music]
i was hoping for someone to make
something like that
[Music]
hey but now i don't know when to use it
like during the normal stream or during
the evening or during the opening
oh my god
it's pretty long
[Music]
it's not just one 30 seconds loop it's
it's four minutes 40 of original stuff
whoa
always opening hey but i want to use it
more than just for the opening
it's no no
[Music]
no i want to use it all the time
oh
[Music]
wait but
this has several parts right
i wonder if i could get
several those parts like separated
and loopable
and then use one
for the opening one for the ending and
one for the main stream
[Music]
this is like a different part
but it's very
smoothly mixed in there so i don't know
if that would work to
cut it and loop it
you could split them in honesty it will
be [\h__\h] if i do that
[Music]
i love it
he used an organ strings
harpsichord
exilophone because of bones
pharah men because of ghosts
[Music]
wait i think it is actually looping
how did i listen to this is it looping i
think it's looping
rotate the music yeah i guess so i love
this
thank you i don't know if you're gonna
watch this but
thank you i love it
i'm gonna be using this
i'm gonna use it right now for the rest
of the super chest there's not much left
a few couples
[Music]
thank you for the
random bird trivia on the pinky
vancouver scientifically birds and
dinosaurs making dinosaurs non-extinct
conversely the common image of a flying
dinosaur the petite terrorist ours is
actually not a dinosaur
[Music]
i did not know that and i appreciate
that knowledge thank you
squiggly mustache donkey are you 18
frankie for the pinkie today's my
birthday i wanted to give you something
you made my year not only bearable but
also more than enjoyable
i'm glad to be part of kfp p.s sorry for
being a lurk on youtube chat can be
annoying sometimes anyway how are you
thank you thank you happy birthday to
you
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you your name is
perfect for this happy birthday to you
18. happy birthday to you
congratulations
don't worry lurking is okay i would
prefer everyone to be super super super
active but lurkers gotta lurk that's
okay i'm now gonna force you out of your
comfort zone whatever feels the best to
you that's the way how you should watch
my streams if you wanna watch them
quietly while doing something on the
side that's fine
as long as you oh
i just heard
i just heard click
in the background
you guys probably didn't hear that
because i was talking over it and it's
quiet for you guys but
he has my crowd
and crown sample in there
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay oh no that's so good you heard it
noise
that surprised me
thank you new 18 and i'm doing fine
thank you i'm looking forward to my
vacation next week i'm really
really really excited for that
i never i never was in a
wellness hotel
before so
it's going to be awesome
[Music]
that's the easter egg oh
it's like that one horse sample yeah but
this is better
okay we're done you gotta tell us when
when you're back of course i will of
course i will write it all down every
little moment
[Music]
i still got to do some things for that
just some some things but
yeah i hope you all will be there
tomorrow for supporting me and choco
sensei
and at the usual time now for her talk
11 pm jst
stay safe thank you i'm probably not
even going to leave my
apartment until
whole talk so
this is the safest place where i could
be
um
[Music]
thank you guys for
enjoying this music with me as well
i'm glad
that you guys
are open to exploring audio stuck with
me
michigan
thank you i love you guys
and in german we say i'll feed us in
take care of yourselves everyone have
some nice food
and make yourself comfy in your beds
with your animals or your
girlfriend bush with indoor or your
laptop
or your netflix
whatever it is
[Music]
your hot chocolate
or your tea
or your glass of wine
[Music]
i love you
i can't say it often enough i do i do
bye-bye
so
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do