[Music]
um
welcome welcome welcome welcome everyone
hello everyone no no i'm not clicking
yet
but it's okay you can say hello
welcome hello another whole live
collaboration between all of the whole
life myth members
yay
so uh we have uh um found
ourselves together here to a witness
the marriage of chiara and calliope
that doesn't sound correct to me
okay i guess it's just a normal
collaboration then
right
oh but we already have a priestess
[Music]
anyway so let's get right into it i'm
gonna call everyone's names and you
please introduce yourselves let's start
with my future wife callie
could you please not
i don't know what you're talking about
oh yeah
hello
hello everyone hello everyone my name is
yes let's all have fun together today um
i think that that is all that i have to
say for now
all right cash money yes cash money
next the small but dangerous gura
[Laughter]
i'm excited to talk to everybody yay
ah all right
then our priestess our
ancient priestess the priests of the
ancient ones
and um as kara said i'm the priestess of
the ancient ones
i mean not look human but i'm definitely
human
and i don't like cucumbers
i got a cucumber right in front of you i
was
i was put into the seat by a certain
detective
it was not my choice oh no
well you gotta eat it you gotta eat
what's in front of you otherwise it's
not grateful i would go to waste
our detective the one and only amelia
watson
hello i'm amelia what's up
hello i'm ian's number one detective
and today i am not investigating but
rather it is my day off
and never wear hats or coats at the
table
um yeah so today i'm in my proper attire
yay well i am wearing my hats because
i'm uh the store
owner here this is my first brand
of the chiara fried phoenix uh
future world dominating franchise
and oh i forgot to say my name
is as if you wouldn't know because today
we're hosting this
on my channel last week it was on
amelia's channel
this week we have we are here uh
so yes as i said it was
one week uh since his debut
so in this only single one week a lot of
things have happened
so i would like to ask all of you
how your experience in the first week
was since it was i think super exciting
for all of us
how was it for you callie
um well
are you sure are you sure that this
hasn't been going on for 30 years
because that is how it feels to me and i
am a raper i have lived for eternity
but the past week well it has felt very
long
yes like we've been doing this for a
long time
that is the first for me not to say that
it's a bad thing
um it has been i suppose as they say a
long week
now i finally understand the saying um
many things happened and i streamed
every day
yesterday also wow yeah
every day of the week i think we all
tried really hard
to make the best out of this first week
yeah but
you released so many songs in this one
week
and every every one of them was a banger
every single one of them
oh a banger thank you
thank you they were fire fire yes i know
that one
yeah we gotta teach you what banger and
bob means actually i don't know what
means what does bob mean
yeah they would definitely bop them or
like if you smack someone on the head
bop them on the head i thought that's a
bunk something hard or something starts
well good night how
it was very emotional um
very exciting um i think i also streamed
every day so
it was really fun too uh i felt like we
really all get got to know each other
and we got to know
all of all of you watching very well you
know and we we
uh learned more about about our
how would you say like all of our
communities evolved
does that make sense indeed indeed i
must agree little shark
and i had so much fun and and now we get
to we get to finish off a great week
with with everybody here and then i'm
tired but i'm so happy and i'm so
excited
it's okay you just eat your fishy and
then we can sleepy sleep
ina how was your week um
it was great um i think it definitely
felt
like longer than a week and uh
i think i was very at my pace but i was
also very nervous
at the same time meeting everyone
it was definitely an emotional
rollercoaster ride but yeah definitely
really fun
anything special that happened in your
week
um i guess well i was so proud to see
every one of us reach 200k subscribers
yes me too i was like tearing up every
time i think of you guys i'm proud of
how proud of you i am
[Laughter]
all right amelia how was your first week
had did you find any anything any new
information
in this week any clues
i i thoroughly investigated chat and
i had a lot of fun doing it yeah i'd say
though
uh the first week is pretty overwhelming
uh i went from not sleeping
like maybe two hours of sleep to then
like sleeping 12 hours a day
but yeah i still had a lot of fun
you guys don't sleep two hours a night
you got a bit more a bit more
sleep sleep is a concept when you're in
the v
chamber rabbit hole that's what i say
but i think in the in the following
weeks we don't
have to force ourselves to stream every
day as i think some of us will be taking
some days off too
to recover cover wink wink wink
what's that funny
you gotta cover all the vases huh yeah
okay now you're pushing it a little bit
now you're pushing
i'm sorry not sorry you're fine we also
had
a lot of accomplishments as just
mentioned so for example
all of us reached at least 200k
in this first week clap club
amazing i don't think any of us expected
uh to us growing so fast but of course
it is also thanks to
uh the senpais who built up all alive so
thank you all the stanford and thank you
to everyone who decided to support us
and we did not only reach those youtube
milestones though
we also uh were able to enable
uh super chat in the first week i think
three days in or four days in or so
way super chat yes
and uh we also by the way reached the
reddit milestone
reddit has been growing a lot since the
uh our generation has been announced so
welcome everyone to the reddit i'm
checking it out every day probably too
much
[Laughter]
but there's a lot of funny stuff going
on there so if you're not on there yet
maybe you should check it out
now before we get into some a warm-up
game i first would like to ask one more
question
what is everyone planning for the near
future like maybe the next
two or three weeks do you guys have
anything
coming up any new games you can tell me
that you want to start playing yourself
kelly you got something you looking a
bit crazy
sorry nothing nothing sorry nothing
um no this week um i'm
going to i'm going to stream some more
uh rpg maker games
and um also uh let's see what else am i
going to do
um i'm going to have an ergo riva
xing
oh no i'll save announcements until the
end let's go okay
i always write a sentence with an a i'm
sorry it's a tick i can't help it
it's okay an a a day keeps a doctor away
ha
um i would like to um play i'm pretty
sure a new amnesia is coming in
awesome uh sometime in october and i
would really
really really like to play that um
yeah we're looking forward to your
future adventures
what about um
well i want to do more drawing streams
of course
i'm gonna play a little bit of the games
i had in my backlog
i'll see which one which ones i can play
and if
possible i want to watch a movie with
everyone watching oh
you want to do that oh nice good idea
you mean like uh
you mute the movie but you watch it
together at the same time with the
audience right
yes yes yes it's popcorn yes popcorn and
snacks
[Music]
very chill should we watch a mafia movie
that'd be fun too dark
what a shame it's fine i'll watch it
with my deadbeats later what about
amelia are you planning any new
investigations or any more screaming
screaming um
um i have a lot of games i want to play
but i'm just like waiting
i guess right now i'm waiting a little
bit um
yeah apex and single player games that's
pretty much it um we have a collab
coming up soon for surgeon simulator
but i'll announce that at the end of the
stream oh
alrighty then uh yeah last but not least
me
i am actually even though i said
i don't want to speak german everyone
keeps
asking me to speak german so i have
decided to start something like a german
asmr
starting from next week or the next week
after
i'll be there yeah
no but i'll show if people really think
that uh
german is like an aggressive language
but that's not true
you can speak german in a very soft way
and i'll be showing you that
stay tuned for that
[Applause]
i'll continue with super mario as well
by the way
gradually
all right then now let's start
the warm up game although i think we
already warmed up
but yeah uh the warm-up game is called
hololive map random association game
[Music]
i i heard some very not excited games
yay i'm very excited for this game
[Music]
i'll explain the rules uh shortly i'm
very bad at explaining the rules but
uh like i think you got you my dear
friends
understand uh basically i do clap club
then i say a word
and next person does clap clap and
quickly says the word that they
uh some like instantly are able to think
of
when they think of the word that i said
and then they do
the next person knows and says another
word that is associated with the
word from before you know you get the
juice right what if it's not associated
uh it's okay as long as you think it's
associated but you gotta come up with it
quickly if you cannot come up with
something right away
then you are out of this round and we'll
continue without you we'll just be
moving on without you
all right just quick quick thinking we
gotta do some quick thinking here okay
so we go in the direction of uh
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let's go brain cells
scissors
[Music]
[Laughter]
the nightmares clown clap
the monster under my bed
club amelia oh
what what magnifying glass
clap clap murder you clapped three times
i clapped twice okay keep on am i
clapping am i clapping
okay we're going here we go okay
scary club clap halloween
clown club pumpkin club club
oranges tree
uh
[Laughter]
fertilizer cows
clap clap moo moo
moo clap
cows like can we repeat words
[Music]
didn't say we couldn't say the same word
twice
yeah when i heard that i was also like
wait do we keep on going or not
i think this round ended uh let's let's
let's make a rule to not repeat
any words again okay no okay
okay new round
[Music]
you love me don't you
phoenix
[Music]
thanksgiving clap clap
please save me
clap i'm hungry clown club dinner time
clap clap shrimp pop pop simp
pop money
coffins clap clap death
clap clap callie these favorite things
clap clap various weaponry good
clap clap cairos swords sword
murder we haven't used it this round
really
oh my princess
you're next am i going off with what she
said mafia yeah
oh the sopranos
what i said don't worry about it
[Music]
clap clap chicken den
isn't the chicken dance wasn't it like a
a maybe
[Music]
next meme
oh no okay okay i'm also uh
amelia i didn't hear you say it one more
time please i said clap clap meme
next meme club clap clap internet
cop dial up clap clap my bad
internet cop
oh
[Music]
nice nice nice nice knives so i'm happy
thank you i think we're all warmed up
now
uh it was a very intense fight i must
say especially between
cali and ame the slow
[Laughter]
yeah your internet is what killed amma's
brain
why would you do that with my programs
alright done now we shall start with the
main thing i will go to the loading
screen really quick
okay what about difficulties technical
difficulty
[Music]
do
welcome back sorry
for uh the little uh technical
difficulties it happens
it happens welcome back kick it again
and don't forget the arm ah oh yeah
thank you yeah so
uh we are now on this screen again
once again uh because last time
we did a quiz about ourselves about
what we like what we do but
now we gotta know a bit more about
where we are holo life so
i have prepared for you today to test
your knowledge
also the chat can also uh participate
a hollow live knowledge quiz
a lot of questions uh some are easy
some are difficult um i
advise you my dear fellow members
to not look in the chat or not look at
google sensei please
but your boy isn't a dirty cheater so i
will not
so shall we get right into it
yes yes
first question
[Music]
what is yeah a got other answers hidden
it froze again
no didn't we really yeah oh no
no ah one second time to go to the keys
[Music]
foreign
oh
we are back again
hello sorry about that sometimes
sometimes our combined mythical powers
freeze uh
everything the time and everything you
know since we're all kind of eternal and
timeless
things happen this is too much so let's
get right into the first question
what is what is hosho marin senpai's
nickname
and what does it mean please ryan i know
i know
no we are writing in the drawing thing
again this is just like last time
it's just like last time
[Laughter]
please write your answers quickly i
cheated
it's okay this time you can cheat but
not next time
i'm using my drag pad give me what
i'm using my mouse yeah it's hard to
uh write with the match but do your best
also
the meaning to amelia please
oh i hope you know you can guess
you can just check what everyone else is
riding
we got all the answers we can show them
i think
the answer is sencho and it means
captain yay i think everyone
everyone deserves a point
let me see is it here
uh no that was down here here
here and here and
[Music]
here and here by the way i have recently
uh been called tencho
which means store owner ah
yeah i'm one of the chose now i love
that
then next question please delete your
canvas okay ahoy
oh boy uh-huh i'm holding me
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm taking a note of that for later
[Laughter]
are you ready for the second question
yes second question is something that
you have to draw
and it's a difficult one possibly
[Music]
what is what is the
oshimark icon of
okami mio senpai
i'll give you 10 seconds for this one
[Music]
tell the answers uh
i have to say i'm surprised because
these are difficult you would not
expect this one from mino senpai
it is a tree
[Laughter]
so in this case only ina has gained the
points
congratulations you are in the lead now
you can delete your canvas everyone who
has a pickaxe oh [\h__\h] doesn't somebody
have a picture
yeah i think someone has that i'm not
asking i'm thinking of
difficult that was a good one
yeah right so are you ready for the next
question
yeah yeah it's one this one could be
easy you can just write the first names
uh great question
who lives in the so-called whole life
house
now i know i know i don't necessarily
need to trust what the others are
writing but i think all of you know this
i'll give you like 10 15 seconds or so
okay 2 3
4 5 6
7 8
9 10 11
and 12 13 14
15. i think we got everyone worked their
answers down you are quick
you are quick now let's show the screen
[Music]
yes yes yes indeed everyone uh deserves
a point for this now please delete your
canvas i hope the audience is
participating too
let's see if everyone in the audience
also got the
the question right or the answer
so oh you are quick with erasing i see
you see
let's go to the next question
now this one is quite the important
question
fourth question tam
i'll give you 10 seconds so you don't
look it up on google okay
ten nine
eight seven
uh six five
four three
two one
yay
it is indeed and i expected nothing
less from our whole life knowledge queen
ina
it is nice
i want a point
[Laughter]
there will be some easier questions too
don't worry
oh wait that was a wrong one human being
yeah i mean
well yeah it makes sense i don't know
please delete your canvas everyone
delete delete
has good chances yeah
okay i have another difficult one but i
give you a bit more time to think about
it
um how uh question
one two three
[Music]
how many members are there
in whole life japan i'm only uh please
only count
female japan members
you start now this is difficult
if you're one off if you're one off i'll
forgive you
okay hold on you can just guess
it's a lot it's a lot
maybe not that bad
does the audience know i'm watching the
chat
oh i see you two i saw one correct
answer
wow you guys don't know damn it get up
oh
lily ina
i hope you're not looking up something
he's doing math well i'm counting
she's calculating you know
i can't think of my head wait oh my god
wait uh
only female japan members
i'll give you eight more seconds
eight dollars
i can't count backwards three
two one
[Music]
okay
the correct answer is
32. i got it right
wow i totally guess what a surprise
nine good job callie
no actually i really did yes so i'm very
surprised yeah i'm also surprised you
got that one
nice good job
please delete your canvas numbers are
hard
good rng in my head you are close now
you are close
you're pretty close yeah
have you deleted your canvas yes okay
uh next one is another difficult
question
but if you miss one or two members
i might give you a point for this uh
one two three four five six seven okay
which members are included or where
included in the azure lane and hololive
collaboration
it's seven members go now
oh i really don't i think
inna might know this one since she's
into gacha
ina is going yes take your time with
writing so the others don't
peep okay
slow slowly
maybe give gouda some time to write her
out
[Music]
you can do it believe in yourself
there might be some members that you
would not necessarily expect
there
how many seven did you say seven yes
seven seven
it's been seven members does the chat
know
ho ho ho ho ho chat yeah
will do some people know i don't want to
cheat i keep looking by accident
[Laughter]
well even if you look at the others it
might be wrong okay
because i remember i didn't get all of
them uh seven well like we got
one two three four five it's seven yeah
but like i said if you miss one or two i
might give you a point because this one
is difficult
i got it i'm not even worried it was i i
think yeah you're what you seem very
confident in your answer
uh-huh i know i already know the answer
that's like the goal to answer if you
don't know then just go with that
what do you mean i do know it is on
purpose
in fact i looked it up full disclosure i
cheated i looked it up
okay i'll give you five seconds five
[Music]
it's okay it's okay the correct members
are senpai
senpai
[Music]
even if you got one or two wrong and you
just wrote the last one in the end it's
okay you get a point
for guru i'll give put our point two
yeah um wait how many did i get right
one two three four five
okay i'll give everyone a point except
cali
well it's okay i suppose i deserve it i
was a dirty cheater
and i got burned in the end so such is
life i suppose and this one is in
it wasn't it difficult especially since
we're there with so many names yeah
it's okay don't worry about it please
delete your canvas
next one is the easy one powerful next
one is super easy
next one is easy you can chill for a
second
let's go
home live japan and indonesia
covered which famous vocaloid song
oh gosh i know what it is but
come on come on i give you
a few seconds ah if we spell it wrong
it's okay don't worry about it
kelly are you okay if you if you can hum
it for me
uh i'll give you a point anyway i can't
hum
it
okay i think we got uh
what's that answer kelly something
something
[Music]
is another name for it right yeah okay
so we got
everyone get the point except
something something i love you okay i'll
give you a point because you know
you know which song it is any points
thank you it's like you don't have to
it's okay no
you got it i'm just going around fooling
around
maybe one day we can cover it too
i want to i want to let me fix it please
okay
okay if you want to work more then we'll
give you more work
yeah okay next question is a hard one
oh god we gotta get a bit faster
actually let me skip that question we
don't have so much time left oh my god
okay
um let me go okay
next question who was the first whole
life production talent that became a mod
on reddit
oh go
only one answer yes one one one talent
became the first uh
mod on reddit now there's a lot of them
also all of us are mods on reddit
we all have different others no
it's interesting that the chat kinda
knows the answer but
many others know think they know but
they don't know
[Music]
i'll give you five seconds
five four three
two
and many think it might have been koko
in the in the in the chat also a lot of
people thought so
but actually it has been archaea that is
why i said uh
who was the first whole life production
talent because that is the overall term
for all the talents ah
yes now please delete your canvas
we gotta move on we gotta do the speed
round
wait we should do like double points
come back round oh yeah wait i didn't
even give uh any points who was the one
who got it uh cali right
yeah good job next question who created
the name yaga who came up with it
she says easy don't look at my thing
amelia
i finished mine before yours
well i'm surprised you guys uh whoa
[Laughter]
okay we're ready already now let's show
the screen yeah
it was senpai and the reason behind
it was that i was not able to read the
kanji
of his name the first kanji so
she just read uh you know everyone's
using it how legendary
wow iconic
okay uh i'll go with one last question
please delete your canvas
going well i see
last question
it should be easy for me this is way too
easy
because i'm a big fan
[Music]
last question what is
third generation also known as
quick quick thinking uh
don't peep
so i mean like just how we are all alive
myth the third generation also has
ah
i was ichiban
yes ichiban hayakata
all right we got the answers locked in
now let's show the screen
the answer is hold on fantasy
[Music]
why am i actually giving myself points
as well the whole time
oh my gosh very sausage
well i guess i need to win too
wait but why then still why do i have
less points than enough
that's a good question
i guess i i don't know i'm stupid wait
i'm taking notes
oh well we have a winner why people
remember that didn't ena win last time
nina gets another girl
[Music]
satsuga because uh inna does indeed
know a lot about her life you know
for someone that has that apparently has
one brain cell
um you sure are winning a lot of these
quiz games i'm i'm
right now
she might be using her her book of the
ancient ones to cheat
into knowledge to become i don't think i
think it's worth an
investigation to check out what is
written inside her book emilia we should
maybe check it out
yeah it's suspicious that she won two
times
don't you think you should i think so
look into that i wanna
look at you what are you hiding in there
huh i'm very curious
we might want to look into that soon but
and now we are uh well we might just
do a little bit of overtime but let's
move on i have a last segment prepared
uh we have a loading screen really quick
oh okay okey-dokey
please wait a moment please thank you
[Music]
we back again we back again
we are back here resting and eating
and uh i see
i'm feeling rather large wait can i fix
my arm
uh does it hurt yeah i'll become smaller
and then i get up like i gotta put it
back into place looks like you're in
pain and you're leaving
[Laughter]
okay oh my god what happened
okay okay okay
that looked painful very painful it was
very nice
are we back nice what
yeah we're having fun oh we are back
oh yeah okay yeah we're back
oh thanks for uh calling an ambulance
no i i was my own doctor really quick oh
yeah right you're like
you're detective and doctor you can't
you have those back in the place
and probably didn't even hurt because
you got those injections huh
my anesthesia yeah
i broke it again
okay i'll stop messing with it one more
time
uh hold on okay
why why does it happen i don't know i
don't know
okay okay are we bad
yeah yeah we're good oh yeah you're good
oh man it must be hard to be amelia
it seems so painful sometimes i'm
flexible
oh yeah show me how
you can move your body yeah we'll do
that
move on to the next activity let's move
on to the next activity shall we
the last segment is
uh something like a
personality uh
something chart please show it oh yeah
i think you guys have seen this before i
don't know what it's called but i
thought it would be a good idea to
uh discuss where we belong on this chart
it's about
purity up until the arrow that shows uh
goes upwards is about purity so the
higher you
are the more pure and safer you are
and the one that goes to the right side
is about intelligence so the more on the
right side you are
the more intelligent you are or the more
you are on the left
you are stupid
what do you have to do to be low on the
purity one
amelia
which all this now but i think first of
all
we can kind of start discussing one by
one where we
think who where who who
where who belongs to well amelia is very
intelligent
so i think that she should be on the
very intelligent side but
she also said she's lucky true
maybe not is she pure though
she said
thank you for pointing that out that is
indeed true she said he's horny no
you guys miss him those injections they
i think if she's under the state of
those injections she cannot be pure
[Laughter]
but she's indeed very intelligent i must
say so
i would actually move her a little bit
more to the right
and a little bit more down
[Laughter]
does anyone have any objections about it
no objections no acceptance i mean you
can defend yourself though if you want
to defend yourself
no you guys are right i'm sorry
don't be sorry you are honest
that's wrong now why do we think ina
would belong to
um that's really on the left side
oh your face when you brainstorm one
brain cell
okay well if you admit it i mean
but what are we basing that on
the same knowledge that
doesn't that knowledge possibly come
from her book from the ancient ones that
keep whispering to her maybe she's not
the intelligent one maybe the angel
another intelligent one
that's a good argument i was smart we
would have taken over the world already
okay maybe she should be like in the
middle because we're not sure how
intelligent
she really is yet yeah right but she is
indeed pure she's
ended pure i must say unless any object
unless what does that mean wait those
tentacles those tentacles don't look
pure to me what where have those
tentacles been until now
on her back
and she's trying she's trying to look
pure with her
uh angelo angelo halo yeah
she's trying to i mean maybe that's is
that
inna is that a real angel's halo yes
see see oh sweet it looks like a big
onion ring to me
i'm hungry well
yeah we are i think we're pretty unsure
still about
inna actually what does that the
audience say in the chat do you think
she's pure or not
dear dear viewers there's something
about that smug face that is making me
feel a bit strange
yeah just your imagination
top right right oh
no no oh they say she's pretty pure
let's
okay let's let's yeah maybe a little bit
higher a little bit higher she can be
all right i think we got the right
position for
inna okay i'm okay let's move on
with kuda
where should the shark be
um what does the shark say
why would we think that she's not pure
has she eaten
human wait you're i'm pure what are you
talking about
that's not your name it's something that
you hear from an incur
[Laughter]
yeah i think she can be a bit purer than
that
and but yeah what about intelligence
yeah
short
top left many people say top left wow
you have proven yourself a bit stupid
[Laughter]
you're like yeah let's get her a little
bit higher a little bit
and a little bit more to love me oh yeah
directionally challenging
i think that's a good spot for gooda
any objection god no you can defend
yourself no
okay wow everyone just admits
to it wow what about keller this is
difficult because she's deaf
i am where would you
would you say you are pure
what does that what does it mean what
does it entail
[Music]
well what do you have to do
people are saying you belong to the
bottom uh the top right
there actually the opinions on you are
quite split actually some say
bottom some say top blue
middle right i wonder what bottom right
bottom
bottom middle wow they're so split on
you
we just don't know what we think about
death i'm confused
i don't understand why autumn right just
like
enlarge your picture so it's like the
entire thing
what do our members think do we think
she's intelligent i think
um
she doesn't know a lot of words for
example she doesn't know
yeah or or both or so
so yeah a little bit more in the middle
i would say when it comes to intelligent
intelligence
a little bit more to the left a bit more
oh yeah
a bit more a bit more other one right
right under kiara
my position is not fixed yet anyway
does being a murderer make you impure
yeah that's a good question
because if it does then i think then yes
maybe i said though
that you just uh kind of said that
you're a murderer even though you're
just deaf and you like taking the souls
the lives of the ones who murdered
but you kind of just said that you are
the murderer
i mean am i not i wouldn't say so
say
[Laughter]
so i would say you're pure you're quite
pure but under enough because uh you
still
kind of kill people yes that's right i
do take some lives
all right i teach big many good spots
good spot
now uh what about me i would say i'm
very pure and very intelligent
now hold on a minute hold on i wanted to
bring something up real quick
but when you say that you're very pure i
would like to remind you of the many
times you have come into my house
and said to me hey when are we going to
have a sleepover
i thought i saw the archives of your
live streams and some of the nasty
things that you said now oh
we're frozen again yeah one minute
technical just one minute please
we will do anyway you've been blessed
[Music]
we are back and in the meantime i have
seen a comment
in the chat from my papa my fuki papa
and my papa says i belong in the bottom
left
i don't know i think so
[Music]
your papa and i are on the same
wavelength it would seem
about words it's not a bad thing
don't you think i have kind of proven
that i am
quite the idol i am bro
i don't think you have to be i don't
think that
idol is always synonymous with purity is
it
um but say so
[Music]
yeah yeah please put me in the middle
you can put me
on the on the middle left if you want
but not
i i i am not impure don't feel bad about
it it is quite all right
um does anyone uh object to this
decision
of my of my position that's
it's fine amelia are you okay
amelia um my arm's broken but i'll i'll
fix it after
yeah the doctor's getting kicked out by
a professional
can you really go see an actual doctor
amelia i beg of you
what are you trying to say medical stuff
i mean if you end up messing it up real
bad i'm going to have to come visit you
soon
that sounds like fun
everyone keeps demanding that i belong
to the bottom left
i don't think you belong on the bottom
bottom person right like me
but like yeah
i guess a bit more to the left yeah
yeah oh and also you're also not stupid
either
oh thank you well i have just opened a
brand a
little fast food chain so i'm a
businessman
and i've made everyone work for me
instead of me working myself
so i think that is smart it's very smart
[Music]
but i think could you please move me a
bit higher
okay it's back it's back to where it was
before
oh lara the more that you beg to be
raised up i think the more
the more that you should be lowered you
can't allow that insecurity to interfere
you gotta accept yourself well if you
defeat it too much it seems like you
have something to hide co-wink wink wink
and nudge night
well but i said before bird brain equals
big brain therefore i'm smart
okay we can go with that and what about
your brain
how does that work
they stand for big brain bird brain big
brain
it's uh it's just how it's supposed to
be me
all right but i'll accept my position
i'll accept my position
just this one time we can do this again
in the future and see how we evolved and
how much smarter and purer or less
pure we got maybe in one year
all of us are at the very bottom
hopefully not like the point of that
let's do our best of charts
yeah let's do our best to stay who we
are in the future
and not change because i think the way
we are
we are the best
i agree well i said something good
all right then we will find it and uh
later
uploaded on twitter i guess so you guys
can take a look at it again and be
oh yeah yeah that's where they belong
now uh we have come to an end
unfortunately
this week's collaboration of holo myth
is
sadly ending um but i hope everyone
enjoyed today we sure had a lot of fun
the first week was very exciting it was
a roller coaster for all of us and i
think we
celebrated it in an appropriate way
today
and at the end if anyone has any
announcements please please speak
now or be quiet forever i'm not pain
we'll call an ambulance right away when
this is over
hey kelly you got something i do
recently uh the song that i released for
my debut
she said she must rip heart emoji
recently reached 1 million views on
youtube thank you guys
hi thank you everyone
uh-huh yeah it's very exciting contest
right that's right yes
in celebration we are doing a remix
contest um
so myself uh i have my acapella version
and also mr case has supplied all of the
stems
uh to the instrumental track and the
instrumental itself
so you can either visit my twitter it's
pinned in the comment
to go download all of the materials and
see all the rules of the contest and
what kind of prizes i will be giving
away
and where you can submit and i'm looking
forward to hearing everyone's wonderful
music
i am dying to hear it
thank you yeah that's really nice
it is quite exciting any other
announcements
uh we have uh ina and i
have a surgeon simulator collab i
believe for
tuesday uh we haven't decided on exactly
what time yet
but make sure you guys keep a lookout
we'll post it as soon as it's scheduled
which will probably be
tomorrow or the day after tomorrow yeah
very nice
exciting and uh i have one announcement
from
all of us uh since we recently
got superchat enabled we are currently
all working on
opening our memberships
so soon all of you can join our
memberships and support us
even more if you wish to do so of course
you don't have to but we're all
preparing it
we will not be openly opening our
memberships all at the same time at this
point
because uh we're all working on it
separately but i think you can really
look forward to it people all work hard
to give you some nice perks and nice
emojis and stuff
and so yeah look forward to that
and uh i think we'll probably do another
collaboration with all members
next week at the same day i think
probably most likely
so that that will be on a different
channel and but in the meantime
we'll see you uh so shortly
after probably good out good eyes
streaming uh afterwards right after this
end quickly yeah dark deception if you
want to see me be chased by scary
monkeys
so thank you everyone for coming today i
hope you enjoyed it this was our live
english first generation second
collaboration on my channel
thank you everyone for watching
hi everyone catch you upon the flip side
goodbye
[Music]
foreign