​​​ ​Would she know that?​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Mel-senpai we're talking about.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll be the women behind the curtain.​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know...!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no idea...!​ ​​
​​​ ​This game is making me feel guilty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! You came, ta!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Amane Kanata from hololive's 4th Gen,​ ​​
​​ ​also known as Kanatan.​ ​​
​​​ ​And with me is...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi! Lamyoohoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Yukihana Lamy from hololive's 5th Gen,​ ​​
​​ ​and my face is a liver!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're saying that yourself now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Then I'll do it too.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a grip strength of 55kg!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway.​ ​​
​​​ ​The show we prepared​ ​​
​​ ​for you today is called...​ ​​
​​​ ​One, two.​ ​​
​​​ ​Result Manipulation:​ ​​
​​ ​Quiz Control!​ ​​
​​​ ​Lamy and I will be co-hosting it.​ ​​
​​​ ​We already have two contestants​ ​​
​​ ​waiting in another room.​ ​​
​​​ ​However, they won't just be​ ​​
​​ ​getting a fixed set of questions.​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't that right, Kanatan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a bit more complicated than that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every round, we'll receive an instruction like​ ​​
​​​ ​"Get a correct answer from both,"​ ​​
​​​ ​"Get a correct answer from only one of them,"​ ​​
​​ ​and so on,​ ​​
​​​ ​and then we have to choose one of 50 questions​ ​​
​​​ ​How about this one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't that too hard?​ ​​
​​​ ​to try and get that result.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then how about this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Right.​ ​​
​​​ ​So we'll be pulling the strings.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll be the women behind the curtain.​ ​​
​​​ ​We might have to adapt​ ​​
​​ ​to our contestants, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right, choose different questions​ ​​
​​ ​depending on who we get.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, yeah!​ ​​
​​ ​Right, choose different questions​ ​​
​​ ​depending on who we get.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's find out who they are, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's important to know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Very important. Who do we have?​ ​​
​​ ​That's important to know.​ ​​
​​​ ​1st Gen​ ​​
​​ ​Yozora Mel​ ​​
​​​ ​EN Myth​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​So... What do you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​You sounded pretty confident earlier on.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well...​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara might just...​ ​​
​​​ ​be predictable enough​ ​​
​​ ​to get the answers we want,​ ​​
​​​ ​but Mel-senpai is a total mystery.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's the worst we could get!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right, she's the most unpredictable​ ​​
​​​ ​of all of hololive​ ​​
​​ ​when it comes to quiz shows.​ ​​
​​​ ​She really is.​ ​​
​​​ ​She takes you by surprise every time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Apparently we can talk with them for a bit,​ ​​
​​​ ​so let's open the intercom.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-senpai! Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​I hear you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kikkeriki!​ ​​
​​​ ​As you know, we called you here​ ​​
​​ ​to take a quiz today,​ ​​
​​​ ​but before we start, please say a few words.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Um...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not sure what​ ​​
​​ ​this is all about, but anyway.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Mel, a genius vampire​ ​​
​​ ​from the Underworld,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'm ready to impress!​ ​​
​​​ ​Such confidence...​ ​​
​​​ ​She's confident, all right.​ ​​
​​​ ​So confident...​ ​​
​​​ ​What about you, Kiara-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm pretty nervous,​ ​​
​​​ ​but since you invited me here,​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess you think I'm smart?​ ​​
​​​ ​We do.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, we do!​ ​​
​​​ ​We all think you're brilliant!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, I hear the quiz will be starting soon,​ ​​
​​​ ​so please be on standby.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​So... Now what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​ ​So... Now what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-senpai and Kiara-chan...​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no idea how they'll answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​You just don't know, yeah.​ ​​
​​ ​I have no idea how they'll answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​But either way...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's try our best to​ ​​
​​ ​control their answers, Kanatan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Quiz Control​ ​​
​​​ ​The first result we're going for is...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Get correct answers from both!​ ​​
​​​ ​A correct answer from both.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​That should be simple, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​We just need to find​ ​​
​​ ​an easy question, don't we?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see...​ ​​
​​​ ​How about #21?​ ​​
​​​ ​Q21: How many days are in a year?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, days in a year? That's perfect!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's perfect.​ ​​
​​​ ​This one's perfect.​ ​​
​​​ ​"How many days are in a year?"​ ​​
​​​ ​They have to know that.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no way they'll get it wrong.​ ​​
​​​ ​By the way, you know the answer, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course. It's 365.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a relief.​ ​​
​​​ ​* The question sheet does not include the answers​ ​​
​​​ ​Whew, I got it right.​ ​​
​​ ​You'd lose your juniors' respect​ ​​
​​ ​if you failed that.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was a close one.​ ​​
​​​ ​I felt a bit of cold sweat there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's roll with this one, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​This should work.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, let's go with #21.​ ​​
​​​ ​"How many days are in a year?"​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​ ​"How many days are in a year?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​We can!​ ​​
​​ ​You're finally back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is your first question!​ ​​
​​​ ​How many days are in a year?​ ​​
​​​ ​Please write down your answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Shouldn't you give us some time to think?​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't that something everyone knows?​ ​​
​​​ ​They must think we're stupid or something!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, did you manage to​ ​​
​​ ​come up with an answer?​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course I did.​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then let's look at what you wrote!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​There we have it.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you both answered 365.​ ​​
​​​ ​The correct answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​What could it be?​ ​​
​​​ ​three hundred and sixty-... five days!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct answer: 365 days​ ​​
​​​ ​You both got it right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Leap years have 366, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see we have an expert.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm impressed!​ ​​
​​​ ​So both of you answered correctly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Amazing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Before we move on to the next question,​ ​​
​​​ ​please give us a moment to prepare.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just a moment.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're making us wait again?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get correct answers from both​ ​​
​​ ​Manipulation successful!​ ​​
​​​ ​That went just as planned, didn't it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm glad it did.​ ​​
​​ ​That went just as planned, didn't it?​ ​​
​​​ ​They're easier to manipulate than I thought.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's working, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​It is, it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​So now that we've gotten the hang of it...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's move on to the next question, shall we?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, let's do it.​ ​​
​​ ​Let's move on to the next question, shall we?​ ​​
​​​ ​What are we going for this time?​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Get a correct answer from only Kiara."​ ​​
​​​ ​This one should also be easy, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​How about something English-related?​ ​​
​​​ ​Exactly my idea!​ ​​
​​ ​How about something English-related?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like question 8 for example.​ ​​
​​​ ​Q8: Write vanpaia (vampire) in English​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, that should be hard for Mel-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, but wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​Recently there was this popular game​ ​​
​​ ​with "vampire" in the name.​ ​​
​​​ ​She might just know it from that.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you're saying there's a chance.​ ​​
​​​ ​She might be a lucky devil, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's a vampire,​ ​​
​​ ​but she might just be a lucky devil.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's pick a different one, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about #15,​ ​​
​​ ​"Write Kiara's last name using kanji"?​ ​​
​​​ ​Q15: Write "Takanashi" using kanji​ ​​
​​​ ​Can Kiara do that, though?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, I guess she can...​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean?​ ​​
​​ ​Of course she—​ ​​
​​​ ​Surely she can, right?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Write her own name.​ ​​
​​​ ​It'd be super awkward for her​ ​​
​​ ​if she couldn't, so let's not.​ ​​
​​​ ​What about question 6, then?​ ​​
​​​ ​Q6: Write niwatori (chicken) in English.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a good one.​ ​​
​​ ​"Write niwatori (chicken) in English."​ ​​
​​​ ​That should do the trick, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​Couldn't Mel-senpai do that too, though?​ ​​
​​​ ​Could she?​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Mel-senpai we're talking about.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! That's not very nice, is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go with #6 then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry to keep you waiting!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're back!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry about the wait!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then, here is the next question!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Write niwatori in English."​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​ ​"Write niwatori in English."​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think of this one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait a second.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-chan is at an advantage here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Piece of cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​What...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, wait, wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​Niwatori in English...?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't wait to see Mel-senpai's answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no way she knows it.​ ​​
​​​ ​No way in hell!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, maybe that's a bit much.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think she knows.​ ​​
​​​ ​What about you, Kanatan?​ ​​
​​ ​Do you know it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cock-a-doodle-doo.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​ ​Cock-a-doodle-doo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cock-a-doodle-doo.​ ​​
​​​ ​No way it's that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, it's not?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm done!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wrote my answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're done?​ ​​
​​​ ​Then let's take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look!​ ​​
​​ ​Then let's take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right.​ ​​
​​​ ​How confident are you feeling?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm confident about my English skills, all right.​ ​​
​​​ ​This isn't fair!​ ​​
​​​ ​If anything, it'd be worrying​ ​​
​​ ​if Kiara got this wrong.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at their answers, shall we?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look.​ ​​
​​ ​Let's look at their answers, shall we?​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal the answers!​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-senpai!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's writing is so small​ ​​
​​ ​I can barely read it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's one is tiny!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's so small.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meanwhile, Mel-Mel's answer is...​ ​​
​​​ ​"Garden Bird."​ ​​
​​​ ​"Cluck."​ ​​
​​ ​"Cluck."​ ​​
​​​ ​Niwa​ ​​
​​ ​(Garden)​ ​​
​​​ ​You split it into niwa-tori (garden-bird), didn't you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori​ ​​
​​ ​(Bird)​ ​​
​​​ ​Genius​ ​​
​​​ ​That's brilliant.​ ​​
​​​ ​It really is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is the correct answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct answer: Chicken​ ​​
​​​ ​"Chicken"!​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course it's that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Kiara​ ​​
​​ ​Manipulation successful!​ ​​
​​​ ​So only Kiara got it right.​ ​​
​​​ ​You get a "well done" flower from us.​ ​​
​​​ ​That deserves a flower!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Amazing!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'd like to go prepare the next question,​ ​​
​​​ ​so please give us a moment.​ ​​
​​​ ​So it's "chicken," huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you seriously not know that, Kanatan?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe you belong over there instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, no! No way! How?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see what our next goal is, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Mel!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the hardest one yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't get any harder than this.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do we pick?​ ​​
​​​ ​How about #30?​ ​​
​​​ ​"What does agari refer to in sushi restaurants?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you know, Kanatan?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's tea!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​I think.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it's that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-senpai should know...​ ​​
​​​ ​Would she know this one?​ ​​
​​​ ​She might not.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not sure anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​We need something Japanese.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, something specific to Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about #4: "What ingredient do miso,​ ​​
​​ ​tofu, and soy sauce have in common?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Would you say "soy beans," Mel-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​Soy beans.​ ​​
​​​ ​She just has to know the answer to this.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right. Let's go with question 4:​ ​​
​​​ ​"What ingredient do miso, tofu,​ ​​
​​ ​and soy sauce have in common?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you hear us?​ ​​
​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​We do!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then get ready for the next question!​ ​​
​​​ ​What ingredient do miso, tofu,​ ​​
​​ ​and soy sauce have in common?​ ​​
​​​ ​Take some time to think about it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, is this about a dish​ ​​
​​ ​based on those three?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, it's not that.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the material that they're made from.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't give her hints, Mel-Mel!​ ​​
​​​ ​She'll find the answer if you're not careful.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know...!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no idea...!​ ​​
​​​ ​This game is making me feel guilty!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​Am I having the wrong idea?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-Mel?!​ ​​
​​​ ​What are you guys made of...?​ ​​
​​​ ​She's talking to them.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's asking them!​ ​​
​​​ ​Should we go back to them​ ​​
​​​ ​before she changes her mind?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go back, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go back, let's go back.​ ​​
​​​ ​So... How did it go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you manage to come up with an answer?​ ​​
​​​ ​Kind of...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure...​ ​​
​​​ ​That doesn't sound very convincing, does it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm really not sure about this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at Kiara's answer first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​soy sauce?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute!​ ​​
​​ ​Right, soy sauce!​ ​​
​​​ ​So it's all made of soy sauce.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see, I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're super close, actually.​ ​​
​​​ ​And the drawing is cute.​ ​​
​​​ ​It is.​ ​​
​​ ​And the drawing is cute.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a billion points on top.​ ​​
​​​ ​One billion bonus points.​ ​​
​​​ ​And now for Mel-Mel.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a bit worried.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know the answer, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​This was easy for you, right, Mel-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's basically free points.​ ​​
​​​ ​It sure is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then let's see Mel-Mel's answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​beans​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we accept this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Does this count?​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-Mel, what kind of beans do you mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​Please do elaborate.​ ​​
​​​ ​I only know the edamame kind.​ ​​
​​​ ​You only know edamame?!​ ​​
​​ ​Edamame?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is there even anything else?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did either of them get it right, I wonder?​ ​​
​​​ ​The correct answer is... this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct answer: Soy beans​ ​​
​​​ ​Soy beans!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which means both of you got it wrong, I guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why doesn't mine count? I wrote "beans."​ ​​
​​​ ​You only know about​ ​​
​​ ​edamame though, don't you?​ ​​
​​​ ​No worries.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can make up for it in the next round.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right.​ ​​
​​ ​You can make up for it in the next round.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're going to prepare the next question,​ ​​
​​ ​so please give us another moment!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Mel​ ​​
​​ ​Manipulation failed!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was...​ ​​
​​​ ​Only knows about edamame​ ​​
​​​ ​"She only knows about edamame"?​ ​​
​​ ​I can't explain that away!​ ​​
​​​ ​Trivia​ ​​
​​ ​Edamame are just soy beans harvested at an earlier stage.​ ​​
​​ ​They're from the same plant.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, what?​ ​​
​​​ ​Edamame are soy beans too?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let us see what our next manipulation goal is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Get correct answers from both!​ ​​
​​​ ​So we again need a correct answer​ ​​
​​ ​from both of them.​ ​​
​​​ ​That should be easy, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it's way easier than​ ​​
​​ ​finding something only Mel-Mel knows.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's like you keep taking jabs at her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no! She'll get mad at me...​ ​​
​​​ ​The remaining questions​ ​​
​​ ​are all pretty hard, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about #17: "Which children's story​ ​​
​​ ​features a poisoned apple?"​ ​​
​​​ ​That would of course be...​ ​​
​​​ ​Sssnow White.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, you hesitated there. What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Which one would you pick?​ ​​
​​​ ​#16 for example.​ ​​
​​ ​"The opposite of east," which is west.​ ​​
​​​ ​They'll know this one for sure,​ ​​
​​ ​don't you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder if Mel-Mel does.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's the thing with hololive members.​ ​​
​​​ ​North​ ​​
​​​ ​They only know north.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's steer clear of this one, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​"Which letter comes after N in the alphabet?"​ ​​
​​​ ​They have to know that.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's M!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go with this.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm worried about Mel-Mel, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not sure she'll remember the song.​ ​​
​​​ ​What kind of dunce do you take her for?!​ ​​
​​ ​I'm not sure she'll remember the song.​ ​​
​​​ ​Should really be worrying about themselves​ ​​
​​​ ​It goes, like, N-M-O-P.​ ​​
​​​ ​It goes so fast that​ ​​
​​ ​you're bound to mix something up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Once again, sorry for the wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're back!​ ​​
​​ ​Once again, sorry for the wait.​ ​​
​​​ ​This next question is​ ​​
​​​ ​fairly easy?​ ​​
​​​ ​We think it's easy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it?​ ​​
​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bam!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which letter comes after N in the alphabet?​ ​​
​​​ ​Which is it?​ ​​
​​ ​Which letter comes after N in the alphabet?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're putting Kiara-chan​ ​​
​​ ​at an advantage again.​ ​​
​​​ ​No no no no no.​ ​​
​​ ​We're putting Kiara-chan at an advantage?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you serious?!​ ​​
​​​ ​N​ ​​
​​​ ​n​ ​​
​​​ ​n...​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, she sounds unsure.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's N, M, L, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​N, M, L, O, P...​ ​​
​​​ ​O, P, and then Q, R, S, T, U, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think they wrote down their answers,​ ​​
​​​ ​so let's go take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​How did it go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you find the answer?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​ ​We did!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then let's start off with Kiara-chan's.​ ​​
​​​ ​By all means, go ahead!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it... is!​ ​​
​​​ ​O?!​ ​​
​​ ​That's an... O.​ ​​
​​​ ​What? It's O?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, I'm losing my confidence!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way. Is it O?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's O, it's O.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it really O?​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​ ​Is it really O?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no.​ ​​
​​ ​I'm feeling super unsure right now...​ ​​
​​​ ​Mel-senpai, what's your answer?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's M.​ ​​
​​​ ​She answered M.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, I'm lost!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know what it is anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​So we have an M and an O.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you mean,​ ​​
​​ ​you don't know anymore, Lamy-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah, don't mind that. It's nothing.​ ​​
​​ ​What do you mean,​ ​​
​​ ​you don't know anymore, Lamy-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought it's M.​ ​​
​​​ ​So did I, but I'm not sure anymore...​ ​​
​​​ ​So what's the result?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did someone get it right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct answer: O​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way!​ ​​
​​​ ​How?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That song misled me!​ ​​
​​​ ​What the heck?!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's true!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's L, M, N, O, P.​ ​​
​​​ ​L... M... N...​ ​​
​​​ ​Did we mix up M and N?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's hololive for you​ ​​
​​​ ​This means only Kiara got it right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get correct answers from both​ ​​
​​ ​Manipulation failed!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder if the editors could cut this part.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's ask them to cut it, yeah.​ ​​
​​ ​I wonder if the editors could cut this part.​ ​​
​​​ ​You were joking about Mel-senpai failing​ ​​
​​​ ​but now three of us actually did.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're such an embarrassment!​ ​​
​​​ ​No kidding.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's make the last question​ ​​
​​ ​a good one at least.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's our goal this time?​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Mel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh boy, it's back.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's like the final boss of this game.​ ​​
​​​ ​The thing is,​ ​​
​​​ ​the biggest challenge is that Kiara is smart.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, you're right.​ ​​
​​ ​the biggest challenge is that Kiara is smart.​ ​​
​​​ ​How about being a bit adventurous​ ​​
​​ ​for this last one?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a question with a picture.​ ​​
​​ ​We haven't done that yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Will Mel-Mel manage that, though?​ ​​
​​​ ​Take #13 for example.​ ​​
​​​ ​"What statue is this?"​ ​​
​​​ ​What was...​ ​​
​​​ ​What was it called again?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not a pyramid, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​a sphinx.​ ​​
​​ ​The Sphinx!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the Sphinx!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the Sphinx!​ ​​
​​​ ​But wouldn't Kiara know this one too?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're right, the whole world knows it.​ ​​
​​​ ​In that case...​ ​​
​​​ ​#24 or something.​ ​​
​​ ​How about #24?​ ​​
​​​ ​The one that says "Where is this?"​ ​​
​​​ ​The "Where is this?" one.​ ​​
​​ ​The one that says "Where is this?"​ ​​
​​​ ​Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Where is that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Where is that?​ ​​
​​​ ​(The Japanese historic village of)​ ​​
​​ ​Shirakawa-go?​ ​​
​​​ ​No way it's that!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're probably insulted now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now I want to know​ ​​
​​ ​Mel-senpai's answer for this.​ ​​
​​​ ​We might have to cut it​ ​​
​​ ​depending on what she says.​ ​​
​​​ ​But anyway, we might as well​ ​​
​​ ​give it a try, despite the risk.​ ​​
​​​ ​Despite the risk.​ ​​
​​ ​It's the last one after all.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here we are again!​ ​​
​​ ​We're back!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have come to you with​ ​​
​​​ ​the final boss of quiz questions!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then.​ ​​
​​​ ​We shall now present it to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bam!​ ​​
​​​ ​Where is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Where is this?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Actually,​ ​​
​​​ ​I've seen this before.​ ​​
​​​ ​You have?​ ​​
​​​ ​You have!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's definitely not in Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's surrounded by mountains...​ ​​
​​​ ​And it looks like some kind of ruin, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like a ruin.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, like a World Heritage Site.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a World Heritage Site?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think so.​ ​​
​​​ ​It looks like they're done writing their answers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Have they finished?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go and take a look, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you hear us?​ ​​
​​​ ​How did it go?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you feeling confident?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, you can easily tell it's not in Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​You look so proud saying that.​ ​​
​​​ ​That doesn't narrow it down​ ​​
​​ ​very much, does it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start with Mel-senpai this time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's her answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​burial mound​ ​​
​​​ ​"Burial mound"!​ ​​
​​​ ​Burial mound?​ ​​
​​​ ​A straightforward "burial mound."​ ​​
​​​ ​So we have one rather unspecific answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look at Kiara's next.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Machu Picchu in Peru."​ ​​
​​​ ​Peru!​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't it just "Machu Picchu"?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this Machu Picchu?​ ​​
​​​ ​Peru is the country​ ​​
​​ ​and Machu Picchu is the place.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've only ever heard it as "Machu Picchu."​ ​​
​​​ ​Machu Picchu Machu Picchu Machu Picchu.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pretty clear, isn't it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then, did anyone get it right?​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the correct answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct answer: Machu Picchu​ ​​
​​​ ​It's Machu Picchu!​ ​​
​​ ​Wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're out of control, Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice, I got it.​ ​​
​​ ​You're out of control, Kiara!​ ​​
​​​ ​Machu Picchu: Ancient ruin of an Inca citadel.​ ​​
​​ ​Also called the "City in the Clouds." World Heritage Site.​ ​​
​​​ ​It says here that it's a World Heritage Site.​ ​​
​​​ ​And that it's the ruin of a city.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara, I'm impressed!​ ​​
​​​ ​Amazing!​ ​​
​​ ​Kiara, I'm impressed!​ ​​
​​​ ​I should thank you for picking this question.​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanted to make it easy for us, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Get a correct answer from only Mel​ ​​
​​ ​Manipulation failed!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure, we assumed you'd both know this one...​ ​​
​​​ ​But anyway, that was the last question!​ ​​
​​​ ​End of Quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for participating!​ ​​
​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, this whole time I've been​ ​​
​​ ​wondering what this quiz was for.​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess you'd find it a bit suspicious...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let me explain.​ ​​
​​​ ​Revealing the true nature of the quiz​ ​​
​​​ ​Does that mean​ ​​
​​ ​you were playing around with us?​ ​​
​​​ ​I wouldn't quite put it that way...​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel bad now.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd like to be a manipulator next time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seeing things from the other side?​ ​​
​​​ ​It'd be fun to do this again​ ​​
​​ ​with other members, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​If you enjoyed this video,​ ​​
​​​ ​please leave a Like,​ ​​
​​​ ​and subscribe to the official channel​ ​​
​​ ​as well as the channels of everyone here!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please do!​ ​​
​​​ ​And now we say...​ ​​
​​​ ​See you next time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye-bye!​ ​​