[Music]
[Applause]
Perfect,
perfect! Hey, Live 3rd generation!
Peko
Luteker
's rabbits Let's
get married to Picole
[Music]
Hololive 3rd generation
Usadate Cola, thank you Almond
Almond
[Applause]
[Music]
Say goodbye  is perfect
Peco Rapiko Nagata from Full Live 3rd generation Hello, my
stomach hurts
[Music]
Poop
[Laughter] Is eggplant better
than carrots?
[Music]
[Laughter] Do you
like bigger boobs?
[Applause]
[Music]
Perfect
This live is a lie from the 3rd generation.
How, how, how much?
[Music]
Hand coke and competitive white cat
worry, let's
settle it there
Worry, rather Robe
[Applause]
[Music] Is it
perfect?
Take a bath and pay for it
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah,
Pikar, that
's a lie.
Pico the Decor
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] It
's a kitten, it's like this
Peko Peko Peko Peko Peko Peko Peko [
Music] It's so
cool.  Live 3rd
generation
Nagata
Decore Pecord-chan Pico is
free tonight Peko is staying overnight
[Applause]
[Music]
Right
Except for the freshly baked popcorn
[Applause]
[Music] -
Yes, I
agree,
it's a lie -
Rabicon Almond
Armor Ah
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa watching
[laughing]
[music] My
throat is dry from Pecola's laughter so I'm
going to say hello The
peeping version is
perfect
Live 3rd generation's plate pecorapeko
Door  Mode Arm
[Applause]
[Music] I'm going to
take the cash register here, which is kind.
Give me the number 27, please.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
nervous.
Let's start
this live. 3rd
generation members,
Usada,
Pikola and Mouse Pika.
[Music]
Starting today, the Kids Channel will be open.
Peko, quit and become an adult kids channel. How can you
guys like this kind of stuff?
[Music]
Peko-chan, I love you more
than anything
in the world. Your
voice is
stupid.
[Applause] [
Music] Ah,
let's talk a little bit about Peko.  Are you
Peko, who isn't interested in water servers?
Where do you get the water that's so delicious?
Nozaki and his friends bring fresh water to you every day,
so that's a trade secret. Huh?
Peko, who's willing to sign a contract with you.
Bond
[Music]
Dear Mr.  Go home,
Peko.
Now, let me show you the eyeballs. Magical Peko Peko Peko Peko. Enjoy your meal. [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause] Actually, this is just a story. The rabbit pillow that Cora wears around her neck came on stream the other day.  It
was Usagi-san who gave it to me, and I
picked it up from my ears as well.