[Music]
man I
yeah uh uhh
uhhuh you're now listen listening to FAA
FM this ain't your granny's radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to jam out let's go
[Music]
K I forgot to open my go
again hello welcome to day six are we
already on day six of Ian
Reco wow wow wow
wow welcome I'm very tired I didn't
sleep for well last night but we're here
nevertheless it's time to build the
library
and I seems like like like narissa
patched things up with Moko so funart is
completely absolved of any legal
issues change the jackpot sign well look
we're fine because we have an asterisk
here which obviously
means no number may be
misrepresented number is not guaranteed
to be in any kind of currency that
you're familiar
with but what is it it's only
coins yeah with an asterisk you can
never get into any legal trouble ever
right also I think I want to move the
library I know I did this but now I'm
like what if we put it here like right
take up all the remaining space right
here and then we can make it more
Grand that's what I'm thinking also
we've got some new stuff we've got
statue of the the absentee
Queen yeah I also think it's a
bit cramped
here and we can we can break it like liy
split with our licky split with our
pickaxe
ah no
problem our our lucky Enchanted
pickaxes yes so the plan
today uh make sure that FAA Mart is
sitting pretty in terms of any legal
issues that might come up that's
certainly the plan I want to do the
dungeon from yesterday and then there's
no new dungeon today
ah
but I don't so I don't know what's going
on like the next couple days there's
going to be a a big finale at some point
I think
in I think it's in two
days oh narissa is here you paid off
Moko so there are no more legal issues
that's what I like to here nothing that
money can't fix
right all thanks to the potato
salad yeah finale for chapter one I
think
settlement we just got to make
sure that you know moco's lawyer gets
paid her Fair her Fair
dues I would say you know lawyer work
hard they deserve a big paycheck I
think to the tune of of maybe 9,000
coins is fair she got paid 100
coins well we'll see also I've heard
some
slander I'm I'm I'm bold enough to call
it slander against fellow small BS
business death do us part Diner I've
heard that people have been lodging all
sorts of complaints about the food
safety of this establishment and what I
have to say about that is that we small
businesses need to stick together and we
need not be bullied by
regulations and and food
safety we not be bound by
that so you know that I've got I've got
death to part uh in my in my
heart and yes I'm going to build a giant
Library they completely blocks the rest
of their
view FDA got nothing on fall
apart it was was 12 wide
before I don't have
enough stone
bricks
um I also want to make it even so I can
have double
doors okay well
that'll that'll
help but I don't know if I should make
all of it into stone bricks cuz it's
nice to have some texture well we can
worry about that
later also I think I have a bunch of
money that I can use for the
construction packs cuz only 3,000 of
this belongs to the
lottery yes some moss
stone
gosh what are we thinking
so wouldn't it be cool to put it on a
diagonal I'm so tempted to put it on a
diagonal but that's probably a bad
idea cuz we want like a cool pathway you
know leading up to
it that would be hard but diagonal
builds are like a cheat code in
Minecraft wait my pickax is already
dying
diagonal builds are like a cheat code in
Minecraft like everybody wants to build
it on the grid so if you put it
diagonally it looks really
cool I'm up for it I should give it a
go I mean what's the worst that could
happen I guess it's like how do you do
the doors
it's the world tree on a diagonal the
world tree is an organic shape that does
not confine itself to the laws of
XYZ elit but it's going to be a
hat how far can
[Music]
you I died I died
I I flew too close to the Sun
ouch oh dear okay I've learned my lesson
don't try to see what lurks beyond the
walls your mortal mind was not
made to
see how
symbolic see I feel like a diagonal
would be really cool
but how do we make see wouldn't it it
would make so much sense like
this how do we do the the entrance
then it just leads your eye nicely
doesn't
it think about the
bookshelves I'm thinking
double doors with one pressure plate
would that look cool or would that look
weird you know what let's just go for it
1 2 3 4 five 6 7 8 9 10 but remember
diagonals are bigger than than
straight uh one let's just see two three
four five 6 7 8 9 10 because of
Pythagoras diagonals
are are
bigger so don't let it fool
you we making a
Rus well geometry
is is
another important aspect of
Education so I feel like doesn't this
fill the space so nicely actually I
think it could be a little
bigger
maybe what if it was too
bigger am I infringing on the The
Gallows
space wait this is way too big isn't
it am I going to have enough am I going
to have enough resources to build
this that's
good am I blocking the view of The
Gallows it's
perfect should it what if it's one
bigger
instead the library is worth it I do
think it was wait this one is my fortune
3 I really shouldn't use
that for or
for anything but ores
rather okay well this is like the
foundation and then we want to go like
one
in or two
in oh I'm going to waste a lot of Bricks
Like This
do I have any cheaper cheaper
materials I think that'll be okay your
brain hurts already well don't worry cuz
I shall do the thinking for you here at
Scarlet wand with
my my big
head
um maybe just Oak wait not Oak
probably maybe just
Spruce Spruce it up a little
bit oh B you're so
funny and
witty I sure do want to buy some lottery
tickets okay put that
back oh yeah narissa sold
hat I feel so silly
for being like you can keep 50%
commission to narissa who has like all
the money in the whole
server I don't think she needs the 50%
commission but she's so dedicated all
the same it's like give me tips of
billionaire I am I'm like I'm like
sliding her a $20 bill and I'm like keep
the
change how is the fart CEO so
comparatively
broke it's
fine hello narissa
it's the potato salad
life I see the
vision
hello I accept
thank you thank
you my my pleasure my pleasure please
enjoy I will look forward to the
completion of the library thank you I
will use this for the library thank you
anything for the library of scarlet wand
thank you thank
you good luck thank you
The Witches here Scarlet wand is full of
witches and
capitalism all manner of Witchcraft
here this will help I need to buy a lot
of construction boxes I think the
diagonal is
good Scarlet witches it has a nice ring
to it
am is it going to look Stumpy though
because of the the build height
limit just got to get the outline and
then I can add add details I was
thinking I could use
terracotta for
texturing so that it's not just bricks I
think like orange or red or
something terracotta will
look nice
but I also might do like marble columns
too to give it that
library
look oh what's see it at the build
height I'm getting scared that we're
reaching
it
35 so each wait that's fine isn't it get
the Tam statue
so it's higher than
this okay well they've got like three
levels over
there okay okay I choose not to worry
about
it I will continue to expand the
library wait actually you're right maybe
someone said do we even need doors
earlier and I thought they were just
trolling
but maybe we don't even need doors we
just need like an entry Archway because
otherwise nons Scarlet wand members
won't be I'm totally blocking this view
too I'm sorry but it is the
library we want people to be able to
enter you know
oops it's nice having this feather to
fly
is that good or should I go one
more for the first how tall is it 1 2 3
4 5
6 seven one
more okay and we're already almost out
of bricks
Good Start good
start this is just like the sketch
though you
know you have a brutalist
architecture no no it's not it's not a
brutalist or at least it won't be when
it's
done it's going to be very beautiful
oh gosh what am I
doing I'm building a
floor I'm already
out okay then we go in
like
this yes that will look really really
good oh it takes too
long in
further should it be in further it's
like a cake
why is Diamond so slow it's because I'm
flying so you get like the same speed as
if you're like
[Music]
underwater but I can take
these no cuz in floor three will be too
small yeah this way it'll be it'll be
nice and spacious
so you can do your
studying am I doing the
corner just like
that so you can have plenty of room to
do your
[Music]
studying it does look like a cake I
can't help but think about
cake I wish I could get like a statue
but like a small
one in the front you
know like statues wearing the Scarlet
wand hat like marble
statues that would really fit the
academic
feel I
think need more
wood I know I wish wish you could put
the hats on the stands and I would do
that for
sure in
[Music]
here very
good armor Sands do not work
unfortunately I don't know if you can
even get armor in this in this
world I'm not calling it a game in this
world
I've seen it on the armor stands in the
in the
blacksmith okay I need
more
construction ouch
packs in this fantasy world realm of no
armor I mean I respect it because that
makes me think that it's a realm of
fashion instead of armor like we put all
these resources into getting these hats
who
needs who
needs armor when you look
good okay just don't buy too many I mean
actually I could buy a
lot and if I get a hat that
means we can sell the hat
and if I get Construction Supplies even
[Music]
better okay
10 that's pretty good to start
with gambling
wo there are so many different ways to
gamble in this
world they had to have been thinking
about that when they when they called us
in
right bricks please let's just start
with
one Mar is one of
them the only one I might add where you
can win so much
money asterisk
like sure you could get a 10x payout at
the at the pit
[Music]
allegedly but your chances are so
low and fmart is so cheap to
enter that was a
fast
stack of bricks
max payout is 5,000 is it actually in
the in the
pit see fart you can win so much
more looks like a nice
prison I'm scared of reaching the build
height one two three 4 5 6 7 1 2 3 4
should we make the next layer only
six is it okay if they
get oh smaller as should go
up the the Disney
[Music]
trick 7 * 3 is 21 well we really not
reach the build height but I feel like
it's I feel like we're going there
though I feel like we're breing
it oops oh
I'm so
messy I could make a pillar in the
middle for
reference five six 7 8 N 9 10 11 12 13
it's not the middle 14 14 15 16 17 18 19
20 21 22 23 oh it's pretty tall
actually
uh-oh okay we reached the the height
limit now don't
die okay that's pretty tall actually
I can probably
make I could make it taller but then
it's going to it's going to use more
resources do we have
enough I might have to start making some
potato salads myself
be so many
blocks let's just see oh I think it
should be
more 1 2 3 4 five
6 well the top layer will be small so it
will not take too many blocks
right I could even have it Go in further
but let's see
how how this
feels I mean at this size you might even
still be able to use it for
something does it look like a library
looks like a place I want to
study oh I love I love placing
blocks
so
satisfying no window Library we haven't
gotten there
yet there will be
windows it's called a sketch
sweetie look it
up it's called
architecture
um and this is all thanks to
fart that we are building this Library
it's called a
vision I why do I feel like it should be
taller on the top one two three four
five six well cuz it should
be one more at least
I feel like it's too
short am I
crazy it's a birthday cake it
is build the top layer should we have
one more layer is that
cheating It's a Good
Hat pen each Flor but then I have to
reconstruct the whole
thing and I don't I don't know if fom
are we might need to hold more lotteries
if I'm going to be doing that
much 10 10 10 is not a bad idea
oops it doesn't do look that imposing
you
know I have to go to an idle meeting I
know it's only been like a 1 minute
since I started the stream I have to go
I'll be right back sip sip sip I'll be
right
back VA FM this ain't your granny's
radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to jam now let's
[Music]
go 1 2 3 go there is spot with a flow we
Holo promise I'm famous heyo I am a big
shot look M on TV gaming Idol here in
as me bucket we ball never punish never
greedy no i' win
Unstoppable dance back it up
let that's what
[Music]
I rain
H promise ladies a m you're so cute
thank you
s i
get thank you so much get your head out
of the gutter man oh be it's not a face
God f is
real what we're known for big deal man I
love Pa don't you it is on PA over it's
you
[Music]
wow a dramatic entrance just for
me okay I'm back
now I have fresh eyes to look at this
thing I don't want to redo it
though I'm lazy consider that I'm
lazy and we could oh does it look Grand
enough
though make it 10 14
20 top layer bigger only
let's see if it looks unbalanced that
way will anyone notice that just the top
is is taller
out it's a lot of
blocks who's going to count I don't know
that princess has been
sticking her nose in everybody's
business asking for
executions asking for Juke
boxes sticking out her
nose I feel like this layer should also
be taller though
looks good
[Music]
noticeable it's not bad
noticeable maybe it's fine I have a maal
latte today and ice
water I get two
drinks I saw a
Tik Tok it was
like women coming into work and Men
coming into work and the men bring like
nothing with them they have like like
they're not carrying anything and then
the women have like a whole bag and they
have like two drinks maybe even three
drinks and
snacks and that's definitely
me I'm I don't understand understand how
you can just bring your body and nothing
else sometimes I have like one backpack
and my purse
and I mean I could see the case for
three
drinks in fact I had three drinks
earlier because I was also drinking hot
tea so I had hot tea iced Machel latte
and
water sometimes you need three drinks
so yeah that's that's definitely me
going into
work get some help why why if it makes
life better why shouldn't I why
shouldn't I have three
drinks sip sip
sip I'm not
alone I don't know when I worked like a
I mean I don't have any memories but if
I had memories and IID remembered
working a regular job I was definitely
bringing lots of stuff to
work it makes it easier to get through
the day especially if you've got like
your thermos full of hot tea and you can
you know you can count on that when the
afternoon sleepy hit you know you can
bust that out get you through the rest
of your
shift is that even
bring your whole fridge I mean don't you
want your whole fridge at
work I
do it's what the 300 p.m. coffee break
is for
ah but I don't drink
coffee that's that's the
problem okay I thought we could use
these Mangrove logs
inside
oops oh wait but do I want like
a would a different kind of floor be
better like not
wood use logs and strip it wait that
could look good but that's expensive and
I just I just made a lot of the L
dogs Marble Marble is so bright though
don't we want it to be kind of cozy and
dark in
here is this like
triopia this might be a trophobia
situation
is it
yes
sideways let's see it looks nice though
it kind of is
giving like medical exam like you're
going to the dermatologist because
something that looks like disappeared on
your skin
I don't think I like it
sideways alternate
sideways
maybe looks like
sausage like this hey it does look like
meat
floor Library no Uta no no no no no no
no no no no no no
no not not my
[Music]
library checker
board checker board could be
cool gosh oh a big staircase up the
middle would be
cool do we want a quartz
floor why is everything so hard to
decide no space what do you mean there's
plenty of space we've got three
levels we've got
bace for a grand
staircase but what's the other
one a little bit of
meat meat
floors
maybe Sal me
what about red
terracotta cuz I do I do want it to be
red because we are the Scarlet wands you
know this is our library so I think red
would look
nice for
our our
color redstone blocks I don't know if
we're that
fancy we don't have that much
funding at the
library maybe we do
though red glass that would be cool I'm
thinking red terracotta I don't know if
we can get dyed concrete is the
thing we're going to have to dye
the the Terra Cotta
I'm going to buy the dye
too cuz I'm I'm fancy like
that oh
gosh my inventory is very
full okay let's look at let's check this
out Demir I don't get the demure meme
well I kind of get
it I don't know if there's anything to
get it's just like things that are not
demure but you say it is cuz that makes
it that makes it
funny maybe I get
it wait no it looks like a kitchen
now it looks like a
diner it was supposed to be fancy oh no
this is not the
vibe how do we make it not look like a
diner oh no no no no no
no make it
FAS oh make
FAS out of f f e e
o a pattern instead of just Checker what
is a
pattern okay what about what about
Redstone would that also look like a
diner or would it not
because I mean this is so expensive
ensive
zigzag I don't
know I'm not
sure two
R I think it's better than the
Terracotta but it might that might not
be it
zigzag could work how do you do a
zigzag oh who knew making a library
would be so difficult I don't know why
I'm starting on the inside by the way I
mean I guess it's just the
floor it's cuz I don't know how to fix
the outside
so just work on the inside instead
isn't this just going to be like
Stripes I don't know how fancy this is
going to
be we really want to stay away from the
McDonald's play place
looks like a mouth it looks like a mouth
like a monster's mouth with sharp
teeth
waro
mouth it
does SP
spirals I don't even know how to do
spiral a Scarlet wad symbol wait that
would be cool wait can I do that hold
on I have the reference in the
corner now I'm regretting doing it on a
diagonal we don't babbe diagonal is good
actually wait is it
good hold on where's the
middle is this the
middle I think
so no oh one 2 3
4 one oh you're right it's definitely
not the
middle is there just
one one two 3 4 One Two 3 4 One Two
Three 4 now it's the
middle compare corners
at the corners one 2 3 4 5 6 7
8 1 2 3 4 five 6
78 1 2 3 4 five 6
78 one 2 3 4 5 6 7 it's the middle don't
be fulled just cuz this is here
here
okay make the Scarlet wand
logo but it's okay to simplify
it in fact I probably have to simplify
it
and then
like sort
of fish that's not right what do you
mean it's exactly
right looking like a club well that's
what it's supposed suppos to look like
right they're
all suits which should have clued
everyone in into the the potential
gambling that they would run
into oh wait you're right there's only
three
diamonds so we could or three yeah only
three diamonds
[Music]
um
better no what is that it's it's a l
go it's the
logo no V on the
bottom it looks like an angry
face yeah like a threee
monster I mean what if it was like this
cuz it has that
detail but I feel like now it looks
like like
nothing that's cool you see it I mean it
doesn't it can just be an abstract floor
pattern
Right add the quartz
okay let's let's
see how we feel I mean we want it to be
very fancy and very Scarlet
wand so that people can feel actually we
don't want it to be too fancy though
because then maybe nobody's going to
want to buy lottery tickets to support
the
library like it has to be fancy enough
so that they know that their money is
going to a good cause but also not too
fancy where they feel like they don't
need to donate you
know like we definitely still need your
money to make the
library P
please get it
twisted we need money
it's kind of
okay the outside could also
be
red I mean it's like kind of subtle
right fix the bottom what about the
bottom a full triangle
like
this should I get rid of
these sad clown now well I like sad
clowns
so so that's fine
okay that's
great now for the
staircases should the staircases be wood
or or uh quartz
what if you want people to think you're
poor little do they know that everything
costs the
same in the construction box should it
be this wood
though wait I don't even know if I want
stairs this might have been a
mistake I might wanted
[Music]
slabs but what if it's like this you
know I'll fix it later but just for
now just
imagine yeah stairs on both sides is
what I'm thinking like
this and like
this leads you up to the next level
they're kind of shiny these
stairs these should be wood for sure but
that's
fine we can fix
it and then like it
turns ow
oops like
this to continue
up do you see the
[Music]
vision it's kind of a grand Library
liary we just have to make you
look
better
oops all it needs is
books that's what the lottery tickets
are
for our library is desperately
in need of
books is that the
same you kind of hid your head on the
floor well we'll we'll figure it
out and then you have the Second
Story why guess we don't even need a
floor here just let the light
in it's pretty dark in here anyway how
are you supposed to
read
yes we kind of need railings
though rain fill Library
oh reverse trap doors to make rails what
is the mangrove trapo look
[Music]
like let's see
that might look
cool I'll just make a bunch I'll just
use all of the wood that I
have oh no
it's getting dark I should put some
lanterns up that's not that's not what I
want do I need to place
blocks if I delete this will it oh it
does stay
okay that's kind of
cool
maybe we have magic we don't need
handrails but the guests might need
handrails
Scarlet wand Public Library
is free for
all red stone lamps can you make a what
is the red stone lamp there's a redstone
Lantern you can't make one of those that
looks like a like Redstone right that
might look too evil though
oh yeah glow stone and Redstone we could
make a cool
chandelier just just put some lights in
for
now oh
can't put one there cuz
it overlaps
wait wait can you put one here though
yes safety
hazard
um
it's it's safe enough just don't
fall right
here is this another lawsuit in the
making it might
be faart is never
free princess will fall
100% well she's not going to fall very
far
I don't think you can even get hurt
falling from this height so we're
good she's
shorter yeah so like ants you
know ants can fall from any height and
they're really
short basically
look we have
books the first of our
books look at
that not a scam wait I should put the
windows
in probably it looks kind of evil with
all the red is red the color of evil
[Music]
so I think we need like whole glass
blocks so I'm going to I'm going to get
some should I dye them red that's the
question
or what about a different color what
about like yeah like
gold yellow
maybe
black
pink those black look cool black glass
something that
[Music]
contrasts
blue not black try various colors but
can you dye it back once you've dyed it
one
[Music]
color actually the white glass looks
pretty good instead of
clear no
I'm too scared to die it cuz it's
expensive we don't have that kind of
money
[Music]
here what if we had like a big window in
the
back I want a big window or just small
windows at least I have silk touch
now I think it would look good if it was
[Music]
dyed windows with
bars what kind of
bars
fence I was going to do
[Music]
um more of
these I guess I could use I don't have
to just use the red
ones actually what did the nether one
can you make trap doors out of the
nether
logs oh it does look kind of cool
I feel
like off
center oh it is off
center but is it it's not really
possible for it to be
centered hold
on we could have it next to each
other you just have to make
two two wide
like
this
nope not like
that
this it's coming together I don't think
it was a bad idea to do a diagonal
okay one taller yeah maybe one
Higher I might try
red with just a little
bit of the glass to see what red would
look
like I is looking good so far thank
[Music]
you thank
you yeah have a table there that's what
I'm thinking
too I think I
need
[Music]
some
Mangrove fences
[Music]
um very
good
[Music]
and oh is slab a slab better though
maybe actually we'll have use of these
what was I going to do I was going to
dye this
just a little though
uhoh got no
room sorry
sticks are they gone
forever well that's okay we
will we will
live without them
I keep being afraid that I'm not using
my thr pickaxe I'm just going to be like
L destroying my
library red kind of It kind of Blends in
it looks
invisible but it's not that bad
that looks kind of
cool hold on this
one oh I see it's kind
of it's kind of not going to combine
nicely so
[Music]
slabs maybe slabs and some plants we
need some green in
here definitely need some
green stealing my own
stock we've got we've got plenty of
books right here look
all the books you could you could ever
want I don't know if I wanted to come
out that
far I want a really
green
plant for
contrast uh
oh maybe this
one I know it's not that green
but it has
green can this one go in the in the
pot yes I think that looks pretty
good a sapling we'll get some saplings
in here too don't
worry the library is coming
along
wah let's fix the
stairs we can
do upside
down stairs to make it
look nice
oh I don't not like that let's just do a
whole
block and a
stair I should get a crafting table in
here
slab I have feather I do have the
feather it's right right it's right here
in my
[Music]
inventory if I'm not using it it's cuz
I'm afraid of
heights what was I cooking I was going
to do like a you know where it combines
and it looks really good it was going to
look really good you just have to trust
me on
that we're going to need way more also
the outside looks bad
I think I'm better at doing Interiors
the
exteriors
possibly okay oh paintings that's
true do paintings use
wool I should get shears I think I have
iron
now some chains a
big chandelier would be
good listen
fauna CEO of
faart has not been getting much sleep
lately and is very sleepy as a result
yeah vines on the outside I'll try to do
that make it all cool and
wizardy the inside is looking pretty
good
though I think I might just have it like
open you know on the second
floor like you can walk
around I don't know can you even make it
to this side I'm not sure
then just have more
books in the third third
row is yeah big chandelier oh hello
hello hello greetings to you fair lady
greetings um I I I don't want to
pressure you uh what you're building is
beautiful I just wanted to ask if you
want to take a break and do uh the Ena
dungeon one more time with me n but you
don't have to I I just want to like lay
out the offer um I think I'll pass if
that's okay it's just it's just puzzles
anyway so if I come along I'll just be
spoiling it I'll carry you anyway on
accident no no no no don't tell me
anything okay okay then have fun
building Library thank you good luck
good I can't wait to see it later what
books do you have we've got at least
four books St yeah what actual books um
no we've got yahi we've got Yuri we oh
hey hello those books didn't exist in
the medieval fantasy Ro time sure they
did did but they were forbidden they
were
forbidden forbidden scriptures no band
books in thear liary yeah
exactly forbidden scriptures they must
be burnt yeah must burn this
Library you can't burn down the library
of scarlet
wand well it's not even finished yet so
maybe after it's finished just kidding
good luck good luck thank you good luck
to you
[Music]
too okay wait my
quest I'm grateful they invited me but
as you will recall
the the ENA dungeon is only puzzles and
mazes so I don't think they
would benefit from my
healing put the
heels the library isn't going to build
itself oh gosh what was I
doing the sanity
heel oh the second floor can be full of
Le
turns that's a good
idea I don't know what the I don't think
I want it to be
glass but I don't know if this part I
might just make this part the
same wood which I have now run out
of so you could go up there and then
have a big chandelier
carpet oh carpet would be
cool you can make empty wait oh yeah
didn't they add that wait how do you
make can you make an empty bookshelf did
they add that cuz you can fill it with
books that you wrote yourself
right how do you make an empty
bookshelf uh
if I were an empty
bookshelf planks and
[Music]
slabs if I were an empty bookshelf I
would look
like this oh my gosh I'm the best
Minecrafter to ever do
it I'm so good at
Minecraft my Minecraft intuition
bo bo bo bo
bo Minecraft natural put me in the
Minecraft
movie or you're a
coward I mean if we fill it with empty
bookshelves then people will definitely
want to donate
right are you sure you want that I was
dying a little bit when Jack Black came
out
like my name is
[Music]
Steve what are you
doing what are you doing Jack
Black you are so good as
Bowser but I don't know
about about
[Music]
Steve you blame the director I'm
sure well who knows maybe the trailer is
just bad and it'll be it'll be
good maybe it'll be good no need to be
[Music]
Hasty oh look at these sad empty
bookshelves I kind of want this to be a
window
also like back
here excuse me bless
me I think I do like the red Windows not
just because I'm too cheap to buy more
die
also red is good red is Scarlet
wand
okay on the diagonal that's the wrong
tool 1 2 3
4 than that's pretty
cool three
four benefits of diagonal
building and we going have
[Music]
bookshelves going
up put that there
I don't know if it should
be symmetrical I kind of like asymmetry
but I know it's not everybody's cup of
[Music]
tea
yes something like
this we could also o we could hang it
with chain like ooh that would be cool
let's do
that but I don't have I think I'm out of
chains I think I have one chain
left but we know where to get
more yeah time to steal some
chains yes that looks pretty cool
cool I
think I could do one here
too it's coming
along I
[Music]
think there's still a lot to do though
especially to the
[Music]
outside which maybe I should work on a
little bit I do want
Vines I mean in my my experience like if
your Minecraft
build looks bad just put a bunch of vs
on it and it will greatly
improve the
Aesthetics
okay also I don't know if it needs
does it need a platform all
around like a
foundation or just in the
front missing
dirt hide it with Hedges ooh that would
look good see I feel like it doesn't
need it on the
sides which maybe is like why did I do
that
then I don't
know but it's it's
fine uh-oh we're
full inventory is very sick hold on yeah
I'll replace the wood with with
[Music]
stone let's just let's try to do the the
front hole I'm just going to delete
everything so I can
add a bit
of a
[Music]
variance to it
that's what we call
texturing here in the
business the business of the
library oh I definitely need
[Music]
slabs can you make these into slabs you
can
oh my inventory is is full
again
okay I'm never going to find that
leather again and that is a valuable
book right
there so I'm thinking
like something like this
and
then yes and then just like build the
pathway
out and then it probably goes like
further but you
know worry about that later
and then I think we need like
Columns of some
sort needs a sign it does need a sign
some gargoyles it does need
gargoyles like statues it
does I need to help my
inventory let's just put everything in
here I'm sure I'll be able to find it
again when I need
it I hope these
walls can join together
they can good
stuff yeah yes it looks like a castle
wait it's not
[Music]
even uh
wait was it even oh
no what am I
doing I can't
tell I think it's even
now but then I want I think like do I
want pillars
I want pillars like that or do I want
like marble
pillars lamp
posts yeah like an I'm yeah I'm thinking
like an
overhang Archway type
deal marble would look
good cuz you can make marble into a
pillar but it would be a full
pillar not
a yeah like
this and then
maybe some of those
does it go right here we do need outdoor
lighting and
then oh maybe I need half
slabs for a cool
overhang uh
here I would like to make the top darker
like the
hat and I think I might do that well I
don't know if it's going to be
darker but I might add visual
interest
using I need more
using the dyed
terracotta I don't know if it's
darker it might be
darker somehow it doesn't look that
dramatic maybe they need to be taller I
mean it's an
[Music]
archway just add
lighting
[Music]
where where do I add the
lining
nope fire good idea let's slide it on
fire wait that's not going to work what
am I
doing I'm too sleep to be operating
this Minecraft world right
now A F
door it looks like an angry old
[Music]
Dragon
eyebrows catfish and old man
it kind of works though now it's got the
Hat the head wearing the Hat it
is I think the pillars need to go all
the way
up but I do want to
have like this overhang
um very good set them into the building
but I feel like it's good to have like
texture or like three
dimensions now it's an
H which says
hello Hospital
I mean I do have healing to
[Music]
offer is it a hospital how do I make it
not look like a
hospital that's not what I
wanted oh I need more I need
more building is
so so difficult I should go back to
just running running scams I mean
running
Fair
lotteries fair and Equitable
lotteries but this is what it's all
about this is what
we this is why we do the things that we
do that looks
[Music]
okay I think I don't know how to make it
this layer
though
II the bat
signal well that's f it does look like
an
H I don't like the h
no
h what if we make it uh a
[Music]
proper
Archway
like this
is that still an
H H but
fancier fancy
H we can live with fancy
H it definitely still looks like an
age oh my inventory is so
full listen it's not my fault this time
though
because I can only have so much free
inventory let's see if we can
add
details I mean how dark is
it it's darker I think it's brighter
so what if we add like the
arrows like
this but it's not it has an even number
so you can't do a single point it has to
be double point
this will
add
dimensionality and
character to the
library or alternatively it will look
bad and we will undo it immediately now
it's an arrow it's like a big Arrow
hospital here hospital
here get your healing right
here looks good well we can do it to
this layer
too
potentially make it pointier I can't
make it pointier
though cuz then it won't be even
Pokemon
Center it's
fine yeah we need more
arrows I think
more
arrows will help
us
ah what am I doing is this an
[Music]
arrow it looks like the Hat more or less
emphasis on the
list this is good enough I call it good
enough we'll fix it by obscuring it with
a bunch of
vines ooh brick stairs maybe would look
good I think I have oh I have a bunch
more bricks
too I they are but I don't even know who
put those there
but everything that belongs to the
Scarlet wand belongs to the
library that's what I was say it looks
like a
hospital maybe we need to change the the
H the inside is looking pretty good
though
trust the
process oh
gosh is that
fine I just feel like it's not it's not
all
even the middle stair just don't look
too hard
is it supposed to alternate I don't
know make it
alternate oh on God you missed the facee
entrance don't worry trust the process
we will get there what's your favorite
sound effect in
Minecraft the brick cutting
one is is kind of
satisfying sip sip sip good answer
walking on honey good
answer
ouch I like the
bees I know they were traumatizing me in
yesterday's dungeon but
but I recall fondly
my my bee
farm it's not even but you know I think
we're fine with
that I don't know should it start like
here instead all the pops of the bees
entering the hive
it's very good I feel like that looks
[Music]
better which means I might have to
change other
layer I think we can join
them too I'm going to need way more
stairs I should just
commit and convert them
all two stairs
Empire State
Building that's not that's not a bad
that's not the worst comparison we've
had
[Music]
certainly this is this is
architecture it could be worse for get
gargoyle how do I make a
gargoyle does the Empire State Building
have
gargoyles I think every building should
gargoyles I don't know why we moved away
from them as a
society oh I think I have to change this
one it should be law it should
be I mean how there we supposed to keep
the like evil spirits
away frolo is going to take over not
Frodo that would be
fine froo not froo
I'm learning how to place
stairs this is better I think can we
join
them wait what what the heck was
that not like that not like that is
there like a limit to the amount that
you can
join oh these don't want to be friends
you know actually this could just be a
regular full block couldn't
it oops just every
[Music]
other I feel like my ankles should have
snapped just
then but they
didn't
okay you have to do it in order order
what do you
mean like the whole
thing is that interesting or is that
weird we could put lamps here
piz slice
roof it's very
zigzaggy the
face don't worry about the
face okay now how the heck did I do this
not like
that wait is
that am I doing
it is that what is this what it's
supposed to be
like wait I'm I missed one what am I
done why is it like this oh my
gosh not like
this zigzags of my
nightmares how do I
know what to
do like this
that's kind of
cool cool
zigzag how do I
remember looks great from above good
thing people
will definitely be viewing it from above
right hold on hold on hold on
I'm
panicking already messed up wait
what
oh how do I know what I'm supposed to do
how did I just build it at
random and then it goes out and then we
go in and then we go out and then we go
in and then we go out then we go in
then we go
out was that
right like crochet you just need a
little
song to help you
remember Finding Nemo Vibes I am
starting to feel like Dory right
now
okay okay we can do this except I'm
about to run out of stairs
first you go
in then you go
out so then you go
out then you go
in then you go
out then you need more brakes then you
need more construction boxes because
you're completely
out and you're spending all of the guild
money but is for a good
cause then you need more
bricks and then you need more inventory
space okay
[Music]
good good the time when you actually
don't want a hat good
just don't spend too much money cuz you
need to keep some for the the
[Music]
jackpot okay I'll just just go with that
for now ly drawing in 14 minutes wait
it's been 2 hours already oh my
gosh how has it been 2 hours already we
didn't have many tickets sold yesterday
so I'm not anticipating a winner but
we'll
see bricks
please does the jackpot roll over it
does it
does spam call
Kiara well she's fighting for her life
in the
dungeon I mean she did see the library
she saw
that it is in in
need
so what if this one in the middle didn't
stick out because it's like the middle
you know what I mean
you feel you feel
me like
this then it just sticks out on the
sides I feel you man
[Music]
like oh hello
thank
you you are
welcome not well I'm singing B
Thunder I know this pretty Rave girl
always think about her how come those
songs are the same I don't understand
how they're allowed to do that can I
also make a song
like that oh trade was cancelled I I'm
sorry inventory
full it's
fine I should fix my
inventory let me Dota here DOTA in the
sky I want to play as Witch
Doctor you're already witch doctor
wait that's the wrong
song or would
[Music]
be rainbow in the
sky
no it's surprisingly hard to sing a song
you know in a completely different tune
is it even I'm like staring at it and
now I don't even know I think it's
even it's even you like the pillars
we'll figure out
[Music]
pillars I think it just needs to
be slightly different
like what if they were right here
instead and we didn't have
that thank
[Music]
you sorry my inventory was full
I want to put vines on
here I do think like an archway is
good but I don't know
I could work on the top
too the librar is crying
why we're working hard on the library
though why is it crying
it's a big
chimney let's go get
vines vines might be 2016 Minecraft you
might be right when you say that
but we like them anyway what what time
is it 8 minutes until our
drawing wait it's right
here actually I think I have some in my
backpack too
this is how you get vines
right oh that's fine you can deactivate
my magic
Feather by 8 minutes we will surely have
plenty of time to gather Vines and maybe
more
chains while we're at it in 8 minutes
and then we can draw the
lottery and then and then
who
knows what will have it what kind of
what kind of leaves do we want for the
hedges is the other
question pink I don't know about pink
I mean I know I build my whole brand of
gomart around the color pink
but the library is going for more of a
dark
Academia sort of aesthetic you know I
don't know if Vines
grow in this
world so I might need a
bunch go light Library
exactly you just fill my inventory
needlessly maybe these leaves would look
[Music]
okay is this just
Oak oh
yeah I love that
sound I love that popping sound isn't
that new that's not that's not defa
[Applause]
Minecraft that's probably that's
probably
enough let's go oak bubble
[Music]
wrap
delicious tasty
sound okay
ASMR stream to recreate Minecraft sounds
you don't want me to do that cuz you
know I'm just going to
go for 60 Minutes the whole
stream then you'll regret ever having
asked sip sip sip
that looks
good now
this this is a
library I need to do I have my wheel
ready did I get it ready I think I did
I did get the wheel ready I'm so
prepared onen dungeon yeah I don't know
I don't know what this onen dungeon
is a fountain in the front that would be
cool where did I get this
grass I don't mind putting some grass
around though oops I destroyed my grass
it's not
even that's
[Music]
fine there's
holes there's holes in my
house said dungeon the literal
sewers I haven't been down there maybe
it's nice
is it nice down
there oh
bricks maybe I'm missing
out I've never been to the
sewers in real life but they're in so
many movies that it feels like it's the
you know the thing to
do you might find a clown in there
a scary
clown for all kinds of
things okay how are we doing on the
inside how are we doing on the
[Music]
outside maybe I should just fill the
roof
in just be careful up here cuz your
feather
will will'll
perish is another floor no it
[Music]
doesn't the third floor will be like the
the secret floor
ouch The Observatory oh maybe I should
have a cool Skylight
actually could be cool do I have my
[Music]
glass also it's almost time to draw the
numbers I'm
ready I've got it all
not a not a minute too early
though the people aren't ready
yet for the
jackpot ooh how about just like a like
this a diamond oh am I really one brick
short I am that's fine
I don't think I can do the Scarlet wand
logo all right
everyone it is time once
again to see what our lucky numbers will
[Music]
be let us draw them
in our
new Lottery
[Music]
system
okay the first number will
be zeros now
included lucky number six
oh sorry
for I forgot to change the
wheel just close
that lucky number
six and next we have lucky
[Music]
number three it says
three lucky number three and and finally
we
have
Lucky
Number
[Music]
Nine and these are our winning numbers
for today
folks if you've got a ticket with these
numbers be sure to report back to fart
[Music]
and does anyone have these numbers we
only sold a couple
tickets
I I think
not we will have to sell more more
[Music]
tickets then lucky numbers for today's
fart Lottery are
639 remember to check your tickets
folks the jackpot only grows larger
[Music]
and that is
it okay back to
the who won nobody won as far as I'm
aware which means the jackpot carries
over to the next
day did Moco fill in the survey yet
no she did
not I know I got to I got to move some
tick
kids but your old CEO is getting getting
tired from the
hustle of
retail got to win her back I
know I think we need more
bricks see you looking to
retire maybe I should like build a
Chocolate Factory and then
like put people through a string of
death
traps culminating in a in a terrifying
elevator ride trying to choose the next
CEO of of
fmart that could be good
[Music]
um oh am I out of the red wood
too let's get some
more of
that
okay so we can build on the inside we're
going to need a ton of
this
stuff Beast STS do I know that is that
in the in the
sewers oh yeah is that the one that the
one that Rams
you I do need to do the
new
dungon at some
point is there more dungeon there's the
one from yesterday that I have not done
yet before the server Clos well they're
not closing yet we still have two more
days I think after
today it's fairly
short I could solo it let me solo
it two is not
enough old CEO fauna can can't take too
much
more too much more
excitement um
oh I kind of need to get rid of
this early retirement okay well when you
guys say it then I want to like reject
it I'm not ready to retire just
yet maybe I should be grateful you're
saying early retirement though instead
of
like you are at that age after
all you are at that retirement
[Music]
age what else can we
expect go
two I
think it's
time for
more up sign downstairs actually I don't
know if it is maybe it's
not is
it I'm
afraid cuz it's like more
zigzags like this oh I don't
know for the second
floor no more zigzags but doesn't it
look kind of weird if it's just like
this
this shouldn't there be some kind of
transition can I make a banner do you
need a loom wa you can get a loom I've
seen
them I've seen
them
oops just brick walls anti-alias it I
love your your
terminology of
anti-aliasing in
Minecraft cuz that's exactly what it
is
oops more terracotta and less brick you
can't do terracotta stairs though right
that looks pretty
good I wonder if they're doing
the the Phoenix
dungeon right
now that dungeon
m not my favorite kind of game design
where it's just oh
you a foolish foolish player you didn't
foresee that the floor would fall out
from underneath you and it is completely
unavoidable it's intentional just cuz
it's intentional doesn't mean
it's it's
good like how I intentionally plac these
blocks here but it still doesn't make it
a good
build made some great content I guess
that's what what matters at the
end as long as we had some good
content out of
it more
stairs girl was gushing over the dungeon
I liked
the
uh the fight
the statue part that part was
cool uhoh not
this getting over streamer mad at noise
puzzle well getting over
it is consistent in its rules once you
learn the rules that's the
thing if it's a puzzle where there's no
way to know if you will die then there's
really no way to like get better at it
it's all
right the dungeon has rules
too the rules are you
die you must
die you're not supposed to get better at
it but doesn't that lead to a
frustrating
experience Dark Souls but Dark Souls
you're supposed to get better and you do
get
better that's what I learned from
playing Dark
Souls Dark Souls you're also get
reborn you're supposed to but I didn't
most honest Souls
gamer I respect
it okay we do need some lights in
here I do want like a
big
chandelier I don't know how you get to
the next floor also
[Music]
um cuz I kind of want this floor to be
open I mean it could also the next floor
could also start lower is the
thing stairs in the middle oh I could do
stairs going up
here oh wait but they can't be they
can't go like well they could if there
slabs
maybe would it still be like open enough
at the
bottom I don't want the ceiling to feel
too
low let's oh gosh that's full too oh
everything is full I hate full
inventory ah
are there any
chests hold
on we
need I'm just going to embrace the chaos
and just put all my materials
in these chests over
here which I probably should have done a
while ago
and
then hold on I should make a crafting
[Music]
bench do you call it a crafting bench
even though it's a crafting table or is
that just
me I feel like that's what people called
it back in the
day you say table
just
me I swear some Minecraft youtubers
called it
that back in in the day of Ye Old
Minecraft and then
you come up here
let's just see what this looks
[Music]
like if it doesn't impede the flow of
the next
level of the first level I
guess I don't know sort of I could hang
a big chandelier from right there though
not a lot of space for books we're
getting there don't
worry and
then no
spiral up it could or we could just
start
here or I don't know I guess it could
spiral up and we could just put books
along the whole
way the book part is for future fa to
worry
about I like the way this part looks
I feel like the first impressions are
good when you walk
in and it does it does vaguely resemble
the
Hat I think it's maybe a little short
but you walking oh I forgot to get
chains that's fine we figure it
out you come up here
[Music]
no you walk up
here and then you
have a
floor maybe not though cuz then this is
going to be really classful if I
actually fill it in
[Music]
there I could just continue the stairs I
guess could keep going up either side
I need
food see there's plenty of room for
books up here
right plenty of
room I mean the main
floor that's just where you like check
out the
books if we had a
receptionist please please donate
to
fart because the library needs
it this was not even what did I do did I
have two there just one make it even
right now or you will regret it
later uh about one two
three I mean these are stairs but are
they good stairs I'm not
sure uh
uple
one same on this
side it's not the
same what am I done what have I
done I'm going crazy trying to make it
even the library is all stairs I guess
that's what happens when it's a
when it's a
tower what do you
expect the organic stairs hold on Tetris
piece there
perfect and then and then it's the other
Tetris
piece yes it's all
Tetris now I
understand of course
it was Tetris all
along don't hit your
[Music]
head more
Tetris beautiful
get rid of this
one sometimes you don't take fall damage
with the feather do you never take fall
damage with the feather is it only when
it gets
deactivated am I learning things that I
should have known many times many years
ago
more
Tess not books just
stairs please
donate so that we can purchase
books
[Music]
please hold on and then this
side in the library library's
defense books are expensive and stairs
are
cheap is this
right hope you're not afraid of
heights see it just becomes clustr fob
big now because of
this then how do we put the floor
in come up
here go up the
middle ladders I don't want ladders
though I think the split staircase no
the split staircase is
cool and good and it gives people
options in
life in the library is all about
options I am getting dizzy
though building this ooh
planks
please maybe we should have built the
floor cuz then it would give us an idea
of where
see that doesn't work you're going to
hit your
head there's no room for books as it
turns
out you
slabs you're probably still going to hit
your
head I just have to make sure it's on
the right block
so I can actually Place stuff on
them how's the life of an NPC going is
hard also it's really hot in
here and I'm sleep
deprived and it's hard to build a
[Music]
library NPC
fa is struggling today on day day
six of Yen
Reco I keep breaking my
ankles everything is starting to blend
in I just want to deor into my
library all cute like
I was going to get I was going to get
[Music]
paintings let's go Shear some Shear some
sheep really
quick let's do
it and maybe some
[Music]
chains as
well little sheor accent there I thought
of her too
when I send that she I feel like she
often says stuff like
that
oh is the is the lamp never going to
come
back have I made a terrible
mistake oh
no I bring you dark Eternal Darkness to
the land
just remember actually I could I could
delete all the
lanterns and then get a lantern Monopoly
[Music]
going and then people will have to
buy my
lanterns dark lord
[Music]
F got to get a cool chandel
clear lots of chains any
sheep can you leave me
alone I'm like the rber baron that's a
good thing right that's a positive
comparison can you abstain that's a good
one that one's got two that's
good we should start some more
schemes like an upside down triangle
scheme if I
just find five people willing to give me
10,000 coins and then those five people
each find five more people willing to
give them 10,000 coins and
everybody will be up 40,000
coins
infinite money hack but it turns out
it's just easier to make potato
salad it does kind of make me want to
eat potato
salad potato salad is nice and summery
potato salad is also popular in Japan
like surprisingly
right I think like Mayo in general is
surprisingly popular in Japan
chain
please yeah Japanese Mayo is different
though I forget why doesn't it have like
a higher proportion of egg yolks or
something I don't
know this good Mayo is
delicious Mayo is delicious and I'm
tired of pretending like it's
gross and then it's not delicious
because it is delicious
and I won't be shamed for saying
it wait this could make a
good decoration for the
library maybe I'm not sure I'm in
decisive I'm going
home Mayo makes you
sick that's
understandable it's very rich for sure
tired of it being in
everything you tell
me that's a
mood I mean that's how I feel about
butter though but that's just cuz I
don't eat
dairy or
eggs and they do they put it in
everything they really put milk and
everything
the follow your heart vegan Mayo is
yummy I think so too I like just Mayo
[Music]
also didn't they get sued by what is it
Helman for calling it mayo and Helman
was like um you can't call it Mayo if it
doesn't have eggs in it but then they
lost and then Helman was like okay fine
and then they came out with a vegan Mayo
of their own if you can't beat him join
them
the big Mayo battles
exactly I was going to do
this it's good to put the Lance in when
it's when it's dark
oh now that's this is an idea hold
on is this how you make
chandelier in
Minecraft I can't put that
there what am I making
it's it's a
chandelier I'm pretty sure you can make
like cooler ones
but
whatever this is good enough little too
low nobody's hitting their heads on this
don't don't delude yourself you're not
this tall in Minecraft well actually my
pointy had my hidden it
oh actually does just barely grazes
it that looks that looks
fine it looks good
enough is this how you make paintings
oh it
is
ooh oh wait I hate this
one no
stop I don't want two of the same but
how many 2x ones even are there are
there only
two aren't there banners
though like not not not banners but
didn't they have paintings they look
like B
banners what's wrong with this
one I just like don't want this like
Mario pixel dude in my house you know I
want like Fine
Arts not a not a video game
poster portrait of the queen
I hate the college
Vibe I do kind of hate Mario I think
that
Luigi is way better and I think that
Mario
is bad to his
brother I think he let the spotlight go
to his
head and he takes all the credit when
Luigi
is just as good if not better than his
brother very good
take I don't know but every time I say
that people like no
Mario he's he's an innocent
guy he's just doing his best it's
like I don't know is he
I for
green Luigi's holding back for Mario I
think so I think Luigi lets Mario be in
the spotlight but also Luigi wouldn't
sometimes he does he does wish that
Mario would share just a little
bit you know instead of them being the
Mario Brothers if they could be the
Mario and Luigi brothers you know
you think Luigi is so scared cuz Mario
bullies
him is that
true how could he do
this Luigi just has a bad home life
no but we
accurate his name is Luigi Mario so it
all goes back that
far to like their family naming them
that
way we I don't have like any place to
put paintings any place places to put
paintings in
here what if we
do
cartz
pillar wait
wait hold on imagine the vision
for one
[Music]
second what
if and then we could put like a big
painting do we got big
paintings do we got 3x
twos I thought there were did they
change the painting system
a big off center
painting bottom
left there are four by
two so I'm
doomed so my whole Tower is doomed
oh
no it's over we have to have the Mario
painting well how do you make how do you
make
a a
banner do you need a
loom put a statue how do you make a
statue
wool and a loom is that all you
need I can do that I
think armor
[Music]
stand yeah I could try to make a pretty
Banner wait do you need my dye I have
red dye
wait do you actually need a
loom isn't there a loom over
here I
think loom
loom loom and
Gloom glom is looming over
me why is so emo
oh that's not a loom I thought one of
these guys had a loom am I
crazy Mario's a good brother maybe when
the cameras are rolling he's a good
brother but have you considered what
happens off
screen on the beach
one excuse me pleas
me evil Mario
Theory and also he was voiced by Chris
Pratt you
know
Alum wait is this also the wrong way I'm
lost wasn't there a
loom I swear there was a
loom
somewhere I'm a loom more like a loon
right
now brain is
melting by the volcano is this the way
to the volcano
you guys got any
looms wait is this the way to a
dungeon you guys got any
looms wrong
way Ena dungeon has a t where's are
we're not inside
outside I thought one of these lovely
groups had a
loom did they
not am I just
crazy wait is there stuff over
[Music]
here oh wait I'm
back how do I get string though wait do
you need string for a a banner to make a
loom cuz if I just make if I just can I
swear there was a
loom try ceran where's the
Cerulean
Camp six wool and one stick wait Loom is
optional for banners is that just how
you customize
it should I
just get one out of the construction
box oh I checked the ran Camp I guess we
don't need to customize it though that
would be kind of
cool let's just make
regular
[Music]
banners is it
ugly maybe a
little maybe a
lot decently ugly
looks if you just put plants on
it everything looks better
though that's my principal like
decoration technique
kind of asymmetrical though or
unbalanced
rather it's like a bank a corrupt
Bank
good perfect
I like how this gets a nice view of the
this
tree and we have turned their view into
just the
tower okay I'm going
to
purchase
wo put that away and I will
dye the
wool
red that's not how you Dy
wool it's so
expensive this was before they changed
the balance
of of
dyes a stick
you
say wait other
way like a sign yes
oh this is what the library
means just a a plain r head
Banner looks
great very beautiful
wow make it green maybe it should
be I'll worry about that later
two off the ground right now
okay not
bad the railings are uneven I'm just not
done yet with the
railings the first floor looks pretty
okay wait I could add like pots I think
you can't put anything in the big pots
right can you dye
them the big
pots you
can you can put the smaller pot in it
can
you this is too many
pots it's only two but it feels like too
many put small pot on top of big
pot is that the The
Meta maybe a sapling
need to shift
click it's going to look silly isn't
it I trust oh
wait oh that must be the
meta it actually looks
good it's magnificent it
is let get a nice how about this
one Blue Orchid this is how we can get
some
colors in the
library you know books are all so
colorful um if people try to go to the
third floor oh gosh I don't want to go
to the third
floor it makes me
dizzy we could get some
signs let's make signs
work in
progress It's just like a real
construction maybe I should say do not
enter do not
enters that way I can't get sued if they
get
hurt going on the third third
floor
okay it's like a museum
now maybe I could add
more
bookshelves oh I need to go buy
more stuff though and more food more
reads you use reads to make books which
you
read everything makes perfect
[Music]
sense she will live in there she's
welcome to
I can eat a lot of horse deficiency is
like eating in the
car okay where's the
leather I bet we'll be able to make like
three whole
bookshelves with all the leather we've
collected I thought there was one in
there
30 leather four
leather I thought I abandoned like one
piece of
leather should I make like you can make
I think they added a
quill 21 books
cuz you can like put books on these
shelves
right but how do you take them out you
can just take them
out so we can actually write
books and put them in the
shelves okay but these shelves are like
expensive
cuz they take six to
do yeah put the fan fictions
[Music]
there I'm going to make a
few regular
shelves my few me three they're so
expensive
and I don't know where we even want to
put
them I mean do we want it to go all the
way
up under the stairs like
here like
that I mean there's books there's
books maybe I should write a book
I think I probably won't stick around
for too much longer I might not even do
the dungeon today I'm pretty
tired but maybe I could write a
book we need a
[Music]
feather I
believe and then other people could also
write
books to add to the
[Music]
library I'm
sorry it's for the
sorry we didn't get a
feather wait I have more leather wait I
didn't make all the
leather I must have run out of
paper we could make more books
oh wait I did get a
feather
probably for the
library I'm
[Music]
sorry this isn't who I am this isn't who
I want to
be
okay I need ink sacks check it
out right there
boom boom
boom
okay sacrifices must be made for the
[Music]
library I don't know what to write
though I'm too sleepy to ride anything
good it is the fanfic corner
how do you do
it book and
quill copy facee just right
Twilight we could certainly use TW but I
don't want to I don't want to like low
effort it you know I'm all about the
High effort
usually when I have brain
power for the
library CH GP book no
no copy dist Track lyrics
wait once you start riding do you have
to like finish it and sign it maybe we
do this later or maybe I even do it off
screen and
then maybe you'll see people read it at
another
time I'm just
sleepy you can sign at any
time other people are also welcome to
put books in
here I'm pretty happy with this though
this is
progress maybe I should put one
sign
outside this
is hold on hold
on
the Scarlet
wand Library
[Music]
paid for by
FAA hold
on we can we can fix
this brought you
by brought
to
you
by by for
Mar do I have
any cool
dyes sorry
[Music]
flower I gray is cool enough
it's pretty good that's I'll call that
progress for today I didn't sell many
lottery
tickets and I didn't get involved in by
the
shenanigans but I trusted the
shenanigans will
[Music]
happen with or without my
presence all right no lawsuits well
we'll see I'm not sure sure Moco is
totally
sold on the way things turned
out inside looks nice when you say it
like that it makes it sound like the
inside looks bad or the outside looks
bad the outside is the best
part it looks just like the Hat
outside is
perfect okay I'm going to go take a
nap it looks good the library
definitely
exists the sky looks
cool it's a real life Library no one can
doubt the existence of the library
anymore I like how the floor turned out
I'm pretty happy with how the first
floor turned out the rest needs some
work but that nothing a work in progress
sign can't
fix the pillar is missing yeah it's not
done yet on the outside but it'll be
[Music]
fine okay thank you for watching today
sorry was an uneventful day on my end
luckily there's plenty more streams
happening from everybody
else we'll see what happens thank you
for tuning in regardless and I'll see
you next time I'm going to go to
sleep bye-bye F Well
byea FM this ain't your granny's radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to J and now let's
[Music]
go 1 2 3 go there is spot with flow we
are