[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
yo boy
oh wait
lana is not being picked up
property
system
let me say something
i started say something
no i still can't hear you
why
okay
[Music]
i hear the monsters
hunting for me
i can't i don't know
uh
[Music]
why is the audio's weird
already ordered
[Music]
say something
i said something hello
yeah i hear you but obs doesn't hear you
no
maybe the input or something i don't
know yeah i'm changing it i'll keep on
changing it but
oh yeah
yeah you heard her
say something lena
um quinoa is so cute
oh i guess i guess because okay
yeah yeah because okay
yeah you guys hear her in an input that
i don't want you to hear her from but
okay that works hi
hello
okay i think i'm ready sort of
i can do this
[Music]
oh she's giving me bread so nice okay i
am ready now i'm ready my minecraft
window is like all over the place but
i'm gonna sweet uh
yeah i'm also all over the place because
i don't i came here i was kind of lost
but i don't know where to buy the
tickets so i guess like whatever maybe
we just bet on the horses in our head
then at least we don't lose money
exactly let's do this
are you guys ready for the festival
are
we there's so much stuff here and i had
like no idea so so much was being built
because just i think ian and id was not
really notified of like the process of
this until a few hours ago
i think um
i think no no like i know a little bit
at least about like the building but
it's not like i wanna i can't
participate anyway so
yeah at the end of the day i'm just like
you know let's go to the festival yeah
there's more than i expected it's even
bigger than last year i think damn
[Music]
oh my gosh i'm wearing pants
i'm gonna take it off okay nice
i was like the skin of your new outfit
noise yes you're still wearing the
sports festival you know i changed my
clothes because people keep telling me i
never changed my clothes so i did just
for the festival and then here you are
with the sports festival off
i didn't realize it well that's a little
bit embarrassing but okay no problem
no problem no problem
where is the
there's a lot of people here but i don't
know where evil the horse betting places
and where the horse
ticket buying places i don't know where
any of that is it's not here right this
is they're doing some horror stuff
yeah this is the horror house do you
want to go to the whorehouse later
yeah we can do everything
yeah enjoy the festival
oh my gosh there's music
what
they must have built some kind of like
tune here we should just follow where
everybody else goes but currently
everybody's here so everybody's here
probably didn't start yet
it's 8 p.m at 8 p.m they start
uh okay okay okay yeah the horse bidding
place i don't think we need to do that
maybe when the horse bidding starts you
can like follow everybody
oh
oh there's like an
english explanation for this chicken
game chicken shooting game
oh this is ollie's ah that's why it's
english nice very nice
shoot as many chickens doing her best
for trying to read it right now falls
into the lava
oh
no let the chicken out
[Music]
[Applause]
this is not rust okay this is minecraft
sure it says shoot as many chickens ah
funny aren't ya
yeah i'm pretty funny aren't i i see i
didn't even make a connection because
i'm a phoenix
exactly
yeah i was just um what if it's a water
situation you know like what's this
what if
oh
where do we go when do we go
[Music]
is that supposed to be like um carousel
a merry-go-round
oh my gosh what is that what is the
horse like that
oh my gosh it is it is like a
merry-go-round kind of thing but it's a
pig
it's just not twirling it's not going
around but
betting to your right oh really
oh okay let's see
i think
it's like five minutes until it starts
oh can we really steal that betting
ticket ah how to buy how to buy
how to buy
how to buy oh
i've ate eight diamonds give me one
ticket please but what do i bet on how
do i bet how does this work
i don't even know
um
what is this oh
gosh
[Laughter]
you can get diamonds here in case you
don't have any
apparently
okay okay okay okay okay
ah okay okay
uh i will bet on
huh
what first race runner
ah
first race runner is
uh yes whose horse is um
i think it's on the uh the list is the
complete list is on the thingy
[Music]
how did i get
it can you please i think like they're
in the they're in the public vc um ah
do you want to vet oh
wait i think
how do i open here
ah oh no that was
yes yes yes of course uh
number one yeah i think
so once you put once you you get like
one slip every single time that oh for
each like diamond so ah
betting slips back if you win okay next
good i don't know
yes yes
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
okay nine
guys i don't know who these are
apparently supporters in the first one
who else do you guys know who else are
these
i'm rooted by the way
you you plus
20 are you saying 20. oh me do i need
you my okay
[Music]
oh wait the last three ways i messed up
wait maybe i'll just choose random
numbers
[Music]
hey
thank you
[Music]
i
how many
[Music]
okay
how
[Music]
uh
how many were you supposed to have left
over 20 right
she's gonna keep myself muted until
they're done because i can't talk
together when i'll interrupt him
um i i found the list it's senpai text
also i think elena's in the other voice
channel or she's back maybe i don't know
but i found the list
with the names
hi
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
let's go back to our voice chat
okay okay
uh
okay
i just don't know where to go
now let's follow everybody i guess
i didn't bring diamond but uh if you
want you can you can try out her booth
oh no no it's okay it's okay i already
bet it's better
oh okay okay okay
where do we go next though everybody's
still here so i guess we're safe
yeah okay i think let's just wait
which voice chat is the
horse race say i'm not sure if they want
everyone to be together for that but
uh maybe
oh there a lot of people are number
three
are we supposed to join that one
to hear their screams
maybe
where is the location though
that's that's what i want to know yeah
but they're all still
here they're not still
chilling
um
but maybe they're chilling because
they're talking in the vc wait who's in
the vc i don't know oh
no i think like after the horse race
it's gonna be like uh free yeah yeah
yeah yeah then we can do whatever
yeah then we can do whatever we want
maybe it's like right behind this thing
here yeah everybody's in like three
chaps do you wanna go to three chat
oh or i don't know
yeah it's up to you yeah okay
maybe i don't know what they're talking
maybe drop a little bit of what they're
talking about okay okay okay
you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
riding a horse
[Music]
okay
i think it's good for now that we stay
here
um
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
um
hey
[Music]
oh yeah and then i don't have to put it
anywhere right i just gave it back later
to get my diamond spoons
[Music]
foreign
go straight
[Music]
after the second round the goal
is there
[Music]
um
oh like what's the word no
[Music]
hey
so
[Music]
oh she's just explaining like where the
horse that was used in the first race
goes next and please check
[Music]
she looks at me like is she confused she
must be confused
[Music]
okay
by the way
[Music]
is
let's go back to the other one
where i'm going for elena
all right
is that
yeah yeah they're they're slowly leaving
the voice chats
i think
elena is still not here though
[Music]
i want to ride a heart
nihongo utenai
wait how do you
oh
ah okay we just do this one
can't find the the heart thingy
please let my
thoughts come across
oh there we go
welcome back i think they said something
like uh believe the voice should accept
if you're a racer so that's why i came
back here okay okay but i'm i don't know
i'm confused i translated a little bit
for my chat while i was muted
oh yeah i was like um awkward i was like
hmm how do i mute because there's so
many windows yeah basically it's like
starting from now they're gonna
they're gonna like test drive
before the real deal okay this is test
testing round yeah really oh they get a
testing round that's pretty nice of them
yeah who did you bet on by the way first
round super right and then do you have
the second round
i don't have enough diamonds
ah in some meaning you went all in for
subaru yeah i'm guys i went all in for
savaru let's go oh sweet
well i bet for i think uh second one
miku and third one pickle yeah ah nice
nice nice but uh maybe third round is
later right i think
four i think fourth round is kind of
late
is later okay okay okay because i guess
the yeah the winners and second place
riders of the first three rounds will be
in the fourth round so i couldn't bet on
anything there yet wow
thank you
[Music]
tonkatsu hey
i love tonkatsu
the food yeah bonnie really likes her
puns
pun birds
humber why is there so much violence
here they're like infected by rust
i know
yeah too much rest hello oh my god are
you gonna
play on the day where like
supposedly everyone fights for
like death
yeah that's what i'm asking like i asked
a bunch of people if they're gonna come
but um i don't know um i haven't seen
the answers yet
maybe after the stream i just i didn't i
didn't know when exactly that would
happen anyway so for now i just
scheduled a stream for 31st but i think
that day there won't be any fighting yet
because the reset is on the second so
probably on the first
is where the fighting happens but
whatever i don't really
i don't think i really would want to be
part of that anyway what is that yeah
maybe i would want to like sightsee but
not much but i want to at least like
watch it you know so i'm not like behind
yeah
it's so easy to feel me
like you're missing out so i'm just
gonna you know watch yeah
oh they are they're introducing the
oh yes writers now oh they come up
cool
that's so cool
so that was vatamin and max
[Music]
oh wait they're they're they're sharing
horses though because like for example
meals horse will be used by both on
senpai too
yeah so this is just like the sponsor of
the house diago apparently yeah
[Music]
are they all listening to the
introductions now no
maybe it's just the writers and the
organizers i think right now together
yes yes
okay it's it's like i don't know what to
do this time in this festival like
yeah there's like uh i have i have no
clue where to be and where to go
but okay for now
right now is the horse race and watch
the iii
let's go
i'm betting all in for subaru senpai
guys
to show that holotori um bond wait so if
i bet two diamonds on salvador senpai
and let's say she wins which i doubt now
um
but how much would i get back
maybe i don't know
is it double or hmm
i don't know
because they never really said the
multiplayer
i don't know i bet one i mean oh i got i
got my diamond from choco sensei's booth
what did you have to do for that
um
she uh we have to always give her a love
message they're kind of hesitated
love message yeah
love message that's why um yeah i was
telling you you know if you want to give
give it a try
okay
is this a test round now
yeah i think it's a test round now was
that what
how did you zoom again
with octopus right
i know yeah i love spines
no that was you know oh monthly go go oh
they returned
oh i think that's a test
i feel backwards
sort of goal
really for real and she went back okay
that's obviously a test round
yeah
okay okay i'll go okay
okay hopefully with that one test round
she realized how to
ride a horse she has potential oh
confidence you know have confidence
yeah have confidence i'll be up here
cook chicken
were you oh i'm gonna i'm gonna fight me
with you
fight to fight tall oh sorry for cora
okay picora
i call russia i'm gonna be here and his
voice a little bit low oh really sorry i
i'm i'm kind of capturing the audio
differently from usual so i'm i'm
confused too
i think like my my bgm is also kind of
low
but
it's fine
yeah
it's better to have it rather than too
loud if it's too loud you can't hear
anybody
it's about to be fast whatever is so
fast though oh oh sweater is not doing
bad
either oh she kind of like uh got hooked
on the fence for a moment but she's
still going fast it'll happen she going
somewhere far behind
oh all the spider webs
yeah bye
they did nothing to what they i wait
enough around is she doing oh yeah yeah
maybe maybe multiple laps maybe yeah two
laps they said
oh so i i'm impressed by somebody she's
second but you're basically
[Music]
don't give up
never give up the book
how many lives is this the second left
[Laughter]
is really cool though it's like red and
black yeah she probably had a [\h__\h] horse
though
just look yeah i think yeah i think it's
about like the stats of the horse yeah
yeah that must have carried vatima's
empire perhaps so it was her own gamer
skill who knows who knows
it's a teamwork between like the person
and the horse right yeah
they have they have to trust and love
each other
they have different colors that's so
cool it's just like
i don't think yeah ever
seen that kind of armor how did they do
that this is like
maybe like with dye
i don't know dyed legs
yeah they dyed the leather maybe because
you can right
i never tried that in minecraft but it's
also been way too long i forgot so many
things
oh
look at them riding by the audience
it's so cool oh
nice
oh yeah let's applaud eight eight eight
is petty petty party party party eight
eight eight eight eight eight percent
rashi
shuba rushing
wow
go go next go next connect go next
go next let's go
so next i didn't vet for anything
ah well then you can lean back or you
can bet um without you know without
money yeah yeah i can bet in my heart oh
let's see who's up next uh bhutan senpai
with uma uma umadayo poruka
they start announcing the rankings in my
place oh yeah oh i'm i'm reading a
different list
i have my second three million
senpai a watermelon
senpai oh okay yeah she slurped it nice
she slurped it yeah
watermelon
why is i uh you know has a date uh at
collabo stream of vatami senpai right
now but she's cheering for her date
isn't that cute oh that's so cute
oh what am i on oh
that's isn't that fitting
oh
thank you
what did it give you uh
oh okay okay
what's happening down there
i don't know
bedding maybe
let me see it
i don't know because i don't know
maybe they're just checking
maybe maybe maybe maybe before before
the next round they're like twisting
though
zeta is here
oh everybody who
betters on what bet on whatever senpai
is uh they get a return of 10 times the
bets that day
10 times y'all sometimes we're rich not
bad
nice you you're going i guess
uh i wonder
do i get a return for betting on second
place um
they didn't say anything on second place
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh oh no they're now gonna prepare for
the second race okay i guess only first
place
everybody who bets on the first place
gets
diamonds really um really what about
second
come on
can we at least get like five times
it's okay i'm glassy shibo senpai was
like second so i'm proud yeah proud of
betting
betting for her
let's go yeah for riding a horse the
first time
yeah first time rider at least like i
feel like riding a horse in minecraft is
a million times easier than in rust and
more intuitive like when i was riding a
horse on rust and i pressed space to
jump i just fell off the horse and the
horse went like 10 kilometers away
i was running away from a bear and then
i pressed space because i wanted to trap
no did the bear kill you in the end
yeah oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] horse
why you leave her to die like that
yeah and then you know what like i got
myself a horse and then i
left her like overnight because i wanted
to sleep and then in the morning she's
gone maybe she died so weak
oh that's weird i also had like
something weird happen like i found
ina's horse somewhere
um just standing randomly without cover
without food so i was like okay i'm
gonna like protect it so i took it to my
place and i built like a theater and
everything for it and it was perfect it
should have been fine it had food inside
too a lot of food and then i i i'm gone
for like three minutes i come back and
it's the horse is just gone
just gone yeah which
it shouldn't there's no there was no
reason no explanation for it
the food was still left in the in the
feeder
it's dramatically
yeah
and there was no one around that could
have i don't think anybody took it to be
honest yeah yeah yeah yeah that's why i
was like you know even though i have a
horse like maybe i'll just not use it no
i just not use it and then maybe it's
better to you know
use somebody's taxi if you see someone
and then if they have a car i'm going
okay i did um use the the hot air
balloon the other day
uh when i logged on the water the hot
air balloon was like right in front of
my house was that you or
no
no no no no no no i left it far far away
because then when i wanted to use it to
go back to
well my house then with the field
somebody took the fuel a certain
somebody
oh my god
anyway
but but hot air balloon um the the
controls are really difficult but once
you've got it it's it's actually a quite
a good
like way of getting around um
it's hard to shoot you
from like down there so no one can get
you
can you shoot somebody from up there
though from up i didn't try i didn't try
but
wherefore try perhaps
oh okay
that's something to definitely try for
next time yeah
why are there two riders in there
oh number one
with them
[Music]
the white one okay
let's see
oh and then overpower
[Music]
number two
um
oh i wanted to give you a flower but
thank you i got it i got it i think you
got it now gave me a flower because my
joke was so good
it's a token of appreciation
you are the bridge basically of whole
life what a name
what a name
where is
[Music]
that
is kopo not here by the way i've seen i
don't think she is a couple of ideas but
not all of them
who are you are you rooting for who
today
for you in this this race no in this
frame
race
see one time i was actually fast enough
to to say something sweet
in this one i'm vote i'm rooting for you
okay okay
i'm gonna root for
masjid
oh okay
well i mean the horse name says it
is
[Music]
let's go
it's because it's it's the mako sample
fight
don't let me down
yeah
might say let's go
yeah i'm gonna root for my day
all right let's see if our recipe is not
participating okay uh testing run oh
tessa says this
test obstacles
don't do that a second time
wow
oh come on
come on yes
are they are they rigged did someone put
like butter or oil on the on the shadows
yeah yeah
man she's so fast
two laps
interesting
okay i didn't even use the chance to do
a second lap i think they did one and a
half yeah
[Music]
i'm rooting for uh
ah they're ripping
was it the horse that kicked them off
really
sheesh
[Music]
let's
[Applause]
nice jump nice jump now don't fall off
now yeah this is your chance go go oh
what around
i'm watching over you
oh
her horse is so motivated let's go
ah she got a she got a safe distance
from puerto rico no problem here
wow
[Music]
also pretty good he has pretty good
stats
oh
ooh
i will not be in the third race though
no who am i supposed to root for
let's see let's let's see the list of um
participants i can tell you it's pecora
with tekashiritio noel with tobenai uma
uma
rui with kaya number 69
okay okay okay
my truth for
mello
who tori oh yeah
horatoni yeah
[Laughter]
do i get it now
maybe she's she seems to be working
number two jaguar
thank you tai chi
okay number tiny
this one
i wonder is she gonna
i don't think there's time to give
everybody their winnings right now
you can say psycho dances
[Music]
are we doing this now really really is
there time
let me check in the voice chat
that she's in
i really would love to see with her care
on a stick wait i don't have carrots i
she's can't
in any voice chat okay
are we
maybe
maybe later or is it uh
[Music]
third race is
wait seven times
how is it
what is going on
[Music]
what what i just i'm just gonna
i'm just gonna keep it whatever it's
only two diamonds in the end whatever
who cares
i'll try again at the very end because
i'm confused
nobody i'm gonna
bet all in
all in as in my heart
um for kyle
because that shows my support for the
fellow hulatori which is louis and kyla
oh
okay by the way i have six ninety subs
nice
six ninety sums
what are we waiting for right now um
for this for the third round
yes to start but
i don't think we're starting yet
yeah whoa what's this one
i think i want to touch the bed around
here i keep on pressing e to open things
it's right click right that's right
click
should i claim really okay okay okay
i'll just i'll just give it to her here
hi uh oh [\h__\h]
what was it qq
okay
what's she gonna do
she looking at it oh
oh
oh yeah i think i might be getting my
winnings
oh why not guys
um maybe should i try the first
returning the first one as well
what about what about what about what
about that [\h__\h] what about this one
arigato
do i get something from this too
[Music]
what if
if if i don't get anything back for that
that that's good that's good to just
just wondering just wondering
she's thinking
hard
in a long time i think
oh i guess not
maybe not
okay
i got what i wanted and what i needed
nothing for second place only first
place
but different even when on
if the horse even if it gets number one
the the horse that got number one in the
second round only got seven times the
return while in the first round the
number one horse got ten times the
return
why
what
what what
why
because maybe like they already know the
power like oh this is the most powerful
horse well it depends on how on the
other people bets on on the bets from
the other
there's a lot people
people betting on yeah
that's how this kind of stuff works i
don't i forgot
oh my gosh crony's burning wait so the
lower
the odds are the lower the return is
the that means the
more people
bet for that person or the less people
bet for that person
tell me chad
you're the big brain people yes okay
that's correct okay so that means that
seven times it was lower because more
people bet for mikko senpai than people
bet for vata messenger
so like uh the more underrated someone
is the bigger the payout will be so this
next so the snack okay so this next
that's nice nice nice okay okay okay
who's flying oh matsuri senpai
nice
everybody's all lined up now
okay
i love noel senpai's face
what is that was she wearing i was
wondering too
i mean did the coolest simple end up
like having the mask style
if she ends up doing it i really want to
visit it do you know
i don't know about it
oh we can check it out if she does that
if i knew that this was happening i
would have liked to participate in the
race or like riding horses
next time maybe
we have to make an enid
focused uh festival
event yeah
[Music]
we should yeah i feel like we need to
make because i know like japan like
makes a lot of events too which is great
but i think it would be nice if we also
make our event yeah
especially because i did
i never was on the server finding but i
saw and i heard that you guys are really
good at building stuff so
oh we have our people
[Laughter]
we'll leave it all to you guys ian will
just be mental support for building
we'll just give you the materials and
you guys build it
i mean i'm not the one that's good at
building it's um
uh kyla's like really crazy about
grinding and i think like the person who
built the most on the whole idea cup was
um
ali muna and oh kyla was sponsoring one
of the prizes like we were doing like
this uh
climbing thing like climbing like a
pole
and then on the top there's like prizes
and the prizes are like netherride
swords and then you know the right shoes
and stuff like that oh
yeah
nice id is pretty crazy like not me like
i'm just like super casual but the
people at night are kind of crazy yeah
yeah i mean i just saw like clips of
kayla's collection of elijah's and stuff
like that
oh this this elytra i'm using it's kyla
i'm not surprised
yeah we were like working on something
that's why i was in a deserted island
remember when i logged in earlier
and then yes
nice i was like oh shoot oh trial trial
oh oh my god so fast
also pretty fast yo
so fast you disappeared
damn yeah
wait that's really fast what the heck is
that
damn
yeah everybody unity has their roles you
know kyla kayla grimes and samuna builds
and me i'm i'm in charge of writing
fiction you know i'm i'm the librarian
like librarian
yeah he's a librarian
oh we're starting
soon
where are you
i had to go a little bit further because
when i'm back that far i couldn't see
the like the beginning of the race
oh okay okay oh cause you don't have
zoom in no i'm using zoom but still i
wouldn't see them
okay then yeah weird
like they're too far my my loading
thingy is too low
okay okay
game
i keep on hearing those
hey but i don't see them did you hear
that too
the sound of the the flying thing is
when you don't sleep
oh phantom
i hear them but i keep hearing like
weird sounds but i don't know i can't
really pinpoint what it's oh my god
where
you so high up there
what is she doing
oh
she's flexing oh stand up i know
stop
well this time it's a bit more balanced
not an obvious first place right away
the fir the the first third ones
are all very close
this is riveting content
oh [\h__\h] so what's up i just went past it
as if there was nothing there oh where
the hell is it but
oh here here
come one come on
where is the nozaki power
come on
well told us that i once again had no
troubles with that part i'm like an
announcer am i doing a good job
you are
i i will also announce our wedding soon
don't worry and here they go um
i guess i don't know
i'm louie cam right now
she tried she tried
she tried wow
damn wait first was
who was first where's the people i
didn't even look probably told us him
but
commentary
kyla
what the heck that horse
wait that one's stellar i have a ladder
kyle doing my 69.
well thankfully kaiduma 69 is not in the
last race
yeah so no one gets that [\h__\h] horse
[Laughter]
gonna turn that into basashi right away
of course sashimi
oh no
i had it once
i can't get to her she's so it's kind of
sad she's here all the time she's not
even watching the race
what are you doing
oh
she's up there i wanted to get up there
but it's so hard it's just one pixel
wait what did you do again to get that
one diamond
i don't know she's just really rich uh i
should just say
id server is a little bit messed up
look
just because
[Music]
[Applause]
actually
[Music]
foreign
got it
[Laughter]
[Music]
you
no no no why would i do that
thank you thank you
[Music]
well you stole my diamond so i stole
your amber rule
fine it's an exchange it's that it's
kind of like we're we're trading lunch
you know and it's like oh you want to
swap lunch yeah
wait ah they're currently betting for
the last race right
oh okay okay oh
yeah are they bidding yeah the horses
are
yago
oh my god
and number one
i want to get for a monday uh
i might bet for number one because toast
empire was on number one and one with
that one
but also
ah vatami's horse is not in there and
she got number one but it's not in there
the other one
that one was
oh oh yeah mikko senpai right
[Music]
i know wait they're choose ah those are
the available
wait let me see let me see they wrote it
here right
what's it say last race
last race
wait do we have number one yeah we have
okay i'm just gonna bet on number one
but it's gonna take a while okay
okay um are you gonna go now if you're
going tell me i'm gonna go too
[Music]
i'll stay here the line is long
yeah okay okay okay okay um
you're loyal to number one huh
like how i'm loyal to my eye
no no i never bet on that one before oh
really oh oh what am i saying yeah yeah
um
ah everybody who bought a ticket please
go away yeah yeah i didn't buy a ticket
yet
[Music]
oh
is saying anya stole her
ticket or diamonds mm-hmm
yeah
oh yeah
delicious delicious
dangerous you're playing a dangerous
game here they're gonna let out the
anger and frustrations in
in rest later
gonna kill expression
aggression in my minecraft summer
festival more likely than you think
[Music]
oh by the way
fireworks didn't they say
oh was it 9 45
45 minutes
the line is long it's freaking long
and yeah
yes when i see senpai is a minecraft
head like she also has like the blue
thing on the left side right reminds me
of my
reminds me of my own head ah
my like my default that's right yeah
so i was like huh it's me no oh she's
not the same guy
i got sticky key
why are you not turning it off i don't
know
men look side
i mean looks like
you can you can't squat if you don't
turn on stickers i can't i just have to
do it slowly which is more challenging
anyway isn't it when you when you no
slowly
oh [\h__\h] i cut it again come on
calm down
speed squats see you can't do you can't
do that if you don't if you have sticky
keys on
normally i don't have that problem
anyway
okay
yes yes i'm here
[Music]
when did you wake up today
um i wake up at like noon
that's just a normal wake-up time for a
whole life member yeah
i usually wake up a little bit earlier
but yeah i just felt like waking up at
noon i woke up at like
at nine
was supposed to have a recording at 9 30
was waiting in by for half an hour was
told to come back in
like one and a half hours because
something went wrong and it got delayed
and i came back at 11 yeah then we
recorded for an hour and a little bit
and then and now i'm here
nice yeah
you're feeling you're feeling refreshed
though right no sleepy no uh
right now i'm okay but i'm sad i could
have slept longer why are you aiming uh
i mean at my height
it's a it's a love arrow kiara will you
accept it shoot me
wait wait wait wait almost
[Laughter]
nice feels
feels just like when you're in love i
think that's the feeling oh they're
building an actual line a little bit of
a heart ache
pain pickle pain
[Music]
what are they lining up for they're
lining up to bed for the last round guys
okay let's light them up number one
oh that's perfect combination
number one horse strong because
one in the third race and bottom isn't
by strong because one in the first race
let's go
best choice i think
[Music]
they need a second stall
i'm gonna turn into karen soon they need
a second i don't think
yeah one more employee please
i have a lot of employees can you right
you can't like uh land them
for the festival yeah yeah
true right
unbelievable i'm like waiting for so
long here out in the blazing sun
please give me some water at least yeah
so much sunny i know it's different
remember like because last year i think
it was like night time but somehow it's
day time it keeps day you know when is
night time are we never going to have
any night time oh i think that turned it
off yeah
they also turned off the spawning of
enemies
okay
yeah but are we gonna have fireworks too
maybe they're gonna no
night time
oh hopefully yeah they should
they should
they have to
okay
daytime fireworks so cool
yeah
wait have i ever seen daytime fireworks
no i think it was always the heart
mhm
[Music]
oh
nothing what are you doing
you're flirting with someone else you're
playing yourself no it's not
you're flirting with fauna and sword i
can play
i was trying to get food ah
i have food too
okay give me yes
eat my food only
yeah good job did i get it i think so
potato potato
[Music]
we need to we need to stay in the
secluded place but maybe after we bet
yeah oh after we bet oh oh oh okay let
me go uh i think my friend might be soon
where is she
gracie
oh okay well
uh
number four number four uh
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
uh
okay
[Music]
there's just so many people there were
like 15 people in that voice chat i feel
intimidated too intimidated to talk okay
so i bet 10
yeah yeah 10 here
hello i'm back i don't know
wow
how much did you bet
one i only have one oh i bet 10 on
number one oh look now there's an actual
row here now nice yeah yeah wow they're
doing it so properly
nice they're in line so cool
yeah with so many members
in charge of like the line uh
you know in like conventions they always
like uh dude have that sign like this is
the last point of queue and then
whenever someone behinds them behind
them like queues they you know yeah we
transfer the sign
i wish we could have that i thought the
like they're standing on the side now
somebody says i caught in line did i
though because like i was i thought i
was standing in a line in the middle
here and then suddenly i was in the
front so i was like okay
i think
the line is so long
it's so long it's gonna take ages maybe
i should just stand in line for fun
i know me too
no no no don't make it longer than it is
i guess
no it's just time to discourage others
from betting so not so less people for
number one maybe we can play something
while we're waiting
oh true true true true a fishing game
you can't fish right you're good at
fishing
oh yes um push the button to start the
game was to say aim to get pushing
there's hoppers in the water
i gotta try it out oh
i guess you're gonna try to i don't know
how it works though
where's the center item
the center item hopper what's the button
to start the game there's a cat in there
what trying to get the fish someone
rescued the cat
wait
[Music]
what exactly
fish but like what
oh oh i get it
it's so hard really i don't even know
what i'm doing
the center hopper do you mean this one
or that one
cat no
oh i want to help the cat oh
can i can i put the cat in the house
wait i thought the music was for you
but no there's nothing in the chest at
least yeah there's nothing in the chest
okay
oops okay
i'll try
i don't know how this works wait i
forgot how to okay there we go no no
what are you supposed to aim at
uh like
like you move the items to the hopper
how do i i'm not oh i moved something i
guess i'm not a good fisher you know i
don't have much fishing experience
i feel like things that move
i feel like i did something oh
i got an iron
i got something yeah
okay
who
what is this slot
slots oh yeah that looks that looks
dangerous it's a crude
whoa no money oh my god
you can
lend money
get three gold blogs to get a prize cute
cute uh throw golden glass
no i got this i got three gold ingots
from choco sensei oh
i didn't bring any gold i brought
emeralds oh man
what's this ah a ghost place
should we go for the uh can we don't
know if they're busy do they need like
an an employee for the announcer will be
made when it reopens oh yeah right they
didn't say it's closed
can't
yeah okay okay okay
what about this thing
yeah shoot the chickens uh oh but shoot
the chicken yeah should as many chicken
before the chicken floats lava take bow
and arrow and barrel stand behind the
button press the emerald button start
shooting game as if you hear belle
please return bow and arrow put your
high score in the tube what's the side
of the game okay want to try how many i
i can take just a stack of arrows i
guess
oh man give back the rest take
behind the button okay so here
press the emerald button start shooting
game ends if you hear a bell right click
all right
oh they come down pretty slow oh
i didn't get that one though more please
are there out of chickens
only one came down
did you think this chance was like
really low because like they hatched the
egg and then sometimes it becomes the
chicken sometimes it doesn't right
at least i didn't shoot it let me try
one more time
oh there you go that's
more right
and let me try let me try
put your high score on two i don't know
i don't even know if i hit that one
correctly
if if that was hit i think you will get
um
if you miss it ends automatically ah
oh
it keeps going if you actually get
everything
go get em
no
one more come on
try again one more
yeah the younglings not the younglings
oh
whoa
you got
ah but you i think you missed one of
them
uh that's right that's right and then
the last one i saw you hitting that one
so three
no i didn't i only shot once much
that's one
oh nice
oh let's go
more chickens please yeah i hit both of
them i swear
yeah you hit two you hit two something's
a bit broken here
oh
what
hello
huh
oh my god come on i like the idea of
this but it um
the chance of the
hatching is really low i guess
what
that's rigged i hit all of them but
there was only one ah
[Music]
what's on the scoreboard no one yet
high school well i'll write down two
i
[Music]
missed made this one i wonder
the this chicken one it's ollie
i are you all right oh yeah two
chihuahua
but it was it was
two out
it's
how are you supposed to like hit him
when they're like
don't get salty nina don't get salty
it's my middle name
yeah
yeah oh i missed that one but i got the
last one hmm
two out of five just two
all right two two good stuff good stuff
okay wait where is it
huh i forgot okay
okay
now okay i'll return it i'll return it
later
two out of three
i need to save
how does that work that's fascinating
though
fascinating there you go
damn
nice nice nice day okay what next go
next
okay go next what is this library by the
way
write your memories all
that's sweet oh i didn't make so many
memories yeah maybe at the end of the
day
whoa
why
[Music]
that is so smart
that's isn't that a tree that's
something yeah yeah mangrove vlog
that's so cute i love that oh there's
like names
happy potato
oh okay crazy kebab oh you can get all
the sushi
you needed food get it go get it
funky
hello
please press the button oh okay we can
order it looks like what should i order
what should i order
what should i order and your favorite
my favorite but there's no quinoa kebab
i would go for the subaru then
um okay okay okay
oh
i thought it was going to be free i
think it's free
oh i got it i got it
you want to see you want to see the
kebab yeah
yummy
thank you but i'll give it back to you
because i have already i got another
different one yeah okay
you have to eat lena
yeah
emma wrote oh i do have hammer rounds
i can play this one
i have i'll give you one two which one
this is yours that you were supposed to
win from uh
and i have 64 more
button push gotcha emma wrote one play
where do i put them okie mochi ah you
don't even have to put them in
but i will what was that what did i get
something is this this one oh
cool
let's go i will i want more okay one two
cool okay two emma worlds i owe it two
emeralds one more
oh
taco cute you got two dinner you go too
where do i put in my diamond and my
emerald where do i put in my emerald
you don't actually have to but
okay
oh
what did i get
invisibility potion i got that one too
okay i only have one so why don't you
put the throw in the hopper
ah
that's a dropper
and it's full um
that's what you can get here i guess
i want to keep on the right on the rail
on the right on the rail rail oh this
one yeah the hopper is the hopper
ah
there we go
yeah it goes and i just put it in there
okay i got free but i want to do more
wait
wait wait i'll give a six so i'll do
three more
i'll show you okay
one
oh i can't pick it up
there you go enough fire resistance
[Applause]
i don't need that
hatred
go go away tree sapling no fauna
saplings more fire resistance
yeah
and one more
oh wait ah
[Music]
secret is living things
oh really oh yeah i got i got one living
thing i got a tadpole
what
weird
oh i think i got everything that i
needed
nice
we still have some time
[Music]
oh oh okay okay oh she accidentally set
it off i think
when do we go next
where'd he go where do you wanna go
oh
look at this what is this
is this where those sounds are coming
from
oh that's 45
yeah oh my gosh i think this is like
what piccolo's empire made right i could
be wrong what look this the mask the
math shop is like here oh
you wanna eat unit
oh you have to ah that's how you oh
i see
hello my mouse wait
oh i see amen callie and gouda
um
what'd you do um
i accidentally somebody
did it but i got matsuri senpai masks oh
how do you take it one person would
drive festival only
[Music]
no i don't think so
just just right uh
like in the minecraft chat
yeah how should i ask um
okay okay close eyes
oh this is a game you can play with two
people elena
oh yes yes oh
someone guides you to the melon and you
might die
from the lava yeah this is the
let's see
oh but i have two so many items where do
i put them
kiara do you want to try one yes i want
a match
i want but how do you have to have to
pay
no i think it's free but only you get
you get only one try
i technically didn't try but i got
somebody else's mask so
uh
where do i push
that
thingy there
yeah
okay like they're doing it right now
anya got something
[Music]
oh my god
i wanna try i wanna i wanna try pulling
because technically this is not oh my
god i'm full okay
well uh
i know your date is now a focused empire
[Music]
oh my god
oh my gosh and then you're wearing the
sports uniform so technically you take
off like your cape and shield
i am her maybe the fujiki senpai i
talked to like i looked at in minecraft
maybe that wasn't even publicly senpai
imposter
moguls
what
okay
okay let me see if i
who did she get i wanna play this but
where's space to put my [\h__\h] maybe here
okay oh no
okay i'm gonna put on my mask
yeah everybody's head is there well what
are the odds how the [\h__\h] did you get me
did you cheat
did you ask so did you did you exchange
oh my gosh
[Music]
[Applause]
because you didn't say anything i
thought
i thought that was you
oh crony
[Laughter]
[Music]
never mind later
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
more this one is what do you call that
god fox
how about that god fox yeah the fox god
yeah
they're cute
i'm ready
way way
maybe i can find focus senpai
surprises senpai
is there for rookie 75 with eop mask
oh
[Music]
she talks in the eof language now
there's pagie
is that what she always says
again oh my god
that's in five minutes
hello
i want to talk with her about tunic but
i don't know how to start the
conversation
yeah monster senpai is flying with
luna's infamous right now oh
oh she took off her head
oh wow you guys are twins now
twinning
was so naughty
oh okay
oh man i wish i didn't take out my
sports festival outfit
no fox
[Music]
i said i said something
i'm so proud okay back to elena elena
one and only just plain just ready
it's test round right
yeah
oh
it wasn't bad
it's going pretty fast
come on
but usually i think usually it's like
the result is always different you know
like somebody who goes like super fast
at like the practice you know yeah yeah
so far it has been kind of different um
indeed
okay
let's see
[Music]
go
go go power reindeer
i'm counting on you
oh commentary has come back now
oh yeah
yeah yeah commentator
kiwawa
i think we'll see in a moment
yeah we will see
oh i guess fawn also bet on vatami
senpai
oh
yago mm-hmm
interviewing currently i guess
number two miku senpai
money
no pgm yeah i don't have any pgm on i am
the bgm
oh
oh god we have no idea senpai
yes
who's writing a
[Music]
ah you didn't even do that on purpose
did you
i'm lucky
yes
wait did somebody get fake suicide head
i didn't see anybody
[Music]
that was number five and this time we
have one more number six
number six is uh
ah she lost her old minecraft account ah
that was the only other name available
aha oh i see
ah
[Music]
this is i stole her face this is a water
gun oh no she has to use another
person's face now
number one water isn't fine
will she really become number one
or
what will happen
this is the last round
the final round that will decide who the
best horse is oh oh number four they
have the owner wrong but i'm um because
she's last because she's
announcing pie
two rounds no armor no swords wait is
she talking about oh they're doing
something else somewhere else right
i'm gonna give her
chicken
[Music]
god and god
wow oh nice this is a really
special interaction
the gods are friendly with one another
because she's lucky
what else i can give her who's the real
one
man if only i'm wearing my sports
festival
yeah maybe you shouldn't have changed
after all
[Music]
oh
cute
cute yeah
i'm gonna
zombie
the gods are watching above us
we are so
do lucky like game of thrones
no i haven't watched it i'm sorry how do
you like it
okay just saying because after this is
done i'm gonna watch the new episode of
the spin off because
like this night the new episode came out
so yeah you've been talking about it a
lot so i was like huh she likes it
really yeah she really likes it huh no i
don't know yet to be honest the first
episode um came out last week and it was
very
violent like
pretty bad
no not violent but there was so much
blood that it was like too much to be
honest but that's just game of thrones
style
yeah
oh
no anya is killed where were you when
anya was killed
where were you on your skill where are
you when i'm starting soon
japanese members probably don't
understand at all
it's called that they got the horse
tickets no okay we'll see this is
one huh
what's going on
[Music]
she wants everybody who bought a ticket
to write down how many you got
there's no
there is no there's no actual text
channel though
yeah there is there's the horse ticket
no kai kata
can you write for me because i don't see
it
oh it's in the micro holo derby
you're not in it oh i didn't join that
one can you write for me
sarah is what uh
number one ten tickets
thank you
what's up there oh they're so excited
what are they doing are they wrestling
i want to check out what they're doing
later
dunk
wait guys how do you
ride a pig
um you have to like put the saddle oh my
god put the saddle and then but you have
to
be holding uh the carrot on a fishing
rod
it's an item you combine the fishing rod
with the carrot oh that's uh only then
you will be able to drive with it yeah i
didn't know you could put a saddle on a
pig
yeah i used to do that a lot
first time i saw that back then
yeah it's it's really funny but not very
fast
oh my god
come on
i ain't got all day
crony come picky
yeah yeah perfect cronie
cronichi
what yeah where is cronie
come on come on horsey what you waiting
for
oh flair senpai is kind of the senpai
so confusing
i can't even like look at their head
anymore
also look at this
[Music]
bae looks like she's an image that got
censored mozart
where where is she
just like because there's so much going
on in her outfit that when turned into a
pixel art like that
like she's censored
too spicy for minecraft
[Music]
everybody's like betting like um
50 like my god you guys are saying
and here i'm like
[Laughter]
well you know in the end it's just a
game it's just a game
if you want to gamble more then you can
do it on the rest
yo
you tried right
yeah i tried like twice how did it go
it went well it went well but it was
like the lowest thing oh
yeah
but at least you know the server like i
remember like last year it was a little
bit laggy
but yeah
today seems to be
totally bad time when i first logged in
i was like should i turn on my shaders
apparently no
um oh you got your shaders on
fancy
it was more like but i think they
improved the server
didn't they do something
i feel like they think they did
something
no before i think like they expanded it
my keyboard died i feel like i feel like
problems with like you my usb hub
oh
yeah where when you when laying aboard
was dead he's dead
i'm such a meme lord well funny
well okay it's connected
it's my usb hub it's not really my
keyboard is there anything happening to
myself specifically indonesian memes
oh there's a lot
tell me indonesian memes
oh indonesian memes
well guys what are some good indonesian
memes um usually there's a there's a
really annoying meme when when i talk
when i talk in
i don't know where i forgot where the
meme came from i think it's from like a
person for example like they're they're
asking for direction in like another
language that's not english but then the
person
uh responded to them like
it means like i can't speak english
it's like a meme but then like people
started using it in chat and i'm
speaking english and i'm like shut up
yeah these days
uh these days you are yeah it's it's
mostly like taken from like tv or like
some you know something like that so
it's like really not very contextual
um
more okay chat
uh apologia i don't know i'm not very
like what was that how about you guys
how about you guys
i don't know you you tell me of um
memes from
memes from where you are
austrian memes uh
specifically german ones i only
is german i can i can pick up one right
now and i'm really um questioning myself
why that is the only one i can think of
um
it's like um
you walk into a room
where there is um
[Music]
uh
wait what was the word
[Music]
oh yeah uh like a lot of
straw
and you're like oh oh why is there you
know what the horses eat or what they
lie on
straw and they're like oh what why is
there so much straw in here um yeah but
that's um but that's done
[Laughter]
yeah my the few german speaking people
in my chat are like no
no no no what what
um
um no no no it's not it's not it's not
children safe or uh
it's not family friendly
oh it's not family friendly okay okay
okay okay
yeah and then somebody's like oh
basically the whole isen means yeah you
know like indonesian memes like internet
memes are so nonsensical so you know
eisen from bleach
like oh
yeah basically like this guy with
glasses and then like it's it's a
caption of his face and then like
it means
it's like
ah it's like a really weird play on
words
uh you know how the saying it's like you
know when you when you think of it and
then you usually like say another
statement right for example when you
think of it this is expensive or
something
but they make it so nonsensical like
when you think of it why are you
thinking about it or like the more i go
this way the more it goes that way
something like that so
and then
you know it's just like really really
nonsensical i really don't know how to
explain it to you i feel like
the recent state of like indonesian
memes is just
we laugh the more absurd it is the more
we laugh at it
i
understand everything
yeah yes
i probably would need to say it yeah
like see what you're talking about that
like i don't even know that character
from bleach
yeah i don't think it really makes a
difference
the more it goes here the more it goes
there
uncle
26 times multiplicator
if they win
jaguar five times only
oh
yeah
we're kind of like in the past modern
era of indonesian memes yeah
like nothing makes sense and exactly
because it doesn't make sense that's why
it's really popular my god
well my gahashira is 13 times
multiplicator
that was the one that
is that yours
no
yeah
oh my god
is five times multiplicator
i guess what is it what about number one
number one
[Music]
yet but the fact that 26 times is for
uncle means people don't believe in
uncle and their writers oh my god uh
wasn't it noir senpai on uncle
i think it was not just simply oh yes
it's not a senpai on uncle
she must go against all odds that should
like motivate her even more people
didn't bet on her so go go
i mean if i had more diamonds i would
have liked bet on people yeah
yes yes yes yes yes
they're definitely missing they're still
calculating one two
i think so because they were like yo if
you are betting
foreign
kill all the fakers
wow so like just for today the names we
say homono really is important yeah
hold on i've lost you know five times
oh
oh yeah it's
impossible mask
[Music]
uncle fourteen oh oh that's really low
uncle fourteen let's go oh sad
not twenty six times not twenty six oh
my gosh thirteen times thirteen times
okay okay okay okay
not bad
and
we're missing two
mighty hi five
[Music]
times mine
free
ollie why is mine so low the lowest er
i'm the og much the higher fan everybody
else go away
no well well let's see if we might have
some surprises here
yeah we have okay i bet all in from
majde hayes just so you guys know
um
i bet 10 on number one
uncle muscle power
master remastered
[Music]
yeah i bet all in i bet all information
one diamond
because
technically it's all in right yeah
you're all diamonds i have left you're
all in doesn't mean very much
hey
you know like on top of your name
there's so you say homonos like i had to
take i had to make a double take oh wait
that's
awesome yeah
so we say crony
oh oh mikko is leading
so what's that by following up subaru is
kind of third
but who knows we might have some
surprises in spider webs
oh miko is taking some time toba also
last time she went there easily i think
she went for recently but miegle got a
big lead now
oh
where is my
oh no
go
[Music]
close close eh noel what
no i was doing a third round or was she
really that slow i guess she was running
was she around behind so far really
damn she's taking her sweet time
when was her horse called
that horoscope must be taken apart
afterwards
wow
so
put it in the recycler
i spice my spices
[Music]
what there was like a fewing thing oh
sorry excuse me excuse me oh well
i think this this is also for viewing
everything's revealing it's okay
looking
[Music]
my life has changed
we can go play now right now until the
fireworks
yes
let's go play
oh who's distributing what oh those are
just two tickets
let's go play elena i can't even look at
these people's heads anymore i need to
i want to play the lava thingy elena
come here yeah let's do it let's do it
let's do it
oh mikko senpai gets the horse oh
nice what oh
the first person the first gets the
horse around yeah
oh i hope they will
have a a beautiful time together
beautiful life mm-hmm cherish
the color of the horses where are you
so cute
[Music]
i'm behind the stand behind uh by the
beds
do you care to join me
what are you which beds
um
right behind the watching stand like
there's a newly built uh watching family
oh there you go
[Music]
let's go
let's go i think it was somewhere over
there
[Music]
i think you can just use that one
yeah i guess so i have like seven arrows
but i'm just gonna use five oh sure are
you supposed to stand on the
on the cow you're supposed to sit here
but what is the cow there yeah
cow go away no cow
i don't think it's oh no no no no i
think like you hit the you hit the this
instead you hit the the cart instead
okay let me read the rules again no
actually fireworks is soon do you want
to wait for fireworks first
i think i can squeeze in one game but it
says here you have to be on the on the
top
right on the mic on top of the gonna be
on top of the cow
i don't think so come on come on come on
come on i think you have to like
ride it
is it okay if we kill it
i'll kill the minecart
oh yeah yeah it's true
you will be free kyle
sorry sorry sorry i'm really bad at
doing stuff like that uh uh wait i have
my inventory so full
uh
yeah okay
uh um i get it for you no i got it i got
it
oh you mean the meat
oyster
okay five shots
that's the phantom you say you keep
hearing a phantom there's a phantom in
the mine car oh there it's like how do
you shoot them
it's in the cart
i have no
cows in the way
[Music]
gonna get dizzy with this
oh i got the sheep i mean i got the card
off the sheep
[Music]
oh wait i wasn't using my five shots i
was using like an endless uh oops and i
don't know how how often i even shot but
oh well um i think i broke the game
so we must say
something mustang i broke the game
because i shot the cart instead of the
sheep
uh what do you call this place
[Music]
shooting game
koashi mashita
[Music]
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry i'm sorry
sorry sorry
let's uh watch fire work together
yes
[Music]
where
ah i think there's a
you could go up to the carousel to watch
that ah do you want to go up you want to
hear yeah sure sure sure doesn't even
have to be the very top but let's see
what's up at the top
uh-huh
oh it's a bit dangerous here though
there's no like rails oh wait wait where
are you
on top of the
oh
[Music]
where is the fireworks gonna be
uh we will see it
i think um that stage is where the
fireworks go off maybe
which stage
uh if you look to the right
the white blue thing
huh
the cool stage with all the of the
middle stage
and the seating
oh there ah
there's actual seating there maybe we
should be there
yeah maybe
okay
although this was a good view too
oh yeah they're all they're all going
there now so i think that's where it is
i see like the things where they're
probably going to get out of yeah
okay
where do you want to watch
yeah
next to you
next
[Music]
so here
fireflower
fireflower is fireworks right i guess so
okay
yes
we are at the stage in my already do you
want to like go at the back so you can
like look up better or the first um
there are so many people there why not
be a lonely thing
okay okay
let's let's let's let's at the corner at
cozy cozy corner
cozy corner exactly
oh yeah
that's the kanji yes
the kansas turned into fire flower funny
yes
[Music]
gather in front of the stage wait so
like here like in front in front
that's what the seating is for
ah in france like what's in front of
like he
isn't that dangerous just being up there
that's where the fire flowers will go
off
eh
two minutes
wait so on top or what um
oh my god
control yourself
don't die with the elytra
huh
so where on top how do i get off the
stage
um there's uh
some stairs in the front of it
awesome stairs really
i am seated correctly
you are but why why are they telling us
to go upstairs
you're confused
believe they believe in your
correctness we should believe in your
correctness okay
we have to set an example you know
oh so there's people behind us too so
yeah so maybe it is behind
they said in front but maybe this this
is in front yeah
yeah i think so oh now they're taking
seats properly
bay
is is bail
a space sword no is that
wait that face i'm taking pictures right
now it's gonna be so weird because
we're just
fine
just trying to see who all those heads
are
oh
oh no so senpai is wearing coyote's head
and it fits her her clothes really well
because they're pink
i'm just looking for if somebody got my
head but apparently not
also ahead
of your hand oh my god
oh my god
that's a lot of fireworks
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
slower i feel like this
fly is it
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
i have a firework now
this is gonna go for two minutes
maybe incredible
i'm not the only one flying around
anymore
wow
dangerous dangerous
[Music]
[Applause]
it hurts
[Music]
i want to check from the top from the
top of where we were supposed to be
[Music]
a lot of people are on the carousel food
yeah
i'm just gonna take like a lot of you
know
[Music]
oh
yes
okay we got it
oh
i think it's calming down
yeah
oh thank god
it gave me [\h__\h] anxiety
i think it's longer than two minutes
[Applause]
what
it looks so pretty from the stage
yeah
oh god i'm feeling sick
what are these weird sounds
[Music]
they have turkey stuck under the stage
sounds really weird what is it or
pigeons kitchens
shulkers
oh
that's it oh it's done
[Applause]
let me party party amazing
how much gun powder was wasted today
[Music]
10 out of 10.
[Laughter]
are you going to eat it are you going to
eat the fireworks yummy
the stage is so good
for my eyes
they did a great job building all of
this damn
nice
yeah gunpowder well spent although i'm
really i'm really lacking gunpowder in
minecraft i wish they would give me some
you should start killing the creepers
then ah nah [\h__\h] creepers
let's play yes let's play that one
oh my gosh the car was back there
hey
but they didn't nobody fixed the other
thing i think yeah yeah
i want to play this
but yeah but how
i have so much i got something
let me find the chest
oh melon attack game player close eyes
navigator guide to melon ah
[Music]
i found chests but they're for building
oh but here's your lives this chest
literally in front of the thing um i
don't know if um no no but there's um
isn't there like a lot of axes in there
i found some chests where there's some
space
for stuff
there's also an ender chest
through this year you'll have free time
oh yay
nicer
oh my god
okay let me put my
my important things
[Laughter]
in here
festival only using okay
don't need sticks
i'm gonna take off my
mask because it's a little it's getting
a little bit suffocating
mask oh
yeah
finally
some fresh air that don't need that
okay
and what about the horror game oh yeah
yeah
oh but you want to try the melon first
right yeah let's just do that one first
because now they're already lining up
for that
for the [\h__\h] house
okay i'm gonna put my stuff away we can
do once uh you lead me and once i lead
you
okay
the lava is really hot
axis in chest
oh
what is the ax for
oh here we go
is there anything to fight i thought
you'd just walk through no you you you
the watermelon attack the watermelon oh
okay okay
oh it's okay i put everything away i'm
coming
oh except okay
[Music]
wait i thought it was an empty chest
what is is there no um
chest where you can put your stuff i
didn't see one over there
hmm they must have forgotten oh the
navigator is up here oh ah
okay supposed to be up here okay no
one's doing it right now so i'm gonna go
okay
i close eyes you tell me where to go
okay uh if you go straight three steps
how far do you go
uh one two three
okay um take one step take two steps one
two
oh
now turn left
here
and take one step one
turn left again
take one step one
okay take three steps one two three
oh that was maybe too short three more
steps one two three
okay turn slightly right take two steps
slightly here
one two
go turn slightly left again and two
steps
one one two
and then take two more steps
one two
one more step i think one
okay one more one more i feel it's hot
around me
one more sorry
oh why do you keep like making it
shorter one more time i don't know i'm
scared but no i'm not scared
as long as you're leading me more
yeah one just one
okay turn right
more
try walking one step
yeah
okay take three steps
[Music]
oh my god okay slightly left left left
not slightly just very left
very left
here very left yes
later later uh more more more left more
oh yeah and then take one step one
one more step please
okay
um
and then turn right
right
uh more please no more
um
too much too much slightly to the left
okay
and then try one step one
[Music]
um okay so go slightly to the left
and then one step
okay uh one more step one more tiny step
same direction
okay turn slightly right slightly and
then take one step please
hi
yes and then two more steps please one
two
okay uh take one more step the same
direction one
okay and then turn right
i thought you know your voice it makes
me
ah it's so sweet it makes me feel so
safe
okay then you better be safe um slightly
more right please
okay and then um go straight one step um
okay uh turn slightly right just
slightly
slightly to the right yeah up
and then okay try two steps one
two
okay
slightly to the left again
[Music]
just one step try one step
okay uh three steps
one
two two three this reminds me of two
knees okay turn slightly round left and
then hit
slightly left here
yeah and hit was hitting left or right
mouse button
left left
really alright
why okay maybe turn a little bit to the
left again and then hit it you're right
in front of the melon the left here
really and then okay left maybe aim
lower maybe or i don't really know
wait can i see if i have the axe
selected just just one peak yeah yeah
selected i have
did it look
yeah it's working it's glowing but you
have to destroy it or what not sure
can i look
okay there we go oh you have to hit
longer
oh but
ah and then you place a new one there
[Music]
nice thank you
that was quite that was actually
relaxing kind of
really relaxing yeah guiding you to
watermelon in a lava surrounded area
how do you put it on top of that though
water uh press shift maybe
no it opens the chest i guess i have to
like put one here first and then
but then
i don't know i don't know i don't know
hold shift it
yeah you hold shift while you put it
but now if i destroy it i'll just get
another like pack of melons right
oh really
wait uh okay hold shift
crouch hold shift
yeah no no so it's like you get the
watermelon and it's kind of like the
same thing maybe as if you want to put a
sign on top of a chest
so in order so you don't open the chest
you press shift while you put it
let me let me let me try i'm too stupid
nina i'll just do it like oh i can't do
it
oh god oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh
yes that's how you do it so you crouch
if you crouch while putting it like it
won't make you open the chest oh i think
cronie is standing there ready to do the
do it once yeah and she can go first
it's okay
[Music]
yeah
riveting
but it was actually kind of relaxing for
me to be honest
really yeah just closing my eyes and
letting it happen ah actually not that
bad and the bloop
bloop sounds from the lava they're also
relaxing like as actually it sounded
like as if i'm in the middle of a
jacuzzi a world ah i hope you think
about it that way
you know hot water right yeah
yeah
just a bit more extra hot for the
phoenix
my stuff
my bucket
my my happiness bucket
and
[Music]
a
fireworks a big potato
this i bring back
i wonder if the other game was fixed too
i'm sorry i broke it
um yeah it should be
[Music]
oh you put your mask back on yeah
who was the the first
um whole life member whose stream you
watched
me
i forgot who the first is it's
definitely like somebody
but um
oh there's a cow
somebody no i wait it has to it has to
be like from a clip i think like a
memorable thing actually is about like
matsuri senpai it was a clip about her
like the band-aid one where she put her
band-aid over her
ah
do you think that's the first one you
saw
yeah oh the air
by me
or
this piece
yeah it's music it's you whoa
[Music]
i have two painting partners now
from black hair to white hair
yes i feel like in um
maybe you should stand in line to assert
dominance
okay wait how how do i put my stuff
though do you want to hold my stuff if
you go i don't i don't know if i have
enough space but if you go all the way
over there straight
there's some some chests of like
building materials i put my stuff in
there
i already took it back though
oh ender chest i haven't under my under
chest is full
why do i have heads why do i have miko
stamped my head in front of sarah's head
in my head
[Music]
no
she's burning again
okay
don't die don't die don't die if you die
don't don't die here
hmm
what stuff is this
it
where
in the chest than i told you no in my
inventory
i'm i think like i'm i'm holding some
stuff that are not mine like this fauna
head don't worry about it if it's just
the heads then don't worry about it if
they want a new one they can just go get
one again right
it's true
no worries
okay i'll put the head in the ender
chest though because
it would be sad if i lose them
oh my god
this is really cool i like the idea of
this
damn who built this one do we know
i don't know i don't think so does chad
know
this chat no it might only be one of
each chat really
hmm i can put mine back but i don't know
where don't forget the elijah oh shoot
you're right
the elytra i just put it in here
i become kiwawa
like this
maybe
it has been the life in the under chest
and swap it with something else
okay i have a torch but i don't really
mind it is fine
come on come on
there's like
cronie is still playing very slowly
trying slowly all right then we're
really fast i feel like we did it pretty
fast
hmm
but there you know cronie and mummy are
on a date with like three girls from the
sixth gen
so they're communicating probably in
very broken english and broken japanese
right now
wow taking three girls
so spicy
ella
who's guiding her
a lot of people being like
it's mumei because she's the one looking
down and robokan is not part of the
group i think so
okay then yeah i think that's woman then
they shouldn't have problems
communicating wait no double sign is in
their voice chat now
oh all right
but maybe like only one person is
guiding because if there's multiple
people guiding it's very
um you can't have multiple people
guiding it's supposed to be a game where
you test the bond of two people not
three or four or five
exactly oh i'll take the axe
yeah
maybe
we can do two at once
what if somebody accidentally pushes
someone though yeah then you just wait
behind them like oh just wait a little
bit for five minutes later cronie needs
some time
you can try
you wanna
yay
i don't know trust me okay go
no no wait i don't i don't i don't want
to accidentally
because we're kill
fast right she's almost there though
almost yeah she's almost there wait i'll
be right back okay
it's harder with more people guiding
really are they doing that is that what
they're doing
there's like four people up here
no
god by the crony
time is ticking but take your time
because your time
your time is your time
time is time is no problem for you
this is time
just just joking
not very funny
okay wait i'm kind of curious where
crony how corny is doing actually
she's so slow and now she's facing the
[\h__\h] lava
to the right to the right
come on should we confuse them even
further by helping them
be like the fifth sixth person to guide
her joining in the voice chat
right crony go live
[Laughter]
wait let me let me show that
kiara kara yeah
what if i were to um sneak up behind you
and slowly push yourself
left left left strength
[Laughter]
[Music]
what did you say what you know
eh i i just said left left straight but
i don't know
what happened with iroha
what happened to vito has she burned to
death
was it my
fault
i hope not
not sorry i don't think so
i don't think it was yeah i don't know
where she was
she burnt her stuff geez what
come on cronie you just have to go fuel
me this is dragged oh my god crow is so
close though she's been there for like
10 minutes
come on
[Music]
come on come on
yeah straight straight
straight up
yeah yeah go straight yeah go straight
straight straight's fine she's back on
track
she's back on track though yeah
why is she looking out there yeah she's
always looking in the wrong direction
it was i also always looking like
sideways with my head no
no i think i pretty much told you to
like turn so that if you turn then
you'll be turning your head right right
her head is stuck
like me when i this is what this is how
people feel i think when uh when we do
like mario kart tournaments like they
can only watch so they're like oh my god
cronie has trust trust issues
i think she has trust issues with like
her um
her girlfriends
oh
oh oh but she's she's closer though
maybe they're like just leading her in a
less conventional way yeah definitely
chat is saying that we were really good
at it
yes let's see how it will be the other
way around though it could be different
well it just means like if you're doing
well it just means that i am a very good
guide right
yeah are you are you are you as good of
a god as i am
i can be a
i can be a different kind of guide
sure
[Music]
it's an idol song from
my my favorite idol group
you probably expected something else but
i'm just nerding out
ah she's there
yeah
okay
hit it
you're doing it
maybe she needs to like walk further or
maybe ah yeah and look longer
mind watermelon
watermelon
[Music]
oh my god okay i'm gonna i'm gonna go
down so i can
apply some pressure
oh my gosh she's literally in front of
it
yeah it was kind of like when i was
doing it
like when you were doing it let me i
wanna like what are they doing
[Laughter]
i'm back
who would you would say
i don't know it was mumei guiding her so
i'm wondering like where's the problem
they're speaking english also they broke
with sand block
what the heck
oh my god okay we just start okay we
just start
she's already there like i i think it'll
be yeah she's literally already there
okay let's let's let's start okay close
your eyes close my eyes yeah
um
[Music]
right now yeah so
that's not like baby steps okay
one um three steps straight
how far is this very good another three
step straight
i'm gonna do a speed run
turn left
is this enough
oh only your head moves interesting
yeah um do one tiny step
okay
a little bit more left
yeah one more tiny step
uh-huh uh a little more left
a little more left
yeah tiny step
i'll be careful uh louis is passing by
okay no problem that's crony passing by
we'll just wait wait uh okay okay go
crony go run it okay okay um a tiny tiny
bit left
this yeah and straight
straight
another one
one straight yeah
okay one more
one more
a little bit more left
right yeah straight one okay two uh-huh
uh
yeah three one more
one more a little bit more left
a little bit more left here yeah and
straight
one
two
two three
three four
four beautiful five
five six
six seven
seven eight
eight nine
nine
oh one more
okay i turned right
how much oh quite a bit a nice nice uh
was 90 degrees 16 90.
just turn around no a bit more
a bit more
okay make a step
one tiny step
here okay a bit more right
okay
um a bit more
and one baby baby step
bubble bubble step more right
all right another baby step
oh more more right i guess
okay oh another baby's dead
yes okay
[Music]
more right more more more more more more
more okay step baby
yes yeah okay that's good um one more
step
one more step one more step
one one more step
okay and
90 degrees left
just a good is that about the left yeah
yeah
enough yeah and then well one step
another one
and a good amount of right please to the
right
this yeah and then a step
uh-huh amazing
step please
step yes one more
one more yeah another one
okay always so fast like what the hell
were they doing before another one
another one
another one yeah
okay more step more step two more two
more
one two
one more
one more one more
one more and then to the right side
to the right side how much quite a bit
more put it more yeah well yes a bit
more
a bit more beautiful
please step ahead about one two step
a little bit more right
a little right
more more more more more yeah yeah uh
step one baby step baby step baby step
yeah yeah a bit more to the right
uh-huh
okay baby step
uh-huh uh now
a baby step
baby step
okay uh one step
one step
two steps
three steps
cute
four steps
yeah uh three more steps
beautiful turn left
left
a bit more a bit more a bit more and
um step big step
yeah now hit it
uh do i need to aim lower or no i think
you're good but just uh hit stronger
like longer
yeah you did it
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah do you know how to place it oh i
think so
here we go
wow we need some time and chat you have
to time how long my try took then how
long crony stride took and how long
might uh let's go
yeah i want to see the times oh she's
doing one of matsuya's empire i think
nice
nice winner we were so good at this oh
you're really you're you're a really
good guy i acknowledged it and really it
yeah it does actually sound pretty
relaxing
and then like the guy like turned left
it's actually relaxing yeah i got it i
get it
[Music]
okay let's play another
what do game
what do you want to play what what
speaks to you
what speaks to me um
aside from the face oh look that's so
cute yeah
a great one it's kind of like the
takoyaki stand oh
it's always so nice to see how like they
come up with these creative solutions i
love it
yeah and they're i'm gonna take your
eyes oh yeah we're gonna take oh do you
wanna go to the horror house oh yes
let's go
yay
oh
they did say something in the chat that
like when it's um open again uh like
when there's space again they let us
know
oh [\h__\h] okay open open
i can hurry
people
yeah
do i do i go to the is there is there a
chat room for a whorehouse uh
they're vc from harlem
[Laughter]
because um yes matsu okay futari
highland moscow
can we enter it with two people does it
have to be
lalo
solo
man they're gonna have a long shift
today i think the horror house is
relatively long
so
damn oh cute cute
i watched real luna i watched luna's
empire playing
rust a little bit the other day oh
really yeah
very cute destiny
very cute
looking at subaru senpai doing her thing
oh are we like registered i wonder can
we go
watch wait um i'm gonna take all my
stuff
oh yeah you don't you didn't take it
back
was it did you
oh no not yet okay
okay
whorehouse is always popular
yeah i think um
[Music]
squishy wait please
yes
squishy away please oh my gosh i'm so
close to like holding
i'm so close to like holding h to like
put all the stuff in the inventory is
there like um oh oh yeah this is like a
minecraft equivalent of that ah [\h__\h]
right i have no gold
[\h__\h] i need gold
oh yeah i have gold one four what four i
wanna play the slot missing
oh sure sure sure sure hold on excuses
my diamonds oh i put them in the ender
chest i think
is this broken though is it supposed to
be like this like
is this normal
is this just what the last person ended
up with i guess
what is up
they're giving out like uh tickets with
like numbers to
like say it again
so you know when's your turn
okay
um we're supposed to get one too
i might take a while
[Music]
really i think so
it
should be daijoubu
i got number 10. i think that counts for
both of us
um
okay i wanna play slot machine
[Music]
give me
wow
[Music]
okay i like the sound it's so
loud so dramatic
so industrial oh
come on come on
no i can gamble more oh you got a
diamond out of oh diamond
oh my god i could have used that for
horse bedding
only one
two i got two oh can i can i do one one
cilantro
here
thank you
hi
nice
oh no
i already
lost later
no
i'll have your gambling luck
ah
i feel like there is like so many more
like games and they're also so
professional compared to last year
it's so cool right the stall that they
came up with damn they all got so much
better at minecraft
respect what is this one you know i feel
like even if the festival is over you
can still play
is this one look at that review what's
this it's like entrance ah safe locker
what's this
free play
is it like a [\h__\h] house but it looks
happier
um what is this
we shall try maybe a trap house or
something oh dear okay cause it says
like a safe locker it says
yeah
please put your stuff after please go in
after you have the you know
put your stuff away yeah i'm putting it
in now does it have space for all of our
stuff
i don't think so
okay i'll go in fast
oh oh oh what i'll be fast
okay you'll be fast okay okay okay
i'll be speed
whatever it is that waits in there i'll
be fast
all right i still have
hot wings and my shield there we go
i shouldn't have brought so much stuff
but i was stressed out okay ecozo how to
open oh i forgot to return the axe
okay you can do that
what do we have please touch
okay please touch
portion
oh if you go in you can't go out okay
wow
so
reassuring what so safe
oh was that supposed to bounce
ah
because i
i need to show i don't think i'm
supposed to be here
[Music]
i glitched under the base of this thing
that they built here i think i have to
drown myself because i don't know how to
get out
okay okay killing myself right now
okay that was weird
no problem for phoenix
dying once dying twice styling dying a
million times no problem dying in style
um
phoenix
die now by water oh fire in the water
water in the fire
yay
kiana's round let's go
mama
what the hell was the problem what did i
do wrong i messed up
yara halloween
you know the the the like beside the
takoyaki stall they have a ringworm
stand it's so cute oh
who built this thing i want to um
write an an inquiry
and the scaffolding leads up to nothing
because it's blocked i have to destroy
something oh
[Music]
i want something's free
oh my
my
i'm stuck at the jumping position
because my keyboard is dead i'm almost
hey
[Music]
oh my god
thank you
[Music]
hmm
something's broken
[Music]
clear i'm gonna play with pumpkin pie
yes
quantity
[Music]
yeah my keyboard got stuck yeah i think
i need to check the connection of my usb
hub it's been really annoying these days
i wasn't crouching and the first time i
went on it i was also jumping but it
didn't work i don't recommend you dana
to try this one because um you get stuck
in a place that you can't get out of
unless you break something i don't want
to break anything
oh
wait can you come out i'm i'm yeah
i'll come out by
taking my life
a third time
okay uh
i i give up i guess
i give apple i wonder what this was
yeah maybe like a trap house ah
yeah
oh oh well
okay unless you want to try do you want
to try
oh but i'm i'm afraid i'm going to break
something though
it's already broken you can't break
anything more
[Music]
do you think i look good with mikutsi
head
i
looked at your headphones that was
mikoti yes you look good
i was like why is she standing next to
me
is it she built this here
there somehow i have mikochi and fauna
head in my inventory ooh
time to play some pranks on mikochi go
go
yes i'm done though here
oh my god i thought it was real kayla
but why is
what is this what is this what is this
wait wait that's like a shooting gallery
oh oh is it like the hammer thingy the
hammer you oh and then
the stronger you hit the or i guess it's
like but there's no hammer function so
you shoot yeah
yeah i guess so i tried
what
it's a bit higher
oh
what did i get what did i get do i get
something from that there is there is
reward i made this
oh it did give me it gave me a golden
thingy for for the slot machine i can
use it on the slime machine
more oh
that was a bit worse
i'll take the gold
demon
oh
blazing rug
okay i'm gonna i'm gonna check i'm gonna
try
it oh
nice one just wait there let's stay stay
stay stay there and then we'll give you
something
this takes a little while
did you get it
i don't know
i think you did i heard like a oh a
blaze rod yeah
[Music]
wait no wait i didn't cut
when did i get grass
my ball what did you get
i got totem of undying
what but i got the fireworks doesn't
that mean that oh is that venus firework
yeah it was mine i think
i was like i was in the max green we
shot like at the same time i was so
confused
give me maximum i know i got it now i
got it
wait is this already free
can i really get all these
like precious things for
free i guess no
no payment i guess
[Music]
[Laughter]
no miss up is there so i had to take off
my mask
yeah miss lupe just like went oh [\h__\h] oh
someone oh a couple people in there
maybe they can figure out what's broken
well maybe
yo slot machine let's go
[Music]
someone's like it's id economy so it's
cheap
[Laughter]
oh
you must have been really lucky there
when you come yeah can i throw away the
place
well you brought me good luck i think i
sucked away all your luck
[Music]
and i still haven't even brought in the
third person right for the
wakayashi yeah i guess so i don't
know i don't think i can wait that long
at this point
soon
no i just don't feel so well to be
honest oh no we should rest yeah i also
haven't been like feeling well
especially them like the past week so
yeah i totally i think i get it
uh
um i mean if you if you want to go now
it's um it's all right um
are you i mean you want to like go
around a little bit first like probably
maybe check out the stuff check if we
missed something nice let's go yeah just
the stuff that doesn't need like um
lines yeah yeah
where are your words and oh don't forget
to write your console before you leave
so the snare
saw this new yeah
so what is in there
what is this thing
that's chocolate how is that okay
and this is just the back side of
something oh oh that one took that one
too
what's that one where kyla was fighting
oh where's that one
oh look at them chilling
they're chilling oh those are oh
nice chair solutions oh
these are that is so genius louis garden
nice too
i want to
drink i love that stuff
[Music]
you
the server
yes i think so because it's her shop
yes yes
[Music]
oh they're like please
oh
next is number three dang we're number
10.
yeah i don't i don't think it's
happening in the next one hour
or even two
like since since number two is called
it's been what 20 minutes or so it feels
like yeah i guess so
pretty long
so so popular damn
yeah
yeah but it is like amusement parks like
you know when you go to amusement park
yeah
sometimes you have to wait for like two
hours or so yeah
yeah gotta get the fastpass
fastpass please
yeah
where is my queen where is my kinoku
i'm waiting oh
[Music]
that's fun
what's that an obstacle course
am i allowed to like rob this place no
they don't know
you can taste
more like emo like potato
ah i see
oh there we go
thank you
ah you wanna try the obstacle course
thanks
thank you louie
yes of course i do
is there a chest here too there's a lot
of people trying it here
uh but also much stuff in here hmm
yep how about just not dying i mean
dying here is a
not so high chance because there's no
lava it's just lava blocks and i have a
totem of the undying which i guess i'll
waste right here
i'm gonna just like
put the important stuff
in my under chest okay okay
but even if you die it just drops there
on the floor
true i don't know
don't die no no i haven't seen anyone
die here before
i don't take too much damage
yay
okay um
how do you
okay
i didn't take any damage what the hell
what
how do i what
[Laughter]
i'm like that was pretty bad like the
stuff from the festival
i don't want to lose them so i'm gonna
put them
what is this place is so popular now
yeah
i failed whoa
why am i not taking damage
i mean now i was crouching but
do i not do i not exist here right now
you're on top of the bed right now just
like staying quiet
yeah you're here on top of the bed on on
my side
interesting
i think
uh must be some kind of
lag because i i ran through the obstacle
course two times already
and i never took damage when i fell down
cool
i'm ghost
like your body is here but your soul is
somewhere yeah yeah yeah that freaks me
out reyna i follow you
let's see i'm your i'm your angel i'll
protect you
okay oh
those all please
you don't see me right now
no i don't see you
so sad
you know i think there was like there's
definitely like some kind of tv shows
where
like you know the lover is dead and
they're watching over
yeah they're just like here
so sad see the door won't even open for
me i need someone else to open the door
for me
i'm standing behind the door
oh no
the pressure plate won't work for me
astral projection i'm dead
forever no okay i'll open for you for
you thank you there you go
okay
you can't see me but you can feel me my
my existence i guess uh my presence wow
such a supernatural experience i'm gonna
eat what if i what if i hit people wait
can you feel it when i hit you here
right
no i can't no i didn't even
register okay my dad my game is
completely dead i guess you want to try
relogging
nah it's okay
but but you have to ride you have to
ride the console and before you go home
yeah yeah yeah i will
what is this this is climbing thingy no
wario fighting ah
lima oh my god le mao 69 arena
i have no idea where she is
okay wait let me let me
let me quickly
let's see if every log fixes this
oh my god it's so hard the timing
all right what did i do
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no no no no we've already
established i'm real
yeah i just wanted to make sure
listen by scaring me she was about to
hit you know
she was about to be on an intentional
target
i'm gonna um
give back my ticket unless you want to
keep it and go later
oh
[Music]
right
i wanna know
i also don't know
um or do you want to give me the ticket
yeah that's what i mean like if you want
to sell stuff yeah and then i guess if i
end up not going then i'll return the
ticket to them okay
[Music]
oh thank you
writing thingy the message yeah yeah
yeah let's look for it let's look for it
i wonder if you can like run the
obakeowski like after this festival is
done because that's what i'm afraid of
it seems like though that they need
someone to supervise it
that's why they need them to be in voice
chat and that's why it was close during
the horse race
maybe maybe it's okay okay i don't
really i don't really like obagi anyway
scary
okay okay okay okay yes yeah where's the
console place
[Music]
i was the one with the books right
oh i don't even remember anymore
but honestly you know i think um
is is is everybody else still streaming
because i feel like i also want
stuff oh i think bay gouda amer they
left go down they just left now yeah
okay i feel like i might wanna
you know do a bucky ascii but maybe like
maybe off stream i could record oh my
god somebody's on fire
master senpai
on fire do you think we can ride the
carousel though
does that actually work
i want to try i want to try i want to
try they all have saddles so i don't
know does it work
can you mount them
oh my god oh my god
[Music]
i wish we could have like something that
two people can ride in minecraft it
would be so nice we're riding it right
now but how do we how do we safely get
off oh that's why there's water at the
bottom i think
i guess so
[Music]
look this way i wanna take a picture
okay hello
hello hello
hello i think if you uh okay you never
mind yeah i was gonna say i think if you
like uh use the
uh the the the one next to me we can
take like a good picture oh because they
right next to each other
can you get off safely
well it was i didn't die
i mean technically it's safe yeah that
was safe i'm coming
swim swim
[Music]
yeah only a boat in minecraft i think
i should make it
why i wonder
i noticed that this season this season
this year there's no such thing as like
a love tunnel i think like muna made
that ah yeah
that was nice yeah obva yes
yeah we ended up going like the six of
us last year
okay cara look this way this way
i think feeling hurt
okay i think i think i took a good i
took a pretty good picture i think i
kind of don't know
it's not safe this is what's the word
ow ow [\h__\h] hazard
oh i better
be i'm safer
[Laughter]
wait how do i come down uh shift
wow i literally didn't fall what
yeah i didn't fall i left
i'm out here i'm impressed okay guys
yeah i'm pretty pretty right
i'm gonna go down
i wanna take one last picture
the pig is down okay oh that's a whole
live logo let's i'm on the stage there's
no more firework now but maybe here we
can take a picture maybe here you can
take it okay i don't i'm not wearing the
mask anymore am i yeah i'm not wearing
the mask i don't think i'm not ready but
wait uh
let me put away
oh
okay
paper
oh shoot
okay
hold on
[Music]
i'm gonna i'm gonna crouch ah
okay
[Laughter]
yeah i took i took i took pictures okay
so beautiful
beautiful story skye
yes yeah thank you everybody for
watching cool thank you
i am
do you still want to like ride the
console are you up i can ride the
console for you you can type in okay
yeah i know i'm i'm good but i had fun
thank you for being my dates today leina
yeah thank you i had a lot of fun
they approved like so much holy [\h__\h] the
games are incredible
yeah it's so amazing
i didn't realize at all that this was
like there's so many people were
building so much stuff
yeah
it's very very very lively
someday we will go to
festival in japan together
yeah i want to
you can watch fireworks yeah
and guys i i see you soon okay and
schedule is out and
uh
secret collab partner on friday by the
way is ahmed not much of a secret just
wanted to sketch all the time
we're gonna play an fps game probably
ooh
a kiss to end the day
lovely lovely lovely
i'm gonna watch uh the second episode of
house of the dragon now and then fall
asleep and have a second breakfast
okay
i'm
are you gonna continue streaming we're
gonna like take a break for one minute
and then i'm probably gonna continue
streaming but i think i'm going soon oh
okay okay i want to ride the console for
you too yes
tell them uh
10 out of 10 on yelp by kiwawa
10 okay 10 out of 10 yelp let's go
very very
tatty moments
uh
much
love
and uh kiara is killed
four times three three times no
yeah chad you better take notes
[Laughter]
my i can't i can you know my brain is
not working correctly because the very
cute girl is right in front of my eyes
oh no what do i do
[Music]
i'm gonna do you once do you want the
the thingy uh the keychain they wanna
yeah
yeah of course i do uh i'm gonna make it
into a keychain i need to figure out how
because like i
i made the
the pixel thing the ironbeats thing
oh yeah looks exactly like you look
right now but i don't know how to make
it into a kitchen i'll figure it out and
then i'll send it to you
[Music]
my gift to you
okay i'll be looking forward to it okay
okay i wish you a lovely evening lena
beautiful look at her look at her
rocking the stage dance lady dance no
stay on stage be an idol go sing
i'll stay here i'll stay here i'll stay
here my idol
i'm gonna
whenever kiara gets offline i'm gonna
like take like a break for like one
minute and then i'm gonna come back
so if there's like a now loading screen
the stream's not ending oh okay no
yeah continue watching later
yeah
and in german we say
[Music]
thank you for watching
okay guys
ah thank you for watching
sorry you guys know i i had to get up
early because of a recording and then
now i'm hungry and tired and luck but i
think we saw what's like the important
part of the
festival
yeah
um
yeah guys
thank you for watching i hope it was
okay uh i
i
i'm glad i at least had a date
yeah
thank you
also um there's like things that certain
things that you're waiting for such as
first
uh
stream on german channel and that early
access holocure stream and the re
um
back
the comeback of phototalk are all coming
in i think the next two weeks or so i
made a little mistake with photo key or
like um i didn't realize that like i
don't know that you know it was still
the release was still so far
uh probably gonna like stream like on
monday or tuesday of next week the early
access so like two or three days before
yeah and holotalk coming back
all around all that is like kind of
happening the german channel and the
huda talk is kind of happening around my
anniversary
just so you know
yeah
okay now i will go have a second
breakfast
yeah
bye-bye
[Music]
well thanks for the pinky and the other
super chats
thank you
i'll be reading soon
next stream was
ah code of the lamp uh
i'm not streaming tomorrow apparently
[Music]
bye bye
bye