foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
it's kind of yeah I'm spelling it a
little bit differently but it's
definitely how we would say it in
Germany
do you know that roosters tilt their
heads to block their ears to stop them
from going Deaf from themselves because
cockatiels are really so loud yeah fun
fact did you know okay
[Music]
thanks for the lore
it's kind of crazy
it is really crazy actually
we're back
baby's gate yeah
chat is the sound okay maybe the other
chats can answer it too oh you're not
playing darling I don't know why that is
oh really uh maybe it's because I'm like
constantly lining up
wait let me try lighten up lower my or
high because like my rapper hat
I'm lining up for you
I mean you're permanently lit up
actually yeah oh yeah you're permanently
not lit up let me turn up here oh that's
weird
[Music]
what about
there we go this should be good
according to the Discord my buzzing is
like so loud I'm so sorry if it bothers
anyone
from the background yeah okay good okay
I don't have to light up people probably
recognize my voice at this point yeah
oh
yeah
maybe I can get your PNG or something
more PNJ yeah now you have it so that it
doesn't it doesn't go dark it just
completely is not there
no it's there but it just it's just
permanently dark right now oh okay I'll
give you a bright pink yeah give me a
bright PNG yeah there you go let's see
how about how monkeys it's from my
thumbnail yeah
I'm the yellow ostrich
yellow I want this okay context I got a
super chat a while ago that was like
probably just a parody but they called
me a yellow ostrich streamer
tanakishakaria and it just cracks me up
all the time
yeah
honestly I thought that was hilarious
right it was great it was nice don't
worry about it
I finally understand Cali thanks to me
using Carla in my private playthrough
that you your thing your class or
whatever is like stronger when you naked
yeah that's right that's the thing well
see here's the thing is that like this I
mean clothing I could at least put on
clothing that isn't armor and that would
be fine I just think it's easier to cut
to the Chase and just be naked
and show your strength assert your
dominance yep
hey Siri
I've changed my mind and I'm we're
breaking up oh
noise okay
oh no but he likes you
the nipples
oh they're popping off
the player's death
he's so naked
he is naked
so naked
naked little guy oh we just had this
conversation you just confessed to me
he's a vampire and I'm very confused I
thought we already went through that
evil leave
no you can't banish him right
well man
can we permanently remove him from the
party not just kidding I'm joking I why
do you hate a Starion I just pretend to
hate him
I'm a magistrate back in the city it's
all rather tedious he's a magistrate oh
my God what's weird
neither do I actually that sounds like
adult speak yeah right
big words that adults use
convince the right people to talk all
right cool I get it moonrise Towers well
I don't need you in my party oh game
quiet okay hold on
does this look right to you guys uh
small anyway
so today's uh leader we have decided
generally will be people but maybe if we
go to the tea house then the leader
there will be Kelly because she's the
only one who hasn't really seen the tea
house yet and it would be nice to have
some innocent mind going through it I'm
far behind
what are we doing it's okay oh we need
to get the lady that's the first thing
we should do I think yes
yeah yes yes let's go Carla
we're missing the camera
best best wife Carla okay where are we I
meet you guys at blighted Village
okay oh yeah
this is teleportation Point people play
The Village
yes oh yeah I'm I'm so sorry that was a
silly of me
aren't you ahead of all of USA uh yeah
but so I I can't go to this area anymore
so ah I see oh you can no return
yeah I'm past that point is it like
every act you can't go back to where
you're doing uh after after a part in
act two you can't go back here and after
act three you can't go back anywhere
except for the new areas so okay wait
there's something I want to get from the
blighted village while we're here okay
yes you know how to get it
um yes I do I think
so
so people your footsteps are
so fast they were they were very very
bloody oh yeah I stepped in a puddle
hold on a minute the blind Village is so
much more than anything it is
for life oh Authority
um
thank you
I'm not seeing that what's going on
it's like something's happening
yeah I also don't see the role scissors
mind your manners of course we will
nurse signs inspired it was I don't it's
in one of the houses
right oh wait yeah yeah is it in the
basement of The Alchemist building yes
yes I think
we need it though we need it you want it
I I want it so bad okay
remember what I found that I wanted
Marissa to get oh with my stream
no it was something I told you that we
need to get the other house it's the one
it's this house sorry
ah yeah
the the it's it's in the the bottom the
bottom uh it's in the underdark yeah
sword I know yeah I know where it is
yeah yeah okay okay maybe we can get
that tuition why is there so many things
for you and nothing for me I found it I
found it yay
alcohol I loot give me all the booze all
right where did they go down there oh
okay okay I don't know where it is down
here I just know it's here go explore
okay be careful
a little potion of sleep yum yum
that curious
I totally didn't know that there was a
lever there I didn't know that at all
oh
yeah
did you guys go into a different room oh
yes let me come pick you up down in the
Hat
is that not where that book is I'm blind
eyeballs
where'd they disappear to I mean it
Blends in really nicely so weird
you just everybody
I I get you
suspicious poison that sounds fun
it does
hmm
where is this past the perception check
yeah you think it's in this room because
there's other rooms the one that I just
opened the the door to oh probably
yeah sounds accurate feel free to open
all the caskets good
there's nothing in there I need my book
oh wait are you looking for the
oh
surprise indeed are you looking for a
nickel nick yeah oh okay all right I
missed it in my run so I need it please
help me with my dad and fully now you
are surprised how do I play this okay I
am
you said to open all the caskets
I think this is how I play it and then
what do I do
it's been so long
just a little refresher course
I'm ready well you guys got it all taken
care of I guess yeah
yeah
with books she should talk to them
this is a thing over there never so you
already know it right I don't I missed
this in my run through I didn't even
come here you didn't get the book okay
we need the book and the book key so the
book key is also somewhere
yeah the book here's the the team right
yeah I know where both are
what's your name Mirror Mirror I'm a
mement race what are these answers
oh
Good Luck
Good Luck what wow does Disney tried to
sue step forward what oh my God this
looks literally like Snow White yeah
I don't think they invented that
oh good job
let me in
you did that
girl
[Laughter]
um
I wonder what that is oh my God what's
that looks like a trap do you need me to
disarm it I think it looks in there
oh wow okay wait let me see if I can uh
I found a bunch of Scrolls may I take
them yeah I'll take them yeah yeah take
everything that looks interesting I have
no idea tools so I can't lock pick this
people attack the door
this
is
yay I'm wearing this one now
where are we I feel
I'm here
thank you can you does it Charlie we
need you yes
[Music]
not ranged attack Jesus Cali I've got
gloves for you
oh good gloves
thanks in my inventory if you find the
blue gloves the bracers of the fence
those are for you oh thank you let me
equip them really quick yes
Maury Oak
s
a week
you gotta let Cali do this
I can't uh I can't take it from you
actually here I think you got to give
him me oh okay yeah
he also has bludgeoning dips
now put it in your inventory thank you
oh it's working you got it there you go
[Music]
it's the only thing I can do
the book is an important thing no
visibility
this is my book
that's your book yeah
[Music]
in circles
I love this book oh
you feel better the second oh you drop
your book The Voice
I didn't have an option
they have no hold on
all you have to do
what oh did you do oh
uh oh it's just about he's got a little
fire breath
okay be careful just just walk out of
there just walk this walk out maybe yeah
little fire breath gargoyle dude I don't
need to be in turn basement
well good thing we got out of it yeah
yeah
what the
okay
it's a gem down here to unlock it no
I'll show you I know where it is oh
my nose
it goes pretty deep we have to go pretty
deep for them yeah if you want to like
be fast and we could get out of here
first and yeah then we have to jump into
the into the whole of the other building
I think oh we can go through the well
the well isn't that bad oh yeah there's
several places to get whatever down
there it's all connected
the
the South It's gotta be a like a stone
round Stone I picked up the key I think
that was the key to the cell that
we we don't need it we don't need it
yeah I can break any any game
Mario play Smash everything okay
are you still down there
oh
where's the exit oh yeah there we go
right here let's go through the well the
well is fun
okay
yeah I will even break the the lock on
balder's gate
on the Baldur's Gate what more you open
Smash what does the gate go into
what the gate guarding yeah I don't know
what holders I guess
we sing the song of bolderon who founded
Baldur's Gate you know Moss yeah looks
unremarkable conversation I just want to
open this chest really quick
you guys can do your thing dry Stones
line the wall
Callie being a little bit aggressive
over there
Kelly follow us you got it just just
definitely grabbing some things wait
I'll find them sorry
Rod next eyeballs
for this one
okay where are we going forward what way
Eddie just go explore I think the poison
one might be a good one direction to go
I trust you baby
[Music]
oh there's a spider web that's not
creepy or anything
don't get caught ladies
oh me looks like that
um
let's party oh you guys already started
oh
behind us
all right okay
well now I know where we are okay
are those little alligator dudes no
they're spiders
it looks like alligators too far away
they they do you're so right oh they're
kind of cute
let's go
all right I don't think I have any
ranged attacks
oh I'm just oh music changed
I'm just gonna
long
[Laughter]
good luck
nice one
yeah yeah
oh there's another one far away that's
coming up oh blue oh they're coming
um
yeah
[Music]
zoom zoom zoom
I'm stuck
you are
in the web still yeah
far
yum Chomp jump try jumping or so there's
those are yeah
I think oh well good luck
wait I'm still stuck in the web you guys
need to get me out
another one skill issue I'm sorry
Marissa that's rough
is helping
okay well
I guess I'll just keep let's go Kelly
yeah
I'm sorry I killed your enemy yeah no
it's cool I'll get the spider yes yeah
we'll just chill back here
no damage please well I'll try to I'll
I'll come over here
to you but I have I don't have no more
action
this way I have range if you want yeah I
don't know do I not have I bet I don't
have any arrows oh it hurts all right
let me throw something Dale teleport
probably next turn again you don't need
carols more
fine
[\h__\h]
oh there it is
okay can I hit it to help my friend here
oh I'm not lived anymore
get out of here
go kill that spider bee boo got it yeah
beat him up
steal his lunch money
yeah yeah feeling it I'm gonna go fly
out of the web too
my voice is so husky because it's really
early in the morning drink some tea with
honey
for
it's got two
together yeah oh it's up there and I
guess
they can just range attack it I suppose
or he could just come down here I mean
that's what I was thinking too
little baby oh baby bear baby dudes
[Music]
is that correct yeah that is correct
that is not the correct way
but I knew that the poison filter it's
good to explore you know it's good yes
yes oh you're right you're right oh
you're going that way
I don't know where I'm going I haven't
been here before anyways I think you're
naturally progressing correctly oh yeah
oh yeah oh yeah
don't do anything
what's up
like this
yeah
it's prone baby oh I know this is good
it did Big damage
all the babies oh she's coming
I want she coming
wow it's kind of awesome that was
one-third of the house yeah we could
continue that whenever she's on the web
if anybody has something with fire just
shoot the web with the fire
um
she's currently is she considered I
don't think she's on the web right now
no she's on the she's on the thing she's
offline
oh okay
okay I killed most of the babies
nice
we feel very strong 30 that's nothing
I gotta rely on the
wow wow oh what's what's going on today
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh okay okay makes sense the real
opponent hey as we should be honestly
oh
come here
go up to this little spider
um oh
kill the spider
okay I'll try if it lets me not enough
movement all right I guess oh you guys
are blocked oh that's fine
incredible
yeah I can't see Pastor She's Too Tall
I'm too short it's okay oh she's so thin
I'll go for the other one
yeah Point Blank never said that come
and hit me
swords
whoa
whoa gotta get rid of the smaller ones
too that is true
you guys got the big one yeah
nice yeah I'll throw something you know
what to do
oh it didn't work oh [\h__\h] I threw it
wrong Maybe
should have gone on the web more than on
the spider Maybe
okay
oh you inspired did you inspire me there
I saw I got some Bardock roll here
because you inspire me every day so
ah
does it go away
or am I using it
oh now I'm using it
it hit
Mutual inspiration oh it's running when
it flew away
that little cow baby
don't hurt noisa
what a freak it's okay I can take a
little bit of pain a little bit
very much
oh it's so big how can you miss
so people can we still multi-class yes
well you have to turn it back to normal
I think
but if we turn into Easy Does It undo
the multi-classing
no because I still have my cleric stuff
double Miss okay I'm a genius maybe next
time we're at Camp it doesn't have to be
right away it doesn't matter but um I
might want to pop well now I can move
away wizard
I want to be strong nice cloud of
daggers
making me excited to play on my own at
some point I just got it on PS5 baby
and playing Boulders get a little
bit of you guys somebody oh I agree this
robe
it's a different game this is roped at
the spider dropped good oh yeah we're
not done yet
oh
maybe maybe
he's stronger without armor no
hmm oh wait oh there's only two ones
like wear clothes just like me for real
for real
it never ends
kill one spider find five more
grow business armor okay okay
so some alone time with the Vampire dude
shut up Ally looks so much better
without clothes
excuse me sorry I mean like well your
character
because I gave that same rope to Carla
and she just doesn't look good at it
I get it
oh I killed that one
yeah
I believe in you guys
from the throw
yeah eat yeah get it get it path is not
interrupted what are you talking about
[Music]
it's not that bad can you jump sometimes
it gets a little frustrating
there we go
yeah
all right wrote for somebody in the big
spider are you okay
oh no okay I've only got eight health
left
is that so far fall oh at least you got
the thing right
I'm about to I'm trying to pick it up
but it's it's tiny there we go dark
amethyst acquired
I'll just take it from that for now okay
how do I get back to you guys it was oh
yeah where I am there's a little
climbing thing
okay you don't have to go back down and
climb up yeah yes I see it you see me
yeah we should probably short rest
thank you that doesn't nothing
oh no I'm not basking in in the the
weird God's love anymore oh wow what a
shame
no I mean I still have it so whenever it
was a permanent blessing oh it is but uh
it's you you have to meet certain
standards to reach it you know what I
mean so it's a it's La Via Tara's love
pain is the path to Clarity when you
have 30 hit points or less you gain a
two percent bonus two attack rolls and
wisdom saving throws for three turns
pretty cool that's the buff
that's pretty cool have you not been
engaging in the sages enough these days
uh it seems not
so do we want to like explore this place
even more or do we want to move on to
the tea house okay
we go back to blighted Village yeah we
can we can just teleport to play it
yeah let's do it
language
[Music]
are we ready let's go yes yes ready
friends you get it ladies
we gotta meet the hot lady
hot lady literally and figuratively yeah
she sets my soul on fire mine too man
I have a Siri in this one though yeah um
I will steal him from you by the end of
time
but
I just don't think he's feeling it break
someone else I think we can go from
that's right over here if we jump
yeah this is a bit of a hard one I
remember a bridge
that you had to jump
oh yeah I walked over a piece of uh tree
a long tree log
I think I think we can oh we could go on
the other side there's there's a side
over here down here what's the Ping
again
oh
it's up by the Risen Road
um oh yeah it's up over here
yeah and then we go up I believe
we'll find it eventually
we gotta get our car what happened oh
yeah I'm just loading off my weights to
you girls because I'm my inventory was
too empty yeah it doesn't feel happy
who has a conversation
all right I'm on the way
oh this one's power cool I guess we do
it on here and then I don't know how you
guys climbed all the way over there but
we'll find it
find the way jump yeah the vendor at
some point that would be cool
oh my gosh
I'm watching you
I'm watching you she looks a little bit
like Nami from live action
a little bit oh my god oh yeah is it
good I've heard you guys it's so good I
like it a lot
it even made me like one piece who had
nothing to do with one piece until now
you know why can't I jump please just
let me jump game I see his sibling game
I'm begging you Brenna I don't know how
you guys got over there you went down
over by the the cave for the owl Bear
yeah
and then we just walked over we didn't
have to jump
mind
you can walk over the water oh I guess
you can just walk through the freaking
one
are you underestimated
it's not the brightest
it's all right absolutely okay let's go
to win
um well
the last one I think I consumed so
and Theresa got one so
Kelly and people should I want to eat a
worm yeah are you testing us yeah
[Music]
she's going to rip down the old world
order they don't know we killed all the
Goblins oh yeah oops uh
do they know
like you has been chosen by the absolute
absolute you speak with her voice and
when the time
well I can make them do whatever will I
want
um
You Will Rule it flashes back to bibos
like half this person
that's comedic a crucial you have more
to learn about faith novice I'm sorry
true soul I
it seems the absolute still has a great
deal to teach me
um
good job guys lighting her yeah just
just tell him to leave just time to
leave
so you killed that thing oh yeah I did
absolute continue to guide your hand
madam as for us we won't take any more
of your time May the absolute guide us
okay bye
Maya bye you freaks absolutely do just
wanted to get you out there to loot his
body
the body
you can have it Bieber
oh wait there's one on here
where'd you put that robe I wanted to
see it oh the robe it's uh it's in my
first row oh
I think I swear by weight transport it
to me I will take the weight off your
shoulders if you want it sure okay I
gave it to you thank you
oh
a very cute little robe oh it looks nice
looks taller than you
can I wear this
yes it reminds me of your RPG outfit
yeah
what which one ah the one I'm wearing
now true oh it's
oh
nice
okay oh okay go next oh okay wait Carla
this way
the way
wait
let's go this hold on let me think
um I don't think we've been to the Risen
road yet
but we'll be able to get to Carlock from
here
um but I think it's up pretty sure it's
up yeah it's up more we need to go north
we're going south
I don't remember anymore this place is
too
um
I think it was the other way from play a
village to the other side
oh yeah we're jumping over this uh no we
not this bridge there was jumping over a
bridge okay I guess I'm doing this
I didn't really care but apparently I'm
talking to dead board but not really I'm
just examining it I'm back at the
blighted Village I've walked back over
I presume we go north yeah we go out the
other side and then go north
a vampire's been eating yeah I wonder
what vampire has been eating it
estarian
oh okay wait where did you girls go I
will wait for you
um
okay
is that you oh is it that way
it's north I follow narissa
it could be wrong
so you think
quick save oh no her Autos oh no oh no
no
or am I that it's quick saving
[Music]
trouble
yeah he's ready smash
smash
yeah with big fist
and Meaty thigh fish I like that fist
meet the eye
oh oh I can finally jump over this
actually eat me eat me I would like to
be okay
I got you hold on a sec all right let's
see where is it I need to watch this ah
melee I might not make the jump you know
so just in case
okay let me use my mouse
let me just use my mouse bagel
roof pickpocket no do not pickpocket
bro
there go on yeah
oh wow that was pretty bloody
boo come back she's dead they're really
okay
thank you
can you jump getting thrown by catleans
uh it comes with someone your back is
broken downsides hello oh
what happened to the dog thick with
blood
almost gagging you mutter are quiet
we're fighting them I smashed them
it's not my turn
ER
how do you say it in English
definitely kill them that's a lot of
strawberries yeah yummy
um
nice
some some very fruity Jam yeah that's a
lot
it's a lot of fruit chunks in there yeah
I guess they like it chunky yeah and
there we go
pretty rough oh yeah
yeah
I'm sorry I have to make you wet it's my
turn
I thought you know was in the chat
yeah
because hyena
[Music]
you made me scroll up in the chat guys
where is she
inadoko
Kelly punch him smash him kick him yeah
I did
again oh that could be more
oh okay oh boy oh boy oh
you see that glitch yeah
okay here we go
nice
bonus action huh
I'm just gonna electrocute us like that
very cool
this will not be the first time I
elected you don't worry
I'll look forward to the next time
okay
come on kids wait let's take this food
because
um we need camera supplies
all this stuff
yeah you're trying to load some food too
here and there
oh yeah nice idea grab all that all
those goodies
more you open fine red apple
um
I like I like your um
I like you
rotten food
did you find her
yeah she's down here I haven't
interacted I'm waiting for you guys oh
down down
[Music]
who wrote the lyrics to that song no
that's Daisy
okay
you too she's on fire just like me
yeah Sparks like the flame yay she's
starting a fire every day
oh the leg oh yeah oh [\h__\h] her Flames
always make my OBS lag so much is yours
yeah
met some of the alturans who got trapped
in the Hills though
so weird I love her when she lights up
yeah I love her too it's you from the
nautiloid please tell me I found you
before those so-called paladins of tear
did does she not remember me
a matter and my team all this time loves
me what why
good great
glad I don't have to kill don't hurt me
carlak
no please hurt me
please
fiery as the hell s then your last
envisions of demonic
she's so beautiful landscape of fun yeah
I relate to her on another level
mm-hmm
my my Burning Angel
foreign
[Music]
I'm your girlfriend now
hey you already have a Starion don't you
no I'm joking
helping me kill some evil she's all
yours Kiana I know you love car lots all
right I see how it is everybody's turned
their back on me just because Therian
decided that he wanted a little poke
no no no no sorry everybody deserves
some love made me her personal attack
Jokers
please
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah yes yes
they've gone far after the scorching I
guess she's great yeah we can work on
evicting this parasite and take pharoon
by the short hairs sound good
my favorite companion I think oh oh yeah
we'll hug you if it wouldn't Scorch your
skin off yeah
we already have a Berserker Barbarian
yeah for the party for you
no sorry I'm sorry
this one at the camp Queen the fun stuff
without me got it
we have to do the fun stuff without you
though there's no room wait a second
okay sorry we're a full team you're
gonna have to deal with that where did
that oh my boo boo hold still yeah wait
never mind I can't do it ah why can't I
use my speaker dudes yeah let's go beat
up the dudes
yeah those guys suck erisa needs healing
at some point emotion I'm throwing at
you no I've got potions
um I was trying to use my spell but I
found one of the things I had applied
wouldn't let me do my healing word so ah
okay can I do one more short rest before
this fight
yeah okay
guys
that's a dude's head cool
I just picked it up can't wait to throw
it at someone you're welcome I'll let
you see I don't know I want to go up
here before we start the fight oh sure
okay oh I just want to kill him
yeah yeah we're going to be
understandable for sure
wait wait wait yes uh Kiara you want you
want to talk to someone who will sell
you things yeah yeah pass this door
there's a person you can buy and sell
things from we'll have to kill them in
the fight to come but if you want to
quick sell off some stuff you could
before the fight starts okay yes I do
that's that's awesome wait we're selling
eh
Amy
try try talking outside she's cute oh
yeah she sells stuff here you can go
first Kiara okay
here Papa oh wait oh she's going inside
to her sales table or what
oh well you guys are doing that I need
to how do I turn off nudity again I
turned it back
once you turn it on Marissa why do you
think she turned it on me
private moments has nothing to do with
that yum yeah private moments is like
blocking the scene or so no one else can
see it cool how do I uh
uh what's the quick way of doing this
again
is there a quick way to sell stuff I'll
just double click okay
double click double click done
quickly double check and make sure
nudity off
yeah that I would turn it on because I
don't care about those things but let me
see it's not about preparing about those
things what's it about vendors is it
about the immersion or something about
the emergency in real life
the authentic experience you see yeah I
don't want I don't want little leaf
covering my my nip knobs I know what
they look like already you know all
right
I get you yeah this is mature yeah you
understand yeah all right whatever you
say
almost done
you're cool take your time
yeah
in Tia's name yeah yeah
no don't do it okay I'm gonna have to
just wait two seconds people
[Music]
okay
we just wait for Cali I'm I'm ready okay
can you get away from him so I don't
make you wet
sure I'm gonna go on this side
is that okay you got a plan don't you I
do have a plan
Nick
thanks let's do this
in the distance could use that all right
um you know I guess that's probably
probably about it oh I have a soul coin
keep them keep them
are they good for Carlock I don't
remember I thought I remember her
talking about them and I was like oh
I've never used this once no yes you
need them for her I
you can you can slot it in her body and
it makes her stronger like a slot
machine oh yeah we also need to save the
infernal irons so if you see that don't
sell it okay okay cool
let me see let me just grab a dagger
really quick so I can throw it and then
oh yeah good idea
hate having to do math right
they should
they should really make this a little
easier to figure out but that's okay
I'm almost done guys sorry
eight plus six fourteen
all right I got it got this all right
let's do it all right kill him hold on
I'm gonna enter turn base
and then I'll kill her
okay don't make noise so wet
oh I didn't make him wet oh yeah he's
wet okay
okay
another one and their turn please
oh
turn ended oh rattle them
like environmental turn environmental
turn okay okay there we go
die
oh I missed oh it's okay
it's fine just kill him
over there
we go all right now now we go we ball oh
we
party time just murder exactly as
planned
you can't see
I don't want to go down
I'm blocking it you can't oh yeah you
can't climb up the stairs
then take this
easy yeah we still have some more right
yeah yeah but they wanted to fight Mori
open
I can't blame them really yeah who
wouldn't want to fight Mario fish
I need this book for my collection yeah
that's great
I guess I should go down though because
they're all like yeah I'm out of my view
theme
hey let you down
[Music]
oh we're gonna kill them oh she's
invisible
poor lady
oh did she turn invisible yeah [\h__\h] but
she's still there you could like if you
have some AOE or something like
something like cloud of daggers you
could place it there and hope that it
hits her yeah I'll randomly shoot she's
right there boom nope
oh burning hands roll Grease
um
it's so cruel we both turn off your
electric water oh you can turn off give
me all your [\h__\h]
oh Callie do you want a sword
of Justice oh
that sounds kind of neat would that be
good for me that might be I gave it to
you
content I found a fan fiction a fan
fiction
a pleasurable deal this is an excerpt
from the play a pleasurable deal of
banned in no fewer than four cities for
its loot content scandalous nature led
to a number of widely distributed and
illicit printings
okay
narrator come here fearful the tail now
lost to time in grief this man will sunk
to death Sublime a gift he saw to win
his lady's heart our Campion smiled for
now the game did start enter Robert male
tiefling crying Carlisle stage right
flash of smoke
weep not young man dough free your wife
has fled and comfort found in comrades
arms and bed she licks her lips and
cries his name oh my and now seek you to
be the apple of her eye
how does a stranger no such things I ask
Carlisle I watch you from the shadows
and I see your shame and grief for
Nature's Melody you seek to win your
lady and her bed to have your name upon
her lips instead Robert you know my
curse my pain my grief my woe Carlisle
of you I know you seek a larger hoe to
plow a Fair Maid and sell sower seed to
grow but lag do ya Mighty Hornet mask
with which to guide a maids to be bad
and fast
that's the only spicy book I found in
this game
[Music]
um
cool
actually under the someone
what
oh that was severed head I was thinking
of putting it in someone's inventory
now what did you do
cucumber I'm cucumber you're a
cucumbered now I can't hold I put armor
on you I put armor on you
Mario pay I need you downstairs yeah
sure what's up please come downstairs
and help me knock down a door
if you tell me where downstairs is I'll
definitely go there it's right here in
the house a hatch
what was this yeah I can't I can't yell
I can't yell things at the door to make
it breaks
ignition
I can't burn a wooden door
okay we've got Goliath cook Memorial pay
yeah
there's a trap there's a trap there's a
trap
we shall disarm it my NPCs I will just
find it
okay uh-oh okay someone come sit on the
other chair on the other side
disarmed I'm missing something okay
you're gonna go loot in that room all
right I'll tell you what I find I guess
but
be careful
this is dark
oh there's a marble plate maybe I can
get around it jump
all right
just a moment
let's go it's trapped and be wary
all right there's 203 gold nine okay and
we can split loot everything all right
hold on there's a great ax great sword
Give Me Everything
and sell all these
no
I feel I want this arm
pleasurable deal hey they really like
this book here
is what it is
by the way the other one
the other pleasurable deal
which one was it Cali trap let's see
this one's just hold on oh
good stuff yeah no there's really good
stuff in this room make sure you take
all of it don't miss anything
is that the same
a pleasurable deal
it's that book right there
it's just a regular pleasure
just wanted the sequel really more gold
did it say it was illegal because it's
too lewd
yeah yeah
[Music]
behind where you just came from
okay get out of there before I lock you
in Cut and Run
let's see where's that girl this great
ax is so nice
great ax
no no before that
you say Cut and Run Cut and Run what
does that mean
it means get the [\h__\h] I mean get the F
out of there
[Laughter]
thank you
you're sort of Justice both are really
nice but I think I'll go sort of Justice
right now
there's a hole do I have to give it to a
Darion
I'm waiting to do it
are you gonna give to a Syrian
the book
yeah can you summon any small animal
oh maybe
listen to the book I can summon the
perfect thing a rant
can you control
and then interact with this hole
uh oh I don't see the hole I
how do I eat way too big this one it's
so dark way too big
oh I haven't perceived it I think
do I need to perceive it I think so
I'm way too big
also I can't walk around there oh here
let me get out of your way
I just can't get there no I'm not
perceiving it ah wait the borough holds
yeah there it is okay okay
[Music]
I could hit what
I'm not sure if the rat can go there
I can't if it no one can I can't yeah I
can click on it with the mouse with the
red
you would need you might need to Wild
shape or Mist form yeah
um
Familia but uh
um is there something we can can we
remove something
no it doesn't it doesn't
I don't think it wants to go there
that's weird it just says can't get oh
you need to be a druid oh
um
I see
rat
you can shape-shift into like a tinier
Mouse
oh it's just another entrance to the
locker room oh okay click and drag what
what
yeah
not that I know I'm using your
controller use our inspiration
if we have any because I'm I'm waiting
oh my God
I got it I just keep rolling above 20s
because I have some things I'm just
reading the books with strange runes
which book Adam Necronomicon
with power
you look very concerned
seen too much
what profane knowledge is now seared
inside he won't let me in you should
never have known are you guys seeing it
you've seen I I'm seeing nurses
cutscenya oh okay
I've seen it before no I'm glad you look
forward to it in knowledge now
I don't know what that does to me but I
have forbidden knowledge oh yeah
yes
[Music]
cool
I don't know it's just as long as you're
smart it's good oh I'm not smart
yeah
I only have charisma
you're smart just uh not in the game I'm
really smart
bye
we all live without you
in the house waiting for you hi hi hello
and a cute new little rat friend
sitting around
oh have uh any of you gone to the gith
Yankee uh crash no nope crashed did they
crash what crap
holy Crush
in case you didn't know
what is going on
I don't know
I don't want a hyena here
yeah I don't want those either
let's just leave it stinky I wonder if
we keep walking down the Risen Road what
we'll find
oh wait there's a there's a teleporter
here
nice Discovery Bijou welcome to the
Discovery Channel Good accident
yeah I've never been up here before so I
don't know what this is um
it's spooky
well there's some pretty boy good stuff
we can get if we
move on a bit from
here okay
I don't know where it is though
just exploring exploring this whole area
there's so much fun stuff you know
there's just something is over there
you and me you know
sorry people you leave okay I'm being a
little nasty yeah be bullied everybody
call me calm your feetsies
we follow people
like simple commands follow people
what's up here
or I'll be understand
I understand follow
there's more death though
yeah there's lots of dead things
everywhere I don't like that you know
they're feasting oh there's nothing
wrong can we kill them I don't have
spells by the way for this
I'm sorry um we can kill them okay how
hard could they be yeah
probably easy let's go
the feast is over
Feast is over come and fight us
we are on easy mode so oh Dad could it
be
yeah
what are these things anyway
so numbed what's that means
[Music]
Mommy
do you think these guys can speak
English
[Music]
oh yeah you're gonna insult them
yeah yeah I'm a boss and their mothers
never loved them wow
okay my first Miss of the day
they're like hyena people oh yeah
marinas who learned to walk on two feet
okay yeah they look like hyenas
you got it
that's what moyopa is here to do
it bonus action
this
a male strike
yeah how do you like that nice hey
goodbye to the rap I was sure he was
gonna last longer than all of us
hey red gone
oh yeah
rip Bales
wow got him nice one oh rude
getting out of here
good luck
okay
[Music]
come on nice
nice shooting ticks
[Music]
what
wow
oh thank you you're welcome I had a
bonus action
oh I probably should have given it to
narissa because it's over it's okay
because they went for me
I've gotta I've got a thing so I
listen around
night yeah
what's going on
I don't know what's happening actually
a murder is what's happening
why
percent
[Music]
oh that's rough
oh boy
nice
I don't know how much respite does yeah
guys
should we do a long run
yeah yeah a long rest I'll put these
guys what's in the forms of these people
an open letter
to Peacock
on the
planet
is Elena being oppressed
gotta go Savor any kind Furious
this is a letter to the elephant there's
this video over here
oh there is a thing shall we rest before
we go in there though oh absolutely
absolutely we should we're going to camp
okay okay
ghost yourself yeah
Kyla
Carla Carla Carla I took care of those
paladins for you did
okay girls we want to have uh
conversations together right not too
separate let's talk yeah yeah
um I always take care of my people
Carlock glad to be counted among them
oh she likes me yeah
but I'm just happy they're off my tail
then again facing me down might put my
tin can into overdrive number 10 can
oh engines
you want my coin my soul coins since I
left baby girl
yeah I'll be seeing my mechanic anytime
soon so I'll just make the most of the
extra heat
just don't get too close until I found a
way to calm it down
we can't give her a hug yet
um
certainly you can't do other things too
that's a dynamic oh back off
the game to be getting don't worry about
it
I don't really understand
for tragedy meanwhile I'll need to find
someone who can tune up my engine sooner
rather than later oh you mean
hand-holding yeah
I'm sorry very much
he might be able to stabilize things if
I can find him
um
there's some tea things in there okay we
look there they're not there anymore
guy will be among them no we saved them
and they left to Boulder's game remember
oh but yeah they did leave but she needs
a tiefling help uh yeah but he's on the
way to Baldur's Gate oh oh sorry Carlock
I guess
apps oops
man
yum yum yum oh she's trying she's trying
to raise up a Syrian again of course oh
she's trying she's trying so hard
I'm looking forward
focusing on what's important for us
even though he loves Mario Fame
he does
bites made me who I am thanks he's okay
do you think that's a threat
let me give you the book why can't I I
ca how do I give him the does he have to
he I bet I can't I better party no it's
too late you already read the book uh
yeah what
yeah I read the book it can't be used
again so you can't read the book no I
can't read the book I don't think
anymore
take it from my inventory oh my God
oh my god did you learn a spell from the
book
no I didn't get anything I don't know
what it was supposed to do oh I passed
all the checks so apparently I got the
knowledge but I don't know what the
knowledge is you keep the book until
later I think apparently okay I'm gonna
send it and I don't need it on wait I'm
gonna read the book the book refuses to
okay yeah see it doesn't open for anyone
except for the person who read it
oh so it's stuck to you now well my book
look at Carlock dancing I love when she
drops
she drops it
oh yeah oh hold on yeah yeah hold on
Bust A Move yeah
some head spinnies
oh oh
yeah
I remember if you okay remember he
killed me and then he got mad yeah
Frontiers
oh shaking you for good after the Mind
Flair ship he just can't get enough of
me can you
Carlock
Advocates diaboli the stink of averness
chill will win anything
why am I making the choices
or no okay sorry oh suggestions
furnace
just ahead a diabolical figure with skin
single curled horn blazes with flame
bloodied great ax held high he chases
the feet ignited you know Will's pretty
cool she isn't in fact yeah I really
liked will his eye his eye I don't
really have him in my party allies are
fraud a soldier in the arch Devil's
Ariel he's the only one who liked me in
my solo playthrough
and I didn't even have him on my team
barely and I was like what what you
think I am how can you struggle with
making these NPCs like you like I feel
like everybody's lusting yeah
foreign
[Music]
I may be an effective Soldier but I
never wanted to serve zariel legged it
away from her the first chance I got and
yet you served
ah
Stand Down
you saw what I saw stop it no Devils
cannot be trusted oh come on
stop being so stubborn will
you listen to sense
this doesn't have to end badly
for either of us we could be friends you
know monsters right because
let me see I'm not what you think
my mans were you not paying attention
he just doesn't want to believe it come
on man
that's okay well deceived
we forgive you
even though you didn't forgive Bijou for
looting your dead friends but okay we
forgive you died maybe he'll join us
after this thankfully maybe there have
been enough threats today
truths
I'll do you one better he missed a
little baby
but luck won't be on our side forever
yes you have my blade Your Leader
willing of course
later why not okay
um the more of the merrier as they say
no dies kidding
they killed me before
my life
and my bow but tonight
I was the rampaging Beast I see the good
in you Carlock I promise not to lose
sight of it even when the hell's burn
hottest wow the famous blade of
Frontiers
are you seeing Shadow heart because I'm
seeing nothing
AKA nothing
nothing
above her head
listen blood will Source sense even more
glad he decided to stick around it takes
a pretty slick mover to try yeah he came
out of nowhere yeah oh I'm just glad
he's not mad at me anymore right
if he turns on you again he's dead yeah
do you've got a little butt chin here
your character has a butt chin
I respect someone who can admit when
they're oh stick around but he's behind
there
you'll see
next time next time maybe yeah you'll
see though you have a bunch oh I think
will wants to talk too yep will wants to
talk let's go listen to his conversation
well what's up
and witness to a pantomime I'm sorry to
say
and I've played my poor guy all too
poorly
only this
is
one night soon when we make Camp oh it's
a hot looking ladies
everybody looks real good you too thanks
I know maybe the most good looking is me
and you'll have possibly
I can't promise you'll like them
well tell us about yourself
you want to talk more of him or sleep
oh house what's going on a house and you
have a house
the guy was here now let me have a
little conversation with him
oh father's blessings to you you have
anything he wants to say oh God
what is this
um
those who remain
if you don't die of their hands then you
become one beautiful Memorial your face
is so beautiful it's hard for me to look
at it for too long it's hard for anyone
to resist
especially a cereal
hideous but fascinating like nothing
else in nature I'm glad to say yes
hideous but fascinating
[Laughter]
I've chosen a success
[Music]
who are we talking about
I do not know and neither do any of the
others The Grove needs to move beyond
the mistakes of the past what it needs
is an unknown quantity an outsider who
can enforce the young fathers get your
reps in ladies this is what you chose
Francesca you guys want to know a fun
fact I learned about housing Purity he's
one of the only companions that you can
date one person also date house and at
the same time and he likes it yeah
polygamy yeah yep
I believe it
what about the secret passage in the
underdark tell us how to go there
because we definitely need to go there
there's stuff we want there one of his
cohorts wait did I go there I think I
went there
like it's not for the content
that's what it's for guys right it's the
content
those illicit creatures threaten the
natural order it's my duty to do what I
can to stop
Shadow curse it's an affront and must be
cleansed under dark is fine I feel like
that's just a better way to go years ago
but I failed to prevent him from
unleashing Darkness across the region
before he was defeated if I can join you
and get close to moonrise perhaps I can
lift this curse just as you find a cure
for your infection
okay Allison I'm kind of done talking to
you
um
Molly smash Molly no talk
another player is choosing camp supplies
leave it to you
I made dinner
nice I hope it tastes good
I made tonkatsu last night
yeah by myself wow it was supposed to be
a Australian schnitzel but I realized I
can just make it into tonkatsun because
it's like pretty similar I love making
tonkatsu with curry too oh yeah
I'll check on him crazy guy
it's like open you're gonna steal the
poor dogs
[Music]
and the dog will feel good about himself
maybe yeah
or he'll bite your hand off which would
be sick where's the ball
not something you see every day
no that doesn't seem right we'll try
again really quickly come on this time
it works
extract the ball from his chin yes it
must hurt oh I guess why are you
stealing the ball from him he's just a
little guy are you okay because he needs
attention
approved
oh yeah cool baby
you'll have the ball in your inventory
if you throw it somewhere he'll bring it
back to you try it that's so cute
let's see now that you can pet the dog
why are there two Gales I don't know I
think he's glitch the way closer to him
oh no he goes
nothing he's coming foreign
oh that's so sweet of you I know I gave
him what I was wearing so now I need to
find a different one but I you know in
this camp for whatever reason I can
never find the Traveler's chest I feel
crazy oh it's over here oh yeah okay
it's just my shadow heart
he's not glitch to talk to him oh so he
just has another dude version yeah don't
question it it's normal
yes because you win in it I can't no it
belongs to only one of them belongs to
you
there's four yeah there's four there's
one for each yeah there you go really we
don't care no we don't share
you're pretty
how do I know which one's mine
the what everyone lets you open it I
guess
Travelers chess traveler's chest I mean
I think you're gonna find the blue
head in there oh this is mine it must be
mine because it's got a severed head
nice should I put that in someone else's
chest now good luck
I don't think you can yeah why is not
the orange one well I'll put it in your
inventory then
arm it I'll just sell that
I'll store my gold
[Music]
what's next
I'm good to go house or let's just keep
exploring up north because there's stuff
happening up North and then the tea
house is down up north because I haven't
been there before
okay yeah okay have I been there
have you been to the crest the crush I
don't think so
then you haven't been up north
okay are you still in the camp I am no
I'm coming out right now
pink chest
I didn't leave
I mean yes
stop running
oh wait for the team wait she's just
coming to me I was first she goes really
far away from everyone yeah I'm just
waiting by narissa
all right thank you please hold my hand
I was alone I was so scared what was
that wait that's lude though right
lead the way
oh good burning Village oh why is
everything on fire I don't know I wonder
what could be up here to cause
everything to be on fire hey what's
happening is it like a raid Maybe
the village is being raided Maybe by God
oh wow I did not see this yet I'm in a
conversation
to face Darkness without fear
what the beep happen
that's no good
oh all right okay
all right guess what once we're doing
what they want us to do
you might as well loot
no wait if we lose don't get mad I think
if it wouldn't it be red then oh it's
fine
strange place to find it the Goblins is
probably fun but what are they doing
yeah what I'm sorry I'm in a
conversation oh at the gate
strength push I don't ask questions I
push
a little bonus yeah
big muscle
mushrooms
there you go
time
go go go well that's what you meant my
work here is done
oh everything is on fire
that's pretty wild
nice bathtub
what's this Blaze it feels wrong to loot
things
I mean they're not using it anymore it's
on fire might as well get it before
don't let the goblins
oh potato porridge
what's up don't find
well we could also go in where I opened
up the door yeah I think yeah there's a
dead end where I am it must be a reason
why you opened the door yeah you gotta
go in
comfortable
yeah I mean it is a burning building
imma save the ham I'm Gonna Save the
food
yeah save the kitchen stuff I saved the
sausage okay oh [\h__\h] one thing that I
wish you could do in this game is cook
yeah right like I know you technically
are when you're camping but like it's
not the same just not this game is being
able to make a recipe you know
Apple
pineapple we need to cook
did you girls go to the second floor
so that way we have food for our camp
it seems like there might be somebody
behind this door oh boy oh
I'm in the scene
yeah I mean I just
I just bloated
I don't think so
we exit that yeah okay who are you
talking to oh it is
no
but I'm saving a guy
oh thank you
is it
right oh I'll try to keep a hug
does he follow you now oh he has one HP
uh oh
I'm like not in the same area as this
guy
why did he die
um
and get out of there completed the quest
in a different kind of way uh okay we
completed the quest
let's go oh yeah was there a quest that
we could have gotten with that guy yeah
oh well wait wait for me I'm getting I'm
loading all the food in here
sounds good
that's pretty rough but I gotta save the
food
yeah that is super rough actually
that didn't go as planned
maybe not that's okay
a lot of burning things in here
yeah
okay I saved the pool I'm coming
okay
no what the [\h__\h] are you doing up there
eh is that will who's that guy yeah he
looks like will right yeah I can recruit
Pavel
able pebble
yeah that's not will just look like I've
got a long road ahead the Council of
Floric needs help too how do I get there
oh there's like so many people up there
well go help him you know what I
realized but I bet we could have saved
that dude if we had did you use the
water oh yeah
I
was too busy looting the food
yeah that's all right you got your
priorities sorry I didn't I didn't even
mean to talk to that guy
okay
I see a bunch of people here
they need help do you need help help
people hi hi maybe spread some water
wherever necessary I gotta open the door
I guess yeah maybe there are still
people to help stop wasting time oh wait
hold on my bacon now
yeah
oh what is going on
okay proper fangs must wait she says oh
let him out now gotta leave
let's go let's go I gotta cut and run
Cut and Run Cut and Run
oh
there's water barrels all over your face
yeah yeah notice
yeah maybe
oh Callie it was damn hit you hard huh
yeah a little bit
oh it takes more than me of fire to
break me Eva Eva
everyone's beauty comes drow have taken
Grand Duke older Raven guard Westwood if
my eyes and ears can be believed oh
Gauntlet report to the man and send for
reinforcements we must find the Duke
on your command counselor she's so
sweaty count the dead I mean yeah we
were just in a burning building
I must ask again for your Aid
please rescue Raven Guard from his drow
captors
the council will reward you for your
efforts
uh why entrust this to me who is the
Duke Raven guard
um
I'll I'll travel West and rescue Duke
[Music]
ravenberg's generosity comment
understood touch the towers with care
yeah the land itself has been swallowed
in Shadow
reinforcements and join you when I can
who are you left
all right yeah
we've got inspiration reward oh don't
give up now reward
reward rescue the Duke we learned that
the Grand Duke was captured by drone
taken Westward
you can only choose one route whatever
it's the same thing
um
early there's like a tried I don't
really know is there a bow
there's a bow I heard there's a bow yes
yeah
I accepted it
can I have both
I don't know I think I see it the jolt
shooter
does that just give it to us already
even though we haven't completed the
quest it should be in your inventory
yes
it's not oh I took it already okay
I think I think this is the one yeah the
jolt shooter what does it do electric
blood when the wheel that deals damage
using this weapon they gain two
lightning charges
Coolio
thank you
no more Goblin bones yeah
now now shall we immediately uh look
West I guess so we can say this yeah we
keep going west for now okay party
members in a conversation no they are
not yeah what about short dress guys
yeah she's trying your short rest it
says a party member is in a conversation
and cannot rest right now oh weird
so odd
nice
oh yeah it says it for me too wait can
everyone try to short rest oh oh
look at that maybe now
um well there's a person over here so
maybe if we talk to them it'll get us
out of our predicament yeah reset
you see that shadow in the background
yeah
it's a looks like a dragon what what's
the matter what above apart from the
drug oh her hair is popping off killed
her yes that lot is swarming all over
the bridge
I don't know what they want but it can't
be good oh wow what could they want the
other way around you ought to do the
same I doubt a fighter would go your way
we could just fight them who are you I'm
done because this is a different group
just another harassing fool trying to
stay alive
there's plenty of us around she's cute
cheers yeah
you want to join me instead what
just follow you around yeah yeah
okay bye
have a nice day that's it reset where
should we go try to get down there and
see what those guys are ah yay
no look up that was your last chance is
stick now burn uh oh
wow
um it's dark in time I think you should
run okay never mind
um wow
what the hell is going on
there's a dragon Daenerys Targaryen
please calm down
we merely sought to no excuses question
kill then move on find the weapon the
weapon find the weapon fail her at your
peril
suicide
at least why am I talking
forever maybe you'll never oh my God
uh we should save before we talk to them
by the way
um whenever we see them again
I they're around here somewhere if we
keep moving
don't worry I have rooms
yes
hey I think I'm experiencing a problem
Oh wait wait
okay
do your best
within my
mind
these creatures are so simple
too much about your task
forgiveness Kid Rock
as for you
you tell me the dragon's kind of big
big yeah a little
uh okay
um persuasion I don't know you look I'm
tiny I pose no threads at all
I'm gonna add guidance
can I add friends oh wait say add
guidance to friends it's too dice better
I don't know
oh two dice is nice
I love just looking at Morgan's ABS I
did it it's fine thank God I raised him
up
much as I want to see the dice roll of
course you are not a threat you are
nothing until wow otherwise all right
can we kill them keep sucking air it is
necessary for you to tell me something
of worth a vessel fell from the sky we
seek a precious weapon that was taken he
suddenly feel this strange anxiety take
hold not your own but that of the
artifact oh no somehow
the artifact does not want depart from
you it does not want to fall into the
death Raiders hands I'll postpone it and
I will leave your blood beneath your
skin unspilled don't let them know we
have a bee boo um
sure I'll help if I can't should I say
that be like yeah I'll help if I can of
course obedience is your only hope now
stand still oh he's gonna Frisk you he
begins
wait wait wait
um
steal my mind
give me guidance
yeah it's fine
my mind is sealed you cannot get past my
mind
Frisk no Jutsu
h
um
[Music]
can I detect his thoughts Ryan woo
oh I have minus one intelligence oops
maybe not oh good luck ah
no thoughts can I roll again empty
sure yeah I'll try one more time
before we not die yeah
let's go a worthless yeah
this one was even even slightly useful I
might spare oh
ah
um
first one why don't they too hasty I I
just read your mind unlikely
but it costs me nothing to spare your
sorry life
very well is yeah survivors from the
ship that crashed on this wretched World
definitely not us we did not crash
if you succeed the reward will be great
now go
here we go I'm great at risen up people
I just gotta be stupid and they will
hurt me
yeah
I wanted to fight a dragon dog in time
oh you didn't it has so much health
oh really
like over two okay look there's the path
this way be aware that inspiration caps
at four so we have four again might as
well use it if you fail things okay I
don't know I was going up there
oh I just follow you guys
follow
eh
I hear kitty cat yeah she thinks I'm
done streaming because I haven't been
talking yes that's her signal
yes I'm still streaming this movie so
smoothly people looking over here
there's a gate there's a gate is it
Baldur's Gate
I must be
it's the first day we've seen only games
oh no this is for the Act 2 now
but but we can come here later but yeah
so but this I wanted us to get the quest
so we can come back here okay okay got
it yeah there's a good weapon in there
we we left lest we lose it okay okay
interesting
well where to next ladies we might as
well go south oh Tea House Tea House
okay we're going there's the underdark
thing right
yeah there's a really good weapon staff
for me there I heard
so yeah I want to keep a lookout for it
okay we gotta keep a lookout
that should be all around
well
Which Way Tea House
oh we can go outside
why the village everyone teleport again
yep okay
I'm fast quick
um okay and then we go this way by the
river
by the river
I'm so
Angry Bird
oh we're playing too much again all
right move it if you right click on
things you can move it to Camp yeah then
to camp and it'll be in your storage box
thing
one more person in chat tells me to put
clothes on I'm gonna take these clothes
off
no
Bird anymore
nice thank you okay
um
so tea house is down here Molly you take
the lead over here
[Music]
they did reveal how many thirsty strange
people are in my chat oh what's going on
talk to them
hello Mario bades
oh you was the last to see me Arena just
be nice to The Hags they're ages
it's not a hack she's not the Apple
yeah she seems nice how about you all
just calm down this has nothing to do
with me goodbye lower your weapons she's
just an old woman sweetie be careful
she's with the hag
don't Bloody Sunday gaping together
seems like we're good
I mean I've seen this somewhere before
we have to protect her yeah and we'll
Smash and destroy
the natural understanding she's a nice
lady
that's all that she is
so rude to hurt an old woman wow
she's got like blood all over her granny
gown what happened it sounded like a
heated argument oh nice thanks are paid
in Gold I like that option oh yeah
they're not lethal boys
staying with me
staying with her made a promise I made
Rita begged me not to breathe the words
if they came looking for her and my word
is my wow she seems like such a nice
lady she's evil isn't she
thank you proper
go with you
all right well can we loot him at least
see what they got all right
don't get mad I mean it I'm only leaving
this note so you don't panic and do
something stupid I'm going to the hag
come on man so rude I owe it to Conor to
make things right you know he'd do the
same for me I'll be back soon so not a
word to ma'am all right she has enough
on her plate
and then yeah chill runs up yourself
I know this is looking at something I
didn't mean to
I don't think I can roll a 20. I rolled
a 20. you rolled a 20.
oh
[Music]
what's going on
is this like some Hansel and Gretel [\h__\h]
no it looks so pretty I don't want to
walk around here anymore
yeah
all right
see the reality of this place so what
poisoned apples give me
yucky putrid bog we're in the Bog bog
beats what's going on
more poisoned apples
who is that who's this little dude I'm
not sure but I don't want to know
Burlington with a piece of gold hi
hi they look sick gangster what's going
on
creature known for its
supposed to scare me buddy boy
pretending to be a sheep
take a deep breath and say bye
ah
wow really cute we had a little
conversation there
yeah that that was a conversation
yeah
shoot for bog hey
seems like there's so much to look
around here yeah it's a pretty big area
[Music]
I think the wooden crates
about these stairs up here oh yeah oh
stairs are you going the right way Cali
you have Natural Instincts oh there's a
frog yeah I just have game instincts a
frog wait hold on a sec let's go down
here first we're going up there there's
a dude there's a duder
I'm talking to a frog oh great I think
the frog doesn't really matter until
later no
what are you croaking on about
thank you stinky
and Romeo spine he hasn't taken a shower
there's something wrong with the Frog
very wrong
oh that all sounds bad
oh okay bye frog okay I'm coming okay
all right okay
oh who's this
don't
know
whatever you're hunting your stench
alone we'll kill it a quick Witch is
rare indeed it was actually pretty slow
it took me about a minute to answer all
things kind of spots whatever you say
did you find yours before dealing with
the lady of this house bargain
Lady of the house
a more innocent name than some I could
we're here for tea but it is what she is
that all to concern you wait what did I
miss since the first Darkness
and their knowledge is matched not much
only by their spite it's just stinky how
to ask
if you're full enough to pay their price
I look so at home here it just looks
like where I
belongs it's your swamp
yeah uh what price is that it was
easiest to lose and the hardest to do
without but speaking of riddles bro
she can tell me how to draw him out and
whatever she asks I guess that she's a
witch
who is it you're hunting truth is like a
blade my friend we can arm ourselves
with it okay don't tell me I guess
pressed against our throat
I would not put you in danger good yeah
that's not what this is about is it
Barbarian I like danger the truth no yes
gonna try I believe in Mario babe come
on
this is what I excel at I'm made to
intimidate
[Music]
yeah yeah a little bit
dummy tell me what's going on oh it's
serious oh and help him
alive
don't help him
we shared a special moment together we
have never met anyone named a Starion
ever
he's no vampire we've met you can give
up your hunts hysterions under my
protection
my people were recently attacked in the
night our camp set upon by a band of
vampire spawn
in the chaos of battle one of them stole
away with our children oh we've been
searching for them
hey what children we believe this
Astorian knows exactly what happened
that night and where to find our little
ones
my people will make him talk
so I ask again
is he known to you've never met a series
never met
there is no we've never met it's I'm
protecting him or I know him just leave
just leave just leave
bye
[Music]
slave no oh I'm kind of curious too
actually
no help him
um some people are saying they killed
him in pretty good loot apparently oh I
mean I'm going to help you find him yeah
can we kill him solo yeah he's easy easy
you'll never heard a Starion I mean not
that I like him or anything but you know
we did share a moment oh yeah sure
so what happens with my Lightning Charge
plus one attack was gonna deal auditions
damage
oh what you gonna do what's he gonna do
when we come for him yeah
you got nothing on me oh okay now you do
never mind good job what if you go up to
him and hysterians in your party I did
that um and I was like I literally was
like uh he's right here on the stairway
and was like what the [\h__\h] yeah and then
we had a fight and I was like sorry it
was a dark histarian sorry about them
it was very funny pretty good gandrell's
aspiration there's a brand new bow for
you if you want here I'll pick up this
stuff I think that one wasn't was that
one good for me you didn't kill him you
just knocked out how do we go good we
can leave him here like that I mean if
you keep hitting him he'll die
eventually but you want you want the bow
do I wanna I mean you already have a
pretty nice one right
there we go I love a crossbow
um yeah okay okay
yeah yeah beat his ass
foreign
and now he's dead
bye again girls party
girls trap this arm kit that's exactly
what we need well let's see
um now that we got that guy maybe let's
go to the house oh yeah
let's do a little excuse me it's show
time Noel I'm looking at the well right
now
okay but I don't think we should jump in
right now yeah I think we should be
going to the house maybe we should just
go in through the front door I won't
don't drink from the well what the [\h__\h]
no
stinky water do that I guess we could
just go in the front yeah yeah if we
come for teeth yeah we help the lady we
need we want to be rewarded I just don't
trust her though
yes
no more has bad feelings Spider Sense
I don't know why you would have a bad
feeling it looks like Fiona
not this yes
you're eating for two years
Ages come in come in come in you look
really dirty now free to release
yourself
Marina
I won't say it again this is messed up
poor girl
I have some bad news
sorry we killed your brother you see all
your guests so poorly I have some bad
news for her under your nose shut or
things will get messy
we say
nothing I mistook you for someone else
messed up
and the Ethel killed your brothers
pretty insane but yeah she did it she
did that [\h__\h] Bros
not very convincing and I used can I try
one more time yeah
before
go for it
oh caught me [\h__\h] up man
we're gonna have a big fight now
uh oh
give me one more time one more time
please
thank you so much inspiration
however if we don't get it this time
it's not meant to be then
it's a critical failure
critical I mean I suppose that's what we
deserve
not true
no
I got it off I mean my girl isn't really
worth it anyway
she's just a drama queen
such dramatic yeah
oh
no bye whoa
sometime in the cage should do her good
wow
sticking your nose in my business oh
it's just a jerk
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
just like us oh
cute oh all right I don't want a fighter
what I mean why not she should be easy
she said yeah no the good thing is she
gets invisible oh she and she's
invisible I think it's better if we
don't manage to go run right I killed
her here and it broke the entire Quest
so maybe don't kill her yeah that's what
I'm saying don't do it oh yeah really
yeah what should we do uh we can kill
everybody cops that are that are
attacking us
yeah okay yeah and then we follow Where
She Went basically
well she's still here just invisible
though yeah for now she's she's running
away though
oh okay
where are the red caps
what if we all just came inside and
closed the door do you think they can
open the doors
I think they can
maybe they're too stupid to open doors
yeah
yummy yummy
Epic
yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy
it sounds like they're saying yeah
[Music]
there is his hands kind of close to my
butt
um
yeah yeah
puppy yeah I don't know why I went the
other one maybe I can maybe I can
distract oh ah there she goes okay she
went through the yeah just like the
fireplace
[Music]
okay she's gone now let's focus on the
red caps okay
[Music]
okay
you guys ain't [\h__\h] crumble
Rumble
yeah
you understood there like a statue oh
[Music]
lap again
get up Wawa get up come on
that was a stick Burn yeah for real
oh
there is a couldn't you have used that
magic hand to give me a hand
yeah
I'm back up again
mommy mommy
oh what was that oh thank you giving you
safety whoa
you're so safe
yeah with my shield oh there's two of
them
yeah too late there was more
yeah I think they're on their way oh
yeah they're about to enter
they're about to acquaint them slowly
a little little music to jam to you know
I can't
why can't I
hmm uh-oh why can't I
um
[Music]
nice nice okay
I wonder so I'm just gonna use this for
now because it's always like throw
daggers on spares I think
if you have some
well
or Bagels nice try okay
when in doubt
get him okay what happened to my bow and
arrow I need to get my bow and arrow
back damn
um
all right I think I can throw some I
can't throw anything but why I think I
need to be enraged
um
let's see
bro yeah get mad
probably could have been a business
you got one Health left
whatever whatever
cool
ah wow
that's pretty rough not doing so well
nice oh crap I love that oh they're
Smalls
hmm yes
oh well
so they're done for and she ran away she
ran away
okay we follow steal this stuff I guess
yeah oh yeah she's gone
perhaps for me and Callie yeah
I took it
see
lotion of Greater healing I steal
because I don't give up I don't give a
[\h__\h] yeah oh I gotta steal everything
yeah steal everything
yeah she sucks there's also so much
bread yeah take the bread bread
buttered buns yeah
we do like buttered buns yeah households
I had a I had a bunch of bread today
I love butter Ed bread
cucumbers and what do you call the uh
um
the long stringy
chives chives butter bread chives isn't
that the best thing
I never understood putting butter on
bread I think it's weird
what you're weird
[Music]
I'm weird but it's like butter on
pancakes too is so weird to me yeah that
I wouldn't do either
thank you
there you are because butter is like a
salty thing I associate like but I would
like jam and stuff so oh but we can
still work with the butter and there's
unsalted butter I do like garlic bread
though oh yes
okay hi
oh thanks
I look like I could be related to you
actually
I feel prettier oh thanks tell me where
the girl is no we can't I think I'll
stay a while I don't think we care about
the girl
leave
oh you'll end up in tonight's gym she's
gonna eat us or I'll make you try it
we'd like to see you try marinating
Marine I don't care we're gonna go in
and do it oh there's a lot of funky
things here what's that is that a
headless person oh
it's pretty wacky wait what did I
perceive I perceived something but I'm
gonna talk to this guy over here my
sweet Callum
family portrait for some reason it made
me talk to the tree so I'm in a cut
scene I'm sorry yeah yeah that's the
presence within the door the coils can I
leave
through not again oh you see you see the
gallery it's walls lined with that
bodies and we have some others Twisted
yeah everybody's suffering yeah yeah you
feel like to cry
that's too bad she's got quite a few
prisoners okay I'm gonna leave so Cali
can do this but I want to talk to Lauren
oh
this guy gnarly yeah
what's wrong with him what's his problem
I see it I see what's happening
some type of spell
dead dead
shining he does look like Legolas
yeah he's a Legolas gone Gollum
mm-hmm
no no
can't stop can't then don't stop don't
stop just go your own way oh please
please
please please please
poor guy give him a hug
no
why are you so mean
Roar
attack
I'm gonna die
I always say such a sadist
must find me mile as he Twitches in
whimper
be nice to him
oh my eyes are so wide and kind
whatever you're seeing it isn't real
nice
moriope would never lie to you
why are you talking like this
he's cursed like the others this is
nonsense
oh I mean his stuff together always say
and it's not oh separated
everyone looks like you do elf it's
shocking I know
[Laughter]
it's so beautiful
this guy must have been inspired by
Colorado mind player
I'm not a mine you're so mean
you think you get him to not be a piece
of [\h__\h] later but we have to continue uh
so why don't you look at this door Mario
Fame all right gnarled door
open sesame
as the presence within the door
it can't let people nice ass
thanks this is pretty good we could just
stay here and look at this for a while
but yeah honestly time to chat
you have like good leg muscles too
paladins very nice
shrouded in the glow of the Divine
weapons brandished they charge Into The
Hags layers
that's a decade for each you're mine for
30 more years
nice leg what the heck will be the least
your problems if you don't open up
cheers
Roar
little ogre Roar
the door shutters imagining its hidden
frame cracking
it's glittering I wish that other guy
would shut up
you feel the presence within shrink
terrified
oh the door open
oh don't look
open oh
oh
should be easy to find her from here
right
can you get in Kiara gotta suck into the
door no I didn't get it
why not gallery
why can't you you don't you just just
walk through you don't need to you don't
need to talk to it that's what I thought
okay now now I can now I can there you
go
onward
[Music]
let's go run it ladies
let's go time to battle some randos yeah
non-lethal attacks random people fight
they have to die
yeah
[Music]
um
who can I read They're possessed but
in Irish I probably gotta go anyway
incredible nice well there was something
in the way
it's going up I want to go apparently I
don't know if this is true but they are
saying pickpocket the masks and save
them oh yeah I picked up some masks well
we don't pickpocket the masks like take
the masks from them via pocketing
rescue them yeah I think I don't know oh
it sounds not possible I guess we can
turn on non-lethal
it's it's an insta kill when you steal
the mask but we want to kill them no
never mind then yeah let's kill him oh
cool
fair and square
sounds good to me
do it
oh she really doesn't want to ah
no I feel like I feel kind of bad
murdering all these people yeah
it's kind of complicated to not kill
them
we'll go ahead and kill them yeah no one
will know it's all happening down here
in the cave no one will know yeah no one
needs to know yeah our little secret our
little murder Secret
murder secret married
owie
are you scared I jump here only a little
bit you shake I mean I'm frightened oh
wait you're not wearing any boots
yeah yeah Reckless attack
Sandy you and then
another frenzied scratch on you
nice nice that was pretty sick
ah there we go whoops nice they're
knocked out I should just kill him
hey or just just take the masks uh you
know oh give it a go yeah good idea
behind people yeah
everybody's in such good shape in this
game yeah
I love it
he's not very smart is he
yeah yeah
cool yeah
oh nice sure I think we can wear the
masks
that seems not great
yeah you've got a good point
ah okay maybe for coffee yeah
maybe I mean
do they carry anything besides the masks
a little bit but nothing garlic
I take slime bomb
let's see there must be another hey over
here oh
find something
this is a waterfall we can jump through
it oh exactly did not I thought that we
could not go through there yeah we have
to jump I see
oh my gosh
this place
yeah
um I would not short rest until we get
all the way down
yeah hold on my game is glitched oh no
okay
I'm fine
Jordan failed cannot join the party what
eh
it's really weird are you very a game
no it's just every time I say except it
like glitches out
I have to restart my game okay a good
thing I just saved yeah yeah yeah but
gotta restart the game no problem no
problem thanks that's gonna be a big
yikes for me bye
bye bye that was super weird
very super weird
oh God
some glitches here and there we can take
it I mean for the most part it's really
not that bad yeah usually you still run
into him as you do with anything play
game
all right I'm pulling it back up okay
and I'll invite you guys back okay yeah
okay
[Music]
please sing it for me Cali
oh Down Down By The River Why do I still
have a morning voice
[Music]
today the throat yeah Valen it's crazy
yeah yeah does it hurt when you talk
it doesn't hurt but it does feel like a
bit of a struggle to speak sometimes
well while we're doing this I'm gonna
quick run and take an idol meeting so
I'll be right back okay I have your
snacks ladies
grab your snacks
we'll be and then I'll invite the ladies
hmm
mommy is not done streaming
cute yeah
invites a game
[Music]
I invited everybody thank you
is this movie yes
gosh
back in the game
yeah working now
where are we okay here
oh nerissa only has 21 HP
oh that's not great maybe a short rest
wait no wait don't don't short rest
until we get down there yeah when I can
throw them maybe she can bring a portion
of healing
oh
maybe big rest we might want a big rest
before we do this okay
I'm fine with that interesting time let
me see
actually
I've returned welcome back hi
thank you oh
we have to leave the the tea house
though because it's not safe here to
rest
um yeah really yeah oh yeah cause the
map is red yeah
okay
we can always come back though right
yeah yeah
I'm here nothing bad will happen surely
potion of animal speaking yay I wish I
was real
I know right
right
let's get out of here mm-hmm
we can see for your fancy Magic
lady
please
oh he's still talking
yeah yeah
Legends say he is still talking to this
day
oh we can rest up here
yeah
alrighty ladies to the camp we go
[Music]
yay
oh will wants to talk I wanted to chat
someone want to talk to him
I'll I'll talk
see look you have a button let's rest
but I need some Botox
Charming
thank you
older Raven guards been taken who's
older
I don't know
oh that's the guy who the who were
supposed to rescue the fire yeah and if
I rebuilding yeah oh okay the one that
died no no they they said he was
kidnapped and that we needed to get him
back remember okay and then he got the
bow
if Floric says he lives then he lives
and we need to free him from his captors
oh
Grand you Graven God is my father
I know I haven't said
our relation was no matter of pride not
least for him oh
um
what do we say
and the choice is clear we should rescue
Duke ravenguard that means a lot but
what about
ravencraft a Duke of Boulder gates are
contrasting to the drows around don't
have little use of my father
[Music]
these absolute Nutters these true songs
he could lead Boulder's Gate to ruin
all the more reason to find him
father but the future of the Soul it was
kind of cute
yeah
um
you should keep secrets like this for me
will I know and you're right you're
right yeah
the coast
a memory of a memory a man who belongs
to the Past
I wanted you to know the blade not the
shadow he left behind
deep [\h__\h] okay
just for you
okay what else nobody else wants to talk
I think yeah yeah yeah he's asking he's
asking I told him someone was looking
for him
uh
but yeah why because kazador sent him
why else tell me about this Hunter he
always sounds so ended whenever he talks
I know
something ferocious surely
um
a girl what are those vagabonds why
would they I suppose I shouldn't be
surprised what do you know about the
children
yeah about the kids man but why send
anyone after me
um
maybe he wants to make an example of me
to show what happens to runaways well
maybe he thinks death is too good for me
I mean true
um we just have to be vigilant people
always about us
and kill any Monster Hunters on site
I love Monster Hunter ah you do is he
really I do I'm not good at it though he
just called me beautiful
[Applause]
I'm gonna kill you
narissa and shambles
all right you got your friend zoned More
Time Lord
oh [\h__\h] what the hell no she's coming oh
no she's coming I remember this part
yeah oh
if evil white hot well
you've been naughty and you know what
happens when you're naughty Gods damn it
anyone but her
uh aren't you a luscious thing
get out of my camp now
but I'm just getting comfy
call me
I'm Will's Patron the fount of his power
will has a patreon my pets I guess he's
a warlocks have like Patriots I think
oh
whoa she's in control
but carlock's still breathing
I've taken more pleasant shits than you
mizor yay
buried after that's no kind of thing
by the way Carlock
Ariel sends her regards shut up mizora
don't even mention Rosario
Devils only
she's a tiefling not a monster oh
precious that vocal delivery is really
good but his face does not match rules
Target shall be limited to The Infernal
the Demonic the heartless and the
soulless
karlak meets the criteria by virtue of
having no heart
[Laughter]
you better not lay your damn finger on
Carla don't you worry yeah oh they all
approve failed the sticks
no did you find pop must still pay his
price
to wait
no
uh
well Birds
gaining their essence
[Music]
like the will
I mean oh is there any way to attack her
in the camp
no come on game oh he just got horns
they're not bad
I'm still looking great he got horny
bonked
I like that what the hell
good a price paid
you know the terms get used to the new
form Pat
there's no going back some magic even I
can't undo then why would you do it
can't wait to kill her he is fair
without that yeah
I have a swimsuit with a cut like her
dress oh yeah
wow I worked okay for me oh and
oh now it's Darian wants oh oh so many
people want to talk I've ever listen to
First
oh yeah bro you can't do this
again
don't do it something you gotta do for
the content
[Music]
is brilliant that's what I deserved
if you let me keep commenting the
joining failed cannot join the party is
full no companions can be dismissed
I mean the games
I'm gonna commit to puku
and then you continue
all right well hold on a second uh we
might need to
uh
am I gonna get jump scared with
something lewd
this glitch is really bad
before like last time yeah it's the same
thing
we have to redo everything yeah we can
just get past the tags too yeah yeah
this is really annoying
I don't know why what's your screen look
like
oh my God uh
it says it just
it's like how do I describe can't join
party full oh okay okay
and then it flashes again all right well
now we wait to be invited again yeah I
guess so
we shall save more often now if this
happens again yeah well we I mean look
all we did was reload go to Camp do that
scene and then you know so we we really
haven't lost a lot of progress
yeah but here's the thing I can switch
to mouse and keyboard that's fine but
I'm gonna have to relearn the game
I mean that's what people are saying but
I don't know
um
it's so easy yeah
yeah well point-and-click yeah it's just
point and click yeah ain't no party like
a pomori party because the Maury party
is small and no companions
[Laughter]
your mouth
oh very odd well maybe if I stop using a
controller it'll work all right let me
get you guys back in the game shall we
yeah
we'll redo the will scene we'll have to
retalk will first and then we'll have to
do that again
Molly talk to hysteria narissa no I
refuse
girls
it's for the content Kiara
are you talking about it's for the
concert you're just so crazy I didn't
expect that from you nerissa you're the
one that had nudity turned off on the
game whereas I kept it on let's not go
there no I put it on what do you mean
let's not go there
the horny Patrol here and let me tell
you it's not me
thank you
oh
see how do I go how do we go to the camp
oh we gotta get out of here yeah
listen powers
okay well let me switch back over to
game shall we
bless you thank you
sometimes
go away yeah we're going okay chill dude
all right let's see map
map ping is it map salute you cannot
fast travel from this area oh we gotta
leave it yeah yeah we have to walk out
again
okay
are you guys talked will I'm just gonna
tell Starion again about the guy same
text Skip through
I'll get up will
are you guys at the camp wait wait yes
wait for him
I have no clue where
please hold on camera
oh this is so weird to control
how do I zoom around do I how do you Pan
the oh there we go you can rotate it
like that
oh
maybe was it back up here up here I'm
coming to pick
you don't have to it's it's okay oh
there it is
got it there's the door
yeah no one left behind me
all right
hey thanks
hey
let's go
enjoying the camera will be a little
it'll be a learning process but we'll
figure it out
called me Stinky oh that's not nice if
you are a little stinky no I I took a
shower today
okay there you go thank you now which
which key do we press to go to the
camera press the campfire icon and then
hit go to camera with your mouth yeah oh
I see almost everything Clickety click
and I think Kiara already talked to will
yeah I did so yeah after she's done
talking to Carla we can just go sleep
redo that cutscene
recognizing
I don't want to bond with Carla anything
I'm so desperate for a hug as this one
[Music]
it's mine
what does that remind me of oh here we
go
okay ready for sleep anytime yeah I'm
ready
and the day nothing is in the day what
does that remind you
but huh Tesla variety I think we talked
about this before
and oh is it me again okay um
uh get out of my cam I'm trying to say
the same things again
yeah yeah
don't touch Carlos
yeah
he's going wild it's getting crazy
oh that's it right yeah and then
I mean I don't know what else to tell
you bro
I can't live any longer if you were
raised the Starion right now I'll talk
more
I'm talking to will okay good everybody
has a nice conversation did you manage
to keep your mind clear enough to fight
I've been thinking about our lives
together I can't I can't stand you
very
you know dangerous
I mean I guess I'll come find you after
everyone is asleep
I guess
hello
she's happy
we're all uh doing our best here
well narissa was trying to do was very
homey like Anyway this whole time she's
trying to steal your man like what the
hell
I'm getting Shadow heart plot
she's always hurting
I'd be lying if I told you no cause
Snoop on you guys this conversation but
don't worry
can't hurt you
only me
just is that supposed to be Shadow heart
sometimes time yeah nothing to be
concerned about
she's just it's nothing to do with the
tackles at least in case your
imagination is in danger of getting away
from you
it's just something I have to live with
oh yeah I get you
how how are you okay
quite a lot if I'm being honest
but it always passes quickly so I can
manage
baby oh that's the kitty cat oh hi
I watched Garfield today
it was cute I know fluffy I don't
understand how exactly but I felt it go
to you
it's important we're gonna get another
Memorial face soon
I don't know if I want that to be honest
I mean you don't have to watch are they
still making out I do
but the artifacts
okay somebody else is really like he
won't let me take it back
the best I can do is to stay close
real Snoopy eventually I'll need to take
she complained about Garfield not
showing his balls
dad said you complaining cats balls are
pretty all right aesthetically pleasing
when they do like uh drawings of cats
and they include the little cat butt and
the little cat you know
Jewels
there's a round and plump you know
they're cute Garfield didn't have that
and there was so many shots of his like
back where you could only see his big
chunky stomach and not not the balls
though it was like something's missing
why can't we go to sleep
canceling
I'm not casting oh
goodness gracious
this is a great
this is a great time to go ahead and let
you guys know that time to look at a
cutscene
um should I get big for this
maybe I have a big announcement you guys
oh
great news everybody
go ahead yeah yeah it's the Vine
let's go
um yeah I asked I asked ahead of time
the ladies said that I could oh yeah it
is showing her oopsies
um it was it was secretly secretly shown
there just kidding huh it's not a secret
because you guys definitely saw it right
um oh God the bgm is so loud sorry
I asked I asked the others permission to
be allowed the show because I have to
because in about in about seven minutes
my my brand new Ep jigo 6 the EP is
being released in a big old record what
uh look at this it's vinyl
single vinyl record this is the chill
hours by the way everybody's gonna show
some stuff hopefully everybody so
yeah check it out you guys in about
seven minutes correct so be sure that
you check the link there's gonna be a
big old big old Link in the description
check it okay
yeah you grab it before it's gone
because I don't know if we'll restock
this bad boy so you wanna you wanna get
it quick you guys you'll want to get it
quick
let's go
thank you you guys thank you
yes the Mori store thank you thank you
thank you
it's the Morris for you guys Maury store
has really fast shipping by the way the
more we start you have a more store yeah
there's like a universal Universal made
it uh it's a Mori store that ships
um do they ship to Europe
I'm not sure I I think it does
does it ship to Europe because I know I
have EU Beats I don't know I don't know
if it ships fast but to Europe but oh
it's a U.S base I think it depends on
the country but oh yeah it does ship to
Europe but um it's it probably won't be
fast
um that's fun worldwide
but I never wanna
one person who's like those are shipped
to my country
sorry I messed up I made a mistake
anyway you guys can get it I have a
couple more images to show sorry for
people that aren't on my stream that
can't see big story there are two
calories to check if you want to see
pictures of it you want to click the
link in the description it'll take you
to where it's going to be sold
um but yeah it kind of looks like this
and then uh there's some of uranta's art
that's also going to be included it says
sample on it because no no thieves No
Stealing oh no yeah no thievery no
thievery Ellis
yeah then you can be and
that's totally cool that's totally cool
no problem
um let me get the link I don't know if
if the if they're gonna paste the link
in it hold on a second I'm gonna put the
link in the description myself because I
am my own master
and I can I can do my own multitasking
yeah I sure can so yeah that was what I
wanted to um promote for today
yeah the description is now updated so
grab your cards
somewhere else
hey just kidding uh but it is really
cool it makes a nice decoration piece
you can frame it you can play it on your
phonograph
Etc so please check it out
um who's next on the the show the show
yeah
in the game afterwards we're not by the
way
we're gonna keep playing designated
yeah
there used to be timing I'm so bad yeah
the very sorry could not change it
but uh Kiara's next yeah I recently
released an album it's still open for
pre-order uh link is also in the
description if you want to get the
physical version and oh surprise
actually today I released the Korean
version of do you oh so good yeah
because it was actually one year
anniversary of do you so I thought let's
make a Korean version because it already
sounds like K-pop let's go yeah so album
and uh Korean version of do you and
pineapple MB is still out there to be
streamed yoroshiku please please take a
look at it and yeah keep on streaming
the album so because it's my first one
so I hope it can do well
yoroshiku hey everybody it's great
there's something for everybody on it
yeah it's my first my first ever
physical like music thing because all my
singles before are like online only
digital only
and this one you can actually get as a
physical thing yeah so very special
yeah yeah that's it stream point of view
point of view
anything else
um let's see oh uh this Friday or
Saturday depending on what time zone
you're in uh but Saturday for uh c
um I'm going to be appearing at Thai
Comic Con oh yeah uh it's so cool yeah
it'll be my first panel ever so I'm kind
of really nervous about it but um I'm
calling my mom so she you know coach me
and teach we're speaking Thai better so
I can I can talk to everyone I'm really
nervous but I'm excited uh a lot of fees
thank you
okay that's it for me
cool that's so cool that you so quickly
get a con appearance that nice nice nice
I hope you get to speak some Thai let's
go
Flex those skills yeah not a flex
I apart from my streaming schedule I
don't have anything I have a collab with
bibu next week I think tomorrow wait no
just now
yeah a thought where we're going to talk
about the first night that we spent
together oh yeah
yeah
details we will so please be sure to be
their typical time at 8pm C team
song covers yeah yeah check out my song
covers so I can release another one
yeah that's all for me
ladies being busy with putting out
things so support us yeah everybody's
working hard to give you guys cool stuff
so hell yeah yeah thanks for for
supporting did you try to talk watch him
again
I'm talking to everybody oh God I'm just
saying this morning so [\h__\h] funny
oh man let me fix my little sensor image
get right in front of me
it's nice weather the blade of Frontiers
he's horny just like you what
is this I mean horny as and he's got
horns now
good morning girl
might make a really good point I spent
more time dueling with fun I heard you
were making fun of me in your stream in
your member stream Kiana I always asked
for good work what and the talent for
court
[Laughter]
what's up
give it some time I'm sorry that no
one's talking to you are you lonely
Maybe
[Laughter]
he brings to mind a story
the Devil with the silver tongue old
fairy tale my father wait Marissa did
you hear about it or are you a member
[Music]
the farmer's dearest fruit naturally was
no apple no Peach
we can learn a lot from fairy tales
why is he acting like this
I mean the dude just got transformed
yeah
and given the circumstance
I do it again
my soul was a necessary price to pay for
you know I can't say more oh but I can
say sorry little guy I had but one road
I could travel
for now you have a dozen the hundred
a thousand to choose from
a room yeah this really wants to make
you this makes you want to play more on
my own
I know right let's see all what happens
to all the characters and stuff exactly
yeah
there's such a different game playing
waves in the river of blood emerging
finally someone approved of something I
did it's a lot like this
I can't please everyone's on my head
please anyone
anyone I mean I feel these ridges
snaking down my neck you're just too
sexy
I was just born that way man I haven't
seen my reflection just yet
be my mirror what do you see oh horns
hot dude
or die handsome devil it's because you
know the heart lurking under the horn oh
she's trying to raise them up
maybe even a beast hungry but will do
you understand that she is also tiefling
now yeah like
what are you talking trying to lecture
and I'm like hello
there's so many there's so many I said
he approves every time I talk to him
he really answers it's getting those
points out well yeah yeah I gotta you
gotta get my approval up even though we
can't check because we can't put them on
our team new child crying out from alone
yeah for real I found him in the Fields
flanked by goblins you just gotta
believe his mother's corpse corpse bled
into this you know what if the approval
only goes to moriope
is she just blessed
with some kind of special magic I mean
I don't know loriopia is friendships
tomorrow
so long for me to see the coast
suffering so I want to understand why
there's two of Gail
don't question it I I am questioning it
don't question it and it's nice to meet
someone it's just the thing that he does
having a worming in my skin does that
sometimes it's in the days ahead no with
you as my Ally the future looks a little
oh he's sweet yeah I heard this before
we count the snakes you want to play the
hero and be the nice character in the
game will is perfect
YouTube
[Laughter]
it could well be if you could clone
yourself wouldn't you what a good
argument which is simply I mean yeah but
what would you do with the clone of
yourself if you had one make it do your
chores what if I had a mindfulness
she'll have to let me you want to make
out with yourself Kiana
what kind of we're standing here with
nothing but the clothes on our backs I
mean you know yourself best don't you
I'm sorry one of my jailbirds just said
something funny and I need to repeat it
to you guys but they said you should
have turned a Starion into the Monster
Hunter and gone the full yandere round
oh my [\h__\h] god
that would be pretty funny actually we
almost turned it man
yeah maybe next playthrough yeah next in
Another Universe I'm sure of it no I
refuse I would never it's okay
I already tag myself every single one of
our one of our things one of the
companions I'm too attached to all of
them I don't want anything that to
happen to them we should go out we
should leave the camera yes let's leave
let's leave let's go kill the head yeah
and kill the hag yeah long rest leave
Camp okay back down gotta learn how to
play again
mm-hmm oh yeah yeah let's go
do you do you say you do feel the same
see I cloned myself and do you already
if you remember yeah yeah but we're
making out with yourself
they weren't they were they were raising
each other up yeah it was like a mating
dance exactly oh my God
no you were rizzing me up you were
asking me if I did I remember I remember
was she talking about it's just going
crazy can someone calm her down
okay
[Laughter]
the noxious oh is this a bug where you
don't see them
I had that bug before that can't be good
do you see the fumes girls no no
okay that's nice actions have both
where's Kelly
I I just figured out how to jump
let us know
okay thanks
just point point
wherever you want to go
often they will just find their way
and learn how to use the camera you're
like a little baby bird how the camera
checks I'm getting used to but now I
would not change my former Child Play
for anything oh what's this event yeah
at least I figured it out yeah yeah we
can like throw something on it that's
normally we should we have a like a
graphic glitch right now I think
normally we should be seeing like fumes
um wait for everybody do a short rest
before we go in didn't we just do a long
yeah short rest and then heal
all right let me figure it out okay
oh okay yeah
if you want to see like items press alt
and you see what's lying around yeah
oh yeah alt currently you don't there's
nothing really around okay got it I'll
remember that
okay all right onward let's get it okay
ready let's find stuff yeah it does in
the cage you want me to kill you maybe
do we care about her
I mean it would be cool to save a life
but I mean we don't have to
attractive yeah yeah we don't wait we
can just you know
go with the flow yeah
oh I see where the wind takes that hello
hag hello
I'm gonna attack her wait wait wait wait
wait longer Bros
oh I'm sorry I thought it dragged
everywhere I'm sorry no no no no no
you know
I'd like to see you try keep you alive
I'm gonna go over here
I don't think that that'll work
the one that
you can shoot several people
I killed your brothers why do you care
about me
shut up she doesn't care about you
yeah but she says just get out of here
please like she has any kind of concerns
me shut the [\h__\h] up
shut her ass
she does
oh that was like half my health yeah
good luck remember you have potions so
mean even though I killed the fan uh I
guess I guess I'll save her here you go
so we gotta figure out which one's real
it's where I had to get rid of them
maybe I don't I guess we'll Frenzy
someone want to attack one of them I
already did I got rid of one another one
saved the girl oh
gross okay I won't do that spell yet
then shame
oh
okay
uh they're so far
[Music]
okay
making clones
yeah I can't breathe
what a cute birdie is that yours Kiara
yeah I brought a raven into the party
Raven Marissa
oh my God it's like you like me or
something there's a murderer
right
a group of is it or is it only crows is
there a difference between the group of
crows and a group of ravens a murderer
yeah
it's an uncleanness the Ravens and I'm
kind yeah
group of animal names so funny
let's see I wish they were invisible no
wait it's the one that's not wet it's
the one that's not wet is actually her
because like I made okay actual her way
the wet one I can beat up
no the one that's not what you can beat
up
oh okay the one the one that's wet I
should not yeah the one that is what is
the one that I saved
okay yeah okay let's see where is the
other one
oh yeah right uh-huh
um
yeah the one that's on level one versus
the one that's on level five yeah oops
that's not what I meant to do but all
right actually I didn't need to do that
either
um
oh
[\h__\h]
well I made our decision easier yep we
made a decision
happens to the best of us it was the
other way around
it's fine it's fine brain empty
let's go there
she's really not that helpful anyway
oh yeah cause like when you save her
she's like super ungrateful apparently
okay
I mean
validly yeah
I mean well yeah because we did kill her
family so I kind of feel yeah you you
killed me but like when you find out her
motivation
he was here by her own you know choice
so she didn't really want to be saved
yeah
so you kind of interfered and then you
know she doesn't mean thank you for
something she didn't ask for she she
doesn't have anything to live here
anymore anyway but you're right
yeah I'll use an action equip
they need help Kelly not letting me what
happened oh no oh what's going on
I'm just kidding I don't have any more I
get it and turn
nice
this is terrible oh
damage let me be useful someday
that's a bit much oh this is going up
there please
annoying I'm just better with weapon you
know
[Music]
um
Go Raven go
rage color
tell her
oh let's go we're doing it guys
figuring it out it's all coming together
oh man I need to get on the high high
ground
yeah
and me and your Raven are beating her up
it's sick let's go none my Raven didn't
do [\h__\h] no he's trying yeah
good luck
I mean bro
this ends well
[Music]
upset
yeah now you're bleeding
she's wet right now yeah she's wet yeah
guys did just realized the girl that we
killed there was a child inside of her
body oh
um
that's no good
um I'll keep that in mind for my
personal playthrough I guess
please kind of forgot about that oh
what
I find a way to return
and you wouldn't be begging for your
life right
so how about we be civilized about this
hmm
I have something you want
um what are you gonna do moriope
continue I want to hear what you're
carry
anything you want you want to be
stronger tougher smarter done
just let me go ability
I mean that's kind of cool we can just
beat her up again if she comes back to
life
give me power the more the better give
me power choice
here
sad yeah
I can set up shop elsewhere people
always need lotions and potions
I mean
get out of here before I change my mind
if I ever see you again you'll be
fertilizing this swamp if I ever see him
again
now that we have an understanding peace
maybe strength min max the strength I
think
yay um the marina necklace
yeah well maybe it'll be useful someday
yeah
yay yay a small price to pay yes
what are you gonna what what are you
gonna go for drinks
big smashies I don't know what these are
all these potions potions potions take
them
free potion everything
I don't know take it
pick everything
it teleports you if you go there
all right then shall we get out let's go
all right you guys got everything right
yeah
okay
yeah okay that was interesting hey hey
where could we be
back in the swamp yeah
oh coffee that's her her guy
um Marina's
can someone talk to the Dead
yeah uh maybe you gave me a thing that
helps me talk to the devil yeah you have
you should have a talk to the dead
necklace
it's a necklace I think
yeah you're wearing it so you should
have it in your skill bar yeah it says
rare speak with the Dead
um in my skill oh yeah there it is
let's go
all right speaks of the Dead
hold on let me turn turn it around I bet
I can oh yeah narissa also has the
ability now because she read the book
that gives her the speak to the dead
ability
I don't know how to use it cast spell
oops okay
it must be playable character
I don't know did I eat it oh I think
it's because the girl's dead that you
can't continue this
um
that's rough that's that's rough buddy
I mean I understand though it makes
sense but
um
I have her necklace should I leave it
with him no just wear it nurse something
if I wear it maybe he thinks I'm her no
that is Undead not dead so apparently
he's a zombie
ah okay I see well
that's that I guess what do we do next
what do we do next
I'll leave it up to you good question
something short well this is short oh I
guess we could go to the underdark
didn't we go there last time
yeah but we know we entered briefly yeah
definitely want to get some health back
maybe a short rest sell United yeah
cello night
s
how do I quick travel
um
and then click solo night Outpost
okay don't go so fast Cali is not even
here oh I'm just gonna grab a weapon and
then I'll be back okay I have a weapon
[Music]
it's a Bard sword
the one that's right by the entrance
just don't get into trouble
I'll try
um
little swords the stone before you
keeping a silent vigilance
[Music]
grant for us narissa with another I'm
gonna get it
the weapons slips yeah we killed that
dude to the Minotaur I'm not gonna go in
I'm just gonna look at what he has
nothing just kidding
[Music]
yay Bard sword
am I solo play for what came to the
underdark from a different place and I I
wasn't able to enter where we're
standing in right now I just explored
everything outside
I think the staff line here from here
you need to collects like three pieces
or something
from oh from people Apple I think
yeah there's a staff of the Moon Maiden
what's that
oh fancy
all right
I think I know a good place where we
could go here in the underdark okay okay
lead the way the Mushroom City mushrooms
I love
that sounds cool mycelium it's not what
it's called oh my God
whoa earthquake we just gotta get down I
don't know where the weight is
isn't that a sign of the that monster oh
yeah let's go oh yeah
was it oh
let's get out of here let's keep walking
let's keep moving okay
okay we're here
I don't know I see what I'm seeing eh
yeah no
okay
oh that's crazy still your mind
there's a voice talking to you
okay he's done coming
now we can go
a big deal there comes who cares I ain't
afraid of no ghosts
penny
looks like I have three elicited
[Music]
oh what's this
oh
stop
nice stuff
whoa Olympic Powers I haven't actually
used these yet
um concentrated black yeah I haven't
used these yet either is that grunt oh
yeah there's a Minotaur up there I've
used one oh I just used one
oh yeah remember we are they all
combined we all share that yeah okay
well good thing I didn't use more oh I
just used one
oh yeah one as well
use your listen
uh
click click on your inventory
and then you see the little things in
the Middle top of the page that opens up
click on the one that says a lithid
powers
and you can read you can you can manage
to lith that it'll bring you to a brain
and you can clear but this one I thought
yeah we we had three
but we can find more there's a lot of
them in the game
okay so it's okay for me to use yeah
yeah we used one
we're all gonna share yeah um help check
which one do I pick
they're not shared yes they are
they absolutely are shared I mean we
don't all gain this name but we we
collectively all have the same amount
this is Minotaur up there
and
now there's only one left mm-hmm
all right eat The Witcher I know I
already ate the hair guys look at my
inventory wait wait okay look look up
here
it has been consumed
it's bad guys oh
you did your best
um
[Music]
what well that's okay we can do a ranged
attack
I'm just kidding it was not a difficult
position to start in yeah me too
well we'll get through it we'll get
through it
where is the second one
I'll find it
oh I'm surprised that hit I only had 55
percentage
we'll be fine we won't die well maybe we
will but it'll be sick
oh he doesn't have that much health this
will be fine yeah it will be fine you
know the middle doors
yeah yeah
I've killed myself
that's awful oh oh there's another one
it was just getting started
horse tunnel
okay
yeah back up okay wait I'm gonna put
something
here don't walk past it oh okay
[Music]
that's so broken I love it so much
oh he dead now oh yeah yeah no he's
super all right then next we just got
the other one yep just one more left
cool
tea
yes
[Music]
good teamwork okay here's a question of
something I haven't figured out how do I
turn off that
how do I do you see on the right side
concentration something something
maybe in your hot bar somewhere
like you're concentrating on it you want
it I have that no I don't I don't know
someone who does that what was it
bludgeoning yeah thank you damage
vulnerability to bludgeoning damage if
someone wants it
you can just take it from my inventory
yeah
in your inventory oh well I mean it's
all our inventors the parties
how about disarming first I disarmed one
if you would just wait I take this hat
in your inventory Cali
shake it okay I'll take it if you want
something just fast you can probably
take it whoa what happened there
did you just I broke it I broke down
guys why did you crawl up
the roomba's going crazy guys yeah
oh I can't get down yeah you can there's
a thing over here a mushroom jump on the
mushroom yeah like Mario
there you go there's stuff up here
though if you want to look goodies
yeah oh goodies I know this place I love
goodies
it's looting time
[Music]
useful friends
oh everything is locked everything is
locked yeah yeah
I can attack it oh
oh nice
Optimus fire
fire
[Music]
you girls being aggressive
oh my God
oh my God I cannot come on I can't set
wood on fire
I know
what if we just break it salutenberg
that one more thing
no
I'm disarming it oh it's got a trap oh I
got gotcha gotcha I didn't see it had a
trap on it I just disarmed it okay
here there you go
okay where I disarmed it but now we need
a key
let me I think there was like
around here
oh yeah yeah do your thing
oh there's skulls in here
nice rolls
it's a ring of fire eel worm today
I like that song so I don't blame you
break it off good man
break it
oh that's pretty sturdy
oh this should totally be possible
yeah there you go
I open sesame
open
all the good stuff Arrow of darkness and
arrow of ill modern oh there's an
elevator here but it doesn't work
yeah it's broken I already looted
everything here
okay okay it's like we got all the
goodies
all right let's go down
to uh mushroom land
I like mushrooms
I don't like to eat them but I like to
look at them
I would agree with that I was physically
pleasing yeah
mushrooms are great eating not so much
like mushroom dresses accessories or so
me too
a mushroom sauce I think I can still I
can still eat but just mushrooms that
are not in the sauce
oh that sounds good don't make me hungry
I'm gonna make you hungry you're gonna
feed me ah there's the people wait wait
yes yes you talk to the people okay yeah
hello
[Music]
are these little mushroom villagers
oh he's got a funny face a single Melody
right they all look so shiny beautiful
Frosty and
oh it's the warm Among Us world
same the sovereign
State your purpose
um
your best I am Adventure
[Music]
yeah there you go Welcome to the fungals
not as good as your cutie
not quite good enough
10th then we couldn't be a mushroom
person that would have been cool yeah
right
yay
well do you want to live in a mice
annoyed company
yeah you'd have to live here underground
that reminds me of
that's the that's the sovereign
shiny like you oh yeah
let's explore Village but follow one
person
yeah
who wants to lead the way I want to go
oh okay hello
oh is this a shop it says shop on the
map yes this is a shop
[Music]
ah a visitor you're a welcome blog what
a name
Cali someone in my chat is saying Cali
taking a compliment is she feeling okay
I can't see my face
yeah that's a big old hand in your face
member of the Society of Brilliance At
Your Service
does he have a worm I don't think so I
wonder
um
what's the Society of brilliant fun guys
he's a fun guy one place for long
ER
to improve conditions
this need not be such a dire
it's curious to find a surface dweller
here what has brought you down so deep
uh
wanna chill
um I'm lost
common phenomenon in the underdog I'm
afraid could I ask what you were
searching for to begin with
mushrooms uh
clean the whole story okay why not
here's my life story
we're infected by an enlisted tadpole
a miracle you're still intact you must
be worried sick but have no fear I have
a friend who may be able to escape
it is
inside her head
we're special
wait it's one of those guys yeah yeah
Tim shocking to have it
is this the one that is he the one oh
the one it's a nice one yeah let's have
them take out our tadpoles oh yeah try
um help
open your mind to me he seems friendly
let us yeah
it's kind of sad yeah totally let's do
it okay okay I trust you
all right let him in let's see if it's
that easy
word it fails ten times its size
awake yeah my smug
is most unusual
the incubation period
s transformation I think it seems nice
[Music]
wait is this the one you can beep
no ah okay that's bad what a shame
uh can you help
no
you're from physical and magical
influence and even without the shield
the extraction would involve severe
cranial trauma
crazy
um
that doesn't
house I have healing magic I intend to
go disrespect
but one can only heal so much of their
own
ah man
but not to worry
should you try oh well I don't want to
transform that's the whole point a
former New Examiner
I have never set foot on one myself
they were all warships during the
greatest eras of the illicit Empire We
Rule the entire astral plague from their
decks the design was lost when the gift
rebelled Dominion
interesting oh that's why they were
dragons or something
okay thank you I guess of course
I am sorry I cannot assist you in its
removal
what well Big Ups anyway
yeah no idea an idea an idea
oh you should start taking notes there
may be a way to bypass
there are many a chemical substances
substances
uh uh what are we talking about what
kind of alchemy
what a silly word right picture I like
that
sounds like sphincter
don't
ask spawns
why are you sound so surprised you
ruined it no I don't like it anymore of
these mushrooms can be
quiet
cause confusion
that approach them the tongue is
self-explanatory you have to eat a
tongue
you
um
okay lovely so where do I find this
mushrooms
underdark of
course recovery perilous hmm
I imagine Lenore would have them in her
possession she served mistra as a cleric
oh
all right where is she living the
Southwest when I last saw her although
her Tower does have a tendency to move
weird it's a lot interesting okay
continue she is quite fond of her garden
Lenore has always been a lonely sort
nature was her only companion I offered
her the Jones to join the society but
remember who asked you her experiments
on Susa he knows a lot yeah right okay
um
I'll I'll come back when I find them I
guess may your travels be safe I like
this too
they're nice
don't you dare don't don't steal don't
steal yeah not gonna steal but does
somebody need to sell some stuff oh yeah
let me sell stuff I'd like to biboo is
very full on her inventory yeah the
customs of the locals
I think after we're done like like we
can explore the city a little bit more
and then we could end it okay yeah good
a good place
proud member of the Society of
Brilliance At Your Service oh Cali's
talking
I mean I thought this was the shopkeeper
but he's like going through a bunch of
weird stuff right now yeah he first
wants to talk fight is far more complex
shopkeepers always so talkative why are
they so talkative
but I can I can sell him stuff
yeah
should be possible okay if you have
anything interesting to trade
all right let me make it quick oh I have
a lot of swords
if you have weapons though you can keep
them to throw teeth I know which is why
I kind of don't so good what about uh
sell all jewelry that isn't useful
correct yeah jewelry and all like
um
you could sell a lot of your great
swords and stuff can I throw the great
sword yeah
I might want to hold on to it then
I wanna know a fun trick
do we still have the girl we killed
no mintara I don't think so oh okay
because what you can do is you sell them
you can collect dead bodies and keep
them in your inventory and then you can
eat dead bodies for big damage because
they weigh a lot that's pretty awesome
yeah
we don't need the masks anymore right no
no okay away with you that would be
pretty cool I do like that that is
deadly
I enjoyed that one
um I'll sell all these poison apples
in my own playthrough I've been
collecting dead bodies yeah you can
collect them at my Camp so I can look at
them and remember my spoils oh it's
pretty base
when the wearer gains lightning charges
they also gain three temporary hit
points one of you guys might want that
oh this lighting charges help me because
I'm lightning
I think so
you should grab that I also have a
weapon that gives me Lightning charges
automatically
so oh nice now you could really use that
so maybe you should buy that after I'm
done in here
on my shoes actually
yeah he's selling something called the
lifebringer it's like a tiara looking
thing two hour four lead hour
Tiara for Liara oh
just give attack and damage bonuses to
anyone so it's good to have yep in
general
uh and then I have to do math oh gosh
okay you can just press the button at
the bottom the to balance it
oh I see yeah
there we go wow that's so nice I didn't
notice that okay
all right I'm done
yeah
do your shop stuff
welcome back
[Music]
what a silly little guy Private
Collection such a silly little guy
indeed
wow I can't look at what's in the chest
without like opening it and stealing
right
no you will you will make everyone here
fight you don't do it not great
that's not great let me save really
quick I'm not gonna do it of course yeah
of course of course you're just thinking
about it no it's good because honestly
here I kept accidentally clicking on the
barrel stock and they will all attack
you if you do that because they think
you're trying to steal
not pleasant
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
the Mind flare can remove your tadpole
if you talk to them oh yeah but why
would I want to do that
okay I'm good
all right okay I'll try again really
quickly too that is not true really
quickly yeah no they're lying don't
listen to them
oh one guy the head could have removed
it though it would have not tried to
kill her
really yeah
[Music]
yeah which is why I kind of don't want
to give it up
yeah yeah but she would kiss your eye
and it would give you a special skill
too that you can only get from the hag
had you not intimidated her right away
I guess yeah
well sometimes we just got to be true to
the characters we play we could have
looked even cooler
the trader has no more no more money
okay uh wait oh no more money okay you
need to get rid of some stuff although
your weight looks fine you can still
carry it I know but I have an Ingot I
wanted to sell there's another Trader
down here oh
okay
oh they're both Merchants the weirdest
thing
oh
[Music]
yeah
hello oh I'm on my way to be coming down
why don't you need to trade
yeah but I okay
yeah balance his name Bello he's cute
he's cute
hello little buddy
you can talk to animals wait I have oh
yeah
are you guys killing people casting
he treats me good now oh yeah he doesn't
say much
lightning thing
yeah I guess I'll buy it he still has it
oh the hag can double your inventory
space that's wacky
yeah sounds tough though and complicated
you think so should I wear it guys
yeah wear what
the Chihuahua yeah Tiara for Liara hey
yeah it looks on you no one back home
well everybody
this one still breathing
oh did you grab it
um
uh grabbing now
okay I own it yeah that's all that
should be useful for your lightning
stuff
okay
yay
yay okay now he also got some money back
good for him
now are we all done trading
then let's we're done explore did we
talk to the guy first who wanted us to
talk to him yeah yeah
this way
up here you go up these uh mushrooms
here
hmm
the guy doing it I like this place hello
what is the creature doing to those oh I
know he's busting it down
what you doing
why don't you ask him don't bring this
thick
thing wow
from just like you that's the creature
she is
chopping my Canadian remake oh no
no I'm not showing people
right this is how I killed those chicks
in my anniversary video
yeah that was raw yeah that was crazy
Kelly you saw it
I mean yeah
Wild
Sunny
yeah
survival in the wild
we gotta beep up some people
uh
sure why not yeah we can help yeah
oh except this
oh no drugs
nice
shrimp powder mushroom does
the sovereign
do the circle of service
we will await word
Circle
um
what are you doing
knife into our enemies flesh
the dead make a fine host for my growing
okay understandable
[Music]
um
don't do it don't do it don't do it how
do I do that I want to learn
oh
all right at least he was honest
they dance to no other Harmony at least
he's honest yeah
okay real for that bye-bye
um but you know if there is a mushroom
you might want to kill I can lead you to
one
we want to kill a mushroom
yeah a mushroom guy okay you mean the
wait the dwarf yeah uh yeah
the fat one
um ah that one one kill him we bring him
with us
he's talking to me
he can sovereign
the other ones the other one's beautiful
this one's cute
no the other one's cuter
you better be nice to him narissa no
he's not cute he's an ugly bastard
is there something you want to admit to
us no he's grown secret projecting
what I don't know she's really
protesting quite a bit
she might be hiding Mario hey do you
have a problem with me see he wants to
join us
okay
we're not enjoying you but he's not
joining me
hmm
yes join yes you let him let him join
you yes he will be my new pet yes your
new pet
oh he's cute
[Music]
why do you think he's cute are you okay
because round animals teddy bear friend
shaped yeah huggable lovable ish I mean
yeah but he looks he looks sticky and
slimy yeah the other's doing too like
the mushroom in your fridge that you've
left in the Slime is fun though
yeah but not not rotting slime he looks
like he'd smell bad he doesn't look like
he's rotting
yes he does look at him when have you
ever seen a slimy mushroom and been like
that looks tasty I should eat that oh I
don't like slimy mushrooms they taste
bad yeah mushrooms yeah nice new friend
yay as long as we stay here
yum
yeah we just can't leave the on the dark
then he's gone yeah yeah but we're
staying here so all is good
what else is there to explore I don't
know much more because this is where I
ended my solo play for a reason there's
just a little oh it's just a village
basically there's not really much here
though to be honest hmm
should we like end it then for today
yeah okay and now we pick up so you
should be fine yeah we're trying to find
that stuff
yeah we made good progress
[Music]
there's still so much more yeah
never-ending content I might I might not
like stream every time that we play by
the way I'm drinking also because that's
fine
yeah that's how I felt last time if you
were on the early turn it's recommended
to not stream yeah definitely
but it was nice to hear your sleepy
voice yeah
eat like some mushroom pasta get
something in my throat it isn't just
water help it wake up still not awoken
what that was that was fun you guys yeah
very effective today efficient I mean
yeah yeah I'm gonna show my EP again
check out the description
and in the chat grab the new EP it's for
sale and we probably won't restock it so
go grab it
um and yeah that's all I have to say
thanks for coming today we have to set a
date for the next collab but it will
probably be at an a morning time again
like this morning okay so I might not
stream that one oh okay
let's discuss after this three months if
we can find a date that works for us
yeah
sounds good let's do it okay okay guys
you guys thank you for watching thank
you for watching everybody and for
supporting us we'll keep doing our best
still lots of fun things happening yeah
yeah see you soon see you soon everybody
okay
let's go let's go over did I adjust my
chatting today I don't remember uh well
let's see how it goes we
night oh yes I did yes I did but the the
text is wrong
[Music]
hi
thinking super let's think some supers
and then we can get out of here uh there
are a few things I wanted to say first
uh number one uh what schedule my
schedule might not come out today
it might come out tomorrow I am waiting
on permissions for a game that I was
gonna put on my schedule next week and
they haven't told me yet whether or not
I can the date that I set to play it is
okay so yeah I'm waiting for perms for a
game before yeah it's lies of pee
yeah is is lies of me I wanted to heck
and go into Liza P next week
um because I'm really really super super
super super super super excited for lies
of me
um but I I didn't get a confirmation on
what day I can play it yet uh so no
schedule until I get an answer about
that but I I do think I will have perms
to play it it's just the the date I
think I don't know what date I can start
yet but I do I think I will be able to
play it yeah yeah so that'll be a good
that'll be fun
um
but yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah why is
it pee I'm excited for it
um I've been really anticipating this
game apparently it was really good I I
didn't play the demo because I wanted to
like experience I don't really like
playing demos too much because I just
want to play the entire game you know
from like from everything so I have not
played it down but I've seen some of the
demo and it looks really really good and
I'm really really excited because it's a
Soul's light game that's been pretty
highly anticipated so I wanted to play a
lot of it next week so waiting on that
so uh please be patient uh for my
schedule I still need to await and
answer for that I'm trying to play it
tomorrow before the
um
Advent pull out next next yeah tomorrow
is garchick fun with Avant because I
have the Thai Comic Con on Friday so I
can't do
um normal Advent collab on Friday as
usual so that's why Advent was nice
enough to move our collab date to
tomorrow thanks
thank you thank you so we're gonna play
garchick phone with Advent tomorrow but
um if I can before garchick Fallen
hopefully I can still give me an answer
on Liza P so I can play otherwise we'll
do it the next day but yeah that's why
that's why the schedule has been delayed
a little bit but whenever I get it
um
I'll I'll tell you but I'll tell you a
few things
um plan on my schedule so that way
you'll know some of the important stuff
uh let's see Tuesday is narissa narissa
on her Channel we're doing azatsu of
like this talking and we finally get to
tell stories about
um when we like met up and like shared a
room
she makes it sound so sauce is really
not that sauce
but but we'll let her we'll we'll let
them believe that I mean
yeah what would you say oh yeah our
first we get to tell stories about uh
how we shared bed and our first night
together yeah
everything
yeah she says sound salsa yes so it's
kind of not
not a new a new a new thing but yeah so
we're gonna just talk and just hang out
on her channel on Tuesday Wednesday
and I are going to play portal we're
gonna finish I don't know how much a
portal 2 we have left with the co-op but
we're going to continue our portal to
play through on Wednesday yeah more
portals more portal yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
um
Thursday is this me day Friday is Thai
Comic-Con so I won't be streaming on
Friday but uh hopefully you guys can see
me in Thai Comic Con
um I'm gonna call my mom a lot this week
so she can coach me
um there was a little promo video that
Thai Comic-Con uh put out and I spoke a
bunch of Thai in it I spent like four
hours with my mom me like Mom help me I
want to sound good to all the time
people toy toy
[Music]
and she she helps me um
and a little bit yeah so yeah if you saw
the video thanks Mom
thanks Mom for helping me with that
um
so yeah I'm Gonna Keep practicing with
her and yeah
I at least somebody said she wanted to
talk some more time with me too because
I'm doing the panel with Louis Senpai
um so she talked with me a little bit
and I'm excited to talk to Louis Senpai
in Thai uh I'm nervous though see I
think she thinks I'm good at it but I'm
not that good at it but you know you
sound fine her outfit I love her new
outfit is so pretty her new outfit is so
is so pretty so pretty
um okay and then
and then yeah that's that's on uh Friday
Friday night for me but Saturday or
see Saturday for Thailand time oh yeah
yeah yeah
so I'm kind of nervous to talk to her
but but I'll do my best I'll do my best
and then the weekend and the weekend we
have two ourselves but yeah so that's
that's the plan for this week
um well I I really want to do lots of
lies of e this week because I really
really want to get into it I'm so
excited for lies a piece hopefully pray
please pray that I can play it okay I'm
gonna think some supplies and then we'll
head off back for today also don't
forget
is
um today at 8pm I'm gonna be watching
I'm so excited for it
I'm gonna be supporting her I love
coroni I love fauna
fun is 3D debut yesterday
[Music]
all her songs were perfect all her songs
that she picked were perfect she killed
me all the songs she did I loved like
um the Toradora song ow my heart the
Kamisama Kiss song ow my heart all of
them her let me stay here I was like
yeah because that's my favorite song
um of of of how I let me stay here and I
was like yeah
and I loved her memes and everything
yeah I really really loved her uh 30 day
real
yesterday it was so nice she was so old
and then and then she slapped us she
slapped us I can't wait until I get an
actual slap are you jealous are you
jealous guys she said she would slap me
I know you're jealous
I know you're jealous she said she would
slap me when we
um do an awful lot one day
Maybe
it's not fair anyway let me take the
stupas from today
um
I will save
Kyla senpai's Minecraft supers for
another day uh let me get to today's
supers and then
I'll head off for the day
um so I can I want to rest a little bit
before before
cronies
dinghy before clony's thinking
[Music]
yeah maybe
redirect to her anyway even though it's
two hours from now you'll stay right
you'll stay in there you'll stay in
there right
this this will get redirected and then
just stay stay
stay
stay yes chef let me hear some yes chefs
and chat yes yeah okay let me thank you
[Music]
thank you I'll be foreign
Region Pokemon that eats rocks and Gem
all I know about Sableye stabilize a
little scary but table light has like
gems in his face so he's not that bad
right
right they will lie I like Mega
symbolize cool yes my baldness I am not
bald what do you what do you mean
thank you Mr foreign
[Music]
what is it what was I doing
I was gonna say something that I forgot
what was I doing can someone remind me
can someone tell me what I was gonna say
[Music]
I forgore
oh well
[Music]
that's about it next time thank you for
the supers everyone
um
what is it I hope you have fun with
Baldur's date
um I really want to play this more on my
own but no time no time no time I never
have any time but I wanna I wanna the
characters are just so cool
um and everything uh but I hope you had
fun today uh we'll continue playing uh
if it is morning PST
I may or may not stream it uh next time
because if it's morning PST I died like
the first the first baldi's gate collab
was morning PST and then I died and I
was very very tired so maybe I don't
know we'll see we'll see
but yeah uh
because we're swapping time zones and
everything every every single time we
collab this so next time I think it
swaps to morning PST and uh I might yeah
I'm not going I'm not good with mornings
I'm not good but I'm sure there'll be
someone else who's streaming so even if
I don't stream you can you can touch
theirs
okay try not waking up at 2PM well
right here's the thing
because I stream so much which isn't a
bad thing by the way which isn't a bad
thing I love streaming so much
um
I have to do my work at night like my
like my homework
like all my homework I have to do that
after stream at night so I get all my
homework done at night time uh because
because of of my stream which is why I
end up not sleeping and then waking up
in the afternoon because that's
nighttime is my work time but it's okay
I'm I'm
here at night I've always been I've
always been the most productive and
creative at the nighttime so that's
totally fine with me it's just you know
I'm in a different I have a different
internal cloth I guess I have a
different daily schedule than maybe some
of yours but it still works for me and
it's still fine and I still
go outside
once in a while
outside once in a while to you know it
stretch my legs go on a walk touch some
grass
grass but I gotta make sure I stay
healthy and happy so that way the
streams are good and everything anyway
what is grass no idea
grass okay
um
[Music]
I'm gonna get some rest before funny
funny stream I'm gonna redirect to her
anyway even though it's two hours
um
away today
yay can I do it I can do it yes okay
yes I can do it okay anyway thank you
thank thank you thank you what was I
doing my mind is empty
my mind is empty today maybe I need some
food maybe I'm hungry I am hungry maybe
I'll eat something actually at a proper
time today
okay thanks everyone for the stream I'll
see you tomorrow or a garchick phone and
maybe lies of pee if I can confirm that
I have permas for it but whenever I get
the answer I'll put my schedule up but
please have patience because I'm still
waiting for the answer yeah and that's
that's why it's not out yet okay
[Music]
I'll see you tomorrow have a good rest
your day go watch ponies
and I'll see you next time
later bye
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]