[Music]
do
um
oh hi y'all good morning
why i just got out there
and my cats i don't need it chunkers is
the whole time she's always like meow
meow meow
what is it now
no no my voice is just like this because
i just woke up
i also didn't eat breakfast but hey you
know what i'm gonna order breakfast now
so i'll i'll not
do the thing that i did yesterday and
wait until after the stream i'm actually
gonna eat it during the stream
if you don't mind ah
um um
[Music]
how are you guys you're gonna
gonna order some yummy yummy yummy yum
breakfast
lunch well guess it's right now it's
lunchtime
but for me it's breakfast
take a break to eat now i'll just i'll
just be uh eating uh
while talking to you guys
you don't mind yay it's gonna be really
yummy breakfast
um oh where is it where is it
or is my favorite where is it
oh there
there it is oh yes
anything else maybe something to drink i
mean i do have stuff to drink but
i always feel bad like um or when i
order
food somewhere and i only need like one
thing
and i only need like one one thing and
the price it turns out to not be so high
i feel bad for ordering
thank you for ordering only one thing
so sometimes i like on purpose
order more stuff so that they don't go
for so much trouble just because of
one one food one meal
thank oh my god bless you
thank you wow
that's how they make you buy more or
they're too safe on the fridge
yeah most of these things though the
problem is most of these things are
always like
meant to be eaten when it's fresh and i
don't have a microwave
very considerate right right
i don't have a microwave so often i just
order
salad because i don't have to warm it up
and i can eat that later
maybe i'll order a salad
on the side should i do that because
otherwise i feel bad
let's get let's get one of those really
fresh summer salads
[Music]
although i do want to buy a microwave
for my new apartment so i might as well
already buy it now i've been thinking
about that
for a while okay there we go suddenly
the price is much much much higher
okay please please give food
lanka
order a microwave sun sun
what blue swimmer tenor for the cuddle
what
what is that a blue swimmer dinner
asaku honey montana
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
oh uh the australian thing again
oh what is it the is it the australian
thing again what you call
wait what are you calling do australians
call ten dollars
blue swimmers
oh my god
why
why that's so weird
and cute and funny and stupid i don't
even know what to call it
no do you not do they not
i don't understand explain yourself
because ten dollars are blue in
australia
did you need i need explanation you
can't drop these things and then give me
no explanation about oh well it's
actually written there
ten dollars ten dollars in australia is
colored blue
it is actually worth in there
oh okay guys
uh i should maybe brush my hair
i have a very bad case of bad hair
very very bad case
do you need five minutes to wake up i
already had more than five minutes
my my breath my brush is not here it's
in the living room
the more hair greens
first of all thank you guys for coming
to the super chat stream
i did not announce it on twitter until
just when the stream started so you guys
are all coming in here from the
subscription box thank you i love you
thank you go get it start brushing oh
one second
these are the moments where people wish
i had a asmr microphone
for brushing sounds
[Music]
hello okay brushing my hair
so that the delivery person
when when he sees me doesn't think i'm
some kind of
i don't know
youtube notification squad yeah
you're sure you're so weird that you
can't
see me brushing my hair i'm actually
really doing it
how come you can't see this brush is the
brush imaginary is
it visible is it invisible
some kind of crazy challenge
oh
uh my hair over just over one night it
gets really
um um
tangled up crazy
okay okay same
yeah the longer your hair the more you
say hello baby
they're so needy right now this was just
this was stronger did you hear her meow
smoothie was annoying me as every
morning
was she was meow meow meow meowings
telling me she wants to have that
sweet nice wet food
so i got up and made it for her
the wet food and i just checked her bowl
and she barely ate it which is not
normal normally she
like she's like a vacuum cleaner when i
give her that
wet food she eats it all up like
immediately
she loves it so much but i guess not
right now she has no hunger then why are
you asking for the wet food if you have
no hunger
weirdo go eat your food let's move
smoothie oh my god there's so
oh god i should turn off the super chats
there's still so many coming in
[Laughter]
[Music]
well if you really want to send
something uh i guess you can still send
it later in the diablo 2 stream
but i'll turn the super chats off now
supercat
[Music]
uh
okay there we go
oh my gosh sean you got it in the last
second
[Laughter]
you guys don't listen to me yesterday
i opened the member stream and the super
chat rating stream
and i i was like guys if you want to
read send super jets go send them at the
at the super chat reading stream not
that the members stream
and then obviously my my
viewers my members my chickens had to be
rebellious
and send it in the members only stream
anyway
even though i had a pinned comment you
little rebels
yahoo
okay and while we are waiting for the
breakfast let's start let's start
scrolling first of all
uh we need to read the ones from the q
and a
first oh
q a q a let me try to
get all the way down get down
ah
[Music]
foreign
you know the other day i ordered
something from this restaurant
and on my app it said
uh it would take like uh uh 30
30 minutes so i was waiting but then
after 15
minutes my doorbell was ringing and i
was like
i'm not gonna open that because
i don't know like um
there have been cases where i opened the
door like i
i i like you know uh pushed the
the the ringy thing uh
so that they can get up and then i was
waiting at my door and nobody came
so recently often um
like somebody just drinks to get in and
to get in into a different apartment
and that has been pissing me off like
and at least at least like
there were there was there were cases
where
uh i was like picking up the the speaker
yeah and
um i was asking like who is it
and sometimes they answer like i think i
had it once where someone said
either i'm from amazon or like i'm from
food delivery
if it was even one of that and i opened
up
now yeah he said amazon and i was like
okay
i don't i don't remember i ordered
anything but
uh maybe my roommate ordered something
so i better i better go
let him in so i let that person in and i
was standing at my door
waiting waiting waiting sleepy sleepy
sleepy
and nobody came i was like what the [\h__\h]
yeah that person probably just ringed in
on a lot of doors
and then or or rang at the wrong door
but did actually deliver it to whoever
ordered amazon
so anyway that was one case and then
before that there was
another case where just no nobody said
anything but i
opened the door anyway and i i
uh because i feel like our speaker
system is just kind of broken too
i wonder if they even hear me sometimes
so then i wait at the door again and
they didn't come at all again so i'm
like
what so that's why after like 15 minutes
of waiting for my food even though it
should have been 30 minutes
until it arrived something like that i
um
i i didn't open the door and then
they rang again and i was like no i'm
not gonna open it no
no and then uh
then it rang again and at the same
moment i got a call on my phone
and then i realized okay that that is
that actually
seems to be my food and i was like oh my
god why are you so early
and they said uh we uh
i didn't have any business right now so
we were super quick and i'm like oh my
god i'm
wow they came like 15 minutes
after i ordered that was way earlier
than expected so i was i was really
eh i do have a peephole beeping hole
people
when you look through but not at the at
the bottom like it's an apartment house
with several apartments it's not a it's
not one house
um yeah uh
anyway anyway but my new apartment will
have a proper system
and i will even have a camera wow
so i can see i can see uh who's down
there
yeah uh my voice is doing fine
but i'm just a little bit you know still
not awake yet
but i'm fine i'm fine i'm fine thank you
for asking
yeah i guess the things that i ordered
were already uh
already kind of ready unfortunately the
food that i ordered on that day was
disgusting
they were super fast but i tried
something new that i didn't order before
and i hated it
so i'm back to ordering the usual thing
i ordered some weird like like protein
uh pancakes that were made out of wheat
and i
i read it as if the wheat is maybe just
like covering
wheat wheat cereal something like that
as if it is just covering the
the pancakes but turns out it was like
made out of
completely oni wheat and it just had the
shape of a pancake
and it was covered in like um a little
bit of honey
and some stuff and it was like pretty
healthy and it had some berries with it
too but i couldn't eat it it was pretty
ew no it wasn't like super dry but
and then i tried to eat it with nutella
but even nutella couldn't save it so
that means something
okay no wait i need the there we go that
that's actually
exactly the one i need here
look at that cute mamaloni art i'm just
using art from the
from the um music video of heart
challenger by the way are you guys
listening to heart challenger still
you should be we're almost at 800k uh
views on heart challenger
it's all right oh okay thank you
and the thing is though i meant
youtube is doing some weird things
because my subs went down to 800
898 000.
we're gonna celebrate again after two
thousand more subs
but but according to history
uh other girls that had the same thing
like gura and soy say uh senpai
and some other girls it was
back again in what two days or so i
don't know
yo
i saw another k it was real was it
really i don't know ah luna luna
too yeah
you know what it's okay because even if
it's the depth of me you know i'm in
phoenix
i'm i'm not like it's just confusing
because i i want to know why
okay uh let's read the super chat cool
let's write some from the q and a
thank you for the pinky which is
supposed to be for the riser stream
thank you
because raiza for raiza streams i'm not
allowed
to take super chats so you were so kind
to send it on a different stream thank
you
great stream a little sad to see the
series ending so soon even without my
bias i really love the atmosphere of the
streams but i'm sure but who's your bias
i'm sure you'll give us something great
afterwards
uh also sorry for saying you can't read
it's okay i forgive you
uh yeah well there
maybe and someday maybe there will be
another
um atelier game stream or
maybe even something like um
wait i'm confused there's so many uh
games
that i'm interested in with blue in
front of them
what was it blue reflection was the
phone game
what was the one the castle the ghost
game
uh wait was it blue reflection on it
blue blue protocol was another one no no
yeah
okay okay bloop reflection was the
magical guy okay
blue archive was the phone game blue
protocol is the online game that i'm
waiting for from little tales of
mmorpg blue protocol is the phone game
and blue reflection is the
oh my god why is this all everything
with blue
so yeah i'm trying to say that maybe one
day we'll play that i don't know uh
so blueberry production show
no no wait clap your hands it's not
called blue clapper don't confuse me
what blue
what blue i uh
look
no wait is that
is it
wait is it i'm getting so confused
because the other day we had
what was it hard clapper or something
like that or a blue
or a blue challenge
[Laughter]
wait is that wait wait i have to look it
up now
blue clapper no way it wasn't blue
clapper no wait
oh it was blue clapper oh my god it
sounded so wrong to me suddenly
what it looks like
i'm so confused oh my god i sang it
already a million times i heard it a
million times but i don't know i got so
confused just now
oh
okay okay okay well [\h__\h] thank you i
hope i can play more games that you like
hopefully
thank you soon
deep breath i'm so lost in your eyes the
gps can't help me find a way out
nervously hands over froze wanna watch
princess bread with me
what's going on cass biggs
what's wrong with you
what happened with you what but then he
sends another chat another super chat
changing his name against normal mr
catfix and asks why not watch princess
brat with me instead
oh my god and then he changed his name
again and changes it to dr casvicks and
asks
i prescribe you one princess brad
wheeling ditch those other guys do they
have medical degrees which i like
100 do yeah so what do you say
oh my god it's
all these personnel you have multiple
personalities
and then the love jumps in as well
saying hi so lost in your eyes
also no what's your princess spread with
me and another one syndic it's not like
i wanted to watch princess proud of you
or anything
what's happening
[Music]
you guys you want to see princess bride
with me that bad
oh my god that's kind of cute
princess bride walks along
maybe maybe maybe
uh harvard
oh god can you point out those other
people
that are asking you to watch pretty
sprite with them
and i think i need to have a little
toggle them young lyric oh my god
oh my god a harvard line that gets in
harmony love 67 duncan
picture to um the one where he's
stuck in my butt that mama
elon drew
oh my god dealer 67 albedo duncan
[Music]
hey mom i wanted to let you know we all
got our w-2 from kfp and we filed our
taxes and we're going to use it to help
make kfc better
much love your newest employee and you
and kelly love child patrons
i don't i don't recall either me
or callie giving birth to you
so that must be uh
[Music]
what do you call what do you call like
rumors and [\h__\h]
rumor but i don't know i can't i don't
know
we're adopted yeah but that doesn't make
any of you guys um
a love child it's
uh yeah it's delusion
well anyway thank you for filing your
taxes i guess
i don't quite understand uh how
taxes work in america
[Music]
but i'm glad you did it i hope i i guess
it helps kathy
as you claim thank you very much
thank you for the red super chat thank
you for supporting me and welcome
welcome
a new employee is am among those
among us and
line duncan looking for the top thunder
sun
oh my god you wrote bacon of light
[Music]
breaking up light every time someone
writes speaking of light i
i want to read breaking of light but you
actually wrote breaking of light on
purpose
looking for the top did you do that on
honda nsx extension crystal kitchen
hatching in the wink oh
soon tm
one two three four five six
twenty dollar super chat
yeah that's 120.
oh my god thank you for the red super
chat decibel and this is a really long
one
oh my god okay i think we have to read
it
okay are you ready uh
this is a long one
[Laughter]
reverend kiara dv your vassal and humble
servant greetings
apologies for the delay in my
mismissives
but messengers began to come very
frequently saying that aid was coming to
the enemy
moreover this report came to us not only
from the algorithm and the bots but was
also announced to us by those who were
in the city
meanwhile good chickens who were
scattered among the fortresses came and
brought arms fitted and repaired them
what is he talking about
uh one of the chickens who was in the
city sent word
to our leaders for epic gamers that he
would surrender the city to us
when to play
[Music]
waffles with nutella
on it [\h__\h] time to tell they add a lot
of nutella
and bananas and raspberries and
strawberries and blueberries
topped with they add a little bit of
a small um
small chunk of vanilla ice cream
which will immediately melt but those
waffles are really good i ordered them
like a million times
yeah boy
honestly even though i love nutella and
i love chocolate i have to say
these waffles always come with a tiny
bit
too much nutella i wish they would um
put on a little bit less than that but
if i would tell them that
then they would probably instead of like
getting rid of a little bit less nutella
they would probably
uh get rid of a lot of nutella
what i mean a little bit i really only
mean a little bit but they probably
would just get rid of like
most of it so i just don't say anything
cutting this in this uh delivery um
uh plastic thingy is kind of difficult
[Music]
so get a little bit of the waffle
and then which fruit do we want on our
first bite
i think i want the the raspberry
come here okay
okay and then we add a little bit of
ice cream
so good
another bite
um
hello cat are you curious you're not
gonna get anything from this
you can look at it you can look but not
touch hmm
french toast no i love french toast
i haven't made french fries in a while i
used to make it a lot when i was in
japan
because it was so easy and so yummy i
should make it again
thank you for reminding me
okay let's have one with a strawberry
[Music]
a shop your shop
and a little bit of ice cream
[Music]
um
tonight we'll be playing diablo 2 again
are you guys ready
for some more diablo 2 action
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
if anyone didn't watch the first part go
watch the archive now
uh at the same time as watching the
as watching the super chat reading
stream
go catch up now ketchup
ketchup i said the title
i said the title you know how when
people in movies are in games
say to say the title i said our title
i did it
this is like one of those epic moments
roll credits
[Music]
this is so good
the people at that restaurant like the
people who deliver it
and they've seen me like so often by now
they've seen all my pajamas by now
every variety
i need
no no no my pajamas are
i would not call them sexy
don't worry i don't have lewd pajamas no
just comfy very comfy
hmm
[Music]
sorry guys for taking time and eating
i'm like almost halfway through though
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
there's so much nutella on this
oh my god even for me
it's a bit too much which really says
something
and i'm a nutella slash chocolate lover
although i don't
my dad mentioned before that dad has
changed a little bit
i can't tolerate as much chocolate as i
used to
um
we a bomb guy i saw your comment
i saw your comment i saw what you were
trying to type out
i saw it
better be careful
it was he was hinting
on the diet
i do not need such a thing
why tensho oh my tangier
is just uh
it's hard to say it's um
i'm gonna try to use the smart english
words
it's an uh deception of of your
imagination
it's a
uh um it's a
[Music]
it's
in english
that's not exactly what i mean
a clump of your
a clump of your illusions
almost done with my waffle that was
quick way okay wait
so i'm what i'm saying is why potential
is not real it's only real in your
imagination
she's reeling my heart my intention is
just
your own nightmares following you
during the daytime
whatever you do you cannot escape
the amount of berries that they add to
this waffle
is so generous i'm so grateful thank you
how
a brand of waffle there's no brands to
this waffle it's
made in the restaurant
i said now
they're sending i spot the white piano
how is that not real hmm
so so polite i say neha and they also
need help back
they got good manners damn
hmm
what so many
raspberry and banana on the waffle
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
oh yummy
oh my god i feel like
i feel like i ate a whole
chocolate factory
oh my god the nutella is real
oh my god that was a lot of nutella
okay
sorry to keep you guys waiting okay a
bit more water
a bit more water
[Music]
i have eaten i have eaten
okay now where did we start with the
desert
super chats
he wrote this whole book to me
he wrote a whole book
okay visible i'm continuing in your
super chat
i know guys
okay one of the chickens who was in the
city sent word to our leaders for epic
gamers that he would surrender the city
to us
when the plan had been communicated they
sent epic gamers and the duke of cows
and the count of deloved tried out
and when they had come to the hill of
the city at midnight the intermediary
sent by him who was surrendering the
city said
wait until the light passes for four men
went along the walls of the city with
lamps all night rousing and
admonishing the watches after this
however our k of peeps
approached the wall raised ladder and
began to ascend it
a certain kfp swamp flare flyer by name
brother of harbor line was the first
boldly ascend to the wall the count of
dela following
sent word to epic gamers and the duke to
ascend
those who had climbed up went down into
the city and opened a
certain little poster and thus our
chickens went in
okay i have to say
i i said before i don't like uh
reading and i don't like uh you know i
i'm not interested in really in
fanfictions
but this is a good way to make me read
your fanfictions just send it all in
super chats
but this one this one is special
because it includes like even the even
the
viewers in the story which makes it
really funny and cute
thank you there's a vault
i'm looking forward to the continuation
non takamoni fanfictions and super chats
what kind of language do you want to
send is it even whole life related
well generally i would prefer if you
guys would not send me fanfic
super chance
but if there's something you really
really really want me to read
i guess go ahead
if you really need me to read it
or do you want to send me like some
fanfiction where callie gets shipped
with someone else just
to trigger me and make me cry
so i don't know good good morning
or something like that
no i will ban you if you sent me that
kitchen
thank you vlog
thank you for red super chat
sorry tanja i've reflected on what i
said yesterday about tap water and we'll
be open-minded about trying it going
forward
we'll lay off my ultra special fiji
water for a week as punishment here's my
penalty payment for disney
australian tap water hope for gucci
yes we are yes yes yes we are gucci uh
we've always been glooty
even because i don't even remember
anything from
more than one day ago
i don't remember anything
got short shirts a short thumb short
short short
short short term
memory thank you i was trying to say
short term memory but the only thing i
could think of was shirt short
time memory i was like that's not right
thank you
i mean it's similar close enough
ah thank you pepperoni
dangerous and thank you for the support
what do they say in german ah it's
called
uh could scientificness
love you thank you
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
okay uh wait so are you saying you're
trying your own tap water
well depending on where you live
you know i said tap water in my country
is great but it might not be good in
your in your
area so i don't know please be careful
maybe it's okay to drink fiji water
it's i'm not you could probably
drink your fiji water and continue it if
you
like it just don't get sick by drinking
tap water
check uh with someone if the tap water
in your city is okay
it's just in my country it's really
really really clean
thank you i actually know that people
have been trying to
prank me trying to tell me who og means
uh
phoenix but it doesn't
but i guess
phoenix is fang huang here we go we've
had that talk before
you can't fool me
you cannot fool me
i'm smarter than that i think
wait how did i just pronounce that what
the hell i feel like i just pronounced
that
uh in a spanish way
did you say huan wait
no it was one yeah it was a one
[Music]
i thought i thought afterwards i thought
it said uh huang with jay and i was like
did i pronounce that spanish
anyway i'm in phoenix not
turkey not chicken nothing like that
i'm phoenix i am dangerous
firebird respect me
to you the person reading this know that
i have forever taken a moment of your
time i will forever be a part of you now
thank you cryptic
you know what i was this is not a red
super chat i was just
you know i was just like ah i need to
read some
um normal super chats every once in a
while in between two and that's what you
give me for that
that's what you give me that's what i
get for that for reading a non-red super
chat
regrets it's too late now
okay this one must be good because i see
it uh in the beginning it
already says ggs kiara and we know what
that means
good day gts kiara
i saw a pic of you enjoying a shook for
brekkie
surely it's not one of the kfp choke it
is
is it may i suggest smashed avo on toast
with corn fritters and grilled tomato
and a cuppa
but these australians are just we can't
control them anymore
these australians are are pushing
and forcing their weird language onto me
what should i do
just kidding i like it it's interesting
to see but i don't like avocado
i don't actually like avocados so
avocado on toast and all that kind of
fancy uh instagramable
foods that everyone is into nowadays
with the avocados
i don't like it
[Music]
sorry
realize it's been quite a bit since the
last super chat it kind of felt less
less like an employer and more just a
simple kfb customer
though thinking about the kfb customers
don't get eaten like the employees yeah
i mean it's not a bad thing
being a customer is actually
maybe in some ways safer
and more fun than being an employee
maybe
so there's nothing wrong with that i
guess you could say that
maybe the maybe the members are the
employees and the non-members who are
watching
are the are the customers
in some way
that's i mean fine with me
i'm promoting myself to customer just in
case you are not allowed to
i love being in danger though then stay
in danger stay in danger
permission to become a customer no
you will lose your your membership
benefits so if that's okay with you okay
bye-bye
it's not like i it's not like i enjoyed
watching movies with you or anything
it's not like i liked spending time with
you and members only streams
i don't care i don't care go
far wherever you wanna go
looking for the top thunderstorm
raspberry alice duncan
i love charm so much i have the entire
series on dvd oh my god
cool yeah you have a charmed fan that
makes me happy
alex thank you soon you told me you
weren't big on justin timberlake when
did i say that did i say that before
and then i read it in my in my
friendship uh
book and i actually did like him before
well but now all days
nowadays i don't care about him
yeah like even though i wrote that there
i don't think i really
wait you know what just popped into my
head something really really random
thinking of justin timberlake wasn't
there like some kind of
show on mtv where
where i look alike of some
kind no wait it was the other way around
someone
or which way was there was like there
was like normal people
and then lookalikes of like celebrities
and i don't know which side was looking
for the other but
but they would like appeal no yeah no no
no no it was a normal person
and then you get like free lookalikes of
the
the celebrity that the person likes and
they're trying to know
to to make that person like you um
uh uh wait
wait wait wait um because that person is
really into that celebrity so he's
looking for someone or she's looking for
someone to date
but that person is so crazy into that
celebrity that they wanted
to have their girlfriend or boyfriend to
like be like that oh my god that's
that's so crazy
is there some people who remember the
show oh my god
and then they would like build whole
like rooms
and and they would they would
impersonate the celebrity by singing
a song and and looking like the
celebrity and then at the end of the
show
the the person like looked at all three
people and and chooses one to date
you know does that make sense to the
people who don't know what i'm talking
about
does that sound like a show to you
there was such a that was a really great
show on mtv
it did exist yeah
and i just remembered that because i
think there was a one
one episode where they we're looking for
um justin timberlake
boyfriends
oh my god
mtv had all these weird dating shows
yeah next for example
i was i don't know i was so young and i
kept on watching next
i don't know i really i really was into
that show
i just thought it was interesting from
the point of view of a really unpopular
bullying uh a very young teenager
watching next with all these good
looking people
who are you know all
like i i guess it's hard to say this in
english
i'm looking for words like japanese word
uh would be
uh someone who's just
you know living their best life having
parties and and
going on dates having boyfriends
girlfriends
and yeah so when i watched next was like
watching those oh yeah just normies i
mean i wouldn't necessarily just call it
normies
but yeah it was very interesting
watching
watching that and being like huh maybe
one day
i'll be i'll be that popular and that
good looking
that i can um have a bus uh
of of of people coming out to me
and i can be like next nah i don't need
your uh next
next next ah you're not you know i don't
like the way you look
like they're oh my god that was so rude
like from
from 20 meters away the
the person would would scream next
because from 20 meters away they would
decide
i don't like that person already so
bye-bye go back into the bus
oh my god crazy they wouldn't even give
them a chance
[Music]
japanese tv is there
i have never i would have never seen mtv
ever before
and japanese um tv i don't think
it fits their culture they would
probably not like it at all
do they still do shows like does mtv
still do shows like that like next and
all that kind of [\h__\h]
do they still do it like i don't have a
tv like i do but
no no tv reception
do they still do shows like that [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's music only now
is there even empty and to be still
around
mgb still a thing i don't know
maybe not
not a lot of shows well i guess it's
better if they focus on music
there were all these kinds of weird
dating shows oh my god anyway let's go
back to superchat
[Music]
this is the peak blackmail content that
we never knew we wanted
you're actually right this gloria no now
i'm kind of
i i regret reading those friendship
books
[Music]
that's actually true
now no there's nothing in there that you
could have blackmailed me with
it's all good real tough these kiwi
streams are some of my faves thank you
maybe i should do more i haven't done
that in a while
until the last one uh
i think at the latest for the one
million
um subs smartphone
i will probably have a little segment
where we can do marshmallows as well
but i don't know if we'll ever do it
before that it
depends on how long it takes to get
there
but yeah you said something about part
two so yeah actually it turns out like
after the stream i scrolled down
a bit more to see how many more uh
questions that i
saved that i had to read and there was
only like two more
or so something about that is like about
two
two more questions so i actually was
already at the end of course there's
questions left that i
didn't uh you know save
uh with the intent to answer them
but those were mostly like yeah well
those weren't saved for a reason
uh either they were already answered
before or uh i just didn't feel like
answering them this time um
well well well
so you only picked around 60 questions
no beginning and was it was it 60
questions that's a lot actually
i think you're anyway just saying this
in an
ironic way
um ah
[Music]
actually wait didn't i
did i i saved two marshmallows
that i would like after
afterwards i think these ones are ones
that i didn't answer
uh
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
well how about we read it uh
hi kiara now that ozora casa has opened
an investigation on you
as a criminal investigator i would like
the attention of kfp to answer
truthfully to several allegations that
kfp and jfb members have kindly provided
but first of all you shouldn't take any
allegations from jfp because they're
obviously a biased and
they're always just talking slander and
[\h__\h]
number one have you ever called
undesirably undesirable employees in the
union room or stay
in the chicken blind no i have not
are you attached to a shinigami yes i am
but she's on hiatus so it's okay
also even if she wasn't on hiatus
it would be discrimination for you to
claim that that is
a bad thing a bad person for me to be
attached to
now discrimination have
a cult following no we're not a cult
experienced amnesia in jail
i i was never in jail
i don't remember i don't recall being in
jail
say sad an iconic phrase after leaving
said jail and regaining memories
i don't recall that actually i really
don't
self proclaim god no no
near automata made me
gone so it's not self-proclaimed
near it was near automata and my viewers
have multiple forms and uh read the view
well what's the problem with that what's
the pro where where is the crime in that
huh
there's no crime again if you answer yes
to the majority of the questions canada
is not just a feelings part-time woman
that owns a fast-food restaurant she is
also a criminal mastermind that goes by
the name piano that uses a certain
notebook
well no i uh only answered yes to number
two
and uh seven
well that's it so i am not a criminal
mastermind
we're good we good we good
and then um
there was a one more hey
hi has been extended in australia wink
again
do you have any tips what to do when
you're bored out of your mind at home
besides watching your videos of course
play games that's all i can really
recommend
play some games or for example um how
about you
start doing some workout maybe you
own ring fit adventure then go go get
started on some workout when you have
the time and you're at home anyway
um yeah that's that's my advice to you
but for me personally
even though is there is it really a
lockdown right now like i went to the
supermarket and it didn't really seem
like you still
locked down a lot of people were outside
i don't really know how it works here
though
apparently i guess it is locked out
right now
but anyway even during the lockdown um i
think you can
go out jogging alone and stuff like that
so
if you need some fresh air i think you
won't
die and yeah i don't know
it hasn't really affected me at all so
and yeah even during a lockdown i'm just
here sitting
uh streaming all day doing my job
basically
so to me it's really absolutely no
no difference whether there is a
lockdown or there isn't
oh that's it that's it those are
two questions that were left over that i
actually saved i just remembered
thank you for um reminding me of that
dear super chat
or wait was it even super chat i think
it was just a normal chant one
yeah maybe i think it was just a normal
chance
good tangent yeah yeah yeah thank you
everyone for sending the questions in
for the q a thank you once again
uh your interesting questions
are the ones that make the content in
those streams so thank you
uh you can already start thinking about
the next one maybe maybe if your
question didn't get
chosen this time then it might not
necessarily be because i didn't like it
uh maybe you can give it another try but
think about it first
did i ever did i answer that a million
times before then you probably shouldn't
ask it again
oh thank you
okay and so once again this long area
did not give you a kiss you didn't say
anything about not kissing you this time
john willard thank you oh yeah and by
the way uh because of the super
super chats here mentioned the erasmus
song sorry
actually i was thinking about i was
aware that uh
i said that during the q a but when i
was making the list
for what to sing yesterday i was like
not really into
learning that song uh at the moment so
i i didn't i didn't uh i and i was
i remember i remembered but i didn't
want to do it so
but you got some paramore again and some
aaron levine again
so
have you ever been to the netherlands no
i think i've only been at the airport
for
uh transferring
uh flights yeah
yeah i don't think no i've never been to
the netherlands properly
come to holland i want to i want to the
neverlands are really really pretty
from what i've seen
so eventually um i wanna i wanna visit
all the other european countries that i
have not visited yet
yeah watching this thing i'm with you
made me so happy
oh i'm glad thank you
i love every levine's bean's songs oh my
god
i accidentally he was about to say i
love aaron levine's thongs
well that can just mean that can just
mean
i love her um you know there's those
uh shoes that you call socks
oh my god and it's slippery slippers i
love her slippers okay
no i love your songs okay
the flip-flops yeah i love havilarin's
phones too
[Laughter]
i've never seen her in the phone okay
never even seen her in a thong she
probably i mean they're probably did she
ever take like sexy pictures she
probably did
although who knows every living
i feel like there's probably some
magazine who did like a laundry shoot
with her before i'm probably
okay okay okay okay sorry you're like 90
minutes in and have free streams then oh
god okay okay okay i will i will
overread the super chats okay
john williams
[Music]
little chiara was so special i wouldn't
necessarily say so but
lexington the lion thank you i used so
much charmed up to school for the hot
witches did young hannah also watch
charms to look at the girls no i was
just interested in
the series itself and i liked the magic
and all that and the story and all that
there was a little juniper back then
miss fist dancer and daisy concussion
[Music]
people sending super chats to make me
into a rich wizard because that was my
dream back then
it is
oh i was reading it as a different word
but now i
understand what that means you're the
chicken
black friend
jesus christ canada how do you always
get cute every day i love this childhood
tangent gonna start going through my
stuff too
you got some like books like that too
unlike other childhood stuff
that's you're very lucky like besides
those friendship books i honestly don't
have much from my
um from from my childhood like for
example
my mom didn't really take
many or any or many pictures
uh from when i was like a toddler
and all that there's i don't i don't
even
i don't own any pictures from me as a
baby or as a toddler
and uh yeah
i don't have like a like a photo album
i mean i i think she took some pictures
but she has them
as or i don't know maybe she threw it
away by now but
i think she had them as what do you call
that um
something really really old to look at
pictures
that like like um uh
um
not polaroids the whole
film no not exactly oh maybe in this
film
[Music]
diaz is it called dions in english too
like you would put them in some kind of
weird
um thingy and it would show it on on the
wall
uh
like is this is it a slide you call that
slimes
ah i said so yeah i think she had
some pictures in slides
which is actually that itself is kind of
uh
cute and nostalgic yeah you would need a
projector for that
cave paintings no my mom
did we are not that old
we are not that old keep me
oh my god oh my god sapphire kitten
thank you
that was absolutely amazing now i want
to go read go for my yearbooks too
but that was not a yearbook but okay you
actually remind me a lot of my little
sister so cute
what i remind you of your little sister
only tongue
m
is he even here if he is he probably
just died
he must have died from a heart attack
now
ah zephyr kitten
[Music]
thank you for the pinky you're already a
magician kiana making fire up here and
making kfc and boys disappear
i did not
okay shout out i will i will quickly
skip over your super chat now and give
no more comments to it
call galleon thank you soon for your
kitten
[Music]
big ups for the cat care advice also
plus one for solo travel being awesome
thank you it's so much trouble
i gotta say we talked about this already
but i gotta say once again
i was solo traveling to japan for me
versus solo traveling to any other
country
is very very different like in japan i
just feel so
[Music]
so safe like because i'm just so used to
being there and i just know
i know where to go and i know
like how things work there
and i know the language so when i go to
other countries i do
feel quite anxious especially if it's a
a country where german or english is not
really
common yeah
then i feel kind of nervous and anxious
a little bit but still
i still feel like it's worth it
and fun
[Music]
wait for a moment okay this is about the
friends question of a moment i thought
you were telling me i'm phoebe from
charmed because there was actually a
phoebe and charmed as well
i didn't really like phoebe though i
think i like
there was one girl called piper um i
also don't think i liked her the most
but
maybe i did like phoebe i liked her
sometimes
but then i didn't like her later on when
when uh she was like getting back
together with that dude again and again
and then and then going like
paige i like paige yeah thank you andrew
how the [\h__\h] do you remember the name
i did like paige i think
wasn't painting the one who came in
later though and replaced
yeah paige replaced piper
oh wait oh my god let me google right
now trump
i don't remember going to nostalgia
a pro yeah yeah no she didn't replace
piper yeah she replaced proof
now that's what i thought no one replies
piper piper stayed
like until oh my god the pictures are so
much talented
oh there are they are uh pretty hot
aren't they
wait who's that what is this new picture
uh i think like back then
like i was so young i just watched it
because i liked the series but
i think they a lot of boys were crashing
on these
women they looked really
hot down
oh my god i bet i bet that
these girls will
wear crushes for all those boys out
there
[Music]
and all kinds of magazines like posing
for some nice pictures
what is this though is this why is there
four who are those two i don't remember
those two
is that like a really late season that i
didn't watch
did they ever have like
cool art i need i need to rewatch them i
wonder how cringe it will be for me to
re-watch
charmed now do they have charmed on
amazon
let me see i haven't
rewatched it or like ever re-watched it
at all
charmed there we go
it's on prime video but i have to pay
okay complete collection
season one to eight
oh oh my god you know what you know what
that will be so so nostalgic
this is my goal today
but why does that picture not look like
the charmed actresses
ah what that's from 2019 that's like a
new
new thing a remake with different
actresses and they are
uh what
they have different names this is not
the real charm what the hell
that's a reboot i didn't know there was
a reboot
why does she look like a doctor what is
this
why don't they why aren't they named
paige phoebe and prue
or piper but whatever
no no no i want the real thing
there we go first season but only dvds
can i have it in
what i want prime video i don't want to
use dvds what the hell
there's only dvds
i want to watch the thing on
on my laptop please
but there's oh my god there's only dvds
of the real thing
what oh my god
you know paige was really hot because of
her red hair i think
i think people really liked her uh boys
must have liked her for being a hot
redhead
[Music]
like looking at her now i can definitely
see
they had a lot of sex appeal
oh my god
oh wait i'm a hot redhead
[Music]
oh you know what i'm actually curious
about the
reboot did anyone watch the reboot is it
good
is it good did anyone watch it
[Music]
on your head shut up
watch never sucks
didn't watch it i
oh my god oh you guys checked
okay i'm curious so i'll give it a try
though and i'll tell you guys if it was
good or not
okay okay okay
[Music]
thank you for the pinky for the new for
four new outfits i think you would rock
a fancy business suit looking as
our ce oh boss customization up to you
of course
yeah that would not only be cool for um
for you know being your boss but also
for holotalk wearing a suit
would be really cool but
i don't think it would be my first
choice of outfit
unfortunately
uh i would probably go for something
else
although it would be really cool to have
a suit ah for a whole talk
maybe maybe i can just wear like put on
like an
oversized image of a suit that will
cover up my
upper body uh and then just have my head
sticking out you know how
how how for example girls have
used that the the blanket for watching
movies
no but then that looks so stupid though
then if i do that in the whole time
it will look so weird
if it doesn't fit well if it
10 yeah like good at school uniform for
example
just put on a suit no i can't do that no
holotalk has to be serious and high
quality production
oh man maybe one day we'll get a suit
but like a hot suit with a skirt with a
pencil skirt
and some see-through tights and
some hot high heels
and glasses of course glasses glasses
are very versatile first version
tile
felix now thank you for the red super
chat
potential sorry i was late and just got
time to send my super chat
i missed about 30 minutes so i hope i
haven't missed my question but anyway
i'll go back for the archive
oh i wonder if i even picked it up i
hope i did for you
thank you for the red super chat though
the good thing is
you all you're a super chat often so
even if i didn't read your super uh your
uh question then you could just send it
as a super chat
something like choco censor yeah that
would be hot
ah so yeah no problem being late
feelings thank you for coming anyway
and thank you for catching up with the
the art guide
that means a lot to me and you take the
time
to catch up thank you thank you for
anyone who does that
watching the archives
message thank you i just wanted to say
thank you for being a parent of figures
that you and kelly are to some of
us oh you are you're welcome
[Music]
when you are on your own and think to
yourself i need to eat or i need to use
the restaurant do you think that in
german english or japanese
it uh it depends like people have asked
this before i think in what language i
think
it really depends on who i am around
with
and what the situation is in japan i
often was thinking in japanese or
english
like actually like every language it's
always mixed but
for example right after a stream i
usually still think in english language
but it's hard to actually also realize
what language i'm thinking
because at the mo the moment where i'm
like
where i i re recall like when i'm like
ah
i wonder what language i've been
thinking in and i try to think back
it's really hard to remember and also
for dreams like i don't remember in what
language my dreams are
usually like it's just language and
and uh it's really hard to recall like
specific words i wish i would just like
i would remember if i would
think of that question right after
waking up
because that's when i still remember the
dream right but then five minutes later
it's already gone
unfortunately i should write down
everything
i should write down everything
but i'm too lazy
is there anyone who in the chat who
writes a dream journal
is there anyone who does that do you
guys have a dream journal
i think it would be really cool to have
one but
yes what i do what me what
what that is so cool
[Music]
that is fascinating
also by the way diaries i used to try to
write write
diaries um but
when i was younger and i would always
like i would buy a new
like diary to write in and i would
always start writing on a day where i
was feeling like either angry or sad
and uh it was so stupid that i would
never ride into it ever again
but i would always write on those
specific days
and feel like really dramatic about it
i don't know really juniper so
ridiculous
and then i would never ever read it
again or write on it again
kiana's emo diary diary reading stream i
don't own any of those anymore
but you know what i had there was
another cute thing and i've
i feel like i might still have that
somewhere
there's something really cute that i had
from my time in
uh grade school um
i had this best friend in my classroom
and we we had some kind of
letter message book thingy
where um i would write in
what like our thoughts what's going on i
would tell her
yeah blue the uh that teacher
sucks and uh oh my god this happened in
my family
and then i i would give it to her in
class even
even though we're in the same class and
she would give it
she would like usually write into it and
give it back in like
two or three days or four days
and and then she would write in oh my
god
i am so into that bullying
class i don't know what to do kiara
he's so cute and he did this and he said
this and
what should i do and then
she would give it to me and i would take
some days to write back and by then it
already doesn't really matter anymore
but it was so cute because we kept on
like exchanging it every couple of days
and it was so cute
yeah like uh like long long letters
in one book that's so cute yeah
you still talk to each other no i don't
i don't uh i i don't even i don't
remember her last name
i wonder if i could ever find her again
i loved her oh you know what actually i
would probably know her last name if i
i do have a picture of our class
where it says each person's name
maybe i could try find her track her
down
knock on her door and be like hey
what up i'm um i'm a fast food franchise
empire owner now and phoenix i'm
everything
now i can do magic i can do everything
that sounds kind of aggressive yeah
i don't know got excited
how's it going
i'm a rich wizard to what i always
aspired to be back then
wrote that in a letter oh just send her
a letter
she didn't know you were facing i was
hiding them i was hiding i wanted to go
to school like a normal
kid
every time i was like burning burning up
from inside i would go to the toilet and
and just
shower myself and chew chill cool down
i would you know my my hair
my red hair it would start like when i
was angry i would
i couldn't control myself because i was
too young so i would like
start like getting really hot and and it
was it would
catch fire a little bit so i would run
to the to the
um bathroom and stick my head into the
toilet
to cool it down and then go back to
class
and they would ask why is your why is
your hair so wet
[Laughter]
there you go have some new lore yes yes
it happened yep
why are you telling not to sink i don't
know it just fit well
i don't know it was it wasn't out of out
of the
out of the um i can't out of the
what's the expression out of the
moment or something like that
i have several questions well wait for
another q a stream
out of the blue moment in the spirit of
the movie yeah that's what i was trying
to say you know
in the spirit of the moment
you know when you're when your head is
on fire you can't think that well
okay i can't think that well
you try that next time your head is on
fire you try thinking clearly okay
don't judge me for that
yeah well it doesn't hurt me but still
like it
makes me feel like stressed out and all
that and
you don't understand i couldn't control
myself when i was younger
okay i didn't know how to deal with it
especially not if it would like start in
school while i was in class i would
panic you know
maybe that's soon maybe that's one of
the reasons why
jugger papa gave me the belt
because i can't control myself and
[Music]
with my fire
no i don't dunk my head in the toilet
anymore
ah that makes sense
did you ever activate a fire alarm
accidentally oh yeah that happened many
times
i i have a big depth i have a
a bank account that's like minus um
500 000 euro
because of all the fire alarms that i've
accidentally activated
and i'll probably never pay it off you
know it's really expensive if you
activate those fire alarms
yeah they make you pay a lot of money
yeah and we work to pay that off
[Music]
before you before being hot when you
were hot-headed
yeah are you going to own a business
with 500k
i don't know it happened i did it i just
didn't tell anyone about it
[Music]
well uh everyone please continue
investing in kfp so i can pay off my
five hundred thousand
euro debt of uh putting uh things on
fire
on a nice
you turned out the super chats your next
stream
what people if you watched my utility
streams you would have heard me say that
a million times by now
the super chat reading stream is where
the real
lore lies at
how's your cats i don't know they're
filming in the living room
okay continue reading super chat oh my
god oh my god oh my god
horrible and that is
oh i'll as a fan of tessa from phonia
would you agree that
lord and sheena are just you and kelly
no i love china but i never shipped lord
with sheena
i think i don't i didn't look like lloyd
anyway
i don't like most of the tales of
male um protagonists
but i genuinely just always only like
girl characters anyway
yeah lord and colette if anything if
anything
and thank you for the question though
i'm glad to have some tesla symphonia
fans
in the in my community presidential
center against monkey nancy and kelly
born english duncan
[Music]
super chat choose for brook gang and
thanks for always thinking about
additional avenues for fan interaction
what did i what did i think of
i don't i don't even remember see this
is a problem this is why i prefer to
read the super chats like right after
each stream
rather than reading it later
once per week because then then now i
don't remember
what these things are but i also don't
remember either well the god damn it
maybe just yeah yeah ah yeah it was
about just the marshmallow because i
said yeah
thank you swatter exactly because i said
this is good for people who cannot read
super chats
who cannot send super chats because they
have no money
uh but still wanna uh send some longer
questions
so that's what the q a is good for there
we go we have remembered
water time
did you die from exhaust yesterday you
seem to have lost quite a memory now
i'm all fine i didn't die
what it didn't happen at the 900k it did
happen
but later on youtube decided to
i don't know delete some subs so we went
down like
a bunch of thousands but according to
other people it will come back
because this is just a youtube thing
we did reach it during the stream and i
even waited
yeah don't say that that's my biggest
worry don't say that
we we did even continue
longer and longer and longer because i
didn't want to
you know i didn't i did i i looked on my
side and
it wasn't the number that you guys said
it was so i just kept on going and going
well we will see we will see if it will
come back i hope it will
thank you guys azuki has the same
problem right now
i saw she was doing a concert um
did she reach a milestone while doing
that
[Music]
um
she reached 400k during the concert
and then it went down again
that is so anti-climatic that is so rude
you do that's sad
fire my head too oh well oh man
why we just we we can only wait wait and
see
but i want you to know ukraine and thank
you for keeping me sane while i'm
dealing with some unfunded medical stuff
and being better than your
personality makes me better thank you i
was asking i'm happy to hear that
i hope you feel better soon and get out
of the bed even though bed is comfy i
would
i it's so hard for me to get out of bed
so
enjoy the time while you're stuck in bed
because
now you don't have to get up that's nice
too
you can you don't have to feel guilty
for staying in bed all day
also about uh not knowing how to send
marshmallows
i'm sorry guys i realized that it's only
in japanese
and that it is kind of confusing for
people who don't understand japanese
uh i don't know why we only use
marshmallow
it's just kind of a cute side that is
easy to use for me
um and that we just used but maybe we'll
find a different side that is uh
i just i just also just like that it's
marshmallows you know
it's kind of cute it's fluffy and cute
it's like i'm eating marshmallows i
don't know and yeah it's anonymous but
i'm sure there's other
other like websites like that where you
can ask
questions anonymously
maybe we'll try out a different site
sometime but you guys seem to figure it
out
fine most of you seem to figure it out
i wasn't sure if my question went
through oh yeah a bunch of people's
questions
were in there in like double
[Music]
i've never said anything because i'm not
sure what to write well that's okay too
curious cat
all right maybe now somebody can use a
different one that is easier to use for
everyone
magic thank thank you gd thank you for
the pinky
good day ggs kiara good girl sexy
love and enjoy this dream mate it was
heaps of fun cute little ripper
fantastic good on you mate
i'm proud to be okay if you chook viva
glory to cathy oh my god judy you're
really letting out that
australianity
nice nice i like
it
i'm getting tired i want to take a nap
oh hi
oh
i think it's wonderful that you use
these q and a's to communicate with
those who can't normally donate
it's that sort of kindness that
reaffirms why am i i am loyal to kfb the
world needs more canada in it
thank you that's so sweet thank you
i love you
just woke up and i am streaming
[Music]
jesus morales
christopher residential and we are done
with the
marshmallow ovary mustang
that's okay next up is
the minecraft super chats
so zoita micron
there it is
thank you thank you for clapping what a
huge uh
uh achievement
thank you okay
let's go mr khan's big function
[Music]
you're telling me a quote from cali that
was pretty cute yeah
kiana is this bubbly sunny being of
light she's so happy and cheerful i
can't help but smile around her cali
open murray
2021. yes you did say that feelings
thank you for the red super chat wow
morning tantra it's me with a new name
felix cell what oh
i know officially kfc is not a cult but
i've recently founded an esoteric order
uh worshipping you in cafe currently
there is only me in the order and you
won't see me often
that is you but why did you change it
back again that's so confusing
ah i won't see you very often okay okay
because yeah okay
after all esoteric order operates in a
dark so that's why you'd like switching
and changing
is that is that what you're gonna do
are two separate accounts okay why one
why
i don't understand this though what's an
esoteric order
what is that is that like a cult
is that a cult
all right then felix have fun there but
don't get
maybe you should get out of there
it doesn't sound sound like a safe
environment
be careful i'm worried about you
be careful don't get into trouble
maybe get out of there okay i don't want
you to
weirdly disappear
red wolf donkey shouldn't be gamer
ah here we go those are the messages ah
the following are more messages from kfp
employees who for one reason or another
are unable to send their own once again
i would mean
it would mean the world if you read them
and thanks not us but them this time
with co-sponsors okay
okay
[Music]
here from philippines uh kaiser for
making cafe
since i was able to get out of my
comfort zone and find new friends even
with
a c word i hope that you stay healthy
since your well-being is important to go
go potential thank you
thank you i'm glad you found new friends
here that's actually something we talked
about
uh during the minecraft stream too
i wish you a nice stream i'm going into
art only soon so i'm just saying i will
keep watching you as much as possible of
you
that's so cool though congratulations on
getting into art university
let's go it sounds really interesting
thank you
yeah samsung 268 thank you
for line i don't super chat since i'm a
student but i love everything you do
your streams are always fun and i kind
of make sure
everyone is on time for those always be
the same and feel good
thank you soon thank you thank you for
your support
all right i need something for my throat
[Music]
i joined the whole a month after your
debut it wasn't the same since
coming into your stream helped me feel
better but also hit me with
reality thank you arigato zamasu and
thank you for being here tento
thank you that's so sweet thank you
well i'm glad your life changed for the
better then
that's good to know
hello kiara it's one of your female fans
here yo maro
[Music]
maro maro
mono
you know exactly what i'm trying to say
thank you for always bringing happiness
and light into our lives i really
appreciate it it's been a fun journey
with you and i wish to support you for
much longer
thank you model
thank you
i'm watching you tomorrow
it's okay it's so good i love you
uh
congratulations on 900k subscriber thank
you for being the blazing flame of
passion we need in our life viva la
porto de fuego
let's just just long live the fire
chicken doesn't it
root
that's just rude
but thank you prove me thank you sir
hello thank you for everything you have
done and thank you for saving me
i was on the verge of depression but
because of you i was able to enjoy and
meet amazing and talented people in the
community oh again
see kfb brings people together
makes them happy i'm so proud
thank you moonlight
thank you for becoming the son when my
world was in absolute darkness
you helped me to keep smiling and
laughing when it seemed impossible and i
feel like i'll never be
thankful enough for that hashtag
fastbird mama
thank you oh all these sweet messages
you're welcome please keep on watching
my streams if that makes you feel better
thank you for your support
six months has passed so fast but every
single moment i spent with you and kfc
is so precious to me
i just want to say keep going and thank
you for everything tanjo and everyone
i carve you also hydration check oh
thank you
[Music]
thank you very much for the support adam
and for always checking up on my
hydration that's very important
thank you
well there's a lot of these messages
they're all pretty long
this year and i wish i did sooner you
are so much fun and i love being part of
this amazing community
just like a phoenix you are incredibly
warm and bright you inspire me a lot
thank you kara thank you
for joining in even if you're not here
from the beginning everyone who comes
afterward is very important as well
so thank you for your support
a message of love and support to yuki
and i'm following you after six months
seeing your heart work
makes me very emotional but by far
happiness is the most palpable
never heard that word ever before
emotion let's find the disguise together
to the stories together
no no
because yesterday i sang fly me to the
moon we're gonna fly to the moon
[Music]
together
me to the moon yeah
and then i'll sing among the stars
[Music]
fly me to the moon and let me play a
mogus
[Music]
i got so confused by these super chats
that i read
the message from emily89 wool
and said thank you as if that's her name
even though that was his message
family 89
[Music]
it's been six months and i was looking
back at your old clips the old
microphone the sink cut
okay with nana ah time surely flies and
we nearly
we're nearing the one million miles down
i'm happy for your attention love you as
well as always
thank you thank you i swear we sweet
duncan
six months a lot happened in that time
so
hopefully the following six months will
be
as exciting or even more exciting i
think it will be more exciting
because in those six months there will
be also my birthday
and that alone trust me will be very
exciting
and who knows what else would happen i
know it roughly but i cannot say
but let me just say it's worth it
staying
it's worth staying for at least another
six months
so don't leave me schrodinger
thank you for everything i'm one of the
broke gang but of course remember thank
you
but watched you from the beginning and
will continue to support you thank you
for giving me inspiration to do art and
learn german
whoa you're seriously studying german
good luck with that field look i'm
feeling live and dank
thank you and thank you for staying here
since the beginning that is very
very very kind of you
thank you for your loyalty gabrielle
one for one dungeon hi danger thanks for
everything you do
for giving us always a love and a good
time we appreciate your hard work for us
you're amazing who you are
we'll always support you happy to be in
kfb here with you thank you
thank you for being part of kfb thank
you and thank you for your kind support
sharon syoza madan kashan finally got
the chance to super chat big love to
thank you for being your cheaper
creative self every day
i'm proud to be a carefree member from
the philippines stay happy and stay
healthy feeling excited manager
we actually do have a lot of viewers
from philippines don't we
thank you for your support thank you
much love back to you
gg stranger dankeshan canada thank you
for being the fun
cheerful energetic and passionate
phoenix please continue to make more
smile and love
also small shout out to the kfp
community thank you for being so amazing
and supportive
yay shout out to you guys you are
all amazing mncg stranger you're one of
them you're also amazing thank you very
much
always super chats on her own or on his
own
thank you carol for being the
kind-hearted person you are you have
helped me somewhere why is this guys
when i saw you sending super chats for a
v-gamer
[Music]
why
oh they don't oh wait it feels like you
do
maybe you just stand up to me a lot in
the normal chat
what
i never had oh my god what's wrong with
my memory
[Laughter]
ah that's so weird i think it's because
your name is in japanese that's why it
stands out to me
him okay okay
uh you have helped me so much in the
past few months we're kindly
we're kind of rekindled my
motivation to continue doing what i love
and the passion to find what i want what
is it tell me more
tell me more tell me more that you get
really far
tell me more tell me more like does he
have a car
tell me mom
tell me
tell me okay no pressure though
thank you panda zan thank you
find what i really wanted to do in the
future to become a successful artist and
a good idea
do you want to become a good
it you want to become a computer or what
good luck with that
you can do the thing you can do it
become a computer
you can do it i believe in you go
[Laughter]
[Music]
i just wanted to i wanted you to know
that you inspired me to audition for her
life i know it would be difficult but
your positive energy and always doing
your best makes me want to follow my
dreams too i love you
thank you that's cool i wish you the
best of luck
but just know that even if you don't get
uh chosen
it doesn't mean that you're like not
talented or anything
hmm because uh they're looking for
specific people that fit um what they're
looking for
this time and um
it doesn't mean that you're not skilled
or whatever it doesn't necessarily mean
that so
please just don't get um how to say
disheartened if you don't get chosen
okay
and there's many other places where you
could also become a youtuber i guess
where you can audition now because it's
really booming right now so
don't give up okay yes the type of
person is very important even if you
like for example
an insanely good singer and uh
really funny energetic type of person
maybe they're looking for like a
quiet cute lowly type of girl this time
so
you know there's just this kind of
things there
so it really doesn't need to mean
anything even if you don't get chosen
just keep that in mind okay
but good luck hey fisla thank you
hi ken i just wanted you to know that
you inspired me to oh wait that's when i
just read it
julian b this look around that question
this little area
is sending us i said this before
but it's very kind of you to send these
donations in honor of other campaign
members but like
i just i feel like you're doing it wrong
a little bit this looks like
there's no messages or anything to read
but it's the thoughts that counts isn't
it
feeling called out well yeah i'm calling
you out
sad
[Music]
the messages are over now the all those
messages from the
the the people who super chatted for the
people who couldn't super chat
[Music]
sullivan thank you
welcome i'm glad i can read your
messages from the people who
normally cannot really super chat and
therefore
mostly don't get read which i'm really
sorry for i wish i could read every
message in the chat but it's just
too many messages if i only had like
what 50 viewers or something like that i
would probably
easily read all of your messages in the
chat but yeah
since there's so many it's impossible
but although although i do have to say
i read a lot of them like right now i'm
while talking i'm constantly looking at
the chat
and they all like get like registered by
my brain
but there's only so many that i can read
out
loud you know but i do see you guys
james o'sullivan
count this night thank you thank you for
the thinking praise the son
praise kiara i think that's what you
mean
it probably is larry danke
hi kenna as a former zaxby's employee
which is not a chicken restaurant
what kind of benefits do i get for
renouncing them and becoming part of kv
do i at least get half off on meals
uh as a employee at kfb you
are welcome to eat as much as you want
from our menu
at any time that is one of our
benefits fill your belly
if that's what you want but you also
gotta work hard
uh-huh no well no oh no i'm just
ask kosovo in winter wish duncan what a
ring thank you i think that's a red
super chat yeah
wondering thank you
[Music]
to my most beautiful phoenix in the
world thank you but i'm actually the
only phoenix in the world so that
doesn't really say
much thank you anyway though thank you
for the support very kind of you
thank you soon thank you for the
generous donation
christoph sanchez and elvis duncan
thank you for two red super chats elvis
hey kara this is the first time that i
write something from more than one line
in the super chat nice
and i would like to say that i want you
from the beginning and you that you are
amazing inspiring and
that's i love your energy and i wanted
to confess that the first time i saw you
i didn't like your model very much i
remembered super chat
but when i saw your first live stream i
it i totally changed my opinion and
today you are my favorite love
everything you do and never change your
way
thank you
nice uh reformed kfp employee
uh this was the super chat i ran in the
face
[Music]
where like 200 people 300 people left
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
stream
oh big stretch and yawn
another usual room success story
[Laughter]
um well elvis thank you
uh i think there were a bunch of people
who really
um had like
uh the same um
image of me that you had uh in the
beginning
but i'm glad for everyone who supports
me now
thank you thank you that means a lot to
me
hope you're enjoying your time here
and hope you will continue to stay to
follow me and support me in the future
too thank you elvis
[Music]
devil devil slayer thank you ronnie
vegas
thank you s17 b32 dan kashan
magnus borsen dankeshen sapphire kitten
poppy j ah russian name
also thanks for the membership welcome
eyes phoenix whoa cool name
example different right the game can
only run so fast because of the
programming language it is written in
main class of lag and minecraft is too
many entities
too many hoppers or very high render
distance
it did get much much much much much much
better
after uh tuning down the render edition
so it was probably that
thank you
thank you daisy duncan riffic
mister dan
harbaugh cyrus thank you
super burger time
thank you for the pink team hey mama i
have a funny story for you
i was playing minecraft with my friend
last week and we were map making while
we were exploring we ran into a drowned
and my friend started to complain how he
never dropped
they never dropped tridents
oh but you are wrong they totally don't
they dropped the trident
for me the first time i killed the
drowned i don't know what you're talking
about you're wrong
[Music]
is there going to be in the manga school
are playing the new airship map there's
a completely new one that i haven't seen
yet
oh i do want to play among us again to
be honest i've been
like really hoping for an invitation
from someone anyone anyone
uh yeah
um i want to play among us i want to
play among us
i want to play among us
but we could we could practice with uh
with viewers
viewers only if there's a new map i
would want to
practice it first anyway
okay maybe we'll play mangas next week
if i have space
in my schedule yeah
[Music]
thank you for the pinky with the
creation of so many villagers and the
weird perhaps in the town now
and you playing so much attilae are you
planning on conducting human
transplantation
transmutation make a philosophy stone
how do you get to that idea
how do you get to that conclusion
thank you guys for sending uh money for
the louis vuitton bag
thank you for the red super chat
your shoes are sporty but what about
your skirt anyway here's my salary to
backfront
it's harder for me to catch the
livestream but still have fun watching
the archive looking forward to the
to watch along thank you i'm glad we
were able to do the watch along anyway
yesterday because i was really
um not sure if it was gonna happen
but i didn't have the energy to play
diablo 2 yesterday i think it was the
right choice to watch the movie after
all
for today i do plan to play diablo 2.
but it might get really late i mean on
my time it might start at 1 8 p.m
or or 9 p.m something like that
and we might play for like uh three
hours or so
and then maybe on monday
maybe on monday we'll play for another
a couple of hours now i'm personally
not sure if we get to finish
until the end of act two and i
i don't want to pressure myself anyone
a near yeah tomorrow no near uh it is um
going to be replaced by diablo tomorrow
today today today today today was
supposed to be near
automata but it's going to be replaced
by diablo 2 because diablo 2 is
currently
in an alpha test which is only goes
until tomorrow
evening so i want to make the best out
of it
listen to your commissions until i
pre-ordered the d2 remake right after
your stream yay
nice one tell them tell them
did you guys see actually the english
official diablo 2
uh twitter account replied to me
on twitter uh and i checked their
account it's funny they reply to a lot
of people
and uh like right as diablo it's so
funny
and they give out a lot of free codes
for the alpha as well
so i think their social media team reads
a lot
on twitter really cool
i was excited when i saw they messaged
me
and that was cool
[Music]
i'm not gonna let you guys come close to
my baby
baby is saving my arms right now
get sassy
no
no no
no oh my god you guys are
insane you guys are insane
it's disturbing to me
it's disturbing absolutely disturbing
i'm shocked
[Music]
oh baby
i don't like it give the baby better
treatment
don't be like that guys
why are you cooking an egg in a in a fry
van
yeah give it sweets yes yes and milk and
burgers burgers are okay too
oh thank god the milk is overwhelming
now
yeah yeah oh
oh beautiful
ah teddy bears hearts snacks
snake not snakes snacks sucks
so stupid why are you guys trying to
kill a baby that's already dead
[Music]
i want to protect the baby okay
you have you have angered me i have
no choice you leave me with no
choice
[Music]
you leave me with no choice guys
i will protect the baby with my shield
and my soy
no one can come close the baby anymore
[Music]
i protect
i protect the baby
here i can move my sword
[Music]
here this is this is me attacking you
slightly very slightly
bunk [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm trying i'm trying
okay
i'm trying
[\h__\h] slash
noodle arms shut up oh no it hurts so
much doesn't it
does it right
hahaha
nothing nothing happened i none
nothing nothing nothing happened
nothing
nothing happened nothing nothing
happened
i will continue to read super chats
okay
thank you again chunky chunk
and
i read the full one though here's my
salary to back fund it's harder for me
to catch a livestream but still have fun
watching i got looking forward to the
watch along
yeah uh i think i read all of it already
anyway thank you for watching the
archives too
i know uh that for your time zone it
must be a bit rough
for most of my streams recently i'm
sorry about that i'm sorry
but i appreciate the support support
nonetheless thank you so much
[Music]
thank you the
my girlfriend finally learned her place
in my heart she just texted me saying
if you aren't busy watching kiara call
me i'm so lucky to have such an
understanding girlfriend even if it
it did take her some time to get to this
point
well what did you did you call her
did you uh
did you call her or did you not because
you were busy with me
um you should probably have
uh called her
[Laughter]
i hope i help you and your girlfriend
are still
happy and together
uh shout out to your girlfriend um i'm
not trying to steal your boyfriend
i just need him to work for me at kfp
and and and because because
he he has a girlfriend i will not give
him a kiss
for this red super chat i will
give the kiss to someone else in the
chat oh catch it
three two one who caught it
wow fast nice
wow a lot of people say they caught it
are you are you all sharing one kiss
of me i don't
know if i should um
that's that might not be such a good
idea
you sharing among us among
us
i fell a few more
[Music]
okay now you don't have to share
now you don't have to share my she got
kissed
shut up maria thank you for the pinky
duncan the villagers of phillipston are
experiencing stockholm syndrome they
need to recover from the ptsd
i don't i don't even really know what
that syndrome is i've heard of it but i
don't really know what it is
but no my villagers are totally fine
they
they're fine they are fine
they are fine
at the office yes i've watched it but
but i learned nothing from it
falling in love with your kidnapper oh
oh my oh i don't think my blood just
fell in love with me
they fell in love with each other and
that's great
and i'm not that kidnapped or anyone it
doesn't apply
gosh i'm so tired for some reason my my
head just
ah
um
i should open the window
okay
i've been drinking a lot of water right
now
i think uh just a bit exhausted
i didn't take a break this week either
and i do have some uh weird
uh pain in my upper
upper upper upper belly area
like in my uh um
breast cage is that what you call it
but for the hose for the whole stream
rib cage yeah
how much more do we have i one day
[Music]
and i just need a little break after the
stream
or a big break i don't know see i don't
know i'm not sure what is better
streaming diablo 2 a little bit today
or just taking the rest of the day off
and streaming it a lot
tomorrow or um
like taking tomorrow off
and streaming uh a bit more
today tonight
[Music]
rest for the day yeah the thing is like
because it's weekend i kind of want to
make the best out of it because tomorrow
is monday
a lot of people might go back to work
tomorrow
[Music]
but like since tomorrow the alpha test
goes on
until 7 pm maybe we could just like i
don't know
start at the you know my time 7 p.m so
we could start at
uh maybe like
free three or two p.m
and then play until the alpha test is
over
[Music]
thank you
i did want to play i was i wanted to
stream more today because it's weekend
until we're done uh how much is twenty
thousand
korean uh
one no what's the currency is that a red
super chat
twenty thousand
at twenty dollars korean water is
confusing all those
zeroes
thank you meto fertility thank you soon
thank you
thank you gabe gabe gabe duncan
valkyrie
we love watching you have fun you being
happy makes my day and i'm sure that
sentiment is the same for everyone else
here you worry too much my oshie
thank you hello cat ah baby
i just you know i feel like the past few
days because i've been streaming so much
i've just have been having a lack of cat
i just need more cuddles
way more cuddles
i have i need more cats i prescribe
myself of more cat
iins five one nine dunkeshen looking for
the top function
spikes on top of the walls to keep
stalkers out
big towers with guards to check for
tickets and search lights too
[Laughter]
oh yeah those are suggestions to make
phoenix turn
more like idols it sounds like you're
trying to make phoenix
look like a prison though
but obviously it's just to protect the
idols right yeah
david jacob looking for the top function
igor
[Music]
oh okay
not sure how to respond to that super
chat but thank you for your support i
guess
lord edward thank you and moto account
and thank
yo
um
sorry cat did something cute she did
something cute
just it's a dunk is an iron heart
dancing wondering which turkish
investigation
[Music]
soon it will be the season of suica
of you the season of watermelons is
coming soon
looking forward to eating watermelon by
the lake
outside in the summer oh
thank you for the red super chat suica
looking forward to eating you
can't
baby
[Music]
why are you not a lab cat i wish you
were a lab cat
why not huh you love
cuddling you love being pet just be stay
on my lap and i would pet you for hours
and hours and hours and hours
me
zero three one zero thank you for the
thinking what casualties there are no
casualties what are you talking about
[Music]
rachel khan bathroom security
shift zero zero nine duncan captain coin
cup function
these super chats are
hilarious thank you guys for all the
super chats uh that you guys sent
um specifically during the time the
incident
with uh the incident that we don't talk
about because we all don't remember it
pivot
nothing nothing
18 yeah the incident when when someone
turned 18 we visited someone's uh
birthday party yeah
yep yep yep that's what happened
a raspberry thank you for the pinky
i cannot read your super chat out loud
it will it will um confuse
the chickens i cannot read it
who gave the baby up
how do you call them how do you call
those in english
lucky lucky clubbers cloak clovers club
club covers
clovers clovers clovers
is it clovers or clubbers is it
clever
yo clever
the way you again the way you guys try
to tell me
when you write like when you write out
you you say it like c-l-o-v-e-r-s that's
that it's just not gonna help me
okay the w helps w clovers okay
okay it's so stupid
when you say you read it let you say it
like this and just write the exact
same original writing there
oh that's just because you guys your
first language must be english and you
just that that's
that's that makes sense to you but it
doesn't make sense to someone
who whose first language is not english
it just doesn't help me
but thank you
[Music]
iron hi thank you
general pickled induction space turtle
thank you for the
red super chat last space turtle i'm
riding hikers for all of hallelujahn so
i wrote you one these
lines are three stops as bright as the
sun
she light up the world with her lively
lively
live lively energy i hope you like it
thank you
thank you damson
i am son i am dawson
thank you thank you for the uh haiku and
thank you for the generous donation for
the kind support
i know by the way i know who you are now
i know who this person is
what i will not say
i found out i found out who the ministry
of health is mhm
let's just say youtube talks to you
okay let's see what the which by the way
leads me
to know that this is the the fake men's
federal ministry of health
it's fake so whatever
they say it doesn't matter but let's
read it anyway
hello today we come to do a routine
check on the stock of chickens in your
free-range chicken farm
to do that we will access the facility
to count the number of chickens and
record the increase in your stock
compared to last month
well it's a federal offense to the
knights as well first of all you're fake
second of all you didn't even come last
month
so you don't have any record of last
you're welcome to enter it now and count
how many chickens there are now
but you won't have anything to compare
this
thank you for the pinky
yes instead it's actually a pinky and
then afterwards the people uh
tried to try to confuse me with other
colors
thank you for the pinky aurora thank you
thank you thank you for also pinky now i
believe you i believe that that is a
pinky
what pudding says was uh because he
sends a
uh what was that a blue or a green one
and says it's purple
but let's never can be trusted thank you
thank you for the pinky
weird currency pain yeah
sorry you know what i was thinking i
should make like a little memo
like a um right on a piece of paper
all these currencies uh red super chats
like what a red super chat would be and
just have it like a sticky note on my pc
that would already be so
helpful and just have it open whenever
they are
someone already made one on reddit oh
really
oh send it to me on twitter that would
actually be helpful i write it down on a
piece of paper and stick it to my
monitor
if someone can send it to me that would
be actually really nice
i mean i usually i mean there's probably
some currencies that i never get anyway
but maybe the ones that are most often
uh here
rip the poor cappy sticky notes
oh yeah i think there's still some
things on those canopy sticky notes that
i have not fulfilled
yet
general pickled indonesian mutation
pyramidal question daisy thank you for
the red super chat
[Music]
dojo i guess yeah those are five larges
possibly
maybe thank you daisy for your support
me game of thrones nice to see you more
often again
[Music]
south carolina thank you thank you very
much
steven light angus and boring made fun
duncan
fill in the blank sanctions
[Music]
got my little sister in tv was recently
just right beside me enjoying your
stream
that's cute thank you
oh i hope she's enjoying it
my stomach hurts
and thank you for the thinking
give me kiss back cd made a mistake
give kids back gideon
give back
keep this back
keep
i don't mean i i'm not are you you gave
me but that basically then you kissed me
that's wrong too but no no i don't want
the case from you i'll kiss you back
again so that
wait i'll kiss
[Music]
that makes sense doesn't it
i think it i think
anyway
okay jd is here with some australian
language
once again good day ggs kiara
here's a pineapple fifty dollars mate
enjoying the stream
coral couture is looking a beaut i'll be
missing your livestream
i'm working at camp for a week can i
request but you're here
what happened to the camp can i request
if you do an alarm message mate
a long message for waking up
wake up mate it's time to freaking wake
up
why are you not awake yet i'm going to
smash a pineapple in your face if you
don't wake up right
away wake up
was that okay
you're welcome
[Laughter]
alfie kantakirangishin i went ahead and
looking for the top tank
shin patron stripe thank you thank you
for a red super chat patreon
here's a gift from me and the bro gang
and the other kfb employees with coins
we found at work
so you and dad can go out to eat and
have a fun time the next time you see
each other with much love and by the way
we're actually not going to work while
you're gone loves mom
well i'm gone you're not gonna work
well you will work i will make you work
thank you
thank you though um the time when i will
see kelly again this seems still very
far away but
whenever we meet i will i will
go have a nice dinner with her for sure
we're gonna go eat jackie nicole again i
can already smell it from here
thank you did i hear a cat meow no
what no yeah
huh
i think that was something else
why did everyone hear me out
there's no cat in my room
anyway perfume thank you for your
support thank you
alfie
[Music]
you fail you lost two times now to fall
inside kotori or not there's only a
little detail that no one here just do
the usual room is a cool place thank you
but no
it's not just a little detail i said it
is
only it only applies when i fall inside
kotori
i remember that i don't remember that
shortcut a rare sight that is true yeah
i don't use it much
you are lagging oh my god i am so
annoyed by so many people saying i'm
lagging and this
is i i'm not lagging my fps is maybe a
little bit low
but i'm not lagging
gosh
i'm trying my best here okay
trying i'm trying
eight nine nine now really did we go up
again finally
really
oh my god
um according to youtube channel page yes
but according to youtube
studio i am at
897 5500
i can't i i can't even read numbers
anymore
after that see more noisy
that's that's what my youtube studio
says but okay youtube channel went
up again so okay
okay we will see where it goes they are
going
in different directions sending me
mixed signals
well whatever
saying thank you for the super chat no
no no no you were trying to
write what i will say but that was not
what i said i said thank you for the red
super chat okay and then you're also
missing a chunk
so tai chi if you want to be cool and
impersonate me
in the super chat message then you gotta
try a bit harder
thank you
thank you painting
knee
some of you guys just have really funny
names and profile pictures
staff all that kitchen back folks
function daisy thank you for a red super
chat how long are these
super chess going on oh my god daisy
says i'll leave this here for tomorrow
then have you checked out kelly's lyric
dive yet her comments on you being the
sun were pretty cute but her thoughts on
bully were very interesting turns out
takamaya
interpretation is entirely inaccurate
well yeah actually uh
i've seen the a clip of her talking
about the
the something but about bullying
actually i messaged her afterward after
my stream
uh an astr who's like
what is this actually about and she did
tell me that it wasn't like necessarily
like
about me not not only at least like yeah
i mean she wrote it about like several
things which i guess she also explained
in her own stream
but yeah it's definitely not all about
me
there might be some small parts
[Music]
that are about me but like or
referencing to me but not necessarily
about me
which i knew because that couldn't have
been about me
i told you i
know how she feels about me and that's
not how she feels about me
but maybe it's just this kind of urge to
include me in her songs in some kind of
way
because she just likes me so much and
wants me in her lyrics
even if it doesn't fit very well yeah
daisy thank you samuel potelli thank you
for the pinky
hi ken i would be honored if you adopted
us as children as your children i didn't
really have good parents growing up so
letting us call you mom and dad
it's a real honor i even started smiling
at the fun of it so thank you for
helping me smell more
that sounds very serious so i'm a bit
worried about that but yes of course i
adopt all of you so um
there you go
you're welcome everyone everyone shall
be adopted into this
kfb family
jacob fitzsimmons
thank you for the pinkie ko tony is a
loot tony must i remind you about that
art by mama luna and what
place was his face oh i don't know
i have i don't know i i
i don't know i don't recall that's a bit
embarrassing don't don't ask me
kotori went there without my permission
so i don't wanna i don't wanna think
about it again
we had a little fight after that now
we're good again
mama said on me you said you put
yourself a
stare on your own that didn't sit on you
but it's okay i love you anyway i love
you anyway
what but but but don't do that again
don't do it again okay
chris jobs donkey shin diaz nine nine
nine ten cushion people duncan
beer dad duncan
thank you guys for telling me my english
is good thank you
your accent is extremely cute oh come on
flame extension thank you for the
thinking you have single-handedly made
me like german
accents but i just don't feel about bad
about your accent
uh singing-headedly huh flame accident
i guess it means you haven't heard
anyone yet with a real german accent
because
what i'm the way i speak english okay i
might have some pronunciation issues
sometimes
but listen to
an actual german accents a german a
german woman that speaks english with an
actual german accent
it is very painful
especially to me even it's very painful
and then trust me you will probably not
like it anymore
what i speak is not not much of a
german accent
i guess although i think you probably
heard it like
in movies or so before i'm sure there's
lots of movies where
they have like german characters that
speak in a german accent
uh yeah i've seen that before too
sometimes some american sitcoms or
whatever have like german characters pop
up that
speak in a very exaggerated german
accent
uh even
yeah so in community they had that too
in community there was in the later
seasons there was
a group of i think germans and they
spoke
in a very thick german accent
i think then it's not that cute anymore
germans get it rough on tv shows and cut
that's kinda true
[Music]
a tv series is always going to depict
like
like other nationalities in their
thickest accents possible
uh the statue of me
i think i would if i would build a
statue of myself i would probably try it
to make it look like
a wealthy canada by the way i did see
um in my art hashtag the other day i saw
someone making a statue
of my sword which was
absolutely huge like huge dimension i
wish i could build that because it
looked
so [\h__\h] dope but the amount of
materials that i would need for that is
insane i guess i could build like a
smaller version but then it wouldn't
look so cool anymore
yeah the tip the tip it was stuck in the
in the ground it was turned around but
the st the tip was actually um
i think made with like light stones or
so because it was uh
lighting up it looked so
cool but huge
um but canada you already have a statue
in minecraft
i don't know what you're talking about
that is
colonel kotori
i see some of you saw it too that was
really cool
i wish i could build that huge thing but
um
on our server like if it was like a
server
like a creative server then okay but on
our server
that would take me like a year or so
the amount of resources necessary for
that is just
not normal maybe a bit smaller version
would
would be possible
a pickle
thank you choose for the cats okay i'll
give them some
lots lots of pieces later when the
stream is over
and i see the end of the minecraft super
chat actually
signal boosting discord chat what would
it take to get a watchling of
the cats movie instead of lord of the
rings well a lot of rings were done with
that by now
uh the cat's movie i've actually never
watched it
should should we watch it i heard it's
uh i don't know
cursed is it cursed
don't don't don't please no why
oh my god let's watch it oh my god
well maybe we should watch it i'll skip
your stream oh come on
oh come on oh come on that's what it's
about
the curse also i wanted to watch uh
something i haven't watched yet anyway
so
foreign
yeah maybe i'll maybe i'll make it a
public watch wrong i haven't ever done
should we watch that with ina okay i
finally
thought of a good movie to watch with
ina
we're gonna watch cats you're gonna be
forced to watch it because it's a
special watch along with ina
you can't miss that let's watch it with
inna
oh i wonder if she's seen it before
you know what before i forget it let me
ask her right now
you know have you seen the movie
[Music]
cuts
my people say my weight my chickens
my chickens say it's cursed but
maybe we should watch that
oh she's there she's laughing she wrote
lmao
i haven't seen it yet i just know it's
cursed let's do it
she also hasn't seen that
okay we got a movie
ah we gotta move it we got the movie
we're going watch cats the musical i
hope you will all be there guys
i don't know on which channel yet by the
way we will see about that
oh she writes lmao can't wait she's
excited for it
yeah no no it will not be memories only
it will be public public
yay now uh the other princess bride
what's the name we will watch that uh
members only
okay let's have some private sexy time
romantic movie time
[Laughter]
um
thank you they are all very
chickens to not bring shame to kfp you
have to be grateful to inna
you have to say thank you ina thank you
she's also somehow your boss because
whenever i'm not there
she's your boss instead of me
yes okay good everyone says thank you
look everyone's looking forward to cats
now
nice nice nice wonderful
wonderful you all seem to have a good
manners that's good to see
all right continuing thank you this
logaria for giving me that idea by the
way that's a very good idea
patrick
and that's it that's the minecraft super
chats
now what is left
is the super chats from today's super
chat reading stream
um
[Music]
uh we can do it we can do it we can do
it oh that's
uh it's a bit much but we can do it
[Music]
okay okay let's go let's go
oh it went down again oh my god it went
from
oh my god it's so so stupid youtube what
the hell
patrick
[Music]
your take on clarity really strengthened
the fight on energy and flying to the
moon was so graceful
you really do see and recognize how
passionate you are to do your best
that's okay everyone thank you telescope
thank you
well thank you everyone for um those
congratulations
super chats which seem kind of awkward
now
tai chi
[Music]
chat for 900k but uh
i guess i have to send you back the
money
tai chi
thank you tai cha i'll okay i get i
contact you privately
and send you back the money
thank you
[Music]
hi thank you for a red super chat
send i'll send it back to you too i've
refund you the rents which are daisy
[Music]
uh sores keep playing thank you thank
you for the thinking
with yourself an accent oh god uh
how do i read yourself and like cowboy
i can't i can't i can't whoops i don't
and i can't i can't i can't i can't beat
cowboy
done done i can't i can't i can't i
don't know how
upside down glenn did a super chat hey
hey there let me see i can't i can't
that's
australian i can't
uh you've done a good thing here with
900k of them they're chickens
make sure you keep all wrangle get here
you're hotter than
my curling iron i reckon go get them
bird
i'm sorry howdy hot howdy
howdy on how howdy
i can't you don't feel it today
thank you for the pinky i'll i'll
message you to refund you the money
rise of freedom flanders thank you thank
you for a red super chat
i'll refund you in a moment congrats to
900k
yeah every one of those subs is more
than deserved for all the hard work you
put into this level this is painful can
i read this next week on monday or
tuesday
[Music]
okay
no
i don't i don't know i can't i can't
uh
almost exhausted my head hurts
whoa eric what the [\h__\h] now
okay i think we already read a lot of
super chats let's just read the these
ones either tomorrow
after diablo or like i don't know any
other day
next week if that is okay with you
uh i i guess i will
possibly take the rest of the day a
thankful moment
i might spontaneously put up a stream
later
if i feel better
not feeling uh so well right now just go
chill with my cats
watch some youtube videos
and uh i'll see you either in a few
hours
or tomorrow rather early you gotta
wake up early for me tomorrow because
we're playing diablo if we're playing
diablo tomorrow then it's gonna be quite
the only stream
if we stream tomorrow as i said it might
be 2 pm or 3 pm
my time until the alpha
is over i wonder if you just end up
getting kicked out of the server
if you're still on at 7 pm
probably just kicks you out right and
loses connection
so let's just play as far as we can
yeah it's offline yeah so i wonder how
they do it i guess i don't know
maybe it's um maybe they implemented
some kind of
online function to see if you're online
or not i don't know
i love this btf i'm glad you like it
it's my original
uh museum
all right and thank you guys for taking
your time to um
you know hang out with me reading the
super chats
hope you had a good time
even though we were just reading and
having a little chit chat
and eating breakfast
thank you and i'll see you
later and now i need a break i'm sorry
i'm not very
high energy today ah well yeah we got
the cats watch along with that
oh what a blessed day this is thank you
and in german we say auf wiedersehen
thank you love you all
thank you
bye bye
[Music]
so
you