[Music]
for
okay okay okay I tapped out so that bgm
is gone for a
moment how you
doing let me tweet really quickly I have
to Tab out cuz I have to
tweet
twitter
Twitter how are you
doing no how you
doing
starting
now okay
what what's Community
YouTube music never used to stop that's
because like most of the games are
console games used that's me most of the
games are console games and with the
game
capture window it just keeps on playing
whether or not I Tab out doesn't
matter but this is a steam
game so that's
different
[Music]
oh o
okay s
BTM
K we're starting off
here
cuz I have something to
reveal what could it be okay did you
guys place your bets because I didn't
tell you to place your bets and now now
that I think of it I should have made
you place your
[Laughter]
bets no you know that's narissa narissa
is going to be the
one not saying she's pan don't don't get
it twisted
dead no misunderstanding no there's um
no no new overlay
[Music]
no what what's special enough
to tell you all that I'm doing a reveal
but not special enough to do its own
reveal
[Laughter]
stream no no sword no sword sword is
sword
is don't even get me
started yeah okay new song
no oh oh I see
some something that
maybe oh maybe it's an announcement of
an announcement no I did say I will re I
will reveal something so can't be that a
new
hairstyle
no side games Ambassador oh I
wish Chef head for every outfit get the
hell out of here get the hell out of the
out of here with your
propaganda okay it has to do with this
outfit I'll tell you
that a golden
shepher I hate you
guys
oh wait someone got it where is the oh
yep someone got
it I saw one person got it
okay we want to finish the game today so
I'm not going to make uh too much of a
deal big deal out of it I'm not going to
not going to let you guys suffer for too
long uh can I move the table away yeah
and the chair yeah and
then I'm just going to reveal it and
then we're going to see it all all all
of the stream throughout the
stream bikini armor
bikini armor version of
this
pacifier no
no I don't get any use out of the
pacifier
anyway why would I move it over to this
outfit ripped aror
oh wait for the future I really like
that idea cuz like recently we just uh
talked about you know cuz we saw
someone's outfit being being ripped and
I was like a that's like the god of
games maybe in the future guys can you
remind me of this in the future I want
like a ripped version of my
outfit interesting yeah battle battle
damage remind me although it it kind of
would have fits the most with an outfit
like this not like anything like casual
I don't think that makes too much sense
it's got to be something like
[Music]
this okay okay I'm going to I'm going to
show you it's it's not a big deal I
don't want to make a big deal out of it
uh but I had this idea I don't know why
when how I had this idea but I'll show
you
and why is this making me nervous it's
not not even a big
deal what a tease what a tease she
ran okay I guess I'll show
you I guess I shall show
you are you
[Music]
ready what night
W
oh okay here before after before
after it's a color
[Music]
variation yeah I can of course uh have
it with uh the different hair too so
before H before
after
before
after and then we can also have it
without the
jacket T so even the the darker mesh
over my skin also is a little bit
brighter before after before after
sug do you like it I'll zoom
in so the golden details were previously
white see
and the lace was previously white but
it's now
black like
this
so I love the golden with the
white I still kept like an overall blue
color f i i we looked at like
other
possibilities like having pink or you
know other contrast colors but it still
looked kind kind of the best in blue and
also it works with my hair cuz I
couldn't do a color variation of my hair
before after
before
after
[Music]
after before
after shiny waa I'm a white
knight player to waa oh yeah true just
like Gand
oh player two I like that Paladin
wa looks nice doesn't it I mean
obviously it's just like a simple like
you know something you could do in
Photoshop uh it's not like redrawn
so it is that but yeah oh I did not
notice a flaw right now damn
it the Shadows aren't moving damn it but
they're not were they moving originally
at all the Shadows on my shoulders the
hair Shadows were those ever moving I
think probably yeah oh
well nice
nice Dark Knight over the Holy Night you
prefer the dark version well I don't
know I think you know it's it's uh let's
say I play an RPG that's just a little
bit more on the brighter side then I can
use this one and if I play an RPG that's
on the darker side I can use this one
whoa dark mode light mode now we can
play
chess a
chess
yeah nice
idea ah medieval to you with
this oh I didn't realize that just like
my doy you outfit this is also now like
a black and white color
variation oh my God you like the white
one more oh that's actually nice to hear
thank you I'm glad I could make
something that you like
M you like holy nles thank you bore do
you oh I want to do that
oh and then dancing in this outfit if
only it was 3D oh yeah but here here's
oh looks so
cool yeah I I um got really excited to
show it to you guys because I didn't
know like when else to show you and I
didn't want to make a stream that is
specifically just for showing you this
color so I thought okay while I'm
playing an RPG game I should show you
this cuz when if not doing an RPG game
inav
dark demon Nissa versus V night lawyer
let's fight Nissa but sword look sword
is in in the void sword has been drawn
but sword is in the void for me to never
be
used because of
complicated complicated
things it is what it is it's okay you
guys can still draw me swords as fan art
and I can still pin it as a PNG on my
back I can still do that but it's got to
come from you guys as fan
art is the sword banished into the void
it's gone it's only in our
dreams golden waa skin golden Knight
next oh niny
thank you onini I just revealed my white
night version from this to this w i look
really
sophisticated
sooy okay with this I think we are
ready to go back to Grand blue fantasy
relink yay white Nittis I don't know
something about this it looks so H like
I'm I'm like a I don't know I got I got
a job uh what's the
word up not
upgrade I was
uh I forgot it Warrior flight
yeah a class change well no I I mean a
promotion yeah I got promoted to the the
queens or the princesses Holy Holy Night
Guard m
from night to
Paladin yeah so I'm holy night so you
better pray every night to the Holy
Night pray to the Wawa and I shall
protect you with no swords just my hands
and my sheer presence and the Holy Light
that I
radiate cuz I can't afford the sword
I got promoted to holy night but I
wasted all my money on getting a white
drip new drip let's
go head tohe combat pow pow pow
pow I I can take you down I can take you
down the street to go have a tea a cup
of
tea
yeah
okay turn off the music let's go gaming
Gamers let's go gaming
Gamers over here oh
oh I blend
in I blend
in but only for now only for the
starting screen I'm blending in I I show
my myself a little bit bigger
today cuz I look so fancy chameleon w
she
Blends beat me up with your holy fists
ma'am leave it to me leave it to me ton
ton ton ton all right guys let's get
back into
this let's see let's
see can we finish it
today would be
amazing
I need a red oh a red version would be
dope too
yeah I can see
that okay
okay
[Music]
continue Speed
Run yeah I was I would like it to be
something like that
yeah hisor let's go
we we're
back so
yesterday you guys all watch the stream
right so I don't need to give you a
recap let's go the
part oh did I press the wrong
thing no I didn't
okay
this is just a
beginning second
stream
did I enjoy the snow area yeah but we
were apparently underleveled for the
boss but yeah I don't know if I can
maybe do a little bit flying chicken
look at that a little bit
of grinding a little bit grind
blue oh I worked too much last stream I
watch was heart Challenger you mean the
Valentine's the fa failed Valentine
stream the one that didn't really
happen I tried to change some settings
but I don't really think it's different
much but yeah the mic
settings right they stream outfit this n
it's too
medieval it's different really okay ooh
[Music]
pretty I love the red floor
Dam the names are kind of
weird
[Music]
small
is our ship just going to break each
time we take it
[Music]
out okay travel between towns
congratulations on the reaching seed
Hollow fast traveling between seed
Hollow and FKA is now available from the
docks or the deck of the grand
Cipher oh he's so
[Music]
pretty see I feel like I'm
playing FF
14 this like
an oh side
quest you want me to take down some Timo
wolves
okay weren't those in the first areas
where we were oh do I have to go back
there or are they also in the next area
that we go
to they look like
lalafells
oh
white paper on public transport
uhhuh come get your flower wine clears
your sunny skies won't find it anywhere
else flower
wine I mean flower wine I guess that's
you can make wine out of flowers right
cuz you can make juice out of
flowers not unrealistic right oh W this
is pretty almost looks
like a place that I went to in Paris
but more more fantasy
style rose wine oh well I guess you just
got to make a juice and then add some
alcohol flower juice Works some alcohol
I like um
s flower
FL
whoa yo this city is
amazing they put so much work into this
huh ice SP oh I can already give this
back let's
go chieftain's
braid and
[Music]
fortitude nice
oopsie this is where it came from right
but I went to the side
yeah they have a lot of uh NPCs running
around too so it doesn't look too sad
and
empty they need more people running
these places though like nobody's here
in this
one oh
art art is my passion want to buy
[Music]
something I don't know why I keep on
pressing that I'm confused this is nice
why did they imprison the fountain what
did the fountain
do our little little friend that always
travels with
us naughty
Fountain new
arrivals I don't know what to do
ah I think I was told I should get a new
weapon uh so we got to find the Smith of
this
city I was going to explore a little
more little bit more
anyway so let me look
around oh he was behind me
really oh this is so this is look at
this little path through the shadow and
oh the flowers oh my
God desert Ash okay are we going to a
desert
next oh my
God oh my God so
pretty really great design of this
city
oh oh I didn't even see that what
there's something there oh crap no cat
oh so
[Music]
small are we going to have a problem
here no no don't
worry I need the keys where are the
[Music]
keys
oo oh this place looks like you can buy
some old furniture
[Music]
here I want those I want those couches
and
[Music]
chairs think got to appreciate the work
that they put in so you guys said the
Smith was behind me I wonder where but
this is not behind me I'm just going
somewhere else again it's so pretty this
could be like in Italy where I don't
know cat cat so many cats have you guys
noticed there wasn't a single dog
yet game was made by a cat lover
[\h__\h] yeah Spain
mhm cuz of all the the flowers looking a
little bit more
tropical
a knight needs help from a knight oh I
wish I could make a cocktail a knight
wants help for a
cocktail keep your voice on can't you
see I'm on a secret mission here I'm
trying to get info on a certain cocktail
called Sparkling innocence if you know
anything could you let me and only me
know I'll make it worth your
while okay I'll see what I can
do don't know if I want to support you
drinking during your
job h damage to tail finin
okay
uh what find a replacement
[Music]
okay getting all the Side Quests for
now okay now I'm going back to the city
center let's see if we can find the
Smith
oh oh Treasure Chest
[Music]
cute is this your new man your new man
cave you have a twin brother over there
or what or is it a
clone looks exactly like you a champion
Merit is a resource needed for forging
weapons make your journey Easier by
creating a variety of weapons for any
situation okay so I need to make a
weapon or I can make a Lea Belt doesn't
sound so special but
okay our whip will be replaced by a belt
additionally I would like to have L
shankla
please I guess I'll make this oh I need
the chi ttin braid
okay how much stronger is this done
before ah like
20 oh ah oh from 38 to 70
[Music]
nice let's equip it and then oh we uh
level it up to right away uh what was
that button a the level this
one
enhance goes up to
okay no maybe no cuz I also don't seem
to have
enough material anyway okay and then
people are saying I should bring EO back
into the team so I'll also see if we can
make a new weapon for
E the
ttle what is
this nice looking
okay m yeah that'll be a big upgrade
from look at her original We weapon
stats oh my
God cuz we haven't even leveled it I
think
okay uh so
this and
[Music]
then oh I could do more
hey no
okay okay and you guys said replace her
with what was it Catalina or
Rosetta I'm not
sure no more money oh my God I ran out
of
money oh wait what can I sell do I have
something I can
sell I can be sell for rupes however
they can't be brought back
mm
oh oh will I not need these for anything
else for like
crafting broke
CH that would be a lot of money
sheesh oh okay those are for selling
nice okay get them out of
here H sigil can be sold as well huh but
I I I'll keep them for now
m
[Music]
don't know if it really will make sense
to have health on euo uh later we might
change
it why does no one have this one
equipped what the hell oh but we need
Griffin Griffin feathers for that anyway
okay
oh s is we always need W in the team
right so we better upgrade her stuff
to
durendal
oh I can't now I actually ran out of
these things
no Champion Merit and chief T's
braid I hope we find more of that
soon okay no problem for now and then we
look back to e and see okay we need to
give her some stuff here to bring her
back on our
level skill fire mhm
Burns oh what is this link level gain
okay's
this concentration cast a circle that
grants Stout heart and boost the charge
speed of star
gaze cast a dark ah let's do this one
yeah why not what is this cast a circle
of lightning that in inflicts paraly
paralyzes paraly paral
paralyzes also sounds
useful and I don't have to go this right
way huh but do you guys generally for
the people who did play the game already
do you guys just try to fill out
everything or do you actually ignore
some
[Music]
paths paralysis that's it
yeah I will have everything
okay eventually I get everything okay
what what did just
happen oh was it
trying asking me if I want to put it
there if if if she's an NPC do I still
have to take care of what
skills are assigned so she can use
them I think I was told since uh the
protagonist Wawa has a healing skill too
maybe I don't need to give EO the
healing skill
right
gravity oh that's the one
yeah okay this looks
good is this a g game or regular it's a
got a game originally but this is a
regular game
mmm to he is convenient yeah I I also
have a healing skill though until I get
rid of it but
yeah what's this chicken dizzy fresh
hold plus 1% anyway I'll go up till here
for now and
[Music]
then what is this
again we'll give this priz well okay so
you is improved now and we'll switch out
our party members so what did you guys
say rosetta sorry I didn't see your
answer you wanted to change the scale
from Fairy the one that makes a jump oh
yeah okay I'll look into
it they'll be closer to leveling you'll
still have to get them bonuses in the
tree but they'll all have their moves
unlocked uhhuh
okay so you're saying I should
[Music]
wait I'm one of your favorite
vtubers thank you happy to hear that
change foretta
resett for Aisle
okay Cataline useful as a tank yeah I
would have
green cute almost only Blondie group if
I had like the the Calo girl then we
would be a full Blondie group or even
the Zeda girl is also a blondie right so
many blondies but I really like her P
pastel bluish hair
[Music]
color um okay then I'll look into her
cuz what do I have uh the one that froze
me back was Pendle right
summons Fuji and Nicola to whisk fairy
back to safety so okay it's supposed to
like help me by going back but I don't
know while GG engages foes at the front
all three Pats remain on the battlefield
so what else uh I don't I'd have to give
myself a new skill though cuz I don't
have anything to choose from
[Music]
anyway let's
see what's the next skill this is
something
we
got not what's the next one this one
no the next skin looks so far away it's
this
one H oh it's German for like killing
someone but like you know
H it's more like uh not like killing but
more like taking someone's life maybe
like uh yeah execution yeah
thanks grants attack to fairy as well as
critical hit R supplement it's a
buff okay this I can get behind but that
it will take me oh I can't even afford
it need
76 okay we maybe need to deal with the
current skills a little bit longer
her buff supposed be really good get the
buff
[Music]
emate ah look do I look different to you
do you notice anything
different would be funny if you actually
don't notice
anything I don't know I don't I don't
know I don't I don't feel it yeah I mean
invent really cool but
[Music]
like
how
long did I do something with my hair
[Music]
wow
no get equip slot atast equip slot
what H this
one a new sigil
slot I don't see an equip
slot
okay then let's go to
here and give myself a new
[Music]
sigil
oopsie um how about attack power two
yeah
[Music]
okay ah wait do I huh do I have money
yeah wait if I have money what was I
trying to
do
upgrade no I was going to make her
weapon right for wa
weapon oh no but I don't
[Music]
have
no
materials but yeah I guess I couldn't
upgrade the zel
fully yeah
[Music]
okay
10 she's so behind I mean we could you
know uncap and level this sword
for
now should
I do it time to don't level MC weapon
okay story will help me out I yeah right
will the story give me another
sword for
her
I don't know will
it anyway we have to grind a little bit
right so how about we jump into a
[Music]
fight and let's undertake a
quest by
difficult I don't
[Music]
know uh don't know what you want to do
what are these
rewards I see a feather and a card H
this is this is for getting
another character
right
mhm
can I see details of what I'm getting
for the
re menus are so
overwhelming should I do the second one
for the weapon
okay do all the easy ones first ah
true
okay timber wolves oh I have to do
timber wolves anyway do these do these
timber wolves
[Music]
wait no ah let me out of
here let
me how do I how do I cancel that how do
I cancel that how do I cancel that how
do I cancel
[Music]
it press ready
first
okay what's X right ah
here let me out of here
abandon all the buttons are so
different okay please give me this Quest
again but this time
closed
close I didn't want to play with real
players I was
scared
okay ikim our warm up battle with some
timber
wolves they're yelling timber oh wait I
can press I'm almost
waiting how do I fight
again
[Music]
so
far
how's the audio
guys like battle audio is loud but if
you guys say it's okay then it's okay
what who who
[Music]
who fancy magic
sheesh it's
okay
okay wake
up
I need your
fur for some side
quest give me give me give me give me
your fluffiness M
fluff P J is on the loud side but it's
okay okay ooh so
[Music]
many so far still really weak though
they're level
five should have I could have done these
earlier
huh they die like flies I'm guessing by
the way I never did it but I'm guessing
this
explodes I'm not
really not
much
oh Birds it's the birds this is what a
horn bird what does it say horn
bird horny
[Music]
bird
okay defeat free foes with Throne
objects oh man I never got much of the
side
objects object objects
[Music]
objectives I got the last hit I felt
it e get MVP okay but you got to be
thankful cuz I put you back into the
team
s+ yo okay uh how
[Music]
what picking up items in environment
weap what I don't understand what you're
saying like why why
not let me do another
one how much xed did I get from that by
the way was it a good amount I didn't
look did you guys look
goblins gobble gobble gobble oh and I
get glitter Stones nice we need more
money
close oh I did get a level up oh yeah
right 18 17 17 19
[Music]
okay
did we got a scene like this last time
[Music]
too she gets MV a lot
huh I want to get praised by the game as
[Music]
well
yeah
more more action
please oh my God the W I don't need the
invincibility skill I'm Invincible all
on my
own strong
[Music]
boy
oh does it
[Music]
weak where are the
slimes where
where oh this one oh there why are they
here wait that's like
a more sparkly colorful one
H am I imagining this what it say silver
[Music]
slime yeah I couldn't see much
either
oh that's it again this always makes me
feel like I can jump in and then be
sucked in like it's a black
[Music]
hole I'm
burning oh I saw in the live hashtag
yesterday when I was going for it
uh apparently when I was frozen I could
have
I could have like wiggled my way out of
it instead of
waiting I was wondering like this is
kind of weird that I have to wait for so
long and I did press some buttons at
some
point gold
[Music]
slime but nothing happened when I
pressed the buttons like I didn't feel
like anything was happening so I gave
up I did try but like only for a little
bit and I didn't see any
anything really reacting to it so far
okay I guess I have to
[Music]
wait I'm just a very patient person
okay what the
hell
[Music]
I hate
the 30 seconds remaining what I'm trying
my best here oh okay it's it's it's
manageable if if he doesn't [\h__\h] run
so
far oh my God
done not done still [\h__\h]
[Music]
SL was it just kill as much oh oh yeah
defeat 50
FS oh oh there may have been another
Goblin Slayer wave after the slimes cuz
it was five out of
seven yo I thought I failed the whole
thing what rank do I get for
this oh not even
s oh okay we get S that's fine could
have almost gotten the next
one I feel
like it was all
right
EST
sure my tea is cold I want to warm up my
tea have you guys ever warmed up your
tea in the
microwave is that weird to do that I've
did it I've done it like once I think
you have you do it all the time can I do
it I don't want this tea to be
wasted can I do it please I'll do it
until I don't know maybe 30 seconds 1
minute or
so how long should I put it
[Music]
in yeah I do have a cup warmer but it's
uh unopened I
[Music]
think
say hi to junky
[Music]
wony
te
[Music]
for
oh
yeah I think that got plenty hot in
there
nice nice nice nice nice
nice okay
undertake another quest
uh
H defend hell hello hello hello let me
do this one though defeat we Goblin boss
why is this what is this title why is
this person who wrote this wheezing
isn't that
laughing what do this
mean is the goblin boss going to laugh
at
me oh boy these damned goblins who
attacked our village Huff sick are back
again they obey their Alpha we sick so
if we take him out guess that's easier
said than done man I ran all the way
home all from home to posters while
you're recording how I'm
breathing oh is it like yeah cuz he ran
he was out of breath but what's the
wheezing
about oh
well the quest Giver is tired is there a
different meaning to wheezing that I
didn't know
about a strong breath from from being
tired
okay like
[Laughter]
this what about the sick it's like a
hick but it's
what Bring It
On
oh Ash bom is what you say to that in
German ass bomb when you jump into a
pool your ass first with the intention
of making a Big
Splash in German we say Ash
[Music]
bomber
was will someone revive her or do I got
to do it oh she's back okay
nice bloodthirsty again you just came
out of the bloodthirsty State what wrong
with you it's almost dead
though let's see he's almost dead this
one's a fast
one link
attack take him down we can do it 3
minutes
maybe was that under three
minutes wa is dead
no where were you and W was dead
no we
dead W cleared within 3 minutes but
that's only because I was I guess in
this case overleveled for
[Music]
once
at a lot of time still yeah I know but
maybe it's just because I was
overleveled has the real veal been
revealed is this honestly like a thing
that you're not going to notice coming
in here like when when your lady got a
new hairstyle and you're she's like so
notice anything new and you're like uh
no what do you mean subtle
it's not really
subtle I
mean from this okay I mean I mean no
it's not subtle maybe it's it's more
noticeable if I'm like full body though
right like this is obvious like
hello
hello Mossy
Moss should I stream like this
[Laughter]
like
this okay I'll stream like
this I will do side quest I can report
let's go I'll do one more one more one
more for now should I do all I'm almost
I only need three more of this like easy
mode Goblin Soldier hell ground survives
with at least 65% HP all
right might as well do
all okay I just hope we we really have
time for
this
yeah I'm not brighter I'm not brighter
at all you guys just forgot to put turn
on dark mode
today oh my god did you get a new outfit
huh it's not a new
outfit
I know what you just
said
motion 65% should be doable that's
one4 down or
what need a lot of AOE around here
really good really
good
you have to pass by me if you want to
reach the shiny
stone no no not the
Flames looking good looks like full
HP be how do I throw the barrels
though can I pick them up
oh oh no
hey that's so
stupid that takes so much
time uh
go uh go ah [\h__\h] already
dead okay ah [\h__\h] to I can't do
[\h__\h]
maybe the next
round but now I'm already out of barrels
am I
[Music]
not okay I got one but I'm out out of
barrels
though ah there's
more
no Overkill yeah cuz I broke the [\h__\h]
barrels is there any more
barrels I don't have the time to be on
the look up for the barrels
[Music]
TBE can't believe they make me look for
barels there's nothing there now they're
gone ah
[Applause]
ah is
that is that
they no no
no
[Music]
no no it's it's over it's
over no no
no can I
redo
fu
[\h__\h] this
[\h__\h]
ah the W screams give me
life I'm happy for
you I mean if I still get like S rank or
something gross tea excuse me it's
really yummy and my tea is really
yummy what do you
mean Lord of crits and star piter was
that oh oh that's really
[Laughter]
bad
H what tea it's a froat an herbal froat
tea but I put honey in there so it's
sweet beef for bad I mean I I agree
but rather than doing it again I'll just
go for the next
[Music]
one uh don't end the critical condition
more than two times defeat 120 foes of
an eer
[Music]
Cannon
okay clear with in three
minutes blame the barrels yeah be for
barrels be for shitty
barrels
pew pew pew do I now get my request
fulfilled of using the Cannons
more shooting down animal animals en
enemies at
[Music]
that I like these
scenes okay what Canon
though what
Canon
[Music]
this wait wrong wrong
side let me use it let
me I don't trust them but maybe on this
side maybe ah maybe suddenly they'll be
on the other
side let me use
this all
right they actually have to die by the
hands of the cannon
right it has to load back up right how
long does that take should I
leave okay
just
recharge how can I do
120 right there's nothing
[Music]
here nothing here Evo okay we could just
cleared
around
ah
ah hey they fly so
high holy [\h__\h]
how is that possible
[Music]
120 what's with the camera oh a Cy R
K thank you for the r
oo guys this seems kind of crazy to me
120 killing 120 Foos with the eer cannon
sounds a little bit insane to me okay me
not you
okay I mean look they barely take
damage okay okay I mean maybe if I in
the beginning I would have been a bit
more ah you see now needs to charge a
bit more
efficient should have done charge shots
you think that's more
effective uh well
okay okay no
well we learn and then it's too
late right side
maybe
maybe h no not not the right side
[Music]
you kidding
me it's like [\h__\h] mosquito
[Music]
now all this this one I kind of want to
redo
[Music]
h
nice nice okay can't reach 61 we're in
wave two out of three is this still
realistic H oh oh wait oh oh they keep
on coming and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop coming thank you for the
memberships Overkill Overkill you hear
that
guys nice 28
82 can't count can't say English
numbers what are they ah
hi sent me friends send me more
friends now it's got to be this side
right
[Music]
next
oh and do they send bigger ones now so I
can't
actually get so many down
anymore [\h__\h] they're already Landing too
late too
late
H that oh oh there's more smaller ones
too does it count when my friends also
take them down like if I start taking
them down and they also get some hits I
wonder the big ones are kind of
impossible to do in one
go nice nice nice nice
[Music]
nice if I have fre wait wait there's
more there's
more I don't know where to shoot they're
like all
over yep
yep
crazy chaos
this 15 more at least sent me another
wave are they any flying no I don't see
any flying
ah very very regretti
spaghetti very regret spaghetti flying
any dying any he
dying I can't see okay that's it no
[Music]
no maybe I would have gotten like 20
extra points if I would have taken Vern
down with a
cannon Super Special rare
mob rare kill extra points
[Music]
maybe what no way not even
no no we do be getting some levels but
oh my God no I will not take a c
[Music]
rank at least I got MVP huh did
I he's your best friend wa no he's not
my best
friend I tried so hard but I only really
understood the efficiency of the other
cannon in the like second half of the
second
wave it's fine W the accident it wasn't
your fault this accident certainly was
my fault but I didn't know I didn't have
the knowledge
[Music]
okay
okay which side which
side which side which
side
[Music]
okay
this is like a different kind of game
now
[\h__\h] I mean if if I do this since the
beginning then it should be
manageable oh yeah yeah cross your
pths cross your PS not very smart you
are okay keep an eye if it's happening
on the other side but no no they're
still on the
side no
nice very different maybe even if you do
it like this you could actually get the
free
minutes Mark what about the other side
no there's cannons over there is there
never any on the other
side taking Pro reinforcements have
arrived
okay wouldn't mind some motion control
here like the
[Music]
switch for moving the
cannon martion Mansion all right
[Music]
69 no yep yep get those big AOE cannons
out
there Mass
Destruction we already at two out of
three sheh oh
[Music]
yeah having them come on board wastes a
lot of time I
guess oh
[\h__\h] oh nice nice ah nice nice nice
whoever is shooting over there my aim
got a little bit
shitty
we're probably over 3 minutes though
no like one bird may have entered
yeah I did I did
[Music]
120 ah this one these ones
are okay we took one down
oh oh oh
oh okay
okay got to be
fast
dead
[Music]
okay let's get the small ones first I
mean now we don't even need the numbers
anymore
but
[Music]
okay ah don't sh what to aim
at
okay
[Music]
wait okay W focus on Battle again
maybe
[Music]
y rounds better than a Char sh for the
big oh
really
[\h__\h]
[Music]
really
it's okay we definitely did
better
y that was the last one how do you do it
in under three
minutes
she so still I'm
satisfied this time we easily
12 I guess maybe higher level
yeah s executioner what that's all I got
for working so
hard a only almost s almost
s but okay I'll take I'll take it I'll
take
it H with all these Quest rewards we can
probably give back some side quests and
do some upgrades again and then got to
get going in the story we got a lot of
levels too though 23 22 22 23 look at
them look at them but there's one more
wasn't there one more if there's one
more I got to do one more
right was there one more yeah the
hills defeat all avf forces clear within
four don't enter critical condition one
in one time clear within 2
minutes sounds
Musashi the
condition yeah I can do that but
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's
[Music]
go
I like these entering scenes F I have no
time no not the
[Music]
lasers oh
my mhm
oh already wav two of a
three
okay maybe if I run further over there
we waste less
[Music]
[Applause]
time
I will take you down and I will stuff
your dead body with the
flag but I feel like my combat is shitty
because it's constantly being
interrupted I hate the laser it makes me
so
nervous my
[Music]
God don't run away don't run
away so soda soda
soda toino
soda what we got to go in oh my God okay
we infiltrated the
[Music]
base okay I can I can get it into
critical condition one time apparently
oh now I'm really trampled now I'm
[Music]
scared wait I was that not was that wait
it says zero out the two is that not
critical is that dying is only dying is
uh oh my God is only dying critical
condition
[Music]
okay just down
okay wait that Wast time doesn't it I
don't
know oh time has been
St okay nice nice scene w running away
from the
explosion
okay we CED within 4
minutes let's
[Music]
go
oh my God y I got last hit executioner
and backstabber
we jamming expert Dodge Master Dodge
lover what are these ptal s FL
baby
[Music]
so yeah it was pretty close to S s++
2 no oh that is a satisfying ending and
now let's go to the side quest and go to
all the reportable ones he must be in
the same town oh for [\h__\h]
[Music]
sake the Timo
BBS thank God this is kind of fast cuz I
don't have to run to them oh okay yeah I
don't know if we'll get back to the
quest anytime soon
but and then since we got some Quest
items maybe now we can do like make the
wa weapon at
[Music]
least we got to we got to speed through
the story though there so much prep
work well we're going to forge a weapon
right D can I no I'm missing Champion
Merit
[\h__\h] don't I get ah isn't that one of
those items that I get from making one
of the
medium
difficulty thingies here wasn't that the
same
[Music]
icon this
one maybe you can buy it in the shop
which
shop uh do you mean the small
what was
that oh
here today can I buy
[Music]
it
no I don't see it it's not
yes well I can quickly try to do one
more like the medium one that one single
one and hope I get the I get that one
anytime anyway right no matter what rank
I get I
hope but I have to beat the boss fight
the boss
again but then we get the reward first
clear reward I I'll [\h__\h] it I'll do it
[\h__\h] it first time clear re okay welcome
to grind blue fantasy
reform
I hope I hope I won't regret this at
like
midnight I've got
time ah you you're the
one na
Bondo here we go guys we got plenty of
time
okay
[Music]
fore oh he's first you
already
oh wait do I have to hide what if I'm
behind him if I'm
behind he's going C he's going
CRA oh my God stop one stop
him okay
well I learned my
lesson oh all the lasers ah yeah that
one I hate that oh I didn't get
hit
[Music]
okay we got a big Ice Crystal
back uh-oh uh-oh uhoh I didn't want to
break it I I I didn't want to break
[Music]
it she said so to me dodging that
[\h__\h] I am indeed sugy you you are so
right
almost go get him go get him who cares
about this over
drive why do you got to do it now at 1%
health I want to hit him somebody hit
him ah thank
you you gets the [\h__\h] last hit
man was easy though was fast didn't take
so
[Music]
long I I achieved all the goals how am I
doing better at this than at the easy
one I think I'm better at fighting one
target versus all like 50 100
targets cuz I can focus all my skills on
that one and don't have to keep on
Switching targets when I'm done with
one I smell weakness one of my
achievements Bam Bam and Bam y oh s++
baby I got an achievement for that on on
Steam sniff snof you're weak Champion
Merit there we go it might be worth it
to use it on on
WWA maybe do I maybe only need Champion
merits to make Wawa's weapons that would
be
nice yeah s++ and level 25 holy [\h__\h] e
is level 26 we we leveled like 10 levels
almost wait where am I going to
here I mean it's not like we're doing
completely meaningless things this will
make us go through the main story easier
cuz the fights will be easier right oh
what I did it are you proud of
me so people did say something about
don't make her weapon I don't know why
not it's much stronger should I last
chance to tell me to not make it because
I don't need it or
whatever to anybody who knows the game
well think it is a good
investment make
it it's St bonus not worth it make it
cuz it's cool I have no
clue you need all the weapons eventually
weapons only permanent Buffs so it never
hurts to have them
oh
okay
okay let's level
it to
yeah okay uh cap can stay the same for
now perhaps hers cuz it's only level
[Music]
okay
the this was her first one right and
then this is the second
one I could it's only 30 I could still
bring it up to 50 cuz the others are all
[Music]
okay now I'm broke I'm back to 160
coins we're perfectly
calculated
okay and once again we go in here or
where was
[Music]
yeah uh here this thing yeah this is why
I need the weapons cuz then I get this
stuff
right
M interesting system haven't seen a
system like this in any other jpg before
I
think with the same kind of
[Music]
use
interesting
interesting make sure the weapons are
actually equipped
[Music]
oh I'm so
what wait
durelle no wrong buttons ah this one's
the wrong one okay
she had the wrong weapon on the whole
[Music]
time
okay
okay I think finally finally we can go
finally what were you saying again
desert
Ash
H what's
this nice Quest markers showing me in
this narrow alley where to
go
[Music]
for
go
[Music]
chill I do be on a
clock so we make their
errands for
[Music]
them yeah of course what else what else
can we
[Music]
okay I just want to see something from
the front they look
normal what's with his shirt they wear
the exact same uniform same pants same
shirt but why is he extra edgy and
spicy with a whole opening on his
back a r fashion wait him too ah wait
it's the same model okay I like how they
have a lot of NPCs but like putting the
same exact same NPC so close to one
another I've seen it several times now
and uh yeah that's that's a big oopsie
that a lot of games
make the same copy paste so close to one
another
he's feeling hot only on no he feels
that breeze only on like the his lower
back that's actually so
ticklish everything's covered except for
that that's the joke what the the copy
paste or the
shirt they always have open back uh wait
isn't isn't she also on a room this
fairy
girl it's legit a
meme and
the interesting
[Music]
okay
okay I'll talk to
them from the
side sorry I always jump cuz I always
think it's that button to
talk
cute she's pretty I really love the
uniform I think I said it before but I
really love their uniform
hello
[Music]
small
cute cute
voice running around the whole
city Guild receptionist
VOA I
mean that's that's still kind of like
similar to what I have now I feel like
cuz it's going in the sameish
direction
I don't know if I would do that anytime
soon but for fan art
please please make any kind of Wawa fan
art commission it if you got
to raise our eyes to the blue look into
the sky go to the
Outlook
fin
[Music]
alley looking to shade is what it
said
okay the back streets we're now the back
street girls and boys mostly
girls ignore the
[Music]
boys this team consists of only
us cat it was a
[Music]
cat I love
cat cannot be
mad
[Music]
for I don't mind going on a wild cat
Chase more of that
please more more and more
short on
ears Castle guards
okay EES
dropping I don't feel so comfortable
about doing that but
okay we're not even doing it
really ah okay up there I thought so I
was thinking so but the quest marker was
over
there okay this is
better
[Music]
I heard the same thing yeah me
too okay that's not helping
us let's go up
here
uh it always shows me afterwards where
to listening
okay he's alone though he's going to
talk to
himself who are you talking
to you know you have a brain you can
think with instead of talking out
loud wants to be
heard
yeah okay obviously can't L from here
but from here
[Music]
yeah H I found out about
that a couple months
ago very
interesting
oh and you know I think the place where
I found out about that
was that YouTube channel cut with the
whole with all the
dating speed dating
videos cuz they make different kind of
videos too that are not about
dating and I think they did something
like
a like something ask questions to person
without inner dialogue or something like
that
maybe maybe
oh oh I can already report this there's
[Music]
no oh when when when did I make a
disaster
report
what
what nice no fall
damage this sigil is very good
oo potion hoard of Might Bel love love
it well is it something that gives me
more
[Music]
potions
oh okay uh where where am I
[Music]
going where where's my
quest here
maybe
eh I'm so confused BL I walked past wait
is it
him I thought that was one of the side
quests I thought it was one of the side
quests that I keep on talking to and I'm
like oh [\h__\h] I still don't have
it
[Music]
shut the
barit I think I'd have to look up a
picture cuz I don't know what that is
but you actually made the KA did you
take a picture I want to see if you made
it
properly
now I want some K what the
hell oh
nice I got to look up that Mar what
what's it made
of
this is so
intimidating he looks like he could be
in
Yakuza chocolate cake P cream whipped
cream well that
sounds
okay I looked it up ah
y yeah that looks amazing I don't think
I ever had it but they also make it with
strawberries oh [\h__\h] I want if you make
that why you have to send it to me
though that looks amazing I want to eat
it oh we're bringing
bread I can
imagine
I'll take that
literally I'll I'll get your help if I
scratch you back
[Music]
right oh man you mean the
choker
fore
foree
okay
honestly his voice actor I wouldn't be
surprised if he was also acting in
Yakuza sounds
like it fits right
[Music]
in of course I'm doing it what the
hell look at this though wow
[Music]
like having actually like a bar like
this to go inside
too but it's interesting cuz it's like
kind of like a path
too it's like partially inside partially
outside I
like
and
chest oh and another
Quest
oh I hope I still get to fight
[Music]
them one way to avoid renters bu on the
path no I think you still would have to
pay rent for that though realistically
speaking
cuz that's like putting up a store in
the middle of the street you can't do
that without permission and all that and
if you have it all the time you need
rent okay I mean you probably know that
I'm just like answering very
[Music]
seriously what he's the Japanese voice
of katos I think I remember katos having
a
[Music]
really wait which
Kos Tes Symphonia Kos or uh that
game wait a
second I got to know crew
F but someone said to not use it
yet no I don't
know yeah God of Warcraft
though could be both
honestly
[Music]
for hi I guess I'm ready to
go no it's Kos shut up sounds cooler as
Kos I would
say crto
stupid trust me guys so many games use
like German words for cities and names
and all that so you got to trust
me this pronunciation is just the better
way to say
it
[Music]
c yeah cuz right in tesia they say in
Japanese they say kuratu right so
obviously in English they would also say
sayos katos ideally with the r like
katos not
katos no I'm not saying it's from the
German language at all I'm just saying
especially if it's Greek I doubt that
you say CR creat
us I don't know but
like brings us back to like you know
language
[Music]
pronunciations
I'm just saying that German
pronunciation would probably get closer
to
[Music]
it yeah okay bye
bye
now come
back
[Music]
for we're back in the sky
o uh if you want characters early and
like fairy for combos you might like
charot or Zeta both are heavy DPS focus
on self bus you might like Naya too oh
only the reason I chose fairy was
because of you know
multiplayer reasons
yes I cuz I was told I should go for
something that's not close
combat
so as far as I know Zeta is a close
combat normally I'm not but I don't know
about
[Music]
shalot are you sticking with her for the
whole game I don't know maybe
not but the whole game is today so I got
to make these decisions
soon inot oh okay then I don't want to
play her
then people used to S my oh well there
you go okay I'll stay with
fair I mean I don't have
to you know play the same character in
multiplayer as I do in Solo right
maybe I want to get
Calo yeah I want to try Calo out then we
can have a full Blondie
team but then if we do CIA then we have
to get IO out of the team probably and I
don't know if I'll be a better Mage than
NPC
iio oh my wife
I love
[Music]
you this felt
very much like repetitive
Visions
oh
she seems kind of uh like
she she's she has her
senses
she's like a like a drug
dog sniff
snof desert
[Music]
is this am's
desert where is
amen obligatory Amma mention red hot
Cactus whoa
who crap
[Music]
yo am I would love this crap
too all right hell
ground I'll save we did a lot of stuff
but it was probably AO saved too right
doesn't this game have allo
save
surely that's Auto safe right I forgot
already more like a moon
stage I was about to say wouldn't it be
cool if we can like surf in the
sand and there it
is
[Music]
oh what was that eel
why did you make that
noise which way I'll check here
first
oh
I by the
way I finally picked up the gift yes you
know remember what I told you yesterday
about my internet
provider so basically they were telling
me what compensation I'm
getting and
then told me um by the way I'm also
going to have a like a present you sent
to
you w like
okay and then like I think two
days two days later
I
think I got a notification that the post
man like uh tried to reach me I I was
home by the
way but po man just decided to not give
me my present I guess then I have to
take it up but since it was so to say
apparently a
present that I don't even know what it
is I didn't feel an urgent need to pick
it up right away
so it's been
like a
week or
more since it supposedly arrived cuz I
had the note and it was like two days
after they told me which yeah if if they
send it immediately it it could be there
2 days
later and then I pick it
up and I I bring it back home and I open
it up
and it
was I'm so confused guys it
was it was
um and another box in the box and in the
Box in the Box was
another Mo modem Internet modem I don't
think this is the present but nothing
else ever arrived so now I'm really
confused is this what you wanted me to
have are you mocking me it's like
exactly the same modem as I got
originally double internet what am I
going to do with this modem I think they
that's like
maybe from like before when they said
we're going to send you a new modem and
it never
came I mean I guess it did come but h
I'm so confused nothing was supposed to
arrive I'm very confused where is the
gift now I'm curious but I'm not going
to like go out of my way and be like hey
by the way your gift never arrived what
was it supposed to be I'm not going to
do
that I don't care
enough but now I got to bring all these
modems
back to
them I just Dro it off a store
but I have so many modems
[Music]
now which one is a
slime none of
them box for my cats no I'm going to
keep it closed
uh so that I can give it back in a fresh
and nice manner it's like as if it was
never used
before
ooh yes you can't sell them no I'm not
going to sell them you're supposed to
give them
back desert Ash I think that was a quest
item we needed
too H where are my slimes
at a side chest cuz it's on the side of
the
street the private kid of boxes oh my
God they have enough
boxes what's going on
[Music]
this is this a
sign I've Got The High
Ground is it good to be on The High
Ground yeah cuz there's an item
there oh the curve oh I got it I think
yeah clear
wo ah [\h__\h] no the chest [\h__\h] you that
curve was so difficult like it drags you
so
slowly over the
sand you can't make like sudden
[Music]
curves that was a big
jump and sand Anakin's worst
[Music]
nightmare you are a
slime
[Music]
n someone's just coughed yep they really
record coughing sounds for randomly
inserting them like
this how much do you know about the Star
Wars prequel and Anakin and his hatred
for
sand uh I don't know I don't really know
much the only uh Star Wars movie that I
remember
watching um was the one where they
race do they race more than once perhaps
then that's the
problem yeah the pod raceing which one
is that episode one oh didn't we watch
episode one together as well though I
don't remember them racing did they
race but I did watch that when I was a
child I'm probably honestly are we once
four okay I probably did also watch
the second movie
too it watched four and
five the golden path the golden path and
the golden door oh my God this feels
like
tunic
tunic my
beloved ooh
W oh didn't I stumble into ena's stream
when she was
here like I remember
[Music]
this
left right down up up right down down
left that game is so
crazy what are these green
things oh I have so I go
[Music]
faster
Birds oh they already gave
up well I think I'm like highly leveled
right now so I don't need
to a battle with
everybody I saw a chest down there
[Music]
not that one what the [\h__\h]
snack
CRA got
poison oh I jumped over that ta so
smoly
nice danger noodles oh
no you guys know the guy who says
h a
slime this time I I don't be because I
saw your eyes peeking
out suddenly loud voices in my
head so
yeah
anyway
a good
question should I look around this whole
desert or should I go straight to the
quest
[Music]
marker
explore
really
this area has a lot of Secrets look
around okay an SIS Hill that's funny
because Ane is older sister and in
Japanese and in sis obviously no so this
is the older sister sister
[Music]
Hill
oh oh that's what a quest marker is
anyway huh I just wandered over here
naturally a
[Music]
griffin let's go oh
no how strong is this Griffin he's at
least only one level above us
[Music]
I
love they
make with your
free she really thinks
I can get there that
[Music]
fast I mean I
can
can you the alliance for
the well especially with my current
White KN
arm I belong to the
alliance
okay I should have I should have not
risked
that should no thank you you ah [\h__\h]
okay I'll I'll revive myself cuz W also
needs
help a
[\h__\h]
H [\h__\h] okay okay thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank
you yo we got
wrecked I got an achievement for um
helping five times oh my God let me
attack you're just a big fancy
chicken
beautiful
[Music]
onee
foree
don't die again
wa ah I guess it is a bird fuse of a cat
oh my God my two favorite things in the
[Music]
world waa casually opening chest the
middle of the
fight ah
for the key is
activating is that
good oh wait is this another one of
those cases that could end without me
killing the the boss no
[Music]
right I'm doing a good job really I
don't know about that you are you
sarcastic right now cuz I
[Music]
died you're doing a good job you
say you're so
funny so
funny
this Griffin over drive
is my biggest
[Applause]
[Music]
problem
[Laughter]
for
Biga imagine we would have gone straight
into the main story without getting
these 10
levels imagine how much worse this would
have been we would have wiped we were
not ready we had to do
[Music]
this Jinx
much it's like oh we're halfway there
hopefully nobody's going to interrupt
us
okay
[Music]
no stop stop I can't stop I can't stop
moving
[Music]
there we go where are we going with this
oh
speed
uh why why w
why what why are we
fing
I'll go this way
anyway I wonder where the goal
is cuz usually there's always chests at
the
end I would have wouldn't have minded to
find them
[Music]
first what are you can you guys shut up
stop
fighting so annoying
[Music]
one more
time you you mean
maybe they're here to stop me from
moving to fast
[Music]
maybe right where was the
chest I want to start
over
you can Dodge or cancel oh wait I didn't
I didn't even consider that
okay maybe I shouldn't have not
[Music]
here but I think that was the end that
must have been the
[Music]
end so difficult holy
[\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] this one
how can I miss it so many
[Music]
times
stop I hate this desert now I hate
[Music]
sand I can still do it I can still do it
I can still maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe do it
there was actually in this case no
special other chests at the end there
huh I didn't see
any oh that was unnecessarily
stupid
okay let's go to the next
marker let's go wait you're not a slime
are you of course not of course
not I knew
it just checking just checking
oh there's a safe Stone over
there wow I'm slime
Hunter
yeah I definitely do be a slime
Hunter and the SL
spitter cuz damn I've been
having slime
problems for a while
now it doesn't matter if I have
to humidifier on or off I tried two
nights without it now and I had Le a
little bit less slime production going
on
fum but on the other hand the whole
night I woke up several times feeling
like I'm my throat is in the desert you
want to fight or
what it's going to start moving in like
halfway through me activating the key
right sleeping in the healing pod like
Goku I don't know um never considered
that cuz I didn't know Goku sleeps in a
he
PA there it
is the weird thing is I don't think I
ever had
to strong flum problem without being
sick for whole
winter I hope it goes away
after after winter is completely over I
mean I feel like winter is over but I
don't know is it officially still
winter or is it spring
now it's still
winter firsty
oh they come in two different
timings they still got oh because okay
oh my
God holy
[\h__\h] guys don't stay too
close know it's spring when the Spring
Fest Comes live spring
[Music]
that sounded like
be
F's birthday is on the first day of
spring oh that's a nice way to remember
it oh so when I see fa's birthday coming
up I'll
know I didn't know they did
that they made a birthday to be on the
first day of spring that's so
cute that [\h__\h] gets me every time what
if I hide here here it still gets
[Music]
me oh my
God where is perfect Dodge
WWA Simulator for a class full of
children
nice what a nice
ending
explosion yeah my birthday is on
National Fried Chicken D I don't know
which nation's Fried Chicken D it is but
it's I think it's America or na or
[Music]
Canada
obviously
America oh today was
International Cat Day meow meow meow for
me every day is cat's day every day I
cuddle wle my
cuddle I love
them so
much by the way oh wait so how do
you
my sweet beloved cat smovie what is
this
I should I I pressed the wrong button
twice does this do something uhhuh it's
like a
bomb so smoothie you guys may have been
curious during my break she would still
kind of like wake me up but uh she did
generally stop waking me up way too
early and way too
[Music]
often like instead of waking me up after
3 hours of sleep now it's generally
waking me up
after 7 maybe which is
fine it's
fine and then sometimes even if I ignore
her meowing sometimes she would indeed
stop sometimes not but as long as she
doesn't wake me up too early it's like
okay whatever yeah thank you for being a
generous
goddess
so yeah overall Improvement a little bit
and
yesterday I had no more wet food so I
gave both of them two liquid
snacks everybody was
happy and there's another one of
these
where's the next one what the
[\h__\h]
oh is this one more like looking like G
good luck finding
them wait
what what
I I legit don't see them on the
wall another one up there
huh is that the last
one is that the last
one no I always you guys you don't
understand I always have Kibbles out
there for them oh wait now I see the ah
now I see the like
stairs they always have a [\h__\h] on the
kbl and chunky wonky generally only eats
the Kibbles
anyway wait so what then you go back
here or how are you supposed to do this
cuz then I got to go down again what oh
or you go up first and oh and then fall
down and then get the last ones over
here
maybe okay one more
[Music]
time but the first two I can get now I
would
say
or maybe this one
too wobble
wobble it's still it still feels like
yaai I missed
one I start to dislike this
invisible
chests I think getting the free on the
bottom first is
fine I wish I would surf less at times
where I don't want to be surfing thank
[Music]
you ooh that jump was kind of
sick I skipped some okay this jump
[Music]
is got to carefully position yourself
before you go in for
it cool down free 2,000 Rupees 5 MSP all
right I'll take
it I'll take
it yeah steam achievement too
oh I feel like I can make that
jump no okay somehow I'm sure you can
get up there
[Music]
though let's grab yeah it doesn't exist
in this game
[Music]
huh hold the glowy thing I must have all
the glowy
things so over here oh maybe up there
there's something too I'm
[Music]
curious let's
grab [\h__\h]
it
yeah my whip surely what the hell is
that over there my whip surely could
help me get up there if you think about
it logically is that one of those like
uh dark thingies to activate like a
difficult fight yeah
[Music]
probably why did they build these
buildings on sand in the first
place I mean
if you're surrounded by only sand where
else are you going to build it but yeah
probably not the easiest ground to build
[Music]
on oh wait I I did not expect it this
time what the hell
he's shaking he's
tribling
[\h__\h] he died so
fast like a lot of the time for these
enemies I see this like blue bar above
their head and I feel like that's their
HP and then they die even though the
blue bar is still super full and then I
realized oh yeah right that wasn't the
HP
uhhuh
when you least expected
exactly I did expected the
least I want to go up here can I no so
disappointing oh my God why you baiting
me like this
game where even where am I even supposed
to
go over there
okay sorry for running around
aimlessly just assessed where I need to
go and I still go to the other corner of
the map because I'm looking for
something oh yeah
just and now we can surf and now R man
we got a lot of raids
today thank you for the
raid
I have a feeling there's another one
coming
today this is not the last
raid so popular oh my God
[Music]
popular
h
okay
no permission to
ascend ra Shadow Legends there's a lot
of slimy thingies
here are there secret
slimes or is it just decoration yo this
feels like I'm playing elen ring this
kind of
enemy he looks like he's straight at of
Ellen
ring
I feel like today I'm using um this
handle
skill in a way that makes more sense
like I I used it several times now to
get
away from the fight which is I think the
intention how far does this
reach what the [\h__\h] oh they want to
curse
me calina
I'm the distraction take me down while
katalina is being
resurrected oh not
me I'm not ready him give me some
time I'll be the last one
okay here we
go but obviously yeah the way the way he
fights is
not not good enough he auditioned to be
in alen ring but he failed cuz his like
his looks are
unfor but his battle skills is really
lacking
[Music]
I like the idea of having boss monsters
and other monsters audition to be in
other
games but they fail so they end up there
and I I kind of like that idea that
imagination let's do
this he going to die from my head my
head my
head my head
I think that was my
hand yeah you could make a light novel
out of it like from the POV of the boss
or
whatever he auditions for some really
cool game and then he goes to another
one and another one like a model in LA
or whatever oh my God that would be so
cute wait what the [\h__\h] wait I'm going
to I'm going to become a novelist I'm
going to write this I'm going to write
this that's so cute actually I feel like
that become could become a really cute
anime
too that's so cute and then you you find
at the auditions you get to know like
all all kinds of other like
interesting villain looking people or
maybe even some people um audition for
protagonist
roles maybe at each audition you don't
only see the people who audition for
your role but also like you know the
protagonist and the Side characters and
the here the mascot and so on so you'll
see all kinds of
characters and maybe in each in each
episode if it was an anime you get to
know a different group of characters and
and they get to know each other they get
a little bit closer
maybe and then you say goodbye and you
move on to the next
audition oh my God that's so cute oh my
God wait oh my God
if only I was actually like a
professional writer I could totally
write this
down they did that in rord Ralph
what but I wanted to be in a setting
like this more like this not like raed R
I think I've seen that it's like more of
a like a Disney look I know it's not
Disney
but you
know
what if that's my next voice pack me
auditioning
for game protagonist
roles now I have an
[Music]
idea that wasn't an evil laugh that was
more like a I don't know let's go let's
go I'm a genius kind of
laugh I'm here we got them all right
insect the
chest what are you guys
doing all right I'll join you really
quickly
okay level up for someone who's not in a
group
[Music]
cool refill potions first oh okay okay
TR true true true I can do that at the
safe Stone
right you would look forward to
it you know even for the non- aniversary
non birthday voice packs you know the
one I talked about yesterday where you
sign up for cuz the company's doing it
you do get the choice to ride it
yourself but I generally always leave it
to them cuz I'm like I don't know I
can't think of anything I'll leave it to
you but my first birthday voice
pack uh like any voice packs that I made
for birthday or anniversary which I
think is only one is it only one was
written by
me yeah oh no yeah the zoo date the zoo
date and the get well soon one both are
from me okay there was another one yeah
I forgot about the zoo we forgot about
that
zo how could
we is there anything new that I could do
I don't
[Music]
know did she just
say the zoo that idea was so dky the
thing is I didn't know back then that
the company would help me make proper
sfx uh so I kept it to a minimum and and
that's basically also why I did the The
mzo Voice pack I mean I think it's a
cute idea but like I thought okay with
amzo I'll be making all the sfx myself
because that's just how you know the zoo
works I'm I'm the
zoo and that way I don't have to you
know find all the sfx myself cuz I
thought I kind of have to do
that didn't know that they could like
you know do a proper sound design more
or
less I am the whole
zoo
yeah now I have the knowledge that they
can do a bit more than I thought so next
time I might make use of more sound
effects why go to the zoo when you are
the zoo
exactly I don't really like going to
zoos anyway I think I probably told you
before but but when I go to a city I've
never been to before I wouldn't go to
the zoo as a tourist thing to do because
zo are pretty much the same almost
everywhere it's boring to me like seeing
a few animals living in captivity and
they're not even doing
much see you again can I see your face
today yeah aquariums too I feel like
aquariums maybe even worse
[Music]
wow
interesting small blonde
child who thinks she's
really cool and
[Music]
Powerful insane ear Rings
though oh he won't even participate all
right if evil white
potatoes you guys are so
mean ah just attack from
behind
no I want to attack this one this
one oh my God okay you'll just become
collateral damaged
[Music]
then the fellow
ship Fellowship looking kind of
different
todays [\h__\h] come down here rapon to let
your hair
down
[Music]
fory
little
spee
foree
[Music]
spee
what am I attacking what's this why are
you why are you tickling
me when I'm like pretty outside of the
circle of the link attack Circle it kind
of makes it easier to see that there's a
link attack going on right now cuz I see
when the circle reaches
me just notice that
now
yes I'm game
tester let me test your sword Veil
o let's go oh magel it's the small
version of magil isn't magu a blonde
too this is Baby
M
oh my
God
she tell her to stop
lying there we
go don't call her mag po the
[\h__\h]
all right this feels good
now yeah trying finding that
tornado try Gale
burst
for when you goes into
OBU ah ah ah ah monkey
monkey
[Music]
interesting what did I say
about
[Music]
DOD DOD do
do what the [\h__\h] is that
hammer what the [\h__\h] are all those
weapons
nice
ger the [\h__\h] what going
on ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow [\h__\h] stop
it
I'm still trying is that not impressive
that I'm still trying to like get to
her okay come
[Music]
on yeah I'm
trying there we go hammer time is over
baby it is
now too first Trident time oh my God
it's a trident
right okay okay first Trident is
gone it heals her what heals
her
what is she
[Music]
doing cool fight
though cool
fight she become quite a bit more tough
uh ever since she reached like
60% it's hard to focus on
her a famous spare oh so it's not a
right okay actually thinking about it
now it didn't look like a right did it
but I forgot about the existence of the
weapon that is called their
[Music]
spear I forgot that was something
Ascension that's new
[Music]
too
oh it's like the last 30% suddenly went
down like from 50 to 20 it went down
with within a blink of an eye but 60 to
50 was really difficult slow because I
guess we were busy with the weapons and
she was in
[Music]
overdrive hel Miss Le you little
[\h__\h] oh can we get
[Music]
another
yeah now I even have the
YuYu the brain space to look out and aim
for link attack I see the bar filling up
and I'm like working on it
wow wow
[Music]
Improvement
the weapons are
back where's my focus on I don't see it
it's glowing gold so how can I see my
Golden Circle for the
focus now now I see
it I want the
gun I swear I didn't even press Dodge
and I still got an invincibility fr
I hate this face I hate this face stop
following
[Music]
me get up get up D
girl
girl okay
[Music]
hammer
W was did a little bit of
[Music]
healing
calina it's always katalina always a
tank who dies what does that tell us we
have a shitty
[Music]
healer
all I'm at I'm at 100% let's go let's
finish
this oh blue kills everyone I didn't
even know nice but generally I feel like
healing our team back up always happens
very quickly and with without me having
to worry too
much
so
we're Ascension
[Music]
baby I've ascended to White night today
is my Ascension Day yaho yo we took her
down let's go we did
it finishing in
um like special attack thingy feels so
good doesn't
[Music]
it it's not that easy
probably
did finish game that's something I would
also like to
know how close are
they
[\h__\h]
no people finished Ena streaming later
today
and I'm pass J okay
cool what the hell is the
epilogue what what does that mean again
what is epilog after the
story or when is
that prologue is before
right oh so it is
okay and how long is the
epilogue do I have to do
that by the way in multiplayer if I join
them will my level be adjusted or will
my level be however my level is in the
game of my solo play pro do you know
does anybody know
I don't have to do it for multiplayer
okay good holy moly you like a whole
city no adjustment okay
h ah they they scale it down but not up
okay you
[Music]
for damn what
the
uh what
how how am I supposed to fight this I'm
so far
to
excav
oh grab on to something oh I was going
to like go closer to
him wait I'm basically
here hey I'm like here this is like Star
Wars pancakes so can I attack
how far is everybody
[Music]
in should I not
try am I just like are we just
chilling wait do I go can I climb
him
right I'm doing like the 100% is not
really going
[Music]
down what are you guys doing in
here
interesting we took we took that one
down
right
next leg
[Music]
okay feels like near right now and Star
Wars and
everything are they already inside from
the other side oh my God I can't believe
I'm like on the wrong
side yo
[Music]
laser don't turn where you
going byebye
byebye yeah
skills triangle well done oh my God oh
my
God oh oh my
[Music]
God where you
going so
far
why do they make us run so far that's
insane I'm just
chilling maybe that's why they kept us
so far so that we can't
[Music]
go to the circle oh my
ah farming this boss for rare
[Music]
material but I mean just like every
other bus surely gets easier oh my god
dude never a broken
ship oh
ah sh
[Music]
somebody help thank you girls for coming
over so nice of
you what is this fight
man
okay is there also one that's better for
this can I
zoom
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
finally stand
still I mean yeah no I need to aim for
the red St spot just
instin
nice
aim when you're on the Canon you just
ignore everything that's happening
around
[Music]
you please don't kill
me
uh [\h__\h] he's moving oh it actually hit
him let me take his hip though you'll
need a hip replacement after this I'm so
sorry I'm not paying for it
though cuz we need a ship replacement
you need a ship replacement I need a
ship
[Music]
replacement W did the bunny again she
did it
again what what don't don't come so
close how come we're just now not taking
any damage ever cuz we're just chilling
on the
Cannons how is this such a life
hack game way too nice uh what the [\h__\h]
what what what what should I be worried
a he was charging the big explosion
again
okay he can hit you on the cannon if he
wants to guess he didn't want to he
really liked
me
[Music]
with a perfect platform on your
back
oopsy sorry you hear me OBS just died
for a second don't worry guys don't
panic always you panicky chickens
don't worry it's it's OBS
sometimes sometimes doesn't want
to
function cameras doing interesting
things can I fall down from
[Music]
here yeah we're
back
[Music]
guys is everything okay cuz you're still
saying OB we back as if it took much
longer stop saying we're
back this
concerning I'm almost
there wait
okay it was like 1
second
hey you lucky [\h__\h] you can fly yeah
shoot him shoot yes yes go for it oh
yeah yeah he's got the right target
he gets
it let's
[Music]
go
oh what the
[Music]
hell
what they make us link attack what if I
wouldn't have done it what we just have
fallen into his
eye sliding into her
[Music]
D when you slide into her DM so hard
that she's on her knees what
I I meant
joke don't
know we no this thing is
on I don't
know yes power is
[Music]
power do we only need specific
plugs
how can you go into
overdrive you
just a
[Music]
mechanism oh
thanks almost cooked that one I did
[Music]
cook
hey
[Music]
I love
this it's cuz she couldn't uh Dodge
anymore okay I could have totally done
it
[Music]
sh not
thank you E I love
you here I'll heal you guys though at
least so
[Music]
nice
how we loving this epic hero
music I freaking love
it oh in search of
Hope ch
complete
woohoo
yit Which chapter did we start today
five
right end of five or beginning of five
six oh oh oh
[Music]
damn is a long
one yeah it was a good fight epic fight
they have good ideas for boss fights I
like
them and this one didn't feel like a
damage Spa probably also cuz there were
so many different
stages that were so different from each
other and cuz we're higher
leveled
[Music]
for the icon fights were
Epic
I have a sandwich by the way just in
case I get really hungry
later so before I start snacking like
crazy tell me to just eat my
sandwich scared is scar
scar
no not yet I don't need to eat it
now
[Music]
eand today sandwich is egg and
tuna but not
separately
collaboration
M huh maybe you better give me a VIP
treatment 500 Mastery oh [\h__\h] okay
maybe magel one of aia's free generals
she seems to employ cir's
magic this secret of all Harvin regiment
is led by mag one of the fre avf
Generals in combat its members
manipulate levitating
swords much of this region has been
claimed by desert in whose Embrace lie
huge ruins rumored to be filled with
treasure
yay back on the
ship big ship
you little
ship you big
[Music]
ship why still applies although this is
the big ship the other one was the small
one H
wait so let's look at the masteries
we have
450 Grant Stout heart to fairy and
summons a damaging Spirit of the circles
around her which what which what what
does it do block enemies or what block
attacks wait why am I so far down anyway
um
[Music]
h goodbye
Pender you guys said this is good so I
guess I'll take it nice
buff
ST means punishment and I'll take that
instead of
benediction that's not German you're
going to said everything's German this
one's not
German okay
so actually no let me switch
that and no oopsie uh let me
switch what what was I going to
do I want the attacks up and the buff at
the bottom that's easier to remember I
think yeah it says brings all your pets
out
no it looks like my main attack though
anyway
let's get some defense stuff
too
yes sure why
not oh Wawa Wawa only has holy [\h__\h] 3%
oh is this R damage cut to the caster
and nearby allies affect strength and
duration wow 10 memberships thank you
based on Arts level okay yeah yeah let's
do it all of this cast a spell that
inflicts slow
infos let's go until
here oh oh yeah right I have to
[Music]
choose what was
that wait which one is the new one phink
gr Caster nearby
allies h
[Music]
he I don't
know swap rage okay thank you can't make
decisions
um
m just going to go down
here
ah
uh
[\h__\h] this feels kind of
wonky and
then let's do Catalina katalina is still
on our team right yes yes yes yes she
has a new skill here a multi-hit attack
that deals a high amount of stun
M deals more hits when attacking with
[Music]
arest sounds
good oh and I don't have to replace it
cuz she didn't even have so many skills
yet nice ranged ice
[Music]
spell take even more memberships thank
you are you trying to like get someone
specific a membership or
what the ice
one this one's water this one's plain
this one's water okay we can get rid of
one of the water attacks or one of the
plain
ones
healing oh she does have a heal
attack should I get rid of the heal cuz
we leave we kind of are leaving it
to the protagonist but then we have even
less
heal
maybe this
one I mean yeah invincibility is cool
but like for how
long I'll I'll get rid of this
one wait it's also water I thought it
was Ice that's considered
water wait which one's the did I get two
new
ones is it both of
them wait Frozen
blade and Winter's
[Music]
rain aha Enchanted lands is
old okay let's do it like this something
new is probably
better um
M some more
defense but not until the skill cuz then
I have to think again what to
replace
[Music]
okay and then
e oh no
[Music]
thaning get stronger
eel skill cool down minus 50%
what during link time oh that's
crazy
okay you're making her so strong
wait Wawa has like barely any defense oh
my
God wait what's this skill stall cast a
spell and inflict Soul a yeah slow on
the foes hold while casting to aim the
spell effect duration is based on Art I
don't know if I should include this in
my skill set not
now what's this redistributes the
Caster's s goge to all Alice Spa uh the
the special burst attack the amount
shared is based on Arts
level
[Music]
interesting charge bar
mhm oh wow
okay
okay I'm running out of points again so
this is maybe
fine and
then I was wondering what's this about
the
potions uh does uh that potion sigil
have to be on
Fairy Oh my God there's so many what are
these
rare
dude has to be on the one I play
okay what's where do I
see oh reduces maximum base Health in
exchange for a boost to
attack skill cool Downs oh this is the
portion increases the stock H I never
really felt like I needed that so
far maybe if we struggle in a fight I'll
put it
[Music]
in critical
damage
last one is like 500 plus
attack wait this one right
now no is
it crappy
resonance
what fate
episodes what Oh you mean I have I watch
uhuh yeah cuz I didn't
watch I didn't watch them where are they
[Music]
again not
here ah the quest counter
mhm that reminds me we do have the
choice to go to the town right then can
I go that to the to the first town and
give those two quests or one Quest
back not this time how do I go to the
other
one use do to fly to another town or
board the Grand's
deck and
Fala I think right yeah
nice
uh
this
one or do you mean the last one
and I'll just watch
this we just
[Music]
go this may have actually been something
somewhat interesting but
[Music]
well a couple a couple you have to
fight yeah we don't have
[Music]
time we're back story super sad I'm so
sorry so
[Music]
much so
much
my
embroidery thank
you that was deep
knowledge oh okay the rest is uh I got
to progress in the main story okay wait
those stats are they only for that
character
specifically uh like for now for this
one I only get the stats for Wawa
then I don't have to look at the other
ones that I'm not playing currently at
[Music]
least I mean these really seem just like
reliving things we already did the ones
from
Wawa
[Music]
for it's just her
diary only the first three of backstory
others are current
aha oh this one's fighting you must play
as wa okay wait who else is in the party
okay they don't let you bring party
members that's
fine right it's been a while since I
battled with
Wawa but we can do
it why are we fighting though
this
goblins
[Music]
huh yeah you suck no just kidding I feel
bad that's that's
sad small Dragon can't SP
fire
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay it's just a ver
being like me me me me
me and with me me me me me I mean m I m
I m I m I
[Music]
playing a sad
violin
basically oh wait right I'm not I was
like
purposefully okay I was just fighting
like as if I was fairy pressing X longer
and keeping the distance oopsy all right
all right all right
for I I kind of miss finding with her
it's nice to be in the front line
and mash
buttons
oh oh that was a healing skill
[Music]
ha falling is one I could
use that was something that wasn't
wasn't that the
buff
easy guess some kind of a wait what's is
the cargo can I take
it guess I'm kind of overleveled for
this memory
stuff I'm protecting it okay okay
okay
always more please
e this m this music is
sick
wo hey I can't even reach them they're
already dead by the time I
[Music]
arrive
he also already dead the moment I touch
him go go burn go
go
what hey give me some
[Music]
hits oh there's some enemies I see
you let me
find
okay
okay okay okay I'm finally doing
something again being
[Music]
useful oh wait let me go there oh my god
get away the
supplies I have to
protect
okay dead
Dragon can't reach oh I did get the last
did I not I mean it looks like it was
Catalina but only from this point of
view it's all about the angle guys the
angle
me oh you're
welcome no no no no I was the
[Music]
MVP why are we hosting Burns confidence
I need to have boed
confidence stupid ver I can live without
it I don't need that
Dragon okay here we go here we go he he
has a
fum oh new sigil slot let's go okay now
I can put in the potion I wouldn't mind
although that's for
Wawa
right
H
uh even
more one more probably yeah
the dragon changed the protagonist
panties when they were a baby anding
themselves what was that part of the
[Music]
lore
way the dragon did
that
[Music]
I mean if you're V Watcher you can pause
all of this and readed if you're
[Music]
curious we got to boost
you
[Music]
she's a
chicken
I was actually reading
it I can read yeah
[Music]
surprise
for
okay wasn't so
interesting o nice pictures
though smile conjurer sounds just like
another joke name for heart
Challenger oh she lost her ability to
cast
Magic
[Music]
for real smile con is like
a like a
prequel
chall
same
epidemic oh
[Music]
no
another
raid thank you it's for you I'll get rid
of this cuz you know the Raiders
probably are
like oh my God mucho
texto okay okay okay okay you know I
would actually be curious about fairy
um fairy story but but not like we have
time to read everything oh there's
something on the roof I just
noticed and a chest too let's
go wait so I was going to give back some
quests here
um this one is it
yeah sorry it's been a while I've had
your Golem fingers for a while they're
kind of moldy right now but I still want
my reward he gave me Silver
Key silver
key is that my first silver
key what did you
want uh what do you
need oh okay
cool sa chest is
below
oh
there's another normal
chance was it down
[Music]
here ah this one yeah I saw from a
distance I thought there must have been
more attack power free health free oo
free
Health attack Health what free
what skills gear
Gear yeah
gear attack power can now be attack
power
free and oh wait yeah wow I can get
another one here you can have this one
you
welcome free health
care
okay did I have another Quest here to
give
back yes this
one chair charred scared scarred chair
Char tomato
tomato and this one was in the other
city right yeah this one too right okay
so we did I think
everything except for the Crustaceans
can I get another reward thank
you
than
yeah and now we
go back to I would say we continue the
story right
Away
Great
[Music]
yooo we got a keep on going no time to
waste
depart lar we're coming for
you just a short hop step and a flight
[Music]
danger until I
start indeed I
agree she wouldn't like being used to
kill
Innocents Zoom zo
[Music]
Zoom
verra I do want to unlock someone
yeah maybe I get Calo for real or naria
but just not going to play her I don't
know thanks for the membership oh ver is
not in this game V isn't in this game
yet
oh
[\h__\h] AIT made costra and secret H I'll
keep it in mind I was considering CIA
but then that would mean I'll probably
get rid of eel right is that worth it
isn't e good on her
own oh
well and secet that sounds like a guide
to
me but that sounds like a tank what kind
of character is
secret would be funny if he's actually a
tank
he's a turbo
DS
[Music]
sword
okay we
[Music]
be
all of his skills are in German just
like
fairy yeah Grand blue creators really
like German maybe they should make me
their
ambassador of the German
region wink
[Music]
wonk salamander egg
egg
the other day when I
opened a cooked
egg I was like eating it of a
spoon and then I
saw at one
point thankfully I didn't eat
it some small
dark black or dark
red M Small thing that was not soft it
was kind of
hard I was like what the [\h__\h] is this
was that supposed to be its heart
[Music]
or what was that supposed to
be
uh what is there
time you just
disappear
ah the [\h__\h] how do you make that jump
how do you make that
jump didn't you have to jump
there yeah anyway what could that be
guys in the egg you guys are the
experts Run and Jump okay I'll
try attack in there ohuh
okay
no okay this time I'm not opening the
chest so uh we could be okay even if I
ran back for a
moment
hey I did it possible fertilized egg
yeah it was a cooked egg like like I
didn't even cook it myself it was like I
bought a box of cooked
eggs there's blood in the egg it means
that the chicken broke a blood vessel
when laying the egg I don't know if it
was blood it was like solid a solid
piece of some I even took a
picture it was really small but um I
didn't want to eat
it a blood clot from an embryo oh my God
terrifying you guys my
eggs
for still edible yeah of
course took a bit of
effort
oh is that her
he seems kind of like a nice dude
generally but he's just on the wrong
side
no the [\h__\h] did you
do I take a
back funny I said
that
okay that seems like they messed
up why the [\h__\h] is she in
there and with this we fight a dragon
hey yo are we following
him
you brought her
here something obviously went
wrong
yeah magma looks good looks
like orange pudding I don't
know
for oh I fighting
now
I'm chilling here in the front I feel
like all the actions behind
me I'm burning
though
they never stop talking yeah no they
[Music]
don't well that's for
you doesn't look like
me it's just a dangerous danger noodle
fire danger
[Music]
noodle
y I think we would be melted after
that can we go
now M
MH enjoy the scenery guys isn't it
beautiful
oh
okay I arrived at the right
[Music]
time I feel like I'm playing an M ref
right now these other NPS they're my
group
members they're carrying
me you're in a dungeon right
now oh oh what
[Music]
what that was
close she just went for it who the [\h__\h]
was that was that katalina or or
him nice the floor is
lava
if you close your eyes it sounds like
really strong ocean
[Music]
waves
ASM zero
zero
wait have I been getting zero this whole
time cuz I'm standing here or what
what's going
on have you no respect for
me now use the Catalyst use the
Catalyst use
it they do be yapping y y me y
y hey I'm
dead thank
you thank you
eel thanks
girl and why didn't you do it
earlier
[Music]
please
there's an eel here you're
welcome you feel like I'm talking to you
this whole time huh
huh you know what that's fine you can
have this
one I'm talking exactly to
you that's what I'm
doing
money cash
money
delusional delusions are what connects
us all of
us the the entire Discord server is
fighing about eggs why why why are you
talking about what that could have
been or what don't
fight
love hey yo what is he
doing why are you moving
St
can't believe you can fall down here
during the battle can't believe
[Music]
it how can I fall in that previse well
nobody put down their jacket for me to
walk over
[Music]
it so much for
gentlemen we only did a triple first
what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
OU
all zero
[Music]
again do it ver Do
It Go e go E I don't know what you're
doing but oh
[\h__\h]
uh she's in the [\h__\h] lava alone I
have to save
her
I'm not going to revive myself here that
would be insane okay maybe
now calina is she gone forever no wait
where is she where where should I be
where's everybody else oh they're
fighting
okay she revive it's just like an MMO oh
my God I'm in my the MMO of my dreams
oh wait are we the only ones here
Catalina does the others ran too far no
we're not okay y'all are so
[Music]
tiny it's about
time
[Music]
wow now we're doing
damage ah there was a link
[Music]
attack nice timing on the heal
man
[Music]
okay better wait
here you
good e come
here oh oh oh oh
nice oh
[\h__\h]
fore
I'm so
[Music]
focused I'm chilling I'm like in the
zone in the O
Zone wait what song did old do
what am I
[Music]
thinking we're back in full
power so it was my
I was
right I'm in the O
[Music]
Zone
stop we will stop
it
[Music]
wait am I supposed to fight the the ball
or so am I am I fighting the wrong face
no right I'm good
right
wait oh well they did
it I saw eel casting things towards
me I can't see I can't see where where
am I oh God oh God the L he covered
everything in lava but I'm still
here wait is it all zero again
very oh wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait everybody's chilling
here B do
it okay okay okay okay DPS check DPS
check Vern do your job what did we bring
you here for oh
why does he get to do the cool [\h__\h] oh
now they're like a
[Music]
team it said
he you must have
[Music]
Mard w
interesting
[Music]
timing
you huge
[Music]
damage I'm doing huge damage
yes yes yes the greatest damage of them
all greatest damage of all
time absolute
zero sounds like a macro
song
oh he's
almost ver why are you destroying this
moment for
me very and uh do
[Music]
it how is it still
alive
what
[Music]
too strong for this
script she
oh
donk who's going to catch her oh
nobody thank you for the Applause thank
you
l
lulia oh it works it works oh why did my
phone die was I out of battery
Fu excuse me that was
rude is that how you GRE
people my
[Applause]
God wait are they sis like um sister and
brother because they both have white
hair and red
eyes
I love
her talk more
yes she has the perfect not only the
perfect hair color but also the
perfect the perfect eyes the perfect
lips and her perfect shaped
Banks and the volume of the curls is
gorgeous
and I also really like her
[Music]
outfit I can touch her let's go I'll
touch her I'll go touch
her I'm touching
her she's resisting how can you resist
me love me I can't resist
you this is one side of Love
huh please accept my
love
for she wants to play with
me she's so
strong save me
Mommy
Sam thank you for 32 months
ago what are you doing over
there hello someone help heal me thank
you oh where she
go oh oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is that
knra goodbye
everybody she's going to kill us what do
you mean what are you going to do
[Laughter]
obviously
9,999 bad
ending
how are we
alive is it the power of
friendship of course Wawa is the
one to be strong enough to get up cuz
she loves
her mhm m
h yeah take him
away oh she only took the the the the
device H I guess so sounds fair she
destroyed
it
no
God damn
it just got back hope things are have
been going well thank you I'm not sure
if things are going
well I don't know if it's realistic for
me to end the game today how what do you
think guys people who played the game
before
I can
manage oh hi
dude
nice 4 hours okay okay okay okay
I try to be
fast but that's okay I don't
mind really late
anyway these
days my armor yes my
armor you know
this you actually noticed other people
come in here like what was the
reveal
thank you for
noticing I didn't know it was
so like
subtle but I really think it's um mostly
just like like the closeup is subtle but
the full body is not subtle I would
[Music]
say
fondom the scarred Isles this tumultuous
Little Island floats a short distance
away from do Relic belt spearing lava
from its Cy surface
okay now it's notable you think so thank
you you make my worries go away the
worrior I become the black blue gold
white dress oh my God
you're so
right what the hell is
this yeah yeah yeah furry
[Music]
cane
uhuh
[Music]
for
fore
foree
you
Chad you the best oh [\h__\h] oh
oh
[Music]
hello
welcome guys before you leave
immediately give me one
second let me show you can you see
something new on
me do you notice my reveal hi people I'm
almost done
people wait ah [\h__\h] right if I tap out
you can't hear it okay then wait a
moment until he's done
talking I'll show you new outfit
color oh just stop it can I not stop it
like this no what wait I'll just stop
all the
play
[Music]
look I'm a white night I'm a
paladin see
before after after before after and then
without jacket before after I'm light
mode now which do you prefer dark mode
or light
mode and H a different hair of course
and yeah I'm a white night I'll protect
you my
eyes light is cool right it was a nice
idea to do this
huh yeah yeah yeah
oh Nissa I'll be your white
night I feel you know the the dark
version of this fits better if I collab
with you but at the same time I want to
be your white night then we have a nice
contrast as well
genius where your where your oh so I go
back here guess we'll continue with
short
hair I'm so shiny ah it's like someone
finally polished my armor finally
cleaned it it was just
dirty I'm glad you like it guys o how
was Advent collab what did you guys talk
about was just a dotson right what was
it
about I'm a palad yeah let's go aluda
were you watching
Advent did you abandon me aluda just
kidding no pressure what canni what they
talked about cannibalism I mean in some
way we also did didn't we we talk I
guess we talk a lot about cannibalism at
[Laughter]
kfp we kind of always
do why would you talk wait why the [\h__\h]
did admin talk about cannibalism oh my
God why the [\h__\h] would you do
that that's so cursed I mean Shield yeah
I I can see
shiy and then there is I maybe talking
about cannibalism I don't know about the
others oh dear
[Music]
oh dear
those conversations are too cursed for
our new newbies I feel like leave that
to myth to have cursed conversations or
to
promise you guys are still too innocent
for talking about
cannibalism it was
Shi
nice Advent tax what's the Advent is the
Advent tax Advent raid
someone did you talk about pregnancy
too it's an important
topic isn't she
gorgeous I want to marry
her
Li I love
you she she let me touch her at least
she did
Nissa she looks like Nissa doesn't
she AB said the same didn't
she no
we
let's go let's let's use the cannon
[Music]
again oh my all my
mouth Cannon
time so anyway he started
[Music]
blasting ah no Cannon fights all
right let's W
[Music]
who oh these Savers I needed them for
side quest anyway this is good this is
good bar yes I'm playing Fair the
fair with her ghost
[Music]
watch her whip watch her nigh NE watch
our
[Music]
whip
she got so loud this honestly it must be
sound
buug
right this attack is so
cool is that eo's attack
what the hell that
rolling yeah that was wrong okay it
makes sense that I never saw it
[Music]
before
fore an an
ego
[Music]
oh my God is he a
god a
god well I wouldn't say a
God
good
[Music]
he's a
go
[Music]
astrals are the ones who created Primal
Beast
[Music]
interesting
it's okay Roland It's pretty
dope it's okay we got to leave some
important information for the second
half of the game Rolland so that we
still have something to
[Music]
reveal super powerful race oh h
foree
W no now I hate
him thinks he can dot do dot me just
because he's a
god
oh yeah we do have the better
team yes we'll run for
it to the
altar vicar visar employed at vul's
church he moonlights as the local hand
men earning him the nickname Mr Fix It
oh astrals wield terrible power defying
even the laws of nature they once
subjugated the Sky Realm but in a
miraculous reversal of Fortune lost to
Sky dwellers in the Great War and were
buried deep in the sense of
History
H damn not so strong after all
huh Sky dwells it's just everybody else
I guess the denisons of the sky they are
broadly divided into four peoples each
with distinct physical characteristics
humans drafts Arun and
Harvin so
this they're powerful but they can be
defeated and that's what we'll
[Music]
do why am I singing
that every time you got to pick up yes
the trash on this ship man who keeps on
trashing this
ship I
mean
partially it's us we always get these
ships
destroyed right it's a
[Music]
go
our with our air
[Music]
shoe the
one are those air Air Nikes or
what w those sh a
thing Air Jordans this is an Air Jordan
that I would
wear Air Jordans for
gods that are bigger
than the [\h__\h]
Earth
[Music]
y
the BB keep the BB safe no matter
[Music]
what interesting it's night time here
now I guess normally there's no day and
night rhythm is there
[Music]
should I buy something should I do
something while we're
here we could get
some oh we have a new fairy fate episode
that we can skip through but it's a boss
fight all right actually I wouldn't mind
doing a do Bo boss
[Music]
fight oh yeah we could get a uh a new
card yeah we already have a card that I
haven't used
yet oh yeah I never a s slot but I'll
skip for this forgive me forgive
me but we're still only talking about
cloes it
seems yeah ooh where're
here
okay
you guys looking forward to a possible
collab with and maybe Zeda although you
guys told me that Zeda is further behind
so I got to wait for Zeda now I thought
people would be waiting for
me very much
[Music]
so I'm hoping we can maybe do it during
like an Ena time slot or
so but then then it's shitty for zaa ah
the time
[Music]
zones got to check with z Oh wait I
jumped down down here
[Music]
right my second collab
was yeah I
don't collapse much with her but that
doesn't mean I don't like her I really
liked her when I met her too
IRL I like all of the ID girl I love
them oh what was that oh yeah right
nice Ana actually invited me to a
collab um but
unfortunately the timing wasn't good but
of course it wasn't a one-on-one collab
because we have an
understanding yeah sudden sadly I had to
say
no that's the rule it's it's funny to us
though we both like this meme that's
going
on
The Forbidden any you're
right it will never
happen why did I activate that
now it's not a birthday sword it can't
happen all that reminds me I think some
might demon who's whose birthday is
coming
up I think somebody's doing
Callin
birthdays you guys keep a calendar for
our birthdays
huh why not if
not no not uh in ID I mean isn't there
someone's birthday in ID coming up as
well
hey bay and Iris
e
maybe it wasn't the birthday maybe it
was just a random
one L's already
passed I don't think I was thinking
[Music]
about oh wait
what what are we going to use that on
let's keep our special burst for
something
else yeah February is almost over oh my
God wait this year's February is 29 days
right oh
[\h__\h] one
week
wow we are blasting through this
year first actual
birthday
[Music]
INF y we got the slowmo right away
woohoo starting
[Music]
good music is nostalgic are they using
soundtracks from the
game I
me I wouldn't even mind if they like
reuse stuff like that I feel like it's a
nice a nice thank you to everybody who
played
the uh g game for also oh my god did you
just see like EOS was that e or wa or
Ina whoever did the healing there they
were like pre-planning they saw the
enemy rolling in they knew we were going
to get damaged and then they already rep
placing the healing
spot in
advance play you
funed that's one way to see it for
sure
why' you run
[Music]
away all right it's almost dead let's
go link
attack did we just threw a link attack
finisher w w
w
some sound effects are also from the G
oh that's so
[Music]
cool
cute
nice your PC is a real potato is it only
available on
[Music]
PC I hope you get to play sometime but
for now you can enjoy several whole life
members play
it and watch
them was it skills no was it gear gear
for Fairy our third
sigil H wait I have okay then I will put
in potion hoarder uh this one
right more
potions m
the game will give you the general gist
of the conversation
uh-huh you giving me another
card
[Music]
no
okay give me give me give
me we have two cards I have to hire
someone come
[Music]
on oh cute wait what charot she looks
like the the evil one kind of she has
like this huge little
Crown how can a crown be little and huge
at the same time guys tell me love her
my C
PTI oh he looks
cool people have been recommending this
one to me but I also really want to have
Calo a brilliant Mage who founded
Alchemy in the Sky Realm she has learned
how to achieve virtual imortal ality by
regularly replacing her body with new
vessels that suit her
taste where did you get this body from
what the
[\h__\h] the
[\h__\h] I'll get
her the voice
interesting uh uh I don't I'm not going
to use her myself so no need to
practice
um yo he looks
funny
zaa there's so many
blondies I love her too a swordsman Oh I
thought she was a mage or so oh a
swordsman born to a long line of martial
arts master she has trained ously to
combine her family's martial arts and M
magic into her own SW play should I
would it be worth to getting her and
then um switch her out with
[Music]
Catalina I know B's playing her so I
wouldn't
um play her in the
multiplayer
no oh n doesn't heal Kina is a better
teammate oh okay she looks so good
man
katalina's better for support okay what
am I going to do with the create cards
[Music]
then
um okay
but in any
case e I love you and you're amazing but
apparently there's someone
who's about as amazing as you but eight
levels
difference
[Music]
eight levels maybe try out Kia she might
she could be more fun for you for
[Music]
me and that's what you meant with like
wait for later
maybe
exp books exp books I would have never
noticed that I picked up something like
that never opened the inventory before
uh exp
books is that what they're
called probably not
right do you guys see
one I don't have any
[Music]
okay well it is what it
is let's see
her oh 36 okay well at least she's got a
lot going on over here cuz I don't even
have so many points to use I guess I
don't need to help her at all look at
her she's doing better than everybody
else in my
team speaking of I'm going to upgrade
Catalina a little bit
maybe
m
maybe up until
here uh we got a new skill uh what was
it what was it Emerald shield grants
defense and stout heart to Catalina
grants both Buffs to the entire
party I don't know if I should keep this
maybe instead of light
w
check if Kio has her resurrect spell yet
okay yeah let's try it Out oopsie sorry
wrong thing no no we want to keep the
heal this one will be switched out I
[Music]
guess
Oh Oh I thought it would fill this one
up
too
W not even looking at what I'm selecting
it doesn't matter oh
[\h__\h] oh I out of points
oh my
God what okay what skills does she have
Pain Train charges into F while writing
who
[Music]
Aon was that a like a not a randomly
thought of
name
[Music]
what is this
overlap
it's it's a mythological
[Music]
thing
H H my have many thoughts right
now
alexandraa so she has a snake
what she does have like a magical
snake Dodge backward after
[Music]
placing ah she has a healing skill too
does she have something else we don't
need another
healer uh although E's heal would be
gone
this uh which one's not being used this
one
what's this ah this is the resurrection
thing
[Music]
right I mean not like we urgently need
it Alexandra for
Fant what for I don't have that I don't
have
it maybe
[Music]
later
well now she has a resurrection skill we
don't die that often because we're
skillful but
okay um what about
[Music]
gear what can we give
you does attack power matter for magic
users too is that like the they use the
same stat for that probably right they
don't have so many different
stats
yes okay uh a quick cool down would be
nice too
probably free she gets
free SEL she give her some critical hit
rate
too
um
a a
wa wa has critical damage
Health what's another good
[Music]
one
um I maybe maybe
guard ah this could be good too
[Music]
M okay I think we good or did we get
another one no
okay
moving on sorry for the
wait it do be like this
sometimes uh
uh where are we going ah
here hey dude what's up how you
[Music]
doing trophy rewards no didn't check
ever I
think give me give me tell me
yeah I mean we kind of could have
guessed
that 5,000
people
but the leader is my future wife I don't
know if I can smack her unless you know
it's like
a you
[Music]
know are you ready chickens Cy once
again we must
walk in Rhythm to the
music or to the sounds of people's cries
we shall March March to war and to
Victory as it will be ours if
only we put our full heart into it your
little chicken
hearts and every single brain cell that
you guys have have put it together and
got time the small chickens the big
chickens the totem pole
chickens the eggs the
buckets together we stand strong and
nothing will be able to overcome us
BR fro the egg
yeah
eggum
[Music]
egum they're all really damaged this
will be an easy
one let's go wait is there something
here busted mannequin what is that how
you write
that now I want mannequin
waffles oh wait those are are people oh
yeah right there are people oh [\h__\h] I
thought I was going to fight
them wait
[Music]
right man waffles do you guys know what
I mean when I say mannequin
waffles belon
waffles I get them in
Japan all the
time interestingly
enough cuz they have mannequin waffle
storage all
over
I bought them as like souven like
sash there's so
many how am I supposed to listen to him
talking when there's so much going on
right God what able
jum me when watching multiple streams
honestly I really couldn't do
that oopsie
oh no
no
that's so nice of them to give you like
an overview what the hell is going
on hey yo Roland is doing his
thing
it's just I just hear voices and I don't
I even understand Japanese so I don't
even really have to
read but
dude still not entering my
brain
H girls don't use it now cuz it's kind
of a
[Music]
way is he saying you can't blame an
army for their war
crimes feel like that's only partially
true me yeah you're doing what you're
being told to
[Music]
do well that's a difficult topic
H I don't know
really yeah cuz you I guess I
mean as long as you have the choice say
no something that is obviously wrong but
whatever yeah don't [\h__\h] up the castle
man there's still trasure chest that I
need to
open not held up in
damn hey yo are we in front of a boss
fight or
what duped them she cloned
them cure
Sunshine she's cure Sunshine wait that's
not one of the ones I watched I think or
is that
[Music]
wait you are open the door
properly ah duped as in fool
[Music]
okay here such
an let's go what a coincidence I just
randomly sung a song of one of the few
ones that I know a little bit okay I
want to focus on the boss where where
where is he where is he where is
he which one is
it
is there even a yeah is it the
reaper he's almost dead anyway ah
whatever you're all trash right
whatever I mean he's got a little bit
more though he barely got any damage
from my special
attack
not the best time
[Music]
for
speee
is are those circles from The Archers up
there going to [\h__\h] you
up
they're
strong don't need to spam that I should
upgrade my weapons now cuz I can't in
the mid battle but
uh look into it whenever I
can hey yo hey yo welcome to the Stream
woo oh Callo nice
[Music]
pose I is still talking as if she was
still here I still hear her voice
sometimes
man I replaced her and I still hear her
voice heo what there a chest I didn't
see
that it's like she's still around found
[Music]
me it's like she's still
alive I need to move on it's not been
years it's been minutes at the safe
Point what what should I go back to the
safe point was there was one previously
right maybe another one is coming
up I don't even remember when
[Applause]
[Music]
the
why does it show up
now where's e she's
[Music]
dead how can you do
both
this one now is
tight I did have some problems with
setting the camera correctly so that I
could get the jump right I guess you
just got to be lucky with the jump
because I don't have time for this yeah
okay don't my shut the hell up
Fern don't want you
pity
for it's
[Music]
j
no I touched it
[Music]
you I can't
believe this
scam what a
[Music]
scam
yo can't believe I was able to do it
even faster
she that was the Run oh I got a champion
Merit from that let's
go uh so I don't remember where the last
safe point was if there was one re
recently or not it feels like there was
one recently but it could be my
imagination so whatever we're fine I'm
going to continue as if uh everything
was okay R in the previous one okay
that's why it
[Music]
felt I get
back is that door is that is that a door
wait that's not a door that's a door did
I go for
here
here ah
here hi hi
hi oh yeah thinking about it uh we
didn't look
at we didn't look at the weapon
from
calo
[Music]
arel
okay so they're all 50 now are saying we
should go
higher well I don't have enough treasure
for that
anyway no I uh I
can't so I don't know I can uncap but
yeah no quality refining
but at least we got the cio's weapon
there oh and wait we can do from 40 to
50 probably at
least that's all I can
do I
think and we can upgrade sigs if we want
[Music]
to I
could how much is it a griffin
feather don't know about that
one but what was I just about to
do
ah uh I think
here uh no what am I thinking of uh ah
masteries this
one
all right yeah that's good that's
better another 8 Hour
stream we're lucky if we're done uh in a
total of eight
hours I should be so lucky lucky lucky
lucky it's fine though I don't mind and
tomorrow I was going to do a somewhat
long stream too but the plan kind of
fell
through because the
game I want to play I have it on the
switch but we only have terms for it on
Steam right
now so I have to wait longer I don't
want to buy the game a second
time understandable
right I think it should be no problem
get the extra sh up W they were like
extra loud too oh my God sorry sorry
sorry sorry this is
loud if only I could turn your voices
down only for the
battle but yeah um shouldn't take too
long stop yapping to get extra burms for
a different console version of it but
yeah not until
tomorrow what the [\h__\h] is this backup Ro
surprised
me armored Core let's go yeah now it's
time to
use
[Music]
oh my God it's so much better I can't
hear her
now that I would like to
hear
M holy [\h__\h] yeah it's so crazy right
now it feels like it's
bugged
why are it legs gr glowing rolling
what's it's going to do it's preparing a
huge fire
blast oh
no
this thing has a head harder than roams
but he doesn't move like the wind his
legs should be lightly armored compared
to the core that's where we should focus
our
fire okay Roland thank
you it's not like I can attack anything
else
R A none of a speak nerd what do you
mean yo
EO EO the nerd
hater
[\h__\h] are you done yet oh
my oh no I can't get close to
him okay
now changed patterns this there
okay this is why we had to kick e out
she's a nerd
[Music]
hater we don't take that
lightly
[Music]
yeah yeah that's what I'm saying D
yeah
exactly preach
[Music]
it but it's a nice change especially cuz
we're doing a long long long long long
stream so we don't need all this
yapping oh can I bring the voice back
now cuz that was kind of my
concern that was
easy maybe I'll do this for every fight
now
oh
[Music]
yeah you fight those I knew it you're
going to like take care of them stay
behind even
maybe thank you thank
you oh can I play it oh operating the T
TI is now at your disposal give ABIA
thanks for the membership a taste of
their own medicine but then who plays
fairy
condemnation
[Music]
s what is this
stuff I'll just do
this I don't know what I'm doing but I'm
[Music]
mashing
happening you can get him just by
yeah was trampling does that actually do
[Music]
anything
maybe that's more
efficient just
shooting can I reach
them that looked like I kind of
could never mind sorry sorry sorry
sorry
are we
done now now we're doing that but this
one first
okay
ooh o so many
[Music]
numbers leave it to
me and
[Music]
robot what about the other ones
no oh oh
[Music]
hi the whole time I'm pushing
down that button so to
say it really feels like I'm using a
machine gun cuz um it's vibrating that
button
specifically it
[Music]
goes ah
no hey it's dead right it's
gone yeah the Dual sense
controller is fair doing okay I'm
worried about Fair's
wellbeing if she's not controlled by me
then I don't know if she'll be
safe she surely misses my present in her
heart wait wait I don't want to destroy
the castle but this is
[\h__\h] here there we go there we
go she won't be
F fa I love you I love so many of the
women in this
game okay one more but now I understand
the
Rhythm got to take care of
him
as if you don't already have enough
[Music]
power that was another
Rob
[Music]
okay
T I love ta ta's
great I know T does
great
my
colleague oh thanks for the heal oh
thank
you oh there's one of these here as well
wow looking for items though oh what was
that a prayer book wait is that an exp
book could it be
it
is let's go is this really the first one
in the game or did I just miss a couple
of
them I have five
now
wait oh I don't think I can use this is
this
really wrong
book hey I trusted
[Music]
you
wow o t voice actress oh
[Music]
damn
byebye
oh
oh oh this reminds me of a hall we had a
fight in Final
Fantasy even though they're not really
similar actually they're not similar at
all not at
all is that a huge egg and
te
this fight is
rough oh and the
only am I finding both of
them where fight
love
didn't he do that that first also the
first time we fought out of
[Music]
nowhere wait top bar is
fromel so is she like the the real boss
of this fight or does it change if I
Target
[Music]
him oh it does
okay
[Music]
for I want to fight him actually I don't
know I should focus on one of them maybe
I'll focus on
Mago the force field is that impossible
to beat her she's down to 98 but maybe
he's
more
[Music]
can use her resurrect
skill
[Applause]
[\h__\h] the
memor
[\h__\h] hi call I see you
coming there
you oh why is she not using her
Resurrection
[Music]
skill
he's really just
[Music]
saying
you can't force me to listen to your
[\h__\h]
[Music]
ooh
what you saying sorry a little bit
louder so what did you
say ah damn I can't hear
you ah too
bad of course your skill just doesn't
work on
me if I can't hear you the words are
very important oh my
God Catalina is dead though katalina
just use a Revival potion oh [\h__\h] okay
I'll use mine this time cuz we're
[Music]
busy oh the camera [\h__\h] me over I
would say hi thank you oh no no
girls girl be
careful
w
[Music]
oh I SM
now recus
C
Tempest
C bur absolute
[Music]
set where is he he's almost dead oh but
he's
overdriving
huh ah for [\h__\h]
sake waa where's the
waa you helping her
okay does Calli only get like one
resurrect spell
per each
fight that would be
stupid oh [\h__\h] a long cool down
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
get down here
Mago the AOE SM
ah it's too much all at
once oh come me little
[Music]
[\h__\h] what was my invincibility
now a [\h__\h]
I'm on water help
me how long is he an
[Music]
overdrive oh mama
M give me that give give me
[Music]
that let's
go oh
[Music]
sh so
sorry
what everybody else was
alive you're not going to remake me re
make me do all the whole fight again
when I all just defeated
galanta I died too
often uh checkpoint is in the battle or
what my critical bar was depleted [\h__\h]
F Well now I feel real
stupid reach my
battle is the whole
[Music]
battle that is so
sad
oh
[\h__\h] I always wait for the
screen for the loading
screen I'm not sure if I can really
manage to die
less I'll try it I can't
[Music]
promise
at least we start out with no voices oh
my god oh thank
you no
[Music]
what already
firsty
[Music]
what I just got up I just got up back up
on to my
fees they're [\h__\h] me
over it's so difficult oh are you good
[Music]
Kina
no
double
[Music]
invincibility such a coward oh my
God
wa
[Music]
we need to destroy the weapons M little
Frozen it will weaken her Shield it's
okay because I'm kind of focused on him
first
anyway first
death first death
a yikes sorry guys making they they
don't all have to run towards
me
[Music]
I'm scared cuz he keeps on interrupting
my attacks and then damaging me so I'm
like more bouncy now
[Music]
now oh thank
God
oh special attack time
ooh I'm always
bouncy
yeah I I did think a little bit the
enemies voices partially would give me
some TS maybe or yeah even some of our
own
voices
but I don't know the yapping is making
me go
insane hey I'm not getting hit
uh-oh well that one was
tough
uh sorry
sorry well I didn't die did I no oh
no oh was she about to
huh why did I have to die at the
[Music]
end that was my second
death oh
no you can't disable the
[Music]
yapping I know so
sad wait they didn't ask me though I was
at 100% but it didn't goow up until now
oh I was too far I didn't know that was
an
[Music]
issue oh my
god wow
[Music]
insulting
uh-oh uh-oh ah
a he's almost dead
though
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
yeah
everybody half time half time wasn't
that super bow recently
man absolutely didn't cause any of it
it's so crazy how when you're in
Europe you can just go through life
ignoring the existence of the Super
Bowl who even performed Taylor Swift or
was she just there I think I saw a video
of I think m i saw a clip recommendation
of M I think talking about the fact that
Taylor Swift was at the concert or
something something like
that so
Random ah wait I was not focused on
[Music]
it Asha Asha was that what isn't Asha
like retired million years
ago you're lying you're lying I was just
playing uh what for real what
AA she she's dating a player that's uh
good for
her uh oh it's coming from the other
side is
it I'm scared
mommy I couldn't jump over
it oh what is this what is this okay
okay okay okay okay uh hey yo hey you oh
okay okay here I'm taking
you I'll
try
ah no ah what the [\h__\h]
that ah
ah okay well this is her her voice face
as we know once this is
[Music]
over it may not be so bad
anymore come on come on come on come on
come on okay
yeah oh can we do it together this
time uh uh
uh get hit once and you can't do
anything exactly thank you for
understanding oh yeah I heard something
about spongeb SpongeBobs and
Patrick commentating the game which is
so Random what is that like do you have
to listen to them uh or is it like you
can switch whoever you listen
to when you in the actual venue oh is
she dead when you're in the actual venue
do you listen to them
there no let me let me get the dialogue
I can't I can't they won't let
me I hope they don't talk too much I'll
voice it I'll voice
it my
lady
I know well the lunacy of my position to
be making demands of
you but please the sword Veil are my
family if you can find it in your heart
to spare
them pry soon
over take me I stayed my life on this
Death Match now come claim your hard
earned
spoils
no we are good protagonists we don't
kill people look we just want to get
through here without
trouble as long as you stay out way we
got no reason to fight anymore do
you there's no time to waste we just run
by we don't give a [\h__\h] about you guys
wow that's so
sad forgive my failure lady Lilith
complete another defeat they might
actually pull it
off sorry I said it too
fast okay now we can bring him
[Music]
back
okay yeah that was quite a fight we had
uh one actual game over could you
believe it
crazy
o I love how the coins jump out of that
Treasure Chest every single
time so
exciting
it's like when you open a box of
Pringles and there's only snakes coming
out hi
[Music]
slimy
Pringles Maybe the real prank is then
there's potato chips inside and we had
it wrong all
along cuz why wouldn't you not want a
little
snake snake snack snack s n e k not s n
a c
k what is this cool place oh my God W
check oh my God there's a crap there I
didn't see
it this is so nice well
lit kind of spooky but
nice
[Music]
damn whoever is taking care of the
flowers and choosing the flowers in this
Castle has
amazing sense for
it oh so we got to go here so it that's
special for a reason is
it green F
here no no not to eat the snake but to
cherish and love
this it's me your favorite enemy
[\h__\h] this feels like end game
guys another safe
Point did I get any materials to to like
upgrade
again foring probably nothing new right
why don't we get more weapons to
forge okay no I still don't have
it oops I did it
again after the story oh post game open
faster oh my
God
no I want to look on the side for
items I know that looks interesting but
what about the
items it's too late is
it
hi
wifey she sounds
happy they must be related
[Music]
right
oh I love
her edgy very
edgy oh
Showdown
director no
what she's fine I can't see
blood she's fine
right
Mommy I thought they were
siblings a she says
[Music]
mommy yikes
and he's Left
Behind to join our
team
oh is the
scripted are we going to lose
[Music]
this dude don't blame us for your mom's
craziness and you no I just want to
treat her well I I'm I like her oh wow
it's actually
[Music]
weak can I not jump over
this he Blends in so much with my team
that I don't know where he is in the
middle of all of
this but nice
music oh stream is dead
hi welcome back I was saying he BLS in
with the group
somehow and the music is
amazing I love this
violin if it's a violin or cello I don't
know ah [\h__\h] I jumped into
[Music]
one Oh e
guar
[Music]
what do I ever get to hit you ever
again hey I didn't get the heal oh thank
you
[Music]
[Applause]
I was fall in my
[Music]
way
ah
[Music]
first okay sounds
familiar become my power but I just
activated my buff
what are you doing my buff is running
out I'm sorry guys we don't guard here
don't
even this is like Fire Emblem craziness
right
now what what are you
doing
can I ever hit him
now nice
heal he's too fast what do you what do
you what do you want me to do and I'm
dead
thanks okay he's chilling
maybe he I literally don't get anytime
to hit
him chain chance
mag only
Edge he learned his Edge from the best
his mommy o those
Dr while he's already down
two half less than
half okay okay firsty
[Music]
time yeah well I mean you saw what just
happened
I dodged it for so long finally got hit
at the end and was bounced into the next
attack I'll help you I'll help you I'll
help
[Music]
you yo a lot of us died from
that take
me take me
instead but not in a way I I I'll go
game over I have a maximum of depths
that I can take as we now
[Music]
know I don't have an LB
button I only can
dodge that's all I know oo let's
[Applause]
[Music]
go that was me I broke him
I did
[Music]
that oh he's a little bit angry about
his mommy he's a Mommy's
boy what happened to your
daddy what happened
huh you need a father figure in your
life how about
Roland
I'm sure Roland would not
mind if you chill out for a
[Music]
moment adop don't drop
going to
[Music]
adopt oh
no no why yeah oh my God
I'll use my
potion it's okay we're almost
there is it safe to
go looking
good
oh is it time for a fanty
finish n he's already
dead can we finish it in a fancy way
feel like he's already dead he's just
doing it for
us to okay what I was almost there but
okay it's something new a doet blue
detonation I had
92% but maybe they just really wanted me
to have a fancy finish that's better
than
nothing
yeah we're not going to
talk all right let me check for
items oh there's nothing here is
there
kick him well he's down no I that will
leave a bad impression of his
mommy he'll tell his mommy
Noe into the black hole oh
Wormhole become as worm
she'll like me more if I did maybe
she'll respect me more is that what you
mean
oh trap trap or she's already dead so
it's not a trap they're just like I'm
done with her she's not she doesn't have
the choker
anymore they are done with her
oh fore
for Fore
spee
speech oh
[Music]
okay damn looks like some kind of rhythm
game help him
stop the
eyes oh
no e is that
a
Chima I don't know what the [\h__\h] is this
angry
m
[Music]
Satan what the hell damn where's the
real face I've see like several faces on
this
[Music]
oh why did I get myself into this
[\h__\h]
where do I
even
[Music]
the
interesting
hey
[Music]
hey the flower is purple lava pink
lava shake hands of the devil this is
really really
[Music]
crazy I don't know if I can win this
no matter if it's scripted or
not no what let it go can I can I
[Music]
help she's
gone wa that script that as
[\h__\h]
no don't my
party gate of Silence mon no what who
are you taking
out no she's so cute I just got to know
her I still don't know [\h__\h] about
her
no why am I even fighting this is so OB
descriptive what why am I even
trying I'll just let it
happen as long as I don't die on my
own it's like whatever I
[Music]
guess wait do I gate of Tru there we go
what are you taking what's that oh my
dragon oh yeah you can have that
[Music]
one yeah that one doesn't matter
really
[Music]
uh I'm next me really
okay well then I don't have to fight
anymore I don't mind
[Music]
that but if I play Wawa in this case
I'll get abducted later or or
what
[Music]
all the kidnapping man and the yapping
the kidnapping and the kid yapping it's
too
[Music]
much
you're saying as if it's like some kind
of
Aro yo your Bes is
being kidnapped do something I know you
have hidden power somewhere in your body
you're powerful yeah unleash it Unleash
Your
true
um oh oh no
stream oh
no guys why why streamed
die when did it die did it die when she
when
when she disappeared
Unleash Your
TR how perfect cuz she like just
exploded
imploded she basically imploded
Lia what
timing yeah I was like only sh your
power and then she's like I I can do
this and then she goes like and then she
implodes and disappeared just
she's gone
guys
oh what a toxic
family
oh yeah right cuz we're linked
50/50 is she in me is that where she
went
oh she's saying that she's in
here the power of
friendship once again
I have a feeling we're going to have a
sword after
[Music]
this
yeah
[Music]
contrarian
they're
invisible oh there we
are all right I'm not
very is this a real fight now should I
actually try
[Music]
hard yeah
that's heal
[\h__\h] all right good that I have a
healing skill in my skill
set the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
this what what is
this ah it's pushing me
[Music]
back am I supposed to hit
that whoa I free
him oh I undid his
[Music]
shield all right let's go oh will he get
another shield
now
oh the music it's
[Music]
emotional thank you I'll do my best
Laria but I don't know what to find
there's nothing here oh there we
[Music]
go a [\h__\h] I
heal I don't know my skills right now
you know
[Music]
it's
okay I'm pretty chill fight they're
going easy on
me
[Music]
although my fingers are getting weak
getting a little bit spaghetti she'll
notice notice what oh there's the light
is
back go to the light wa go to the
light it's okay I got it I got it I got
it
[\h__\h] my
[Music]
pH where you going
stop are we're doing this for another
63% although I'm getting my super
special attack
soon damn damn
damn it's going to take a long
[Music]
time every blue light PB is 10% uh-huh
oh
[Music]
okay
oh I like when the music does
[Music]
that okay
go oh do we get a
[Music]
shortcut or it activate something I have
a holy
sword link Master Sword is nothing
compared to
this
ooh swim
[Music]
swarm what what is
that oh no not the
[Music]
tentacles damn Lara do
something
oh as I was
saying
oh we touch cuz Every Time We Touch I
get this
feeling n what the
[\h__\h]
we
survive
[Music]
okay oh
yeah the silence and then suddenly M the
power
oh I see what's going to happen we're
going to control
Bahamut are
we yeah this looks too familiar this
looks a little bit and feels a little
bit too
familiar no
oh even the menu
oh oh no no no no no feel almost
nostalgic I feel I need to accept the
truth
oh how many phes does this one have I
wonder also why is it back up to 70%
didn't we have like down to
60 oh this is too
funny oh it's oh maybe if we go behind
can we no ah wait
what oh I no we can actually destroy it
okay never
mind and yeah it's Bahamut didn't we
have Bahamut in the ff6
too fly fly yeah we
[Music]
did
hey what is this what is that you guys
say charge why what is that
[Music]
doing s
tole space
tole best boy oh Sky
Fall hold Circle wait what I we talking
now PlayStation controller controls are
you telling me like the translated
version
or are you talking what the game is like
showing
me X which one which one which one which
one oh any button Works apparently
really I'm pressing all of them
Square damn it to
L but anything seems to activate it
pressed all of
them yeah
right and that saved me 60 [\h__\h]
[Music]
per. complete chapter eight oh when did
when were we in chapter eight
999999 can't believe we still have the
[\h__\h] 999
OTE comes in handy hand hand handy comes
in handy comes in hand comes in
handy and at these
time comes in
handy how do you speak myth
language an
comes and
R what help me
guys comes in handy okay sounded weird
to me
[Music]
suddenly you're
welcome no I don't care I'm not going to
specifically ask for Vern maybe if I say
aren't we missing someone it's I I mean
the IT
[Music]
guy I have I have a tinitus in my ear I
think man how do you get a Tinus out of
your ear you guys got any
advice
it's really
[Music]
loud got to wait it
out you learned to ignore it
okay of course Lara of
course we knew it wasn't you
[Music]
fore
fore fore
for
[Music]
fore
o they just got to bring out their
weapons in such a fancy way each
time
yo one day maybe we should make a kfp
101 about motion
mention or just a general one with
several smaller
terms and one of them will be motion
menion cuz I bet new people don't
know what we mean when we say motion
mention I don't even know why we started
just because I mentioned motion a lot
back in the ater times I guess
but not even
no I mean it was the Motions
presence and then me just saying motion
randomly
let him go no you can't take it what the
[\h__\h] she just going to clap
him
clap no he's coming back come on okay
we're just got to turn into Bahamut
again
again yeah I'm ignoring her bad side cuz
it's shreding her cat she can't be evil
and
hot but she's certainly hot so that we
can
see
yeah she's just
[Music]
pretending n need the
[\h__\h] did she just Su
what oh yeah seen been there done that
se seen it a lot times yeah
yeah I have you not seen it before
happens a lot in
games piercing the sky with a big
[Music]
laser salvation follows at your heels
and so do
[Music]
I
bye-bye
foree
fore excuse me ma'am this is a
[Music]
kfp excuse me I mean I don't know man I
mean nice nice talk but you want a
burger or
what if you don't want a burger I mean I
mean we got Nuggets we got
fries we got all kinds of stuff like you
just choose I mean I've been listening
to you for half an hour you just don't
choose chapter nine what did you say how
many chapters there are 10 or
12 10
oh let's
go main story is All I need maybe I I
don't know
maybe I don't know if I'll play the
prologue
epilog is it worth it maybe privately
I'll play it I don't know do I need to
play it for the sake of multiplayer do I
want
to that'll be decisions to make later I
guess but I'll just be glad to finish
the main story today I'll be able to say
I finished this
game in two
days and that'll be
satisfying
I have time anyway if we wait for Zeta
so it's
[Music]
fine cat Watchers
digest so I wonder how long this chapter
is cuz I wonder if I should eat my
sandwich or not if I don't eat my
sandwich I'm not not like crazy hungry
right
now I could just eat my pizza
afterwards it's short h two more hours
huh
what which
one I'm not that hungry honestly but I
could eat I
guess and I need an idol meeting too for
this last chapter that's for
sure eat if you're hungry it's about 2
hours okay
and an idol meeting and sandwich
ghetto and
maybe yeah
for you guys can also go take a short
short short short short short short
break short okay
short I'll be counting the clock is
ticking
okay
I I pet smooy and chunky wonky a little
bit they were sleeping so
happily on the
sofa and now smoothie thought that I'm
done streaming so she's
like she got
up aren't you followed me
around oh damn I bought the sandwich
today and it's actually
um off to day
interesting expiration date I saved the
sandwich from being thrown away from the
supermarket okay I hope this one's good
normally I wouldn't eat a tuna sand a
tuna and an egg sandwich
together it should be separate but okay
why they're
talking how much have they been talking
I know we can't hear it oh God I dropped
some tuna
smoing
[Music]
oh my tuna is so
dry
M oh she
[Music]
flopped that was cute
M that was a cute
flop tuna it literally looks like
there's like it's just tuna that's not
mixed with
anything just put on top the other
things so it might even be safe to eat
for a cat but I don't
know h
[Music]
also remember the other sandwich I
ate where I was so happy about the
Tomato the second half of the sandwich
didn't have it the second
triangle didn't have the Tomato I I took
another bite and another bite and
another bite looking for the tomato and
it just wasn't there I was like what the
hell was it supposed to be there or was
it never supposed to be there or was it
really supposed to be only on one
heal you got me excited with the
tomato
free trial
tomato please continue the Tomato trial
please extend
trial the tomato
cheese Co
cat ghost
[Music]
cat it's ghost
cat is why going to play with Ena did
you see the
thumnail did you see the
thumbnail
[Music]
yummy hey why are you making fun of my
thumbnail
pronunciation Oh Oh you mean I are we
going to play together as
cuz she's
starting in 15
minutes it would be so funny after we're
done if we raid into ena's stream and
let her know I finished the game oh no
wait she is she is finished she just is
in the Pro in the epilog
right but we were still way faster than
her
[Music]
now let me just finish
this one
[Music]
sandwich
I could join her for them if I'm
available I don't know if I'll be
available after
that so
short
oh next one is a bus
fight I hate
you she hates me cuz I kicked her out of
the group
no oh wait I don't need to do hers
anymore cuz I kicked her out of the
group
I love her though her next one is called
it's just a
[Music]
face
fore
not
hold
[Music]
yeah right she's switches
bodies I
forgot movie is circling me like a
shark can I switch bodies
[Music]
too
fore
spee
[Music]
foree
interesting
C the
the the switch between the voices and
also
her de demeanor and and attitude reminds
me of
Bales she can also go from
ujis to cutie patootie
energetic oh my
God next
please I'm done eating by the way but oh
that's her
snakes
I smovie on my on my lap but she's tried
to get
[Music]
away
e
did she audition for ATO games and then
failed and then ended up in in Grand
blue but she wanted to be a a
protagonist of a aelier game aier
calostro
imagine the idea is just so
versatile they didn't like her cuz she
they knew
like her cuteness is Too
Fake uh a protagonist
that is cute for real for
real they often heard a Rob when she was
too busy I didn't pain
enough a
[Music]
flashback
oh
she hates the your games
[\h__\h] she didn't
say I need to listen to that again did
she say at least bakay somewhere cuz she
didn't certainly didn't say it at the
end she just ended the yeah the sentence
normally
foolishly mistaking me for a primal
Beast so we're dealing here with an
[Music]
impostor
plane crew are we talking
about
[Music]
airplanes I did I
did
for sounds a little bit to
me that's German for for
snow why so much
German I think from here on out it get
it gets
like you know Side Story is that doesn't
seem so
important
H for another slot let's do it we got to
get strong for the
finale oh I'm going to play her right
oh uh then let me know look at
[Music]
this
okay just for this I'll change
[Music]
it hold while casting to
aim which one should I put in manen or
[Music]
disruption
I'll just put in
disruption I guess I don't
know a rich link Rob
stream it doesn't matter it's just for
this one
fight oh
oh two
[Music]
years uh
St
Poli wow wow wow wow wow
two years
damn you guys are with me for freaking
fin
[Music]
forever there's no end to
this Kos claims to be the founder of
alchemy and she uses it to transmute
Implements of murder that foes want no
part of
she creates various combos using XY and
her y attack is chargeable for more
power C's combo finisher changes based
on the number of X attacks performed
before the finisher try to use the best
combo for the
situation I'll
[Music]
try
oh is it always that short or do I have
to press it
longer oh
[\h__\h]
cute oh I didn't
even no never mind it's
fine we're on chapter N9 yeah we're
finishing it soon TM
what the hell is that clouds and let me
grab
[Music]
this looks
funky
surprise oh that did a lot of
damage
nice took me so long to figure out I
could pick them up and throw
them face triangle can be charged
triangle yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah open
please we better check any spots we've
[Music]
missed
suspiciously
[Music]
large midnight
Sun's
okay okay I'll try to
charge does it get even bigger when I
charge
him
nice yeah she's fun to play with but I
don't know if I in the last chapter want
to uh change the character that I'm
Ming what what what what
what a down there oh my God I'm stupid I
didn't see the
sign are they in these Stones never mind
there's one here out in the
open
waa that had some good
impact wa who's saying these things it's
confusing me cuz Koo basically has two
voices a low one and a Higher
One okay can we get through now GA a
free water Essences a
to oh there's
more and gav monster
tears I need more
monsters I feel like I saw something
exploding
there but no way they came out
again no nothing's here I can go now oh
I thought I need to check all the check
boxes
okay cute I like both sides of
C
[Music]
this
game almost makes me want to play the
gacha version of the game
almost
but jumping into a game like that now
after the game exists for years damn I
would have I would have missed out on so
many banners they probably also have
banners right
honestly same yeah just cuz of the
characters
but no time for gacha game and 10 years
10 years of
banners free banners
[Music]
too I don't even know what kind of like
battle
system
they use for grandl what kind of how do
you fight what what how do you what how
does how do things go
down turn based yeah turn based what is
what does it what does it look like it's
comparable
to
[Music]
for that's the first time I hear
that x y y hold y okay uh if I find an
enemy that's not about to
die
right oh my
ow like
this
[Music]
you took your damn time with
that does the same combo work when I'm
in the
air but I probably have to hits
right God's
sake
[Music]
nice that look
good
nice does she even need to connect the
hits or just
com W good
[Music]
question
yes
we got it
all now back to the main story hopefully
I know we have a few more of these that
we can
do
cute also with other characters but I
don't
know the stats don't
go improve that crazily
so and we don't have much
time m M well let me see is there any
easy ones
anymore uh katalina the next one is a
fight Calo the next one is a talk okay
this one we can
do yeah yeah story progress I know was
necessary m
okay uh that's where it
ends uh I think I saw one for Wawa too
no no oh what was that loud sound some
donk cats are doing some crazy stuff
again I guess we can do this
one one more is the only one anyway oh
we got to fight as Catalina for the
first time let me look at her skills
then she has a heal right I should
change remind me to change calostro
skills I guess I could do it now for
calostro
actually uh
uh here this one we bring back this
one okay the heal I'm probably not going
to use that so let's just put this one
in um and I'll just play around with it
just remember that this is above buff
the one on the right side is above buff
okay okay okay
ah this is one of the best arts for sure
she's
gorgeous the awakened
weapon what's the awakened
weapon I get another weapon for Catalina
or
what
calina gameplay let's go the former
knite of the Empire First
Empire katalina fights to protect Lia
wielding a magic sword she's an adapt
Warrior who adapts to any
situation X
Y pulling off combos first the Irish gge
wants the gge is full K can summon a
primal Beast AR to bolster her combo
skills and SC
okay
we'll see we'll
see gather six wind Crest what do they
look
like
oh I see the charging
thingy
oh wind
Crest is it
you okay one of the
six wait I thought we were fighting a
[Music]
boss
yeah the glowing things here's
[Music]
one wait how do I activate that the
thing is ready to be
[Music]
activated
stop that did I miss anything here ah
yes I
did oh a skill okay okay
okay four out of
[Music]
six
and is that her line that she always
says
ARIS
[Music]
N I didn't run in a circle did
I no that's from God of War hey people
going to be laughing at me again I come
down what the
[Music]
hell
H what where did it go is it
dead okay but no no wind Crest
though
maybe uh where did I not check
yet over here did I come from
here oh yeah
nice but that's a dead
end
oh
huh
ah Hey where's that there
before I got
[Music]
a feels
good what there's threee over
here I don't even need that
many I see now we got to go to the big
area
[Music]
probably my stone
friends
oh great
start level
35 all
right I am the
tech oh
oh I'm dead already well that was fast
as a
tank oh
no yes oh I barely I barely was able to
[Music]
escape I want I'm dead again I used
my thing maybe I'll focus on the boss
instead
I don't care about these small ones I
need tank needs to be at the
bus there we
go gol a
attacks are a
bitak oh no hey I didn't have
time no please don't kill me oh
[Music]
Circle wait I need to get a few more
percentage that's is that
Aris I was always wondering who that guy
was
no I don't even want to try dodging it
this time oh it kills me
what it's
[Music]
okay
again my crytical
somebody help me please oh my that's so
unfair let them please revive me
uhoh the
timing
impeccable there we
[Music]
go there we freaking
go
explosion
and with that we can move on in the main
[Music]
story
okay uh do I just we are we really good
I think we're good we're probably good
we're probably fine ah but skill
change for Catalina she will get which
one did I
switch the first one
right I
think
probably not that she necessarily need a
heal cuz I feel like everybody kind of
has some heals going on
almost but
yeah
oh hey I got your
thing what do I get I got a Chie and
sprayed and Cascade
[Music]
2 you got a slot for that Quest right oh
yeah indeed oh that's in gear right
everything's so hard to
remember how about what does Cascade 2
do maybe I'll give you that
one
stamina Garrison interesting
where is it here raise uh no shorten
skill cooldowns whenever you hit a foe
effect strength changes
B charge
[Music]
speed Makes Your Heart
Guard I just R makes your heart guarder
to break H wait why is there
what what's it the exclamation marks is
it because they're new we can give her
this one I don't know if she ever uses
that
though reduces
no boost damage against weak
points damn it I can't
[Music]
decide boost the let's do combo finisher
that one's surely
great
let's do this really quickly reporting
reporting I don't know where I got your
cocktail
recipe literally don't remember picking
that up ever but
yeah you're
welcome some
ashes
[Music]
and this one oh yeah I got exactly free
I can record one more yeah but like I
mean maybe in the
epilogue now I don't need it cuz I'm I'm
happy with my
team
okay
yes prison
chip hope you guys are ready for one
more
chapter one a more exciting
finale the power of
friendship will guide
us yeah I'm sure sefood would be great
but we do an all girl
team Mr
shades
[Music]
she's
back wait what is she doing
here oh thank
you uh is
been he's been captured he's been
kidnapped he's been adult
napped
crap he definitely was trying to
fight
o nice good to have them on our
side
[Music]
being spook this understandable but you
don't even you haven't even seen what we
saw I'm
spooked
[Music]
you destroy the sky what happens what's
left
this sky is
gone we just out and open space or
what Define Sky
yeah the sky is gone is air gone too I
guess
so
don't
worry we got bam back we can do
this it's time to start would be end of
next month du to have the start Dash
work plus anniversary next month of free
draws oh and this there's
T say that first say that first why did
I go
there why wouldn't you say that
first
nah I'm good I'm
good I don't have time for Goda
games and once I start getting into one
I will get too addicted I'm I'm glad I
don't have such an addiction right
now I was once addicted to a gacha I
know how it is it's better to stay
away once it's too late then it's too
[Music]
late n didn't touch star rail didn't
touch G didn't touch any of those cuz
that's when I started you know
H let's
F spitting fact yeah I said once it's
too late it's too late it is
true it is
known
well I
mean I would say the plan is to save the
world Roland is
aside side
[Music]
quest oh blue archive is less harsh on
your
time m
[Music]
that's
nice have you asked Ena how she handles
playing
gacha
well I mean her streams are shorter she
doesn't read Super Chat so maybe she
uses the Super Chat raing time to play
gacha
games
for yeah Super Chat fun are fora didn't
you
know did you not
know
of
course is there any more I don't see any
only one today only one piece of
trash
disappointing oh different kind of
trash this J looks nearly brand new the
entry seem to be about
wow what did you WR about me kind of
creepy if you're reading this then I
guess something must have happened to me
L is powerful to say the least anything
short of a perfect plan won't be without
its losses but if sacrifices must be
made I want to be the only one to take
the fall so that out of the way I'd like
to make an apology the truth is I used
Wawa I knew it I couldn't go up against
the not once she commanded to church I
needed my own pieces when I saw Wawa's
combat skills in tempale I knew I wasn't
luck also I knew You' carry on the fight
against live should I fail your crew's
Devotion to each other is the pillar
that bolsters Wawa's resolve there's no
evil that can sever severe severe your
bonds that's clear to me now more than
ever I was wrong to keep you in the dark
600 years ago I promised to protect all
Sky dwellers after meeting you and your
crew it further proved I was right to
side with the skies traveling with
everyone over the past days reminded me
of cherished by gone memories it's been
an honor adventuring with you all thank
you for everything
n you found a Jal belonging to Roland
but you may find more out in the world
by doing all the quest his entries are
saved in the arcraft of Li's Journal
okay your Journal is now my
journal
[Music]
W I was my
head one thing I don't really like is
this map there's too many clouds I don't
know what's going on in this map that's
the only criticism I have besides the
voices in my
head but the vo is how
worse a sky them well
yeah yeah true when is it going to clear
up
[Music]
though saying the sky go away yeah maybe
maybe I'll support what L is doing let's
get rid of this
guy perfect
actually realize our interests align so
strongly
wait is that my
song bomit Wait how's it Go
Again
bom but I didn't I have something like
that in my my my
song which song was
it wait it wasn't it sleep
talking uh yeah
wait I know I know which part but like
how does it go the
melody so unfamiliar
now
enti
P
[Music]
talk b
b
[Music]
something like
that I said okay firm
ho wait
what oh it's like a
maze
[Music]
me sleep talking in the night talking oh
that's right
yeah you got me feeling so right I don't
know the melody
anymore wait which which hole this
one
[Music]
so
L talking maybe we all should have
stream sleep talking a little bit
more talking in my dream I'm sleep
talking all these nights
you
no that's just a normal
chorus how do I get to bombell B
bombell dark
liquid oh we may have a bunch of MSP
again don't we how
many 250 is that
MSP yeah
h
[Music]
fore close to okay let's
go they waited a l wait didn't I have to
attack it [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] why did why did they not attack
it you want to max out the character I
plan to play with oh okay okay
okay Dimension
warp well it's the same there it
is wait that hurts
what we'll just go back I guess cuz now
we can go through in the reality
whatever the reality is at this
[Music]
point Bell
B I get the bom B but I don't know
anymore what's after like how the
[Music]
melody help
me
money
[Music]
money she busy now she a YouTuber now
she can't help me
anymore she's lost we've lost
her all right get ready for a funky
fight
probably
oh wait are we going to fight all those
uh Prime Evil
again
he's
[Music]
stronger epic wait okay can you girls
shut up
though let me enjoy the epic music
please yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep yep
yep yep yep yep yep yep be quiet be
quiet be
[Applause]
quiet what's
happening where's even where is safety
oh God oh God they're confusing
[Music]
ah
okay
[Music]
okay this is why I play realink with a
Wawa stream in the back background oh
you just don't you have all the yapping
off and listen to W one yapping instead
nice
decision oh oh you're actually going to
be
useful and bring out your own furricane
mommy can I have a furricane no we got
furricane at home furry canane at home
literally died immediately literally
furry cane at home
useless okay I think I have to voice
over because I can't do it now we'll
talk later r v comes first
okay he joins the
team
zoom
zoom Yap expansion infinite
rambling um can you
stop I forgot furricane could do
that magical girl transformation yeah
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I forgot
too oh
Lord
damn it's like barely hitting us at all
I'm not even trying to stay away
oh my gacha I said I don't want to play
gacha don't
worry well thank you I am your gacha how
about
that oh my God what is that I need to
sneeze oh oh no oh
nice I dodged
it what what happened they were at 87 I
mean couldn't we have waited a little
bit
longer I did it too early well they got
to keep up with me they also started so
early and I always keep up with
them n
yo nice
drums
at least we
[Music]
linked n n
NY
oh hydration time oh no oh
no oh no oh no oh
no oh
no
why am I always alone like they're
always in a group look at them on the
right side running together against the
wall I'm always doing my own thing all
alone I never get the
memo oh
[\h__\h]
I guess they're coded to do that okay I
feel better
now uh uh you're doing me a concern
right
[Music]
now
spamming W
close very close o I saw him I saw I saw
you naked for a
moment oh
[Music]
no
okay almost dead almost dead almost
dead sorry guys I got the
vision I don't think you have it it's
too
bad but the good thing is the magic of
streams
is when you watch a Wawa stream you
automatically Acquire The W Wawa Vision
Wawa vision
and with that you can see the game in my
eyes if you play the game you would have
not seen the furri canane
naked only through my screen through my
stream this becomes
Possible Oh no have
mercy oh wait oh oh W
vision
I'm so
stupid did you see it wait oh I feel
like a million rupes but uh what are we
going to do about
him
adopt dot dot
dot thank you you guys are so nice to
me it's almost 8 you want to stop L too
don't
you after all the time I spent with you
I know how much you care for her but
even if you love her after what she's
done we have to stop
her my
mommy or I should say intends to
sacrifice the future of this world I
know I can't let her get away with that
but I can no longer Fain innocence I
thought
ignorance this has gone on long enough
temporary
chice what do you say to a temporary Tru
Tru Al the TRU oh BR
fist you want to stop her and so do we
so she don't get any easier than that
hey B it how about we could
use why considering the scale of
violence I inflicted on your crew
well in the end you did help
us oh my God so wholesome her [\h__\h]
bro fist is still out
there isn't your arm going to get tired
especially with all that armor on it huh
yes it [\h__\h] hurts fist bumped me
already all right I'll join you in the
fight against
Li the amount of time you kept your fist
up really impresses just
me SK he can do it too of course I can I
can do it longer than any of
[Laughter]
you do I want to edit my
[Music]
party you tell
[Laughter]
me nah okay I like that
level 35 a he under us he's Bel
us the
ladies are going to do the
job I want to check
something yeah yeah that's not really
what I wanted uh do I have to things no
ah uh ah I do I have two so let's do
Fair's
weapon uh I could uncap it again but I
should probably spread it out a little
bit who
else to uncap
guys Catalina Wawa or
kostro
oh I'll turn the voices back on again
don't worry it was for the battle cuz
they're yapping yap yap yap yap yap all
on fairy oh are you saying that because
of
multiplayer uh uh yeah oh I can't oh I'm
[Music]
missing
you need the damage for the bosses well
I literally can't so I'll keep it for
now maybe until the last last last last
last boss some other last bosses will
give me those
[Music]
materials and then the entire ending is
going to be okay I I'll then let's do
our best and listen to their
yapping
uh
we're all in this together after
[Music]
all secret chest time don't troll
me
looks
simple if I didn't just miss one that's
it I
fell wait where is
it that's a weird
[Music]
one oh this one trolly
chest
I
see and then you fall
down
well the camera is making me
dizzy I really hope there was nothing on
the right side here cuz I don't have
time to look on the right
side
okay this one this one yes I'm going to
get
it this time I won't
slip
[Music]
trustful you
suck that
sucks how did I land the first one of
the last two but not the one in the
middle of
that oh my
God no it's not going to take me 20
minutes
[Laughter]
I thought I thought you know to save
speed I should just go for it
but that was very far
off
duh the camera here it turns
automatically and it's kind of lame I
slipped again
it took you 30 minutes what does what's
the matter with these chests oh my God
they're not even that worth it are they
like they just give me a little bit of
money oh wait why am I so slow no no
forgive
me [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I mean that was bounc to fail took
me around 40 holy [\h__\h] I'll give it like
three three more tries
maximum especially in end game like do I
really need
this this is just for flexing your
platforming skill oh
God had enough time but the jump was way
too playing it way too safe
oh attacking ahuh
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh I see yeah yeah okay mm that
helps although I did reach that
like that waved in my jump before too I
just missed one but that might make it
easier yeah I don't know I I'll try it
now
okay
okay uh no I I hesitated I was like what
the [\h__\h] how do I how do I jump how do I
attack here we go this is the real boss
fight I love how they also always join
me in the run the
girls
uhoh almost that was like one tiny inch
however much an interest I don't
know but I also in this case I kind of
messed up the beginning of the jump
actually but the whip the Whip still
carried
me imagine if that's not all the stones
and there's actually one I've been
missing all
along oh what okay I thought I could do
it in one
goal I feel like I can do
it just need to
believe oh
maybe I could do a second attack to save
myself there that's one yeah one attack
is not enough
huh
here we
go
yeah that did not take me 30 or 40
minutes that took me maybe 10 minutes
guys easy that's easy I feel like you
need to understand that you need to
attack you need to use the attack then
it's much easier if you do it without I
feel like you could still maybe make
it but the the jump has to be so
exact which is so difficult because like
balancing yourself into the right
position here while being in time
pressure is tough for
sure nice nice
Flex obviously I'm such a gamer no one
can ever doubt me
again you didn't know you could attack
midair I mean you can
did you know that in normal battles you
can attack midair did you just not
realize oh crap that you can attack
midair even in such a
situation I mean I I probably if I
wasn't streaming the game and getting
hints from you guys I I may have not
tried it out
myself I don't know maybe I should give
myself some credit maybe I would
have
oh my
God the big golden
statue
[Music]
what is it what is it with he's like
recharging his health
[\h__\h] do I even need to do this I can
just go into the into the
hole
wait
what they're here as
well they were like no go back you need
to activate the link
attack wait I don't understand am I
supposed to find them on the inside or
on the outside does it even
matter
what whatever I did I guess I did it
right cuz now I can
proceed
hey we haven't seen a slime in a
[Music]
while what's
up what
up gamer sense I swear it's a thing and
the RPG sense of like placing certain
things placing items placing
enemies time
timing it's a
thing got a new trophy what's wait to
what is it with these trophies you guys
mentioned it before where the [\h__\h] do I
open the
trophies in a joural oh my
God
what what kind of
rewards a for like showing it off in
multiplayer claim
all do you want to set this it yeah no
wait that's not what I wanted to do
anyway claim all this one
[Music]
oh standard we get one standard
reum link together free
quality reum Ah that's what we actually
want yeah
nice okay so we got them
all oh this
ones these are not to claim or I guess I
claimed these ones
too already when I did it the first time
okay nice haul thank you
[Music]
you didn't know this was a
thing yeah well lia's Journal is easy to
ignore here I am once again I turn into
[Music]
pieces wow wait it looks way cooler than
the first
time all right I'll wait a little bit
more for Wawa she's at 80 although she
probably has time when we
start let's do it let's do
it it's
time CR
this there we
go so considerate of me to
wait hey what about everybody else wait
why are they not doing
it
what they're all at
100% hello is it because they knew there
was a script upcoming or
what are you
help why did they not use and they're
still not using it they could do a could
do a
triple okay galanza is helping but why
the [\h__\h] did they not activate
it just use
it oh my oh my God the yapping oh my how
do you not go
insane holy [\h__\h] it's like I feel like
the same person is talking
double so all of them are oh my God it's
like we have like 24
[Music]
voices oh my
God
[Music]
for are some of them louder because I
said it to
head or is it really a
bu it's like a full H yeah yeah whole
live at Minecraft Summer Festival summer
sports
festival
just need the the internet breaking
up oh I got a treatment for using 50
potions and are you not impressed that I
actually understood that I had to go
behind the pillar for once
without watching the others do it first
oh my
God
[Music]
oh he's falling slowly he wants belly
WS it's not falling he just purposefully
fell to the side to show us his
belly okay now you want to do it huh cuz
C you started you don't care when I
started what is this go is some bullying
going on here or
[Music]
what this could have been our second
verse girls
deism KN
[Music]
Eternal
Icee
where is the boss oh
there oh no oh ah
ah no
[Music]
wait okay I got it I got
it two of my friends are dead what the
[\h__\h] is this H made that oh okay wait
wait wait uh let me let me go to one of
them oh they're both they're both
[Music]
back fight I'm going my
b
[Music]
thank you for your mental
support where where is
[Music]
it ah [\h__\h] oh
no don't worry I'll use my
potion you guys seem
[Music]
dizzy oh dodging is hey I do both Dodge
and and
a now that's just not fair saying that
in my presence I'm a Dodge
[Music]
lover what's going on I don't see
sometimes where my goal
is now I see it
[Music]
oh too many special
effects oh
[Music]
no
wow wow wow wow
wow wowow
[Music]
wowow what is he going to do he's
charging he's
charging oh you went a different
direction
unexpected
okay we're doing this
[Music]
again
oh oh
[Music]
no
[\h__\h]
epic oh thanks oh my God nice timing I
was about to
[Music]
die the owner of
invincibility ha katalina is dying and
you're
[Music]
laughing what would we do without lria
who literally like she's not an official
party member she has no HP but she can
still heal and revive
us like it feels like a
cheat just really
okay
[Music]
oh get out of
theree
spee
[Music]
oh uh all right all right all right
right right right run run run
run
clut this guy gets tanky in higher
difficulties of of course he
[Music]
does fancy finish fancy finish
go get
him yeah yeah wa gets the last
[Music]
one we get the
last what that was
Perfection that was per that was
Perfection k
ooh how many more of these like two
[Music]
more same
TBH
a is the small one going to help us
too I
wonder
oh I'm
fine thanks for warning I'm good we can
do this 9 hour
stream I did say by the
way that I
would go on a trip and whatever um it's
still in the plants
but it's it's uh still you know kind of
weird
um it's probably going to be pretty
spontaneous I still don't know like
there was a date where I was supposed to
go
but probably going to be delayed a
little
bit um so I don't know about this week
yet how it's going to
end but we'll just I'm just taking it
day by
day one after
another oh welcome back welcome
home now you know what I should do
masteries yeah so you guys might have to
take a day by day too and at this rate
we might not even have a schedule for
next week even though we could have had
one this week I can make you a uh in
hindsight schedule of this
week
yeah yeah mystery weeks ahead of
us uh anyway okay we have 351 points
let's give a lot to our main character
oh that's that already took a
bunch do we have a new attack here Grant
Stout heart to fair and summons a
damaging Spirit orb I saw that before I
don't know if I really am interested in
that all right let's look a little bit
at defense too A Drop Kick oh wait where
at Wawa oopsie uh I wanted to go
here ooh a new social slot over here
yes Health Points Plus
40 damage taken minus 10% uh during
poison ah I can upgrade this too I
forgot
ooh plus thousand
plus how much does it take me to upgrade
the g p even though I'm not using
it got me
[Music]
curious uh upgrade
we oh I can do that standard refin we
have quite a
bit let's uncap it
twice then we get thous 500 extra extra
HP yo unless we run out of
[Music]
money Oh that's oh was that all can I
not afford
more wa
57,000 o I like it when numbers go up
says
my my
achievement
okay then let's Max it out let's
go
awesome eh 68 well what stopped us now
definitely not the money I guess oh the
the materials we can we can buy 42
crystals don't
know SN
M how many do I
need oh
I got I get them at sio no treasure
train yeah 42 chart s they have but
M no M I didn't say how many I need
though that's a really good level for
your weapon yeah all right yeah I sold
all thether crystals yeah it's not about
the
money now at least oh well okay um
that's
fine uh let's check we only have 169
points left who needs it the
most maybe yeah
Catalina
ooh oh that looks and sounds
epic
well I'm not playing her so she'll
figure it out on her own but I think we
might replace like this it's midnight
for me I'm
good I'm fine don't
worry
over here
right at least the 500 we
get Sac W is good yeah it looks
good fantas
magoria so the
Mastery on
fairy what is that is this this no wait
her skills are
German what what is that a
c thanks for the members ships
membership
gifts well now I certainly can't afford
it
but maybe in a few levels this
one ah so close okay I'll remember it
grants fantasma Gloria to the entire
party
ah a nice buff that apparently you
really
like I see didn't we get another
sigil uh slot or am I ah we
did we
did I can sell all the the ones what's
this enemity
boost attack based on how
L not the worst as I am on low HP quite
often oh boosts link attacks sky on arts
and I love this okay taking it
mine mine and mine
only oh she can have one
too I don't know n what
whatever blind is currently a big thing
isn't
it that would make sense wouldn't
it although I mean NPC's AI rarely gets
hit from my
POV okay hope you're enjoying thank you
I am
enjoying
[Music]
I'm looking forward to putting this on
my list of finished
games and finished games of this year
too oh we have a whole menu guys can you
bring him the
menu I'm busy can someone bring him the
menu
[Music]
please
what I waited to long
okay
oh they do be
running oh she got a shortcut like Mario
Cart oh my
god well great we're going to die
anyway girls any
ideas she's going to help us too
[Music]
huh
uh she she's going to help us right
she's creating land for us yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah just believe
it a
dance
what's coming she said it's
coming which one snake I don't remember
fighting a snake never mind I
do I mean I don't remember it
well
but doesn't matter what I
remember I'll kill you even harder than
the first
time and now I remember it's the one
where old maguma was everywhere we were
jumping from platform to platform and
that's why now we have some platforms
[Music]
again the [\h__\h] blight see it's good
that I gave her bl light
resistance
but again you're mostly safe right in
front of him he moves barely oh but the
[\h__\h] BL this time is kind of
rath let me go over
here damn it he moved
anyway
what's
[Music]
up my my first fight with him was
better take
it's late it's been many many
[Music]
hours I know not the
again
oh my God loud CIO in my
ear oh I'm on top of his
nails
where are
[Music]
you bye-bye thank you for watching for
so
long
what is he going to do the thing again
Escape okay I was first oh no they're
not going to make it okay they did make
it good for them oh he's doing it over
there too oh my God he's doing it
everywhere no place is
safe maybe
here she's chilling over here does she
know something I
don't where where is it going to be
where are we going to have The Showdown
here
[Music]
okay the [\h__\h] Boss Rush man I don't
know if I like Boss
Rush I say no
enough Boss
[Music]
Rush oh wait oh 7 maybe it's too early
for activating it oh
no oh I'm not dead
oh oh double heal there overhealing
me yeah the thingers they're not even
changing
anything like in other games I feel like
often Boss Rush at least they change up
[Music]
some some
things but this is pretty much the same
just in
purple
purple now
wow damn this one's
really tenacious Dark
Rising what is this another Batman
movie okay oh yeah he did the same thing
before right what did we do in that
everybody went to destroy and I didn't
do it this time I'll do it this time
I'll
help
this leave it to
me
yay one tentacle gone I can't believe
they've been doing this but I was all
time in the
front
I didn't even
know I didn't even see the
tentacles okay maybe it's good that
we're uh having a rematch for this boss
in
[Music]
particular
nice we will not let me have this
one I didn't get the heal I gra like a
refund oh nice
Hit
[Music]
N
what's so funny I
hear I don't understand can we keep this
corner clean
please uh-oh how am I going to get over
there there we
go oh
[\h__\h] it
is gener
a really dope
boss I really like
it but now I would like you to die
sooner rather than later
please
what's where what is his face somewhere
else are we dealing with his
tail ra the
action oh well that
was like the safest place to be in
ever
[\h__\h] oh thanks oh so much heal thank
you I can't go over there what the hell
there you
[Music]
go oh we can do fancy finish again
maybe oh that's the new new attack I
gave
her come on please just end it oh
katalina not you I didn't want you to
end your
life not much more yeah but probably one
more of these bosses right or is this
the last one of the Boss Rush I don't
remember
[Music]
yeah we did it again just like the last
fight it's like I calculated it
all the only reason it took so long is
because I wanted it to be finished like
this with
style
nice anime finish number two
I'm so sick of sitting in this chair
today I want to chill in my
bed thank you so nice of them to come
back and help well okay maybe there's no
more boss in the Boss Rush cuz uh we
used up
our helping bosses didn't
we maybe that's
it maybe that was the last one
M almost there
wa going to eat tuna pizza after this oh
had tuna sandwich and then tuna
Pizza you little slime
gold
slime my first one I think where are you
going to hey can he
escape he's
just
wait
Ming six
C I smell them I smell
slimy stinky
slime how much how
much how much in total oh wait there's
slow motion he died in slow
motion 1,21 MSP and glitter Crystal okay
it's all
right he freaking died in slow motion I
was like what's going
on
Mo slow motion
[Music]
mention motion why are you so
slow the
Stars I'm a
star we get any of the ingredients that
I
need
oh we did what I can go up to 7
70 did I need to go to 70 or 75 I feel
like it was
75 I was yeah I was 75 [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] it was probably 75 right
where was it again uh yeah no
skills
uh what I don't know what to look at
anymore I don't know ah and now I know
yeah okay yeah but it's got to be 75
right this looks like the
sky looks like straight from a magic to
gaing land
card
dark hi chunky
wony she's looking at
me menacingly no really
cutely o looks like a the final boss or
probably the final boss version one and
then version two version
[Music]
three poor
guy wish I could help him but too
bad my hands are
tied
if this isn't the final boss right I ha
to see how much it will escalate for
real well we'll just turn into Bahamut
again
probably or something even
stronger our own Chima
of all of our things not just
baham oh there we go
oh
for wait did she say anything about her
son being on my
side
[Music]
oh he
she did where did I go
wrong
no
compromise thank
[Music]
you angry
Mayo the
the
first
[Music]
second oh the keepers on the ground are
new more or
less a
[Music]
sh
what should I kill first the keepers or
the hands probably the keepers cuz
they're
lower
HP oh one hand
down only level 45 yeah pretty low oh
should I jump into the warm row
[Music]
but the blind hurts
me they're also fighting
[Music]
a
uh Wormhole
again I don't really understand this SP
no okay
[Music]
okay do you guys understand
this oh ah she was going to resurrect
me you need to get the
beams uh to spawn Keepers near the boss
break them and then enter the
[Music]
Wormhole Wormhole is now to dodge text
aha like if there's something big that's
hard to Dodge I go into
Wormhole destroy pillars to open
portals ah they make portals
okay the pillars make the
portals what is this
camera a oh oh oh
[Music]
oh I don't know should I
go two people
dead
it hurts but I I'll go to help you okay
why the [\h__\h] did you die in The
Plight
[Music]
girl oh we might have a we might going
to get a game over here uhoh be
careful
let leave it to liia cuz she has no
[Music]
HP I don't know I'll go in here see what
happens
[Music]
oh do I want to be
here maybe
not this seems
[Music]
wrong it's got to be bright
right
nice yeah okay
okay uh did he just teleport me or did I
accidentally enter
I think yeah I think this was script
[Music]
up oh yeah good
timing could there be any better
timing than
now put the
stones oh now understand what you mean
okay how to get the stones there though
I know how
what how do they how I know how the wor
spawn but how do the stones spawn oh sh
what how am I suddenly in the middle of
so much [\h__\h]
[Music]
blind the stones follow me
okay
[Music]
okay it's okay it's okay they don't do
much
[Music]
damage this Last Judgement thing
how do I stop it killing the
[Music]
hands that doesn't look like enough
time oh it's gone okay maybe only one
half of P had to be
gone ah okay
okay I read the
situation
correctly
hey it's almost dead how is it suddenly
at 70%
17 I guess the hands did a good
job
dying I'm going to keep on
running keep on running oh you need
help ah and now yeah okay well they
spawn
here good to know that there's such a
strategy
uh not for me oh okay so ah wait wait
spawned over here here here here here
here here yeah
[Music]
okay destroy that a the boss is gone
though but when you enter the
home is when the stun happens right but
he the boss
moves
[Music]
possible
okay
[Music]
oh what the hell what are you
doing he's making
art he's creating
art wait
I thought that would be pretty
close I thought that would do
something oh did
it oh
did I thought that just was his normal
state right
now
[Music]
oh okay and how are you going to become
even stronger ER from this looking at
your form
currently well often they go from a
really overpowered looking being into a
simple just one human human looking
being to be even
stronger so maybe they downgrade
themselves
now L fight me
oneone
oh she she uses herself
[Music]
now
oh what about your
[Music]
son crazy
woman I still love
her how you going to top
this
I'm curious show
[Music]
me looks like I'm uh like a what am I
thinking of like it's a there's a v that
looks like
[Music]
that
yeah go get him my sweet
[Music]
pets yeah no problem you can bring me
more not three at a time that's kind of
L
lame ooh more
[Music]
blind did he just say to go to his
side I'm here
[Music]
first
nice W I'm surprised he still has any
power in his body left after all of
that I guess it's the power of
friendship damn what is this
creation
W oh
oh how are they even here I thought we
were in some crazy other
dimension
y the
power fren friends ships my friend
ships my friend ships
[Applause]
literally give this on to
me nice
[Music]
pun the cuts oh she's also
here
sweet o nice cut scene
nice I'm
vibing I'm so
vibing yeah I like him he's
cool he's done with his nap I like naps
too I feel
[Music]
you damn will like go freaking
Guild we're
raiding
aves
[\h__\h]
glasses yo must be so annoying to have
glasses when this is what you do all day
they must fall down so often also he has
no nipples by the
way just want to mention this at this
point it's surprising I didn't notice
until now the lack of nipple
arinos in this
game oh
good for free I mean this is about the
world ceasing to
exist you can't charge me for some
ammo do you understand what's at
stake
wow oh that's
beautiful
oh we're so
magical these scenes hit harder when you
actually are using these people as your
party
members I mean I did use e for a
[Music]
while so I still feel like
connected
here we go what are we going to do
attack
this are are the others fighting on
their own again without me or am I
fighting on my own without
them
uh
oh I I'll I'll join you
then
oh what's that oh wait
[Music]
you wait who are we going to use this
on on the hand please
right hopefully on
the W what what what did I what did I do
something wrong
what are they who are they using this
[Music]
on do I even need to fight these
forms not on their
hand why
[Music]
not
hey guys
look whatever damage we do on the hands
also puts damage on on the whole thing
right everybody else was also working on
the hands I thought I could trust them
more oh okay come with me come with me
come with me over here over here over
here ah too
far
okay that's probably too far
[Music]
right I'll
try
[Music]
work I
think
[Music]
okay
nice I think I finally understand the
system I've cracked the Cod I'm
not anymore avoiding your system I am
part of your
system all
right is this a shadow or you or the
blight I think it's the Shad uh no the
blight yeah [\h__\h] you kidding me it's
both the Shadow and the
blight V is exactly what I need right
now last judgment isn't that
a oh we need half of the hands again we
need half of the
hands guys give me your
wings
never mind you can take them back they
don't count apparently they only take
human
hands or Celestial hands or
whatever so mean that it's in the middle
of the [\h__\h]
blind oh but it's not hurting me right
now chickens with tiny human
hands this blight does know damage okay
I
convenience it won't hurt me in the real
world that almost sounds like a a meme
phrase
[Music]
oh
okay
salvation
[Music]
uh-oh
uhoh sound
[Music]
good n the [\h__\h] uh why is this stuff
back in in this face I didn't know what
the hell to do oh wait is this you have
to hide behind
[Music]
it is that what that's
for destroy it okay it's
gone it also helped me what the [\h__\h]
what why is it
[Music]
golden now it's invisible
what's that
laser come here ah [\h__\h]
here I don't know about this
[Music]
one
trying
uh uh didn't work nope no no no no no
should I stay in this world
though
[Music]
H some hands I just throw some
hands what's with the
floor uh oh the bles oh god let's get
out of here ah ah I need a
[Music]
wormhole
get out of
[Music]
here it's so chaotic right
now
okay what phase are we in
guys
what you call this
face oh
we at
50% oh ah uh where here here's perfect
here's perfect hit me hit me hit me hit
me hit
me
get Dad worked one
[Music]
F and we broke it oh my God
double double
breaking [\h__\h] yeah everything everything
you got on the menu today I'm
hungry
27%
[Music]
suddenly that is
huge what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh oh I didn't no
this why was you down again
hey I'm ready for the link
attack I came in time for the link
attack it's okay it's okay it's
fine oh oh yeah chase
me over here over here over here over
here did you just
cancel did you just freaking
cancel we were in the perfect
position
oh salvation time again whatever that
meant
yeah we destroy this
right we need to destroy both oh my God
it's so bright though
so much Bain is this the Barbie
movie all right
[Music]
okay so much more coordinated than
before
oh uh around here please thank
you please please work please work
please
work
H the other girls are all ready for some
super fancy finishing
moves oh me
[Music]
too 14% 13%
12 I might not it might not
finish
but we might get down to 5% or so
oh wait maybe
maybe I have 2%
left no you left is this scrip
it
[Music]
each
[\h__\h] no way that this is not
scripted no oh if we just got slap some
hands
right slap some hands somebody somebody
slap some
hands oh my God they are so out for
me excuse
me come on come
on how much is
1% how much is 1%
oh I guess we have to finish this phase
no go here
probably that's what they
want okay now she
fell
my I got the
kill so so I get the loot that's what
that means I ran for it I freaking ran
for
[Music]
it
nice oh
[\h__\h]
finally it's been over 9
hours
sorry
Mommy I mean it sorry
Mommy sorry
mppy say it say
it
[Music]
oh
a now honestly I don't I think you need
to go to
jail
oh to horny jail no just
kidding no
OBS guys we were just gone for a second
right he doing fine on my time this must
be YouTube to be
honest
no he's a good
boy
what [\h__\h] my father was done
[Music]
y
no
no this game is so
cringy maybe my perception
is wrong because I played it as a
marathon
[Music]
basically what the [\h__\h] mommy he didn't
say sorry Mommy that was the problem
what what why how how is he B
no
how there's several
on that poor
guy he was a good one
[Music]
sheesh for
real is this an
aftermath oh no it's how she found
him a
what
[Music]
um what the
[\h__\h]
oh so he was a
vessel
mhm like
Pokemon
for Fore
speech
foree
yeah for real look are
you
[Music]
she
uh was that worth it bye
what an end to
her
[Music]
life don't make me follow you wait what
or do we not fight him at all just left
your
party
is he just gone is he just like that's
his life
now or like he's been Unleashed and he's
just go to chill somewhere
else Final Chapter you guys said there's
oh you guys said 10 + one
oh I F him immediately
okay
[Music]
hopefully
H Let's help
him maybe we need spaceship now not
Airship oh this is the 10
[Music]
oh
e
[Music]
for
fore
[Music]
yeah that's what she's been
saying yeah who knows why we need a
rebirth maybe too many
bugs the Earth because too many
bugs and viruses which you could take
literally or philosophically
or or
metaphorically
yeah can not just like Cal calm him
down he's a great dude but the vessel is
a great dude I don't know about the
Bahamut but the Bahamut surely can be
just
like go back chill mode
no thank you for not giving me a choice
of what to
say personally you always give me
choices maybe they're thinking I can't
be trusted with choices now
I'm too far
[Music]
gone what
wrong this time can you hear me this
time it was
OBS we got good internet but like today
OBS and YouTube is crashing all the
time why you crash so
much like a
pinata what thank you for the lore Super
Chat any trash on the ship oh my God
there's still
trash
so
last fight really is the last fight
right do we get there
immediately should I upgrade everything
again if I
can I got some 42 chards
yo only one fight okay let me just see
what I can do if I can do anything we
have
154 then let's go
fairy m
I'm just going to put it all into
[Music]
Fairy
Oh yes that's
it
[Music]
and uh what else can I
do I don't
remember my faite lady
I don't know if if it's if the Boss Rush
is really problematically
long generally the game isn't long but
the Boss Rush feels so long or is it
just because we've been like you
[Music]
know we've been playing for the whole
day yeah maybe it's the 9
[Music]
hours
the Boss Rush was a
bit unnecessarily long a little bit just
a little
bit I'm F I'm f this is nothing compared
to the Zelda
disaster cuz there I also had problems
with the fights I'm not I don't really
I'm not really struggling even though
I'm tired I'm not really struggling with
the fights uh I'm also not like hungry
or anything what good what
[Music]
good
is that the true
story
[Music]
Ur oh did we just make a battle platform
no just a
prison or how are we going to
fight
WD40 why does it sound like that why
does it sound like like
metal what is the
platform
[Music]
squeak
he so
[Music]
Rusty yeah sure I like
him yeah
[Music]
yeah just got some freaking flipflops
on he not good foot wear for a journey
like
this
flipflops got some freaking
boots
L holy music of the Lords and churches
maon
why am I looking at this
[Music]
back too late wa too late I thought I
had more time what where
is is he everywhere where I go is he
like
God I move and just kind of follow oh
never mind now
W
dead I help I want to help I want to
help why do I always got to look at his
back no he's taking damage pretty well
a
oh
[Music]
o I'll do it okay okay okay okay almost
party
wise
who is
singing
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh oh no you you're telling me
it's going to get worse ran stop
talking you're the [\h__\h] ship I can't
hear
you he's like rambling
[Music]
rambling why is
heing oh my God the voice is in my head
man this is what happens after 10 hours
of streaming I haven't stream for 10
hours in a
while this is
normal
they want to bring
[Music]
B it's please stop this she's
saying stop listen what are we doing are
we fighting CU it said zero for me where
are you guys doing the
damage here
okay sorry I was
[Music]
late music is so loud I can't even hear
the yapping nice drown it out
uh oh oh wait
hey
here
oh I don't know what's wrong to a
man there we
[Music]
go hey I'm also B what the [\h__\h] is that
e what the [\h__\h] is that oh
him what do you mean you can
separate like a
what
[Music]
the go
back
back what the [\h__\h] just
exploded go back home you're
Dr oh for
real
[Music]
go
home I order you in Uber
okay what is going on with the
[Music]
ground hey hey hey hey oh I know this
yeah he fights the same way as
before it's so fast he's
zooming stay here stay in the middle you
a
little
[Music]
wait oh are we not fighting him what's
going on
hello
what happened to my link didn't I have
like a link slow motion thing going
on he just cancel
it was he at was he at zero heal I
didn't even look now he's back to 100 I
need to
[Music]
FU
oh
[Music]
yeah it's going down fast but dude
dude
oh
[Music]
what is he doing what is he charging
what is he
[Music]
planning just going to spam
this yeah until the end just keep on
standing there and do nothing yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
W no no oh no oh no oh oh oh oh this is
bad oh this is very bad this could be oh
no never
mind ah okay okay okay I'll try my best
to stay alive now sorry for the trouble
sorry oh my God what the [\h__\h] is
that what do you mean you back
did he Sprint you out again you know
what that means you're not part of
him
[Music]
SE oh sco did I just hear
sco
[Music]
there we
go one
[Music]
more that's a typical you have to
remember get a hold of yourself remember
from the time when you were
normal
no don't take
don't B thank you Ma do I play him no
[Music]
no
[\h__\h] this is kind of insane oh
no don't
die I'll try ah [\h__\h]
what don't let
End
come who's
dead here here here here here here let
me do it let me do
it
oh my
God that could have been the
end that could have been the end the end
is never the end it's never the end it's
never the
end until it is the
[Music]
end and maybe that end is
now come on come on come on come on we
can we do a fancy finish can we do a
fancy almost almost almost
[Music]
almost
[Applause]
go
[Music]
spee
fore
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
foree
accept
the oh oh oh oh that's that's good
that's good that's good yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah I'm so
numb I've become so
[Music]
numb
I
oh she's like me she's
done
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm out of this ah leave me out of
[Music]
this it's just those two it's just them
I
quit I
quit nice
bamboozle I'm taking tomorrow
off I have to record some things
anyway
understand
yeah
y
oh
[Music]
n do it just do
it don't let your be wife who be dreams
what don't let your be wife don't let
your wife is be
[Music]
dreams he's going to stay is he
oh
really what soon in the words of uh in
the thoughts of a
God he means soon with when we're going
to start our bakali watchong of all
seasons in my members only yes yes
that's when soon
[Music]
is
bur I hate you but you're cute right
[Music]
now he's so
cool he auditioned for Final
Fantasy he didn't make it get he was
going to be
Cloud I didn't like
him Kingdom Hearts to yeah nobody wanted
[Music]
him we can't all be
Cloud
[Music]
yeah
for
damn that's so
sad
[Music]
uh
oh I guess
so uh you say it like that but at the
same
time look at his
[Music]
face yeah we got to a attached to
him was that the connection or did he
[Music]
die is bro
cooked he's done
[Music]
cooking
for
[Music]
yeah
yes yes you
do
[Music]
foree
yeah I am part of the
cast I agree
[Music]
everybody
I just want to be part of
[Music]
it me too I use my head
I I get head pets Head
Pants I hate them just this once
okay just this
[Music]
once
speeech speech
[Music]
fore
how
many
stoping
Ying R blue y the
sea
I
a flap flop flap flop Grand blue Yap to
see
relink she yap yap I
[Music]
flop I'm I'm
clapping the wings my ass wings
[\h__\h] I'm not feeling so so good anymore
I'm ready to get out of
[Music]
here you
Gaz the
sky why the
wind
the what did you
cry when the said
goodbye still you gaze by
your
us the
star the word is
beautiful full of so many things to
see but if
more will come
tomorrow let stay inside
please good
night good
night sleep tight rest your
wings she's talking to
us
rest
your okay I will we
[Music]
will do you still remember okay okay
okay okay okay nice nice
song
okay
[Music]
oh
nice uh this is musical
yapping what's up it was a good
game can't believe we did all of that in
two days
very very long stream
[Music]
today I hope I don't get copyrighted by
this
song uh I did all of this for the ones
that are in the
thumbnail I probably otherwise wouldn't
have picked it up because time would
have pass I would have felt like
uh you know if I should have played it
then I should have played it you know
closer to the release
so probably this was the only time when
I was going to play
it did it for
them yeah I'm really glad that I finally
got to experience a little bit of the
grand blue fantasy world cuz I was
already curious about it for a long long
long time very aware of its existence
but never gave it a try
so yeah a good opportunity to jump into
it without spending gaja
money had a good time maybe sometime
soon we can do some multiplayer if
there's a EPO I might just play it on my
own we'll see you guys maybe got to give
me more info on how long it is and all
that what you doing it if it's worth a
stream I don't know I don't know
yeah 10-year-old got a very big story
10year old got very big story yeah but
like do they is does this story even
show up in the main Goda
game there's quite a bit more game well
this is going on my finished games list
anyway so I am proud I already finished
the game yeah baby and for the people
who didn't realize the reveal was do
this
outfit uh just to show you the
difference in case you
don't see what the difference
is before after
yay pretty cool right so I'm a white
night
now
shiny okay I'm
gonna how much longer is this I think
we're ending the we we see the end of it
maybe do you outfit
yeah thank you guys for going through
this very very
long but
short playr with me I mean compared to
all the other
games we
played it's like 15 minutes okay
bye compared to the others this these
two streams it's nothing
oh no I started
something we
sleep so Church yeah give me a break I
got new stickers and character colors
character colors uhhuh you un unlocked
the ability to ins Drive between oh
cool okay but bye
I'll
save oh oh theyve
released 12 episodes of the anime on for
free on YouTube oh that's so
cool
wait I have to self
insert
wait
[Laughter]
wow this hand movement is actually
coming in
handy thank you guys for watching
tomorrow as I said most likely is a
break day now and uh I give the game
a on a Wawa
scale I give it
a yeah
maybe
7.9 out of
10 too much yapping
yeah but I like that it's compact
actually cuz we played so many longer
ones it's great that you can finish it
so quickly and then we haven't even
experienced a multiplayer that hopefully
that's going to be fun it will be fun I
know
it good score yeah I think you
know there were not many flaws really
that's fine the story is yeah like you
know I I barely had to
listen it's like I know what's going on
I know what's going on but the fights
were fun the designs were great the
music was great the whole like World
design was beautiful that may have been
my favorite thing next to the character
designs amazing world
design holy
[Music]
moly
but this game needs a patch yeah for
like you know turn like regulating the
voices a bit
more very pretty game and I still love
this menu so much
damn
yeah what's your favorite area the
cities the two
cities for
sure
[Music]
H you think English voice does not Yap
as much I love that I can use this word
so much
today one of those words I pick up and
then I want to use it
actively but I don't get the
[Music]
chance but yeah I love I love the main
villain my wife my Mommy goodbye mommy
sad you had to go like that
Al look at my bunny
ears I got bunny ears
pickle okay I'm going to go uh throw my
frozen pizza into the
oven and yep probably sleep even later
than
usual it's 2: a.m. now oh my God na
Prime Time what's up na Prime Time
what's up any unusual Watchers here
where you at na Prime them any usual VOD
Watchers where you
at okay bye-bye my mouth is
weak thank you for the ones who stayed
from beginning to end you crazy
[Music]
MVPs oh lots of 9 amers you guys are
like in Australia and sea I see I see
thank you thank you morning have a nice
day and a good night and in my throat
hurts
bye I had fun though no regrets no
regrets no regretti spaghetti thanks for
watching
happy
[Music]
and bye
wait
wait oh my
God oh my God she loves
me we're holding
hands I'm so happy happy day of my
life waiting for fan out of white night
Wawa bye
[Music]
h
Once Upon A Yap there was a yapper who
yapped all
day so much so that you would think he
couldn't Yap anymore but he kept on
yapping and with that every day as he
yapped for the
yaps he thought to himself why do I Yap
so
much he would go out to the other
yappers who yapped less than him and
asked him what do I Yap wrong and they
said well my dear
yapper you have to
Yap with your
heart you currently Yap with
your
butt and so he was like okay how do I
Yap with my heart all I've ever done is
Yap with my
butt the yapper that yaps with his heart
yaps to him that is something you must
Yap out
yourself yap yap yap says our butt
yapper
and
dust yapped on with his butt for a long
long
time until the Wawa reached 10 hours of
streaming
time then he said okay enough yapping
[Music]
now