goba and I are going out she will return
later but I will not I will also be
taking a personal day
tomorrow and perhaps the next day you
want me to ask where you're going no
great GAA will be driving me deep into
the European Wilderness oh where she
will then leave me to either die or to
survive the choice is
yours welcome everybody I I have arrived
in the European Wilderness and I
Amit okay guys take two welcome to the
European Wilderness I am here to do a
survival challenge I will prove you guys
that I can survive in the wilderness
alone
because well I am a warrior and warriors
can survive anywhere European
wildernesses tattered in all these
dangerous plants that will hurt you they
will burn you so be careful this is
called a European brle it's a little
[\h__\h] and the first thing you want to do
is find a good place to put up your Camp
don't forget your tools of course in
case something gets in the way or
something attacks you be careful in the
wilderness now let's continue down this
sunny path here you can see a nest that
wild boards have created I'm Legit this
is really I'm I'm telling you this is
true this is actually perfect for us
because all these little sticks and
stones that they have brought here for
their nest uh we can take as materials
for our uh campfire perhaps and if you
want to know proof about them being here
this this here is one of their Trails
okay this actually looks pretty prop
promising here this area is providing
perfect amount of shade for a little
tree to feel more comfortable here and I
even see some stones that we could use
uh for the fire later here like one of
these even with a little snail on top
that little bugger maybe I try to put
some salt on this one yeah just like the
French people H it's the first time I'm
opening this but you
know
of course orange tent first up we will
lay
out the canopy and unzip the flippity
flaps these
things see easy easy of course it's only
easy for someone with a natural survival
Instinct like me stick them apparently
through here okay all right
ooh just fixing up the tent poles here
with a really cute little ribbon yeah
it's taking shape just like the people
back in the day in in in the Stone Age
I've brought the rest of my equipment we
have the sleeping back and here I'm
going to place a little light and we
have some some stuff for cooking let's
take my
trustworthy
knife
and open up my sleeping bag it will
never be this small
again and now we have this
fluffy fluffy sleeping bag very pink I
have successfully captured those
food as you can see in here hi I
captured baby chickens hello and they're
called
Franklin and uh Margaret oh Franklin
just pooped that's okay I was really
lucky in the first place to find such
wild wild rabid animals yeah my goal is
to get an egg out of them and maybe some
meat sounds good sounds good I have
spread some snack for the little babies
look at them look at these bab oh
hi oh little cheeks it's you guys
so I am back to report a success story
they
have created this monster egg compared
to their size it's about their their
size but yeah they totally laid this egg
for me perfect breakfast for tomorrow
all right little babies um there's only
one more thing I will be asking of you
so you know in the wilderness you know I
have to take what I can get because you
don't know when the next Food Source
will reveal itself so I'm unfortunately
I I have no
choice it's time say goodbye my lovely
chickens
oh yummy fresh
meat yeah this will be great for a
little soup for dinner I'll try to get
some potatoes and some carrots I'll I'll
see what I can find I am on the lookout
for something I smell it what is this oh
some
wild vegetables this smells like
potatoes I think I smell
potatoes oh no there it is we've been
lucky it looks like an egg but it's the
Egg of the Earth this is looking like
some fresh natural parsley over here
have you heard of the European
carrot oh [\h__\h]
this one
maybe doesn't feel like being made into
a soup today but I
did look at this
beauty oh yeah that's that's a bunch
that's a whole bunch of them some
smaller ones too but that's okay we
don't judge I have found another great
source of nutrients here this is called
H papum aarum yes this a beautiful
beautiful very tasty vegetable full of
uh vitamins of course I think we can un
pluck that one out after we chill there
you go and what we have it looks like an
apple almost or a pear but no yeah this
is what nowadays they like to call a
paprika yes have you heard of that
before o what do I hear a fresh source
of water oh my that that is perfect to
maybe clean our carrots right here I I
wonder where that's coming from must be
coming from the
mountain oh yeah oh yeah that's a really
strong flow oh wow excuse me Mountain
can you be a little bit more careful
thank you um maybe we can collect some
of that here for our
soup
carefully okay oh by the way I prepared
our um our fireplace a little bit uh oh
there's a
snake po po ooh it retracted its fangs
all right guys I thought it would be
nice if maybe for our dinner time we had
something like a spoon so I'm was going
to try to make a spoon out of this
little piece of wood that I
[Music]
found what do you think guys looks
pretty finished to me um um all right
guys the worst thing that could happen
when eating this soup is that I could
like choke on it so let's cut it up a
little
bit see natural grown potatoes M smells
really good and so crunchy as well look
at
that here oh falling right into it oh
yeah the technique as to be expected
from the CEO of a big fast food
restaurant but of course I can cook more
than just fast food I've collected some
wood so I'm going to start you know in
like a pyramid shape I'm going to build
this just like in Good Old Egypt
oh oh oh wow an apple oh oh must have
come from here in German you know we say
the from so this could be indeed a good
breakfast it's actually the first fire
I'm ever building to be honest with you
guys how's it look where I'm going to
put the pot is another question but
we'll think about that when the time has
come what do you think ooh I have found
something that
resembles those
mysterious red fruit that M keeps on
talking about look at these oh oh wow
there's a little
ant get out of there get
[Music]
out you little
[\h__\h] okay I squashed it here we go eat
ay
m
m it's super sweet wow M that's nature
guys that's Survival did you think I was
actually going to make a real fire with
sticks and stones no of course
not my fingers to wake noodle noodle
fingers oh ooh well that was easy start
a fire today don't stop don't stop just
go your own
way beautiful beautiful I didn't bring
anything to grill properly so I'm kind
of sad so instead I'm just going to pre
Grill the chicken get in there with a
nice stick oh yeah yeah burn chicken
burn oh
yeah all
right there it goes here maybe place it
right here and we going to give it some
time to
cook this soup oh is looking more and
more the way it's supposed to look
wow it what what are you saying it looks
a little bit different oh I don't know
what you mean o chicken
soup
M oh it smells good here comes our
dinner
eim good work getting all those
ingredients good job
[Applause]
me
oh oh yeah it's pretty hot ooh wow a
little bit of chicken and a
carrot I thought you know the egg that
we received from the cute chickens
chicks we're going to boil that for
tomorrow I'm we going to just eat it
together with the uh Apple I think
that's my day started really early so
I'm actually really tired already and
the tent is closed we still have a
little bit of fire out there to protect
us I'm going to get into the into my
sleeping bag now and then
Z as we say in
[Music]
Minecraft
KY oh guys good morning oh let's
see o Sunshine is Back the Night was
scary but ew e e ew ew well go away I
don't want to step on you it's so
disgusting this literally the most
disgusting thing I've ever seen I'm
going to eat my cooked egg and my Apple
for breakfast that's honestly enough for
me honestly I have enough of being
here breakfast was good I'm going to get
rid of this tent now I really want to go
home I feel like mostly the sounds are
relaxing sometimes there was something
weird maybe but how do you make this
smaller
again I did see like one one
Jaguar when I was in the tent she was
waiting I'm just going to assume it's a
Jaguar lady he let me do this without
gloves really quickly cut this part she
was like sitting like around here
staring at me
directly but when I opened my tent door
she like wouldn't really want to come
any closer I was really careful I was
making like these sounds
like baby baby if I tried to get closer
she uh would do a really small quiet
hiss at me maybe she wanted to protect
me maybe she was thinking about eating
me who knows honestly ew oh it's a weird
ew what bug is that it has like a little
Spike on its tail go away I don't want
to touch it if it's going to poison me
okay overall you know I think when I was
younger I went lowy camping before but I
don't I don't know this it wasn't really
the real deal so now I think I can say I
went camping and I would do it
again go away go away please I don't
want to touch
you I think like I want to uh
next time I want to go like camping
maybe with a friend that would be more
fun I do it again and I would say woohoo
I would say challenge
complete
y oh God I'm going to step on all these
disgusting I'll say it now for real
slugs mhm uh there will be one more
challenge what will it
be stay tuned stay
on the stream to find out e e [\h__\h] you
get off ew ew ew there's so many okay
see you guys later